Last season, on "The Flash"...
I'd finally come to
grips with her death.
Finally at the place I can move on.
No!
My father's taken from me.
I need to find some peace.
Whatever you need to do, do it.
You're not gonna kill her ever again.
- Not gonna hurt you.
- No.
You're safe.
There's only one
thing I know about life.
I know some things happen by chance.
Today's the day.
Today's the day. Talk to her.
Where is she?
And some things happen
because we make them happen.
Okay, just do it.
Gonna do it.
You've talked to her a million times.
Say something clever.
Channel 52 breaking news.
The latest from Central City,
where the mysterious
meta-human criminal,
known only as the Rival is once again
terrorizing the populous
with his incredible speed.
Need our help, Flash?
Nah. When I'm done with
this fool, he might.
What have you got against my city?
The city's just fine.
It's the people in it who
need to be educated.
And I have no rival!
Especially not you.
- You okay, man?
- Yeah, thanks.
That guy's really
becoming a pain in my ass.
Don't worry about it.
You'll get him next time, Flash.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
E-excuse me?
Hi, sorry. Is this yours?
I think maybe you dropped it.
- It was just right up there.
- Oh.
I don't know what happened, but...
Oh, my gosh, yeah, I didn't even
realize I dropped it. Thank you so much.
Yeah, yeah, it's okay.
Wait, I've... I've seen
you before, haven't I?
Uhh, we actually went to
elementary school together.
You don't remember me? PS 23?
Oh, my gosh! Right, yes, I remember!
- Gary, right!
- Uh, Barry.
- Barry.
- Barry Allen.
- Right.
- It's fine.
- Sorry, sorry.
- No, it's fine.
Yeah, yeah, no, we had, um, Mr., uh...
- Mr. Hinkley.
- Yes.
Yeah, for math. Yeah, he used to
always hit the chalkboard...
With his fist.
And all the dust would come flying off.
He'd look just like...
Pig-Pen from "Peanuts."
Yeah, that's...
Yes. How are you?
I'm really good.
Yeah, I'm, uh, CSI.
I work over at, uh, CCPD.
Yeah, um, my... My dad works there, too.
- He's a detective.
- Yeah, I see him sometimes.
I don't really know
him, but I, you know,
- see him in passing.
- Cool, yeah.
Um, well, thanks again.
I guess you're my hero today.
Glad I could be there for you.
You know what? Uh, would
you wanna get a coffee?
I mean, I know you're
having a coffee right now.
I meant, like, you
know, at a different time.
With me. Or it doesn't
even have to be a coffee.
It could be any kind of beverage,
like a wine or a beer, or...
Not that I wanna get you drunk.
We... we could get iced
tea. Do you like iced tea?
Do... would you wanna
get an iced tea with me?
Um...
- Yes, yes.
- Yeah?
Yes, I would like to
get an iced tea with you.
- Okay.
- Barry Allen,
you're very cute, you know that?
- Yeah, yeah.
- Yeah, but, um,
you should try talking just
a little bit slower.
Speed...
has always been my problem.
See you later.
What's up, Barry?
- Hey.
- You look a little less glum
- this day's afternoon.
- Captain Mendez,
I asked out a girl and she said yes.
Ah, there's no better feeling, is there?
- No better feeling.
- Well, until the day
she says, "I do".
Yeah, we got a ways to
go before that, I think.
Great, well that'll give
you a lot of time to catch me up
on where we are with the Rival.
Nothing substantive. He hasn't left
any hair or skin
samples at any of his attacks
- on the CCPD.
- So you're telling me
there's no way to ID this guy.
We'll figure out who he
is when The Flash stops him.
Well The Flash better hurry up.
Pun intended.
Okay.
All right.
Has anybody seen Detective West?
You know, I think he
had to stop by evidence.
- Uh-huh.
- I don't know
where he is, actually.
Sorry.
Oh, Captain, is it okay if
I leave a little early today?
- For your hot date?
- No, I'm, uh, just
meeting a friend for dinner.
Barry!
No!
You're not gonna kill her this time.
You're not gonna kill her ever again.
It's okay. It's okay.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
You're safe now. Okay?
Dinner.
There better be curly fries in there.
Yeah, human beings can go almost
three weeks without food
so I'd sound a little bit
more grateful if I were you.
Well, you wouldn't do that to me, Barry.
After all, you're the hero.
Or did you forget that?
Too busy leading your
reverse "It's a Wonderful Life"?
Reverse, huh?
That's irony for you.
So, uh, what should we call this, uh,
brave new world that
you've whipped up for us?
I was thinking...
Flashpoint.
So you don't want this?
You may have figured out
a way to dampen my speed
with this glass cage, but
I will get out of here
and I will destroy your
life, Flash, one way or the other.
No, you won't.
Ah, you're never getting out of here.
And you're never gonna
hurt anybody ever again.
I have everything
back that you took from me.
I have everything Zoom took.
I'm finally free.
I'm home.
This isn't your home, Barry.
This is a mirage.
A fiction that will end us both,
unless you let me the
hell out of this thing!
Well,
you're not listening, Don.
Why would I want to get out of here?
I'm whole, here.
There's even a Flash,
so I don't have to be.
Yeah, who is this dashing
young speedster, huh?
Do you know? You even care?
While you sit around and hide
like a lost, lonely little boy,
letting someone else risk their life
to protect the city, our common enemy
is coming for us both.
What common enemy is that?
Time.
It's already screwing with you
and everyone you love.
And pretty soon, it's gonna take me
right down along with you.
Wow.
You know,
you've got some nerve.
I'll give you that.
Warning me about messing
with other people's lives.
You... you know the
whole reason I did this
is because of what you did to my life.
To my family.
To my mother.
Yeah, well, one day, soon, Barry,
you'll be begging me to kill her again.
- Can you hold this for me?
- Oh, yeah.
Oh, I wanted to tell you, the
car's making these noises,
like a... kind of a clanking noise...
- Do you wanna drive?
- Whatever you want.
- Hey, slugger.
- There's my beautiful boy.
Is everything all right?
Yeah.
Everything's great.
- Mornin'!
- Morning, Barry.
Mornin'.
Ah. Looks good.
- Hey.
- Muah.
What is up with you?
- What do you mean?
- Lately, you hug me
every morning as if it's the first time
you've seen me in months.
Well, I mean, I'll stop
if you really want me to.
Never. I love it.
Oh, Barry, I wanted to tell you,
I sold a house to a nice older couple
- a few weeks ago.
- Mm-hmm.
- The basement apartment.
They emailed me this morning
to tell me they wanted to rent it.
- Cool.
- Very reasonably.
You want me to move out?
No, no, son, come
on. It's just, you know,
if you ever thought about dating...
Oh, I forgot to tell you guys.
The, uh, the... The girl that
- I've seen at Jitters...
- It's the girl
you've been stalking for
the last three months?
I have not been stalking her.
I've been working up the courage
- to ask her out.
- And?
And did.
- And she said yes.
- Ohh!
All right. Good job.
This girl just got the best guy, huh?
- Aww. Mm.
- Oh, honey.
- All right.
- Hey, Bar.
- Yeah?
- Have you seen Detective West?
- He's...
- I told him
that if he was late again, he'd
be facing a ten day RIP.
Uh, yeah, no, he
mentioned something yesterday,
actually, about running another
canvass on that Jefferson case.
Oh! Okay. Then I can see why
he hasn't answered me for the past hour.
Uh... maybe he's in a
weird zone or something.
A we...
Cell zone.
Detective West?
De...
Detective?
Oh, no.
No.
Hey, Joe, you got...
Ohh...
I'm sorry about this, Joe.
What the...
Afternoon, Detective.
- Oh, hey, Allen.
- Hey.
So I told Captain
Mendez you were canvassing
for the Jefferson case again.
Breath mint?
What... why are you talking
to the Captain about me?
Oh, you're just a little late again.
That's my business, not yours.
I was just trying to help you out.
Am I wearing a sign that
says "Help me"?
Might as well be.
Look, like they say in the movies,
we're not partners and
we're not friends.
- Mm-hmm.
- You don't know me.
You don't know my life,
so why the sudden interest
in me keeping my lousy job?
And what the hell makes me so
interesting to you, Mr. Allen?
Tell me. I'd really like to know.
- I...
- And remember,
I have a hangover.
And a gun.
I...
Oh, I get it.
- What?
- No.
I do not approve.
- Hi, Barry.
- Hey.
- Dad.
- Iris.
You think it's a good idea,
dating somebody I work with?
It's just a lunch.
And truthfully, I wasn't even sure
you still worked here.
- You ready?
- Yeah, let's do it.
Okay.
- How's it going?
- Good. I just gotta
go grab my jacket.
I'm sorry about that mini-scene
- with my dad, earlier.
- Oh, yeah.
Don't worry about it.
I just feel bad for him.
And you.
You barely even know us.
Feels like I do.
Is that weird?
Is that a weird thing to say?
No.
No, I mean, strangely,
I know what you mean.
I never say yes to guys
asking me out like that.
Yet, I said yes to you.
Why'd I do that?
I don't know.
Some people are just meant to
be in your life, I guess.
So, um, tell me about you.
- Yeah.
- Mom and Dad?
Uh, alive and well.
- That's nice.
- Mm-hmm.
You guys close?
We are, yeah, very.
I... couldn't imagine life without them.
They're like stupid in love.
I hope I have what they have someday.
You just haven't
met the right girl, yet?
Is that it?
That's the thing about the right girl.
She's out there, waiting.
Just have to be lucky
enough to find her.
Where'd you come from, Barry Allen?
I've always been here, Iris.
- Are you okay?
- Uh, sorry, yeah,
that, um... I was just thinking
of something and...
I lost it.
What's going on?
Flash and the Rival are going at it
in the Werther Building.
Everyone needs to evacuate this area.
I am so sorry.
I have to go.
- Really? What...
- Yeah, yeah.
There's something I have to do.
Uh, this... this was...
Rain check, okay?
Anytime.
Come on.
Yeah, yeah, that's you...
No, hey, hey, hey! No! No!
Thought I had him.
Wally?
Who the hell are you?
So this is your base of operations, huh?
Yeah. What were you expecting?
- A fortress?
- Uh, no, you know, no.
Just something a little more secure.
I mean, you never know who's gonna come
walking through that door.
Yeah, I was just
about to say the same thing.
- Iris.
- Hi.
- What are you doing here?
- I'm not... I'm...
He showed up when I
was fighting the Rival,
and he already knew who I was.
Is that why you asked me out?
Because my brother is The Flash?
Uh, no, no. This is
a complete coincidence.
Okay, how'd you know who
I was under the mask?
Um, uh, CSI.
You know, so I just,
uh... Put it together.
So what I don't know is
how you got your speed.
Oh, okay, so before I went
on the straight and narrow,
I used to drive illegal cars.
- Uh-huh.
- I was messing around
with a new nitro formula to
get my engine revving faster.
Then one night, I'm
racing in a thunder storm,
my car get struck by lightning.
And it must have mixed with the formula
because... boom!
I was in a coma for nine months.
Then when I woke up, I
was the fastest man alive.
The Flash.
- More like Kid Flash.
- Don't call me that.
- I call you that.
- Okay, how about
no one calls me that?
So how did you get involved?
- I'm a reporter for CCPN.
- Uh-huh.
Instead of just reporting on crimes
that are happening in the city,
I decided to do something about it.
Brother/sister crime-fighting unit.
So does your dad know about you two?
You work with the
guy. What do you think?
I think that... we
need to stop the Rival.
- Yeah.
- We're open to suggestions.
I've been trying to
run him down for months.
No luck. He's fast.
Maybe faster than me.
Well, if you're willing,
I think maybe I could help.
There's only one
man who can help us now.
Cisco Ramon.
Didn't this used to be S.T.A.R. Labs?
Where have you
been the past few years?
- Running around.
- Cisco alone
made billions with his tech apps.
- Bought the building.
- Billions.
Yeah, Cisco Ramon is the richest man
in America.
Oh! Is there a better way
to get to work than by helicopter?
Let me answer that. Capital N, little O.
Quite right, Mr. Ramon.
As for LogicFrame,
it's a relatively small startup.
The I.P. is expected to
be in the low teens.
Offer them 20 mil.
Huh.
Babe,
I, um, got some business to attend to,
so we'll get on that other matter later?
- Not if I get on it first, huh?
- Ooh...
Mm. Independent woman.
I like it. I like it.
Huh, well...
I told you never to come back here.
I make you a friction-proof suit
so your clothes don't explode at mach 2,
and you leave me out of
your brother/sister war on crime.
- That was the deal.
- Okay, listen to me, Mr. Ramon.
We need your help.
I'm sure you've seen the Rival on TV.
He is terrorizing the city
to prove that he's the fastest.
I mean, God only knows
what he's gonna do next.
- We have to stop him.
- Okay, so stop him.
Please, go with God, have fun.
But you know what? You know what happens
when you mess with a Speedster?
That. That's what happens.
You get a vibrating hand
going right through your ribcage.
No thanks.
My money needs me.
Wait, Cisco, you're
not gonna help us?
Oh, that reminds
me. Who the hell is this?
Huh? You brought some
stranger into my lab
and told them I helped The Flash.
- Cisco.
- Uh-uh.
I don't know you, string bean.
Str...
- Mr. Ramon.
- Oh, yes?
I do know what kind of person you are.
Deep down, you care
about helping other people.
Please, tell me more.
I heard a story about
how, when you were 15,
your brother Dante owed a bookie
and he couldn't pay back what he owed,
so you gave him all the
money you earned that summer
delivering pizzas to help him.
How do you know about that?
I have a feeling that...
we would work really
well together as partners.
Taking down meta-humans together.
I mean, it's what we're supposed to do.
We're a team.
We're friends.
Hey.
I'm okay. I'm okay, I just...
What was I...
What was I just saying?
What is going on with you?
I'm not sure.
And here, I was starting to think
you'd forgotten all about me.
But I am forgetting.
What's happening to me?
I was wondering when you'd notice.
It's like I'll be thinking of
a moment from my past
and then it... It vanishes.
I can't get it back. Why?
Flashpoint. It's a side effect.
See, I told you before. You don't know
what you're doing.
This new reality you've created
is starting to overwrite the
reality that you and I know.
So your original life...
Your friends, your family...
Pretty soon, all of
that will just fade away.
Why isn't it happening to you?
Not sure.
Unless...
What?
What the hell's so funny?
Your speed!
The more you use it,
the faster you lose your memories.
No.
No, you're lying.
You just want me to let you out of here.
That's never gonna happen.
The you I know from the future,
he's not this stupid. Pretty soon,
you won't even
remember that you're The Flash.
And when that happens,
this world will become permanent.
Time will set like concrete,
and nothing will be
able to change it back
to the way it was.
That's fine by me.
You know what you have to do.
You have to take me back to that night
and let me finish what I started.
You go to hell!
You're taking both of us there!
Now who's the villain, Flash?
Now who's the villain?
Unbelievable.
It's like I'm really there.
Don't do that!
I told you it freaks me out.
It wasn't me.
Who are you?
The man who's gonna
help you stop the Rival.
Barry?
Okay, so...
I can tell from the
"I don't believe you"
looks on your faces
that you don't believe me.
We believe you're a speedster,
but you're gonna have to explain
that part about Flashpoint again.
All right, look.
This is as simple as I can put it.
I'm gonna use this glass, Mr. Ramon.
- Okay?
- What?
Imagine that this line is time, okay?
I went back in time,
stopped the Reverse
Flash from killing my mom.
In doing so, I created
an alternate timeline,
a whole new existence
where you're Kid Flash...
- The Flash.
- Kid Flash.
AnCisco's a billionaire.
So you're saying there's
a time line out there
where I'm not rich?
Boy, that's a glitch in the universe.
No, not buying it.
Um, my life is my life.
Didn't just start three
months ago, okay?
I've always been me.
Yeah.
I don't know what to tell you, Wally.
It's complicated.
Okay, look.
Even if we did believe you,
why are you telling us this now?
Because...
I've been hiding here for too long.
The Rival needs to be stopped.
I stop the bad guys. And...
we can all take him down together.
I can get him myself.
Then why haven't you?
Well, I'm not interested.
I don't know how many
times I gotta tell you freaks,
I already did my bit
for queen and country.
Wait, we're missing something.
Hold on. Excuse me.
What are you doing?
Hey, don't touch that.
Got it.
Oh! What just happened?
Stop bringing strangers into my lab.
Who is this?
This is Dr. Caitlin Snow.
In my timeline, she's
a part of our team.
Did you... You just
kidnapped this woman.
No, I didn't...
Well, yeah, I guess, I...
She's a scientist. We need her.
I'm not a scientist.
You're not a scientist?
I'm an ophthalmologist.
An eye doctor?
Pediatric eye doctor.
And... we're done.
Okay.
Can I talk to you in private?
Yeah.
- Excuse me.
- Mm.
Have Iveeen kidnapped?
Unclear.
Look, I'm sorry.
I know that this is hard to believe.
No, that's just it, Barry.
I do believe you.
You... do?
You believe me?
I have a good life.
I have a good job.
I love my brother.
But something has been off.
Something has been missing.
And that feeling that something
is not right with my life,
that went away the
moment that I met you.
We're something else to each other
where you come from, aren't we?
Yes.
What?
It's...
it's escaped definition.
But it's love?
Because this is what love feels like.
Since the day that I met you.
Hey.
We got something.
Turns out kiddie eye doc
here actually had a good idea.
I have always wondered why no one
turned the speed cameras in the city
to register near sonic velocities.
Seems like a ready-built
early warning system.
So I reprogrammed the cameras.
Babadook!
There's your rival.
The old sawmill out by Williamson.
All right. Follow my lead?
The Flash doesn't follow anyone.
Listen to him, Wally.
He's the Flash.
You know,
you would be an excellent
candidate for Lasik.
You know how to flank?
People always say that in the movies.
Is that, like, a thing, "flanking"?
What are you talking about "flank"...
Yes, flanking's a thing.
All right, look.
I'm gonna go at him head on.
You attack at a 90-degree angle.
When he turns to fight you,
leaves himself vulnerable to me.
When he turns to fight me...
I get him. Exactly how it should be.
How'd you find this place, Flash?
I'm so gonna kick your ass.
Oh ho ho...
There's two of you now?
Okay. Is that supposed to scare me?
A little quaking in your
boots wouldn't be inappropriate.
Well, here's how scared I am of you.
My name is Edward Clariss.
Rivals should know each other's names.
I mean, you might as well tell me,
since neither of you are
leaving this place alive.
Who are you?
Me?
I'm the Flash.
That's all you need to know.
Well, after I rip that
cowl off your corpse,
I'll know who you are.
Just another pretender
who thought they could take me on.
So who wants to meet
the Speed Force first?
Hey, stay in position.
I can take him.
I got this.
The Flash is taking on the
Rival at Prescott Sawmill.
Get down there, make sure the action
doesn't spill out into the neighborhood.
We can't leave the
Flash out there alone.
Whoo!
Wally!
Telemetry from the suit
says he's still alive.
Barely.
Hey, hey, hey... hey.
You're going to be okay, all right?
You're gonna be okay.
I'm gonna get you out of here.
That one was never my rival.
You could be, though.
You want to find out?
Defeat me,
and I'll let you take your
little friend for help.
No.
You're the one who's gonna need help.
Good-bye, Flash.
Oh, my God.
It's like "Twister" in there,
the movie, not the game.
The satellite's picking up two
distinct funnel patterns.
Tornados measure at
F3 on the Fujita scale.
This guy's like a Weather
Wizard or something.
Guys!
I can't stop him.
Listen to me, Barry.
You said we love each
other in that other life.
If I were your Iris from over there,
I'm sure I would
know exactly what to say,
but I don't.
All I can say is I believe in you.
And you can stop this guy.
Be the Flash, Barry.
Because that's who you are.
You're the Flash.
I'm the Flash.
That's impossible.
You really are the fastest man alive.
It's over.
Joe.
It's Wally. He needs help.
Wally?
Son!
Oh...
Son, can you hear me?
Wally's vitals are low,
and he's lost a lot of blood.
He should be rapidly healing.
It's one of the gifts of
being a speedster.
He's not. I'm sorry.
Am I free to go?
Mm-hmm.
This is why I didn't
want to get involved.
Crime fighting sucks.
I thought I could just
make things better,
but everybody's been paying for my hap.
Will you help me?
Do what?
Make things right.
Ah... oh, I need that.
You don't need that.
You do not need that.
Hey, guys.
- Hey.
- Hey, slugger.
Who's this?
This is Iris.
- It's nice to meet you, Iris.
- Hi.
Can I get you something to drink?
Oh, no, I'm okay. Thanks, Mrs. Allen.
You okay, Barry?
Yeah, I just...
wanted to see you both one more time.
What does... that mean?
Nothing.
Nothing. I, uh...
These last three
months have been the best.
Just getting to spend time with you.
I just... wanted you to
know how grateful I am,
to both of you, to be your son.
Barry, you're scaring me.
No, there's...
There's nothing to be afraid of.
Promise.
I just...
I love you both.
Hey, Barry!
Are you okay?
It's getting worse.
We have to hurry before it's too late.
Having a bad day, Barr?
Well... if it isn't
the future Mrs. Allen.
Barry told me not to
listen to anything you say.
Oh. That's just bad advice.
'Cause I'm the answer man.
I am the answer to all your prayers.
All you need to do is ask me, Barry.
We need to go back in time.
To that night.
To do what?
You know what I need you to do.
Yeah.
But I want to hear you say it.
I need you to kill my mother.
With pleasure.
I hate you.
And I hate you.
And I sometimes
wonder which of us is right.
It seems weird to wish you good luck.
I'm so sorry about all this.
Will I know when things change back?
Will I feel it?
It'll be like it never happened.
I'll see you soon.
Barry!
Get back!
God, I wish I could kill you.
But today...
I get to be the hero.
No!
You're not gonna kill her this time.
You're not gonna kill her ever again.
It's okay.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
Okay?
You're safe.
You're safe now.
Actually...
She's not.
Please don't hurt me.
No!
There we go.
Things are back to how they should be.
Well, for me, anyway.
For you...
Well,
I guess you'll just have
to wait and find out.
What? What does that mean?
See you sometime soon, Flash.
What's this for?
Just glad you're here.
Are you okay?
Oh-ho.
Yeah, I am now. Yeah.
You just lost your father, Barry.
You don't have to be okay.
Actually, I feel closer to my parents
than I ever have.
Well, good, son.
- To your pops.
- To Henry.
To my Dad.
Where's Iris?
That ain't funny.
I'm gonna chalk that up to grief.
I'll see you both in the morning.
What was that about?
Are you kidding me?
You know Iris isn't here.
What?
They don't talk, Barry.
You know that.
Oh, God. What did I do?
Clariss.
Clariss!
Oh!
Who's there?
It's time to wake up.
_
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --