Lamb men make good slaves.
Khal Drogo will make a gift
of them to the slavers,
and the slavers will give us gold...
...and silk, and steel.
She is a lamb girl, Khaleesi.
The riders do her honor.
If her wailing offends the Khaleesi,
I will bring you her tongue.
Do as I command
or Khal Drogo will know the reason why.
Moon of my life,
Mago says you haven taken his spoils,
a daughter of a lamb man
who was his to mount.
Tell me the truth of this.
Mago speaks the truth,
my sun and stars.
I have claimed many daughters this day...
...so they cannot be mounted.
This is the way of war.
These women are slaves now...
...to do with as we please.
It pleases me to keep them safe.
If your riders would mount them,
let them take them for wives.
Does the horse mate with the lamb?
The dragon feeds on horse and lamb alike.
You are a foreigner.
You do not command me.
I am Khaleesi. I do command you.
See how fierce she grows?
That is my son inside her,
the stallion that will mount the world,
filling her with his fire.
I will hear no more.
Mago, find somewhere else
to stick your cock.
A Khal who takes orders
from a foreign whore is no Khal.
I will not have your body burned.
I will not give you that honor.
The beetles will feed on your eyes.
The worms will crawl through your lungs.
The rain will fall on your rotting skin...
...until nothing is left of you but bones.
First you have to kill me.
I already have.
My sun and stars is wounded.
A scratch...
...moon of my life.
Where are the healers?
This is the bite of a fly.
I can help the great rider with his cut.
The Khal needs no help
from slaves who lie with sheep.
She is mine. Let her speak.
Witch.
Too many words.
A witch's words poison the ears.
Let her clean your wound,
my sun and stars...
...it makes me hurt to see you bleed.