My name is Barry Allen,
&nbsp
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world, I'm
an ordinary forensic scientist,
&nbsp
but secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
&nbsp
I fight crime and find
other meta-humans like me.
&nbsp
After defeating Zoom
and saving the multiverse,
&nbsp
I ran back in time and created
the alternate timeline, Flashpoint.
&nbsp
I restored the timeline to how it was,
only to find things
weren't as I left them.
&nbsp
I brought new threats to our world,
and I'm the only one fast
enough to stop them.
&nbsp
I am The Flash.
Previously on “The Flash”...
&nbsp
I got hit with the dark matter.
It must have affected me somehow.
&nbsp
We're going home.
I went back in time and
created an alternate timeline.
&nbsp
- Wally?
- Aah.
&nbsp
Wally? Can you hear me?
My name is Edward Clariss.
&nbsp
Rivals should know each other's names.
When I came back,
things weren't the same.
&nbsp
I don't trust you, and I don't
like things that I don't trust.
&nbsp
You'll always be Barry,
and I'll always be Iris.
&nbsp
And we always find each other.
- Who are you?
- I am Alchemy.
&nbsp
- Alchemy!
- You failed, Clariss.
&nbsp
Remember that feeling you got as a kid
when you were so excited about something
&nbsp
that you couldn't focus
on anything else?
&nbsp
That's me right now, thinking about...
well, what I always think about.
&nbsp
Allen! Enough with the knee.
- Where are you going?
- I'm going on a date.
&nbsp
Well, not yet, you're not.
You know, you're not
actually my boss, Julian.
&nbsp
But I am the senior lab tech,
and the last time I checked,
&nbsp
the hours were 10:00 a.m. to 7:00 p.m.
Not 6:58. Not 6:59.
&nbsp
But se...
Remember that other feeling you got
&nbsp
when that thing you were excited about
seemed to take forever to arrive?
&nbsp
Imagine being a speedster.
Days seem like weeks.
Hours seem like days.
&nbsp
And seconds seem like...
you get the point.
&nbsp
Ven.
I'll see you tomorrow.
&nbsp
It's too much? Yeah, it's too much.
It's the heart, right?
&nbsp
It's too cheesy? Hold on.
Is that better? That's...
&nbsp
That's worse?
We'll go back to the heart.
&nbsp
No, Bare. Wait, wait, wait.
It is so beautiful,
&nbsp
and you are so sweet,
but tonight, I want to be with you.
&nbsp
Barry Allen. Not the Flash.
So...
&nbsp
So no Flash talk.
No speed.
&nbsp
No problem.
All right.
&nbsp
Starting now,
the Flash is officially off-limits.
&nbsp
So, wow...
Mm.
&nbsp
Where are we going?
It's a surprise.
&nbsp
Synced and corrected by johnyd13
~ www.addic7ed.com ~
&nbsp
Are you planning on donating a kidney
sometime in the near future or...?
&nbsp
A kidney?
This place is...
&nbsp
Oh, don't look at the prices.
Just get whatever you want.
&nbsp
So...
Yeah, so...
&nbsp
How was work?
Yeah, super busy. How about you?
&nbsp
Well, Julian had me write
up a carbon dating report.
&nbsp
Then a DNA sequencing report.
A couple chemical compound reports.
&nbsp
So he pretty much just
gives me all the work
&nbsp
he doesn't want me to do, so...
Yeah, I know, it's really boring.
&nbsp
No, no. Oh, I'm so sorry, Barry.
I'm just... It's been a really long day.
&nbsp
Yeah, I know. Me too.
What's going on?
&nbsp
Apparently, a robbery's in progress
across the street. Excuse me.
&nbsp
Go, go, go.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
&nbsp
Yeah, use your speed. Go.
Okay.
&nbsp
- Uh, where were we?
- Um...
&nbsp
Cisco.
We should go.
&nbsp
Yeah.
- What's going on?
- That.
&nbsp
Yeah, why'd you open a breach?
- I didn't.
- What?
&nbsp
That's why we called you.
- Well, can you close it?
- Once again,
&nbsp
wouldn't have called if I could.
- Somebody's coming through.
- Get back.
&nbsp
Allen.
Wells.
&nbsp
I need your help.
With what?
&nbsp
- With that.
- Hey, guys.
&nbsp
Jesse. You're a speedster?
Yeah. It's pretty cool, right?
&nbsp
I mean, yeah, I would say so.
When did this happen?
&nbsp
A few days ago.
So, when I got Allen his speed back,
&nbsp
Wally and Jesse were hit
with the dark matter.
&nbsp
Turns out she was affected.
She was totally affected.
&nbsp
But I didn't get speed,
so could it have been
from something else?
&nbsp
No... I mean, I doubt it.
Dark matter affects different people
&nbsp
in different ways at different times...
Sometimes not at all, so be thankful,
&nbsp
but she was affected,
and I want to run some tests
&nbsp
and find out just how much.
Well, then, you've come
to the right place.
&nbsp
Let's go to the Speed Lab.
Speed Lab?
&nbsp
This is insane.
Something tells me you've never been
&nbsp
in this room before.
Nope.
&nbsp
Wait, you... You nev...
Allen.
&nbsp
I suppose that means you
traveled back in time again.
&nbsp
Yeah, but...
How many times did I
tell you not to do that?
&nbsp
You figured that out
pretty quickly, Harry.
&nbsp
Yes, Ms. West, it was easy
because we've never been here either.
&nbsp
- Nope.
- Right.
&nbsp
Other Earths, other timelines.
Yes, exactly.
&nbsp
So when did you do it?
After we returned to Earth-2?
&nbsp
Look, Harry,
only a couple things are different.
&nbsp
Oh, I'm sure. Not.
Really?
&nbsp
You guys are doing “not” on Earth-2 now?
Uh, no. That's all him.
&nbsp
Okay, let's just get Jesse on the track
and see what she can do.
&nbsp
Yeah, let's do it.
All right. Check this out.
&nbsp
Damn.
She really can move.
&nbsp
Yeah, she can.
Um... I got to go.
&nbsp
Wally.
Oh, man.
&nbsp
I'll talk to him.
Hey, Joe.
&nbsp
Um...
Look, it's just...
&nbsp
it is better if he doesn't have speed.
Oh, you don't have to
convince me of that.
&nbsp
The last thing I want is two of my kids
zipping around the city,
running into danger.
&nbsp
'Cause he looked pretty disappointed.
This is about that other
timeline, isn't it?
&nbsp
No, I just...
I think you should keep an eye out.
&nbsp
- Where's dinner?
- It's almost ready, John.
&nbsp
I work hard every day to
provide for this family,
&nbsp
and this is what greets me?
An empty table?
&nbsp
- Just five more minutes.
- I'm hungry now!
&nbsp
And you speak when
you're spoken to, girl.
&nbsp
You understand me?
I saved you from the orphanage
&nbsp
and I provide for you every day,
so keep your mouth shut,
Frankie, you got it?
&nbsp
Sorry, John. Frankie's gone.
Hey!
&nbsp
- Hey.
- What are you doing here?
&nbsp
I was trying to get some information
about the man who was attacked
by a lamppost last night.
&nbsp
Hey...
Just come here for a second.
&nbsp
So, last night.
I know our first date
didn't shatter any records.
&nbsp
I mean, it wasn't that bad.
- It was...
- Okay, yeah.
&nbsp
It wasn't that great, either.
- It was just kind of...
- Boring?
&nbsp
Boring, yeah.
Which feels like my fault.
Maybe I'm boring without my powers.
&nbsp
No, Barry, you are perfect
without your powers.
&nbsp
That's nice, but I mean,
what do you think it is, then?
&nbsp
You don't think it's a
sign that we shouldn't...
&nbsp
No!
No.
&nbsp
Good, I mean, 'cause I do...
I want to try this again,
&nbsp
as soon as possible,
but just with everything
that's going on...
&nbsp
This new case, and Wells
and Jesse showing up...
&nbsp
Yeah. No, Barry.
I totally get it. I get it.
&nbsp
I should probably concentrate
on making my deadlines anyway, so.
&nbsp
Cool.
- Okay.
- All right.
&nbsp
All right, well, I'm gonna... Okay.
- Yeah.
- Work.
&nbsp
Yeah. Work. Cool.
Yeah. All right. I'll see you later.
&nbsp
- Oh.
- No, I was...
&nbsp
- Yeah, of course.
- Yeah.
&nbsp
- Okay.
- Yeah. All right.
&nbsp
So this says you were in the
room when your father...
&nbsp
Foster father. John.
Right. Foster father.
&nbsp
You were in the room when he was
struck by the street lamppost
&nbsp
that flew into the apartment?
Yeah.
&nbsp
But I don't remember any of that.
He came home
&nbsp
and yelled at Karen, my foster mom,
to get him dinner.
&nbsp
Mm.
Is that when you blacked out?
&nbsp
Yeah, I think so.
Has that happened before?
&nbsp
You blacking out?
Is John gonna be okay?
&nbsp
He's in Central City Hospital.
I...
&nbsp
He's pretty banged up.
Frankie, can you excuse me for a second?
&nbsp
- Yeah, of course.
- Thank you.
&nbsp
- Bare.
- Yeah?
&nbsp
- What'd you find out?
- Okay, get this.
&nbsp
So, the outer layer of the lamppost
is a half an inch thick,
&nbsp
but to bend even a quarter-inch of steel
requires 177 tons of
tensile strength, so...
&nbsp
So we're looking for a
meta with superstrength?
&nbsp
Well, I'm not sure yet,
but that's as much as I could find.
&nbsp
What? Why?
- Because I showed up.
- Yeah.
&nbsp
Yes, the only problem with
Barry's little theory
&nbsp
is there were no fingerprints
found on the post.
&nbsp
Again, Julian, not my theory,
and the meta could've
been wearing gloves.
&nbsp
Yes, perhaps.
But the curvature on the post suggests
&nbsp
that equal amounts of
pressure were applied
&nbsp
to the whole thing at the same time.
So, unless our strong man has
a wingspan of over 20 feet...
&nbsp
Something else caused it.
Yes.
&nbsp
Who's that, sir?
That's Frankie Kane,
the victim's foster kid.
&nbsp
That poor girl's been in
and out of homes for years.
&nbsp
Listen, she said that she blacked out
during the incident.
&nbsp
- Blacked out?
- Yeah.
&nbsp
Repressing memories
is a coping mechanism
&nbsp
for lots of foster kids.
Hmm. Is it?
&nbsp
It is.
It could be something else.
&nbsp
- What are you...
- What...
&nbsp
Hello there.
Hi.
&nbsp
You okay?
Yeah.
&nbsp
Can I get you some more water?
Yes, thank you.
&nbsp
Sure.
Gonna need another glass, Detective.
&nbsp
- Follow him.
- Mm-hmm.
&nbsp
- See what you can get.
- What are you gonna do?
&nbsp
I'm gonna finish this
up and convince my son
&nbsp
that he's not meant to be a superhero.
Good idea.
&nbsp
So, how'd I do?
Blood pressure, heart rate,
metabolic rate all excellent.
&nbsp
And you've got some serious speed, girl.
- Mm-hmm.
- I think you're good to go.
&nbsp
Let's not get ahead of ourselves.
I still want to run a few more tests.
&nbsp
- Like what?
- Like more tests.
&nbsp
Hey, so, is Wally here?
No, not yet.
&nbsp
Right. Um...
Okay, I'm gonna...
I'm gonna go grab some food.
&nbsp
I'm starving.
Yeah, there's some PowerBars
in the workshop. Help yourself.
&nbsp
Cool.
- Harry?
- Mm-hmm?
&nbsp
- What're you doing?
- Being thorough.
&nbsp
Yeah? 'Cause it seems
like you're stalling.
&nbsp
Okay, fine. I'm stalling.
I'm stalling. So what?
&nbsp
So what? So why?
So why? Why?
&nbsp
Why? I got to explain myself to you two?
Oh, I guess I do,
'cause you're not parents.
&nbsp
That's my daughter, okay?
And she spent months on this very Earth
&nbsp
watching Barry Allen defeat
meta after meta after meta...
&nbsp
And Zoom... And all of a sudden, bam!
She's got speed, and now she wants
&nbsp
to be a hero just like him.
And I think that's a great idea. Not!
&nbsp
Harry, we can help her.
We can train her just
like we did with Barry.
&nbsp
I don't want you to train her, okay?
I brought her here for you
to talk her out of it,
&nbsp
not talk her into it, all right, Ramon?
You... you should talk
to her. You're a meta.
&nbsp
Yeah, which makes me the last person
she should talk to about
not using her powers.
&nbsp
Okay, Snow...
Caitlin...
&nbsp
You and her,
you've always had such
a special relationship.
&nbsp
You talk to her.
- No, we don't.
- Yeah.
&nbsp
And I don't know anything
about having powers,
&nbsp
so I'm the last person
you should talk to,
&nbsp
so don't ask me.
Wait, I...
&nbsp
It can't...
Dad.
&nbsp
What's going on?
Why'd you want to see me?
&nbsp
Oh, hey.
Uh...
&nbsp
Have a seat.
Look...
&nbsp
I know it's been really hard for you,
seeing Jesse with speed.
&nbsp
I just keep thinking of what Harry said.
How sometimes it takes a
while for powers to manifest.
&nbsp
Yeah, Harry also said that
they may never manifest.
&nbsp
Yes, but I got hit by
that dark matter too,
&nbsp
just like Jesse.
Could still happen for me somehow.
&nbsp
Look, you weren't here
when the first particle
accelerator exploded.
&nbsp
That dark matter went
throughout the whole city.
&nbsp
Everybody got hit.
Me, your sister, this whole precinct.
&nbsp
Do you know how many metas
there have been so far?
&nbsp
I know you want this more than anything,
but you have to face the fact
that it might not happen.
&nbsp
So you think, just let it go?
Give up on wanting to help people?
&nbsp
You don't need powers to do that.
Look, Barry was coming to the rescue
&nbsp
as a CSI long before he was the Flash.
He wanted to help people then
&nbsp
just like you want to help people now.
So he studied.
&nbsp
He honed that brilliant mind of his.
And you have the same
brilliant mind, Wall.
&nbsp
- Dad...
- No, I mean it, son.
&nbsp
Look, a lot of people dream
about making the world a better place.
&nbsp
With that mind of yours and
that engineering talent,
&nbsp
you literally could
build a better world.
&nbsp
So what?
I got to stay in school?
&nbsp
Yeah, you got to stay in school.
Just a couple more years.
&nbsp
What are you doing?
I assumed you'd taken
a DNA sample before.
&nbsp
Okay, yes. I know what you're doing.
I mean, why are you doing it?
&nbsp
Are you looking to steal another sample?
I've isolated an element
&nbsp
consistent in all five of
the husks that we've found,
&nbsp
including Edward Clariss's.
- You mean the Rival?
- Mm.
&nbsp
That's what the papers
are calling him, yes.
&nbsp
What's the element?
I don't know.
&nbsp
But it's not one that I've found
in any other meta-human
samples that I've studied.
&nbsp
So you think that Frankie,
the girl downstairs,
&nbsp
has the same element in her DNA?
Well, I wouldn't be comparing samples
&nbsp
if it wasn't a possibility,
would I, Allen?
&nbsp
It's a good thing for both of us I did.
- Come on.
- What?
&nbsp
- Where is she?
- Calm down, okay? Julian?
&nbsp
You! You, girl! Stop!
- Hey, ease up, Julian.
- Stop!
&nbsp
- Me?
- You did it, didn't you?
&nbsp
What?
The lamppost. You did it, didn't you?
&nbsp
What? No, no, no, stop.
- You're a liar!
- Julian!
&nbsp
- You're a meta-human.
- Stop, no, stop!
&nbsp
You put your foster father
in the hospital, didn't you?
&nbsp
- No, no!
- Didn't you?
&nbsp
Didn't you?
Oh, I wanted to do more than hurt him.
&nbsp
Now I'm gonna do the same to you.
Frankie!
&nbsp
Frankie, stop!
Are you okay?
&nbsp
Frankie!
No.
&nbsp
Frankie's gone.
My name is Magenta.
&nbsp
You're like this because of Alchemy.
He changed you, didn't he?
&nbsp
This isn't you.
Just come with me.
&nbsp
Tell me what happened.
I can help you.
&nbsp
I don't need any more help, Flash.
I just don't want anyone to get hurt.
&nbsp
It's too late for that.
Frankie, don't!
&nbsp
It's me...
or him.
&nbsp
Come on.
Aah!
&nbsp
Her name's Frankie Kane,
but she's calling herself Magenta.
&nbsp
Meh.
That Magenta is a whole different person
&nbsp
than the scared,
kind girl I was interviewing.
&nbsp
She's dissociative.
You mean split-personality.
&nbsp
According to her medical records,
it's a condition she's been dealing with
&nbsp
her entire life.
I'm sure all the yelling at
CCPD is what triggered it.
&nbsp
So Frankie is Jekyll. Magenta is Hyde.
Classic good versus evil.
&nbsp
Or she's pulling a “Primal Fear.”
- She's faking it.
- No, she's not faking it.
&nbsp
I saw the struggle
going on inside of her.
&nbsp
Magenta's trying to
take over completely.
&nbsp
You said she was raised in
the foster care system.
&nbsp
Yep, all her life.
She went from home to home.
&nbsp
Yeah, and maybe not good ones.
Her current foster father, John...
&nbsp
The one who was hurt in the attack...
Yeah, he's got a few
disorderly conducts.
&nbsp
He might have some
information we can use.
&nbsp
I can follow up with him.
There is something else.
&nbsp
She got her powers from Alchemy.
When I said his name,
she knew who he was,
&nbsp
so Magenta must have existed
in the other timeline too.
&nbsp
Who's Alchemy?
Well, Doctor Alchemy is
a magic man in a cloak
&nbsp
who can somehow restore
the powers that people had
&nbsp
in Flashpoint.
Okay, and what's Flashpoint?
&nbsp
That's what we're calling
the alternate timeline
&nbsp
that Barry created when he went
back in time and saved his mom.
&nbsp
Oh.
So Magenta is another side-effect
&nbsp
from your time trip.
Genius. Not.
&nbsp
I don't need to be reminded. Thank you.
Look, anybody with those powers
&nbsp
and as angry as her needs
to be tracked down.
&nbsp
Fast.
Well, great. I mean, fast I can do.
Let me just go carb-load.
&nbsp
He didn't... That's... you don't...
Snow.
&nbsp
Please.
Okay, Harry, I'll talk to her,
&nbsp
but I don't know what I'm gonna say.
Hey, Joe?
&nbsp
Did you talk to Wally?
He still seems a little bummed.
&nbsp
It's not gonna fix itself overnight,
- but it's all good. He gets it.
- Okay.
&nbsp
And I got to be honest, it was one
of my better dad cop speeches.
&nbsp
What's “dad cop”?
There's good cop and
bad cop and dad cop.
&nbsp
Firm but reassuring. Cuts to the point.
I don't think I know that one.
&nbsp
Yeah, I didn't use it on you.
Wally's different than you, Barry.
&nbsp
You're like a second daughter.
You over-share your feelings.
&nbsp
Him, I got to be a little more nuanced.
Huh. Cool.
&nbsp
I'm messing with you.
I'll talk at you if I get any
leads on Frankie, all right?
&nbsp
All right.
Second daughter?
What is he talking about?
&nbsp
Hey!
Hey. Hey, sorry.
&nbsp
You guys were not kidding
when you said speedsters
were hungry all the time.
&nbsp
Yeah.
Listen, Jesse, before you
speed off to find Frankie,
&nbsp
I just want to make sure that
you feel like you're ready.
&nbsp
Why?
Is something wrong?
&nbsp
I mean, did the test
results say something?
&nbsp
No, not at all.
All the test results have
come back fine so far.
&nbsp
It's just...
maybe you should take it slow.
&nbsp
Right. This is because I'm a girl.
What?
&nbsp
No, not at all. Why?
Well, I mean, Barry didn't
have to take things slow.
&nbsp
You know, he was stopping the criminals
the second he got his powers.
&nbsp
Why can't I do the same thing?
Well, I mean, I'm sure you think
&nbsp
that it's a great thing to have powers,
but sometimes, it's not so great.
&nbsp
Trust me.
I'm just saying that if I had powers,
&nbsp
I would probably take it slow.
My dad put you up to this, didn't he?
&nbsp
Yeah. I mean, of course he did.
Jesse...
&nbsp
Hey.
You don't want me to
have this speed, do you?
&nbsp
I mean, that's why we're here, right?
Not so you could test me,
but so you could get everyone
&nbsp
to talk me out of using my powers.
I just want you to be...
&nbsp
To be safe, yeah.
Yeah, I know. I've heard
it my entire life.
&nbsp
This is different.
This is way different.
&nbsp
Yeah, no, it is.
- 'Cause I'm not Barry, right?
- Right.
&nbsp
You're not Barry.
Let me talk to her this time.
&nbsp
She's still here.
I can feel Frankie trying
to stay in control.
&nbsp
You said I could beat her.
What I said was
&nbsp
I'd return to you the power you had
to inflict your pain upon others.
&nbsp
But I need Frankie gone to do that.
Do you remember why you came to me?
&nbsp
I came to you
because you showed me a way
to stop him from hurting me.
&nbsp
Show him Magenta is in control.
And once you've done that,
&nbsp
Frankie will know it as well.
Here you are.
&nbsp
Hey.
Hey, so, where...
Where did you go yesterday?
&nbsp
Wha... I...
I didn't want to
interrupt your training.
&nbsp
Right.
Yeah, well, looks like
&nbsp
there won't be much of that anymore,
now that my dad is getting everyone
to talk me out of using my powers.
&nbsp
Wait, that... that's not
why you're here, right?
&nbsp
No, no.
This is all me.
&nbsp
You all right?
You know, when this whole thing
happened to me, you were...
&nbsp
you were actually the first
person I wanted to call.
&nbsp
Yeah, I was sort of hoping
it happened to you too.
&nbsp
I dreamt about it, believe me.
How did this all happen?
&nbsp
I mean, it was crazy.
So, like, one day,
&nbsp
I was walking home
from a friend's house,
&nbsp
and this car ran a red light,
and it was speeding right at me,
&nbsp
and I just stood there, frozen,
basically waiting to be hit.
&nbsp
And then I looked around,
and everything around me was frozen too.
&nbsp
It was peaceful and quiet,
but I felt this, like,
electricity running in me.
&nbsp
And so I ran out of the way.
I kept running and running, and I...
&nbsp
I mean, now I don't ever want to stop.
So you basically just
jump-started your powers.
&nbsp
I mean, I guess so, yeah. Why?
It's good to know.
&nbsp
Wally!
What are you doing?
&nbsp
Getting my speed. Why would you do that?
To save your life!
&nbsp
- It could've worked, Jesse!
- No, okay? Look...
&nbsp
I don't think so.
I'm sorry.
&nbsp
Seriously, what the
hell were you thinking?
&nbsp
You can't just go stepping
into the street like that.
&nbsp
I mean, you got to use your head.
Nothing happened, Barry. Chill out.
&nbsp
Didn't you talk to Joe about this?
- Yeah, so?
- So it clearly didn't help.
&nbsp
What would you have done if
Jesse wasn't there, huh?
&nbsp
I don't know, man.
Because there's nothing
you could've done.
&nbsp
Because you don't have powers.
Only room in our family
for one speedster, Barry?
&nbsp
Please just stop trying before
you get yourself killed.
&nbsp
- You done?
- Do you have anything to say?
&nbsp
No, you pretty much covered it.
- This has got to stop.
- Stop yelling at me, okay?
&nbsp
I saved his life.
What did you want me to do?
&nbsp
That's not the point. That is not the...
No, I know the point!
&nbsp
You don't want me to use my powers.
- Right.
- Fine.
&nbsp
Fine, but I don't need to stay
here and listen to this anymore.
&nbsp
No... Jess. Jesse!
Don't...
&nbsp
What did you say to her?
Me?
&nbsp
Yeah. You.
Don't blame me for this.
I tried to help.
&nbsp
Help her or help me?
Listen, Harry.
&nbsp
Maybe the reason she's shutting you out
is because you're not
trying to understand
&nbsp
- what she's going through.
- I don't need to unders...
&nbsp
Maybe if you helped her
navigate her powers
&nbsp
rather than just assuming
they'll destroy her,
&nbsp
she'd turn to you rather
than push you away.
&nbsp
Can't even bring myself to
take a lap around this thing.
&nbsp
Why is that?
I mean, you said it.
Everything's different here.
&nbsp
There's a guy creating meta-humans...
Innocent people...
'cause I changed the timeline.
&nbsp
It's on me.
Yeah, I think I know a thing or
two about what that feels like.
&nbsp
You know, I keep making mistakes.
I make mistakes, and then I want
&nbsp
to make up for my mistakes.
Then I just make more mistakes.
&nbsp
Next thing I know, I have a daughter
that won't even speak to me.
&nbsp
How do we keep from messing things up
when all we want to do is help?
&nbsp
I don't know.
But you did once tell me
&nbsp
that you have to trust
it in the long run
&nbsp
the decisions you make
are the right ones.
&nbsp
Yeah.
I was always too good at
forgiving myself, Allen.
&nbsp
You were never good enough.
John James?
&nbsp
Who's asking?
Hi, I'm Iris West.
&nbsp
I'm a reporter for Central
City Picture News.
&nbsp
I wanted to ask you a couple
questions about Frankie Kane.
&nbsp
They find her yet?
I don't believe so, no.
&nbsp
Well, what the hell's taking so long?
That damn meta-human
freak nearly killed me.
&nbsp
I know. I'm sorry.
That's what I get for taking
Frankie in, huh? This?
&nbsp
God help me if I ever see her again.
What does that mean?
&nbsp
It means that she's gonna
be the one in the hospital.
&nbsp
Tough love, John?
Yeah, you're damn right.
&nbsp
She was getting back at
you for hurting her.
&nbsp
And she's gonna try it again.
Nurse!
&nbsp
We need to get this man
to a safe location.
&nbsp
Why?
What the hell's that?
&nbsp
Oh, my God.
Where are you taking me?
&nbsp
Frankie is coming for you.
And as much as it pains me
&nbsp
to help an abusive dick like you,
I can't let you die.
&nbsp
What kind of alarm is that?
That's Iris's panic button.
&nbsp
- Her what?
- Her panic button.
&nbsp
We installed them on everyone's phones.
'Cause we kept getting kidnapped.
&nbsp
At least something's an
improvement in this timeline.
&nbsp
That's the hospital.
Frankie's foster father's there.
&nbsp
Yeah, and Iris went to see him.
Looks like she's not the only one.
&nbsp
- Is that a tanker?
- Th-th-that's a tanker, yeah.
&nbsp
She's gonna kill him and
everyone else in there.
&nbsp
- I got to go.
- What are you gonna do?
&nbsp
You don't have superstrength.
Start thinking.
&nbsp
Guys...
There's not enough time to get
everybody out of the hospital.
&nbsp
This thing's coming down.
Barry, Iris is still in there.
&nbsp
What if... What if I
create a wind funnel?
&nbsp
You won't be creating enough
updraft to keep that tanker up.
&nbsp
No, no. Not with my arms.
If I run.
&nbsp
- That could...
- Propeller.
&nbsp
That could work. Barry!
Run in a figure eight fashion.
You'll act like a propeller.
&nbsp
The wind will build upon itself.
It'll create the supersonic
resistance we need.
&nbsp
Could work.
All right.
&nbsp
Bye-bye, Daddy.
Flash!
&nbsp
Okay, well, that worked, but now what?
He can't stop her if he's up there.
&nbsp
Cisco's right.
Go help him.
&nbsp
Dad.
You need to get out there, now.
&nbsp
- Are you sure?
- Yes, I'm sure.
&nbsp
I know you can do it.
You're more than fast enough.
&nbsp
Now, run, Jesse.
Run!
&nbsp
Hey, thought you could
use a little help.
&nbsp
I got this. You go take care of her.
Magenta!
&nbsp
I got a little help.
So I could help you.
&nbsp
Okay, killing your foster father
and everyone else inside that hospital
&nbsp
isn't gonna give you what you need.
You have no idea what I need!
&nbsp
It's not just John that
I want to get rid of.
&nbsp
I want them both gone.
Barry, you got to stop her now.
&nbsp
That tanker's coming down!
I know you're still in there, Frankie.
&nbsp
Don't let John destroy the
good that's still inside you.
&nbsp
He said I was weak.
That I was pathetic!
&nbsp
He said I was a horrible person.
He's just blaming you for all the
bad things he's caused in his life.
&nbsp
It's not your fault.
This isn't because of you.
&nbsp
I just want him to stop hurting me.
This isn't the way.
&nbsp
Your foster father never forgave
himself for his mistakes.
&nbsp
That's why he took them out on you.
He couldn't move forward.
&nbsp
But you can.
They did it.
&nbsp
I'm so sorry.
It's okay.
&nbsp
I'm so sorry.
It's gonna be okay.
&nbsp
It's okay. It's gonna be okay.
So no one else got hurt?
&nbsp
Luckily, no.
You don't have to worry about that.
&nbsp
What about John?
The DA's prosecuting him
for what he did to you.
&nbsp
So I think he's gonna be serving time,
and he's not gonna ever be
anybody's foster father again.
&nbsp
It's just so strange being
responsible for all of this
&nbsp
and not remembering any of it.
What do you remember
&nbsp
about how you got your powers?
How this all began?
&nbsp
Um...
I started having dreams,
at night, of Magenta.
&nbsp
- Dreams?
- They were more than dreams.
&nbsp
It was like I was living
another life or something.
&nbsp
And then I started getting
them all the time.
&nbsp
During the day.
And the more it happened,
&nbsp
the more painful they became.
Then I started hearing a voice.
&nbsp
What voice?
It was a man.
&nbsp
Named Alchemy.
He said he could give me what I wanted
&nbsp
and make me powerful again.
I didn't understand.
&nbsp
I thought I was going crazy.
Trust me. Magenta is not here
because of anything that you did.
&nbsp
There may be a darkness inside of you,
but if you face it, it'll make it easier
&nbsp
for the good side of you to win.
You're letting me go?
&nbsp
None of this is your fault, Frankie.
Caitlin found you a
good home in Keystone.
&nbsp
People that will never hurt you.
But what if Magenta tries to come back?
&nbsp
Fight her.
And if you need help, we'll be there.
&nbsp
We have faith in you, Frankie.
Thank you.
&nbsp
Thank you all.
Are you okay?
&nbsp
Yeah.
Yeah, I...
&nbsp
I just feel bad for her, you know?
- You sure?
- Yeah.
&nbsp
- No dad cop required.
- Oh!
&nbsp
You heard about that, huh?
Yeah, I heard about that.
&nbsp
Hey.
There she is.
&nbsp
You were tremendous out there.
You really were.
&nbsp
I guess that's your first victory...
as a superhero.
&nbsp
My daughter.
Jesse Quick.
&nbsp
Yeah.
Yeah, well, I mean,
I was only able to do it
&nbsp
'cause you believed in me, so...
No, I should've been that way
a long, long time ago, but...
&nbsp
You know, one day, you'll understand.
I don't expect you to now, but...
&nbsp
but I'm always gonna worry.
I'm always going to be cautious.
&nbsp
I'm always going to love you.
Dad, I know.
&nbsp
I mean, of course I know.
And I will always love you.
&nbsp
Even when you drive me
absolutely insane.
&nbsp
So...
So.
&nbsp
Are we going home or...
I think we'll stay for a few days,
&nbsp
run a few more tests,
and also to see if this fits you.
&nbsp
Cisco did the insignia. Snow
thought this would help you, and...
&nbsp
I agree.
- You do?
- I do.
&nbsp
My...
My fear... my guilt...
&nbsp
has kept both of us back
for far too long.
&nbsp
You know you've always been my hero.
But now...
&nbsp
it's time for me to let you
be one for everyone else.
&nbsp
Thank you.
- Hey.
- Hey, you just made it.
&nbsp
Yeah, I had to make
sure Frankie was okay.
&nbsp
So, are you ready to try this again?
Um... actually, I had a thought
&nbsp
about why our last date was so boring.
Oh, yeah?
&nbsp
Yeah...
Here you go.
&nbsp
Um...
So, I know that you think that
I shouldn't use my powers,
&nbsp
and it's not that I'm
nothing without them,
&nbsp
but they are a part of me now, you know?
They're part of you.
&nbsp
This is our life, and I think,
last date, we were
ignoring that part of us.
&nbsp
We were trying to be
the people that we were
&nbsp
before I was the Flash,
and that's why it wasn't working.
&nbsp
Okay, so what are you saying?
I'm saying we have to stop
denying who we really are.
&nbsp
Well, yeah, I mean,
when you put it that way...
&nbsp
I agree.
We can't pretend like none
of this has happened.
&nbsp
I thought you'd see it that way.
Sorry.
&nbsp
It's Joe. He needs me at the station.
It's fine. Go.
&nbsp
- Really?
- Yeah. Yeah.
&nbsp
This has already been a
really amazing date...
&nbsp
Flash.
- Hey, what's going on?
- There you are.
&nbsp
Listen, Singh wanted me
to show you guys this.
&nbsp
This happened a few days
ago at Iron Heights.
&nbsp
They tried to keep it under wraps 'cause
they didn't want anybody to think
&nbsp
there was a security issue,
but check it out.
&nbsp
- That's Clariss.
- Alchemy!
&nbsp
It was Clariss.
No! Aah! No! Stop!
&nbsp
Dead before he hit the ground.
Alchemy.
&nbsp
You ever heard that name before?
Alchemy?
&nbsp
No, I haven't.
Maybe there's an invisible meta.
&nbsp
Maybe it's a ghost.
Do you believe in ghosts, Allen?
&nbsp
No?
Hey, do you think this thing
&nbsp
is part of the Flashpoint timeline too?
I have a feeling a lot of
things are these days.
&nbsp
Synced and corrected by johnyd13
~ www.addic7ed.com ~
&nbsp