My name is Barry Allen,
&nbsp
and I'm the fastest man alive.
To the outside world,
&nbsp
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
&nbsp
I fight crime and find
other meta-humans like me.
&nbsp
After defeating Zoom
and saving the multiverse,
&nbsp
I ran back in time and created
the alternate timeline Flashpoint.
&nbsp
I restored the timeline to how it was,
only to find things weren't as I left them.
&nbsp
I brought new threats to our world,
and I'm the only one
fast enough to stop them.
&nbsp
I am The Flash.
Previously on "The Flash"...
&nbsp
This has been a really amazing date, Flash.
Cecile, thanks for stopping by.
&nbsp
Hey, anything for my favorite detective.
You restored the timeline,
and things were different?
&nbsp
Exactly.
Jesse, you're a speedster.
&nbsp
When I came back, things weren't the same.
You mean people.
&nbsp
Yeah.
How do I look?
&nbsp
Better.
How much?
&nbsp
Do we really need to ask that question?
Our take wasn't that big.
&nbsp
Big enough.
But the only question
you should be asking is,
&nbsp
what size rock you want dangling
from this beautiful neck?
&nbsp
A kiss from you makes my world spin.
You're so full of it, you know that?
&nbsp
I got to be honest.
I never understood...this.
&nbsp
But like my sister says,
anyone can stoop over and pick up nothing.
&nbsp
What do you want, Snart?
I told you two
to sit on your cut for a while,
&nbsp
until things cool down.
Some of us like to actually spend the cash
&nbsp
we get from these jobs.
Not when it's from the ones with me.
&nbsp
You didn't pull 'em off yourself.
Without us, you'd still be
kicking down liquor stores.
&nbsp
I think you've spent too much time
staring at yourself in the mirror,
&nbsp
because your perception
of reality is a bit warped.
&nbsp
You know the rules.
I don't give a damn about your rules,
&nbsp
or laying low.
There's no one in this city who can stop us.
&nbsp
Including you, Snart.
It sounds to me like
you're saying you want out.
&nbsp
- Mm.
- Guess so.
&nbsp
Well, if you're out...
You're out.
&nbsp
No!
You lost, Scudder.
&nbsp
Sam!
Go.
&nbsp
Go!
Sam?
&nbsp
Give me a hand here.
Demo starts in a month.
Get everything out of here.
&nbsp
The hell?
Where's Snart?
&nbsp
This is from a security camera
inside Iron Heights.
&nbsp
Forensic analysis indicates
that the footage is genuine,
&nbsp
no evidence of tampering.
And we're pretty sure this is
Doctor Alchemy that did this?
&nbsp
The last thing Clariss said before he died.
Unless someone else killed him.
&nbsp
Like a meta with telekinesis
or cloaking abilities.
&nbsp
We've got both on our Earth.
So what do we do now?
&nbsp
Our meta-human specialist at CCPD,
Julian Albert, he prefers to work alone,
&nbsp
but I got feelers out on his investigation.
I'm gonna go there now
and see if he dug up anything.
&nbsp
All right.
Okay, well, until then,
you guys want to train?
&nbsp
Well, now, we have to think about
getting back to our Earth.
&nbsp
We've been here long enough.
I've still got a lot to learn.
&nbsp
Your words, not mine.
I...
&nbsp
Fine.
Well, if you want to train,
&nbsp
let's train...
speedster style.
&nbsp
Damn, Jesse's almost as fast as Barry.
Velocity's just under Mach 3.
&nbsp
Heart rate, 100 BPMs. Her vitals are normal.
Yeah, no, we already know all that.
&nbsp
Cisco, we need to test her reflexes.
Can we test her reflexes?
Patience, Harry, patience.
&nbsp
If anyone's gonna teach Jesse
the ways of the Speed Force...
&nbsp
- It's Barry.
- Thank you.
&nbsp
Aah!
Okay. Well, that wasn't very heroic.
&nbsp
Nope.
But there is a lesson in there somewhere.
&nbsp
What's that?
The difference between having powers
&nbsp
and having precision.
Well, what do you mean?
&nbsp
I mean, it's gonna take more than speed
to take down some of these metas.
&nbsp
You got to think, anticipate.
When you enter a new environment,
&nbsp
you got to case every inch of it.
You never run in blind.
&nbsp
Oh, my God.
I've become Oliver.
&nbsp
Huh.
Maybe we should stay a little bit longer.
&nbsp
Yeah, I guess so.
It's gonna take some time
to master your powers, Jesse.
&nbsp
You'll get the hang of it.
Yeah, I know, thanks.
&nbsp
Well, since I will be here for a while,
do you want to get out of here?
&nbsp
- Where to?
- Does it matter?
&nbsp
No touching.
Not what I meant by staying longer!
&nbsp
I should probably get back to CCPN.
- All right.
- I'll see you tonight?
&nbsp
- Can't wait.
- Okay.
&nbsp
- Hey, Harry.
- Yeah?
&nbsp
Are you really sure you have to leave?
Just a lot I still have to fix on my Earth.
&nbsp
Yeah, but you know it's more fun
when you're here helping us
fix stuff on our Earth.
&nbsp
He is right.
It hasn't been the same without you.
&nbsp
The team doesn't feel complete
without Harrison Wells.
&nbsp
Then change that.
There's a whole multiverse of Harrison Wells
&nbsp
out there at your fingertips.
You want one? Let's go get one.
&nbsp
Yeah, now I remembered it.
Thank you, Officer Mayer.
&nbsp
- Hey.
- Oh, hey.
&nbsp
So sorry. I got held up at the courthouse.
No problem.
&nbsp
You're the one doing me the favor.
Yeah, I wouldn't thank me just yet.
&nbsp
Oh, you couldn't find anything.
Nope, no one at the DA's office
&nbsp
knows anything about anybody named Alchemy.
Oh, damn.
&nbsp
This is, um...
Meta-human related, I assume?
&nbsp
- It appears to be.
- Yikes.
&nbsp
- I know.
- Okay.
&nbsp
You let me know if there's
anything I can do for you, yeah?
&nbsp
Yeah, thanks for bringing it
yourself, Cecile.
&nbsp
It was my pleasure.
This is really nice.
&nbsp
Staying in is so much better than going out.
When you have jobs like ours? Yes.
&nbsp
Yes.
What?
&nbsp
You're just really handsome.
You are not so bad yourself.
&nbsp
Hey, hey... Hi. I thought...
I didn't think you were gonna
be home for a while, right?
&nbsp
My plans changed.
Unfortunately. I'm just gonna go upstairs.
&nbsp
You can have a beer, sit with us.
Have a good night.
&nbsp
I... I know.
I'm...I'm sorry.
&nbsp
I... I... should we rain check, or...
Barry, I am not upset because
our date got interrupted.
&nbsp
- That, I understand.
- What do you mean?
&nbsp
You, speeding away when my dad walks in.
- Yeah.
- Because, what, we're kissing?
&nbsp
Yeah, Iris, exactly.
What, you don't want to kiss me?
&nbsp
Of course I want to kiss you.
But not in front of him.
&nbsp
What does that matter?
He's your... he's our...
&nbsp
Joe.
Joe. I don't know.
&nbsp
- Barry, we are adults.
- I know.
&nbsp
- We are dating.
- Yeah.
&nbsp
We should be able to kiss.
I agree.
&nbsp
Okay, yep.
Yep. You should talk to him.
&nbsp
I... about?
For real? Yeah.
&nbsp
Go talk to him.
- Yeah, sure, I'll talk to him.
- Okay.
&nbsp
- About us kissing.
- Yeah.
&nbsp
It's not gonna be awkward at all.
Let me know how it goes.
&nbsp
It's gonna be awkward, that's how.
Where's Snart?
&nbsp
Who said that?
Where are you?
&nbsp
Boo.
Scudder?
&nbsp
Where's Snart?
I don't know, man.
&nbsp
Then I guess I'll just have to
find someone who does.
&nbsp
And I know just the girl.
Yeah, Sam Scudder.
He threw me into a mirror.
&nbsp
I fell out of a second-story window.
So Scudder's going after
everyone in Snart's old crew
&nbsp
to track him down?
Yeah, but the only problem is,
&nbsp
Scudder's not gonna find him.
Snart's gone.
&nbsp
What do you mean, he's gone?
He's gone. I thought I...
&nbsp
Oliver told me that Snart left
with some friends of ours on a... trip.
&nbsp
I don't even want to know.
One of Snart's old crew is at Iron Heights.
&nbsp
I'll go see if I can talk to her.
Okay, I'll see if I can locate
&nbsp
any others at S.T.A.R. Labs.
Hey, um, hey, actually...
I'm sorry, I just...
&nbsp
I need to talk to you
about something really quick.
&nbsp
Um...
Okay, so I... I know
&nbsp
it's probably awkward
seeing me and Iris kiss.
&nbsp
- Uh, yeah.
- Yeah.
&nbsp
So I... I was just thinking, maybe...
did it have to be awkward?
&nbsp
Do you mean like this conversation?
Yeah, like this conversation.
&nbsp
I don't know, just 'cause
the next time, um, you see us,
&nbsp
we may kiss again in front of you.
Okay.
&nbsp
So I just want to make sure
that that is... okay with you.
&nbsp
- Look, Bar.
- Uh-huh.
&nbsp
- You're an adult.
- Yes.
&nbsp
Do what you got to do.
I love you. I love you too.
&nbsp
I love her.
I don't love watching you two make out.
&nbsp
Um, okay, and just... just so you know,
I am gonna tell Iris that...
that we talked about this.
&nbsp
Yeah, like I said. Do what you got to do.
Okay.
&nbsp
Wow.
How sure are you that this will work?
&nbsp
Pretty sure.
Okay, but how's this going to help us
&nbsp
find another Harrison Wells?
You ever go fishing, Snow?
&nbsp
- No.
- No, all right.
&nbsp
When you go fishing, you use lures.
Lures attract fish.
&nbsp
Fish end up on your fishing pole.
This satellite is our fishing pole,
&nbsp
through which we're going
to cast our very tempting bait
&nbsp
out into the world's largest ocean.
Okay, how?
&nbsp
How? Cisco will open a breach,
and this satellite
will shoot a message embedded
&nbsp
with a tachyon-enhanced laser
out into the multiverse,
&nbsp
and any Earth that is
technologically advanced enough
&nbsp
should be able to receive it.
Okay, let's say this somehow works.
&nbsp
Just 'cause they can solve a riddle
doesn't mean they're
a right fit for the team.
&nbsp
A riddle. Did you say riddle?
- Yeah.
- How dare you, sir.
&nbsp
This is not a riddle.
This is a complex algorithmic cryptogram
&nbsp
designed to test deductive reasoning,
IQ, problem-solving skills,
&nbsp
anything that our team
will need to combat threats,
&nbsp
meta-human or otherwise.
Okay, so you're just sending
out an intergalactic IQ test
&nbsp
to all of your doppelgangers
in the multiverse.
&nbsp
Not just a test.
Think of it as an invitation.
&nbsp
Think of it as an elaborate
"help wanted" ad.
&nbsp
Will it test their attitudes, too?
'Cause I'm not sure
I can stomach another Wells
&nbsp
with your bedside manner.
I care for you too, you jack wagon.
&nbsp
System is calibrated.
What are you waiting for?
&nbsp
And...
That's it.
&nbsp
- That's it?
- Yeah, that's it.
&nbsp
So now what?
Now...
&nbsp
we go get a Big Belly burger.
- That's insane. What a rush.
- I know.
&nbsp
I mean, it took me a while
to get used to it.
&nbsp
I can't believe you're not sick at all.
I must have an iron stomach.
&nbsp
Okay, so you're telling me
that Barry has never taken you on a run?
&nbsp
No.
Well, then, I guess
it's a good thing you've got me.
&nbsp
Guess so.
Whoa, um, hold up.
&nbsp
Oh...I'm sorry.
Am I... am I reading this, like,
really wrong or something?
&nbsp
No, no.
I like you, Jesse. It's just...
&nbsp
It's just what?
You're going home soon.
&nbsp
To another Earth.
Ah, right. Yeah.
&nbsp
Yeah, no, it's... it's cool, yeah.
- Jesse, I...
- No, no, no.
&nbsp
It's... it's totally cool.
I get it.
&nbsp
So... so friends, then?
Friends.
&nbsp
Well, as friends, I mean,
we can still run around the city, right?
&nbsp
Sure.
Good-looking guy.
&nbsp
For a criminal.
Well, he's more than just a criminal now.
&nbsp
Apparently, he's a meta
who can travel through mirrors.
&nbsp
Oh, oh, I got this one. He's, uh...
- Mirror Master.
- What the...
&nbsp
- Boom.
- That's good.
&nbsp
Thank you, we had
a Mirror Master on our Earth,
&nbsp
Evan McCulloch. Wasn't a meta, though.
He had some kind of mirror gun that he used.
&nbsp
- How'd it work?
- Must've had dimensional
&nbsp
warping tech that changed
everything into two dimensions.
&nbsp
Well, Scudder is hell-bent on finding Snart,
and he's going after anybody
that worked with him
&nbsp
in the past.
Joe's interviewing one of 'em right now.
&nbsp
Well, all of Snart's known associates
are either presumed dead
or gone AWOL, except for one.
&nbsp
- That's her.
- Rosalind Dillon.
&nbsp
Says she has the ability
to induce crippling vertigo.
&nbsp
- Oh, um, uh...
- She's, uh...
&nbsp
Top, like a top. She's The Top.
That's her name. Top. Amazing.
&nbsp
What, you want to go?
Okay.
&nbsp
Do we think that she can lead us to Scudder?
I'll have to see if Joe gets
any answers out of her.
&nbsp
Heard your ex is back in town.
You know anything about that?
&nbsp
He pay you a visit, Ms. Dillon?
They don't let people like me
have visitors here, Detective.
&nbsp
All day, all night,
in my boring little cell.
&nbsp
Makes a girl go crazy.
Scudder tried to kill one of
your old crewmates last night.
&nbsp
Leon Williams? Tried? Too bad he failed.
He's gonna try to kill more.
&nbsp
Any idea who? Give us a name.
I'll see what we can do
about your current situation.
&nbsp
Okay.
Let us know if you change your mind.
&nbsp
- Sorry, Joe.
- It's all right.
&nbsp
I appreciate your setting up
the interview, though.
&nbsp
It looks like I owe you another one.
You know, these IOUs
are starting to pile up.
&nbsp
I have an idea about that.
Do you?
&nbsp
- Scudder?
- You want me?
&nbsp
Come and get me.
So you saw Sam Scudder and Rosalind Dillon
&nbsp
escape through a glass window?
Like I said, he grabbed her hand.
&nbsp
They walked to the window,
and then poof, they were gone.
&nbsp
So, mirrors, windows.
It sounds like he can travel
through anything
&nbsp
that has a reflective surface.
How exactly does he do that?
&nbsp
He must be able to link
Einstein-Rosen bridges
&nbsp
to anything with high solar
reflectance, right?
&nbsp
So he creates wormholes through reflections.
That's a new one.
&nbsp
Look, I can't pretend
to understand or care
&nbsp
about the science of it all,
but we need to find Dillon
&nbsp
and Scudder before something
really bad happens.
&nbsp
So I'm gonna go old-school at the precinct.
I'll see you later.
&nbsp
Oh, my God.
Pings. We got pings.
&nbsp
Looks like some of
your doppelgangers out there
&nbsp
actually cracked your code, Harry.
That was fast.
&nbsp
Let's go take a look.
Guys? We're...
&nbsp
Um... Dad seems fine.
Um, yeah, no, he's still
a little weird about it.
&nbsp
You talked to him, though, right?
Um, yeah, I did.
&nbsp
Yeah, it'll be good.
- Okay, great.
- Yeah.
&nbsp
- Then I'll see you tonight.
- All right.
&nbsp
You'll pick a good movie?
- I'll try.
- Okay.
&nbsp
I'm also gonna try to find our meta-humans
that apparently no one else
cares about right now.
&nbsp
Well the hell did you go?
How many times do I have to tell you, Rosa?
&nbsp
I was stuck in there.
Whatever it was that hit me
gave me this crazy ability.
&nbsp
And to me, all this
just happened last night.
&nbsp
It's been three years, Sam.
So many things are different now.
&nbsp
You were hit too, weren't you?
You can do things like me?
&nbsp
- Yeah.
- Show me.
&nbsp
You might want to hold onto something.
Whoa.
&nbsp
Oh.
See, Sammy?
&nbsp
Too much has changed.
Then let's change it back.
&nbsp
Huh?
I can stop Snart, Rosa.
&nbsp
We... can stop Snart.
Snart? He's gone.
&nbsp
Long gone.
Then let's take this city.
&nbsp
We can be who we want to now.
We can be in control.
&nbsp
There's no one in this city
who can stop us now.
&nbsp
There's one person who can.
Who?
&nbsp
The Flash.
Well, hey, now.
&nbsp
I... I solved the derivative
you done beamed up.
&nbsp
My name is Wells, Harrison Wells.
You can call me Hell's Wells.
&nbsp
They call me that 'cause of my past.
I won't get into it
with you now right and proper.
&nbsp
I'd like to hitch wagons and...
I had a bad dinner.
&nbsp
- Pass.
- All right.
&nbsp
This is Earth-17.
I'll be in touch.
&nbsp
Salutations to all of you
out there in the multiverse.
&nbsp
I have of late, wherefore I know
not, received a communiqué
&nbsp
from the citizens of Terra-Prime.
Terra-Prime?
&nbsp
- Nerd.
- Pass.
&nbsp
Bonjour. Moi, je suis Harrison Wells.
You can't trust a mime.
&nbsp
- Can't argue with that.
- Pass.
&nbsp
Okay, guys. We're 0 for 3 now.
This is our last one.
&nbsp
It's coming from Earth-19.
Hello, hello, hello.
&nbsp
Hello, out there in the multiverse,
whoever you may be.
&nbsp
Um...
I really enjoyed cracking
the cryptogram you broadcast.
&nbsp
I like the cute trick,
embedding the secondary measures
&nbsp
in the primary data string. It's clever.
Most people wouldn't have caught it.
&nbsp
I caught it. But that's the point.
You need a genius, I guess,
&nbsp
to help you in your fight
against these awful meta-hominids.
&nbsp
Well, I got to tell you...
I got to tell you, to me,
&nbsp
that sounds like fun.
So... I'll enclose my curriculum vitae.
&nbsp
You already know we speak the same language.
But take a look. Tell me what you think.
&nbsp
Until our next communion.
Oh, where are my manners?
&nbsp
Thank you.
- Not bad.
- Not bad at all.
&nbsp
Harry?
- Pass.
- What?
&nbsp
- Pass.
- Wait, what? Wait a minute.
&nbsp
That guy cracked the code,
and he wants to do it.
&nbsp
And he's nice, and he's not evil.
And that's a combination of
Wells we haven't had thus far.
&nbsp
All my life, everyone
I've ever hired to work for me,
&nbsp
I have trusted my gut.
My gut tells me that's not the guy.
&nbsp
Keep looking.
It's all right. He's my friend.
&nbsp
Sorry. I'm just gonna get...
Oh, for God's sake.
&nbsp
Okay, you know what?
I can't take this anymore.
&nbsp
What?
I thought you guys
were supposed to talk about us.
&nbsp
- We did.
Then why are you being so weird?
&nbsp
I'm not.
Dad?
&nbsp
Iris.
I already told him,
if you two want to cuddle,
&nbsp
make out, do whatever,
I... I... go for it.
&nbsp
I don't care.
- Barry?
- Hey.
&nbsp
Should we give you guys a minute?
- Yeah.
- No, no, it's fine.
&nbsp
Look, Barry, this isn't
about my dad anymore.
&nbsp
He's fine with it.
I'm not totally fine with it.
&nbsp
So why do you have a problem with this?
Thank God.
&nbsp
There's a robbery at First National.
Suspects match Scudder
and Dillon's description.
&nbsp
Scudder and Dillon, yeah,
I'm sorry, I got to go.
&nbsp
Okay.
Hey... let me help.
&nbsp
We've been training for a reason, right?
- I've got to try.
- Yeah, all right, cool.
&nbsp
Just follow my lead. Okay.
We keep this up,
&nbsp
baby, we'll be set for life.
Then what are you waiting for?
&nbsp
Let's do it again.
Anything for you, baby.
&nbsp
Yeah, so we're not gonna
let you leave here with that.
&nbsp
Hey, Flash.
Heard a lot about you.
&nbsp
That's great.
Can't say the same for you, though.
&nbsp
The name's Jesse Quick.
- Oh.
- So... I'm sorry, Scudder,
&nbsp
but your little crime spree,
it's gonna have to end here.
&nbsp
Oh, I don't think
you have much of a say in it.
&nbsp
I'm gonna take whatever I want.
I thought you were looking
for Leonard Snart.
&nbsp
Why bother? His reign is over.
There's a... a new king in town.
&nbsp
And I'm the queen.
Yeah, I wouldn't be too sure about that.
&nbsp
Oh, I would, little girl.
Where'd they go?
&nbsp
There.
Stay here.
&nbsp
I'm not kidding.
Nice skirt, Top.
&nbsp
Top.
I like it.
&nbsp
Because they spin, spin, spin.
What? What's happening?
&nbsp
Aah... aah!
I can't get my balance.
&nbsp
I know. It's okay.
You're gonna be okay.
&nbsp
But you won't.
Oh!
&nbsp
Good luck getting him out.
Barry!
&nbsp
- What happened?
- I don't know.
&nbsp
I don't know, okay? I looked at Dillon,
- and I lost my balance.
- She's a meta-human
&nbsp
who induces vertigo.
She just whammied you.
&nbsp
Yeah, I guess so.
It doesn't really matter, does it?
&nbsp
Because now Barry's trapped
in there and it's because of me.
&nbsp
Well, you know,
I...
&nbsp
I'll go talk to her.
What is he saying?
&nbsp
Is that some sort of mirror language?
Mirrors show objects in reverse.
&nbsp
Maybe that's what we're hearing here.
Only one way to find out.
&nbsp
What are you looking for, Cisco?
You ever seen "Twin Peaks"?
&nbsp
Of course not. Why do I ask?
This is an old backmasking trick
&nbsp
they used for the Man from Another Place,
where they record his audio backwards
&nbsp
and then play it forwards.
Like the Ozzy Osbourne records.
&nbsp
Sure, let's go with that.
Okay, Barry, say something.
&nbsp
Oops.
Say it again.
&nbsp
Um, get me out of here.
Now we can understand you.
How do we get him out of there?
&nbsp
Barry, have you tried to phase out yet?
Yes. It's not working.
&nbsp
If Scudder used this mirror as a wormhole,
then these molecules are in a
hyper state of flux, so all...
&nbsp
We need is something
really cold to slow them down.
&nbsp
I can help with that. Let's go.
Keep him company.
&nbsp
Aren't you gonna need that?
What's the point?
&nbsp
You know, I thought I was ready,
but clearly I'm not.
&nbsp
Jesse, you can't blame yourself for this.
- What happened to Barry...
- It was totally my fault.
&nbsp
I mean, he told me to stay back,
but I didn't listen, you know?
&nbsp
I just ran in blind, and...
and now he's stuck, so...
&nbsp
Look, you made a mistake. So what?
I mean, I'm sure Barry made
a lot of mistakes at first too.
&nbsp
Yeah.
Don't let this destroy your confidence.
&nbsp
You're meant to do this, Jesse.
You're meant to be a speedster.
&nbsp
That's why you have these powers
and I don't.
&nbsp
You're just trying to cheer me up.
I know you said
you don't want to hang, so...
&nbsp
No, I said I didn't want to
hang out because I was scared.
&nbsp
Because you live on another Earth, but...
I realized I don't want
to be scared of that anymore.
&nbsp
I don't think it's gonna work.
What do you mean,
you don't think it's gonna work?
&nbsp
I built this to go to absolute zero.
I realize that. But we need the mirror
&nbsp
to maintain zero-point energy long enough
for Barry's molecules to pass through it.
&nbsp
Absolute zero's more
than cold enough to do that.
&nbsp
Normally, but we have to
account for the internal energy
&nbsp
of the mirror's molecules, as well.
So while absolute cold might be
the lowest possible temperature,
&nbsp
it's not the... It's not the lowest
- enthalpy state possible.
- Exactly right.
&nbsp
So what are we gonna do?
I don't know... yet.
&nbsp
Okay, go with me here.
What if we send this to the other Wells
&nbsp
and see if he can figure something out?
- Yeah.
- What? No.
&nbsp
What? Oh, everybody's
replaceable now, is that right?
&nbsp
- Is that what this is?
- What are you talking about?
&nbsp
What are you talking about?
That's what you said.
&nbsp
That's not what I said.
I'm saying we need to figure out
&nbsp
a solution to this problem, and time's not
- on our side right now.
- That's not gonna help... you're
&nbsp
not contributing to the problem.
You're making things worse.
&nbsp
- You know what I think?
- What do you think?
&nbsp
I think you don't like the idea of someone
- taking your place here.
- What are you talking about?
&nbsp
This is why you don't like the other Wells.
What are you talking about? It was my idea.
&nbsp
But that doesn't mean you have to like it.
It's got nothing to do with liking, okay?
&nbsp
You know what it has to do with?
A molecular decelerator.
&nbsp
If we augment the molecular decelerator
- on the cryogenic generator...
- Of the cold gun...
&nbsp
I can build that. I can build that.
Great.
&nbsp
What are you doing?
Do these pants make my butt look big?
&nbsp
I'm literally stuck in a mirror.
Sorry, yeah.
&nbsp
What's it like in there?
Um...
&nbsp
dark.
Look, Iris, I'm...
&nbsp
I'm sorry that I'm... stuck right now.
Oh, honey, I know that you're stuck.
&nbsp
It's okay, we are gonna
get you out of there.
&nbsp
No, I mean... no.
That was misleading.
&nbsp
Not the mirror. I mean, with us.
This thing with Joe, and you were right.
&nbsp
I mean, it's not Joe.
It's me. It's my problem.
&nbsp
I've just been feeling nervous
about this new dynamic
&nbsp
between the three of us.
I... I don't know.
&nbsp
I have everything that
I have ever wanted right now.
&nbsp
And I've never had that in my life.
In a lot of ways,
&nbsp
it's scarier than having nothing, because...
it's easier to fail than succeed.
&nbsp
And I really want to succeed.
What could you possibly be
laughing about right now?
&nbsp
I am so sorry, Barry.
You are really sweet.
&nbsp
But it is weird talking to you
through a mirror and a speaker,
&nbsp
and I really want to kiss you right now.
But can we please talk about this later?
&nbsp
Yeah. We can talk about it later.
Guess it is pretty weird.
&nbsp
It's like I'm here, but I'm not.
What?
&nbsp
I just thought of a way to stop Scudder.
What is that?
&nbsp
This is how we get him out of there.
All right. Let's do it.
&nbsp
Okay.
Try it now.
&nbsp
It's only negative 280 degrees Fahrenheit.
We got to get it colder somehow.
&nbsp
I thought you guys said this thing
could get him out of there.
&nbsp
Okay, this thing
is a highly advanced molecular decelerator
&nbsp
that's being powered by a cryo-engine,
and we just kind of improvised
it in the last 30 minutes,
&nbsp
so let's just... just cut us
some slack, please?
&nbsp
Just keep trying, Barry.
Meta-human alert.
&nbsp
Oh, for God's sake.
If it's not one thing...
&nbsp
It's the other.
Hold on, Bar.
&nbsp
Guys?
Hello?
&nbsp
Central City Municipal Bank just got robbed.
Let me guess by who.
&nbsp
Guys.
- Barry.
- Hey.
&nbsp
- How?
- Let's figure it out later.
&nbsp
Right now we need to stop
Scudder and Dillon.
&nbsp
Okay, so... so what do we do?
We're gonna use mirrors,
&nbsp
an old trick, and an old friend.
- Yeah?
- It's Snart.
&nbsp
I heard you were back in town.
- Snart?
- Scudder, Rosa.
&nbsp
Long time.
Not long enough.
&nbsp
Hang back.
This guy owes me.
&nbsp
So you called us.
The hell you want?
&nbsp
Same thing.
You two, gone.
&nbsp
Things have changed.
This is our town now.
&nbsp
- Is that right?
- Yeah, it is.
&nbsp
And that little cold gun of yours
isn't gonna save you from me.
&nbsp
We'll see about that, now, won't we?
Bang!
&nbsp
Funny thing about holograms.
They're just pale reflections
of the real deal.
&nbsp
Hello again.
Jesse Quick.
&nbsp
Quick to run, quick to fall.
Quick to learn.
&nbsp
Uh-oh.
Well played, Flash.
&nbsp
Oh.
- What?
- I know, right?
&nbsp
This is the, uh, Droste effect.
I'm sure you've heard of it, right?
&nbsp
It's an infinite reflective loop
that even you can't escape.
&nbsp
Good luck getting out.
So you're sure he can't
&nbsp
Mirror Master his way out of this cell?
No, it's impossible.
&nbsp
Every inch has been modified
with an anti-reflective material.
&nbsp
Even Scudder's gonna forget what
he looks like after a while.
&nbsp
Well, I should go.
Hey. So, thank you for everything.
&nbsp
Oh, no. Thank you.
We got another bad meta
right where he belongs.
&nbsp
- Yep, all right.
- Hey, Joe.
&nbsp
We have an awful lot of IOUs.
Do you maybe want to grab
some dinner tonight?
&nbsp
- Dinner?
- Yeah.
&nbsp
Yeah, I... well, I've got movie night
with my kids tonight.
&nbsp
Rain check?
Yeah. Of course.
&nbsp
Another time, then.
Yo. What was that about?
&nbsp
- Why didn't you just say yes?
- I don't know.
&nbsp
You're not the only one
that gets nervous around here.
&nbsp
You guys, I've never vibed
across 18 dimensions before.
&nbsp
Just a little bit longer.
Greetings, earthlings.
&nbsp
Just kidding. I don't really talk like that.
I've just always wanted to say that.
&nbsp
Earthlings.
Wells with a sense of humor. That's new.
&nbsp
Hey, sharpshooter.
You.
&nbsp
You're... handsome.
I know.
&nbsp
- Likewise, I'm sure.
- Yeah.
&nbsp
Harrison.
You can call me HR.
&nbsp
HR it is.
This is the team, then. Um...
&nbsp
This is Cisco Ramon. He can do anything.
Okay.
&nbsp
This is Dr. Caitlin Snow.
She is brilliant.
&nbsp
- Hi.
- Single.
&nbsp
Don't... all right, that's my daughter.
You don't have to shake her hand.
&nbsp
That gentleman there is Wally West.
This is Barry Allen, or as we call him
&nbsp
on this Earth...
The Flash.
&nbsp
- Welcome to Earth-1.
- Thanks.
&nbsp
Earth-1, that's weird.
Okay, well, we don't have
to stand on ceremony.
&nbsp
We don't have to go through all
the tears again, do we, gang?
&nbsp
- Right?
- Well, did I...
&nbsp
did I cry last time you left?
- I was talking about myself.
- Oh, gotcha.
&nbsp
Hey, listen.
Don't worry about it, okay?
&nbsp
There's only one Harry.
Oh, I wanted to tell you.
&nbsp
The molecular decelerator,
it wasn't working.
&nbsp
Okay, what does that mean?
It means that we did not
get Barry out of that mirror.
&nbsp
It wasn't us.
Then who did it?
&nbsp
You tell me.
- See you later.
- Yeah.
&nbsp
Earth-2's gonna have one hell
of a speedster protecting it.
&nbsp
Well, I did learn from the best.
If you ever need any help,
you know how to get back.
&nbsp
Yeah. Yeah, definitely, I'll be back.
All right.
&nbsp
Okay, you guys.
Ready?
&nbsp
Yeah, yeah.
Okay, Cisco.
&nbsp
Out with the old, in with the new.
Aw.
&nbsp
You'll never be old to us, Harry.
- Ready?
- Yeah.
&nbsp
Okay, let's do this.
Oh, one more thing.
&nbsp
While I'm gone, never, ever,
no matter what...
&nbsp
Oh, oh.
What... what was he gonna say?
&nbsp
And we're all like, "What was he gonna say?"
That's cool, though. I'm starving.
&nbsp
Do you guys have Big Belly Burger?
Some things never change.
&nbsp
Famished.
Did Barry say anything about
&nbsp
this embarrassing moment with Cecile?
- Mm-mm.
- Hey.
&nbsp
How did your first meeting go
with the new Wells?
&nbsp
Uh, good.
Yeah, I think he'll work out fine.
&nbsp
Oh, good. I look forward to meeting him.
- Whoa.
- What?
&nbsp
I'm just kidding.
I got to be honest, it's gonna take a bit
&nbsp
for me to get used to that.
Um...
&nbsp
I actually have something
to run by you guys that
&nbsp
- I think might help with that.
- Really?
&nbsp
- Yeah.
- What up?
&nbsp
Well, I've just been thinking
that maybe for all of us...
&nbsp
that I should probably, um...
get my own place.
&nbsp
- Really?
- Yeah.
&nbsp
What do you think?
- I say yes.
- I thought you'd never leave.
&nbsp
- Seriously?
- Dad.
&nbsp
- Wow.
- Look, Bar, come on.
&nbsp
I'm gonna miss you, but damn.
You grown. About time.
&nbsp
I can't tell if I'm leaving
or if I'm getting kicked out.
&nbsp
- You feel like you feel.
- Feel like I'm
&nbsp
- getting kicked out.
- I mean, yeah, I feel like
&nbsp
you're getting kicked out too.
Like, it's pretty obvious
&nbsp
you're getting kicked out.
Dad.
&nbsp
You're grown.
Oh, well. Cool.
&nbsp