My name is Barry Allen,
&nbsp
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world, I'm
an ordinary forensic scientist,
&nbsp
but secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
&nbsp
I fight crime and find
other meta-humans like me.
&nbsp
After defeating Zoom
and saving the multiverse,
&nbsp
I ran back in time and created
the alternate timeline, Flashpoint.
&nbsp
I restored the timeline to how it was,
only to find things weren't as I left them.
&nbsp
I brought new threats to our world,
and I'm the only one
fast enough to stop them.
&nbsp
I am The Flash.
Previously on “The Flash”...
&nbsp
We have to think
about getting back to our Earth.
&nbsp
We've been here long enough.
A whole multiverse
of Harrison Wells out there.
&nbsp
You want one? Let's go get one.
Wells with a sense of humor.
&nbsp
- Harrison.
- Call me H.R.
&nbsp
Out with the old, in with the new.
What are you doing here?
&nbsp
"“Julian Albert, meta-human CSI specialist”"
I don't trust you, and I don't
like things that I don't trust.
&nbsp
How have I worked
with this guy for the past year?
&nbsp
You say that all the time.
Do you maybe want to grab
some dinner tonight?
&nbsp
I got movie night with my kids
tonight. Rain check?
&nbsp
You were the only one who wasn't affected
when I messed with the timeline.
&nbsp
- Yo!
- You know you don't
&nbsp
need to do this every morning, right?
Oh, come on, it's the least I can do.
&nbsp
I mean, I love Joe, but at some point,
man needs his own space,
&nbsp
and until I find my own space,
that means your space.
&nbsp
So as a token of my appreciation,
two eggs over easy, bacon, toast...
&nbsp
I can't remember, do you
like it buttered or not?
&nbsp
Barry, sometimes a man just
wants to butter his own bread.
&nbsp
Okay, sorry. I was just...
Yeah, no, you're right, I...
&nbsp
Look, don't get it twisted, okay?
I love having you here.
You're a great guest.
&nbsp
I'm not sure how I feel
about our other visitor, though.
&nbsp
Wells?
“Please, call me H.R.”
&nbsp
So you don't like him?
Oh, it's not so much that I don't like him.
&nbsp
I just... the way he says things,
there's something about him.
&nbsp
I don't know what it is.
Dude, he's only been here
a few days; let him settle in.
&nbsp
I know we've had
our Wells issues in the past,
&nbsp
but you can't just stop trusting everybody
or giving them chances.
&nbsp
You know? You can't live like that.
This is true. Wise words from a wise man.
&nbsp
Joe Knowledge.
I'm gonna take this to go.
&nbsp
- Okay. All right.
- Uh, I'll see you there.
&nbsp
Yeah. Oh, I can take you.
No. No.
&nbsp
I'm gonna drive myself today.
Yeah, cool. Cool.
&nbsp
- Can I help you?
- I'm here to see Dr. Tannhauser.
&nbsp
Do you have an appointment?
No, but I'm pretty sure she'll see me.
&nbsp
You can just tell her Caitlin Snow is here.
Dr. Tannhauser's a very busy woman.
&nbsp
I'm sure you can understand.
I appreciate the diligence, Jackie,
&nbsp
but Caitlin's always welcome here,
even if I wish she'd call first.
&nbsp
Nice to see you too, Mom.
So what brings you here?
&nbsp
I didn't forget your birthday, did I?
I'm pretty sure I sent a card.
&nbsp
You did... in April.
Thank you.
&nbsp
Look, I read your new paper on applications
in cryo-medicine, and I think
you might be able to help.
&nbsp
I had no idea you kept up on the literature
over at S.T.A.R. Labs.
&nbsp
That's still what it's called, right?
Yes, and I have a patient
who could use your help.
&nbsp
Well, if you want to send over the file,
I'll be happy to take a look
when I have a chance,
&nbsp
but right now, I have a shareholder meeting
- to prepare for and...
- Mom!
&nbsp
I'm the patient.
Cancel my appointments,
&nbsp
and have Nigel meet me in the bio-lab.
We have work to do.
&nbsp
Synced and corrected by oykubuyuk
www.addic7ed.com
&nbsp
Sumptuous day.
Oh, no, on this Earth, I believe you say...
&nbsp
- Good morning.
And it is, isn't it? I mean...
&nbsp
The music on your Earth,
well, it strikes a chord,
&nbsp
no pun intended.
Please, help yourself.
&nbsp
I find a crew works best
when it's well-fed and well-rested.
&nbsp
Are those coffees for us too?
Yes indeed, Miss West.
&nbsp
I took the liberty of reading
through your ledgers last night.
&nbsp
A lot of information to absorb,
but let's see how I did.
&nbsp
Skim milk chai latte.
- Okay.
&nbsp
And an iced Americano with two... no,
- three shots of espresso.
- Boom.
&nbsp
That happened, Walter.
- Wally.
&nbsp
Now, for my fleet-of-foot friend...
oh, you'd best stick to decaf.
&nbsp
Probably for the best, yeah.
San Francisco.
&nbsp
I have “prepar-e”" a French roast
with a touch of creamer.
&nbsp
- Thank you so much.
- You're welcome.
&nbsp
Did you know, on my Earth,
coffee crop was wiped out by blight?
&nbsp
I mean, that's one more reason
to stay on this Earth,
&nbsp
for the coffee alone.
Yeah, though that's if you stay.
&nbsp
If I stay. Time is of the essence.
Here's what I propose, a series
of team-building exercises.
&nbsp
Now, I've hidden a series of clues
all around the facility.
&nbsp
What I propose is,
we break into two groups, all right,
&nbsp
and you can pick a partner; you're...
Okay, okay.
&nbsp
I have to stop you, H.R.
I am not feeling this.
&nbsp
It's the roast, isn't it?
I should have gone with a dark...
&nbsp
No, it's not the roast. The roast is fine.
Our trust isn't something
&nbsp
that you can just build with games.
- Okay?
- No.
&nbsp
This is something
that goes back three years.
&nbsp
It's something that's been forged in fire,
sometimes literally,
&nbsp
so maybe you should just step back
and observe, see what we do here,
&nbsp
how we operate. Did you get that?
Excellent note. I'm gonna run with that.
&nbsp
Where's Caitlin, by the way? Have you...
- Yes. So she was here.
- She was?
&nbsp
All right, yeah, you know,
we talked, and she...
&nbsp
What?
Knocked back a triple-shot latte,
&nbsp
and she left you a message, so I'm gonna...
Uh, I... yeah, let me just play it for you.
&nbsp
This is not the same as my Earth's.
This is a different...
&nbsp
There it is.
Hey, it's me.
&nbsp
I've got some things I need to take care of.
I shouldn't be gone more than a few days.
&nbsp
See if you can get along without me.
Make sure Cisco doesn't touch
my pizza pockets.
&nbsp
Wasn't labeled.
Okay, you know what, guys?
&nbsp
I got to go to work. I'm running late.
Ooh, yeah. I got to do that too.
&nbsp
- Yeah, let's go.
- I got to bail.
&nbsp
Oh. You know, we'll do
the team-building exercises another...
&nbsp
I'll leave the clues hidden in the facility.
Cool. How do you guys say
“see you later” over there?
&nbsp
Ah. “Until next communion.”
- All right, see you later.
- See you later.
&nbsp
So weird.
Come.
&nbsp
Hey, sorry I'm late.
I had to meet somebody and...
&nbsp
You can add tardiness to the list, Captain.
Allen, it's been brought to my attention
&nbsp
that you've been giving yourself
unauthorized access
&nbsp
to your colleagues' case files.
Excuse me?
&nbsp
Along with multiple infractions,
repeated absences,
&nbsp
disappearing throughout the day,
phone call interruptions, guests in the lab.
&nbsp
The list is pretty extensive, Captain.
I'm sorry, with all due respect,
&nbsp
I do my job here.
You do good work here, Allen.
&nbsp
Don't put that in jeopardy by thinking
the rules don't apply to you.
&nbsp
Understood?
Yes, sir.
&nbsp
Sorry, Captain, that's it?
Sir, I document eight different...
&nbsp
Nine.
Nine different violations of regulations,
&nbsp
and he gets a 15 second talking to?
Must be nice.
&nbsp
We are done here. You can go.
Captain.
&nbsp
Were you really just being a tattletale?
- That's bush league, man.
- You know what? You're right.
&nbsp
Silly me to think the rules actually apply
to the golden boy of CCPD's crime lab.
&nbsp
Detective.
- He's unbelievable.
- You know what?
&nbsp
I wish you two could be
a little less oil and water
&nbsp
and a little bit more oil and vinegar.
You guys have been at each other's throats
&nbsp
- for a year now.
- That's just it.
&nbsp
From my perspective, it's been two weeks.
So you're saying that before two weeks ago,
&nbsp
you weren't Julian's enemy?
I'm saying before two weeks ago,
&nbsp
Julian didn't even exist.
It's because of your Flashpoint.
&nbsp
I know it's because of the Flashpoint.
Cisco.
&nbsp
Hey, is this important?
I don't know; does 30 hits downtown
&nbsp
on the meta-human app count?
- What are we looking at?
- Well, nothing really.
&nbsp
Every traffic cam in a ten-block radius
suddenly went down, so we're flying blind,
&nbsp
and the hits are all over the map.
All right, well, there's one way to see
&nbsp
what's going on. I got to go.
Most of the chatter's coming
from the harbor district.
&nbsp
All right, I'm here. It's a bad scene, man.
You should be right on top of it, Barry.
&nbsp
What is it?
It's a... monster?
&nbsp
Guys, did you hear me?
There is a monster in Central City.
&nbsp
What are we talking?
Yao Ming size or Andre the Giant?
&nbsp
No, it's, like, an actual monster.
- What even makes that?
- I don't even know that.
&nbsp
S.T.A.R. Labs satellite, show me something.
Whoa.
&nbsp
You ever see anything like that on Earth-19?
You want me to observe. I'll just observe.
&nbsp
Iris, what are you doing here?
Working on a story,
&nbsp
and last time I checked, you don't need
super-speed and a red suit to help people.
&nbsp
All right, get out of here.
I'm gonna try to stop that thing.
&nbsp
Come on, come on, come on.
Cisco, where'd it go?
&nbsp
Can't track it if I can't see it.
Know what you could do? Could use your ears.
&nbsp
My ears?
What's that sound?
&nbsp
It's a car alarm; I can use the car alarms
to track the direction
the monster's heading in.
&nbsp
We got him. Head north three blocks.
I lost him.
&nbsp
Yeah, me too.
I don't get it. I don't get it.
&nbsp
Every meta-human we've encountered
has been exactly that, meta-human,
&nbsp
so where did this thing come from?
I don't know where it came from, man.
&nbsp
I just... it just vanished.
That's all I know. It was gone.
&nbsp
Yeah, but in my experience,
things are always different.
&nbsp
- What?
- Than they appear.
&nbsp
There must be a reason the darn thing
can just disappear like that.
&nbsp
Maybe the darn thing's got
some kind of cloaking mechanism.
&nbsp
That's a good idea,
but right now, I would settle
&nbsp
- for “how can we stop it?”
- Yes, obviously.
&nbsp
- Just how?
- I don't know.
&nbsp
We don't have a magic monster lasso.
But you know what we could...
&nbsp
Oh, sorry. I forgot.
I'm just... I'm just observing.
&nbsp
No, H.R., please.
We're open to any idea right now.
&nbsp
On my Earth, we have ropes
made out of carbon fiber.
&nbsp
They are ultralight but strong enough
to pull a battleship;
we could restrain it with that.
&nbsp
Right? What do you think?
- Okay, I think it's...
- Okay.
&nbsp
I think it's worth a shot; we can spin it
- down in my workshop.
- Yes. Good.
&nbsp
Yeah, there was something else
that was weird, though.
&nbsp
I... I saw a transformer explode
as this thing passed by it.
&nbsp
- That is weird.
- What's weird about that?
&nbsp
Monster didn't even lay a finger on it.
It exploded before it got to it.
&nbsp
Kind of reminds me of that Hitchcock movie
where the extra covers his ears
before the gun goes off.
&nbsp
You have Hitchcock on this Earth?
- Mm-hmm.
- Oh, brilliant.
&nbsp
“Murder on the Titanic”!
"“Who did it? Who cares?
We're drowning”"
&nbsp
The beast must emit
some kind of electrical pulse.
&nbsp
Is there a way I could get
a look at that transformer?
&nbsp
No. It's... the whole place
is a crime scene now
&nbsp
with Julian in charge of it.
Ah, Julian. Who's that?
&nbsp
That's the CSI guy you don't like, right?
I mean...
&nbsp
Yeah, all right.
He's great.
&nbsp
Sorry, cold hands.
I didn't even notice.
&nbsp
I'm Nigel, by the way.
Nice to meet you.
&nbsp
We're gonna help you
figure this out, Caitlin.
&nbsp
Let's get you to the lab.
What's this?
&nbsp
It's to test how your ability
affects molecular motion.
&nbsp
That shaft is solid tungsten,
and it's heated to
over 2,000 degrees centigrade.
&nbsp
I want you to cool it down,
and when we determine how you can do that,
&nbsp
we can figure out the best way to help you.
Best we could do in such little time.
&nbsp
So this is where you've been
for the last hour.
&nbsp
I had to reschedule my day
for this, Caitlin.
&nbsp
A lot of things around here
require my attention.
&nbsp
I remember.
Whenever you're ready.
&nbsp
Don't hold back.
Hey, Julian.
&nbsp
Hmm. You seen this?
It's bad enough we have
the metas destroying the city.
&nbsp
Now we have this thing to worry about.
- Mm-hmm.
- Is there any point
&nbsp
in me asking where you've been
for the last hour?
&nbsp
Or should I just assume the rules
still don't apply to you?
&nbsp
I was... I...
Yes, okay.
&nbsp
Look, hey, man, so I know that...
you and I, we got off on the wrong foot.
&nbsp
We never managed to find the right one,
and I'll take that.
&nbsp
That's probably my fault, but I just...
I don't want things to be
like that anymore, you know?
&nbsp
I... I'd... like it if things changed.
It's funny, 'cause I remember you saying
&nbsp
something similar to that
right before you stole
&nbsp
the case from underneath me.
Do you have idea what it's like
&nbsp
to work side by side with someone
with such little regard for the rules?
&nbsp
You may very well be contaminating my work.
That's exactly why I want to learn from you.
&nbsp
I don't follow.
I just... you know,
whenever I read your reports,
&nbsp
it's clear that your
evidence collection techniques
&nbsp
are far superior to mine.
Go on.
&nbsp
I don't know; I mean,
if I could just shadow you
&nbsp
for a day, maybe ask a few questions,
I think that you could
really help bring my skills
&nbsp
up to... snuff.
What do you say?
&nbsp
Sorry.
What if I gave up the lab?
&nbsp
There's a storeroom downstairs
that I could convert,
&nbsp
so if you let me follow you
on this case, lab's yours.
&nbsp
Lab's mine?
Okay. Deal.
&nbsp
You can't slow me down, though.
- I would never.
- All right. I'll call you.
&nbsp
How long have you had these abilities?
They started manifesting a few months ago,
&nbsp
but I'm assuming I got them
when the particle accelerator exploded,
&nbsp
just like all the other metas.
And you haven't told anyone?
&nbsp
Just you.
I told you, you never should have taken
&nbsp
that job at S.T.A.R. Labs.
You could have stayed here,
&nbsp
had access to world-class facilities.
And have all of my work be
&nbsp
in the shadow of your reputation.
Of course, the only time
you need your mother
&nbsp
is when you're in trouble.
What's that supposed to mean?
&nbsp
Oh, come on, darling.
You ran off to Central City
&nbsp
to play scientist with that disgraced quack.
I was trying to make a name for myself.
&nbsp
For three years, barely a word,
until trouble hits, and then here you come,
&nbsp
walking through the door and expecting Mommy
to drop everything in her life
to try to fix it.
&nbsp
You have no idea what I've been through...
Dr. Tannhauser, look at this.
&nbsp
She's absorbed all that energy?
How?
&nbsp
I'm not sure yet,
but if we can figure that out,
&nbsp
this could change
everything we're doing here.
&nbsp
So then The Flash... my Flash,
again, not your Flash...
&nbsp
we hatched a plan to gather
all the remaining meta-humans
&nbsp
into one place for a final showdown.
They called it “World War M.”
It was glorious.
&nbsp
Two forces on opposing sides of the stadium.
The tension built. No.
&nbsp
It was like that movie
where the gladiator was the lead gladiator.
&nbsp
What was that called?
“Gladiator.”
&nbsp
That's better; on my Earth,
it was called “Sweaty Men, ”
and that didn't take.
&nbsp
So the two forces charge
into battle, and when they do...
&nbsp
- I need to take a five.
- Yeah, let's get out of here.
&nbsp
- Let's take a break.
- By myself.
&nbsp
Yeah, you go ahead.
I'll keep working on this.
&nbsp
So entry AAA:2.
Plan is proceeding. Characters are in place.
&nbsp
Nobody seems the wiser as to why I'm here.
- Hey.
- I had to give
&nbsp
a witness report on the attack,
and I thought I would make it a lunch date.
&nbsp
Yeah, cool. Clear a spot.
- Let's do this. Ahh.
- Yeah.
&nbsp
Are things any better with Julian?
Oh, my God, it's like, every time
&nbsp
I try to get to know the guy,
he does something
&nbsp
that makes it really hard to.
All I know now is that
he dislikes meta-humans
&nbsp
about as much as he dislikes me.
Maybe you should try and
see things from his perspective.
&nbsp
He might have a reason
to dislike both of you
&nbsp
that you don't know anything about.
Did you just hit me with a Joe-ism?
&nbsp
Well, sometimes he's right.
Sometimes he's not.
&nbsp
Yeah.
Oh, speaking of which,
&nbsp
I just saw him downstairs,
and he was talking to the DA.
&nbsp
He blew off a date with her.
I saw him do the same thing last week.
&nbsp
I don't know. Maybe he's not into her.
No, he's into her.
&nbsp
I mean, when I asked him about her,
he basically told me to buzz off.
&nbsp
You're not too good at buzzing off, are you?
Nope. When it comes to my dad, no.
&nbsp
Well, look who it is.
Looks like I have an opportunity
to see things
&nbsp
from Julian's perspective....
- Hmm.
- Right now.
&nbsp
Sorry about lunch. I got to go.
Mm.
&nbsp
See you later. Oh, I need that.
If you don't stop squirming,
I'll never find a vein.
&nbsp
What exactly are you testing for now?
Any polymorphism
that could help us understand
&nbsp
how you're able to absorb that much energy
from molecules to create gelid surroundings.
&nbsp
You realize I've run
all of these tests already?
&nbsp
Then what was the point of coming here?
Seriously, Mom?
&nbsp
I'm terrified of what I'm becoming.
You realize you haven't
asked me once how I'm feeling?
&nbsp
I'm trying to keep emotion out of this.
Believe me, it's for your
benefit as much as it is mine.
&nbsp
Right, because that's
your specialty, isn't it?
&nbsp
Being cold, just like after...
After what?
&nbsp
After Dad died.
I did everything I could
to save your father.
&nbsp
Well, you lost your daughter
at the same time.
&nbsp
You're the one who went away, Caitlin.
Because I had to.
&nbsp
You realize you never acted
like my mother again
&nbsp
after Dad got sick?
You would barely even look at me.
&nbsp
I... couldn't handle the pain.
My work got me through it.
&nbsp
Losing someone like that,
you have no idea what that feels like.
&nbsp
Actually, I do.
My husband died over a year ago.
&nbsp
I'm sorry.
Okay.
&nbsp
What do you got?
I said get here quick, but that was...
&nbsp
quicker than I expected.
Oh, no, yeah, it was a...
&nbsp
crazy Uber driver.
Hmm.
&nbsp
Well, the blast pattern
and the scoring on the insulation suggests
&nbsp
that it was a power surge that blew it out.
So it's a coincidence?
&nbsp
I highly doubt it. But I'll figure it out.
Someone in this city has to do
something about these metas.
&nbsp
What do you mean?
We have a whole police force
&nbsp
working to stop these metas.
No, you have The Flash.
&nbsp
So it's not just bad metas you don't like.
It's all the metas.
&nbsp
I'm just saying that because of him,
the police department has got lethargic.
&nbsp
I mean, why do anything at all
if The Flash is gonna
save the day every time?
&nbsp
It's a bit like you with rule breaking...
a momentary fix,
and now you're lazy, sloppy.
&nbsp
Cool. Thanks.
I think The Flash is actually
&nbsp
a source of inspiration for the city.
I think he kind of provides hope.
&nbsp
Yes, well, that's one of many things
that we'll have to disagree on, Allen.
&nbsp
What? You see something?
A pattern.
&nbsp
The creature's movements,
they seemed random at first,
&nbsp
but they were contained
to a prescribed area.
&nbsp
You know, like the creature was
stuck in an invisible fence.
&nbsp
Traffic cameras were down, right?
Maybe it was being watched
or controlled by somebody
&nbsp
that needed to keep it
in visual range the entire time?
&nbsp
Constricting the creature's
movements to the line of sight.
&nbsp
That actually makes sense.
Maybe there is a brain in there
after all, Allen.
&nbsp
Dispatch, this is CSI.
I'm requesting immediate backup.
&nbsp
The monster has been sighted by the harbor.
- Hey, maybe we should split up.
- That's a terrible idea.
&nbsp
Yeah, but we got to do
something, right? Whoa.
&nbsp
Don't worry, I have four
years' training in the military.
&nbsp
Uh, even still, since when
does a CSI carry a gun?
&nbsp
Since there were monsters in our city.
All right, Jul...
&nbsp
Cheers.
You're leaving us?
&nbsp
Yeah.
Things between my mother and me are...
&nbsp
complicated.
We can help you.
&nbsp
I don't need your help with the science.
I can do that on my own.
&nbsp
I came here to get something from my mother
that I realize now I'll never get.
&nbsp
What are you doing?
Sorry, Frosty,
&nbsp
but you're not going anywhere.
Let me out of here.
&nbsp
Open these doors.
I said no!
&nbsp
I am sick of working day after day,
night after night, only to have
my work benefit your mother.
&nbsp
With the information I can get from you,
I can finally get out of this place,
&nbsp
so you're gonna stay here
until I get everything that I need.
&nbsp
You are not going to test me.
Yes, I am.
&nbsp
No, Nigel.
You are not going to test me, now or ever.
&nbsp
Wait, let go! Let go! Ah!
Caitlin! Don't do this!
&nbsp
This isn't you!
You don't know anything about me, Mother.
&nbsp
I... I know I wasn't much of a mother,
and I know I have a lot to make up for,
&nbsp
but I know I didn't raise a killer.
For whatever it's worth, I am so sorry.
&nbsp
It's worth a lot.
Now go.
&nbsp
- What about...
- I... I'll take care of him.
&nbsp
No one will ever know about this. I promise.
- Thank you.
- Just go.
&nbsp
Every time there's been
a sighting of the monster,
&nbsp
multiple transformers have blown.
Hmm, so it's definitely
feeding off electricity.
&nbsp
Mm-hmm, and see, I mapped out
all the streets
that it's been spotted around.
&nbsp
Never leaves a ten-block radius.
You know, this is exactly
what I was talking about.
&nbsp
Some meta's been gifted
this incredible power,
&nbsp
and this is the very best thing
they can do with it...
&nbsp
terrorize a city.
It's pathetic.
&nbsp
Why exactly do you hate metas so much?
If you think I'm gonna break down now
&nbsp
and tell you that one killed my parents
and that's why I have to do this job,
&nbsp
I'm not, okay?
I don't need a deep, personal
reason to hate metas, Allen.
&nbsp
I just need to see
person after person transformed,
&nbsp
given these extraordinary abilities,
and watch them be squandered.
&nbsp
Robbing banks, hurting people,
spreading fear.
&nbsp
It's just... well, it's not just a crime.
It's an absolute waste.
&nbsp
I mean, can you imagine
what it would be like to have those powers?
&nbsp
I mean, I would be helping people.
I would be improving the world.
&nbsp
I guess I wasn't one
of the chosen few, was I?
&nbsp
That's it?
You're mad at them
because you weren't chosen?
&nbsp
Sorry, I mean, I'm just saying,
it can't be easy being a meta-human,
&nbsp
having your life... their lives
change in ways that,
&nbsp
you know, neither one of us
could possibly imagine.
&nbsp
It's got to take some adjusting.
Right. So now you're defending them?
&nbsp
Well, no, I mean, I'm...
I don't think that...
&nbsp
This internship thing
we're doing is completely over.
&nbsp
Whatever.
- Transformers are the key.
- No, I agree...
&nbsp
Anytime the monster's shown up,
- any nearby have exploded.
- They blow up.
&nbsp
Car alarms keep malfunctioning too.
Car alarms, transformers.
What is the connection?
&nbsp
Yeah, we'll get there, fellas.
We'll get there.
&nbsp
We just got to keep trying.
Maybe someone's pulling power
out of the transformers
&nbsp
and using it to power the monster.
Power... yes, the monster.
&nbsp
That's... ah, you just beat me
to it, San Francisco.
&nbsp
See, that can't be it, H.R.
- Can't be it...
- 'Cause we would have detected
&nbsp
- a surge in the power grid.
- We did not.
&nbsp
Not if it was broadcast power
or something like a portable Tesla tower.
&nbsp
A portable Tesla power.
- Tower.
- Tower. That's what it is.
&nbsp
Nice. Mm, mm. Teamwork, hmm?
So PS, where I'm from, on my Earth,
&nbsp
we call that a problem solved.
I'm gonna go for coffee.
&nbsp
On my Earth, the coffee
was wiped out by blight.
&nbsp
- Blight, yeah.
- Can you imagine?
&nbsp
He didn't really do anything, did he?
Thank you.
&nbsp
Took me a while to realize it,
but he's just resaying everything
&nbsp
that we're saying in a different way.
No, he did have the idea for the rope.
&nbsp
Ah, ah, reverse inception.
He made you think he had
the idea for the rope,
&nbsp
but he didn't even tell us how to use it.
Okay, well, we're not gonna be
caught off guard again.
&nbsp
We should vibe him.
It'd be my pleasure.
&nbsp
Hey-oh.
- Hey, baby girl.
- Hey.
&nbsp
You've been hanging out here a lot lately.
Yeah, well, there's a lot of scared people
&nbsp
with this monster running around the city.
Oh, we'll get him. We always do.
&nbsp
Oh, yeah? Is that a quote
I can use for my article?
&nbsp
No.
All right. It was worth a try.
&nbsp
Dad, you know Wally and I
are all right, right?
&nbsp
What is that supposed to mean?
We just don't want you
to not do things because of us.
&nbsp
You know, we just want you
to... find someone.
&nbsp
I'm not having this conversation with you.
Dad, that DA is totally into you.
&nbsp
You should go out with her.
Iris, I don't need you to be Cupid.
&nbsp
I got my job.
I got you, Barry, Wally. I'm good.
&nbsp
I know, Dad, and that's great. I just...
Now that I'm falling in love with someone,
&nbsp
I just want you to have the same thing.
Joe? Alert every task force and sniper unit.
&nbsp
Tell 'em to load up.
I should get to S.T.A.R. Labs.
&nbsp
- What's up?
- Albert thinks
&nbsp
he's figured out the creature's next target.
Well, if there's ever an opportunity
&nbsp
for a 40-foot monster to wreak havoc,
it's gonna be where people like to gather.
&nbsp
2nd Street Promenade.
Well, let's end this.
&nbsp
That's what I intend to do, Detective.
- Where'd he go?
- Doesn't matter.
&nbsp
I don't need him.
What do you mean? What do you... hey, dude.
&nbsp
Come on, you can't just go
through his stuff; that's not...
&nbsp
I'm not going through his stuff.
See, this is what I'm talking about.
&nbsp
What even is this?
Now I seem to have won
most of the team's trust,
&nbsp
except Francisco's.
Those are my things.
&nbsp
What are you doing?
- What?
- Who are you really?
&nbsp
We know you're hiding something.
You've been burned, twice...
&nbsp
by a man with the same face as me.
I imagine it's hard to trust
after something like that.
&nbsp
- You think?
- I do think.
&nbsp
So play... the rest of it.
I've read his journals.
&nbsp
I found nothing that can tell me
why Francisco feels the way he does,
&nbsp
but I do hope I can change
his opinion of Harrison Wells
&nbsp
and the two of us can
rebuild that friendship.
&nbsp
What a fantastic C-story
to weave within the narrative.
&nbsp
What?
What narrative?
&nbsp
Narrative.
I'm writing a novel.
&nbsp
“The Tales of H.R. Wells.”
Catchy, I know.
&nbsp
Wait, I'm sorry, you're
a scientist and a novelist?
&nbsp
- Yes.
- Wow. That's perfect.
&nbsp
Thank you. That's exactly right.
I'm a scientist and a novelist;
I run S.T.A.R. Labs,
&nbsp
and also I'm an author of science-romance.
That's my niche. Write what you know.
&nbsp
And I thought,
“Well, what better opportunity
&nbsp
“than to come to another Earth and pen
yet another best seller
about my adventures here?”
&nbsp
Why didn't you just tell us
this in the first place?
&nbsp
I guess it didn't seem relevant,
and also, I didn't think
&nbsp
you guys were gonna
rifle through my belongings.
&nbsp
That's all it is.
I'm a scientist and a novelist.
&nbsp
Do you think you can trust me now,
or is that not something
&nbsp
that you have on this Earth, trust?
- Trust?
- Oh!
&nbsp
You scared the dickens out of...
Trust who?
&nbsp
It's the app.
It's the monster. It's back.
&nbsp
- Monster?
- Yeah, you've missed a lot.
&nbsp
I'll explain upstairs.
Well, I'll just stay here, then.
&nbsp
Come on. We need you.
All right, guys. I'm here.
&nbsp
Tell us everything that you see right now.
Mayhem.
&nbsp
And the monster.
Okay, so what's the plan?
&nbsp
Great question, Miss West.
So we fashioned just a carbon fiber rope,
&nbsp
but correct me if I'm wrong,
we never actually discussed
&nbsp
how he was gonna use that rope, did we?
Guys.
&nbsp
Barry, we're gonna do “Empire.”
“Empire of the Sun”" Barry.
&nbsp
- What? “Empire Strikes Back.”
- What?
&nbsp
“Empire Strikes Back”" Barry.
Just take it down like it was an AT-AT.
&nbsp
Just like an AT-AT.
"“Bigger they are, the harder they fall”"
&nbsp
Even I've seen “Empire.”
- I like that.
- I like you.
&nbsp
All right, here we go.
I always wanted to be a Jedi.
&nbsp
Guys? Rope went right through it.
It's a hologram.
&nbsp
That explains everything...
the ten-block radius, the transformers.
&nbsp
It takes that much power to render.
Wait, CCPD sent snipers there.
&nbsp
If it's not real...
Then the bullets will pass right through it.
&nbsp
Guys, it's gone. Where is it?
Hold on. Give me a sec, Bar.
&nbsp
Okay, we don't have a second!
H.R., triangulate the signal
being sent to the monster.
&nbsp
We have to disrupt it
before anyone gets hurt.
&nbsp
Okay, let's do that now.
Let's... let's just triangulate.
&nbsp
The computer doesn't triangulate...
- What?
- The signal the way...
&nbsp
not the way I'm used to... this is
a different size computer for...
&nbsp
Oh, my God. I knew it.
What?
&nbsp
You're a fake.
What?
&nbsp
- What?
This whole time, he's been
acting like he can help us,
&nbsp
but he can't because
he doesn't now how, does he?
&nbsp
How? Triangulate!
Guys, which way?
&nbsp
- Get the...
- All right, you take over.
&nbsp
Found it. It's at 2nd and Fulton.
I have a lock on the target.
&nbsp
Fire when ready.
Stop!
&nbsp
Stop firing! It's a hologram!
Hold your fire! Hold your fire!
&nbsp
A hologram? Where'd it go?
Detective West, where's Julian?
&nbsp
He was here!
Cisco, I need that location.
&nbsp
Hamilton building, 25th floor.
There's more power going there
&nbsp
than anywhere else in the building combined.
Line of sight to all the attacks.
&nbsp
That's where he is.
I said put your hands up!
&nbsp
This is CCPD! Freeze!
Stop what you're doing!
&nbsp
I said put your hands up!
You're just a kid.
&nbsp
Yeah, a kid you almost killed!
You're gonna pay for that one,
buddy. You're gonna...
&nbsp
Yeah, I don't think so, man;
I think you're the one
&nbsp
that's gonna be paying
for all the damage you did
&nbsp
to this city... for a very long time.
Hey, Flash.
&nbsp
Thank you.
You're welcome.
&nbsp
Do you realize how many innocent people
could have been hurt, or worse?
&nbsp
What made you do something like this?
I just wanted to feel powerful for a change.
&nbsp
And that did it? Scaring people?
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, it did.
&nbsp
You know, the kids at my school,
they tease me every day.
&nbsp
I'm a weirdo there.
And I'm just sick of feeling
scared all the time.
&nbsp
I just wanted someone else
to feel that way for a change.
&nbsp
Look, I know sometimes
things are hard at your age.
&nbsp
But trust me, it does get better.
So what happens now?
&nbsp
Well, there are severe
consequences for what you did,
&nbsp
and you're just gonna have to accept that,
but listen, you're young.
&nbsp
You can turn all of this around.
All right. Come on.
&nbsp
You were named Entrepreneur of the Decade
by “Tech Magazine”?
&nbsp
- That's right.
- Is any of what's on here true?
&nbsp
- All of it.
- How?
&nbsp
You can barely turn on a computer.
There are two parts to every idea.
&nbsp
There is the inception and the execution.
I provide the former.
&nbsp
So you come up with the ideas?
Yeah, I don't know how to implement them.
&nbsp
I'm the idea man.
So you didn't actually solve
the cryptogram that we sent you?
&nbsp
No, that was my partner
at S.T.A.R. Labs on my Earth.
&nbsp
I'm the face of the company.
I'm more of the inspiration
behind the company.
&nbsp
Then I was exposed.
Well, people thought that I was something
&nbsp
that I... I guess I wasn't.
Anyway, it... it kind of all
fell apart for me.
&nbsp
But then I got your message.
My partner brought me your message.
&nbsp
I realized he's bringing me an opportunity
to come to this Earth to write this book.
&nbsp
So many planets in the multiverse,
and we happen to pick
&nbsp
the one Wells who's not a scientist.
You're right.
&nbsp
I wasn't completely honest with you...
with all of you.
&nbsp
I feel badly about that. I regret that.
But let me ask you a question.
&nbsp
Has there been none amongst you
that has ever shaded the truth
&nbsp
for what you believe to be the greater good?
It sounds to me like you're a con man.
&nbsp
- Mm-hmm.
- Yeah.
&nbsp
Was I a con man
when I showed San Francisco here
&nbsp
how to track the beast using car alarms?
Was I a con man when I showed him
&nbsp
how to fashion a rope using carbon fiber?
I came up with those ideas!
&nbsp
You were prompted by my suggestions.
- Oh.
- That is how ideas work!
&nbsp
People, you need a muse!
I can be your muse.
&nbsp
What about stopping
all the metas on your Earth?
&nbsp
More of an advisory role
for me, but I was there.
&nbsp
I remembered how we... you don't
think that's something?
&nbsp
Let me present you with a scenario.
You're confronted with something,
&nbsp
a threat that you've never seen before.
You don't know how to stop it. Who does?
&nbsp
That's value to you.
Let me prove my worth to you.
&nbsp
If I fail, I will “pfft”
right back to my Earth,
&nbsp
but if I succeed, I will have succeeded
not just in redeeming myself but also...
&nbsp
will have done some good with my life.
You know, you're lucky we're pretty big
&nbsp
on redemption and doing good here,
so I think you can... I don't know...
&nbsp
stay for a few weeks, try to prove yourself,
but if not, “fyoo, ” back to your Earth.
&nbsp
- Thank you.
- Hey,
&nbsp
no more repackaging.
Word is bond.
&nbsp
That... just no more that.
- All right, H.R.
- Okay.
&nbsp
Where you been?
I actually went to visit my mother.
&nbsp
Your mother?
- Mm-hmm.
- Oh, boy.
&nbsp
Why?
To see if we could work
through some of our issues.
&nbsp
And I think we might actually be
on the road to recovery.
&nbsp
When it comes to family,
you got to do whatever it takes,
&nbsp
'cause one day, you might not
be able to do that anymore.
&nbsp
Glad you're back.
This is home.
&nbsp
I nearly killed a kid tonight.
The monster we were chasing,
&nbsp
it turns out it was just a hologram,
operated by a 15-year-old boy.
&nbsp
Flash came to save the day.
And he saved me from doing something...
&nbsp
I heard.
You know what's sad?
&nbsp
That kid, he's just acting
'cause he's scared, you know?
&nbsp
He wants everyone to be terrified
and to run away from the monster
so he can feel powerful.
&nbsp
I know what that's like.
How do you mean?
&nbsp
I come from a pretty wealthy family...
Back in England.
&nbsp
It's a long line
of generations of old money,
&nbsp
tradition... nonsense, really.
And I was the heir.
I was their firstborn son.
&nbsp
I was supposed to inherit the lot.
But I was the odd duck...
&nbsp
Who would rather go in the garden
and collect samples of insects....
&nbsp
Rather than learn how to tie
a Windsor knot
&nbsp
or which fork to use first at dinner.
Yeah. No, I wanted more.
&nbsp
You know?
I came here to do the one thing
&nbsp
that they couldn't stop me from doing.
Becoming a scientist...
becoming a great scientist.
&nbsp
And then just as I got
to the top of my field,
&nbsp
poof, the world changes overnight.
Meta-humans.
&nbsp
I don't know a single thing
about meta-humans.
&nbsp
I don't know how they talk.
I don't know how they walk.
&nbsp
I certainly don't know the first thing
about stopping them, so... rendered useless.
&nbsp
I suppose that's the monster
that I'm running from now,
&nbsp
just feeling powerless.
Yeah, I feel the same way some days, Julian.
&nbsp
I lost my mom when I was a kid.
Lost my dad recently.
&nbsp
It's a scary world. People die.
Trusts are betrayed. Things change.
&nbsp
But change can be a good thing, you know?
It can bring new experiences,
new opportunities, people.
&nbsp
You can treat 'em like a potential enemy
or like a new friend.
&nbsp
Just trust that everything's gonna be okay.
Yeah, maybe you're right.
&nbsp
You can stop.
You can stay.
&nbsp
I was really wrong about The Flash,
so I could be wrong about you too.
&nbsp
Good night, mate.
Julian?
&nbsp
You want to get a drink?
Yeah. Yeah, I'd like that.
&nbsp
All right. Let's do it.
Caitlin, I've been going
over the data we collected,
&nbsp
and I found some disconcerting results.
Your body's chemistry is changing in ways
&nbsp
that I don't fully understand,
but one thing is clear.
&nbsp
These powers you have,
the more you use them,
&nbsp
the more difficult
they're going to be to reverse.
&nbsp
I'm sorry, honey, but listen to me.
You must not use these powers
under any circumstances.
&nbsp
Synced and corrected by oykubuyuk
www.addic7ed.com
&nbsp