My name is Barry Allen,
&nbsp
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world, I'm
an ordinary forensic scientist,
&nbsp
but secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
&nbsp
I fight crime and find
other meta-humans like me.
&nbsp
After defeating Zoom
and saving the multiverse,
&nbsp
I ran back in time and created
the alternate timeline, Flashpoint.
&nbsp
I restored the timeline to how it was,
only to find things weren't as I left them.
&nbsp
I brought new threats to our world,
and I'm the only one
fast enough to stop them.
&nbsp
I am The Flash.
Previously on "The Flash"...
&nbsp
What is that?
Another epidermal husk,
&nbsp
a fully-intact human pelt.
Do we have any theories
as to what's causing them?
&nbsp
- I am Alchemy.
- Well, what do you want?
&nbsp
To help people achieve their true potential.
I know you want this more than anything,
&nbsp
but you have to face the fact
that it might not happen.
&nbsp
There's a whole multiverse
of Harrison Wells out there.
&nbsp
- Call me HR.
- You're a fake.
&nbsp
Let me prove my worth.
If I fail, I will right back to my Earth.
&nbsp
If I succeed, I will have
done some good with my life.
&nbsp
Caitlin, these powers you have,
the more you use them,
&nbsp
the more difficult
they're going to be to reverse.
&nbsp
I'm fast,
really fast.
&nbsp
I might even be the fastest man alive.
And when I'm running,
&nbsp
there's no greater feeling in the world.
I can move through the city
like a guardian angel,
&nbsp
protecting people who need me.
Whoa, you gotta slow down.
&nbsp
And watch where you're going, okay?
- Okay.
&nbsp
Cool skateboard, though.
Thanks.
&nbsp
They even have a name for me.
They call me "Kid Flash."
&nbsp
Kid Flash?
Yeah, the name needs some work, but, Dad,
&nbsp
I'm telling you, it all just felt so real
like it was actually happening.
&nbsp
And how often are you getting these dreams?
Uh, last couple nights.
&nbsp
Last couple?
Wally, this is exactly
&nbsp
what Frankie Kane said happened to her.
She had dreams, a lot of painful ones,
&nbsp
and then she started hearing
Alchemy's voice in her head
&nbsp
- until she became Magenta.
- Yeah.
&nbsp
This is totally different, Dad.
No. No, it's not.
&nbsp
Yes, it is.
I'm a speedster in my dreams.
&nbsp
I'm not an evil split personality.
I'm helping people, not hurting them.
&nbsp
Dad, this could mean that
my powers are finally manifesting.
&nbsp
No, I think this means
that you have a lot in common
&nbsp
right now with people who either
ended up in prison or dead.
&nbsp
Except for the fact that
I got hit by the dark matter
&nbsp
from the particle accelerator explosion,
just like Jesse.
&nbsp
I'm going to class.
Hey, Julian, do you want me to get started
&nbsp
on the DNA analysis for you?
Why would I need you to do that?
&nbsp
I don't know, I just
figured we worked so well
together last time.
&nbsp
What, that I'd want to do it again?
One shared case and one shared drink
&nbsp
does not make us mates, okay?
Miss Horton.
&nbsp
Mr. Allen.
- Mr. Albert.
- Morning.
&nbsp
New one?
Uh, yeah, number six.
&nbsp
Found it last night.
Well, this should
come as a welcome surprise.
&nbsp
You've been reassigned to meta-human
crime scene investigation full-time.
&nbsp
Full-time?
We're pouring all the resources we can
&nbsp
into figuring out this
husk problem, especially
&nbsp
considering the last one turned out to be
that evil speedster, The Rival.
&nbsp
Any questions, concerns,
you guys direct them
&nbsp
to Judge Hankerson, yeah?
All right. Thank you.
&nbsp
Joe.
- Cecile.
- Hi.
&nbsp
I didn't know you were gonna be over here.
Any excuse I have
to run into you, I take it.
&nbsp
You know, I'm really looking
forward to tomorrow night.
&nbsp
So am I.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
&nbsp
Okay, good, then I, uh,
- I'll see you then.
- All right.
&nbsp
Yo. Is that what I think it was?
You asked her to movie night with us?
&nbsp
That's awesome. When did you do that?
How'd you do it?
&nbsp
As much as I'd like to gossip with you
like a teenager right now,
&nbsp
there's something else
we need to talk about.
&nbsp
What?
Wally.
&nbsp
He's been having dreams.
Dreams?
&nbsp
Saving people,
becoming a speedster.
&nbsp
He called himself Kid Flash.
Kid Flash, he...
he said that name, specifically?
&nbsp
He's in trouble, isn't he?
If Wally's having dreams of being Kid Flash,
&nbsp
then he's in trouble,
yeah, but don't worry,
okay, we'll figure it out.
&nbsp
- I'll see you later.
- All right.
&nbsp
Synced and corrected by oykubuyuk
www.addic7ed.com
&nbsp
We have a problem.
Yeah, we do. He's still here.
&nbsp
Cisco, comedy of the obvious.
I made a pact to justify
my presence on your Earth
&nbsp
and I think I got something.
- We're all ears.
- Okay.
&nbsp
I read every news report
I can get my hands on.
&nbsp
And I have come to the conclusion
that this very operation
&nbsp
is a ticking time-bomb.
What do you mean?
&nbsp
You can't spend all your time working on...
working on whatever... whatever this is.
&nbsp
This... this is a very delicate
set of power-dampening cuffs.
&nbsp
We need them to stop the meta-humans.
My point exactly.
&nbsp
It's not gonna be long
before people start
putting the pieces together
&nbsp
and figure out what you're doing here.
You're working with The Flash.
&nbsp
Okay, so what's your idea?
The perfect disguise.
&nbsp
We reopen this laboratory
and I become the face of
the new S.T.A.R. Labs
&nbsp
Museum.
There's only one problem with that.
&nbsp
It's your face.
You're kind of a known murderer
&nbsp
around these parts.
You see, the evil Wells,
&nbsp
not to be confused with
the dick-ish but not evil Wells,
&nbsp
he confessed to killing Barry's mother.
So basically, if you step foot
&nbsp
outside this lab, you'll be arrested.
What... you're just telling me
this now, you two rascals?
&nbsp
What about the cryptogram?
What about the message?
&nbsp
Come to this Earth. Get a fresh start.
Well, what about your risumi
&nbsp
as a world-renowned genius scientist?
That's a good point. I guess we're even.
&nbsp
If a string is in a knot,
patience will untie it.
&nbsp
Patience can do lots of things.
Have you ever tried it?
&nbsp
My dear ma used to say that
to me all the time
&nbsp
any time I had a problem.
Now I have a problem.
&nbsp
I guess I'm gonna use that adage
to figure it out.
&nbsp
S.T.A.R. Labs Museum, think about it.
You think everyone on Earth-19
is missing crayons in the box,
&nbsp
or just him?
Paging Dr. Snow.
&nbsp
Wow, you are out of it. Sorry.
This have anything to do
with your recent visit with mom?
&nbsp
I just... I haven't been sleeping well,
but I'm okay.
&nbsp
Coffee?
Perfect.
&nbsp
So I did have powers?
I was Kid Flash?
&nbsp
In Flashpoint, yes.
I knew that this was happening.
&nbsp
Why didn't you tell me before?
Because...
&nbsp
Because why?
All right, fine, Wally, it, look...
&nbsp
in that timeline,
you were fighting The Rival.
&nbsp
Edward Clariss?
Edward Clariss, yeah.
&nbsp
You couldn't stop him.
There was no S.T.A.R. Labs.
&nbsp
There was no team to help you.
It was just you and Iris.
&nbsp
The two of you were a brother-sister
superhero crime-fighting team.
&nbsp
Why didn't you tell us this before?
You didn't want to know
about your Flashpoint lives.
&nbsp
But look, listen to me,
you got hurt, all right?
&nbsp
You got hurt bad.
So what?
&nbsp
That's that me, it's not this me.
And I want to be a speedster.
&nbsp
I... I want to be a flash.
No, no, no, you don't.
&nbsp
Yes, I do.
You're not hearing what he's saying.
&nbsp
He's telling us it's not safe.
Who cares what Barry's saying?
&nbsp
How do we even know he's telling the truth?
Wally, come on, this isn't because of
&nbsp
the particle accelerator,
it's because of Dr. Alchemy.
&nbsp
It's the same thing
that happened to Frankie Kane.
&nbsp
- You don't know that.
- Yes, we do.
&nbsp
And we need to try
to keep it from happening.
&nbsp
Why don't we just say
what this is really about?
&nbsp
You're okay with Barry having powers;
you're okay with Barry running into danger,
&nbsp
fighting all these metas.
He can screw up over and over again
&nbsp
You're okay with all of it
because he's Barry.
&nbsp
But you won't give me
the same amount of leeway
&nbsp
because at the end of the day,
you just don't trust me.
&nbsp
You know that's not true, Wally.
I don't need you fighting
my dad's battles for him.
&nbsp
Say it, Joe.
You don't trust me, do you?
&nbsp
Wally...
That's what I thought.
&nbsp
Hey, hey...
No. No, you're not listening to me.
&nbsp
I said the shares are undervalued
so if the stock drops,
you should buy more, not less.
&nbsp
No, that... that's not how it works.
Look, just look at its balance sheet.
&nbsp
If you sell now, you're going
to lose a lot of money.
&nbsp
I understand that.
Of course it's your money.
&nbsp
Just hold onto it then.
You know what? If you're not gonna listen...
&nbsp
Petechiae around the eye,
the crushed larynx.
&nbsp
This poor chap has got
fingerprints all round his neck.
&nbsp
He's clearly been strangled.
I heard multiple witnesses
&nbsp
said the man was attacked by a shadow.
Huh.
&nbsp
So a meta from Neverland's made the trip
to Central City Fabulous.
&nbsp
So far there's no forensic evidence
that there was an assailant.
&nbsp
No laceration marks. No fingernail marks.
No DNA evidence underneath
the fingernails even?
&nbsp
Nothing yet, we'll have to wait and see.
There's always something.
&nbsp
Bag the body up and
I'll meet you back at the lab.
&nbsp
- Yeah.
- See ya.
&nbsp
Oh, and Julian, um,
I'm going to that movie in the park thing
&nbsp
with Joe and his... or my...
Iris and some other friends.
&nbsp
Uh, if you felt like going,
it starts at 8:00.
&nbsp
We're all a bunch of nerds, so
you'll fit right in.
&nbsp
Well, that's a very enticing offer, Allen,
but I'm actually seeing
my girlfriend tonight, so.
&nbsp
Oh, you have a girlfriend?
I didn't know that.
&nbsp
I'm sure there's lots
about me that you don't know.
&nbsp
- Cheerio.
- Yeah.
&nbsp
- Albert.
- Detective.
&nbsp
- Hey.
- Anything?
&nbsp
With the... uh, nothing yet, at least.
Have you seen Wally this morning?
&nbsp
No. Why?
He left the house in a huff.
&nbsp
He won't answer my calls.
Iris is out there looking for him right now.
&nbsp
Did you want me to run around the city?
Maybe if I can't get ahold of him.
&nbsp
What Wally said, it's partially true.
I didn't answer his question because
&nbsp
I... I don't trust him with these powers
the same way I trust you with them.
&nbsp
You got to talk to him about that.
You know, tell him why, especially now.
&nbsp
I will, I mean, just gotta find him first.
Look, I'll just keep calling him.
&nbsp
He's got to answer at some point, right?
Man, I feel bad, too.
&nbsp
It's your first date with Cecile
and you got to worry about this.
&nbsp
Don't worry about that.
That's one part of my life I can control.
&nbsp
Yes?
Have you seen HR?
&nbsp
Maybe he's meditating in his room.
No, he's not there.
&nbsp
HR, you're needed in the Speed Lab, now.
He could be doing inversion
stretches in the intake.
&nbsp
You saw that too, huh?
HR! He's not there.
&nbsp
Probably just brewing another pot of coffee.
- It's all he drinks.
- Not that either.
&nbsp
Okay. Why do you need him so badly?
He's going through my stuff, but now...
&nbsp
He's just being stupid about it.
Stupid about what?
&nbsp
God, I swear I fixed the security system.
Who the hell are you?
&nbsp
HR.
Apologies.
&nbsp
HR.
See? Ah. What you've just been witness to
&nbsp
was my partner's likeness, Randolf Morgan.
Okay, I see what's going on here.
&nbsp
You don't have facial transmogrification
on this planet, do you?
&nbsp
No, we certainly do not.
Well then,
&nbsp
it's a good thing for me
I found this little contraption
&nbsp
in my satchel... forgot I brought it.
It's so fun.
&nbsp
So fun? How does this work?
Light refraction technology.
&nbsp
Light refraction?
I think... I don't... Randolf,
&nbsp
my... business partner,
he's sort of more with the science.
&nbsp
But this little sucker
is gonna go a long way
&nbsp
to solving my Harrison Wells facial issues.
I'm gonna hang onto this
until I get my power cuffs back.
&nbsp
What, your power cuffs?
Your meta-human power-dampening cuffs?
&nbsp
Those very ones, the ones that are
missing all of a sudden.
&nbsp
What... you think... you think I took them?
I didn't take them.
What do I need cuffs for?
&nbsp
I just got to this Earth. I came alone.
I haven't met anyone yet;
it's gonna take a while,
&nbsp
even when I do meet them,
to get to the cuff stage.
&nbsp
Hey, guys?
Guys, I need you in the Cortex.
&nbsp
Killed by a shadow? That's a new one.
Maybe that's what killed Edward Clariss.
&nbsp
Clariss was a meta-human.
This victim doesn't appear to be.
&nbsp
Do we know if this shadow meta is from the
particle accelerator explosion
or from Dr. Alchemy?
&nbsp
Not yet, no.
We actually haven't found any
&nbsp
evidence to process.
If only we had a way, Francisco,
&nbsp
to see what happened.
Where was the crime scene located?
&nbsp
In Chubbuck, uh, Palmer and Racine,
around 11:00 last night.
&nbsp
- Whoa.
That's gonna give me night terrors.
&nbsp
- Shade.
- What?
&nbsp
We had a meta-hominid on my planet
who could do virtually the same thing,
&nbsp
called himself "Shade."
What did he do, throw
his side-eye at his enemies?
&nbsp
No, I know, it's a terrible nickname, right?
But what Shade could do was
vibrate at such a high frequency
&nbsp
he created the illusion
that he was a shadow.
&nbsp
That's how I phase.
Do you think he's doing the same thing?
&nbsp
He has to be.
Heat signature's fluctuating.
&nbsp
Red shift is ridiculous.
Okay, so he is.
&nbsp
He must be slowing down his
molecules whenever he attacks.
&nbsp
So we just have to figure out
a way to keep them slowed down,
&nbsp
and that should be enough to grab him.
All right, can you get started?
&nbsp
Okay, but, like, right this minute?
Yeah, I'm sor... we just...
&nbsp
we gotta stop this guy fast
so we can focus on Alchemy.
&nbsp
Wally has been having
dreams about being a speedster,
&nbsp
Alchemy dreams.
He was a speedster in Flashpoint?
&nbsp
Anyone else gonna have powers
we should know about?
&nbsp
No.
All right. I'm gonna work on Shade.
&nbsp
- I'll supervise.
- You're gonna find my cuffs.
&nbsp
I'll have to find some cuffs.
All right, I got to get back to work
&nbsp
before Julian loses his mind.
Wally, it's your dad, again.
&nbsp
Just give me a call back, all right?
Or a text, I just need to know you're okay.
&nbsp
I'm okay.
Wally.
&nbsp
You can't do that.
You can't just disappear.
&nbsp
I just wanted to let you know
I'm fine, so.
&nbsp
Come here.
Listen, you were right.
&nbsp
I do treat Barry differently
than I treat you.
&nbsp
But not because I think
Barry's better than you.
&nbsp
Then why?
Wally, you're a lot like I was as a kid.
&nbsp
You're fearless and you take risks
and that makes you
a handful just like I was.
&nbsp
And now you're getting powers.
That alone would make me nervous
&nbsp
because I know what I
would have done if I got powers.
&nbsp
But you're not getting your speed
the same way Barry got his.
&nbsp
You're getting your speed the way
Magenta and The Rival got theirs.
&nbsp
So it's not that I don't
trust you, Wally, it's just
&nbsp
I don't trust what's
going on with you right now.
&nbsp
And that scares the living hell out of me.
I know, Dad.
&nbsp
I get it.
Okay, so
&nbsp
let's get you to S.T.A.R. Labs
- and see what we can do.
- All right.
&nbsp
Wallace.
Wallace West.
&nbsp
Ah!
Wally.
&nbsp
Wally!
Hey, Cisco.
&nbsp
Yes?
I took your cuffs.
&nbsp
Why?
Because I need them.
&nbsp
Is... is this some sort of, um,
bold fashion choice 'cause
you're not a meta-hu... hu...
&nbsp
human.
Surprise.
&nbsp
It started a few months ago.
That's why you went to see your mom,
&nbsp
to see if she could help you.
But she can't.
&nbsp
I've run every test.
There's nothing that anyone can do.
&nbsp
I need a favor.
I need you to vibe me in the future
&nbsp
because I need to know if I become...
her.
&nbsp
You're not gonna become her.
Okay, just because you have these powers
&nbsp
doesn't mean you're gonna
turn into Killer Frost.
&nbsp
I think it might.
Please?
&nbsp
I just need to know for sure.
I need to know if I become evil
&nbsp
because if I do, I have to leave
and never come back.
&nbsp
And?
I didn't see anything.
&nbsp
You're fine.
Oh, thank you. Thank you.
&nbsp
Please, um,
don't tell anyone about this yet, okay?
&nbsp
- Of course.
- Okay.
&nbsp
According to this,
all your vitals are fine, Wally.
&nbsp
Wally, what did you see?
I was Kid Flash again, but
&nbsp
this time it wasn't a good dream.
I was fighting The Rival
at some abandoned sawmill.
&nbsp
That's what happened in Flashpoint
before you got hurt.
&nbsp
They're not just dreams,
they must be memories of that life.
&nbsp
More and more people are getting powers.
Okay, so how do we stop this?
&nbsp
I mean, is there any stopping it even?
If Alchemy could reach you at CCPD,
&nbsp
he could probably reach you
from anywhere, right?
&nbsp
I have a suggestion.
Why don't we throw Wallace in the pipeline
&nbsp
until we figure this situation out.
You want to lock him up?
&nbsp
Yeah, I agree with Joe, we lock him up
because think about this.
&nbsp
We can't stop Alchemy from
getting into Wallace's head,
&nbsp
but we put him in the pipeline,
then we control the situation
&nbsp
from there on out.
As much as I don't like it, Dad,
&nbsp
maybe he's not wrong.
But only till we figure out
&nbsp
a better way to make you safe.
Yeah, I agree with Joe.
&nbsp
I'm gonna cancel this movie with Cecile.
Whoa-whoa-whoa-whoa, wait, wait,
&nbsp
you've got a date with Cecile?
Yeah, I was gonna bring her
&nbsp
to movie in the park tonight.
Well, don't not go.
&nbsp
You've put your life on hold
for us long enough.
&nbsp
Yeah, Dad, he's right, I mean,
go be Joe West; you're always Dad.
&nbsp
Yeah, we'll stay with Wally,
and make sure nothing happens.
&nbsp
I told her all of you were coming with me.
Am I gonna be the only one that shows up?
&nbsp
Uh, I would love to see a movie.
- What movie is this?
- "The Shining."
&nbsp
"The Shining," oh, I love that movie.
That movie freaks you out.
&nbsp
You have never made it past
the part with the Grady twins.
&nbsp
That's... that's... that was...
I was younger.
&nbsp
Why don't I go with you?
You sure you don't want stay...
&nbsp
No, I want to be with you.
Either way, the more the merrier.
&nbsp
Let's do it.
Hell, this will be
great fodder for my novel.
&nbsp
Hold on, you guys didn't tell him about?
Joe, no.
&nbsp
They... they told me,
finally, the little scamps.
&nbsp
But I think that I've worked my way
around that little problem.
&nbsp
Watch this.
Whoa.
&nbsp
Oh, um, let me just...
- What... ah...
- What did you do?
&nbsp
Did you just neuralyze us?
No, I gave you a simple retinal adjustment
&nbsp
so all of you can see me, HR,
while the rest of the world sees...
&nbsp
Randolf Morgan.
Joe, I promise,
I'll be so... I'll be so quiet.
&nbsp
You won't even know I'm there.
Silent observer.
&nbsp
All right.
Wally, keep me posted.
&nbsp
Yeah, I'll be fine.
Just go have fun.
&nbsp
That's great.
All right, we want to be 2/3 to the back,
&nbsp
- right in the middle.
- That's a very small screen.
&nbsp
Like, I don't know if we're
gonna be able to see from...
&nbsp
No, HR, the screen is perfect, okay?
- We'll be able to see fine.
- But we're so far...
&nbsp
That's where the engineer sits when
- he mixes the sound, all right?
- All right.
&nbsp
When you want to get the
Kubrick experience, that's...
&nbsp
- All right, yeah.
- The sweet spot, right there.
&nbsp
I don't know, maybe we get a
little closer, like right by...
&nbsp
Why don't you let us worry about the seats?
You take care of the snacks and the drinks.
&nbsp
Great idea.
Any time.
&nbsp
Oh, I don't...
I'm pretty sure they're
&nbsp
not gonna take the money from my Earth.
- I don't think.
- What?
&nbsp
- What is this?
- That's a helbing.
&nbsp
Here's what you're gonna do.
You're gonna get us what we need,
&nbsp
you're gonna do that, go over
to that stand over there.
&nbsp
- Great idea.
- You're gonna get us some
&nbsp
- licorice sticks, some Jujubes.
- Licorice... Juju...
&nbsp
Yeah, and coffee.
Do you want anything?
&nbsp
- No thanks.
- Okay.
&nbsp
Okay.
You okay, Cisco?
&nbsp
Yeah. Yeah, you know,
just trying to deal with HR.
&nbsp
Yeah, 'cause you've been on edge
ever since you vibed me.
&nbsp
Are you gonna tell me what you saw?
Yeah, I told you what I saw.
&nbsp
No, but, for real.
I can tell when you're
not being honest with me.
&nbsp
Am I her?
Yeah.
&nbsp
Yeah, you're her.
I... I saw the both of us
&nbsp
fighting.
Like, full-on Vibe versus Killer Frost.
&nbsp
It's like we're meta-frenemies.
Well, have you ever vibed
anything from the future
&nbsp
that didn't come true?
Just Earth-2 being ripped to shreds.
&nbsp
But that doesn't mean
that can't happen again.
&nbsp
Caitlin,
you have to tell them.
&nbsp
You have to tell the team.
We have to figure out what's going on.
&nbsp
No. It's too late.
There's nothing you can do.
&nbsp
Nobody else needs to know.
I haven't been to a movie in forever.
&nbsp
I come whenever I can, I mean,
sort of a summer tradition with the kids.
&nbsp
Yeah?
You know, it's funny,
you don't really peg me
&nbsp
for a, uh, horror movie type.
I thought maybe you'd be
more of a chick-flicky.
&nbsp
- Oh, you got jokes.
- Yeah.
&nbsp
I might be mad if you weren't so gorgeous.
Gorgeous, really?
&nbsp
If I'm so gorgeous, then how come you're
spending more time looking
at that than you are at me?
&nbsp
You know what?
You're right, Cecile, I'm sorry.
&nbsp
My son, Wally,
he's...
&nbsp
going through some changes and I'm just...
- Hey.
- Just really concerned.
&nbsp
Joe, we can do this another time.
No-no-no-no, I really
want to be here with you, I do.
&nbsp
It's just that when
one of my kids is hurting I'm...
&nbsp
Can't think about anything else at all.
Completely understand.
&nbsp
- You have kids?
- Yeah.
&nbsp
- Daughter.
- Oh.
&nbsp
Just turned 18.
I have less than a year before
she leaves me for college.
&nbsp
Oh, man, you should have brought her.
I drag you away from her
so you can watch a horror movie.
&nbsp
Not many men could.
I'm just glad you finally
figured out what you want.
&nbsp
Me too.
Wally, you okay?
&nbsp
- I hate that we have to do this.
- Mm.
&nbsp
He so badly wanted powers,
and, now, to keep him locked up
&nbsp
so he doesn't get them, it's...
It's hard, I know.
&nbsp
I don't know if you actually do.
What does that mean?
&nbsp
All Wally wants to do is to help people.
And to see you do that every day
while all he can do
&nbsp
is stand by and watch,
it's hard being a bystander sometimes.
&nbsp
You don't feel that way too, do you?
Barry...
&nbsp
Come on.
My contributions here are limited.
&nbsp
I don't know science.
I don't have powers.
&nbsp
I don't know how to help you.
I couldn't do this without you.
&nbsp
That's not true.
That is true.
&nbsp
Whether you realize it or not,
there is no Flash
&nbsp
without Iris West.
I'm wolfing this.
&nbsp
- I'm telling you, it's so good.
- It is good.
&nbsp
What is it about popcorn and the movies?
Hey, you okay?
&nbsp
- Hey.
- Yeah, fine.
&nbsp
- Hi, I'm Caitlin.
- Hi.
&nbsp
Cecile. Nice to meet you.
And you must be Cisco. That's me.
&nbsp
Nice to meet you. Hi.
Don't forget about me.
&nbsp
Hello.
I'm HR.
&nbsp
HR Randolf.
It's amazing to meet you.
&nbsp
- All right, now.
- Amazing.
&nbsp
And so then... then she says to me,
"Oh, so you are hot chocolate
from another land."
&nbsp
I said, "Okay, easy, now."
Then she, "Wait a minute.
&nbsp
Do you speak a foreign language?"
What did you say?
&nbsp
Well, I said, "Sure."
"As long as I know the words."
&nbsp
I'm gonna smack somebody.
Everybody, move, move!
&nbsp
It's Shade.
He's at Hofherr Park.
&nbsp
Wallace.
Wallace West.
&nbsp
The time has come
to restore what was taken from you.
&nbsp
The time has come
to set you free.
&nbsp
Hey, hey, the same thing
happened to Frankie.
&nbsp
You have to fight through the pain.
Are you okay?
&nbsp
I think so.
Find me.
&nbsp
And I will release you from all of this.
Wally, what is it?
&nbsp
You have to open the door.
I... I can't do that, Wally. I can't.
&nbsp
I can make you whole again.
Open the door! I need to get out!
&nbsp
Now!
Flash, just who I came to see.
&nbsp
So you like shadows?
Want to try and catch mine?
&nbsp
Barry, we're in the van. Can you hear us?
And I just got tossed
on my ass like a rag doll.
&nbsp
That's not good.
All right, guys,
&nbsp
I cannot do anything if I can't see him.
Can we light this place up?
&nbsp
Light's gonna slow down
his molecular vibration
&nbsp
so we can catch him.
How are we gonna light this place up?
&nbsp
- See all these cars?
- Yeah.
&nbsp
- I hack into their computers.
- Yeah?
&nbsp
- The park's overhead lights.
- Yeah?
&nbsp
Blast this guy with more lumens
- than a Pink Floyd concert.
- Yeah.
&nbsp
What are you doing?
He's gonna need these.
&nbsp
- She took...
- She took the cuffs.
&nbsp
Okay, just drop it, all right?
Barry, I'm in.
&nbsp
Okay.
All right, wait until my mark.
&nbsp
And by mark,
I do mean
&nbsp
next time that I get punched.
Mark.
&nbsp
Flash!
Don't like the light, do you?
&nbsp
Nowhere to hide now.
Get me out. Get me out... ah!
&nbsp
Help me!
Please, make it stop.
&nbsp
Ah, Iris!
Hey, Wally, Wally, Wally, look.
&nbsp
It's over, okay? Come on, come on...
Find me.
&nbsp
Stay out of my way.
Wally, stop.
&nbsp
Stay out of my way!
Wally wasn't himself.
&nbsp
He was possessed.
Alchemy was calling for him.
&nbsp
I knew I shouldn't have left.
It's okay, Joe, nothing happened.
&nbsp
He's not okay, Barry.
This thing's coming after him, and...
&nbsp
and there ain't a damn thing we can do?
Well, we stopped Shade.
&nbsp
And now we can focus on Alchemy, all right?
Unless he sends another meta
to Central City to attack.
&nbsp
Then we're in trouble.
You think Shade was a distraction?
&nbsp
I agree with Iris;
I think the attack on Wally
&nbsp
and the attack by Shade happened
at essentially the same time.
&nbsp
So that's not a coincidence.
If that's true, that means
Alchemy's gonna sending
&nbsp
another one of his metas soon.
We don't know that.
&nbsp
Barry, we found six husks.
So besides Shade, Magenta, and Clariss,
&nbsp
there's still three unaccounted for.
Okay, well, if more come,
then we'll stop them.
&nbsp
But Alchemy can't get Wally
if he stays in the cell.
&nbsp
Barry, we can't just let
Wally suffer in there.
&nbsp
And besides, burying our head in the sand
is not gonna make Alchemy go away.
&nbsp
Ignoring the problem does not get rid of it.
You're gonna have to face it.
&nbsp
Don't we?
- What?
- Nothing.
&nbsp
Come on, Caitlin.
Not right now, Cisco.
&nbsp
I... just... I can't just keep this in.
You have to tell them.
&nbsp
Tell them what?
I have powers.
&nbsp
What?
What kind of powers?
&nbsp
The cold kind.
Happy now?
&nbsp
So, what, we're just gonna
keep secrets from each other?
&nbsp
Yeah, well, this wasn't your secret to tell,
was it, Cisco?
&nbsp
I did that because I care about you.
If you cared about me, then you would have
&nbsp
let me tell them all when I was ready.
Because this is happening to me, not you.
&nbsp
I'm the one turning evil.
I'm the one who's gonna have to leave soon.
&nbsp
I vibed the two of us fighting
each other in the future.
&nbsp
She was Killer Frost.
- I'll go talk to her.
- I got it.
&nbsp
How long have you known?
A few months.
&nbsp
First I didn't want to accept
what was happening to me.
&nbsp
And then I had to.
So then I tried to suppress my powers.
&nbsp
There's no suppressing these powers.
I just can't believe that this is my life.
&nbsp
It shouldn't be.
None of what's happening
to any of you should be.
&nbsp
What do you mean, any of us?
I mean...
&nbsp
Dr. Alchemy.
Wally.
&nbsp
You getting powers.
Even Dante being dead in this timeline.
&nbsp
It's all because I created Flashpoint.
Even Iris, who, I don't know, I think
&nbsp
she's disappointed that
she doesn't have powers
&nbsp
and everyone else does.
And no matter what I do now,
&nbsp
everything's different.
So none of this happened before?
&nbsp
I'm sorry, Caitlin.
Wally's up.
&nbsp
Okay.
How you feeling?
&nbsp
I've been better.
What do we do?
&nbsp
We got to come up with something.
Use me.
&nbsp
No. No, no, hell no.
Alchemy's calling for me to go to him.
&nbsp
Follow me wherever he is,
and we can stop him.
&nbsp
No. We're not asking you to do that.
This is our chance to stop him
&nbsp
We have to do it.
Wally...
&nbsp
Dad, he... he wants me.
He's hurting me.
&nbsp
So let me fight back.
Wally?
&nbsp
Find me.
Turn him on his side.
&nbsp
All right, get him over, come on.
This should help.
&nbsp
It's a mild sedative.
- What is that?
- Lorazepam.
&nbsp
It works on seizures.
Hopefully it'll work on whatever this is.
&nbsp
These episodes keep happening
more frequently.
&nbsp
Yeah, and this is just a temporary fix.
If we don't stop it too, he could suffer
&nbsp
from permanent brain damage.
We don't have a choice.
&nbsp
We have to do what Wally wanted; we have to
use him to find Alchemy.
&nbsp
No, we're no... it's too dangerous.
So is doing nothing.
&nbsp
Need I remind everyone that Dr. Alchemy
has a rock that shoots lasers, so who knows
&nbsp
what he has up his sleeve?
Cisco's right.
&nbsp
What if we're walking into a trap?
You guys aren't walking into anything.
&nbsp
You guys are gonna stay here.
If we're gonna do this,
we're gonna do it right.
&nbsp
What does that mean?
It means that if I'm
gonna put Wally at risk,
&nbsp
I'm gonna use everything
in my power to protect him.
&nbsp
Double-check your packs.
Make sure we have everything.
&nbsp
- Good to go.
- Okay.
&nbsp
So what's the plan, Detective?
This lunatic, calls himself Alchemy,
&nbsp
he's the one responsible for all these husks
we've been finding all over town.
&nbsp
But we believe we found a way
to get his location.
&nbsp
How?
By using his next target.
&nbsp
Your son?
We'll stop him, Joe.
&nbsp
Where's Julian?
He didn't come in today.
&nbsp
What, he never misses a day. You call him?
Yeah, it went straight to voicemail.
&nbsp
Well.
All right, gents, move out.
&nbsp
Let's roll.
All right, be safe.
&nbsp
We'll see you in a few.
You ready?
&nbsp
Yeah.
Hey, you remember when
I said that you remind me
&nbsp
of myself as a kid?
I was never this brave.
&nbsp
They've just left.
I'm almost done. I'll be right there.
&nbsp
Cisco, I am so sorry about how I reacted.
I understand why you told everyone.
&nbsp
Never helps when we
keep things from each other.
&nbsp
You're right.
And I'm glad that you told everyone.
&nbsp
I'm just not very good at asking for help.
I get that from my mom.
&nbsp
You're better than your mother.
I don't know.
&nbsp
I'm just so terrified because she said
if I keep using my powers, then
&nbsp
it'll be impossible to stop them.
Your mother might be
one of the most accomplished
&nbsp
scientists on this planet,
but when it comes to the impossible,
&nbsp
we're the experts.
We're gonna help you, Caitlin.
&nbsp
- Okay?
- Okay.
&nbsp
Let's go help Wally.
You got it.
&nbsp
We're moving in.
Just remember, once you get in there,
&nbsp
we're not gonna have eyes
Copy that.
&nbsp
Of course, dude uses an
abandoned subway to set up shop.
&nbsp
Of course he does.
Where's Grodd when you need him?
&nbsp
Gro... Gorilla Grodd?
You have sentient gorillas
on your Earth too?
&nbsp
Oh,
oh, yeah, yeah, we do, many.
&nbsp
Many. Yeah.
Come to me.
&nbsp
Wallace.
Everybody set?
&nbsp
We're good.
Just lead the way.
&nbsp
You okay?
Yeah.
&nbsp
It's okay to be scared, Wally.
I am.
&nbsp
You are?
Keeps me alert.
&nbsp
Then I'm on high alert.
Let's do this.
&nbsp
Hello, Wally.
Are you him?
&nbsp
Are you the voice I've been
hearing inside my head?
&nbsp
I am Alchemy.
I've been having visions
&nbsp
of another life.
Where... where I have speed, where, I'm...
&nbsp
The Flash.
I can give you that back,
&nbsp
should you desire it.
I just want the pain to stop.
&nbsp
It will, child.
Whatever you desire,
&nbsp
I will see it so.
Now tell me,
&nbsp
do you wish for the life
that was taken from you
&nbsp
to return?
What I wish for...
&nbsp
is all of you gone.
It's a trap!
&nbsp
No!
The boy has been chosen, Flash.
&nbsp
And you will not stand
before what must be...
&nbsp
Ever again!
No!
&nbsp
Get on your knees!
Now! Don't move!
&nbsp
Don't move! Get down!
On the ground.
&nbsp
I said get on the ground.
That was a grave mistake.
&nbsp
- You okay?
- I'll be fine.
&nbsp
Wally?
Yeah.
&nbsp
It's over, Alchemy.
Over?
&nbsp
You have no idea
what's about to begin.
&nbsp
What the hell?
Did you guys see that?
&nbsp
See what?
Go. Get the hell out of here!
&nbsp
Wally, move towards the door!
Stick with me!
&nbsp
The other way! The other way!
Go! Go! Go! Go!
&nbsp
Wally, go!
You all right?
&nbsp
Wallace.
Wallace West.
&nbsp
Take your power.
Wally.
&nbsp
Wally, don't!
Wally!
&nbsp
Who are you?
Savitar.
&nbsp
The God of Speed.
Synced and corrected by oykubuyuk
www.addic7ed.com
&nbsp