My name is Barry Allen,
&nbsp
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world, I'm an
ordinary forensic scientist,
&nbsp
but secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
&nbsp
I fight crime and find
other meta-humans like me.
&nbsp
After defeating Zoom and
saving the multiverse,
&nbsp
I ran back in time and created
the alternate timeline, Flashpoint.
&nbsp
I restored the timeline to how it was,
only to find things
weren't as I left them.
&nbsp
I brought new threats to our world,
and I'm the only one
fast enough to stop them.
&nbsp
I am The Flash.
Previously on "The Flash"...
&nbsp
Caitlin, I'm sorry, honey.
These powers you have...
the more you use them,
&nbsp
the more difficult they're
going to be to reverse.
&nbsp
I took your cuffs.
Is this some sort of fashion choice?
&nbsp
'Cause you're not a meta-human.
- Am I her?
- Yeah.
&nbsp
I saw the both of us.
Like, full-on Vibe versus Killer Frost.
&nbsp
The time has come
to set you free.
&nbsp
Wally, don't!
You may serve the speed force, Flash,
&nbsp
but I rule it.
You are only a man,
&nbsp
but I am a god.
Your god.
&nbsp
I am Savitar.
- Shoot him!
- I can't see it.
&nbsp
Just do it!
Alchemy!
&nbsp
Let's go for a run.
Barry!
&nbsp
- What's happening?
- I don't understand.
&nbsp
The suit's tracker
must be malfunctioning.
&nbsp
It says he's appearing and reappearing
all over the city at once,
and that's impossible.
&nbsp
He can't be moving that fast.
Well, if he can't,
&nbsp
maybe something else can.
Had enough?
&nbsp
Not even close.
Look. It stopped.
He's at the waterfront.
&nbsp
Okay. We have to get to him.
And do what? He's fighting an invisible
force that's too fast to track.
&nbsp
- If I may, I have a plan.
- No. No.
&nbsp
- Pretty good plan.
- Put your hand down.
&nbsp
It's a question of numbers.
'Cause right now, it seems
to be one against one.
&nbsp
What if there were three against
one? Do you know what I'm saying?
&nbsp
Cisco, you can open a breach
and get you both to the waterfront.
&nbsp
Guys, I can't. It's too dangerous.
I'm begging you. Please.
&nbsp
Still alive down there?
You are only a shadow beneath my throne.
&nbsp
You are the past,
whereas I...
&nbsp
I am the future, Flash.
I can't see it!
&nbsp
Just do it!
Whoo-ee!
&nbsp
Ahh. Oh, boy.
I'm gonna feel that tomorrow.
&nbsp
Ah.
That was a new and
painful use of my powers.
&nbsp
Ugh. You okay?
Yeah, I'm okay.
&nbsp
Just cold.
Thanks for coming.
&nbsp
Synced and corrected by Aaronnmb
www.addic7ed.com
&nbsp
Barry, you're already healing.
You should be fine soon.
&nbsp
Um, Cisco, the MRI I did of your brain
shows changes in the
capillary morphology
&nbsp
similar to that of a mini-stroke.
I wouldn't try an intra-dimensional
breach like that anytime soon.
&nbsp
Okay, okay. Mini-stroke?
You can't just gloss
over that like that, okay?
&nbsp
What does that... what does that mean?
Am I gonna have this migraine
for the rest of my life?
&nbsp
It means you should take a
few aspirin and you'll be fine.
&nbsp
Oh. Well, just lead with that next time.
Cait, I know what a risk you
took using your powers. Thank you.
&nbsp
- I didn't do anything.
- Well, you saved my life.
&nbsp
You've saved mine plenty of times.
I'm gonna go check on Wally.
&nbsp
Okay.
What was that?
&nbsp
That frozen thing at the waterfront?
I don't know.
&nbsp
But now we know Alchemy
is just the lackey.
&nbsp
Whatever that thing was, it's
what we're really up against.
&nbsp
Question: you're the
only one who can see him?
&nbsp
Why? I mean... why?
You're both speedsters. Maybe
it has something to do with that.
&nbsp
Maybe. But I think he's
more than a speedster.
&nbsp
I mean, when he had me, it
wasn't like we were even moving;
&nbsp
it was just like, "bam," we were
instantly somewhere different,
&nbsp
even from my perspective.
Did he say anything else?
&nbsp
He said his name was Savitar.
Mm. Hindu god of motion.
&nbsp
What? How do you know that?
Crossword puzzle wizard.
On two planets, I might add.
&nbsp
12 across, 7 letters. Savitar. Bam.
Hindu god of motion.
&nbsp
- He said he was God.
- That's... that's nice.
&nbsp
That's not scary... at all.
- Hey.
&nbsp
- You sure you're okay?
- Yeah, I'm okay.
&nbsp
How are you?
Can you tell anything?
&nbsp
Wally's alive in there,
but his vitals are really subdued.
&nbsp
His brain function is low.
Something like you'd
see in a coma patient.
&nbsp
I was in a coma after I got my powers.
Maybe it's a similar process.
&nbsp
Can we take him out?
When a caterpillar is in its chrysalis,
&nbsp
it literally breaks its
body down into enzyme soup
&nbsp
before rebuilding as a butterfly.
If this cocoon is doing
the same thing to Wally,
&nbsp
I just... I don't know.
You're right. You don't know.
&nbsp
None of us knows a damn thing
about what's going on in there.
&nbsp
And I feel like a fool just
standing here listening.
&nbsp
- Dad?
- Look, I've said it before...
&nbsp
I don't have the
education most of you had.
&nbsp
The science of what we do
here is mostly lost on me.
&nbsp
But what I do have...
is my detective skills and my instinct,
&nbsp
and time and time
again, I don't use them
&nbsp
because you guys all tell me
that everything is gonna be okay.
&nbsp
Everything is not okay.
- I'm sorry, Joe.
- I know you are.
&nbsp
But I can't just stand here.
My gut is telling me
I need to do something.
&nbsp
This is not your fault.
Yeah, it is.
&nbsp
Not so tough without your
friends and your fancy robe.
&nbsp
I want to know about Alchemy.
What he does, how he does it...
&nbsp
His powers are beyond
human understanding.
&nbsp
- Try me.
- Oh, you will be tried.
&nbsp
All of you.
When my master rises, the
human race will be judged.
&nbsp
From where I'm sitting,
you will not fare very well.
&nbsp
You think I'm playing with you?
My son is in one of those cocoons,
&nbsp
and you're gonna tell
me how to get him out.
&nbsp
Now talk!
Go away!
&nbsp
Caitlin, what is it?
It's Wally.
&nbsp
He's out of that thing. He's fine.
- And he's okay?
- Yeah. He's fine.
&nbsp
I promise.
Oh, thank God. Thank you, Caitlin.
&nbsp
You should probably go see him.
Uh, yeah.
&nbsp
Where is Alchemy?
Tell me where Alchemy is.
&nbsp
I sense great fear in you.
You fear your power,
&nbsp
your own greatness.
I don't fear anything anymore.
&nbsp
Where is Alchemy?
The only one I fear is
that whom Alchemy serves,
&nbsp
the dark lord Savitar.
Maybe it's time you started fearing me.
&nbsp
No, no, no... aah!
Who's in there?
&nbsp
Frozen?
Hello?
&nbsp
Excuse me?
Anybody out there?
&nbsp
Let us out of here!
I need you to come with me.
&nbsp
Wait. What is going on?
Hey, Joe. What do you mean?
&nbsp
Caitlin came by the precinct. She said
that Wally was out and that he was okay.
&nbsp
What? I didn't even see her leave.
SWAT needs to establish a
cordon at 6th and Fairmont,
&nbsp
all the way down to Gleason. Move!
Move! Let's go!
&nbsp
Detective Patterson? Hey. What's...
Just the man I want to see.
&nbsp
Your little friend's
in big trouble, Allen.
&nbsp
- My f...
- A female meta-human
&nbsp
attacked the precinct,
took Julian Albert hostage.
&nbsp
Julian? Wait, do you
know who the meta is?
&nbsp
Uh, no. But she's smart.
I'll tell you that.
&nbsp
Took out our security
cameras so we couldn't ID her.
&nbsp
I thought maybe you'd recognize her.
No. Why would she take Julian?
&nbsp
She's a meta. They're all crazy.
But don't worry. We'll get her.
&nbsp
What are you doing?
What are you doing, Cait?
&nbsp
Bit chilly in here, isn't it?
Shut up. I need to think.
&nbsp
Look. I know who you are, okay?
You're... you're... you're
Allen's friend, right?
&nbsp
- Dr. Snow?
- I said be quiet.
&nbsp
Are you going to kill me?
- I need to find Alchemy.
- Alchemy? What?
&nbsp
What do you want me to do?
Alchemy has disciples, followers.
&nbsp
I need you to create an algorithm
that will allow you to locate anyone
&nbsp
who has searched for a specific
keyword in the last six months.
&nbsp
If we find one of his followers,
they can take me to Alchemy.
&nbsp
Okay. But "alchemy" is a
relatively common phrase.
&nbsp
It'll have hundreds of hits.
Then search for an uncommon one.
&nbsp
- Such as?
- Savitar.
&nbsp
Savitar?
Get searching.
&nbsp
So, they don't know why she took Julian?
No, they don't. But more importantly,
&nbsp
they don't even know
that it's Caitlin yet,
&nbsp
so we need to find her before they do.
Savitar. Now, what about this Savitar...
&nbsp
We find Caitlin. Then we
can worry about Savitar.
&nbsp
You know what, guys?
I'm... I agree with Barry.
&nbsp
Let's find Caitlin.
Okay. You're right. And when
we find Caitlin, then what?
&nbsp
I don't know. I mean, she's
not thinking straight. She's...
&nbsp
She's becoming Killer Frost.
It's just like in the Vibe.
&nbsp
- We don't know that yet.
- Her mother said
&nbsp
the more that she uses her powers,
the faster she's gonna go.
&nbsp
And saving you from Savitar...
that must have put her over the edge.
&nbsp
How do we find her?
I don't know. I tried
pinging her cell and Julian's,
&nbsp
but she must have ditched them both.
Ahem! If I may proffer a notion...
&nbsp
Oh, great. More suggestions
from the genius over here.
&nbsp
You don't call the genius.
The genius calls you.
&nbsp
Question:
how did you catch your Captain Cold?
&nbsp
I've been reading
about him in your files.
&nbsp
Seems like a wily fellow. Slow talker.
But his MO... strikingly
similar to our dear Caitlin's.
&nbsp
What? No. We tracked
him using the satellite
&nbsp
to scan for ultraviolet cold signatures.
Got it.
&nbsp
No. Nothing near the precinct.
Wait, what's that?
&nbsp
Frozen food warehouse.
There she is.
&nbsp
Okay, I'm gonna isolate the feed
so that no one else can see it.
&nbsp
All right, figure out what she's
making Julian do. I'm going.
&nbsp
Okay.
That... is cool.
&nbsp
I found two individuals that have
searched for the name Savitar.
&nbsp
Here are both their addresses,
both of them in Central City.
&nbsp
What exactly are you gonna do to them?
I don't know.
&nbsp
What am I doing?
_
&nbsp
Son of a...
Sergeant, we got a location
on Albert. Let's move.
&nbsp
What part of "I'll freeze you
to death" did you not understand?
&nbsp
Stop.
- Get out of here.
- You know I can't.
&nbsp
What are you doing? Take
her out. Take her out.
&nbsp
You don't want to do this.
You don't want to hurt anybody.
&nbsp
She's willing to hurt
someone. Knock her out.
&nbsp
- Caitlin...
- Leave me alone.
&nbsp
- What are you doing?
- I have to find Alchemy.
&nbsp
We will find him. All right? Together.
No. You don't understand.
I don't want to lock him up.
&nbsp
- I need him to help me.
- Help you what?
&nbsp
I need him to get rid of my powers.
Oh, Caitlin.
&nbsp
I don't know if it works that way.
You don't know that it doesn't.
&nbsp
I know that we love you.
And we will do everything
that we can to help you.
&nbsp
You and I... we've been
through too much together
&nbsp
to let each other down now.
Please. Let me help you.
&nbsp
Like you helped your mother?
Caitlin.
&nbsp
Or Wally? Or me?
You keep messing with everyone's lives,
&nbsp
wrecking everything,
and we're left behind
&nbsp
to pick up the pieces
from your mistakes.
&nbsp
Some things you break
can't be put back together.
&nbsp
I can fix this.
Oh, like you fixed Cisco's family?
&nbsp
You didn't tell Cisco that you
screwed him worst of all, did you?
&nbsp
You hear that, Cisco?
Dante was alive,
&nbsp
healthy and happy,
until Barry created Flashpoint.
&nbsp
When he reset things,
that's what killed him.
&nbsp
Barry is the reason
your brother is dead.
&nbsp
Albert's down. Shoot her!
That severed your triceps surae.
&nbsp
Even with your healing abilities,
it'll take four hours to regenerate.
&nbsp
Don't follow me.
Caitlin. Come on... gah!
&nbsp
- How much does it hurt?
- As much as I deserve.
&nbsp
Okay. Let me know.
They took Julian to County General.
&nbsp
He's still out cold.
How hard did you hit him?
&nbsp
I don't know. I didn't
mean to knock him out.
&nbsp
Or maybe I did.
Cisco.
&nbsp
Hey, man, um,
what Caitlin said...
&nbsp
Was she lying?
No. Um...
&nbsp
You're sorry?
That you killed my brother?
&nbsp
'Cause he was here.
He was alive...
&nbsp
until you created Flashpoint,
- until you did this.
- I know, man.
&nbsp
I don't even know how to feel right now.
All I know is Caitlin is out there,
&nbsp
and we need to find her.
Can we do that?
&nbsp
Yeah.
I hacked Julian's computer.
&nbsp
Caitlin had him look up two addresses:
16 Hawthorne Avenue
and 1104 Truman Place.
&nbsp
She's trying to find the
acolytes, I was trying to say.
&nbsp
What exactly would she want
with Alchemy's followers?
&nbsp
She must think that he
can take her to Alchemy.
&nbsp
She wants him to take her powers away.
We know. We heard everything.
&nbsp
Well, two acolytes, two addresses.
Which one's she gonna hit first?
&nbsp
- We got to watch both.
- You're gonna stay here.
&nbsp
You can barely walk.
- I'll take Hawthorne.
- I'll take Truman.
&nbsp
I care about Caitlin, but
I don't want to leave Wally.
&nbsp
Dad, Barry and I will stay
with Wally. You go with H.R.
&nbsp
Oh, yeah, I would love that.
Hey, you and me... all-star team, huh?
&nbsp
All right, you know what? I'll make a
couple cappuccinos for the road, right,
&nbsp
so we're ready for tonight's
adventures. Hey, not to worry, Barry.
&nbsp
Right? We'll help her.
Cisco.
&nbsp
- If you find her...
- I won't call you.
&nbsp
You've done enough.
The acolyte's on the second floor.
&nbsp
- Cup of joe, Joe?
- No.
&nbsp
No? All right. You're
a tea drinker, I bet.
&nbsp
If you want to talk nonsense, I'm
gonna need you to stop talking to me.
&nbsp
You're worried about your son.
Do you have kids?
&nbsp
No.
Then I don't think we could
possibly have a conversation about...
&nbsp
how I'm feeling right now.
Okay, but...
&nbsp
as an interested
observer, I can tell you
&nbsp
Barry admires you.
Yeah.
&nbsp
Well, he needs to listen to me.
Yeah, well, the reason he doesn't...
&nbsp
is Barry's real superpower isn't speed.
- It's hope.
- Mm.
&nbsp
Kid's got an endless reservoir.
Believes everything's gonna work out.
&nbsp
Well, he's wrong about this one.
They all are.
&nbsp
I said it before: when my
gut tells me something is off,
&nbsp
I trust it.
And I need them to trust me.
&nbsp
The next time your gut tells our
team what to do, I'll trust it.
&nbsp
How do I know you're not just
telling me what I want to hear?
&nbsp
Well, what does your gut tell you?
- What is that?
- The satellite.
&nbsp
It's programmed to detect
rapid temperature decelerations.
&nbsp
That's the house Cisco's watching.
Oh, God.
&nbsp
Honey?
Craig?
&nbsp
It's freezing in here.
Go check the thermostat.
&nbsp
- Are you serious?
- Yes.
&nbsp
Both of my parents are doctors.
It's all I ever wanted to be.
&nbsp
Growing up, I used to
practice the Hippocratic Oath.
&nbsp
I was obsessed with it.
If anyone was even gonna step on a bug,
&nbsp
I would say, "Do no harm."
It's built into my DNA.
&nbsp
Unfortunately, my DNA
isn't what it used to be.
&nbsp
So, believe me when I say
answer every one of my questions,
&nbsp
or I will harm you and your family.
- Who is Alchemy?
- I don't know.
&nbsp
I've never seen him without the mask.
I know he can give people powers.
&nbsp
Can he take them away?
Yes.
&nbsp
But you can't make Alchemy do anything.
He's just an acolyte, like me.
&nbsp
We both serve the speed god, Savitar.
He's shown us the future.
&nbsp
I saw you there.
You were glorious and powerful.
&nbsp
My lord has special plans for you,
Caitlin Snow.
&nbsp
Or should I say...
Killer Frost?
&nbsp
Caitlin!
Really?
&nbsp
You brought your toys?
I'm hoping it won't come to that.
&nbsp
It won't.
Look, I'm not leaving you out here.
&nbsp
I want to help you.
There's only one person who can help me.
&nbsp
Really?
You really think seeking medical advice
&nbsp
from someone named Dr.
Alchemy is the way to go?
&nbsp
Why not?
My name is Killer Frost.
&nbsp
Your name...
is Caitlin Snow.
&nbsp
Can Caitlin Snow do this?
Caitlin, please!
&nbsp
Aah!
How's the leg?
&nbsp
I'm sorry, Caitlin.
That was cold, Flash.
&nbsp
But this is colder.
Start vibrating. It'll warm you up.
&nbsp
Whew.
Guess I just needed a little sleep.
&nbsp
Thanks, guys.
I'm feeling much better now.
&nbsp
It's okay. You can let me out.
I promise I'm not gonna hurt anybody.
&nbsp
Hmm.
Guess you're all smarter than I thought.
&nbsp
You know, that was some
blast there, Vibe boy.
&nbsp
It kind of hurt.
I didn't want to hurt you.
&nbsp
You're pathetic.
Alchemy can't help you.
&nbsp
But we can. I promise.
Oh, like you promised Eddie?
&nbsp
And like you promised Ronnie?
You know, for a hero, Flash,
&nbsp
you sure let a lot of
people around you die.
&nbsp
This isn't you talking. It's the powers.
They're messing with
your mind. You're sick.
&nbsp
I'm broken, Barry.
But what do you care?
&nbsp
'Cause you've got Iris.
You got your happy ending.
&nbsp
Everyone else be damned.
So, I'll tell you what:
&nbsp
you guys let me go,
and I will leave you to
your sad and miserable lives.
&nbsp
No. We're not abandoning you.
You did this to me!
&nbsp
Do you have any idea
how we can reverse this?
&nbsp
How we can get her back?
It's like Caitlin said:
&nbsp
sometimes when things get broken,
they can't be fixed.
&nbsp
My son's not gonna end up like Caitlin.
- Help me get him out of this thing.
- Oh, no, no. Joe, no.
&nbsp
We don't... we don't want
to touch that thing...
&nbsp
First off, we don't know what
that's gonna do to Wally, right?
&nbsp
Maybe this is the kind of situation
best left to the
people with the science.
&nbsp
You mean Caitlin?
Please help me.
&nbsp
What are you doing down here?
We should all be working
&nbsp
to find Alchemy and Savitar
and figure out how to stop them.
&nbsp
Instead, we're fighting each other.
Yeah. Team Flash is not at its finest.
&nbsp
Why didn't I just follow
you inside the house?
&nbsp
Because you were hurting.
You would do anything
to make the pain go away.
&nbsp
That's why Caitlin
is so lost. And Cisco.
&nbsp
We will do anything
to make the pain stop.
&nbsp
That doesn't make you a bad person.
That makes you human.
&nbsp
Tell that to my friends.
My best friends,
&nbsp
one of them is locked up like a villain;
the other one hates me.
&nbsp
- You can not take this all on yourself.
- Why not?
&nbsp
How do you know that Caitlin
wasn't already affected
&nbsp
by the accelerator explosion,
or that Dante wouldn't have
died in a car accident anyway?
&nbsp
You are not God, Barry.
That's what Jay said.
&nbsp
Jay's a smart man.
You can not keep doing this to yourself,
&nbsp
constantly going over the what-ifs.
You'll go nuts.
&nbsp
Everyone in this building
needs The Flash right now:
&nbsp
my dad, Wally... even Cisco and Caitlin.
So, be strong like I know you are.
&nbsp
I know you don't want to
be the leader right now,
&nbsp
but you have to be.
I told you I couldn't
do this without you.
&nbsp
And you'll never have to.
- Wally.
- Yeah. Come on.
&nbsp
There's an energy surge
coming from the Cortex.
&nbsp
What?
Joe! Hey! What are you doing?
&nbsp
- Hey, Barr.
- Hey, stop! You can't cut him out!
&nbsp
I have to.
Joe, don't!
&nbsp
Wally.
Wally?
&nbsp
- Joe.
- What did I do?
&nbsp
Was this your idea?
No. Joe... I was helping Joe.
&nbsp
No sign of Wally.
I've got the satellite scanning
the entire city for rapid movement.
&nbsp
If he's a speedster, he could be
halfway across the country by now.
&nbsp
Barry, we have to find him.
I'm more worried about what
happens when we do find him.
&nbsp
He didn't seem like
he was all there, Iris.
&nbsp
I shouldn't have cut
him out of that thing.
&nbsp
Joe, I... what we need
right now is a biochemist.
&nbsp
You've got to go talk to her, Barr.
All right.
&nbsp
We need your help, Caitlin.
Wally... he's...
&nbsp
he's out of the cocoon,
but his biochemistry
is all out of whack.
&nbsp
He went AWOL.
So?
&nbsp
So, when we find him,
he's gonna need your help.
&nbsp
He's gonna need your medical expertise,
your experience with metas.
&nbsp
What he needs is Caitlin Snow, MD.
So, you came to try and
talk some sense into me.
&nbsp
No.
I came to let you go.
&nbsp
For a smart guy, that
was an awfully dumb move.
&nbsp
Like I said, you're free to go.
What's the catch?
&nbsp
You have to kill me.
- What is he doing?
- I don't know.
&nbsp
It's gonna be all right.
You want to fight, Flash?
&nbsp
No. I'm not gonna fight you.
But if you want to leave this room,
&nbsp
you're gonna have to kill me.
- Don't think I won't.
- Then do it.
&nbsp
What are you waiting for?
What's the big deal?
&nbsp
Come on. Live up to
your name, Killer Frost.
&nbsp
I want to see some killing.
You want to be the villain?
&nbsp
This is what they do.
They kill their friends,
&nbsp
because nothing matters
to them anymore, right?
&nbsp
Right?
Come on.
&nbsp
Kill me, Caitlin.
You can't do it.
&nbsp
You can't,
because underneath all
that cold, you're still you.
&nbsp
Barry!
It's okay.
&nbsp
I got you.
It's okay.
&nbsp
I think extracting Wally
early from that cocoon
&nbsp
left him in a fugue state.
His synapses aren't used to
functioning at super-speed,
&nbsp
so his mind and muscles are misfiring.
I mean, will this stuff help?
&nbsp
I've synthesized a neural compound
that I think will get his mind
and body running at the same speed.
&nbsp
We just have to find him first.
Where'd he go, Joe?
&nbsp
What's your gut tell you?
The house that he grew up in.
&nbsp
He used to go there when
he missed his mother.
&nbsp
In Keystone.
Thank you.
&nbsp
Wally!
It's your dad, son.
&nbsp
You're gonna be all right.
We're gonna take care of you, okay?
&nbsp
Dad.
Ooh!
&nbsp
Damn. How fast is he going?
Faster than Barry
could at the beginning.
&nbsp
I, uh...
I just wanted to...
&nbsp
It's okay.
You scared me for a second, getting all
Mother of Dragons on me with that hair.
&nbsp
Thank you.
That is the greatest
feeling I've ever felt.
&nbsp
- Barry, it's unreal.
- Yeah, it is.
&nbsp
- How fast was I going?
- Too fast.
&nbsp
Dad, don't look so worried.
I'm fine. I feel fine.
&nbsp
In fact, I feel kind of awesome,
like everything is buzzing, electric,
&nbsp
like I could do anything.
That is what it feels like.
&nbsp
Got the Speed Force coursing
through you... giving you power.
&nbsp
You're a speedster now.
Cool.
&nbsp
Um, so, what next?
Um, Caitlin is gonna run every
test she can think of on you.
&nbsp
I mean, if you're up for it.
Being a doctor? That, I'm always up for.
&nbsp
Yeah, um, but when do I get
to go out, Barry, with you?
&nbsp
Uh...
Okay, let's just take it
&nbsp
one normal-speed step at a time.
Slow down, Wallace.
&nbsp
Barr, it's the hospital.
Julian's awake.
&nbsp
He knows it was me. He knows what I did.
Don't worry. I'll talk to him.
&nbsp
You'll be fine. I promise.
Hey, man.
&nbsp
I just wanted to see if
you wanted to talk about...
&nbsp
I don't.
All right. Um...
&nbsp
Look, Cisco...
you're my best friend, man.
&nbsp
Are we gonna be okay?
You and me?
&nbsp
You want me to be honest with you?
Yeah. Yeah.
&nbsp
I don't know.
Okay.
&nbsp
Hey, Patterson.
Barry Allen, don't you ever work?
&nbsp
I just wanted to make sure
that Julian was doing okay.
&nbsp
Well, I'm about to take
his statement, yeah.
&nbsp
Uh, would it be okay if I
talked to him before you went in?
&nbsp
I just... we're pretty close, him and I.
Yeah. Go ahead. Just make it quick.
&nbsp
Always. Thank you.
- Oh.
- Hey.
&nbsp
A hospital visit. I didn't
think you missed me that much.
&nbsp
What did the doctors say?
Concussion and frostbite,
&nbsp
but I'll be dandy in a few days.
That's good news. I'm glad
you're gonna be all right.
&nbsp
Yes, and as much as I appreciate
your outburst of emotion,
&nbsp
I think we both know the
real reason you're here.
&nbsp
Your friend Caitlin Snow.
She's a meta,
&nbsp
and not one of the friendly ones.
Did you know?
&nbsp
She's sick, Julian.
She is a bloody menace.
&nbsp
Julian...
man, I know that you think that
getting powers is this binary game,
&nbsp
that you're either good or evil,
but life isn't like
that, even for metas.
&nbsp
Look. Caitlin... she's a good person.
I'm begging you: don't turn her in.
&nbsp
I will do anything you want, but..
please don't do this to her.
&nbsp
I got hit pretty hard,
and I don't have the foggiest
who even kidnapped me at all.
&nbsp
Thank you, man.
Thank you.
&nbsp
There is one thing you
can do for me, mate.
&nbsp
- Anything.
- Quit.
&nbsp
What?
Tender your resignation
&nbsp
from the Central City Police Department,
effective immediately.
&nbsp
I can overlook the unexplained absences,
the constant disregard for
the rules and regulations,
&nbsp
but your moral compass
is broken, my friend.
&nbsp
I point-blank refuse
to work with someone whose
sense of right or wrong is
&nbsp
as flippant as the weather,
someone who thinks friendship
is more important than justice.
&nbsp
You are unfit to be CSI.
Barry Allen has no
place in law enforcement.
&nbsp
Now, do we have an agreement,
or would you like the
detective to meet that girl?
&nbsp
All right.
He's all yours.
&nbsp
- Hey, Albert.
- Hey.
&nbsp
So, what can you tell me
about our... our meta friend?
&nbsp
I don't really remember anything.
To be honest with you, it's
all a bit of a blur, so...
&nbsp
Hey.
We just heard from Singh.
&nbsp
You quit? What... what is going on?
I, um...
&nbsp
didn't really have a choice.
What do you mean, you
didn't have a choice?
&nbsp
Julian.
You quit, he keeps his
mouth shut about Caitlin.
&nbsp
That son of a bitch.
I don't know. I mean, he said I couldn't
do something like protect Caitlin
&nbsp
and still be a good CSI,
and maybe he's right.
&nbsp
No, he's not.
Barry, you are an incredible CSI,
&nbsp
and no one in this building cares more
about helping people
find justice than you.
&nbsp
And that was long before
you were The Flash.
&nbsp
This lab... it's your life.
You're my life.
&nbsp
Both of you.
And Wally and Caitlin, and...
&nbsp
Cisco.
If these past few months have
taught me anything, it's that...
&nbsp
I would give up everything
I have to keep you all safe.
&nbsp
No regrets.
Every time I think you've
run out of ways to be a hero,
&nbsp
you show me another one.
- You hungry?
- Yeah.
&nbsp
Yeah, let's get out of here.
Julian.
&nbsp
Julian!
No. Stay away.
&nbsp
No, Julian. You can't get away.
There's nowhere I won't find you.
&nbsp
Only together can we
bring about my return.
&nbsp
Become my servant once more.
Become Alchemy.
&nbsp
Synced and corrected by Aaronnmb
www.addic7ed.com
&nbsp