My name is Barry Allen,
&nbsp
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world, I'm
an ordinary forensic scientist,
&nbsp
but secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
&nbsp
I fight crime and find
other meta-humans like me.
&nbsp
After defeating Zoom
and saving the multiverse,
&nbsp
I ran back in time and created
the alternate timeline, Flashpoint.
&nbsp
I restored the timeline to how it was,
only to find things weren't as I left them.
&nbsp
I brought new threats to our world,
and I'm the only one
fast enough to stop them.
&nbsp
I am The Flash.
Previously on "The Flash"...
&nbsp
They don't see your potential.
I do. You want to train?
&nbsp
I'll train you.
You're Allen's friend, Dr. Snow.
&nbsp
I'm begging you, don't turn her in.
I will do anything you want.
&nbsp
Tender your resignation,
effective immediately.
&nbsp
It's a story... it used to be
written by Iris West-Allen.
&nbsp
Something's changed with our future.
- God, what did I do?
- My brother's dead.
&nbsp
Now I'll never make another
memory with Dante again.
&nbsp
You're only a man, Flash.
But I am a god.
&nbsp
I am Savitar.
Now we know Alchemy's just a lackey.
&nbsp
Julian, become my servant once more.
Become Alchemy.
&nbsp
It's been six months since
I arrived here in India.
&nbsp
Though I have faith it's out there,
the voice that once drove me has waned.
&nbsp
And I fear my quest may be for naught.
Julian, come quick.
&nbsp
I think we found it.
This is it. Here, hold this.
&nbsp
This is it.
I can feel it.
&nbsp
I think we should wait before we open it.
It needs to be set free.
&nbsp
Synced and corrected by oykubuyuk
www.addic7ed.com
&nbsp
Holy winter wonderland.
Took the words right out of my mouth.
&nbsp
Well, I guess Earth-19's
Christmas is just like ours.
&nbsp
Some traditions are multi-versal.
So, um...
&nbsp
any more info on Savitar?
Nope, all the we know
is that he's a speed god
&nbsp
and you're the only one who can see him.
All right, well, Alchemy is
Savitar's high priest
&nbsp
and he gets his power from the stone
that he uses to create meta,
so I was thinking
&nbsp
if we can find out what that thing is,
maybe we can figure out how to stop him.
&nbsp
I want to see if I can dig something up.
Okay.
&nbsp
I know this is our first
Christmas together as a couple
&nbsp
and I want everything to be perfect, but...
You need to get to this.
&nbsp
Yes... no, I totally get it.
Hey, uh, I got a dissertation
here from Oxford University
&nbsp
about the myth of an ancient Hindu weapon
- called the Brahmastra.
- Mm-hmm.
&nbsp
Legendary artifact with incredible powers,
capable of... wait for it...
&nbsp
Creating metas.
Creating meta-humans.
&nbsp
Guys, that looks just like Alchemy's stone.
More importantly...
&nbsp
look who wrote this paper.
Julian?
&nbsp
Love what you've done with the place.
Ah, Allen.
&nbsp
Thought we had a deal.
I keep your frosty friend's secret,
&nbsp
and you never darken
these doors again, remember?
&nbsp
I just need some information from you
about that stone that Alchemy uses.
&nbsp
And you've come to me because?
Apparently, you know a lot about it.
&nbsp
Well, why don't you tell me
everything you know?
&nbsp
And you'll never hear from me again.
Fine.
&nbsp
Many years ago,
I heard about the Brahmastra,
&nbsp
or as it's colloquially called,
the Philosopher's Stone.
&nbsp
It is said to be the first object
to give human beings powers.
&nbsp
Like the Particle Accelerator.
Over the years, it got lost.
&nbsp
I became quite obsessed
with trying to find it.
&nbsp
Did every piece of
available research I could
&nbsp
and much to my parents' dismay,
I used my future inheritance
&nbsp
and funded an expedition to try and find it.
But we never found it.
&nbsp
Pretty soon after that, I came here.
Now, if you'll excuse me, I have work to do.
&nbsp
In your research, have you ever come across
the name Savitar?
&nbsp
How do you know that name?
I've done some research of my own.
&nbsp
As far as I know, Savitar
is the first meta with speed.
&nbsp
That's all I know, Allen.
And I suggest that you don't
waste your time on this.
&nbsp
Move on.
Alright.
&nbsp
Julian.
Here you go.
&nbsp
One whiff of aliens
and all the crazies come out.
&nbsp
I'm gonna be buried under these alien files
until next Christmas.
&nbsp
Well, if by some Christmas miracle
you dig yourself out sooner,
&nbsp
we do it up at the West house
on Christmas Eve.
&nbsp
Turkey, tree, Grandma Esther's eggnog,
the whole shebang... and we would
love for you to come.
&nbsp
One condition, I bring the nog.
My Grandma Millie's recipe, it
is gonna knock your socks off.
&nbsp
- Oh, wait a minute.
- Hmm?
&nbsp
We gonna have a little nog-off.
Really?
&nbsp
Grandma Esther versus Grandma Millie.
Oh, you know I love a challenge, Joe West.
&nbsp
May the best grandma win.
I am so sorry for your grandma.
&nbsp
We'll see.
- Fine.
- Oh, yeah.
&nbsp
- I'll pick you up, all right?
- Christmas miracle.
&nbsp
I told everyone inside I'd let them live
if they followed my instructions.
&nbsp
But I tricked them.
Which is so me.
&nbsp
Give it up, Trickster!
Hiya, Swiftie.
&nbsp
Will you do me the honor
of allowing me to kill you?
&nbsp
You're out of ammo.
But I'm not out of bombs.
&nbsp
What do you say we take in
the afterlife, big boy?
&nbsp
- Nice timing.
- You're welcome.
&nbsp
There's something wrong with my eyes.
I'm seeing double.
&nbsp
The Flash hit me too hard!
I'm gonna sue you, saucer-head!
&nbsp
One day, I'll own that helmet,
and I'll use it as an ashtray
or a candy dish.
&nbsp
No, wait, a hubcap!
I had that, kid.
&nbsp
That's what I always say.
Especially when I didn't have it.
&nbsp
So I'm assuming you didn't
come all the way to Earth-3
&nbsp
to stop my Trickster.
I have something I need to
talk to you about.
&nbsp
A speedster.
Calls himself Savitar.
&nbsp
- So... Savitar.
- Yeah.
&nbsp
Apparently, you've grown powerful enough
to challenge him.
&nbsp
Who is he?
Don't know, never seen him.
&nbsp
You're the first speedster
I know of who has.
&nbsp
But every story I ever heard about Savitar
is basically the same.
&nbsp
Savitar was the first man
ever granted speed.
&nbsp
And over time, he became the god of motion,
the fastest of us all.
&nbsp
Before Savitar graces an Earth
with his presence...
&nbsp
He sends a predecessor to
prepare for his arrival.
&nbsp
- Alchemy.
- Mm.
&nbsp
What's he preparing for?
A battle with you.
&nbsp
Why me?
You're threatening his power.
&nbsp
How do you know all this?
Speed Force myths, legends, rumors.
&nbsp
If Savitar's come for you once,
he'll be back.
&nbsp
Then I'll be ready.
We'll be ready.
&nbsp
Run! Wallace, run!
You got to torque to the left!
&nbsp
- How'd I do?
- How'd you do?
&nbsp
Oh, I don't know,
why don't you see for yourself.
&nbsp
Hold up, are you saying
I'm faster than Barry?
&nbsp
I'm saying that at this point
in his training,
&nbsp
you're faster than Barry.
You're faster than Barry,
you're faster than Barry,
&nbsp
you're faster than Barry!
- We got to tell everyone.
- Not a good idea.
&nbsp
- Why not?
- Self-preservation, basically.
&nbsp
Look, Wallace, you have
tremendous potential.
&nbsp
Yes, clearly, but one thing I've learned
since coming to this Earth
is you do not trifle
&nbsp
with the West household.
No, you know... no, say you're with me.
&nbsp
- Yeah, I'm with you.
- Yeah!
&nbsp
Now, we're gonna work on
your... your... yeah, your dodging
&nbsp
and your weaving.
I've read every Hindu textbook
there is on mythology
&nbsp
and spirits and demigods and nothing.
No mention of Savitar, not once.
&nbsp
In my experience, the answers
usually tend to come in time.
&nbsp
Yeah, I can't just sit back
and wait for Savitar or Alchemy to attack.
&nbsp
You can't worry about what
may or may not lie ahead.
&nbsp
Besides...
it's Christmas.
&nbsp
A time to be with the ones you care about.
You know, it's just,
Savitar's still out there.
&nbsp
Yeah, but not right now.
And your beautiful girlfriend is.
&nbsp
Get your head out of the books
and back into your life with your loved ones
&nbsp
while you have them.
Hey, Jay thinks he figured out
a way to find the stone.
&nbsp
You okay?
I don't know.
&nbsp
I keep seeing my brother.
Everywhere... here, in the cortex...
&nbsp
Well, this is your first
Christmas since Dante died.
&nbsp
Maybe your mind's playing tricks on you.
Yeah.
&nbsp
Probably.
There was this one Christmas,
big family affair.
&nbsp
and Dante and I, you know,
we used to fight all the time as kids,
&nbsp
but that one Christmas,
we didn't fight.
&nbsp
We just sat and we talked and we drank
a whole bottle of whiskey, and...
&nbsp
that whole night, we were laughing.
It's...
&nbsp
And that one night...
that one night, it was like
we felt like brothers.
&nbsp
The last Christmas before my dad died,
it snowed and snowed.
&nbsp
He and I just sat inside,
watching old movies
&nbsp
while the whole world turned white.
It was magical.
&nbsp
Hmm.
Are we about to be the Grinches this year?
&nbsp
Nice use of restraint.
Yeah, well, I shopped,
&nbsp
and I shopped, and now,
I am ready to drop into your arms.
&nbsp
I'm sorry I missed
Christmas shopping with you.
&nbsp
It's okay. I have everything I need.
So are you as excited to give me my present
&nbsp
as I am to give you yours?
Yeah, of course.
&nbsp
Definitely. Yeah.
You did get me something, right?
&nbsp
I did get you something, yeah.
I just... I haven't wrapped it yet, is all.
&nbsp
- Okay.
Okay, um, by the way,
after you told me about
&nbsp
Julian's archeological dig,
I started doing some digging of my own.
&nbsp
Uh-huh.
Turns out, a few years ago,
&nbsp
four scientists were killed
in an excavation in India
&nbsp
and Julian was the point person.
He didn't mention that.
&nbsp
You said he was obsessed
with that stone for years.
&nbsp
What if he was covering something up?
Or someone?
&nbsp
You think this is about Alchemy?
There's only one way to find out.
&nbsp
Julian lied about the Philosopher's Stone.
I think he found it back
on that archeological dig.
&nbsp
You think he's working with Doctor Alchemy?
He's not answering my calls.
&nbsp
Hey, everyone.
Gang's all here, what's going on?
&nbsp
I think that Julian is
connected to Doctor Alchemy.
&nbsp
Jay, we got a hit.
There's energy coming from the
top of the Schults building.
&nbsp
- That's the stone.
- Are you ready?
&nbsp
- Ready.
- All right.
&nbsp
I'm coming, too.
- No you're not.
- No.
&nbsp
Dad, I'm ready.
You... just tell them about how fast I am.
&nbsp
Tell them about the training.
- Training?
&nbsp
Oh, training. The vocal training.
Because we're thinking of going caroling.
&nbsp
We're gonna talk about this later.
We're definitely gonna talk about it.
&nbsp
With energy form this stone,
and this building as a refractor,
&nbsp
I shall restore the powers of all the metas
from Flashpoint.
&nbsp
They will become the servants of Savitar.
It's over, Alchemy!
&nbsp
Please tell me you're seeing him.
Oh, I see him.
&nbsp
We have to take him together.
No, I'll cover Savitar,
&nbsp
you just get that stone!
This is not your fight, Garrick.
&nbsp
Julian.
Where am I?
&nbsp
What's going on?
Let's just say you're gonna be
&nbsp
our guest for a while.
You.
&nbsp
I always suspected you had
your own private facility
&nbsp
for holding enemies.
You care to explain what I'm doing in it?
&nbsp
- I know you're Alchemy, Julian.
- What?
&nbsp
Turning innocent people into meta-humans,
worshipping this Savitar?
&nbsp
Sorry, um, I'm still not following.
You think that I'm Alchemy?
&nbsp
That's the most absurd thing
I've ever heard.
&nbsp
Is that a mask?
I've never seen that before in my life.
&nbsp
I caught you!
I caught you wearing this mask.
&nbsp
You're trying to set me up.
You're framing me, aren't you?
&nbsp
The Flash, of all the people,
you're setting me up.
&nbsp
- The hero.
- You're insane.
&nbsp
The great hero!
I want my phone call,
when do I get my phone call?
&nbsp
- Hey.
How you feeling?
&nbsp
Not too bad for a guy
that got beat up by a myth.
&nbsp
- Yeah?
- You stopped him.
&nbsp
Well done, Barry.
It was nice, having you out there with me.
&nbsp
Yeah, I never had a sidekick.
- Oh, I'm your sidekick?
- Well, as a senior partner.
&nbsp
Senior citizen is more like it.
I'll bet your dad
would've been proud of you.
&nbsp
Right?
Hey, why won't you just
take it easy, all right?
&nbsp
- I'll see you in a little bit.
- Yeah.
&nbsp
What do you think about
what Julian was saying?
&nbsp
I know that every bad guy we've ever had
has pretended to be our best
friend, while really being
&nbsp
an evil, murderous bastard, but...
I think if he's lying, he sure believes
&nbsp
the hell out of his own lie.
Okay, well what do we think about this box?
&nbsp
It's creepy.
Like, "Indiana Jones" melt your face creepy.
&nbsp
Have you guys figured out
anything about it yet?
&nbsp
It's nothing.
Mm, it's something.
&nbsp
No, I mean the box is literally nothing.
I've run it through every
possible test I can think of...
&nbsp
MRI, x-ray, mass spectrometer,
the photon shifter.
&nbsp
Not a single reading. Nothing.
It's like the box
&nbsp
doesn't even exist.
Two weeks ago, I almost lost you to Alchemy,
&nbsp
then last week aliens.
My heart can't take it, Wally.
Dad, he gets it.
&nbsp
- Iris, does he?
- I think so, yeah.
&nbsp
And you...
A couple weeks ago, you were telling me
&nbsp
how you believed in me and my instincts,
and now you're encouraging Wally
to do exactly the opposite?
&nbsp
I don't know how much encouraging he needed.
- What's the deal with you?
- Hmm?
&nbsp
You have some psychotic need
to make other people like you
&nbsp
no matter what?
I wouldn't call it psychotic.
&nbsp
No, my deal is,
I find people's true talents,
&nbsp
and I just marshal them along.
Do you even have your own opinions?
&nbsp
Stop. Stop banging on H.R.
This was all me, okay?
&nbsp
I pushed him to train me.
I pushed him to help me.
&nbsp
Wasn't like anyone else
was lining up to do it.
&nbsp
Hey. What's up?
It's Wally.
&nbsp
I don't get it, Bar, it's like
his brain goes to sleep
&nbsp
and somebody else is at the wheel.
Have you been losing time? Blacking out?
&nbsp
Hours passing,
waking up somewhere different?
&nbsp
Not being sure of how you got there.
- No.
- No?
&nbsp
No!
I've had enough of these
&nbsp
baseless accusations
and ridiculous theories of yours.
&nbsp
Julian, I'm trying to help you!
But you need to trust me.
&nbsp
Says the man in a mask.
No, you're right.
&nbsp
I should've known.
I should've guessed it.
&nbsp
Ah!
The unexplained absences,
your passion for metas.
&nbsp
Your general thumbing your nose
at authority.
&nbsp
I'm sure you had a good laugh
behind my back.
&nbsp
I actually wished
I could've told you before.
&nbsp
So why tell me now?
Because I need you to trust me, Julian.
&nbsp
You are Alchemy.
I just don't think you're aware of it.
&nbsp
Now, have you been blacking out?
Yes.
&nbsp
When did it start?
My sister, Emma, died when I was 20.
&nbsp
And it really broke the family up, you know?
Mom and Dad weren't speaking,
&nbsp
they wouldn't even stay at the house.
One night, I was there alone,
&nbsp
and she came back to me.
She stood right in front of me,
&nbsp
clear as day... a ghost
or a vision, I don't know,
&nbsp
but...
she was real.
&nbsp
What happened?
She told me about the stone.
&nbsp
She told me where to find it,
she told me that if I got it, then it would
&nbsp
bring us back together again.
And at that point, mate,
I would've done anything
&nbsp
to have her back.
That's what I did.
&nbsp
I mounted an expedition to India.
Days we searched, weeks.
&nbsp
Nothing.
And then we found it.
&nbsp
And the next thing I remember,
I woke up in the hotel room.
&nbsp
I...
didn't remember anything,
and that's when the blackouts
&nbsp
started happening.
There was a news report saying that
&nbsp
every other member of my team
had been found...
&nbsp
dead at the site.
I panicked, I thought they were
gonna blame me for their deaths,
&nbsp
so I ran.
I ran to America.
&nbsp
What happens when you black out, Julian?
How does it start?
&nbsp
I hear the voice.
Cisco.
&nbsp
You're losing it, man,
you're losing it.
&nbsp
Stop scaring me!
Whatever you are, it's not cool, okay?
&nbsp
Oh, I know exactly what you are.
You are a figment of my grief.
&nbsp
Please just leave.
I can't do that, Cisco.
&nbsp
This is not real.
Okay, I need an anti-psychotic. Caitlin!
&nbsp
If you leave,
I'm gonna have to leave, too.
&nbsp
So you're telling me that...
that every time I'm blacking out...
&nbsp
You've become Alchemy.
That's impossible.
&nbsp
Alchemy is a monster,
he's been terrorizing people for years.
&nbsp
Look, it's not you.
Just like it wasn't you back on that dig.
&nbsp
I know that this is hard to believe,
but you have to start accepting
what's happening to you.
&nbsp
Don't you want us to be together again?
The stone.
&nbsp
It's the key to everything.
It can transform people.
&nbsp
Open it and I can be reborn.
We can be together again.
&nbsp
We can have that bottle of whiskey.
After all, it is Christmas, hermano.
&nbsp
It's the time of miracles.
I just want this to be real.
&nbsp
Just open the box.
I love you, Cisco.
&nbsp
Dante.
Dante?
&nbsp
What's that?
- Guys, what's going on?
- Cisco's workshop.
&nbsp
Barry, he opened the box.
Wait...
&nbsp
Cisco?
Bow to your god.
&nbsp
- What is happening?
- We can't see it,
&nbsp
just like at Alchemy's lair.
Savitar's loose.
&nbsp
Hey, Jay, Jay, you're still too badly hurt.
Remember, dodge and weave.
&nbsp
Wally, no!
I can see him.
&nbsp
Great. Get his attention.
Uh, yo, metal mouth.
&nbsp
Clearly, nobody taught you how
to place nice with others.
&nbsp
Cisco? Cisco, you have to close the box!
I'm gonna save Dante.
&nbsp
It's... that's not Dante, it's Savitar.
Please, he's using
your memories against you!
&nbsp
You're a good brother, Cisco.
Cisco, we're running out of time.
&nbsp
Please, just hand me the box.
I won't lose him again.
&nbsp
I will not lose my brother again!
Cisco, Dante is gone.
&nbsp
I'm so sorry, but there is
nothing you can do about it.
&nbsp
But there are people you can save right now.
If you don't close that box,
&nbsp
Barry and Wally will die.
If you do, we can't be together.
&nbsp
Cisco, listen to me!
Don't.
&nbsp
Lo siento, hermano.
Thanks.
&nbsp
You kidding? That was awesome.
Are you sure you're okay?
&nbsp
Still in one piece.
I don't know what happened.
&nbsp
So now that the box is closed,
Savitar's, what, gone for good?
&nbsp
I don't know, but we need to find out.
Cisco?
&nbsp
If we can't use this box, Julian,
he may be our only link to
Savitar now, right?
&nbsp
I think we can use both of them.
If Caitlin's right and this
thing messes with brainwaves,
&nbsp
then I have a plan.
Hey.
&nbsp
You put my son's life in danger again.
And he saved Barry's life.
&nbsp
Joe, why...
why do you think I help Wally?
&nbsp
'Cause I'm selfish, I get something...
I don't get anything out of it.
&nbsp
I help Wally 'cause the kid is special.
He's extraordinary.
&nbsp
His powers are extraordinary
and... look, I get it.
&nbsp
I'm... I'm not his dad
and I don't have the same
&nbsp
safety concerns as you, of course not,
but Joe, one thing I do know,
&nbsp
the longer you deny someone their potential,
the more they're gonna
look for it elsewhere.
&nbsp
So what am I doing here?
Okay, Julian, today
when I was fighting Savitar,
&nbsp
it... he and Alchemy, they had the same voice.
All right, what does that mean?
&nbsp
I don't think there is an Alchemy,
I think it's Savitar speaking through you.
&nbsp
Savitar clearly possesses
someone who rallies worshippers.
&nbsp
But he's like a poltergeist,
he needs a medium
&nbsp
to manifest himself.
You.
&nbsp
Right, but what does that mean?
We think we figured out a way
&nbsp
to sync your brain to the stone.
And it'll allow us
to speak directly to Savitar.
&nbsp
I thought...
If you want to try to be free of this,
&nbsp
you need to trust us.
- I've never liked you, Allen.
- Yeah.
&nbsp
Having a little siance with your friends now
is not gonna help change that fact.
&nbsp
You do know that.
Fine, I'll try it.
&nbsp
Deep breaths.
- Okay?
- Yeah.
&nbsp
You're gonna count backwards from ten.
Te...
&nbsp
That was quick.
Okay, so, um, how long till this works?
&nbsp
Not really sure, it may take
a minute for his brain waves...
&nbsp
Hello, Barry.
It's been a while.
&nbsp
Savitar?
None of you are on your knees.
&nbsp
It's a smart move to bow before a deity.
You're not God.
&nbsp
To be a god, you just have to make people
believe you are.
&nbsp
No one believes in you.
You should, Iris.
&nbsp
I hold the power of life
and death over all of you.
&nbsp
How do you know so much about us?
I know you, Caitlin.
&nbsp
Cisco, Joe, Wally.
The fake Wells.
&nbsp
I know your fears
and I know your weaknesses.
&nbsp
I know you better than you know yourselves.
I know your destinies.
&nbsp
One shall betray you.
One shall fall.
&nbsp
One will suffer a fate far worse than death.
This is the knowledge I have for you.
&nbsp
About your everlasting damnation.
Who are you?
&nbsp
I am the future, Flash.
What do you want from us?
&nbsp
Everything!
Everything you took from me, I want it back.
&nbsp
And I'm gonna take it back.
Then, I will destroy you.
&nbsp
Then why haven't you already?
If you're all-powerful,
then why don't you just
&nbsp
go ahead and kill us all now,
be done with it?
&nbsp
Because you can't.
You did this to me.
&nbsp
You trapped me in eternity.
Your future self...
you did this to me, Barry.
&nbsp
And now the age of my revenge rises.
My freedom is at hand.
&nbsp
You will feel my wrath.
The wrath of Savitar!
&nbsp
Did it work?
That was so scary.
&nbsp
I mean, that was...
was it not truly frightening,
&nbsp
what the voice and the prophesies and the...
oh, it was... I mean,
that a scare-a-thon, wasn't it?
&nbsp
I'm gonna have a mint tea
and a coffee and a lay down.
&nbsp
Do you think the things that he said about
one of us betraying him and one of us dying
&nbsp
could really be true?
I mean, if it really was future Barry
&nbsp
that pissed him off
and locked him up somewhere,
&nbsp
then maybe he knows
what happens to future us.
&nbsp
He doesn't.
He's never getting out of
wherever he's trapped.
&nbsp
So how are we supposed to stop him?
The stone.
&nbsp
Jay's right, the stone has
been the key to everything.
&nbsp
It's... it's how he controlled Julian,
it's how he's created more metas.
&nbsp
So we destroy the stone
and Savitar is gone for good.
&nbsp
It's impossible to destroy.
It's been around forever,
there's a reason for that.
&nbsp
Why don't we just bury it again,
put it back in the ground
where you found it?
&nbsp
Mm-mm. "Jumanji."
Someone would just find it
and we'd be right back
&nbsp
where we started.
We need to make that box disappear forever.
&nbsp
There's only one thing we can do with it.
Throw it into the Speed Force.
&nbsp
- Wait, you can do that?
- Oh, yeah.
&nbsp
The Speed Force is eternity itself,
an endless void of time and energy.
&nbsp
It'd be like trying to find it
after it got lost in space.
&nbsp
But that stone is loaded
with gravimetric force.
&nbsp
I mean, I don't think
you could run fast enough
&nbsp
to reach the Speed Force and
carry that at the same time.
&nbsp
He can with my help.
We run as fast as we can.
&nbsp
You trail behind me,
siphon off some of my speed,
&nbsp
combine it with your own,
and when you have enough,
&nbsp
throw that thing deep into the Speed Force.
And that would work?
&nbsp
We need to find out.
Sure you're up for this, Flash?
&nbsp
You got it, Flash.
I'll let you know
when you reach optimal speed.
&nbsp
Ready... go!
Jay's moving really fast,
this might actually work.
&nbsp
Now, Barry!
In other legal news,
the highly publicized trial
&nbsp
of Jared Morillo, AKA
"Plunder," comes to a close.
&nbsp
Morillo was found guilty of grand theft
and aggravated assault after he
was caught by the Flash
&nbsp
robbing the Central City Museum
earlier this year.
&nbsp
Don't!
Please don't!
&nbsp
Don't do this.
Now, finally, I am free of you.
&nbsp
Barry, I love you.
No, don't say that, all right?
&nbsp
You're gonna be all right.
- I'm begging you, just...
- Barry!
&nbsp
You lose, Barry.
No!
&nbsp
Hey, hey, Iris.
Iris, hey...
&nbsp
No. Iris.
Iris, Iris...
&nbsp
Jay?
What the hell was that? Where was I?
&nbsp
The future.
I've never run to the future.
&nbsp
I've traveled to the past,
but I always came back to the present.
&nbsp
I saw myself.
And Iris.
&nbsp
And Savitar, what...
he killed her.
&nbsp
That's five months from now.
Is that actually gonna happen?
&nbsp
- I don't know.
- You don't...
&nbsp
You shouldn't have seen that.
This doesn't make sense, we...
&nbsp
we just got rid of the Philosopher's Stone.
I mean, Savitar shouldn't have
even been there!
&nbsp
Oh, my God.
This is why the newspaper
in the time vault changed.
&nbsp
The byline, this is why
it's not Iris, this...
&nbsp
Iris didn't write that story anymore
eight years from now, because...
&nbsp
She's dead.
Barry...
&nbsp
I just watched her die.
I saw myself try to save her,
but I wasn't fast enough.
&nbsp
Jay, tell me that this isn't my destiny.
What you saw was one
possibility of the future.
&nbsp
What may be, or may not.
Okay, then I can stop this from happening.
&nbsp
- I can run back there...
- You can't go back there.
&nbsp
Not again, not ever.
All right, then I'll figure
out exactly how it happened,
&nbsp
how we wind up on that street,
and I'll just make sure
that we don't go there.
&nbsp
- And if we don't go there...
- Barry!
&nbsp
This is why speedsters
don't travel to the future.
&nbsp
Nobody should know this much
about their own.
&nbsp
Just as their are infinite
Earths in the multiverse,
&nbsp
there are infinite possibilities
to the future.
&nbsp
It's always bending, always changing.
Every decision you make
creates another alternative.
&nbsp
I won't let Iris die.
The future isn't written yet.
&nbsp
And it might not even turn out
to be what you saw.
&nbsp
You need to focus on the here and now.
You have to live your life.
&nbsp
- Hey, guys.
- Hey.
&nbsp
Are you okay?
You and Jay disappeared, and...
&nbsp
Nah, I'm okay.
- I'm just glad to see you.
- So where's Jay?
&nbsp
Jay, uh, decided to
go ahead and go back to Earth-3.
&nbsp
But he wanted to wish everybody
a Merry Christmas.
&nbsp
So, it worked? The stone...
It's gone.
&nbsp
- It's lost in the Speed Force.
- Good, good.
&nbsp
I don't know about you guys,
but being mind-punked
&nbsp
by a speed god that we
piss off in the future,
&nbsp
it's... it's enough to kill
your Christmas spirit.
&nbsp
Guys, Christmas time is here.
We need a little Christmas.
&nbsp
Right this very minute. Who's with me?
- BA.
- Well, he's right.
&nbsp
It's Christmas, we should be together.
Let's have it.
&nbsp
I'm still in if everybody else is.
- Yes!
- Okay, we'll be there.
&nbsp
Yeah!
Julian...
&nbsp
Where's he going?
Hey, where are you going?
&nbsp
Do you have Christmas plans?
The West's are having
a Christmas get-together.
&nbsp
After what you've been through,
you shouldn't be alone.
&nbsp
I actually prefer to be alone at Christmas.
Rain on Christmas.
&nbsp
That's neither holly nor jolly.
Hey, listen, um...
&nbsp
about Dante.
Thank you for talking me off the ledge.
&nbsp
Of course, you'd do the same for me.
In fact, you did the same for me.
&nbsp
I was gonna say.
Caitlo... Caitlo, Ciscan...
&nbsp
okay... whoo... you got to try the eggnog
a holiday concoction done by Joe
&nbsp
and his hot girlfriend...
Babe.
&nbsp
- Hey.
- What's up?
&nbsp
- Nothing.
- You seem a little weird.
&nbsp
No?
You do know we won, right?
&nbsp
We defeated the bad guy.
- Yeah, I know.
- Okay.
&nbsp
- Grandma Esther.
- Grandma Millie.
&nbsp
Let's see.
Mm.
&nbsp
- Damn, that's strong.
- Oh!
&nbsp
So is that, my God!
Our grandmothers are alcoholics.
&nbsp
Yes.
You know, technically,
we don't have to be standing
&nbsp
under the mistletoe to... mm.
Finally.
&nbsp
No comments from the peanut gallery.
No, but really, it's about time.
&nbsp
Mm-hmm.
Hold on.
&nbsp
And it's my daughter.
ah, just give me a quick minute,
&nbsp
and then we can... yeah.
- Hey, kiddo...
- Joe.
&nbsp
I saw you kiss her, good job.
We're... oh, that's right, the thing.
&nbsp
BA, hey.
How many of those have you had?
&nbsp
- B... where'd you go? Here.
- I'm right here.
&nbsp
Oh, I see ya.
Now that Cecelia's away,
&nbsp
this is from all of us to you.
Merry Christmas, son.
&nbsp
- Are you serious?
- Yeah, man, it's time.
&nbsp
You're ready, Wallace.
Welcome to the team.
&nbsp
Kid Flash.
Are we really calling me "Kid Flash"?
&nbsp
Yeah, I think we are.
- Kid Flash!
- Shh!
&nbsp
- Police!
- I got it.
&nbsp
It's not the police. We're the police.
- You're the police!
- Calm down.
&nbsp
Hey, Julian.
- Hi.
- Come on in.
&nbsp
- Here, let me get that.
- Thanks.
&nbsp
Uh, after everything that happened,
being alone felt a bit lonely, so...
&nbsp
- Yeah.
- This is for you.
&nbsp
What's this?
I spoke to Captain Singh,
and he hadn't put through
&nbsp
your resignation paperwork yet, so...
well, if you'd, uh, you know,
like your old lab back,
&nbsp
or you'd like to share it again.
Thanks, Julian.
&nbsp
Merry Christmas, man.
- Cheers, mate.
- Yeah, thank you.
&nbsp
- Merry Christmas.
- Can I offer you some eggnog?
- I'd love some, yeah.
&nbsp
Happy Christmas, everyone.
- I'm glad you came.
- Thank you, yeah.
&nbsp
- Do you hear that?
- It's outside.
&nbsp
Caroling in the rain.
That sucks.
&nbsp
Hey.
- What're you doing?
- It's okay, I got this.
&nbsp
We may not be able to have
a perfect Christmas,
&nbsp
but we can have a white one.
So.
&nbsp
When are we gonna exchange presents?
How 'bout right now?
&nbsp
- Okay.
- Follow me.
&nbsp
- Okay.
- Let's get out of here.
&nbsp
Okay, going through a door, be careful.
Okay, right here.
&nbsp
- Okay, are you ready?
- Yeah.
&nbsp
All right.
Open your eyes...
&nbsp
now.
I... I don't understand, where are we?
&nbsp
Home.
What?
&nbsp
I couldn't sleep on Cisco's couch anymore,
and your place is sort of small for two,
&nbsp
so I signed a lease
and I put both of our names on it.
&nbsp
I got you a wallet.
I'm sure I'll love it.
&nbsp
Barry, this is a big step.
Not for me.
&nbsp
I don't know what's
gonna happen in the future.
&nbsp
All I know is, right here, right now,
I want to spend every moment I can with you.
&nbsp
You're the first thing I
want to see when I wake up.
&nbsp
And the last thing...
I love you, Barry Allen.
&nbsp
I love you, Iris West.