You're wondering
why I brought you all here.
After all, we just had a feast.
Since when does old Walder
give us two feasts
in a single fortnight?
Well, it's no good
being Lord of the Riverlands
if you can't celebrate
with your family.
That's what I say.
I've gathered every Frey
who means a thing
so I can tell you my plans
for this great house,
now that winter has come.
But first, a toast.
No more of
that Dornish horse piss.
This is the finest Arbor gold.
Proper wine for proper heroes.
Stand together.
Not you.
I'm not wasting good wine
on a woman.
Maybe I'm not
the most pleasant man.
I'll admit it.
But I'm proud of you lot.
You're my family.
The men who helped me slaughter
the Starks at the Red Wedding.
Yes. Yes.
Cheer.
Brave men. All of you.
Butchered a woman
pregnant with her babe.
Cut the throat
of a mother of five.
Slaughtered your guests after
inviting them into your home.
But you didn't slaughter
every one of the Starks.
No, no.
That was your mistake.
You should have ripped
them all out, root and stem.
Leave one wolf alive
and the sheep are never safe.
When people ask you
what happened here,
tell them the North remembers.
Tell them winter came
for House Frey.
Episode 1 - Dragonstone.
You wildlings?
I'm Meera Reed,
daughter of Howland Reed.
This is Brandon Stark,
son of Ned Stark.
And how do I know that's true?
You were at
the Fist of the First Men.
You were at Hardhome.
You've seen
the Army of the Dead.
You've seen the Night King.
He's coming for us.
For all of us.
All right, come on.
Let's get them inside.
I want every Northern maester
to scour their records for
any mention of dragonglass.
Dragonglass kills White Walkers,
it's more valuable to us now
than gold.
We need to find it,
we need to mine it,
we need to make weapons from it.
Everyone, aged 10 to 60,
will drill daily with spears,
pikes, bow and arrow.
It's about time we taught these
boys of summer how to fight.
Not just the boys.
We can't defend the North
if only
half the population is fighting.
You expect me to put a spear
in my granddaughter's hand?
I don't plan on knitting by
the fire while men fight for me.
I might be small, Lord Glover,
and I might be a girl,
but I am every bit as much
a Northerner as you.
Indeed you are, my lady.
No one is questioning...
And I don't need your permission
to defend the North.
We'll begin training every man,
woman, boy and girl
on Bear Island.
While we're preparing for attack
we need to shore up
our defences.
The only thing standing
between us
and the Army of the Dead
is the Wall,
and the Wall hasn't been
properly manned in centuries.
I'm not
the king of the free folk.
But if we're going to survive
this winter together...
You want us to man
the castles for you?
Aye.
Last time we saw the Night King
was at Hardhome.
The closest castle to Hardhome
is Eastwatch-by-the-Sea.
Then that's where I'll go.
Looks like
we're the Night's Watch now.
If they breach the Wall,
the first two castles
in their path
are Last Hearth and Karhold.
The Umbers and the Karstarks
betrayed the North.
Their castles
should be torn down,
with not a stone left standing.
The castles committed no crimes.
And we need
every fortress we have
for the war to come.
We should give the Last Hearth
and Karhold to new families,
loyal families who supported us
against Ramsay.
Aye.
The Umbers and the Karstarks
have fought beside the Starks
for centuries.
They've kept faith
for generation after generation.
And then they broke faith.
I'm not going to
strip these families
of their ancestral homes
because of the crimes of
a few reckless sons.
So, there's no punishment for treason
and no reward for loyalty?
The punishment for treason
is death.
Smalljon Umber died
on the field of battle.
Harald Karstark died
They died fighting for Ramsay.
Give the castles
to the families of the men
who died fighting for you.
When I was Lord Commander
of the Night's Watch,
I executed men who betrayed me.
I executed men
who refused to follow orders.
My father always said,
"The man who passes the sentence
should swing the sword,"
and I have tried to live
by those words.
But I will not punish a son
for his father's sins,
and I will not take
a family home away
from a family it has belonged to
for centuries.
That is my decision,
and my decision is final.
Ned Umber.
Alys Karstark.
For centuries, our families
fought side-by-side
on the battlefield.
I ask you to pledge your loyalty
once again to House Stark,
to serve as our Bannerman
and come to our aid
whenever called upon.
Stand.
Yesterday's wars
don't matter anymore.
The North
needs to band together,
all the living North.
Will you stand beside me,
Ned and Alys?
Now and always?
Now and always.
You are my sister,
but I am king now.
Will you start wearing a crown?
When you question my decisions
in front of the other lords
and ladies, you undermine me.
So, I can't question
your decisions anymore?
Of course you can, but...
Joffrey never let
anyone question his authority.
You think he was a good king?
Do you think I'm Joffrey?
You're as far from Joffrey
as anyone I've ever met.
Thank you.
You're good at this, you know.
At what?
At ruling.
- No.
- You are. You are.
They respect you,
they really do.
But you have to...
Why are you laughing?
What did Father used to say?
Everything before the word "but"
is horseshit.
He never said that to me.
No. No, he never cursed
in front of his girls.
Because he was trying
to protect us.
He never wanted us to see
how dirty the world really is,
but Father couldn't protect me
and neither can you.
Stop trying.
All right, I'll stop trying
to protect you,
and you stop trying to
undermine me.
I'm not trying to undermine you!
You have to be smarter
than Father.
You need to be smarter
than Robb.
I loved them, I miss them,
but they made stupid mistakes,
and they both
lost their heads for it.
And how should I be smarter?
By listening to you?
Would that be so terrible?
A raven from King's Landing,
Your Grace.
Cersei of House Lannister,
First of Her Name,
Queen of the Andals
and the First Men,
Protector of the Seven Kingdoms.
What does she want?
Come to King's Landing,
bend the knee or suffer the fate
of all traitors.
You've been so consumed
with the enemy to the north,
you've forgotten about
the one to the south.
I'm consumed with the Night King
because I've seen him.
And believe me, you'd think of
little else if you had, too.
We still have a wall between us
and the Night King.
There's nothing
between us and Cersei.
There's a thousand miles
Winter is here.
The Lannisters are
a Southern army.
They never range this far north.
You're the military man,
but I know her.
If you're her enemy,
she'll never stop
until she's destroyed you.
Everyone who's ever crossed her,
she's found a way to murder.
You almost sound
as if you admire her.
I learned a great deal from her.
What is this?
It's what we've been waiting for
our whole lives.
It's what Father trained us for,
whether he knew it or not.
He knew it.
Made me memorize
every city, town,
lake, forest and mountain.
It's ours now.
We just have to take it.
You've been quiet
since you came home.
- Are you angry with me?
- No, not angry.
Are you afraid of me?
Should I be?
Daenerys Targaryen has chosen
Tyrion to be her Hand.
Right now, they're sailing
across the Narrow Sea,
hoping to take back
her father's throne.
Our little brother,
the one you love so much,
the one you set free,
the one who murdered our father
and our first-born son.
Now he stands beside our enemies
and gives them counsel.
He's out there somewhere,
at the head of an armada.
Where will they land?
Dragonstone.
They have deep-water ports
for the ships.
Stannis left
the castle unoccupied,
and that's where she was born.
Enemies to the east.
Enemies to the south.
Ellaria Sand
and her brood
Enemies to the west.
Olenna, the old
Another traitor.
Enemies to the north.
Ned Stark's bastard has been
named King in the North
and that murdering Sansa,
stands beside him.
Enemies everywhere.
We're surrounded by traitors.
You're in command
of the Lannister army now.
- How do we proceed?
- Winter's here.
We can't win a war
if we can't
feed our men and our horses.
The Tyrells have the grain.
The Tyrells have the livestock.
Will the Tyrell Bannerman stand
alongside a Dothraki horde
and Unsullied slave soldiers?
If they think Daenerys will win.
No one wants to fight
on the losing side.
Right now,
we look like the losing side.
I'm the Queen
of the Seven Kingdoms.
Three kingdoms, at best.
I'm not sure you understand
how much danger we're in.
I understand
we're in a war for survival.
whoever loses, dies.
I understand whoever wins
could launch a dynasty
that lasts a thousand years.
A dynasty for whom?
Our children are dead.
We're the last of us.
A dynasty for us, then.
We never talked about Tommen.
There's nothing to say.
Our baby boy killed himself.
He betrayed me.
He betrayed us both.
Should we spend our days
mourning the dead,
Mother, Father,
and all our children?
- Cersei...
- I loved them. I did.
But they're ashes now,
and we're still flesh and blood.
We're the last Lannisters.
The last ones who count.
Even Lannisters can't survive
without allies.
Where are our allies now?
You saw what happened
to Walder Frey and his family.
I heard.
How could we ever trust
a man like that?
We couldn't.
He was a useless old coward.
But the Freys supported us.
Now they're all dead.
Whoever killed them
is no friend of ours.
We need allies.
Stronger, better allies.
We can't win this war alone.
Do you think I listened
to Father for 40 years
and learned nothing?
The Greyjoys...
You invited the Greyjoys
to King's Landing?
Not all of them.
Well, it looks like all of them.
I invited Euron Greyjoy,
the new
King of the Iron Islands.
You said yourself we needed
stronger, better allies.
There you are.
How are they better allies?
How are they
different from the Freys?
They both broke their promises
and murdered
their former friends
as soon as it suited them.
So does everyone,
when it suits them.
Unlike the Freys,
they have ships.
And they're good at killing.
They're not good at anything.
I know the Ironborn.
They're bitter,
angry little people.
All they know how to do
is steal things they can't build
or grow themselves.
Euron Greyjoy
didn't come here for that.
Oh, what did he come here for then?
A queen.
The moment I was chosen
Lord of the Iron Islands,
they turned on me.
Their own uncle.
They stole my best ships
and ran.
Sailed them
right across the world
and gave them
to the Dragon Queen
so she could bring her armies
here to attack you.
It's nothing
compared to the treason
you suffered
at the hands of a family member,
from what I hear.
But still, it bothers me.
Murdering them
would make me feel a lot better.
And since it appears that all
our treasonous family members
are fighting for the same side,
I thought we rightful monarchs
could murder them together.
You're not a rightful monarch,
though, are you?
The Greyjoys
rebelled against the throne
for the right to be monarchs.
But as I recall,
you were soundly defeated.
Come to mention it,
weren't you the one
who started that rebellion
by sailing to Casterly Rock
and burning the Lannister fleet?
You certainly caught us there.
Very smart move on your part.
Of course, we all made it
to the Iron Islands anyway.
I was there.
I remember very well.
I saw you.
I heard so much talk.
"The best in the world.
No one can stop him."
I didn't believe it,
to be honest.
But I must say, when you rushed
through the breach
and started cutting people down,
it was glorious.
Like a dance.
The people I was cutting down
were your own kin.
The place was getting crowded.
I enjoyed watching it.
I truly did.
And I enjoyed killing Greyjoys.
A good thing for me.
If you hadn't crushed us,
I wouldn't have gone into exile.
And if I hadn't done that,
I wouldn't be the greatest
captain in the 14 seas.
If not the most humble.
You're not humble.
You're the queen
of a great nation.
You don't care
about the Iron Islands.
They're nothing but rocks
and bird and...
And a lot of
very unattractive people.
The Iron Fleet,
on the other hand,
that's something else entirely.
It's the greatest armada
Westeros has ever seen.
With the Iron Fleet,
you own the seas.
You can defeat
the invaders in the East
and the pretenders
in the North and South.
What do you want in return?
Ever since I was a little boy,
I wanted to grow up and marry
the most beautiful woman
in the world.
So, here I am,
with a thousand ships
and two good hands.
I decline your proposal.
Why?
You're not trustworthy.
You've broken
promises to allies before
and murdered them
at the nearest opportunity.
You murdered your own brother.
You should try it.
Feels wonderful.
I don't expect you
to trust me outright.
You need proof
of my honest intentions.
In my experience,
the surest way to
a woman's heart is with a gift.
A priceless gift.
I won't return to King's Landing
until I have that for you.
Ah, Maester Weyland.
A drinker's liver
if ever I saw one.
Weigh that.
The triumph
of transitory pleasures.
Mankind's curse.
Archmaester,
I was wondering...
- What's the weight?
- Um...
A hundred and forty-seven.
I was wondering if
you'd considered my proposition.
I don't remember
your proposition.
I asked you if,
in light of what
I'd seen in the North,
if I could have access to the
restricted area of the library.
That area is reserved
for maesters.
- Are you a maester?
- No.
Not a very strong proposition,
is it?
Archmaester, with respect,
I've seen them.
The Army of the Dead.
The White Walkers.
I was sent here to learn
how to defeat them,
but everyone in the Citadel,
those who'll even talk to me,
they all doubt the Walkers
ever existed in the first place.
Everyone in the Citadel
doubts everything.
It's their job.
But the tales of the Long Night
can't be pure fabrication.
Too many similarities from
unconnected sources.
Sources in the restricted area?
The very same.
And the simplest explanation
for your grating obsession
with the White Walkers is that
you're telling the truth,
and that you saw
what you say you saw.
So, you believe me.
I do.
You'll finish
weighing that heart?
That makes you the only person
south of the Twins who does.
We're not like the people
south of the Twins.
And we're not like the people
north of the Twins.
In the Citadel,
we lead different lives
for different reasons.
We are this world's memory,
Samwell Tarly.
Without us, men would be
little better than dogs.
Don't remember any meal
but the last.
Can't see forward to any
but the next.
And every time you leave
the house and shut the door,
they howl
like you're gone forever.
When Robert's Rebellion
was raging,
people thought the end was near.
The end
of the Targaryen dynasty.
"How will we survive?"
When Aegon Targaryen
turned his eye westward,
and flew his dragons
to Blackwater Rush.
"The end is near!
How will we survive?"
And thousands of years before
that, during the Long Night,
we can forgive them for
thinking it truly was the end.
But it wasn't. None of it was.
The Wall has stood
through it all.
And every winter that ever came
has ended.
Be a good lad. Clean this up.
No.
You're a lucky man.
I've heard she beat
the Hound in single combat.
She's a very impressive woman.
What do you want, Lord Baelish?
I want you to be happy.
I want you to be safe.
I am safe.
I'm at home,
surrounded by friends.
I have Brienne to protect me
from anyone who would harm me.
What about happy?
Why aren't you happy?
What do you want
that you do not have?
At the moment, peace and quiet.
No need to seize the last word,
Lord Baelish.
I'll assume
it was something clever.
My lady.
Why is he still here?
We need his men.
Without the Vale,
Ramsay Bolton
would still hold this castle.
Littlefinger saved us.
He wants something.
I know exactly what he wants.
He rode through
the streets of the city
Down from his hill on high
O'er the wynds
and the steps and the cobbles
He rode to a woman's sigh
For she was his secret treasure
She was his shame and his bliss
And a chain and a keep
are nothing
Compared to a woman's kiss
For hands of gold
are always cold
But a woman's hands are warm
For hands of gold
are always cold
But a woman's hands are...
That's a pretty song.
I've never heard it before.
It's a new one.
Are you hungry?
We've got some rabbit.
I don't want to steal your food.
You're not stealing.
We're offering.
Come on,
it's gonna be a cold night.
You heading south?
King's Landing.
Poor girl.
It's not so bad, is it?
Depends on your taste, I guess.
If you like your streets
covered in and pig's blood,
it's the town for you.
All my life I wanted to see
the Red Keep,
the Sept of Baelor,
the Dragonpit.
Then when I finally make it,
they wouldn't let me within
a mile of the Red Keep,
the Sept of Baelor's
blown to hell,
and the Dragonpit
is a ruin.
The people who live there,
they'd skin you alive
if they could make two coppers
off your hide.
Worst place in the world.
What are you doing
in the Riverlands?
There's been some trouble
with the Freys up at the Twins.
So, we're part of the army
that's been sent to
keep the peace.
Here you go.
Guests first.
Oh, no, I couldn't.
You don't have enough.
Well, my mother always told me
to be kind to strangers
and strangers will be
kind to you.
You're a long way from home.
I'm sure you've had
some adventures, though.
Yeah, endless adventures.
They'll be singing
about us for a thousand years.
The truth is when we left home,
we couldn't wait to get away.
And now that
we've been gone a while,
we can't wait to get home.
I just think about my dad
out there on his boat all alone.
I ought to be
out there with him.
My wife just had our first baby.
Boy or girl?
Oh, who knows?
You think soldiers get ravens
with news from home?
I hope it's a girl.
Why?
Girls take care of their papas
when their papas grow old.
Boys just go off to fight
in someone else's wars.
Are you old enough to drink?
It's blackberry wine.
I made it myself.
It's really good.
So, why's a nice girl on her own
heading to King's Landing?
I'm going to kill the queen.
Bad night to be outdoors.
You've got real powerful magic
to figure that out.
Did the Lord of Light
whisper that in your ear?
"It's snowing, Thoros."
"It's windy.
It's gonna be a cold night."
You're a grouchy
old bear, aren't you, Clegane?
You want some rum?
Don't like that
It's too sweet.
Why you always
in such a foul mood?
Experience.
This seems like a good place
to spend the night.
These people don't want us here.
Seems deserted to me.
No livestock.
No smoke
coming from the chimney.
I don't like the look of it.
For a big, hard man,
you scare easy.
I'll tell you
what doesn't scare me.
Bald cocksuckers like you.
You think you're fooling anyone
with that top knot?
Bald
Come on.
Maybe they got some ale
hidden away.
They don't.
See if there's a larder.
They always
leave something behind.
How do you think
it ended for them?
With death.
Girl died in her father's arms.
Both of them covered in blood,
and a knife at their feet.
I'd say they were starving.
And rather than
let his little girl suffer,
he ended it for both of them.
- Doesn't matter now.
- No.
Doesn't matter now.
I've known you
a long time, Dondarrion.
Aye. I think
the first time we met
was at that tournament.
And I always thought
you were dull as dirt.
You're not bad.
I don't hate you.
Don't like you,
but you're not bad.
Thank you, Clegane.
That warms the heart.
But there's nothing special
about you.
You're right about that.
So, why does the Lord of Light
keep bringing you back?
I've met better men than you,
and they've been hanged
from crossbeams or beheaded
or just shat themselves to death
in a field somewhere.
None of them came back.
So, why you?
You think
I don't ask myself that?
Every hour of every day?
Why am I here?
What am I supposed to do?
What does the Lord see in me?
And?
I don't know.
I don't understand our Lord.
Your Lord.
I don't know
what he wants from me.
I only know that
he wants me alive.
If he's so all-powerful,
why doesn't he just tell you
what he wants?
Clegane. Come over here.
Don't worry.
The fire won't bite.
I want to show you something.
It's my luck I end up
with a band of fire worshippers.
Aye. Almost seems like
divine justice.
There's no divine justice,
you dumb
If there was, you'd be dead.
And that girl would be alive.
What do you want?
Look into the flames.
I don't want to look
in the flames.
You saw me bring him back
from the dead
after you cut him down.
Don't you want to know
what gave me the power?
I keep asking,
and no one wants to tell me.
We can't tell you.
Only the fire can tell you.
What do you see?
- Logs burning.
- Keep looking.
What do you see?
Ice.
A wall of ice.
The Wall.
What else?
It's where
the Wall meets the sea.
There's a castle there.
There's a mountain.
Looks like an arrowhead.
The dead are marching past.
Thousands of them.
Do you believe me now, Clegane?
Do you believe
we're here for a reason?
What the hell
are you doing, Clegane?
Burying the dead.
You knew these people.
Not really.
We ask the Father
to judge us with mercy.
We ask the Mother to...
I don't remember the rest.
I'm sorry you're dead.
You deserved better.
Both of you.
Mom.
You should really sleep, Sam.
The dead don't.
"Legends of the Long Night."
The Targaryens used dragonglass
to decorate their weapons,
without even knowing
what the First Men used it for.
What is it?
It's a map of Dragonstone.
The Targaryens built
their first stronghold there
when they invaded Westeros.
That's dragonglass.
A mountain of it.
Beneath the ground.
Stannis told me,
but I didn't think...
This is important.
Jon needs to know.
- Has she come yet?
- Who?
The Dragon Queen.
Daenerys Stormborn.
Haven't heard anything.
Shall we begin?