My name is Barry Allen,
&nbsp
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world, I'm
an ordinary forensic scientist,
&nbsp
but secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
&nbsp
I fight crime and find
other meta-humans like me.
&nbsp
In an attempt to stop
the evil speedster Savitar,
&nbsp
I was accidentally thrust into the future,
and I saw him murder the woman I love.
&nbsp
But I won't let that happen.
I'm going to do everything in my power
&nbsp
to change the future, and I'm the only one
fast enough to keep her alive.
&nbsp
I am The Flash.
Previously on "The Flash"...
&nbsp
You wanna open S.T.A.R. Labs to the public?
In two weeks?
Soft open.
&nbsp
- I'm Alchemy.
- Turning innocent people
&nbsp
into meta-humans worshipping the Savitar?
An article used to be written
by Iris West-Allen.
&nbsp
Something's changed with our future.
- Barry.
- No!
&nbsp
What you saw was
one possibility of the future.
&nbsp
Then I can stop this from happening.
I... I don't understand. Where are we?
&nbsp
Home. I don't know...
what's gonna happen in the future.
&nbsp
All I know is right here, right now,
I wanna spend every moment I can with you.
&nbsp
Don't!
- Don't do this!
- Barry...
&nbsp
You lose, Barry.
No!
&nbsp
Babe, are you okay?
- Yeah...
- Yeah.
&nbsp
Just a bad dream.
Go back to sleep.
&nbsp
Yeah, sure. I'm not completely wide awake
after hearing you scream in your sleep.
&nbsp
You wanna talk about it?
No, you know what I wanna do?
&nbsp
Hmm.
I wanna unpack.
&nbsp
It's been a month.
Do not change the subject, Bartholomew.
&nbsp
- Bartholomew?
- Mm-hmm.
&nbsp
Am I in trouble?
Well, this is the third night in a row.
&nbsp
I know something else that's happened
three nights in a row.
&nbsp
It's a fire.
Richmond Heights.
&nbsp
Go, Wally's gonna beat you there.
- What?
- I just...
&nbsp
I just really love you.
Detective Patterson just ran inside.
&nbsp
He hasn't come out yet.
The fire department will not
&nbsp
make it here on time.
Help!
&nbsp
I'm trapped in here!
We gotta get him out of here.
&nbsp
This place is up in flames any second.
You see the soot around this door?
&nbsp
- Yeah.
- 'Cause the fire has
&nbsp
no ventilation, so if we open the door now,
the sudden inrush of oxygen
will cause an explosion.
&nbsp
Help!
Okay, so what do we do?
&nbsp
Create an exit point
for the heat and smoke,
&nbsp
and remove all the oxygen at the same time.
- Which will put out the fire.
- Help me!
&nbsp
When I say so, open the door, all right?
Now.
&nbsp
Flash, thanks.
Two of 'em.
&nbsp
Synced and corrected by oykubuyuk
www.addic7ed.com
&nbsp
Oh, man, that was so dope.
How do you stay so calm?
&nbsp
You're like scary calm
in the middle of a fight.
&nbsp
It's just experience, Wally.
That's why it's important for
you to shadow me for a while,
&nbsp
and try to learn everything I know.
And then I get to kick some ass.
&nbsp
Let me give you some advice, Wally.
Being a superhero's not about kicking ass.
&nbsp
Well... nope, actually
that's a straight-up lie.
&nbsp
There's a lot of ass-kicking involved.
Just keep doing what you're doing...
&nbsp
watching me. You're doing great.
I gotta go to breakfast with Dad,
&nbsp
but I'll catch up with you guys later.
Yo, that's where... mm... [grumbles] Nope.
&nbsp
- You okay?
- My suit goes there.
&nbsp
Ah, two suits, one mannequin.
That is what we call a conundrum.
&nbsp
No, I...
Hey, are you okay?
&nbsp
Yeah, these things have just
been on the fritz lately.
&nbsp
It makes me feel like a criminal.
Hasn't been on the fritz, okay?
&nbsp
Uh, maybe if you charge
the battery, like I told you to.
&nbsp
Oh, I'm just supposed to
hook myself up to an outlet,
&nbsp
like I'm some sort of human tablet?
Either you charge the cuffs,
&nbsp
or you go all Frozone on us again.
Or... you could fix them for me?
&nbsp
Or I could fix 'em.
- Sumptuous day, brethren.
- Oh, boy.
&nbsp
- Good morning, H.R.
- Oh, not just good.
&nbsp
It's g-r-r-eat, and why is that?
Because I'm finally ready to announce
&nbsp
that the new S.T.A.R. Labs museum
is ready for its opening...
&nbsp
soft opening... so come.
Let's take the tour.
&nbsp
This could've been avoided.
You know that, right?
&nbsp
Mm-hmm.
I just don't see why
you're defending the yellow guy.
&nbsp
Yes, he goes everywhere The Flash goes,
but this morning, for example,
he's just standing back,
&nbsp
waiting for the warehouse to burn down.
Well, maybe he's training with The Flash.
&nbsp
- You know, learning the ropes?
- Okay, well, we send
&nbsp
rookie cops out on patrol,
expect them to perform.
&nbsp
Look, I think the yellow guy's
gonna surprise you.
&nbsp
Once he gains a little bit of experience,
he's gonna give The Flash
a run for his money.
&nbsp
You know what I think? I think
maybe he's just not that fast.
&nbsp
- Or maybe he's just a coward.
- You don't get paid to think.
&nbsp
- And Kid Flash ain't no coward.
- Kid Flash? Okay.
&nbsp
There it is. The name says it all.
Hey, I say we just send him to Keystone.
&nbsp
We already have a Flash.
Wally.
&nbsp
- Did you hear any of that?
- Any of what?
&nbsp
Nothing, it was just a cop being stupid.
- Take you to breakfast?
- Please.
&nbsp
- Behold.
- Whoa!
&nbsp
- You did all this?
- Yeah.
&nbsp
Well, I don't wanna take all the credit.
I'm too modest to do that, but yeah.
&nbsp
Uh, who exactly is paying for all this?
That's a great question.
&nbsp
Olga!
Allow me to introduce you
to your new coworkers.
&nbsp
Everybody, this is Olga.
- Da.
- Hi.
&nbsp
Oh, and she doesn't really
speak English so much,
&nbsp
but she's great. So right over here,
we have the ticketing and the admissions.
&nbsp
Over there, our specialty coffees...
Oh, uh, that reminds me. Caitlin...
&nbsp
Initially, I had you targeted for ticketing,
but it occurs to me,
with a few lessons in foam art,
&nbsp
you could very well man up...
excuse me... woman up
&nbsp
our cappuccino stand. What do you think?
H.R., I think Caitlin's gonna
have plenty to do as it is.
&nbsp
Can I ask you a question?
Do you want to eat pizza pockets
for every meal
&nbsp
for the rest of your life?
You don't; nobody wants that.
&nbsp
What you want is an income,
and we collectively need a cover
for S.T.A.R. Labs
&nbsp
for our continued operation.
He makes some good points.
&nbsp
Now for the pièce de résistance...
Welcome to S.T.A.R. Labs.
&nbsp
I'm sorry, did you make a hologram of me?
Oh, Francisco, you made it perfectly clear
&nbsp
you didn't want to be a tour guide.
You're not. You're a virtual tour guide.
&nbsp
Guess what. That falls under the umbrella
of not wanting to be a tour guide.
&nbsp
- On we go.
- My name is Francisco Ramon.
&nbsp
I wasn't always the esteemed
engineer you see before you.
&nbsp
It was my love of science
that allowed me to overcome
my tough upbringing
&nbsp
and join S.T.A.R. Labs, before our beautiful
and handsome founder,
Harrison Wells, stepped down.
&nbsp
I hope my love of science
will inspire some among you
&nbsp
to join the scientific community.
- Wow.
- Thanks.
&nbsp
Here's the thing.
I don't sound anything like that.
&nbsp
My love of science... my love of science...
- Uh-oh.
- My...love...of...science.
&nbsp
Yeah, I'm gonna need you
to take a look at that.
&nbsp
I can't do it...
'Cause I have important things to do, so...
&nbsp
- Oh, wha... oh, hey! Ugh!
- Right now, so...
&nbsp
Guys, I gotta run an errand. See ya later.
Where you going?
&nbsp
- Ah, hello you.
- Hey.
&nbsp
Am I in for another kidnapping?
Okay, I deserve that.
&nbsp
No, um, I just came to check on you.
We haven't seen much of you since Christmas.
&nbsp
That's very sweet of you.
I'm doing well, thank you.
&nbsp
You know, what Savitar did...
forcing you to hurt people...
&nbsp
Savitar was controlling me, okay?
As far as I'm concerned,
my conscience is clear.
&nbsp
Really?
Then why the Zolpidem?
Are you having trouble sleeping?
&nbsp
Why don't we stop playing games, Dr. Snow,
and you tell me what you actually came for
&nbsp
rather than accusing me of having insomnia?
I actually need your help.
&nbsp
How can I help you?
Well, you're the world's
foremost specialist
&nbsp
- on meta-humans...
- Yes, this much is true.
&nbsp
And I need you to help me
get rid of my powers.
&nbsp
I've tried everything.
I've run every test... blood, DNA...
&nbsp
and I can't reverse this.
I need to get rid of my powers before...
&nbsp
Before what?
Before I hurt someone else...
the way I hurt you.
&nbsp
I don't cure meta-humans.
I put them in prison.
&nbsp
You're on your own, I'm afraid.
No, no, no, no.
&nbsp
Please.
Okay.
&nbsp
Can I open my eyes yet please?
Um, yeah, but just one second.
&nbsp
- Okay.
- Just, um...
&nbsp
yeah... okay, open 'em.
Um...
&nbsp
I know you wanted to unpack slowly,
like a normal couple, but I don't know...
&nbsp
between our jobs and
the S.T.A.R. Labs museum and...
&nbsp
do you hate it?
Uh, n-no, no, I don't hate it.
&nbsp
You do. I just... I don't...
I just wanna give you
the home that you deserve.
&nbsp
- I...
- Barry, you have.
&nbsp
I love our loft.
Look... what I don't love
&nbsp
is you not talking to me
about these nightmares.
&nbsp
I don't know. I mean, I've seen
a lot of terrible things in my life.
&nbsp
The nightmares, they're just a part of me.
Yeah, but, Barry, I have been with you
&nbsp
through all those terrible things.
This is different.
&nbsp
It feels different.
What are you not telling me?
&nbsp
I'm sorry.
Oh, that's a robbery in progress.
&nbsp
That is a robbery in progress.
I'm sorry.
&nbsp
Go.
See, I'm living with someone now,
&nbsp
so I can't have criminals
constantly interrupting
&nbsp
our alone time.
Flash.
&nbsp
Morillo was found guilty
of grand theft and aggravated assault
&nbsp
after he was caught by The Flash.
That gun.
&nbsp
I've never seen anything
like that in my life.
&nbsp
- I want a gun like that.
- What happened out there?
&nbsp
Your telemetry readings
dropped precipitously.
&nbsp
I don't know, but...
It caught me off-guard.
&nbsp
I've gotta run an errand.
I'll be right back.
&nbsp
Okay, so we're up against
a guy with a futuristic rifle
&nbsp
that steals jewelry and looks like a pirate.
A pirate. Right, then...
&nbsp
we shall call this scurvy lad boy
the name of Plunder. Plunder, agreed?
&nbsp
Jared Morillo, aka Plunder...
Okay, aren't you supposed
to be working on, like,
&nbsp
- your museum, or something?
- Aren't you supposed to be
&nbsp
helping me, Francisco, with me hologram?
Um, that's not my problem.
&nbsp
Yeah, I just wanna show you something.
Why do I feel like
I'm walking into a trap?
&nbsp
Anyway, I'm gonna get CCPD to monitor
all the jewelry stores in the city.
&nbsp
This guys must be pretty full of himself,
knowing he escaped The Flash,
so ten to one, he'll be back.
&nbsp
- All right.
- When he is,
&nbsp
we'll be ready for him,
though, right, Barry?
&nbsp
No, not we, Wally.
This... you're still training.
&nbsp
Have you seen my times
in the Speed Lab lately?
&nbsp
- I'm almost as fast as you.
- Okay, this isn't about speed.
&nbsp
This is about gaining
knowledge and experience,
&nbsp
so please just trust me, all right?
Look, I am as overprotective
a father as you can get,
&nbsp
but I gotta be honest, Barry,
I'm... I agree with Wally.
&nbsp
I don't know, Joe.
Let's just see what else
&nbsp
we can find on this guy
before we let Wally loose.
&nbsp
Okay, well, remember, the best way
to teach somebody something is
to throw them in the deep end.
&nbsp
That's how I taught you how to swim.
That was... I'm still mad about that.
&nbsp
You can swim now, can't you?
Yeah.
&nbsp
Got your text.
Hi. Come and take a seat.
&nbsp
Look, I... I know I was... rude yesterday.
Yeah, you were a world-class jerk.
&nbsp
Yeah, there is a reason.
Because you are a world-class jerk?
&nbsp
Fair enough.
Listen, I've been trying
really hard not to think
&nbsp
about my alter ego, about what he did,
and seeing you, it just...
&nbsp
it brought it all back.
Look.
&nbsp
What Alchemy did was not your fault.
Yeah.
&nbsp
Tell that to Dave Frieman,
Ben Edwards, Jorge Gonzales.
&nbsp
These men were part of the CCPD task force
that Savitar murdered.
&nbsp
I should've died, not them.
Julian, what you're feeling,
it's completely normal.
&nbsp
It's called survivor's guilt.
But it wasn't your fault, okay?
&nbsp
You're a victim too.
I... I tortured people
&nbsp
and nearly killed my best friends.
I didn't ask for these powers,
&nbsp
just like you didn't ask
to be used by Savitar.
&nbsp
Yeah.
I just don't know how to move forward.
&nbsp
Why don't you come join us
at S.T.A.R. Labs?
&nbsp
You can help Team Flash fight meta-humans.
- You're being serious?
- Yeah.
&nbsp
Barry and the team,
they'd be thrilled to have you.
&nbsp
I would be thrilled to have you.
Ah, I'll give it some thought.
&nbsp
Uh, thanks for coming.
Tell me why I'm in here
fixing your hologram.
&nbsp
Well, I'm just so persuasive.
As a matter of fact,
&nbsp
my partner on my Earth,
Randolf, used to say,
&nbsp
"Why, H.R., you could convince a cowboy
to buy dirt in a sandstorm." Cappuccino?
&nbsp
Didn't you just have one of those?
Oh, yeah.
&nbsp
Look, I gotta order
more parts for this thing.
&nbsp
Yeah, no, go ahead. Price is no object.
Mm.
&nbsp
- Hey.
- How's it going?
&nbsp
You know, S.T.A.R. Labs museum,
gift that keeps on giving, so...
&nbsp
- Okay.
- Barry, cappuccino.
&nbsp
- Hi, uh, no... uh, good.
- Okay... all right.
&nbsp
- Sorry.
- You know I'll double down.
&nbsp
- Yeah, no...
- Sure.
&nbsp
Um, I just actually wanted
to ask you something...
&nbsp
- Mm-hmm.
- About your scientific, uh,
&nbsp
- romance novels?
- Oh, my novels, yeah, sure.
&nbsp
Please, ha... have a seat, yeah.
Okay.
&nbsp
Ask any... anything you want. Any questions.
- Yep... all right, cool.
- Yeah.
&nbsp
Um, well, I was just wondering
if you've ever written about time travel.
&nbsp
But more specifically
traveling to the future.
&nbsp
Oh, no, my best seller... oh, hey,
"The Future Ain't What It Used to Be"...
&nbsp
that was...
it was all about...
it was all about this guy
&nbsp
who's actively trying
to prevent his own murder.
&nbsp
Won the Nebula Award. It's well-received.
- Wow.
- Yeah.
&nbsp
Um, so this character... your character...
uh, was he able to change his future?
&nbsp
More specifically, if he allowed
certain events to occur naturally,
&nbsp
was he only cementing the very timeline
that resulted in a horrible event later?
&nbsp
There were two schools of thought.
One faction... one group
of fans... they believed,
&nbsp
you know, the future's ever-changing.
You know, it's not fixed, and so
&nbsp
you could make of the future
anything you wish.
&nbsp
- Right.
- Another group of fans
&nbsp
vehemently disagreed with it.
They said, "No, no, no.
&nbsp
"The future is fixed,
and you can't change it
&nbsp
no matter how hard you try."
Mm-hmm. Where do you come down?
&nbsp
On a fixed or ever-changing future?
Well, I think that a man
often meets his destiny
&nbsp
on the very road he takes to avoid it.
- Meaning?
- Meaning...
&nbsp
the future is fixed.
- Yeah.
- Yo, there's a robbery
&nbsp
at the Payson Hotel.
- Go.
- Yeah.
&nbsp
Hey.
Bring that chopper back.
&nbsp
You just couldn't resist
another heist, huh?
&nbsp
Oh, what's the fun in one and done?
Avoiding a 15-year jail sentence
&nbsp
in Iron Heights would've been nice,
but you're forcing my hand.
&nbsp
I guess it's a little late for that now.
Eh, guess again.
&nbsp
Barry, behind you!
I can't shake these things, Cisco.
&nbsp
- Shake faster.
- Huh?
&nbsp
He means phase.
Barry, what are you waiting for?
&nbsp
After he was caught by The Flash...
Watch out!
&nbsp
No, Wally.
I caught that whole thing, man.
&nbsp
Anything you wanna say to camera?
Oh, for real?
&nbsp
Uh, what up, Central City?
The name's Kid Flash.
&nbsp
Wally, congratulations.
- That was amazing.
- Great job, Wally.
&nbsp
- Kid Flash! Let 'em know.
- Whoo!
&nbsp
That's how it's done.
We just deposited Plunder in Iron Heights.
&nbsp
- Yes, you did.
- His real name is
&nbsp
Jared Morillo. Turns out he's wanted
for a string of robberies
from here to Star City.
&nbsp
Wally, what was that?
I mean, you're supposed to be shadowing me.
&nbsp
Wait, you're mad at me? I thought...
Observe and learn. That's it.
&nbsp
- Whoa.
- That's it!
&nbsp
Barry, ease up.
Wally just saved your life.
&nbsp
I'm sorry, Wally, but if you
can't learn to follow orders,
&nbsp
this deal between us, it's over.
Okay. Who's ready for...
&nbsp
oh, man. Wallace, B.A.,
you're supposed to be dressed
for the museum opening.
&nbsp
H.R., we're speedsters. We have time.
- Nobody likes a braggart.
- Yeah, but we were actually
&nbsp
talking about something
important before you showed up,
&nbsp
- so...
- You...
&nbsp
Okay, you clean up well...
Thank you.
&nbsp
I like the way you dress.
Guys, this is a very, very
big deal for all of us.
&nbsp
Come on! Don't be late to the part-ay!
Wally.
&nbsp
Look, I'm gonna go over to CCPD
and fill out this Morillo paperwork.
&nbsp
Whatever the reasoning you have,
for ragging on Wally,
&nbsp
- please get over it.
- Mm.
&nbsp
Caitlin, where is everybody? Nobody's here.
No one showed up.
&nbsp
Ah! A custom... our first customers!
Welcome. Welcome to the grand
&nbsp
S.T.A.R. Labs museum opening,
and today, for your ticket price
of admission...
&nbsp
today only... you also get
a free steaming cup of joe.
&nbsp
- Ticket price?
- Yep.
&nbsp
I thought this museum was free.
Oh, did you find us
through social media? 'Cause...
&nbsp
Welcome... welcome...
- Olga!
- Da.
&nbsp
The thing... it's doing the thing.
Folks, no... wait, do... oh!
&nbsp
Wait... no, wait, half-price!
Half! Quarter...
&nbsp
I'll make a new pot of coffee.
- Don't bother.
- No one's coming.
&nbsp
This isn't working. I don't know why.
You see this?
&nbsp
Do you see what you've done, H.R.?
You have distracted us for months, so what?
&nbsp
So that you could feel useful?
You're not useful.
&nbsp
This museum isn't useful.
You know what?
&nbsp
- That's mean.
- Yeah, well, I guess
&nbsp
I learned that from your doppelganger,
and at least he contributed something.
&nbsp
Uh, guys, there's another customer.
Hey, welcome to S...
ah, it's Julius, you guys.
&nbsp
What are you doing here?
Well, uh, I've given it some thought,
&nbsp
and I'd like to accept your invitation.
Invitation for what?
&nbsp
Did you ask Julian
to join Team S.T.A.R. Labs?
&nbsp
I know, he's an acquired taste, but...
Yeah, well, he is Dr. Alchemy,
&nbsp
the big bad's little bad, so...
Yeah, he... he gave Wally his powers.
&nbsp
- That, I don't mind.
- Guys, I need his help.
&nbsp
I'm sorry, Cisco, but these
cuffs, they aren't cutting it.
&nbsp
Every night, when I go to bed,
I'm afraid that I'm gonna wake up...
&nbsp
be her.
Maybe Julian can think
of something that we haven't.
&nbsp
Barry... when your mom was murdered,
Joe and Iris, they took you in.
&nbsp
Cisco, when Dante died,
I slept on your couch to keep you company.
&nbsp
The things we see,
the things that we face...
&nbsp
no one can do this alone.
Trying is the biggest mistake
that you can make.
&nbsp
He hasn't told anyone
that Barry's The Flash.
&nbsp
I think we can give him a chance.
Tell Julian we'll think
about it, all right?
&nbsp
- Iris...
- Hey.
&nbsp
I need to show you something.
- I forgot this place existed.
- Yeah.
&nbsp
The original Wells
used to call it his time vault.
&nbsp
I've been coming down here a lot lately.
I guess I've become
as obsessed with the future
&nbsp
as he once was.
After Flashpoint happened,
this article reappeared.
&nbsp
"Flash Missing...
Vanishes In Crisis."
&nbsp
Julie Greer, April 25, 2024.
I d...
&nbsp
The byline used to read "Iris West-Allen."
The future's changed.
&nbsp
So maybe I quit my job.
Yeah, that's what I'd hoped
at first too, or something,
&nbsp
but I...
Look, Iris, I'm sorry
I didn't tell you this sooner.
&nbsp
When I threw the Philosopher's
Stone into the Speed Force,
&nbsp
I accidentally ran to the future.
I saw Savitar murder you.
&nbsp
And I saw myself, and I...
I wasn't fast enough to save you.
&nbsp
Barry, no... I mean, we...
We destroyed the Stone.
Savitar's gone, so...
&nbsp
Maybe not. I...
I don't know. I don't know. Maybe not.
&nbsp
Is that why you keep having nightmares?
You keep seeing me?
&nbsp
So what does this have to do with Plunder?
He was already in jail in the future,
&nbsp
so I don't know.
I thought if I didn't catch him,
&nbsp
that I could stop the timeline
from cementing.
&nbsp
I could prevent your death. I don't know.
Barry, you cannot stop
protecting the city to save me.
&nbsp
Why? Um, why not?
I'm sorry. Uh, one robber goes free.
&nbsp
It's that versus your life.
Joe would want me to make
the exact same choice, Iris.
&nbsp
He...
Iris.
&nbsp
- How long?
- How long what?
&nbsp
How long until it happens?
This is not gonna happen.
&nbsp
Hey, look at me. This is not gonna happen.
Jay said that your death is
just one possible future, okay?
&nbsp
So that gives us four months to figure out
how to stop Savitar.
&nbsp
I swear, on both my parents' lives,
I will protect you.
&nbsp
We can't do this alone, Barry.
Hey, guys, um...
&nbsp
Iris and I, um...
we have something we need to tell you.
&nbsp
So you're saying that
four months from now,
&nbsp
- Savitar will...
- Kill me.
&nbsp
Possi... possibly.
It's okay. Guys, I am okay. Really.
&nbsp
- How are you gonna tell Dad?
- I'm not.
&nbsp
Iris, he needs to know.
I agree with Wallace. Joe needs to know.
&nbsp
No, guys, this news would blind him, okay?
We all saw how crazy he went
when Wally was in danger.
&nbsp
Imagine if he knew that
Savitar was trying to kill me.
&nbsp
He would go after Savitar himself.
Wally...
&nbsp
The future isn't set. There's still hope.
But, Barry, the future,
&nbsp
it's harder to change than you can imagine.
The future wants to happen.
The way it was explained to me
&nbsp
was, imagine if you had
a row of dominos, okay?
&nbsp
Now, those dominos are
all set up, and it... it's...
&nbsp
Here.
So convenient... yeah...
uh, Barry, if you wou...
&nbsp
So imagine, okay,
domino... each domino is a moment in time.
&nbsp
One moment in time leads to the next,
so as one domino falls, it hits the next,
&nbsp
it hits the next, and the next,
and the next, and so on,
&nbsp
leading to the inevitable
conclusion, and that is...
&nbsp
The future.
And what happens
if we alter certain events?
&nbsp
Well, you... you could conceivably
change where you end up, but...
&nbsp
but, Barry, if you would...
So you could change the future,
&nbsp
but you'd have to be very careful
about which events...
&nbsp
you alter.
We need to figure out
everything that happens
&nbsp
leading up to Iris's death.
Wait, when I saw the future,
there was a news scroll on TV.
&nbsp
I mean, that could offer us some clues.
Absolutely. I think I can help with that.
&nbsp
Hang on, McFly.
About to vibe you back to the future.
&nbsp
Can you pass me the multi-meter please?
Yeah.
&nbsp
- The multi-meter.
- Yep.
&nbsp
- The multi-meter?
- Yeah.
&nbsp
I'm better with the tools of the scribe.
There it is.
&nbsp
You sure your buddy Randolf
back home didn't just
&nbsp
solve that cryptogram to get rid of you?
Well, perhaps he did.
&nbsp
Look, I came to this Earth
seeking redemption,
&nbsp
but I realize now, you're right.
Greatness isn't in the cards for me.
&nbsp
Okay.
So you failed.
So nobody came to your opening.
&nbsp
Don't end it like this.
Greatness takes time...
&nbsp
and you know this.
If a string is in a knot,
patience will untie it.
&nbsp
Patience can do lots of things.
Have you ever tried it?
&nbsp
All right.
All right, guys. You ready?
&nbsp
- Yeah.
- Yeah, we're ready.
&nbsp
The machine's souped up and ready to go.
It's gonna be a hell of a vibe.
&nbsp
All you have to do
is just sit back, relax...
&nbsp
or, well, try to relax...
and concentrate, really focus
&nbsp
on the exact date in the future
that you traveled to.
&nbsp
Yep.
May 23, 2017.
&nbsp
Barry, whatever happens, I am right here
waiting for you, okay?
&nbsp
I know.
- Crank it.
- Three, two, one.
&nbsp
What do you see?
An empty street.
&nbsp
A bus stop.
The me from Christmas just
came out of the Speed Force.
&nbsp
In other legal news,
the highly publicized trial...
&nbsp
He's watching the news report.
Aka Plunder, comes to a close.
&nbsp
Morillo was found guilty
of grand theft and aggravated assault...
&nbsp
These are the headlines, right?
Headlines. Yeah... you know what?
&nbsp
Call... call 'em out. I'll write 'em down.
Um...
&nbsp
"Music Meister gets six-figure book deal."
"Luigi's opens after murder."
&nbsp
"Joe West honored at City Hall."
Good for you, Joe.
&nbsp
"Killer"...
What does it say?
&nbsp
"Killer Frost still at large."
"S.T.A.R. Labs museum closes."
&nbsp
"City still recovering
following gorilla attack."
&nbsp
Don't!
Savitar has Iris.
&nbsp
Don't do this.
Now finally, I am free of you.
&nbsp
Look, up on the roof.
Barry... I love you.
&nbsp
Hey, no, don't say that, all right?
H.R. is here.
Me? Are you sure?
&nbsp
- Yeah, you weren't here before.
- Future's changed since then.
&nbsp
You lose, Barry.
No!
&nbsp
Just get us out of here.
You had a rifle pointed at Savitar.
&nbsp
Somehow telling you about Iris's death,
it changed the future.
&nbsp
I was wrong, you were right.
Your theory is correct then.
&nbsp
Guys, my future isn't the only
one that we need to change.
&nbsp
No, the... these headlines, though,
they... they tell us
what happens in the future...
&nbsp
where Caitlin becomes
Killer Frost and Iris dies.
&nbsp
If we can change the headlines,
that means we can change the future.
&nbsp
That's right. Challenge accepted.
Dad's upstairs.
We've been looking for you.
&nbsp
What happened?
Plunder escaped.
&nbsp
Morillo assaulted two guards
on his way out of Iron Heights.
&nbsp
Any idea where he might strike next?
Well, we've got it narrowed
down to 35 jewelry stores
&nbsp
and 48 hotels in Central City, so...
What about banks? Auction houses?
&nbsp
He was caught by The Flash,
robbing the Central City Museum
earlier this year.
&nbsp
Central City Museum.
- That's where he is.
- Where'd you get that?
&nbsp
Um, isn't there a jewelry
exhibit there right now?
&nbsp
- Yeah.
- Uh-huh, with diamonds...
&nbsp
big ones, so it makes sense.
- Let's suit up.
- I don't understand.
&nbsp
Come here.
I was a dick yesterday, Wally.
It wasn't about you.
&nbsp
I was scared when you caught Plunder.
I didn't know what it meant
for Iris's future.
&nbsp
You're ready,
far more ready than I was when I started.
&nbsp
What do you say?
- I'm in.
- All right.
&nbsp
Plunder, my man.
Where do you think you're going?
&nbsp
Right through you.
- You all right?
- I'm good, dude.
&nbsp
You can have this one.
No, Wally. This one has to be you.
&nbsp
Why?
Because if you take down Plunder,
&nbsp
the news report that says
that I captured him
&nbsp
in the future, it's wrong.
We can prove that we can alter the future
&nbsp
here and now.
So that's why you sent me out here.
&nbsp
Hey, I sent you out here
because you're a hero.
&nbsp
Iris needs a hero right now, Wally.
They are running.
&nbsp
Wally, take your next left.
The streets meet up
&nbsp
in about two miles.
If you time it just right,
&nbsp
- you'll be able to blindside him.
- Got it.
&nbsp
Kid Flash! Kid Flash!
Do you hear that?
They're saying your name.
&nbsp
Kid Flash! Kid Flash!
Kid Flash!
&nbsp
Today's top story,
Jared Morillo, aka Plunder,
&nbsp
is back in police custody
after attempting to rob
the Central City Museum.
&nbsp
Morillo was apprehended by a new speedster,
who goes by the name Kid Flash.
&nbsp
Well, that settles it.
I think you're officially Kid Flash now.
&nbsp
Yeah, it's growing on me.
And this rifle is growing on me.
&nbsp
Heat-seeking bullets are just the beginning
of what this bad boy can do.
&nbsp
How did you end up with Plunder's rifle?
Barry stole it for me. Right, Barr?
&nbsp
- Mm-hmm.
- Oh, so you plundered Plunder?
&nbsp
I had to do something
while Wally was cuffing him.
&nbsp
Thanks to you, we changed the future.
If we can change one of these events,
&nbsp
we can change 'em all.
Nothing is set in stone.
&nbsp
We'll see you guys tonight.
- Can't wait.
- Yeah.
&nbsp
I called the local elementary school,
and gave the principal discounted tickets.
&nbsp
I figured, hey, you know,
if the kids love it,
&nbsp
they'll tell their parents, and, well,
the rest writes itself.
&nbsp
You, Francisco... are brilliant.
Of course, science
&nbsp
is what will inspire these children...
not just The Flash.
&nbsp
Check it out.
Welcome to S.T.A.R. Labs.
&nbsp
My name is Francisco Ramon.
I wasn't always the esteemed
engineer you see before you,
&nbsp
but after years of hard work and studying,
I joined S.T.A.R. Labs.
&nbsp
- I hope my love of science...
- Should we go talk to him?
&nbsp
Will inspire some among you
to join the scientific community
&nbsp
as we strive to reach
a new age for humanity.
&nbsp
Thank you.
You're very welcome.
&nbsp
Okay, the quiche is in the oven;
the beer and wine are in the fridge;
&nbsp
and the candles are on the table.
- Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
- What?
&nbsp
I forgot the ice.
Instant party save.
&nbsp
Baby, you've never been sexier.
I know.
&nbsp
Hey, Iris.
How are you doing? For real, are you okay?
&nbsp
- Yeah, I'm fine.
- Because if you're not fine,
&nbsp
you can talk to me. You know that, right?
I know.
&nbsp
All right.
- You ready?
- Yeah.
&nbsp
All right.
- Hey.
&nbsp
I got you guys a plant.
That's like a standard
housewarming gift, right?
&nbsp
- Yes, perfect.
- Not on my Earth.
&nbsp
- On my Earth, we get reptiles.
- Whoa.
&nbsp
I present to you McSnurtle...
the turtle. Careful, she bites.
&nbsp
- I... this is for me?
- It's for the housewarming.
&nbsp
- Wow!
- Hey.
&nbsp
You two did really well.
This place is "noice."
&nbsp
Thank you. Mm, hi, Daddy.
Aww.
&nbsp
Oh, my God, it's perfect.
- Wow.
- Yeah, right?
&nbsp
What are we gonna call you?
Look, I... I got a pet.
Who are you trying...
&nbsp
- Hello, hello.
- Oh, hey.
&nbsp
Hi. I hope I'm not too late.
- Right on time.
- Yeah.
&nbsp
Good, good. This is a... it's for you.
- Ah, thank you.
- Yeah.
&nbsp
Um, yeah. So we all talked it over,
and welcome to the team.
&nbsp
You being serious?
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
&nbsp
Yeah, it's so exciting.
I mean, my last team,
&nbsp
they were all murdered by Savitar, so...
We need to work on your small talk skills.
&nbsp
Yeah, sure. Just wanted to be upfront.
- Come on in.
- That's nice of you.
&nbsp
- You want a drink?
- Uh, yeah, I'd love one.
&nbsp
- Thanks. Cheers.
- Is this for me?
&nbsp
- Oh, yeah.
- All right.
&nbsp
This place is incredible, Barr.
Thank you.
&nbsp
I have to admit,
I miss you around the house.
&nbsp
- Yeah?
- But Wally over there
&nbsp
keeps me plenty occupied.
Yeah, um, I already talked to Wally,
&nbsp
but I'm sorry about yesterday.
You were right.
&nbsp
He's really important to this team.
He's a real hero, Joe.
&nbsp
Both of my sons are heroes.
Julian and I were talking
about your battery problem
&nbsp
with your cuffs.
Uh, we decided we'd invest
in an alternate accessory.
&nbsp
Voilà.
Every time you go outside,
solar energy will recharge it.
&nbsp
Guys, this means so much to me.
Thank you.
&nbsp
Of course.
Thank you.
&nbsp
- Oh, wow.
- Ta-da!
&nbsp
Hey, guys. I asked myself
to say a few words, um, on this occasion.
&nbsp
A home, you know,
it's more than bricks and mortar
&nbsp
and a turtle. It's a... it's a feeling.
It's a feeling of belonging, isn't it?
&nbsp
Of... of love, of course...
uh, hope for the future.
&nbsp
I don't know if I have ever met two people
who are more suited
to one another than you two.
&nbsp
- To Barry and Iris.
- Barry and Iris.
&nbsp
To Barry and Iris.
- To us.
&nbsp