He's the most handsome and
coolest guy in all of year three.
I think we're going to sleep together.
I like it.
I think it's a little hot.
You! Don't be some dick tease.
Ingrid..
I miss you.
You look like a slut.
I'm not going behind
your back and talkign to Ingrid.
Where are you?
-I can't come.
Who was that?
Jonas!
Sorry, I have to go.
Hello.
Hi.
So sad?
No!
I bought coffee for you!
Thanks.
What should we talk about?
Nothing. It's just nice with coffee.
What did you do on the weekend?
Eh.. Nothing.
What did you do on Friday?
Mom had her birthday.
So you were just home?
Yeah!
Did something happen on Friday?
No, I was just wondering what you did.
I think that maybe
Jonas was with Ingrid.
Do you know anything about it?
No.
Why do you think so?
I talked on the phone with
him and heard her voice in the background.
Did you ask him?
Yeah, but hee said it was his sister.
Maybe it was.
I know Ingrid's voice.
We were best friends since we were four.
Say that to him.
I did, but he got really mad
and said that I didn't trust him.
Eva, why are you with him?
What do you mean?
Jonas is my bro, but why
are you with someone you don't trust?
So do you think I should trust him?
Or you could go for option three.
You could ask Ingrid.
I'll soon meet William again.
I think we have something going on,
but the age difference is quite sick.
There can really be something between us.
He said he thinks I'm really special.
And I'm ready for it.
Did I tell you I had an orgasm?
[Smile.]
How was that?
[Smile yourself.]
It was a bit like
a sneeze. Just down there.
[Smile yourself.]
It was a bit like
a sneeze. Just down there.
Like a sneeze?
Hm-hm.
[I am smiling.]
I think I know
why everyone got an orgasm with him.
[You're angry.]
I think I know
why everyone got an orgasm with him.
Yeah, why is that?
Because he was really big.
You can't go around telling
people about his dick.
Why not?
You're asking why you
can't tell people about his most vulnerable body part?
Firstly, that body part wasn't that vulnerable.
And secondly, he'll surely talk
about my body to his friends.
Girls should also
be able to do that.
I support equality and feminism.
But Vilde, firstly, size doesn't
have anything to do with orgasms.
And secondly, just because guys
are fools, doesn't mean we have to be fools as well.
It doesn't have anything
to do with equality at all.
Whatever..
But it was good, then?
That's the most important.
It was really good.
But, there's just one thing.
There's no one who tells you
it practically runs out again.
You didn't use a condom?
No, he said he tends to not use one.
-Vilde!
What the fuck is that?
Where are those from?
-Sana knows someone.
It's to fetch the toilet paper.
But I need to have a payment first.
-That's not how it works.
He receives payment from his people,
and then you can pay your people.
But I don't have "people".
Do you think MasterCard operates without people?
Hello.
Hi!
-Hello.
Are you guys coming
to the Halloween party on Friday?
Yeah, maybe.
-We're coming!
Good. We'll talk.
Bye!
You smell like smoke.
What's up, Eva?
This doesn't bother me..
I think there's something
between you and Ingrid.
Really?
You still think so?
I know I heard her voice on the phone!
For the last time, that was my sister
talking in the background!
Why would she be talking in the background?
-Because she thought it was my mom!
Wasn't your mom at home?
Jonas!
You said you would help
your mom with something at home.
But your mom wasn't even home?
-No, she came home later. That's why I called.
Why are you lying to me?
-I'm not lying!
This is not working.
It doesn't work?
What do you mean by that?
Do you want a break or something?
That's what you want.
-No, that's not what I want!
Stop being so
insecure all the time.
What's up with you? Why aren't you
listening to me? I want to talk to you.
Can't you come to
the point? Just admit it!
I got a glass of water and..
He's a guy who only looks-
How's it going with
the alcohol for the party?
I sent William a message if he
could get it for us. -Can he?
He hasn't replied yet. He's extremely busy.
He's in the third year, and he's the bus boss.
He has so much to think about in his situation.
We haven't talked properly since last time.
But we do keep in
contact via Snapchat.
You know what I did yesterday?
No?
I sent William a topless picture.
What did you do?
They're just boobs.
William likes confident girls.
What did he reply?
-He didn't reply directly, but he took a screenshot.
Now listen, Einstein.
William is not interested.
How do you know?
-He didn't even reply to a topless picture.
In "The Game" it says that boys
don't reply to make girls more interested.
If I were you, I would put down "The Game"
and start reading "He's just not that into you".
Why are you always so mean?
Hello?!
We are her friends. If we don't
tell her the truth, who will?
She's sending topless pictures
to a guy who is lying to sleep with her.
That's mean!
-You don't know if he's lying!
He doesn't really seem
like the most trustworthy guy.
I mean that you can't just
claim people are lying without having proof.
Sometimes you have to trust people.
Everyone knows that guys lie.
And how do you know that?
-Their stories are inconsistent.
They get mad when you ask.
Afterwards, they get a bad conscience..
.. and they start drowning you in compliments.
Believe me, just wait and see.
William will break her heart.
[You know you're the coolest, best, hottest,
funniest, prettiest girl in the whole world? I love you.]
Were you with Jonas last Friday?
Just answer me.
Last Friday?
Yeah! Yeah, I was with Jonas.
He didn't tell you?
Oops.
Fuck you!
No, fuck you Eva. Fuck you!
[I talked to Ingrid and she told me EVERYTHING!]
You're sitting here?
I'm sitting here.
Someone's obviously trying to reach you.
-Yeah.
Who is Jonas?
My boyfriend.
Or, eh..
You don't know if he's your boyfriend, or?
He is my boyfriend, it's just that..
We're having a fight.
Hey, you..
Fuck him.
If he makes such a
nice girl cry, fuck him.
This can't happen.
There you are.
What are you guys doing?
Eva's fighting with her boyfriend.
Have you greeted Eva?
Eva, this is Iben.
My girlfriend.
You shouldn't be talking to me.
Iben's really good with boyfriend trouble.
She's fighting with her boyfriend.
-Ah, poor you.
I'll give you two some time.
I'm fine, really.
You don't need to-
Believe me, I know what it's like.
You're a first year. When people try to figure
out who they are, and they change a lot.
People might not be
the way you thought they were.
The same goes for boyfriends.
When I was in the first year my boyfriend was an asshole.
He cheated five
times without me knowing about it.
It gets better when you get older.
It's going really well between me
and Christoffer, because third year guys are mature.
We can talk about everything,
and I trust him 110%.
You'll get a more mature
relationship, if you know what I mean.
Are you also in the third year?
No, second. But a lot happens
from your first to your second year.
Don't take relationships so seriously.
Think of it as something temporary.
Don't let him stand in your way.
It's Halloween! There's a really cool
party here. And you're sitting here like a sad ballerina.
Don't you agree?
Come on, let's go.
Let's have an awesome time.
Thanks, you're really kind..
But I don't feel too good,
so I think I might go home.
Are you sure?
Really sure?
It'll get better.
Black Swan?
I can't handle us breaking up.
The thing is that
Ingrid's brother is a dealer.
Dealer of what?
-Greens.
Have you started smoking marijuana?
Huh?
Why?
You're reacting as if it was heroin.
Marijuana is a drug.
So you think it's equally dangerous as heroin?
-Yes!
I was at Ingrid's brother's place to buy stuff.
Ingrid showed up. But she lives there,
so I couldn't say anything to you.
Why didn't you say anything to me?
-Seriously? Did you see your reaction just now?
Anyway, my point is that
there's nothing between me and Ingrid.
And there never
will be anything, either.
It was really dumb of me to lie.
The fact that you believe there was..
That really hurt me.
Because I trust you 100%.
You have to start trusting me.
I would never do
anything that could destroy us.
Because it's us.
Right?
Don't cry.