Eva, this is Iben. My girlfriend.
It was just a hook up.
You just follow what
everyone else thinks is exciting.
Chris hooked up with
someone at the party. I saw it.
You saw it?
-On the staircase.
Staircase?!
I got an unpleasant phone call from the Rad girls
saying that as long as Eva is on our bus, we're all blacklisted.
I don't understand why you're
attacking Eva, when they're the enemy.
Jonas and Ingrid were a couple. So Eva has
herself to blame for the situation she is in now.
[PS: On the back there's
a greeting in period blood.]
Hi.
You were right.
The Rad girls are after the entire bus.
Whatever. I'm not on the bus anymore.
Why not?
Why bother being on a
blacklisted bus where everyone hates me?
There is no one who hates you, Vilde.
-Sana made it pretty clear.
Anyway, I'm back with Pepsi Max.
Vilde!
I just want you to know I'm not
the type of person who steals other people's boyfriends.
What kind of person are you then?
When I think of Foss, I see
a dude jamming on his guitar.
When I think of the entrance,
I see those majestic stairs.
I strongly recommend this school.
[Hi! I would like to change high school in the middle
of the school year.]
[Immediately. From Nissen to some place else.
Preferably Foss. Or Elvebakken.]
Hi.
-Hi.
You weren't at school today.
No.
It's really unfair
that you get this much hate.
I have decided to change schools.
Why?
Because everything is fucked at Nissen.
And that's why you're changing schools?
Yes.
Okay..
Okay what?
It's just not typical of you.
What is that supposed to mean?
-I didn't know you were someone who would just give up.
What is this bullshit about what kind of person
I am? Maybe I am somoeone who gives up!
I don't know! Why would
you know what kind of person I am?
Everyone is like: "What kind of person are you?
You have to know who you are!" What a fucking cliche.
Yeah, ok.
Just chill.
I didn't mean it like that.
Sorry.
No..
It's actually not that complicated, Eva.
It's just what people do.
If you want to change schools because
things are a little fucked up, you are someone who gives up easily.
I'm not five years old. You thought
reverse psychology would work on me?
I don't know. Does it?
You've got to fight back girl
Is there something?
Are you Maria?
Bus boss from Rad?
Yes.
I am Eva.
Okay.
I am that Eva.
I just want to say that I got your letter.
I know I fucked up, but I think it's unfair
to blacklist the entire bus. My friends didn't do anything.
It was me. Take me, not them.
Okay, Eva..
You can say hi to your friends
and tell them we won't "take" them.
We have more important stuff
to do than blacklisting first years.
So, what's up with the letter then?
We haven't given you a letter.
Someone's fucking with you.
So you guys aren't mad
that I hooked up with Chris?
Eva, we don't give
a shit who you've hooked up with.
Even Iben's boyfriend?
Even Iben's boyfriend. Eva, listen.
I'm sure that in your head, this hook up is the
most important and dramatic thing you've done in your life's story..
But for us who have been here
for a while, it's only a little comma.
So I suggest you accept these terms, okay?
Okay.
And relax.
You shouldn't care. Youre in
the first year. You'll hook up a lot.
But don't sleep around. There's a difference.
When we were in our first year,
we had a chlamydia epidemic.
Did you find out who started it?
-It was William.
It wasn't William.
Chris had it too, right?
It was one of the guys for sure.
[Inaudible.]
I see what you did wrong.
-I didn't do anything wrong.
You did it completely wrong, Sana.
-The answer key is wrong.
The answer key isn't wrong, Sana.
-It is! Because it doesn't have the same as me.
Hi!
Hi.
I talked to the Rad girls.
They aren't after us.
-Now I can finally breathe again!
It's Vilde who cares about that stuff and
is pees her pants about some blacklist.
She isn't on our bus anymore.
Huh?!
She said she didn't want to be
on a bus where everyone hates her.
Something's wrong.
At the bus meeting, she was mean.
And Vilde isn't a mean person.
What?
It seems like you just defended Vilde?
I'm just saying something's wrong.
We are her friends.
You guys should pay more attention to her.
Okay..
You guys..
I feel like I owe you an explanation.
About what Vilde said about me and Ingrid.
But I don't have one.
I know I should've done things differently.
Save that speech for Ingrid.
-Fuck Ingrid!
You don't owe her shit. She was sucking up
to Iben and hooked up with Chris herself.
I'm sure it was her
who sent the period letter.
What are you saying now?
-You don't think it was her? I think so.
Has Ingrid hooked up with Chris?
Yes, I saw it at the Halloween party.
I saw her and Chris making out on the stairs.
Are you kidding me?
-No, I saw it!
And you're telling me this now?!
What? I've told it before.
I thought I told it before.
We have to talk.
Unless you want me to tell
Iben that you hooked up with Chris.
I know you don't want
to listen to me, but you have to.
Whether you want to or not,
we'll be going to the same school the next three years.
You can't continue trying to block me out,
throw shit, or send me threat letters.
Just hear me out, okay?
I moved here from Bergen in the 7th grade..
No one wanted to hang out with me
because I talk so weird.
You were the only
one who took care of me.
I remember how proud and lucky..
I couldn't believe the most popular girls
in our class wanted to be friends with me.
I always really looked up to you.
You're the best
friend I've ever had.
Just the thought of me destroying that..
.. makes me feel sick.
More than sick.
It made me stop
liking myself as a person.
But I can't continue having
regrets for the rest of my life.
It wasn't going well between you and Jonas.
You talked about breaking up with him every day.
I know that's not an excuse, but..
I loved him.
I wish I could do it
all over again, completely different.
But I can't.
I'm just going to have
to accept it and move on.
I'm saying this for the last time.
Okay?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry that I lied
and went behind your back.
I'm sorry that I ruined our friendship.
You didn't deserve it.
I'm not trying to say you should like me.
Or that we should be friends again.
I just..
I can't bear any more threat letters, okay?
Okay.
No more shit.
But I didn't send a threat letter.
And I barely knew Iben when I hooked
up with Chris at the Halloween party.
Fucking hell!
Seriously?
You have serious issues.
What's wrong with you?
You can't just jump on people. Pull yourself together.
You're with the school's largest douche. Your way
of coping with it is to jump people and send threat letters?
I have a better suggestion for you..
Break up with your fucking
boyfriend. He's a fucking asshole.
I didn't mean it like that.
Yeah, I'm fine.
I know it's true, so..
I just..
I think you deserve better.
Everyone deserves better than that.
I love him.
Maybe he'll change.
It was good that he told you.
What?
That he had cheated.
He didn't tell me?
He didn't?
-No.
Some people told me that's
how you knew about it.
That your boyfriend told you.
My boyfriend?! It was
your boyfriend who tipped me off.
My boyfriend?
Yes.
But my boyfriend didn't even know.
He must've done it.
It was him who sent the tips.
That's how I found about it.
Huh?
The little blonde one. The one
you're always with. Isn't he your boyfriend?
Isak Yaki? Isak?
Isn't that what he's called?
Did Isak sent the tips?
I thought you knew.