My name is Barry Allen,
&nbsp
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world, I'm
an ordinary forensic scientist,
&nbsp
but secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
&nbsp
I fight crime and find
other meta-humans like me.
&nbsp
In an attempt to stop
the evil speedster Savitar,
&nbsp
I was accidentally thrust into the future,
and I saw him murder the woman I love.
&nbsp
But I won't let that happen.
I'm going to do everything in my power
&nbsp
to change the future, and I'm the only one
fast enough to keep her alive.
&nbsp
I am The Flash.
Previously on The Flash...
&nbsp
When I threw the Philosopher's Stone
into the Speed Force, I accidentally
&nbsp
ran into the future.
I saw Savitar murder you.
&nbsp
I wasn't fast enough to save you.
We can't do this alone, Barry.
&nbsp
Why don't you come work with us?
You can help Team Flash fight meta-humans.
&nbsp
- Welcome to the team.
- Yeah.
&nbsp
If his powers are linked to the energy
that ties together the multiverse...
&nbsp
He can open a breach to any Earth he wants.
The thing they never tell you
about fighting villains
&nbsp
is that nothing ever stays the same.
The harder you work
to take down the bad guys,
&nbsp
the more they up their game.
Gentlemen,
&nbsp
welcome to the future of crime.
Not even the military has these yet.
&nbsp
Looks like Christmas came early.
You know what the only problem is?
&nbsp
You're on Santa's naughty list.
Christmas is canceled.
&nbsp
Fortunately, our team
has a secret weapon of its own:
&nbsp
a man of science, a man of action,
and that man's name
&nbsp
is H.R. Wells.
Look who has a vortex cannon.
&nbsp
Ho, ho, ho.
H.R.?
&nbsp
With a blast from my trusty vortex cannon,
- I dispatch the miscreant...
- H.R.
&nbsp
- Hey, yep, here we are.
- Barry needs help.
&nbsp
- Yeah, Barry needs help.
- Where's Kid Flash?
&nbsp
He's on his way. Are you on your way?
They need you at Keystone Bridge.
&nbsp
Surely all your adventures
are not this disorganized?
&nbsp
There's a method to the madness, mate.
Watch and learn.
&nbsp
The Electric Gang is headed north.
You gotta cut 'em off
before they reach the freeway.
&nbsp
Oh, hey.
How you wanna play this?
&nbsp
I have an idea.
Eyes up!
&nbsp
Here he comes.
Just the red one.
&nbsp
Nice work.
They're out cold.
&nbsp
Okay, boys.
They saved us.
&nbsp
They saved us!
- Who are you?
- Um...
&nbsp
I'm Kid Flash.
Oh, my gosh. Can we get your picture?
&nbsp
Yes.
Whoo.
&nbsp
Okay. Bye.
- Go Kid Flash!
&nbsp
Synced and corrected by oykubuyuk
www.addic7ed.com
&nbsp
Nice save!
Could not have scripted it better myself.
&nbsp
Thanks.
Barry did most of the heavy lifting.
&nbsp
- B.A.
- Yes, bravo, boys.
&nbsp
Although I did find at least six ways
you could have done it more efficiently,
&nbsp
just... just saying.
I mean, the busload of hot cheerleaders
&nbsp
seemed like the way that we did things.
Oh, that's going in the book. You know what?
&nbsp
I'm running low;
let me buy you a cup of coffee
&nbsp
over at CC Jitters.
- Bond, are you coming?
- No, thank you.
&nbsp
So exactly how many hot cheerleaders?
I was a good boy.
&nbsp
You know, he's just been
looking forward to this
&nbsp
for a long time; he's enjoying the moment.
Well, I'm glad you have his back.
&nbsp
We have each other's back.
It's actually been really nice
having him out there.
&nbsp
Hey, I meant to ask you.
When you found the Electric Gang,
&nbsp
did you see them meeting with anyone else?
- Like who?
- Well, word on the street is,
&nbsp
there is a new arms dealer in town
with access to sophisticated weaponry
&nbsp
like the gun that Plunder used.
Don't you think that's something
&nbsp
for the police to handle?
I'm still a journalist, Barry.
&nbsp
I can't hide from the world
because of what you saw.
&nbsp
See you at home.
Can't lose her, Cisco.
&nbsp
Please tell me you found
a way to change the future.
&nbsp
We found a way to change the future.
Did you really?
&nbsp
No, but Caitlin and I
did find a way to map it.
&nbsp
You're gonna love this. Follow me.
Julian suggested we make
a 3-D reconstruction
&nbsp
of the scene from the future
exactly as we saw it.
&nbsp
With toys.
The medium's not important.
&nbsp
Thank you. Eye on the ball, Barry.
Is this me?
&nbsp
Why is he an astronaut?
Eye on the ball, Barry, okay?
&nbsp
Now, this diorama tells us
you need to cover this distance
&nbsp
in less than 0.21 seconds
if you want to save Iris from Savitar.
&nbsp
What do you guys think?
Think what you're proposing is impossible.
&nbsp
- Therefore, you will fail.
- Why?
&nbsp
Multi-universe is maybe a new concept to me,
but mathematics is not.
&nbsp
Pay attention, Allen.
This is your speed timeline.
&nbsp
This is your maximum velocity
when you first acquired your powers.
&nbsp
This is your current top speed,
and this is where you need to be
&nbsp
in May to cover that distance
in 0.21 seconds.
&nbsp
At your current rate of improvement,
impossible.
&nbsp
Wow.
Thank you for that rousing pep talk, coach.
&nbsp
Okay, why don't you take a knee?
I think we got it covered here.
&nbsp
It looks like it.
I actually have to be back at CCPD.
&nbsp
As do you.
Cheerio.
&nbsp
He really does want to help
in his own snobbish, thoughtless way.
&nbsp
He is right.
I mean, he's kind of a dick about it,
&nbsp
but you can't argue with his math.
Okay, well, then, we'll find another way
&nbsp
to make this work.
We need to.
&nbsp
Iris isn't gonna die.
Thank you very much.
&nbsp
Gotcha.
Freeze!
&nbsp
How'd you get in here?
You know what they say.
&nbsp
Every time a door closes...
A window opens.
&nbsp
Barry.
- Hey.
- Nothing's missing.
&nbsp
- Nope.
- Cash is still in the register.
&nbsp
Safe's not touched.
I mean, it seems like a lot to go through
&nbsp
to just get a late night
cup of coffee, right?
&nbsp
Yeah, it's definitely a meta.
I'll have Julian look into
his meta database,
&nbsp
but I think this is someone new.
New and dangerous.
&nbsp
Well, it's nothing that The Flash
and Kid Flash can't handle.
&nbsp
My two superhero boys.
He is doing great.
&nbsp
Speaking of my kids,
Iris, she tell you about this
&nbsp
arms dealer story she's following?
Yeah, she's mentioned it.
&nbsp
Well, now that you're her live-in boyfriend,
could you look out for her
&nbsp
and maybe get her to back off a bit?
Because this isn't something
she should be doing on her own.
&nbsp
I agree. I'm trying.
She seem... okay to you, otherwise?
&nbsp
Yeah, why? Do you not think so?
If you guys got something going on,
&nbsp
I hope you know you can talk to me.
Yeah, I know, Joe.
&nbsp
Thank you... I... we're...
both doing great.
&nbsp
Okay.
- All right.
- Talk to you later.
&nbsp
Yeah.
So this is the footage from Jitters
&nbsp
that should help us ID our new meta.
Brunette? That really narrows it down.
&nbsp
Mm, I'll clean that up.
Oh, look how clear
the picture is on that screen.
&nbsp
That's 'cause that's not from Jitters.
That's our security footage.
&nbsp
H.R. Wells.
I know you're in there.
&nbsp
Come quietly if you don't want trouble.
H.R., how does she know you?
&nbsp
Talk. Who is this... gorgeous intruder?
Her name is Gypsy,
&nbsp
and she's what's known
on my Earth as a collector.
&nbsp
What is she collecting?
She's come to collect, you know, me.
&nbsp
Oh!
- Where does it hurt?
- Oh, everywhere.
&nbsp
You can vibe?
Oh, I like it.
&nbsp
Slow down there.
Let's just talk about this, like two adults,
&nbsp
over coffee, or maybe dinner,
if you prefer that.
&nbsp
There's a great Thai place
up the road, if you like Thai.
&nbsp
I'm Cisco, by the way. You must be Gypsy.
It's nice to meet you.
&nbsp
Are you asking her on a date?
Are you kidding me?
&nbsp
I am negotiating.
Well, you showed me yours.
&nbsp
Only fair I show you mine.
Cisco!
&nbsp
Ma'am, I'm gonna have to
ask you to leave the building.
&nbsp
Speedster.
That's fun.
&nbsp
I like to have fun too.
I see you've got a lot
to learn about your power.
&nbsp
Yeah. Like that.
How do you do that? That's cool.
&nbsp
You're harboring a fugitive from justice.
Our world has a strict ban
on inter-dimensional travel.
&nbsp
He knew that when he came here.
- So you tracked him here?
- Honestly, it wasn't that hard.
&nbsp
Not when he's beaming "H.R. Wells'
Adventures in the Multiverse"
back chapter by chapter.
&nbsp
You know what? Whatever H.R. did,
you can't just come here
and take him by force.
&nbsp
Not without going through us.
If I really wanted to go through you,
&nbsp
you would all be dead.
I've got a lock on you now.
&nbsp
There is no getting away.
You've got an hour
to get your affairs in order,
&nbsp
and then you are coming back with me.
Adios, Cisco.
&nbsp
What an exit.
"As Francisco threw back his lustrous locks
&nbsp
"and laughed, I outlined my plan
for neutralizing the rampaging creature."
&nbsp
It goes on like this for pages.
He's been broadcasting this
&nbsp
without our knowledge or permission,
all the while making himself the hero.
&nbsp
Yeah, every book needs a central protagonist
that the audience can invest in.
&nbsp
I would have gone with Barry.
Barry?
&nbsp
Cisco, what was that back there?
First Golden Glider and now her?
&nbsp
I can't help who I'm attracted to,
even if it is the...
&nbsp
sexy, intense, deadly ones.
So she takes you back to Earth-19,
&nbsp
and, what, you pay a fine?
The punishment for
&nbsp
an unauthorized breach travel on my Earth...
it's death.
&nbsp
Death?
About 24, 25 years ago, a neighboring Earth
&nbsp
invaded our planet through a breach
and almost destroyed the place.
&nbsp
So to prevent it from happening again,
they banned all inter-dimensional travel.
&nbsp
And then they put the collectors in place
to punish those of us who violated the ban.
&nbsp
I didn't think that she'd track me down.
So why would you
risk your life by coming here?
&nbsp
I... I'm gonna get packing.
It's time for H.R. to face the music.
&nbsp
Mm-hmm.
Guys, I know H.R. can be annoying,
&nbsp
but he doesn't deserve to die.
Different Earth, different morality.
&nbsp
But he doesn't go back. I saw him.
In the future, with me and
Iris and Savitar, he was there.
&nbsp
I mean, that must mean
we don't let her take him back.
&nbsp
Maybe we do.
Maybe by letting him go back to his Earth,
&nbsp
it changes your future
and prevents Iris' death.
&nbsp
I gotta go see her.
Are you just gonna let this woman take H.R.?
&nbsp
I don't know.
No. I just...
&nbsp
I wish I knew if it would make a difference.
You know, I mean, what if
he goes and nothing changes?
&nbsp
How do we ever know if our
actions now impact the future?
&nbsp
Yeah.
You know, sometimes I wish
we had normal-people problems.
&nbsp
Yeah, that would be nice.
Hey, you didn't tell Joe
&nbsp
about the future, did you?
No, of course not.
&nbsp
The last thing I need
is for him to worry about
&nbsp
something four months away
that might not happen.
&nbsp
That won't happen.
Maybe in the meantime,
&nbsp
you could let this arms dealer thing go?
Oh, God, did my dad put you up to this too?
&nbsp
No, he didn't have to.
- Barry, look, this...
- No, look, I'm sorry.
&nbsp
I'm not trying to keep you
from doing your job, okay?
&nbsp
But when we're all focused
on this H.R. thing
&nbsp
and trying to prevent the future.
I mean, do we really need to go
looking for more trouble?
&nbsp
Please?
Okay, I'll drop it.
&nbsp
Really? Just like that?
Um, yes.
&nbsp
Sometimes I do listen to you, you know?
That hasn't been my experience.
&nbsp
Shut up.
All right. I'll see you later.
&nbsp
- 'Kay, bye.
- Thank you.
&nbsp
Don't you get tired of running?
That's the thing, running just
&nbsp
sort of keeps my mind
off of things, I guess.
&nbsp
Must be an amazing feeling.
It is.
&nbsp
You know, cracking a big story
gives me an amazing feeling.
&nbsp
And... I think I'm onto one.
Oh, that, uh, arms dealer thing?
&nbsp
How do you know about that?
Because both Dad and Barry
want you to lay off of it.
&nbsp
The phrase "death wish"
got tossed around a lot
&nbsp
by them.
Okay, I do not have a death wish.
&nbsp
I just want to see justice done
like everyone else in this building.
&nbsp
I get that, but it is dangerous, Iris.
Wally, how dangerous could it be?
&nbsp
I don't die till May.
Barry said that in Flashpoint, you and I
&nbsp
were a brother-sister crime-fighting team.
I say we make that a reality again.
&nbsp
Shouldn't we ask Barry first?
No, this is just between us, Wally.
&nbsp
We can do this together.
Do you know what I'm really
gonna miss about this Earth?
&nbsp
- I don't know. Uh...
- Soap operas.
&nbsp
I mean, a long, winding story
served up daily in hour-long chapters?
&nbsp
You never answered Caitlin's question.
Oh, about why I put mustard on my fries?
&nbsp
Why you risked your life to come here.
That.
&nbsp
I looked in a mirror.
I don't follow.
&nbsp
Look, on my Earth,
I had fame and power.
&nbsp
I had respect.
I was "H.R. Wells."
&nbsp
But when I looked in the mirror,
I knew the truth.
&nbsp
And the truth was...
I didn't matter.
&nbsp
I was a fraud.
That is why I came to this Earth,
&nbsp
so I could rewrite my story,
both literally and figuratively.
&nbsp
There's gotta be something you can do, H.R.
There's not.
&nbsp
You can't hire a lawyer? Appeal the case?
There's nothing I can do, B.A.!
&nbsp
I don't mean to snap at you.
It just... I don't have
any options here, all right?
&nbsp
Unless, of course, I appeal for
trial by combat.
&nbsp
Guys, Gypsy's here.
Always so punctual.
&nbsp
I'm impressed!
Thought you'd try and flee again.
&nbsp
Time to go.
All right.
&nbsp
Gypsy,
take me home.
&nbsp
Wait.
You're not taking him anywhere.
&nbsp
- What?
- Why not?
&nbsp
Because I challenge you to trial by combat.
What are you doing?
&nbsp
I'm challenging her to trial by combat.
No, no, he isn't.
&nbsp
Okay, I am. I'm gonna fight you.
Well, that one spoke first.
&nbsp
What? That's like a real rule?
By the laws of Earth-19,
I hereby challenge you
&nbsp
for possession of H.R. Wells.
If you want, we can solve this another way.
&nbsp
There's a great spot for drinks...
You realize trial by combat is to the death?
&nbsp
Yeah. For the loser.
Listen, you want him?
&nbsp
You're gonna have to come and claim him.
Hmm.
&nbsp
That's Arwen. That's... Arwen.
I take it you also want the
customary 24 hours to prepare?
&nbsp
Do I want the customary...
Yes, you do.
&nbsp
I would love to take advantage
of the customary 24 hours,
if you don't mind.
&nbsp
Very well.
One day.
&nbsp
See you then.
She's gonna kill me, isn't she?
&nbsp
She's good.
She's great.
&nbsp
I mean, Gypsy is a legend on my Earth.
So why, exactly, did you agree to fight her?
&nbsp
I don't know.
You did what any of us would have done.
&nbsp
I might not have done it, just being honest.
Okay, all right. Lay it out for me.
&nbsp
What are my chances here,
scale of one to ten?
&nbsp
She's gonna kill you.
It's a pretty solid "one, " mate.
&nbsp
You have the same powers Gypsy does, right?
I mean, she's not doing
anything you can't do.
&nbsp
Much better... look, I mean,
she's doing it just much better.
&nbsp
You can do this, okay?
You just need a little practice
and a little confidence.
&nbsp
And we're all gonna
help you with that, right?
&nbsp
- Yes.
- Uh, sure, sure, yeah.
&nbsp
- Yes.
- Yeah.
&nbsp
Hey.
I believe in you, all right?
&nbsp
You can beat her.
Listen, I have some ideas
&nbsp
for a training regimen I can set up in here.
Caitlin, why don't you get
&nbsp
the medical bay prepared in the meantime?
What? Well, why does... why does she
&nbsp
need to set up the... the medical bay?
For when you...
&nbsp
beat her, when you beat her,
she's gonna... she's gonna
need medical attention.
&nbsp
'Cause you will beat her, I have every faith
that you're going to beat her.
&nbsp
We need to work on
your interpersonal skills.
&nbsp
I was really trying.
Has anyone ever beat her?
&nbsp
Yeah.
No.
&nbsp
Oh, okay.
Well, I've officially reached
a nice, comfortable level
&nbsp
of just straight-up panic.
I mean, you don't even like me.
&nbsp
Why would you risk your life for me?
Well, you heard Barry.
It's what we do around here.
&nbsp
Come on. Why?
You're not like the other Wellses.
&nbsp
Yeah, so you keep reminding me.
No, I mean, those two, they were geniuses.
&nbsp
We depended on them.
But with you, the roles are reversed.
&nbsp
You depend on us.
Harrison Wells was always there for me,
&nbsp
so I guess in some weird way, I just...
I want to be there for Harrison Wells.
&nbsp
- Anyway...
- Yeah.
&nbsp
So what are we doing here?
I thought you didn't want Dad to know
&nbsp
we're going after this arms dealer.
Oh, yeah, no, I don't.
&nbsp
But, um, actually,
I need you to swipe his file on the case
&nbsp
and photograph the pages
and then put them back.
&nbsp
Thanks.
What?
&nbsp
Iris.
Have you lost your mind?
&nbsp
Dad will kill us.
No, no, Wally, he won't.
&nbsp
He won't even know that Kid Flash was there.
First, you have to tell me why.
&nbsp
Okay, look.
I know everyone is working really hard
&nbsp
to prevent Savitar from...
Yeah.
&nbsp
But, honestly, these could be
my last few months on Earth.
&nbsp
Can you not talk like that?
I'm just being realistic, Wally.
&nbsp
I get to do that.
Look, I want my life to mean something,
&nbsp
more than just a daughter or as a sister
or as a girlfriend,
&nbsp
but as a reporter.
This story can do that.
&nbsp
It can say that I, Iris West, mattered.
You know, my life was a lot easier
&nbsp
before I had a sister.
But it's a lot better now, isn't it?
&nbsp
Come on.
Okay.
&nbsp
I can get you the no-knock warrant,
but, Joe, this guy is armed to the teeth
&nbsp
with God only knows what.
You're gonna have to move
in there fast and hard.
&nbsp
"Fast and hard, " okay,
I kind of walked into that...
&nbsp
Hey. Sorry.
- Hey, sweetheart.
- Hi.
&nbsp
Hi, Iris.
Hi. Good to see you, Cecile.
&nbsp
Um, Dad, can I borrow you for a second
for a little father-daughter talk?
&nbsp
Uh...
I need to go
&nbsp
catch up with Captain Singh,
so I will be back in a little while, yeah?
&nbsp
- It's good to see you.
- Good to see you too.
&nbsp
So... what's up? How can I help you?
Can I talk to you for a second over here?
&nbsp
Um...
Uhh, yeah, so, um,
&nbsp
I wanted to... to speak to you about
me and Barry.
&nbsp
You and Barry?
- Yes.
- Okay?
&nbsp
So there comes a time
in every couple's relationship
&nbsp
when you realize that there is
too much love for two people.
&nbsp
And...
Uh, when that happens,
you know in your heart
&nbsp
that the only solution is
to make your family a little... bigger.
&nbsp
- Okay, I'm gonna need a second.
- Oh!
&nbsp
Dad, hey, hey, listen to me very closely.
This is so important to me.
&nbsp
Oh, God.
Um...
&nbsp
Is Barry a dog or a cat person?
What?
&nbsp
Yeah, what kind of animal does he like?
Because I was thinking
about getting him a pet
&nbsp
and I don't really remember
him having a preference.
&nbsp
Oh, man, you had me
going there for a second.
&nbsp
What, what did you
think I was talking about?
&nbsp
Nothing, nothing, I...
you can get him any kind of animal you want
&nbsp
as long as it has four legs.
Good, great advice, four legs, copy that.
&nbsp
Thanks for the chat. Okay, bye.
Damn.
&nbsp
Oh, yeah.
Facing the wrong way again.
How many is that?
&nbsp
- Three.
- Nine.
&nbsp
- You'll get there.
- Yes.
&nbsp
Hopefully in the next
21 hours and 46 minutes.
&nbsp
All right, look, whenever I'm out there,
I'm in a tough fight,
I think maybe I don't have it,
&nbsp
I just take a deep breath...
Trust my instincts.
&nbsp
Trust my instincts, that's good.
That helps.
&nbsp
- Where'd he go?
- I don't know.
&nbsp
Guys?
Up here.
&nbsp
- Let... let's go talk.
- All right.
&nbsp
We can't let Francisco fight Gypsy,
because if he does, he is a dead man.
&nbsp
- You don't know that.
- Oh, I know that.
&nbsp
You know that. He knows that.
- Okay, I get it.
- She knows that.
&nbsp
- We know that; everybody knows...
- So what are we supposed to do?
&nbsp
We're supposed to stop her
before she fights him.
&nbsp
That would be great
if we knew where she was.
&nbsp
- Yes?
- I know where she is.
&nbsp
- How?
- I tagged her with a tracer
&nbsp
last time she was here.
A magician friend told me you kind of
&nbsp
- distract 'em and tag...
- H.R.
&nbsp
I needed to know where she was
so I could stay one step ahead of her.
&nbsp
She is...
- At the waterfront.
&nbsp
What do you say? For Francisco?
All right.
&nbsp
This world may be a primitive,
uncultured backwater,
&nbsp
but they do make an excellent cup of coffee.
That they do. You know what you gotta try?
&nbsp
You gotta try the Brazilian roast, it's new.
It is so good.
&nbsp
Maybe I'll take a few bags back with me.
Yeah, think that's wise.
&nbsp
Will you be going back in a bag?
Look, that kid, Francisco,
&nbsp
he's just trying to protect me.
Then he's as foolish as he is cute.
&nbsp
Okay, Gypsy.
Let's go home.
&nbsp
B.A.!
Nice try!
&nbsp
You think I didn't see that coming?
Stop, stop!
&nbsp
- Stop what?
- Stop...
&nbsp
Stop trying to enforce the law?
You are a criminal.
&nbsp
Now, it's great that you made friends here,
but that doesn't change
the fact that you lied.
&nbsp
You broke our most sacred laws,
and now it is time for you to face justice.
&nbsp
Wait!
You still need to face Cisco.
&nbsp
No, I think this
little stunt forfeits his claim.
&nbsp
And his time.
You just said you believe in the law, right?
&nbsp
We made a mistake.
Cisco will hold up his end of the deal.
&nbsp
He will.
You have really pulled
a number on these people
&nbsp
if they would die for you.
Tell Cisco there is no backing out now.
&nbsp
I'll keep this one as insurance until then.
B.A...
&nbsp
That's not good.
- She took H.R.?
- Mm-hmm.
&nbsp
Can she do that?
I mean, I though this whole
trial by combat thing had rules.
&nbsp
Which apparently we broke
when we tried to get the drop on her.
&nbsp
Well, that wasn't very clever, was it?
A deal's a deal. It should be honored.
&nbsp
You know what? You're right, Julian.
A deal is a deal.
&nbsp
And our deal was that I would train
so that I could fight Gypsy,
but I guess you two
&nbsp
wanted to go behind my back
and try to sub in?
&nbsp
We didn't go... we just thought
maybe you could use some help.
&nbsp
Yeah? What happened to,
"Cisco, you can beat her"?
&nbsp
- You can.
- "I believe in you."
&nbsp
- I do.
- "Trust your instincts."
&nbsp
Well, right now,
my instincts are telling me
I should be writing
&nbsp
my last will and testament,
so please excuse me.
&nbsp
Cisco, come...
Should I go talk to him?
&nbsp
No, I...
I got it.
&nbsp
Looks like I'm not the only one
who has to work on
their interpersonal skills.
&nbsp
Oh, hey.
I'd be careful if I were you.
&nbsp
Last thing we want is
for me to touch a button
&nbsp
and blow your head off, right?
'Cause I don't know what I'm doing, right?
&nbsp
You know I don't think that.
Yeah, well, you have a very,
&nbsp
very strange way of showing it.
You're right, man. I'm sorry.
&nbsp
I don't know. I just...
guess this whole "not getting faster" thing,
&nbsp
it just has me rattled.
I was always able to do it before, you know?
&nbsp
I mean, against Reverse Flash
and then against Zoom, but...
&nbsp
Savitar's on a whole other level.
And knowing what he'll do to Iris if I fail?
&nbsp
I'm afraid just...
thinking what's gonna happen
to H.R. if I don't beat Gypsy.
&nbsp
But you, you're the hero. I mean,
how do you handle
all this pressure all the time?
&nbsp
By just leaning on all of you guys.
You know, I mean,
you're always in my corner,
&nbsp
helping me face my fears.
And it is okay to be afraid. Trust me.
&nbsp
And when you are, I'll be there
in your corner.
&nbsp
Yes, lovely little speech, Allen.
But what Mr. Ramon needs to defeat
&nbsp
his inter-dimensional adversary
is a practical stratagem.
&nbsp
Lucky for you, I found one.
This is Gypsy's signature move.
&nbsp
I call it her "breach and blast"
Oh, yeah. That move.
&nbsp
You see just before she comes
in and out of a breach,
&nbsp
her feet come off the ground.
So for that split second
she's off the ground,
&nbsp
she'll be off-balance.
Yes, and vulnerable.
&nbsp
It might behoove you
to use this during the battle.
&nbsp
This is great, Julian.
Hmm, just glad I could be helpful.
&nbsp
This is... more than helpful.
I gotta work on this.
&nbsp
- Thank you.
- Cheers.
&nbsp
Thanks.
You sure this is the place?
&nbsp
- Positive.
- All right.
&nbsp
You ready to bust an arms dealer?
- Get me a front-page headline?
- Wally, wait.
&nbsp
CCPD's been looking for this guy for months.
He might have some sort
of secret tunnel network
&nbsp
that helps him slip out and get away.
I should do a quick recon.
&nbsp
Yeah. Thorough.
We don't want to miss anything, okay?
&nbsp
Be back in a you-know-what.
Hope you like what you see,
&nbsp
'cause this sneak preview
is gonna cost you your life.
&nbsp
Yeah, I don't think so.
Are you crazy?
&nbsp
This'll rip a hole right through you.
Everyone's gotta go sometime, right?
&nbsp
And I am pretty sure today just...
isn't my day.
&nbsp
What the hell, sis?
Are you trying to get yourself killed?
&nbsp
God, okay, look,
we gotta get you out of here
&nbsp
before CCPD sees you.
Don't worry.
Dad's, like, my biggest fan now.
&nbsp
He's totally cool
with me doing stuff like this.
&nbsp
Hell no, I ain't cool with this.
You two almost compromised
a major CCPD sting operation
&nbsp
that took the DA's office
months to assemble.
&nbsp
You still got the guy, right?
That is not the point, Iris.
&nbsp
The point is, you had
you and your brother out there
&nbsp
in danger, and for what?
A story? And where the hell were you?
&nbsp
Dad, this is more than just a story for me.
Yeah, which you almost got shot for.
&nbsp
Oh, God.
What?
&nbsp
Iris.
What is going on with you?
&nbsp
Joe, I'm sorry...
Can I talk to you for a second?
&nbsp
We'll be right back.
Joe already suspects something's up.
&nbsp
You going out there like that,
it just hangs a bell on it.
&nbsp
This story is going to change lives, Barry.
Why do you think that you're the only one
&nbsp
allowed to risk your life to do good?
I don't.
&nbsp
It's okay to be afraid of the future.
But I won't let you die.
&nbsp
I am not afraid to die, Barry, I'm not.
Then what?
&nbsp
I'm afraid...
What if I end up just like my mom?
&nbsp
Just gone without making a mark,
without leaving anything behind.
&nbsp
Iris, your mom,
she left something behind.
&nbsp
She left a brave, wonderful son
and the woman that I love.
&nbsp
All right?
I don't know what the future
holds, none of us do.
&nbsp
I know that we will face it together.
Gypsy just vibed me her location.
&nbsp
Let's do this.
I don't think the
literary critics on our Earth
&nbsp
would know a real sci-fi romance best seller
- unless it bit them in the...
- Time's up, Wells.
&nbsp
Looks like your so-called
friend is a coward after all.
&nbsp
He's not a coward.
He's one of the finest men I've ever known.
&nbsp
Oh, you're right about that!
I'm fine as hell.
&nbsp
There he is.
Didn't think you'd show.
&nbsp
Oh, I wouldn't miss an evening with you,
even if it is for a showdown.
&nbsp
I will kill you, Cisco.
We'll see who dies tonight.
&nbsp
To the victor goes H.R. Wells.
May the best vibe win.
&nbsp
Part of me was hoping
you wouldn't show tonight.
&nbsp
How do you want to do this?
"Westworld" style, back to back,
ten paces, turn and shoot?
&nbsp
No.
This does not bode well.
&nbsp
Cisco can hold his own.
Hmm. Barely.
&nbsp
Barry, we can't let this happen.
What if he can't defeat her?
&nbsp
I can't interfere again.
If I do, then we forfeit. H.R.'s a dead man.
&nbsp
At this rate, Cisco's gonna be the dead man.
Oh.
&nbsp
Ooh, girl!
You done did it now!
&nbsp
Stronger than I thought.
I'm just getting warmed up.
&nbsp
Yeah, maybe not do that.
Time to turn things up to 11.
&nbsp
"Spinal Tap."
That's, like, one of my favorite movies...
&nbsp
Where did they go?
I... they could be anywhere by now.
&nbsp
In any universe.
This is Earth-2.
&nbsp
You're cute, but you talk too much.
Oh, you want to play dirty, huh?
&nbsp
Let's play dirty.
Oh! That hurts.
&nbsp
That too.
Is it me, or is this city getting weirder?
&nbsp
Well, this is hot.
I think you're flirting
with me to distract me
&nbsp
'cause you're afraid.
My collection record is flawless.
&nbsp
In these trials, I am undefeated.
Oh, please.
&nbsp
Everybody's got a weakness.
Even you.
&nbsp
Says the man afraid of showing everyone
how powerful he can be.
&nbsp
You and I resonate on a similar frequency.
I can feel it.
&nbsp
Yet you allow your fear
and insecurity to hold you back.
&nbsp
That's why you're gonna lose.
Does this look like holding back to you?
&nbsp
- I could do this all night.
- How did you...
&nbsp
You might want to work on
your balance next time, girl.
&nbsp
Admit it,
I won.
&nbsp
- Yes!
- He won.
&nbsp
- Yeah, he did.
- He won.
&nbsp
Yes!
She must have been having an off day.
&nbsp
- What?
- Wow.
&nbsp
By the laws of Earth-19,
the prisoner is yours for the taking,
&nbsp
as is my life.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
&nbsp
We don't roll like that around here.
Come on.
&nbsp
In all the multiverse, I have...
never...
&nbsp
met anyone like you, Cisco.
Please, call me Vibe.
&nbsp
Or... or you can call me Cisco.
That's also allowed.
&nbsp
I'm just a regular guy.
Just a regular...
&nbsp
single guy.
It says you're totally fine.
&nbsp
So what happens now? Go back to your Earth?
Tell all your superiors
that you were bested in battle,
&nbsp
all the charges against H.R. are dropped.
No.
&nbsp
I tell them I killed him.
Wait, what?
&nbsp
If I return empty-handed,
they'll know I failed.
&nbsp
And I never fail.
Until today.
&nbsp
Okay, but if you
tell them that you killed me, then I...
&nbsp
You will never go back to Earth-19,
ever.
&nbsp
Do we have a deal?
Yeah. I guess we have a deal.
&nbsp
I don't really have anything to go home for.
You'll always have a home here, H.R.
&nbsp
Listen, I know there's
no coffee on your Earth
&nbsp
'cause of the whole
Blight thing or whatever,
&nbsp
but this... this is just an absurd
amount of coffee you're
bringing back to your Earth.
&nbsp
That can't be legal.
I mean, I won't tell if you won't.
&nbsp
You know, for someone
so fixated on enforcing the law,
&nbsp
you sure seem oddly at ease
about breaking it.
&nbsp
Well, I guess some laws are worth breaking
for the right person.
&nbsp
- Mm.
- Hmm.
&nbsp
So this goodbye then?
For now.
&nbsp
Wow.
What an exit.
&nbsp
Okay, you know, for the fastest man alive,
you are the slowest reader.
&nbsp
Hey this is your big article.
I'm not gonna rush through it.
&nbsp
I'm just kidding.
I read it five times already.
&nbsp
You sure sold the hell out of Kid Flash
as Central City's next super savior.
&nbsp
I'm sure Wally's loving that.
Well, I did promise him the front page.
&nbsp
But what do you think?
Do you think it'll make any difference?
&nbsp
Kid Flash already changed one thing
that we saw in the future.
&nbsp
No, I meant the article.
What?
&nbsp
The article?
I think you should be really proud.
&nbsp
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
&nbsp
It's the beginning of...
an amazing journalistic legacy.
&nbsp
- Really?
- Mm-hmm.
&nbsp
How amazing? Like Pulitzer amazing?
Time will tell.
&nbsp
Hey, I'm sorry. I...
Do you know what I realized?
&nbsp
Savitar, he said that I trapped him
wherever he is; you know what that means?
&nbsp
Means I beat him.
And I'm gonna do it again, I promise.
&nbsp
So don't worry.
The Flash is gonna save you.
&nbsp
My hero.
The thing they never tell you
&nbsp
is that nothing ever stays the same.
So the harder you work
to take down the bad guys,
&nbsp
the more they up their game.
- Hey.
&nbsp
Oh, I'm sorry. I didn't mean to interrupt.
No.
&nbsp
Just had to grab some stuff for...
Yeah.
&nbsp
I thought you were finished
working with that stuff?
&nbsp
Oh, no, it's just, uh, this is just for me.
No, the... the book, it... you know,
&nbsp
my own personal sense of accomplishment.
Well,
&nbsp
you've accomplished plenty.
Ha! Ha!
&nbsp
What have I accomplished, Francisco?
Well, for one,
&nbsp
you got me to risk my life to save yours.
And trust me, my friend,
that is a huge accomplishment.
&nbsp
Yeah, about that...
I just want to say that
&nbsp
I appreciate what you did for me.
Yeah, it's what we do
for our friends, right?
&nbsp
Besides, it was a way
for me to balance the scales.
&nbsp
Balance the scales, right.
What does that mean?
&nbsp
I just mean...
I can't tell you the amount of times
&nbsp
that I've been in your shoes
and a man with your face
&nbsp
has made me feel better.
Yeah, about that, I would...
&nbsp
I would love if you could share
some of my doppelganger's knowledge.
&nbsp
I would love to know what
the smarter versions of me think.
&nbsp
Okay. Um...
The first Wells told me
&nbsp
my time would come
to be a hero,
&nbsp
that it was my job to show up,
to be ready for when it did.
&nbsp
You know why I love working here?
Why?
&nbsp
We're all making investments in each other.
I made an investment in you,
&nbsp
and one day, that investment's gonna pay off
when you use that...
&nbsp
crazy way of thinking you have
to help me out.
&nbsp
I guess if he were here, he would say,
"Show up."
&nbsp
Yeah.
- Be ready.
- Yeah.
&nbsp
'Cause...
one day, you might need to save my ass.
&nbsp
Keep it up at this rate,
you're gonna reach Mach 3 soon.
&nbsp
I know, it's... it's crazy
how fast I've gotten
&nbsp
- in such a short time, right?
- Yeah.
&nbsp
And I'm gonna need you to get a lot faster.
Why's that?
&nbsp
Because I've done the math
over and over and I finally
&nbsp
realized that I've been looking
at things the wrong way.
&nbsp
I'm not gonna save Iris from Savitar.
You are.
&nbsp