I'm just sorting my salad.
I'm not on the bus anymore.
Anyway, I'm back with Pepsi Max.
Eva, this is Iben. My girlfriend.
It was just a hook up.
Why did you have to cheat
just because you thought I was?
It was your boyfriend who sent the tips.
My boyfriend didn't even know.
-The little blonde one. Isak?
Isn't that what he's called?
Hello! This is Isak.
I'm a bit busy at the moment.
But you can leave a
message after the beep.
Okay, just wait for the beep.
Isak. You better answer the
phone because I need to talk to you.
Hi.
-Hi.
Where's Isak?
Isak is a bit upset.
What happened?
His dad ran away,
and his mother completely collapsed.
Shit.
Yeah, it's quite shit.
But, is everything okay?
I don't really know.
His mother was already pretty crazy.
Yeah.
Do you want me to fetch someone or?
Eh, no. I just wanted to talk to
him about something.
He's not answering his phone.
-I think he turned it off.
How are you doing?
Good!
Or..
You know.
Yeah, I know.
Say hi to him.
Don't you want to come in?
I'm sure he wants to see you.
No, eh. I think..
He has you, so..
Yeah.
Bye.
What's the symbol for porridge?
I'm really struggling here.
"In the barn sits Santa with his Christmas porridge."
What's this porridge?
Porridge is porridge.
Why did you choose this song?
-I thought it was simple.
You have to hand it in next class.
-I know. And I forgot.
Porridge is the symbol of..
Life?
-Life? Fits perfectly. Life.
Did you do it?
What did you use?
-"Deilig er jorden"
Isn't that a really bad song?
It has a beautiful message.
Fuck! Message! What's the
message in "På låven sitter nissen"?
Vilde?
Hi!
Hi.
How's it going with you?
-Really good! With you guys?
Come sit with us.
I would really love to, but me,
Sara, Ingrid, and Pepsi Max are going to the coffee place.
So.. Maybe next time?
How's it going with your bus?
Good.
Did you find a sponsor yet?
Not yet.
It's just one thing. They'll come running soon.
Hi! Are you guys here?
Do you want to eat here?
I'll just go and get my
jacket, I'll be right back.
What happened just now?
Hi.
Look out when you go up the stairs.
Me?! It's you who has to look out.
Okay..
How's it going with Isak?
Yeah, it's going better now.
But he's not at school.
No, he's chilling at home for a bit.
Call or text him. He would like that.
Yeah, I'll do that. I forgot.
What do you have now?
-French.
Awkward.
Jonas!
What are you doing?!
Fuck, you have to back me up!
-You hooked up with his girl. If I were him I would've killed you.
Hi!
Hi.
How's it going?
Fine. Or..
It's going great.
How's it going with you?
It's going well.
I dumped Chris.
Did you?
-Hm-hm.
That's good, Iben!
-Yeah.
Also, I'm having a girl power
Christmas party on Friday. You have to come.
Girl power Christmas party?
-Yeah, where no third year guys are invited.
Okay.
They have too much power
at this school. All the drama is because of them.
Us girls have to start sticking up for each other.
Agreed?
-Agreed.
So, an all girls party?
No, no. We need guys there.
So I thought we could invite first year guys.
They're the most undervalued
group at school.
But come on Friday! Take your friends.
Yeah, cool!
If you know any delicious
first year guys, invite them.
Yeah, I'll try.
-Okay, good.
But, I was wondering..
Could you maybe ask Vilde if she can come?
Vilde?
Yeah, Vilde Lien.
She's a first year.
Of course. Just take her with you.
I think she'd be happy
if you could invite her.
Yeah, okay! I'll find her on Facebook.
Thanks.
I need water!
Have you heard from Vilde?
No.
Eh, no.
Iben, did you invite Vilde?
Yeah, she said she would come.
Check this on snapchat.
Even more first year guys!
Isak?
Hi! Eva!
How's it going with you?
It's going.. better.
Good.
How's it going with your mom now?
Good.. It's a lot of stress.
Her and dad will
surely find a solution.
Good.
So, it's going better with you now?
Now it's going better.
I have news for you.
-Yeah?
Me and Jonas are back together.
Seriously?
He hasn't said anything, but.. great!
Yeah, I know.
He has forgiven you and everything?
Yes!
Great!
So I just want to say..
Thanks so much for being there for me.
I don't know what I would've done without you.
I don't have many people I can trust.
But you're one of them. So, thanks.
I'm just glad you guys worked it out.
Yeah. I'm happy you support us.
Team Jonas!
There's just one thing I'm wondering.
Hm?
Did you also support us when
you told everyone that me and Chris hooked up?
Because our relationship
went to hell after that!
My whole life went to hell after that!
So you have to tell me what you were thinking.
Because I think it's psycho.
Why did you do it?!
What were you thinking?
You really don't know why?
No, I really don't know why!
Think about it.
What? Do you have..
Do you have..
.. feelings for me?
Like you didn't know?
No..
I didn't know.
So it's not that great for
me to have to listen to you..
.. talk about Jonas,
and me having to be your advisor.
That's really not great for me.
Sitting there like an idiot.
And hoping that one day you'll know..
.. that he's not good enough for you.
Isak, I didn't know.
Honestly, Eva. How did you not understand?
Anyway, it's not an excuse for what you did.
You outed me to the whole school!
-It was stupid. I fucked up.
I was drunk and..
I was also quite mad at you.
I thought you used me.
I didn't know Chris had a
psycho girlfriend who would create a bunch of drama.
Then I wouldn't have done it.
Eva, come.
Now!
Eva.
Don't..
You can't tell Jonas anything about this, okay?
Call an ambulance!
Vilde!
What happened?!
She came in, started staggering,
and then she tripped. She's not responding.
Is your mom home?
-No, no!
I think I killed William's baby tonight.