My name is Barry Allen,
&nbsp
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world, I'm an
ordinary forensic scientist,
&nbsp
but secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
&nbsp
I fight crime and find
other meta-humans like me.
&nbsp
In an attempt to stop the
evil speedster Savitar,
&nbsp
I was accidentally
thrust into the future,
&nbsp
and I saw him murder
the woman that I love.
&nbsp
But I won't let that happen.
I'm gonna do everything in my power
&nbsp
to change the future,
and I'm the only one
&nbsp
fast enough to keep her alive.
I am The Flash.
&nbsp
Previously on "The Flash"...
When I threw the Philosopher's
Stone into the Speed Force,
&nbsp
I accidentally ran into the future.
I saw Savitar murder you.
&nbsp
- How are you gonna tell Dad?
- I'm not.
&nbsp
If you guys got something going on,
I hope you know you can talk to me.
&nbsp
Every night when I go to bed,
I'm afraid that I'm
gonna wake up and be her.
&nbsp
I didn't ask for these powers,
just like you didn't ask
to be used by Savitar.
&nbsp
So you're telling me that
every time I'm blacking out...
&nbsp
You've become Alchemy.
Alchemy can restore the powers
&nbsp
that people had in Flashpoint.
What Alchemy did was not your fault.
&nbsp
I'm saying that at this
point in his training,
&nbsp
- you're faster than Barry!
- What?
&nbsp
It's crazy how fast I've
gotten in such a short time.
&nbsp
And I'm gonna need you
to get a lot faster.
&nbsp
I'm not gonna save Iris from Savitar.
You are.
&nbsp
- So this is it, huh?
- Yeah.
&nbsp
This is the starting line to our race.
Cisco set up sensors
all along the course,
&nbsp
and he'll be tracking your speed
all the way to the finish line
&nbsp
on the other side of town.
No, I meant this is it...
&nbsp
the day the greatest upset in
speedster history goes down.
&nbsp
Wally, man, this isn't
about winning or losing.
&nbsp
Okay?
This is about training
&nbsp
so you can get faster and
beat Savitar and save Iris.
&nbsp
- Yeah, which I'm gonna do.
- Okay.
&nbsp
But first I'm gonna
make you eat my dust.
&nbsp
I'm sorry.
Okay, you know there
is a reason they call me
&nbsp
the fastest man alive.
Cisco, you good?
&nbsp
Ladies and gentlemen,
the Central City Speedster
500 is about to begin.
&nbsp
But first, I've got five-to-one odds
Barry takes down Wally.
&nbsp
- Any takers?
- Yep.
&nbsp
Game of speculation?
Are we... we're betting?
&nbsp
Yeah, no, I'm in.
On my Earth, financial
wagering was banned
&nbsp
after an unfortunate incident
with Vice President Al Capone.
&nbsp
Well, lucky for you, you live here now.
- Yes.
- Put me down for 20 for Barry.
&nbsp
- Joe, got to be in it... come on.
- No, not me.
&nbsp
That's a Sophie's Choice
I'm not gonna make.
&nbsp
$80 on Barry.
Mama needs a new confocal microscope.
&nbsp
All right, H.R., you put
your life in my hands,
&nbsp
so I know for a fact
you like high stakes.
&nbsp
How much you in for?
Wallace's recent speed tests
ensure that he is a lock.
&nbsp
Put me down for an Abe Lincoln.
- Hm?
- Uh, 100.
&nbsp
Whatever 100 is on this
Earth, put me down for that.
&nbsp
- Guys, we're ready.
- All right, all right.
&nbsp
All bets are in, and may the
odds be ever in your favor.
&nbsp
Gentlemen, start your engines.
- Ready?
- Get set.
&nbsp
Go.
At the first marker, 1/3 of the way in,
&nbsp
Flash is in the lead...
or is that Kid Flash?
&nbsp
Kid Flash! Come on, little Joseph, go.
Come on, mama needs a new pair of shoes.
&nbsp
Come on, Wallace, down the lane!
I think he's done this before.
&nbsp
Ooh, second marker. Wally's in the lead.
Yeah, Wallace! That's my boy!
&nbsp
- You mean that's my boy.
- That's your boy.
&nbsp
I want to double down.
I want to double down on that right now.
&nbsp
Oh, H.R., big spender.
- You serious?
- Serious?
&nbsp
Serious as a heart attack, Rich.
Guys, they're neck and neck.
&nbsp
And almost at the finish line.
- Oh!
- Oh, yes!
&nbsp
- Pay up.
- Hmm?
&nbsp
Now?
Do you guys take IOUs?
&nbsp
Come on, man, that didn't count.
You know I can't phase yet.
&nbsp
Man, you just saw me do it, right?
And you have to be ready
to face any obstacle
&nbsp
that's put in your path.
Yeah, well, don't worry, Barry.
&nbsp
I'm gonna get faster.
Pretty soon I'm gonna
be faster than you.
&nbsp
Oh, yeah?
Well, until then, what's my name?
&nbsp
Subtitle sync and corrections by
awaqeded for www.addic7ed.com.
&nbsp
Joe, hey, this one, is, uh...
Pretty ghastly, Detective, I warn you.
&nbsp
- That's the body?
- Yeah, why?
&nbsp
Because he died less
than eight hours ago.
&nbsp
Eight hours?
He was a chef here...
&nbsp
Stuart Holzman... and
the owner confirmed
&nbsp
- that he was working last night.
- Huh.
&nbsp
That's a lot of damage
in a short amount of time.
&nbsp
We thinking he's a meta?
Possibly, although certain chemicals
&nbsp
can cause a similar reaction.
Yeah, any acid with a pH below two.
&nbsp
Precisely.
We could be looking for
an aggressive variant
&nbsp
of a necrotized fasciitis.
A flesh-eating disease.
&nbsp
In a restaurant?
I'm never eating out again.
&nbsp
Okay, so an autopsy
might help us hone in
&nbsp
on what really did this.
Yes, I agree.
&nbsp
Unfortunately, County denied my request
for a 3D image medical scanner,
&nbsp
which would make short
work of the process.
&nbsp
Okay, well, we have
one at S.T.A.R. Labs.
&nbsp
Allen, this is an active investigation.
There is protocol to follow...
&nbsp
surely?
Not if we're gonna figure this out.
&nbsp
Okay, I'll bag the body
myself and meet you there.
&nbsp
Great.
Iris, hey.
&nbsp
You okay?
Yeah, I'm just, uh,
&nbsp
running up against a deadline, so...
Since I have you both, I wanted to ask,
&nbsp
um, Cecile's daughter, Joanie,
is in town, and I was thinking
&nbsp
that maybe we could all get together.
If you don't think it's too soon.
&nbsp
I mean, I haven't exactly been
dating Cecile for that long.
&nbsp
It's not too early, Joe.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
&nbsp
And Jitters... is that cool?
Or is that too casual?
&nbsp
Dad, don't worry, okay?
It's great. Joanie's gonna love you.
&nbsp
I love my kids.
I'm gonna set it up. Thank you.
&nbsp
All right.
It's nice to see him so happy.
&nbsp
Yeah, it is.
You okay?
&nbsp
Hey, I need to show you
something at S.T.A.R. Labs.
&nbsp
Okay.
Look.
&nbsp
That's the name of the
restaurant where we just were.
&nbsp
- Yeah.
- I spoke to the owner,
&nbsp
and he said he doesn't think
that the restaurant can survive
&nbsp
an attack like this...
that they'd most likely
&nbsp
have to reopen under a new name.
It's all coming true, Barry.
&nbsp
No.
I thought things were changing.
&nbsp
Things are changing, okay? They are.
I was supposed to stop Plunder, right?
&nbsp
And instead Wally did.
And we're gonna...
&nbsp
Stop Savitar too. I'm making sure of it.
What if we can't stop all of this?
&nbsp
I'm scared, Barry.
Okay, uh...
&nbsp
Maybe we should tell Joe.
No, no.
&nbsp
No, we agreed that we wouldn't.
Besides, you saw him earlier.
&nbsp
He's... he's planning
for a future with Cecile.
&nbsp
If we tell him about Savitar,
it's all he's gonna think about.
&nbsp
I-I can't do that to him.
- I won't.
- Okay.
&nbsp
Whatever you want.
Now listen to me.
&nbsp
I promise you I'm doing
everything in my power
&nbsp
to make sure that that
future never happens.
&nbsp
Okay.
You think this is what it's
like to be a character on "CSI"?
&nbsp
What do they hope to gain
from that examination?
&nbsp
They're trying to find
the exact cause of death.
&nbsp
Once we know that,
we'll have a better idea
&nbsp
of what we're dealing with.
But until then, we need to train.
&nbsp
I'm gonna teach you everything I know,
starting with phasing.
&nbsp
- Yes! Finally.
- You know what we should do?
&nbsp
We should concoct some simulations
to help Wallace learn this new skill.
&nbsp
What do you say, Francisco?
I got one word for you:
&nbsp
quebracho.
Let's go.
&nbsp
Quebracho!
What's his name?
&nbsp
Doesn't really matter much now, does it?
Of course, we should
call him by his name.
&nbsp
After everything he's been through,
he deserves that much respect.
&nbsp
He is a corpse,
thus impervious to such bedside manners.
&nbsp
Well, thank goodness,
'cause I'd hate to have
&nbsp
to subject him to yours.
Victim is male, between 30 and 40,
&nbsp
with a highly necrotized epidermis.
We plan to do a full-body scan
&nbsp
and a chest wall retraction.
Julian, look.
&nbsp
The decay continues even
after the tissue's dead.
&nbsp
This is... this is not a bacteria.
Or any other disease
known to medical science.
&nbsp
That was one crazy set, man.
I'm telling you, Rob, you
keep wailing on that saxophone,
&nbsp
you're gonna running up to
Lee Jay Thompson in no time.
&nbsp
All right, have a good
one. Catch you laters.
&nbsp
All right.
Whoo!
&nbsp
- Do I know you?
- Unlikely.
&nbsp
But I know you, Julio Mendez.
Man, that was some set.
&nbsp
Your cover of "Dock of the Bay"
took me to a different time and place.
&nbsp
Well, I'm glad you dug the set, man.
Hey, before you go, uh,
&nbsp
I'd just really like to shake your hand.
Yeah, anything for a fan.
&nbsp
What'd you do to me?
What you deserve for all
the pain you caused me.
&nbsp
Oh!
Oh, no!
&nbsp
Ouch!
That hurt like a...
&nbsp
Like you ran into a giant wooden wall?
'Cause you did.
&nbsp
And it's not just any big wooden wall.
That's double-reinforced quebracho.
&nbsp
That's like the strongest stuff
on the planet, right there.
&nbsp
Well, fantastic choice, Cisco.
Well, it shouldn't matter if
it's wood or steel or stone.
&nbsp
If you're moving fast enough,
you can phase through anything.
&nbsp
Even molten lava... you know, if
you ever ended up in a volcano.
&nbsp
You know, I... I still don't get it.
- How do you do this?
- All right.
&nbsp
Here. Watch.
When you vibrate at the
natural frequency of air,
&nbsp
your body, your cells,
will be in an excited state
&nbsp
that'll allow you...
to phase.
&nbsp
Yeah, it's not... it's
not really helping.
&nbsp
What exactly do I do?
Connect with your body, right?
&nbsp
Connect with the air.
Be pure electricity.
&nbsp
You have to feel everything
that's around you.
&nbsp
All right?
So go fast and feel things.
&nbsp
Yeah, no worries.
You can do this, Wallace.
&nbsp
Okay.
All right, all right.
&nbsp
You can do this.
Oh!
&nbsp
All right, again.
- Yeah?
- You got this.
&nbsp
- This isn't working.
- It's not working.
&nbsp
You've been training him. What's worked?
You know what works with that guy?
&nbsp
Vocal encouragement.
You got this, Wallace!
&nbsp
I don't know why you even ask him.
What did Wells do with me?
&nbsp
His plan was, uh, more
methodically constructed
&nbsp
than John Doe's in "Seven."
And he had a bit more
time to work it out
&nbsp
by, give or take, 15 years.
Well, we don't have 15 years.
&nbsp
I have a crime scene. I got to go.
I'll be back.
&nbsp
Just make sure he keeps practicing.
Go, Wallace!
&nbsp
Body was found by that bicyclist.
Same M.O. as the first one.
&nbsp
This victim was
performing here last night.
&nbsp
He's a lounge singer named Julio Mendez.
Julio Mendez?
&nbsp
Has anybody seen Detective West?
In Flashpoint, he was Captain Mendez.
&nbsp
Sorry. In Flashpoint, this...
this alternate universe
&nbsp
that you lived in,
he worked at the CCPD?
&nbsp
Yeah.
Wait a second, the other...
the other Vic, Stuart Holzman...
&nbsp
do we have a photo of him?
- Yeah.
- Can I see it?
&nbsp
Yeah, hold on. That's him.
What is it?
&nbsp
He was a cop there, too.
So this is the second
dead cop from Flashpoint?
&nbsp
Yeah.
We got to figure out who this guy is.
&nbsp
Well, if we hurry,
there's still a chance
&nbsp
we can get some of the attacker's
residual DNA before this
corpse disintegrates,
&nbsp
but we've got to move quick.
Barry, you can help with that.
&nbsp
All right, come on.
Did anybody see me?
&nbsp
Damn, I barely saw you.
Look, we got to get going.
&nbsp
Hey, Joe, hold on.
Um, look, I-I know how excited you are
&nbsp
for this coffee thing
with Joanie and Cecile,
&nbsp
but I think we should hold off.
I don't think it's a
good idea right now.
&nbsp
Bar, these two attacks
don't establish a pattern.
&nbsp
- Well...
- And besides, I'm a cop.
&nbsp
If I canceled my plans
every time I was in danger,
&nbsp
I'd never leave the house.
I-I hear you.
&nbsp
I would just feel a lot better
knowing you were someplace safe.
&nbsp
Name a place safer than a coffee shop
with my two speedster sons.
&nbsp
Meeting Joanie is important to Cecile,
therefore it's important to me.
&nbsp
Some things are worth taking risks for.
All right. Let's get out of here.
&nbsp
Anything?
Aside from this body
&nbsp
disintegrating before our eyes?
Nothing unusual.
&nbsp
There must be a heightened
point of necrosis somewhere.
&nbsp
Look!
We have less than 50 minutes
before this corpse disintegrates
&nbsp
into ash like the last one.
- We need to find it now.
- I'm aware.
&nbsp
This might be a faster
process if I did it alone.
&nbsp
You know, I've done
autopsies before, Julian.
&nbsp
I'm sure you have.
This might just be a quicker process
&nbsp
if I did it alone.
What are you doing?
&nbsp
The gradation is darker
on the palm of his hand
&nbsp
from the point of contact.
I see, I see.
&nbsp
You know, I used to think
Barry was overreacting
&nbsp
when he complained about
sharing a lab with you.
&nbsp
But now I understand his frustration.
Believe me, no one is
more frustrated than I.
&nbsp
You do realize that it's
possible not to be a jerk
&nbsp
all the time, right?
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
&nbsp
Two strains of DNA.
One of them must be from our killer.
&nbsp
But, you know, there's
something else here.
&nbsp
Have you ever seen
anything like that before?
&nbsp
I have...
in all the meta husks
created by Alchemy.
&nbsp
Which means the meta that
killed our two innocent people...
&nbsp
was created by me.
- French roast for Cecile.
- Thank you.
&nbsp
Non-dairy green tea latte for Joanie.
You not much of a
coffee drinker, Joanie?
&nbsp
Well, I used to be, but then I learned
hot roasted coffee beans contain
&nbsp
cancer-causing levels of acrylamide.
Well, damn.
&nbsp
Uh, Joanie, Cecile
says you're at Coast U?
&nbsp
- What are you studying?
- I'm undecided.
&nbsp
Are you leaning towards anything?
Not really.
&nbsp
Uh, Coast U's pretty far, right?
Do you ever miss Central City?
&nbsp
Actually, I like it better there.
Well, there is one thing
I miss about Central City.
&nbsp
What's that?
You're gonna regret that you asked.
&nbsp
Kid Flash.
She's a little... little obsessed.
&nbsp
Kid Flash is the one thing
you miss about Central City?
&nbsp
Whoa, Barry, slow down.
You don't have to be
so skeptical about it.
&nbsp
Kid Flash is cool.
What do you like best
about him, specifically?
&nbsp
Well, he's fearless.
- And he's brave.
- Yeah.
&nbsp
He's a hero, and he's probably
pretty cute under that mask.
&nbsp
Yeah, I think so, too.
Come on, Joanie, honey, Kid Flash?
&nbsp
He's a showboat...
he's snapping selfies,
&nbsp
he's leaving graffiti
bolts on buildings.
&nbsp
- Okay, that's his signature move.
- That's kind of his signature.
&nbsp
Yeah, well, from what I hear,
The Flash is the one who's
actually saving people.
&nbsp
Sounds like Cecile's Team Flash.
Uh, Joanie,
&nbsp
my dad would never brag about this,
but he knows Kid Flash.
&nbsp
You do?
Is my mom right?
&nbsp
Who's the real hero...
Flash or Kid Flash?
&nbsp
Mmm... they both are.
Uh, they both do great
things for Central City.
&nbsp
Okay, but if you had to choose?
I-I don't...
&nbsp
I don't think I could choose.
Yeah, but if you, like, had to.
&nbsp
Um, would you go get me
some cream, Wally, please?
&nbsp
Yes.
Ah, this is work. I'll
be right back, sorry.
&nbsp
- Hey, what's up?
- Barry, we got some DNA
&nbsp
off Mendez's corpse.
We were about to match
it with CCPD records.
&nbsp
The meta's name is Clive Yorkin.
We're sending you his info now.
&nbsp
Detective Joe West!
Long time, no see.
&nbsp
Do I know you?
You don't remember me?
&nbsp
You and your cronies had a
very fun time ruining my life.
&nbsp
Not gonna let you do
that this time around.
&nbsp
I think you have the wrong guy.
No, no.
&nbsp
You're the Joe West I remember.
Look a lot more full
of life now, though.
&nbsp
But don't worry...
I can change that.
&nbsp
- Everybody get back.
- Joanie, go.
&nbsp
Everybody get out of
here. Everybody go! Go!
&nbsp
Yes, everybody run.
I only want him.
&nbsp
You can't hide up there, Detective.
No one can hide from me anymore.
&nbsp
- Joe...
- One more step, and I'll shoot.
&nbsp
Didn't work then.
Won't work now, either.
&nbsp
Told ya.
Stop!
&nbsp
Ah, ah, ah.
Can't touch me, speedster.
&nbsp
I knew it. Kid Flash is the hero.
Well, thank God for Kid Flash, huh?
&nbsp
He's gone.
This guy's got the touch of death.
&nbsp
Yeah, he does, and it's not just people.
Anything he touched turned to ash.
&nbsp
Joe, I... I really think
you should just stay here
&nbsp
until we find Yorkin.
No, I'm gonna go check
on Cecile and Joanie.
&nbsp
They were pretty shook up.
Dad, are you crazy?
&nbsp
This guy wants to kill you.
If it wasn't for Wally
and Barry, he could've.
&nbsp
He could've killed any one of us.
Come on, we have been through
much worse metas than Yorkin.
&nbsp
What?
Iris, I'm fine. We're all fine.
&nbsp
We're not losing anybody today.
Maybe not today, but soon.
&nbsp
Soon?
W-what are you saying?
&nbsp
Iris...
Wally, he needs to know.
&nbsp
Needs to know what?
When Barry threw the Philosopher's Stone
&nbsp
into the Speed Force,
there was an explosion,
&nbsp
and he was propelled to the future.
The future?
&nbsp
It was a few months from now.
What he saw was himself
&nbsp
standing before Savitar...
and me.
&nbsp
Right before Savitar killed me.
So you're saying that in a few months...
&nbsp
you die?
Unless we can change the future, Dad.
&nbsp
Which we're gonna do, Joe, okay?
I'm not... we're not
gonna let this happen.
&nbsp
How long have you known about this?
How long?
&nbsp
A couple weeks now, Joe.
And you're just telling me now?
&nbsp
That's my daughter!
Dad, I didn't want them to say anything
&nbsp
because I knew how you would react.
This is not something you
keep from your father, Iris!
&nbsp
You should've known that.
- And you should've too.
- I know, Joe.
&nbsp
Look, I can understand why
they didn't want to tell me
&nbsp
because they didn't grow
up under the same roof
&nbsp
that you did.
They don't know... they don't
know what my baby girl means to me,
&nbsp
Barry, but you do.
I know.
&nbsp
Joe...
I'll talk to him.
&nbsp
I'm... I'm gonna go to CCPD,
see if I can find anything
that might lead us to Yorkin.
&nbsp
Well, that went swimmingly.
Joe's right. We should've
told him before now.
&nbsp
What you should have told him
is that I'm the one responsible,
&nbsp
that the meta trying to kill
him is one that I created.
&nbsp
Julian, you can't change
what happened to you.
&nbsp
It's not your fault.
You keep saying that,
but it is my fault.
&nbsp
People are responsible
for their own actions.
&nbsp
To say otherwise is just...
it's just a way to make
yourself feel better.
&nbsp
Is that what you think I'm doing?
Making excuses for things
I've done in the past?
&nbsp
You know, I'm really starting to regret
bringing you in here.
&nbsp
Come on, Dad.
Ah, hey, Dad, it's me...
&nbsp
calling, again.
Look, I know you're upset,
&nbsp
but, um, give me a call back, okay?
I love you.
&nbsp
Honey?
Good evening, Iris West.
&nbsp
It's Iris's panic alarm.
She's at the apartment. I'll call Barry.
&nbsp
No, no, no. I-I got this.
Uh, he's at CCPD, and I'm closer.
&nbsp
Okay, go!
You know, initially,
I wanted your dad dead.
&nbsp
But then I thought, "If I
really want to make him suffer,
&nbsp
I should kill his daughter instead."
This is not how I'm supposed to die.
&nbsp
Oh, I'm pretty sure it is.
No, stop!
&nbsp
Too late, Kid Flash.
Me or her?
&nbsp
I got you, baby girl.
I'm not going anywhere.
&nbsp
Elevated heart rate. Temperature's 104.
The decay is reaching
her subcutaneous tissue.
&nbsp
I'm here, all right? What happened?
Yorkin went after her.
&nbsp
Why didn't you call me?
Because I was here.
&nbsp
You call me! All right?
We have to give her something.
&nbsp
There has to be
something we can give her.
&nbsp
It's not bacteria.
Antibiotics won't work.
&nbsp
We have to do something.
Nothing's not an option.
&nbsp
Okay, what do you do
when a banana ripens too quickly?
&nbsp
- Put it in the freezer.
- That's brilliant.
&nbsp
Caitlin, you can freeze her arm.
It'll stop the spread of decay
&nbsp
and give us some time to find a cure.
I trust you.
&nbsp
I can't, even if I wanted to.
We're not talking about a cold blast.
&nbsp
This is a specific and
continuous cold stream.
&nbsp
Too high a temperature
and the decay spreads,
&nbsp
too low and the frostbite will
destroy your nerve endings.
&nbsp
And that long using my powers,
I could lose control.
&nbsp
Caitlin, you are strong,
okay? Stronger than you know.
&nbsp
You are not going to lose control.
Caitlin, try, please.
&nbsp
It worked.
Oh, thank God.
&nbsp
- You okay?
- So far, so good.
&nbsp
Wally, where are you going?
Out of the way where
I can't screw up again.
&nbsp
You okay?
Yeah.
&nbsp
Hey, look, what I said back there...
No, you were right.
&nbsp
We should've called you.
I just thought... I
thought I could do it.
&nbsp
I thought I was ready.
Obviously, I'm not.
&nbsp
It's not on you.
I wasn't fast enough, Barry.
&nbsp
That... that is totally on me.
No, not really.
&nbsp
It's not, all right?
Look, when I got these powers, I-I...
&nbsp
I was really lucky, in a weird way.
You know, I had a lot of people
helping me through all of this.
&nbsp
I had Wells... both of 'em...
and Jay and Zolomon.
&nbsp
I mean, two of them
turned out to be bad guys,
&nbsp
but even they were good teachers
who really taught me
how to use my powers.
&nbsp
I just don't think that
I've been that for you yet.
&nbsp
You're telling me everything
that I need to learn.
&nbsp
I'm just not getting it. I...
No, that's not it.
&nbsp
It's... I've been...
I've been letting you
coast by on your raw talent,
&nbsp
which you have a lot of, but
teaching... it's a lot more
&nbsp
than just doing something
and expecting you to follow.
&nbsp
It's about inspiring
and empowering you to use your gifts
&nbsp
to succeed on your own.
That's what I need to do.
&nbsp
That's what I'm gonna do from now on.
So the next time you're
out there and you're alone,
&nbsp
you will win.
Deal?
&nbsp
Deal.
H.R. and I just came up with a way
&nbsp
to track down Yorkin, and it's...
crazy.
&nbsp
Like, defies time and space crazy.
Okay, here's what we know.
&nbsp
We know Yorkin's going after
cops in Flashpoint, right?
&nbsp
What we don't know is
who he's going after.
&nbsp
But if we find out who they are,
then we can be ready for him.
&nbsp
Right, so how do we do that?
We vibe Flashpoint.
&nbsp
Flashpoint doesn't exist anymore.
Stop you right there, BA.
&nbsp
Flashpoint doesn't exist
anymore in this universe.
&nbsp
But in quantum mechanics,
the daughter universe theory tell us...
&nbsp
- Universe theory.
- For every decision you make,
&nbsp
a universe exists where you don't.
Yeah, I actually went to that class.
&nbsp
You better be going to all your classes.
So if there is a universe
where you stay in Flashpoint,
&nbsp
Francisco here could vibe it.
And you're sure you can do that?
&nbsp
No, no. Not at all.
But Gypsy did say I could do
some pretty incredible things
&nbsp
- with my powers...
- Yeah, she did.
&nbsp
Things I'm not even aware of yet, so...
things I haven't even imagined.
&nbsp
- Well, let's get to imagining.
- All right.
&nbsp
- What do you need me to do?
- Oh!
&nbsp
All I need you to do is to stand there,
focus on Flashpoint, okay?
&nbsp
Focus on CCPD, Joe,
Mendez, that part of it,
&nbsp
and I'll take care of the rest.
It worked!
&nbsp
I'm here.
Huh, for some reason
I thought Flashpoint
&nbsp
would look a lot different.
Okay, all right, if I were Joe West,
&nbsp
where would I be?
He was at the same desk.
&nbsp
Got ya.
If it wasn't for this takedown,
&nbsp
we'd be having a different
conversation right now, Joe.
&nbsp
Understood, Captain.
Ooh, Joe's in trouble.
&nbsp
Ladies and gentlemen,
for today's perp walk,
&nbsp
we have a literal degenerate:
the one and only Clive Yorkin.
&nbsp
Here we go.
Captain Mendez, Detective West,
&nbsp
thanks for the assist.
Couldn't have bagged
this goon without you.
&nbsp
Get him to Iron Heights.
Stone...
&nbsp
- Who's Stone?
- Stone... that was the other cop.
&nbsp
And let me tell you,
she loves her perp walks.
&nbsp
Laura Stone. She's a PI.
Yeah, that's her.
&nbsp
It was you, Mendez, Holzman, and her.
You guys took down Yorkin in Flashpoint.
&nbsp
Well, then, that means
she's the only one
&nbsp
that Yorkin hasn't gone after yet.
Classic example of
saving the best for last.
&nbsp
I'm on it. You guys stay here
and try to figure out
how to catch somebody
&nbsp
we can't touch.
Joe West. Long time, no see.
&nbsp
Hey.
I wish it were under
better circumstances.
&nbsp
Listen, you're being targeted by a meta.
Sweetheart, take a look over there.
&nbsp
I'm the only one doing
the targeting here.
&nbsp
That chick's husband is paying me
twice my going rate, so scram.
&nbsp
Look at this.
The guy that's coming after you
&nbsp
can do that with one touch.
Attention, all passengers.
The S.T.A.R. City Express
&nbsp
- is now boarding all platforms.
- How about we multitask?
&nbsp
All aboard, please.
Hey, Julian.
&nbsp
You have anything?
Look, it's early days, but...
&nbsp
first tests show that her blood
is attacking the cells in her body.
&nbsp
Wait, that's the
opposite of how my blood
&nbsp
causes cells to regenerate.
Precisely.
&nbsp
Can we use my blood to save her?
Listen, I don't think that your blood
&nbsp
is the key to saving Iris.
But I do think it might
be exactly what we need
&nbsp
to take down Yorkin.
All is not lost, mate.
&nbsp
- The decay is spreading.
- Why?
&nbsp
I don't know.
Caitlin?
&nbsp
- Caitlin?
- I'm losing control.
&nbsp
Okay, all right, it's spreading.
We need you.
&nbsp
Hey, it's okay. It's okay.
Just a little bit
longer, and she's dead.
&nbsp
How's that for changing the future?
I know who you are, Caitlin.
You do not want to do this.
&nbsp
This is who I am. You said it.
It's time for me to take
responsibility for my actions.
&nbsp
Time for me to own who I really am.
Who you are is Caitlin Snow.
&nbsp
I know firsthand the battle
going on inside of you.
&nbsp
I know what it feels like.
When it happened to me, I lost.
&nbsp
All right? I was weak, and I let it win.
And I did... I did horrible things
&nbsp
to a lot of good people.
And you don't have to do that.
&nbsp
You're not gonna do that.
You're stronger than I am, Caitlin.
&nbsp
You're far stronger than I am.
You're one of the strongest
people I've ever known.
&nbsp
You can win this fight.
Iris needs your help now.
&nbsp
It's all right.
It's gonna be all right.
&nbsp
And how do you know this
guy's coming after me, Joe?
&nbsp
We have pretty reliable Intel.
Look, Laura, this is not
someone you should be ignoring.
&nbsp
He's dangerous.
He's already killed two cops.
&nbsp
He tried to kill me and my daughter.
Well, I've certainly pissed
off a lot of people in my day.
&nbsp
But the only thing I fear now is
forgetting to clear my browser.
&nbsp
Consider me warned.
Oh, my God.
&nbsp
What is that?
It's Joe's panic alarm.
&nbsp
He must be on that train.
There's no way that train can stop...
&nbsp
It's not gonna stop in time.
We have to get everyone out of there.
&nbsp
We don't have enough time.
- Oh, no!
- What is it?
&nbsp
- Everybody brace yourselves!
- What's happening?
&nbsp
We're gonna move the train.
How are we gonna do that?
&nbsp
I'll vibrate it.
I'll vibrate it fast enough
that it can phase through this.
&nbsp
- You can do that?
- I don't know.
&nbsp
I've never tried before.
Everybody hold on!
&nbsp
Is that even possible?
We're about to find out.
&nbsp
Holy Kardashians.
- Yeah!
- All right!
&nbsp
Barry. Barry!
We're good, man.
&nbsp
Took a lot out of me, but it worked.
Yeah, maybe, but we got another problem.
&nbsp
Yorkin's back.
You know what they say, Kid Flash.
&nbsp
If at first you don't
succeed, try, try again.
&nbsp
You have to stop him.
I don't have it in me right now.
&nbsp
I need you to get your blood into him.
It'll counteract his cells
and negate his powers.
&nbsp
How am I supposed to do that
when I can't even touch him?
&nbsp
You're gonna phase it into him.
You know I've never done that before.
&nbsp
And you just watched me do
something I'd never done,
&nbsp
but I did it because I had to.
All right?
&nbsp
I know you can do it, okay?
I need you to believe it, too.
&nbsp
Now run, Wally.
Run.
&nbsp
It worked!
- I did it!
- You sure did.
&nbsp
Good-bye, Kid Flash.
Oh, wha... look at that.
&nbsp
Your powers are neutralized, Yorkin.
What did you do?
&nbsp
I won.
Dad?
&nbsp
The last time I was this
happy looking in your eyes,
&nbsp
you'd just been born.
Hey.
&nbsp
It's okay. You're okay.
Yorkin's done.
&nbsp
What happened?
I'll tell you what happened.
&nbsp
Wallace was a total badass.
That's what happened.
&nbsp
Translate.
Yeah, he phased his speedster blood
&nbsp
into Yorkin and neutralized his powers.
That's the science behind it.
&nbsp
I had a great teacher.
And me?
&nbsp
Once Yorkin's blood was stabilized,
we actually managed to get
an antidote that cured you.
&nbsp
You'll have to wear the
bandage for a few days,
&nbsp
but other than that,
you're absolutely recovered.
&nbsp
Thank you.
I know what you risked for me.
&nbsp
I had some help.
Couldn't have done it alone.
&nbsp
It was all of us working together.
Yup, really proud of everybody.
&nbsp
Great job. Big ideas today.
My point is, if we're gonna
save Iris from Savitar,
&nbsp
we're gonna have to up our game.
No more lies...
&nbsp
even well-intentioned ones.
We have to be completely
real with each other.
&nbsp
- I agree.
- I agree with Joe, too.
&nbsp
From here on out, complete honesty.
Honesty.
&nbsp
All right. Get some rest, all right?
I'll check on you in a bit.
&nbsp
- Bar?
- Yeah?
&nbsp
Savitar's prophecy of someone dying...
was it Iris?
&nbsp
Yeah.
But it's not gonna happen.
&nbsp
Look, I'm glad she comes
first in your life now.
&nbsp
If you're gonna date my daughter,
that's the way it should be.
&nbsp
You're still a close second.
It's just heartwarming.
&nbsp
It's just truly heartwarming.
You're already crafting
a version of this
&nbsp
for your book, aren't you?
"Peace finally descends
upon the family West."
&nbsp
The West family, or family West?
Right, it's time I get to work.
&nbsp
At this hour?
Yes, there's still one
husk meta out there,
&nbsp
and I intend to find him.
Good night.
&nbsp
- Hey, Julian?
- Hi.
&nbsp
I don't think you're weak
because of what happened
to you with Savitar.
&nbsp
The strength that I found
to stay in control...
&nbsp
that came from you.
So thank you.
&nbsp
Well, I wasn't gonna let Iris
die at the hands of Killer Frost, was I?
&nbsp
I knew there was a good guy
inside of you somewhere...
&nbsp
one that the rest of us would
like to see a little more often.
&nbsp
Good night.
Do you want to get a drink?
&nbsp
Uh... what? As in now?
Yeah.
&nbsp
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I'd love that.
- Hey.
&nbsp
What brings you to my
neck of the bullpen?
&nbsp
Oh, Joanie's headed back for midterms.
We just thought we'd
come and say good-bye.
&nbsp
Aw.
I was hoping a redo on the coffee,
&nbsp
seeing as how the last
one went off the rails.
&nbsp
- Yeah.
- Are you kidding me?
&nbsp
I got to see Kid Flash
in action, right up close.
&nbsp
Well, we got a lot of
stories about Kid Flash
&nbsp
I can guarantee you've never heard.
Maybe we can tell you them over dinner
&nbsp
next time you come to town.
I have a long weekend next month.
&nbsp
You sure you're ready
to commit to something
&nbsp
that far in the future?
I am absolutely sure.
&nbsp
Hmm?
Good.
&nbsp
We should go.
- Good luck at school.
- Thank you. See ya.
&nbsp
- Bye, babe.
- Bye.
&nbsp
Okay, good as new.
Actually, it's better than
new with the three extra locks
&nbsp
that I added.
Which you didn't have to do.
&nbsp
Well, Cisco did offer to build us
a custom security door,
&nbsp
but we've both seen how well
those things keep people
out of S.T.A.R. Labs.
&nbsp
- So...
- I like deadbolts.
&nbsp
- Deadbolts work.
- Yeah.
&nbsp
It's just with... what happened here,
I want to make sure you feel safe.
&nbsp
I do.
About everything?
&nbsp
You know, you've been saying for weeks
that you were gonna
save me from Savitar.
&nbsp
- Mm-hmm.
- And while I trust you
&nbsp
with my life, it was
hard not to feel scared.
&nbsp
You know, sometimes it feels
like The Flash is this guy
&nbsp
my boyfriend becomes when he
runs off to save other people.
&nbsp
Like I'm the only one
who doesn't get The Flash.
&nbsp
He felt separate from you.
But yesterday when you saved me,
&nbsp
I remembered that I have
no reason to be scared.
&nbsp
Mm-mm.
The man I love is a superhero.
&nbsp
I love and trust you, Barry Allen...
The Flash.
&nbsp
I love all of you, and I always will.
I love you.
&nbsp
That was so nice.
Jesse!
&nbsp
No, no, no, no.
What's wrong?
&nbsp
Grodd.
He's got my dad.
&nbsp
And he has him in Gorilla City.
Subtitle sync and corrections by
awaqeded for www.addic7ed.com.
&nbsp