My name is Barry Allen,
&nbsp
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world, I'm an
ordinary forensic scientist,
&nbsp
but secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
&nbsp
I fight crime and find
other meta-humans like me.
&nbsp
In an attempt to stop the
evil speedster Savitar,
&nbsp
I was accidentally
thrust into the future,
&nbsp
and I saw him murder
the woman that I love.
&nbsp
But I won't let that happen.
I'm gonna do everything in
my power to change the future,
&nbsp
and I'm the only one fast
enough to keep her alive.
&nbsp
I am The Flash.
Previously on "The Flash"...
&nbsp
It's definitely a meta. I
think this is someone new.
&nbsp
I'm Cisco, by the
way. You must be Gypsy.
&nbsp
- So is this good-bye, then?
- For now.
&nbsp
Caitlin, you do not want to do this.
Time for me to own who I really am.
&nbsp
You're one of the strongest
people I've ever known.
&nbsp
You can win this fight.
- Jesse!
- No, no.
&nbsp
- What's wrong?
- Grodd.
&nbsp
He's got my dad.
He has him in Gorilla City.
&nbsp
_
Synced and corrected by Aaronnmb
www.addic7ed.com
&nbsp
It's been two weeks
since he disappeared.
&nbsp
I mean, no one's seen
or heard from him since.
&nbsp
Slow down. Just start
from the beginning.
&nbsp
Okay, why did your
dad go to Gorilla City?
&nbsp
Wait, can we slow down even further?
What the hell is a Gorilla City?
&nbsp
Okay, so...
there are sentient, highly intelligent
&nbsp
evolved gorillas in Earth-2.
And they all live in a city
deep in the heart of Africa.
&nbsp
We sent Grodd there when
he went after Fay Wray here.
&nbsp
- Grodd's there?
- Mm.
&nbsp
Why on Earth, any Earth, would
your father want to go there?
&nbsp
I mean, we received a
mathematical cryptogram
&nbsp
at our S.T.A.R. Labs.
It was highly complex.
&nbsp
It took a week to decode
it, but my dad and I did.
&nbsp
What did it say?
It was an invitation...
&nbsp
from the gorillas to my dad.
Why Harry?
&nbsp
They wanted to meet him.
So he mounted an expedition
with ten other people,
&nbsp
and they went into the jungle.
But they failed multiple check-ins,
&nbsp
and a search party went in after them.
But all they found were the bodies...
&nbsp
all of them beaten to death.
But no one's seen my dad.
&nbsp
- I mean, is he...
- No.
&nbsp
No, he's alive. They...
they went to a lot of
trouble to get him there.
&nbsp
They need him for something.
We're gonna figure out what that is.
&nbsp
Oh! There you guys are.
I've been looking all over for you.
Are we going for coffee or what?
&nbsp
- Dad!
- Ah, oh.
&nbsp
Yes, that's how you say
good morning, people...
&nbsp
with hugs. Hi!
Jesse, that's not who you think it is.
&nbsp
This is H.R.
You met him briefly
before you left last time.
&nbsp
At your service, madame.
He's Harry's replacement.
&nbsp
Some would say improvement.
Um, this is Harry's daughter.
&nbsp
- Yeah.
- He's been kidnapped.
&nbsp
He... I didn't know. I'm so s...
- I thought...
- Sorry about that.
&nbsp
I'm sorry, too.
I'm sorry I took the
smile from your face.
&nbsp
What are you thinking about?
The future.
&nbsp
This headline from the future:
the city's still recovering
from a gorilla attack.
&nbsp
So you're thinking this headline
and Harry being taken are tied together.
&nbsp
I mean, it can't be
a coincidence, right?
&nbsp
Harry getting lured to Gorilla City?
Grodd must be planning something.
&nbsp
Seems like he's planning
to come back to this Earth.
&nbsp
And not alone, by the sound of it.
If we rescue Harry,
then maybe that stops
&nbsp
whatever Grodd's planning here,
and maybe that changes the future.
&nbsp
- Which would change my future.
- Mm.
&nbsp
So we save Harry, we save Iris.
But you're not sure.
&nbsp
No, but...
I'm going either way.
&nbsp
Harry's my friend. I'm
not gonna just abandon him.
&nbsp
I'm going back to Earth-2.
And I suppose you'll want
somebody to come with you
&nbsp
who's gonna open those breaches for you?
We had so much fun last time.
&nbsp
Fun-ish.
I'm in.
&nbsp
I'm gonna come too.
I have a special connection with Grodd.
&nbsp
Maybe we can use that
to get through to him.
&nbsp
- Yes, okay.
- Great, yeah, I'm coming too.
&nbsp
No. I'm sorry, Jesse, no.
Look, I didn't come here
for you to take all the risk.
&nbsp
- I'm going to help.
- Your dad would kill me
&nbsp
if I let you come along.
I'm a Speedster now, okay?
&nbsp
I can take care of myself.
I know, which is exactly
why I need you to stay here.
&nbsp
I mean, this city needs
protecting while we're gone.
&nbsp
Besides, maybe you can
teach Wally a thing or two.
&nbsp
Wait, what is he talking about?
Um...
&nbsp
Wow.
So you're... you're a Speedster now
&nbsp
Yeah, we're both Speedsters now.
Great, yeah, that's, uh...
&nbsp
... that's awesome.
I, um... I thought she'd
be more excited than that.
&nbsp
Hey, Julian, would you
maybe be able to cover for me
&nbsp
at work for the next few days?
Few days? Why?
&nbsp
I... I just, um, have a thing...
we're... it's just... it's Flash stuff.
&nbsp
Such as?
A friends of ours is
lost on a parallel Earth,
&nbsp
and we're gonna go get him back.
- A parallel Earth?
- Yeah.
&nbsp
This is the... this is the multiverse.
I'm fascinated.
&nbsp
And do you often travel to other Earths?
No, I... well, when I have to.
&nbsp
Look, Julian, will you
just tell Singh that,
&nbsp
I don't know, I'm under
the weather or something?
&nbsp
It's... you know, it is kind
of what we do on Team Flash.
&nbsp
We cover for each other.
What does Caitlin think of
all this multiverse hopping?
&nbsp
- Does she approve?
- She's coming with me.
&nbsp
- You're letting her go?
- It's her choice.
&nbsp
Allen, it's not a wise move, surely.
She can barely control
her cold powers as is.
&nbsp
- I mean...
- We might need her for Grodd.
&nbsp
Grodd? Gr...
- Telepathic gorilla?
- Yeah.
&nbsp
Where... where are you going?
Are you going to Planet of the Apes?
&nbsp
No, it's just a city of them, okay?
Will you cover for me?
&nbsp
Are you going to Planet of the Apes?
I'm not going to Planet
of the Apes, okay?
&nbsp
Calm down. Will you cover for me?
I got you. Yeah, of course.
&nbsp
Okay, thank you. See you in a few days.
All right, now.
&nbsp
- And make sure Wally doesn't...
- I won't.
&nbsp
Because, you know, sometimes...
- he can be a little...
- Barry...
&nbsp
You know, if given the opportunity...
Barry, I am very good
&nbsp
at bossing my little
brother around, okay?
&nbsp
- Don't worry.
- All right.
&nbsp
Just please don't do anything stupid.
You mean like voluntarily
going to a city of super apes?
&nbsp
I'm being serious.
Rescue Harry.
&nbsp
But other than that, you...
you don't have to do this for me.
&nbsp
Everything I do is for you.
Good.
&nbsp
Y'all know Wally can hear you, right?
Sorry, Wally.
&nbsp
Be safe.
Hey, you see anything hinky, you run.
&nbsp
Listen to me. I don't
need to tell you that.
&nbsp
I promise.
All right.
&nbsp
Detective. Hmm.
Indiana Jones much?
&nbsp
Cisco, my friend, this is
not my first expedition,
&nbsp
and believe me, this
is the perfect attire.
&nbsp
Wait, Julian, what's going on?
I thought you were gonna cover for me.
&nbsp
I spoke to Captain Singh.
He thinks we're at a
morphology conference
&nbsp
up in Bludhaven.
So if it's all the same to you...
&nbsp
All right.
You don't have to come, Julian.
&nbsp
- You don't even know Harry.
- Come on.
&nbsp
A chance to travel to
another dimension...
&nbsp
I mean, I wasn't gonna miss that.
We're not going sightseeing.
&nbsp
Neither am I.
Well, damn.
&nbsp
All right, Jesse, Wally,
you make sure this city's
safe while I'm gone, all right?
&nbsp
We will.
Hey, Barry.
&nbsp
If you... if you see
my dad, just tell him...
&nbsp
You'll see him real soon,
Jesse. Speedster's honor.
&nbsp
All right, let's do this.
Okay.
&nbsp
Earth-2, here we come.
How was that?
&nbsp
Bloody brilliant.
Wow.
&nbsp
Well, we made it.
Welcome to the jungle, baby.
&nbsp
Earth-2 Africa.
Not hot.
&nbsp
Guess global warming's
not really a thing here.
&nbsp
But bugs are.
Someone please help me out.
&nbsp
How exactly does saving
someone on this Earth
&nbsp
prevent an attack on ours?
If Grodd is planning to attack,
&nbsp
he's gonna need to open
a breach to our Earth,
&nbsp
and the only one over here
that can open one is...
&nbsp
- Harrison Wells.
- Harrison Wells, yeah.
&nbsp
So if we save him from Grodd,
then he can't get to our Earth,
&nbsp
the attack never happens,
we change the future,
&nbsp
and we're one step
closer to saving Iris.
&nbsp
Hey.
You want to go for a run?
&nbsp
Uh, yeah, yeah. Maybe later.
Are you okay?
&nbsp
Yeah. Yeah, I'm fine.
Look, I know I haven't been
great at keeping in touch.
&nbsp
It's just everything's been so crazy
trying to train with Barry
and shadowing him, and..
&nbsp
I just haven't had that
much time for other things.
&nbsp
Yeah, or other people.
That is not what I meant.
&nbsp
No, look, I... I get it.
Trust me.
&nbsp
- It's not easy being a hero, is it?
- No.
&nbsp
But I love every minute of it.
Great.
&nbsp
Are you sure you're okay?
- Because...
- Yeah.
&nbsp
I'm just worried about my dad.
- Hey.
&nbsp
I hope we didn't interrupt you two.
Nope. Nothing to interrupt.
&nbsp
- Mm.
- Aren't you...
&nbsp
you aren't happy she's back?
I am. I just wish she felt the same.
&nbsp
Ever since she got here, she's
been acting so weird with me.
&nbsp
I... I don't know if
it's because I have powers
&nbsp
or if it's just me.
Wally, she's probably still just upset
&nbsp
because her father's missing, right?
Yeah, it's hard to focus on other things
&nbsp
when something like that
is weighing you down.
&nbsp
Yeah, Wally. She'll be fine. Just...
give her some time, and then,
&nbsp
you know, lock it down.
- Uhh, lock it down, hmm?
- Yeah.
&nbsp
What, you think I didn't notice
that your Facebook profile
&nbsp
still says "single"?
What? I mean, technically,
I'm still single.
&nbsp
What was it?
Ugh, robbery in progress
at O'Sullivan Bank.
&nbsp
You two go.
Come on, let's go.
&nbsp
- Didn't hear the news, huh?
- What news?
&nbsp
That you don't mess with Kid Flash.
We got to get back to our
friends. They're expecting us.
&nbsp
Yeah, they picked some real winners.
I know, which is more
than I can say for you two.
&nbsp
Be right back.
- Sorry, I... I had to stretch my legs.
- Mm.
&nbsp
Hey, guys, come out.
Oh, it's...
&nbsp
it's nothing to see here, guys.
It's just a couple fools getting
their asses handed to 'em.
&nbsp
Thank you.
Oh, my gosh, thank you.
&nbsp
Ah.
Want some water?
&nbsp
I'm okay, thanks.
It's important to stay
hydrated on a parallel Earth.
&nbsp
So weird being back here
on this alternate universe.
&nbsp
This is where I met my
doppelganger, the evil one.
&nbsp
- Killer Frost.
- Ah.
&nbsp
She's the one I'm always
afraid of becoming.
&nbsp
And where is she now?
Dead.
&nbsp
That's not gonna happen to you, Caitlin.
I'm glad you came with us, Julian.
&nbsp
You're a nice addition to the team.
Yeah, well,
&nbsp
I live for danger.
We're close, guys.
&nbsp
Do you hear that?
This is it.
&nbsp
It's a trap.
Ugh!
&nbsp
Welcome, Caitlin.
Knew you'd come...
&nbsp
Flash.
You guys all right?
&nbsp
Yeah, I'm okay.
Yeah, me too.
&nbsp
I've lost my gun, but I'm all right.
Well, looks like you're gonna
have to phase us out of here.
&nbsp
I can't. I...
I don't know. Something's
holding me back.
&nbsp
Can you open a breach?
- No dice.
- Yeah.
&nbsp
I don't think it's the cell. I...
Grodd must be dampening
our powers somehow.
&nbsp
Okay.
Harry?
&nbsp
- You're all right.
- Wells.
&nbsp
Hey! You got to help us get out of here
before the gorillas come back.
&nbsp
Hello, Flash.
- Grodd.
- What?
&nbsp
That's Grodd the gorilla?
He's talking through Wells?
&nbsp
- That's a... a thing?
- Yeah.
&nbsp
Yeah, sort of trips you out at first,
but trust me, you get used to it.
&nbsp
Grodd, let him go.
This is between you and me.
&nbsp
Not yet.
- I need him.
- For what?
&nbsp
Why'd you lure him here?
For you.
&nbsp
Need your help.
Help?
&nbsp
Got a funny way of asking for it.
You sent me here!
&nbsp
Remember?
To live in this hell!
&nbsp
Where I am forced to serve
under the rule of Solovar.
&nbsp
Who's Solovar?
Leader of Gorilla Kind.
&nbsp
Ruler of Gorilla City.
And now...
&nbsp
he wants to rule the humans.
He will bring war to your Earth.
&nbsp
- Why?
- He has seen many conflicts
&nbsp
between gorillas and humans.
He is afraid the humans will attack,
&nbsp
but now that you're here,
he will bring the fight to you.
&nbsp
So you lured us here to stop him?
As trespassers...
&nbsp
you will be sent to the arena...
and executed.
&nbsp
What? How about a signpost at the front?
"All trespassers will be executed."
&nbsp
That wouldn't be the
worst idea, would it?
&nbsp
Will be Solovar's great honor...
to kill you...
&nbsp
himself.
- Mm.
- But, Flash...
&nbsp
if he were to be defeated,
the other gorillas
would see his weakness
&nbsp
and would no longer follow him.
Well, I'm not gonna kill anyone,
&nbsp
not even a gorilla.
Kill or be killed!
&nbsp
This is the only law
Gorilla Kind understands.
&nbsp
How do you benefit from this, Grodd?
Solovar falls.
&nbsp
I take his place.
I rule the gorillas,
&nbsp
and I promise to keep
them in Gorilla City.
&nbsp
How do we know we can trust you?
Because...
&nbsp
even though you sent me away,
your Earth is still my home.
&nbsp
And there are those among you...
I will never forget.
&nbsp
Kill Solovar,
and Central City will be spared.
&nbsp
Fail, and see your home...
turned to ash.
&nbsp
Hey, Jesse, you got a sec?
Did I do something wrong?
&nbsp
I don't... I don't think so.
Okay, then why are you
being so cold with me?
&nbsp
Jesse, come on, you can talk to me.
I know that this is about
more than just your dad.
&nbsp
Look, I guess...
I guess I thought...
&nbsp
one day we'd figure out
a way to be together.
&nbsp
You know, but now that you
have your powers, it's...
&nbsp
it's like I never hear from you.
Jesse, if...
&nbsp
if you would,
I want you to stay.
&nbsp
- I can't.
- Why?
&nbsp
Because of your dad?
Because Barry is going to find him.
&nbsp
Look, you don't know
that, okay? You don't.
&nbsp
When I first got my power,
you were so lost not having yours.
&nbsp
You know, and I thought
maybe part of the reason
&nbsp
why you liked me was...
'cause you were attracted
to the speed and not me.
&nbsp
I know, I know, okay?
But I saw you out there today...
&nbsp
being Kid Flash.
Okay, and you were complete, Wally.
&nbsp
You were scary complete.
I could have all the speed in the world.
&nbsp
I'm not complete without you.
Stay.
&nbsp
Barry, do you really think
you could kill this Solovar?
&nbsp
Do you think you could take a life?
It is as I feared.
&nbsp
The humans court war with Gorilla Kind.
Why did you not tell me, Grodd,
&nbsp
more humans had entered the city?
I was about to inform you, Solovar.
&nbsp
Why?
Why are you here?
&nbsp
To study us like animals?
Make us your pets?
&nbsp
No, no. I'm... I...
We came here in peace.
&nbsp
We entered your city by mistake.
Uh, we mean you no harm.
&nbsp
Please...
just let me and my
friends go, and I promise,
&nbsp
we'll never come back here again.
My brethren have seen you.
&nbsp
Your fate is sealed.
You will all die by my hand...
&nbsp
in the arena...
so that all will know
that Solovar's justice
&nbsp
is wise and swift.
All right, I'll make you a deal.
&nbsp
I'll fight you in the arena... just me.
But if I beat you,
&nbsp
you let my friends go,
and you leave us alone for good.
&nbsp
I accept.
Humans and their arrogance.
&nbsp
First you will suffer.
Then I will grant you each...
&nbsp
a horrible death.
Speedster versus super gorilla.
&nbsp
Best worst video game ever.
Do you really think that
Barry can beat Solovar?
&nbsp
Well, he'd better, for all of our sakes.
It's starting.
&nbsp
After you die,
your friends will follow
you into the black.
&nbsp
- We'll see.
- Okay, Barry.
&nbsp
I got a plan for you.
It's all about the speed punches.
&nbsp
Speed punches.
Come on, Barry.
&nbsp
Change of plan, Barry.
It's all about the running away.
&nbsp
What about the lightning throw?
Yes, Barry, lightning throw!
&nbsp
Worth a shot!
That's oh for two.
&nbsp
Come on, Barry, get up.
All my days, this is quite
the reversal of our fortune.
&nbsp
Reversal...
Barry, it's time to
pull a reverse Flash.
&nbsp
Do it!
He did it! He actually did it.
&nbsp
He bloody well did it.
I won't kill him!
&nbsp
I won't!
I know you all fear humans!
&nbsp
You think we want war with Gorilla Kind!
We don't!
&nbsp
We're not all murderers and killers!
We only want peace!
&nbsp
Which is why I'm sparing your leader!
We call it mercy!
&nbsp
Take him out.
Oh...
&nbsp
what happened?
Congratulations.
&nbsp
You won.
What about Harry?
&nbsp
He's still catatonic.
- Flash.
- I won.
&nbsp
Solovar promised to let us go.
No.
&nbsp
No? What do you...
I don't understand.
&nbsp
Solovar's words mean nothing now.
You never had any intentions
of letting us go, did you?
&nbsp
I told you I needed you.
I could not defeat Solovar
in combat, but you could.
&nbsp
You did, and now I am
the ruler of Gorilla City,
&nbsp
and all the gorillas will follow me.
Solovar never wanted
to attack Central City.
&nbsp
You do.
You took my home away from me,
&nbsp
and now I will take it back!
The gorillas saw what you did, Flash.
&nbsp
They saw you defeat Solovar,
and now they are afraid of humans
&nbsp
and will do anything I order,
and I will order them
to invade your Earth,
&nbsp
and your city will burn.
You were planning this the whole time.
&nbsp
Yes.
Father taught me well.
&nbsp
Always think ahead.
And I had plenty of time to think
&nbsp
in cages built by you
and then by Solovar.
&nbsp
Then why don't you just kill us? Huh?
Since we already did your
damn dirty work for you.
&nbsp
Still need you.
I'm not doing anything for you.
&nbsp
Not you, Flash.
You.
&nbsp
Me?
You will open the breach to First Earth.
&nbsp
My army will cross that breach,
and all the humans in Central City
&nbsp
will burn before Gorilla Kind!
Grodd, you are smart,
&nbsp
maybe smarter than all of us,
smart enough to know
that you cannot do this.
&nbsp
Intelligence and violence,
they're opposites from each other.
&nbsp
What you want to do, it's not logical,
not for someone as wise as you are.
&nbsp
You forget, Flash,
I am an animal.
&nbsp
I am a gorilla.
Kill or be killed!
&nbsp
I'm gonna get out of this
cell, and I'm gonna stop you.
&nbsp
No, you won't.
You will die.
&nbsp
- Snow?
- You okay?
&nbsp
I...
I have a headache, I guess.
&nbsp
Ugh!
And I think...
&nbsp
I... is that me? I smell.
That counts as okay.
&nbsp
Jesse, my daughter. Where's...
She's fine. She's on Earth-1.
&nbsp
She's totally fine.
Barry?
&nbsp
Cisco.
You guys all came for me?
&nbsp
A city of evil genius apes.
Sounded like fun.
&nbsp
Well, I don't deserve it, but...
thank you, Snow; thank you, Barry,
&nbsp
Cisco...
Indiana.
&nbsp
It's Julian Albert, thank you.
And I came along for...
&nbsp
I live for danger.
Looks like you came to the right place.
&nbsp
I still can't phase through the bars.
We have to find a way out
of here so we can stop him.
&nbsp
You keep saying that, but
what if we can't get out?
&nbsp
What if we're stuck here?
What if this is the way...
&nbsp
Well, we can't think like that.
While there's life, there's hope.
&nbsp
And if there isn't life?
What is that supposed to mean?
&nbsp
Grodd needs me to open the breach
so he can attack Earth-1.
&nbsp
What if I wasn't alive to do that?
You planning on dying?
&nbsp
Only if you kill me.
Look, this is something
we have to consider.
&nbsp
Right now, I can't think of
any other way to stop them.
&nbsp
They'd have no other way
of getting to Central City.
&nbsp
He's right.
Cisco's death would change
&nbsp
the newspaper headline in the future.
- Headline?
- It's a long story.
&nbsp
But it would also make
another one come true,
&nbsp
the one about Killer Frost.
You want me to kill you?
&nbsp
Think about it.
Grodd doesn't know you have cold powers.
&nbsp
You might be able to use them.
Cold powers?
&nbsp
She... you have cold powers?
I knew it. I knew that you and I
&nbsp
did not get Barry out of that mirror.
Wait, now. Caitlin.
&nbsp
If you kill someone,
there's no going back.
&nbsp
You'll be Killer Frost
for the rest of your life.
&nbsp
Now, I did not come all
this way to see that happen.
&nbsp
Did you come here because
you "live for danger"
&nbsp
or to protect me?
I just don't want to see you
become something you're not.
&nbsp
Okay, Cisco.
I'm not gonna kill you, and
neither is anyone else, okay?
&nbsp
So let's come up with the next best plan
that doesn't involve
murdering one of our friends.
&nbsp
No, Cisco's right.
It's the only way.
&nbsp
One of us has to die.
Ho!
&nbsp
Hey.
Hi.
&nbsp
What you doing up there?
Just, uh, hanging out.
&nbsp
What're you... what're
you thinking about?
&nbsp
Wally. He wants me
to stay here with him.
&nbsp
Ah.
Yeah, he does.
&nbsp
Guy is no dummy. Congratulations.
Oh, that's great. Love...
&nbsp
nothing like young love.
Yeah, I just... I don't...
&nbsp
I don't know if it's the right thing.
Why?
&nbsp
He's on his own journey.
Besides, my dad just
got captured by gorillas.
&nbsp
And if... if he does come back,
how could I ever tell him I'm leaving?
&nbsp
Well, 'cause you're human.
That's... that's how. That's what we do.
&nbsp
Look, my point is this.
When it comes to love,
&nbsp
you got to go for it.
You know? Everything else be damned.
&nbsp
'Cause if you don't,
you're gonna end up being
the kind of person that lives
&nbsp
the rest of their life with regret.
I mean, I know that telling your
dad that, you know, you're...
&nbsp
you're switching Earths,
that's gonna be a difficult
conversation to have,
&nbsp
but one that you've to go for...
if you want to be happy.
&nbsp
But that's, you know, just my opinion.
What do I know?
&nbsp
I'm just a handsomer guy than your dad
with a song in his
heart. Good luck, Jesse.
&nbsp
He started coughing... violently.
And then he clutched
his side and keeled over.
&nbsp
The injury...
it must have ruptured
one of his kidneys.
&nbsp
He went into shock.
His heart stopped.
&nbsp
I couldn't resuscitate him.
Cold.
&nbsp
He's dead.
He was of no use to me anyway.
&nbsp
He's gone, Barry.
Grodd is gone.
&nbsp
Come on, mate.
Yo, it worked!
&nbsp
Shh!
It worked.
&nbsp
Allen, Allen, you all right, mate?
Yeah. Yeah, I'm good.
&nbsp
I didn't freeze you too much, did I?
No. I'm good.
&nbsp
Well, then...
let's get the hell out of here.
&nbsp
Yeah.
Go!
&nbsp
- All right.
- Hallelujah.
&nbsp
Let's go.
All right.
&nbsp
We should be far enough out that you
should be able to use your powers.
&nbsp
- We need a breach open right now.
- Guys, we got to go
&nbsp
before they realize we're gone!
It's too late for that.
&nbsp
- Run!
Open a breach!
&nbsp
Time to warp out of this madhouse.
All right, go.
&nbsp
Hey, gang, who wants to take
their mind off their troubles
&nbsp
with a "sure to take your mind off
your troubles" game of charades?
&nbsp
I'll go first. Okay.
Ah, let's see. Movie... I mean...
&nbsp
one word.
Dad!
&nbsp
Aww.
- You okay?
- Good, yeah.
&nbsp
I'm sorry you guys missed it.
I ain't.
&nbsp
Ohhh.
Word of advice:
&nbsp
don't volunteer for these things.
Nothing ever tries to
rip you limb from limb
&nbsp
if you don't volunteer.
I'm fine. I'm so fine, thanks...
&nbsp
thanks to our friends,
our good friends.
&nbsp
You're welcome, Harry.
Wow, I... I think...
&nbsp
I just forgot how handsome you were.
Oh, I forgot.
&nbsp
He's... you're still here.
Yeah.
&nbsp
Still here.
I guess we have your
tactical and technical genius
&nbsp
to thank for getting us out of that fix.
No, no, nah.
&nbsp
Nah?
Nah.
&nbsp
You were completely right about him.
He's a total fraud. He's
not even a scientist.
&nbsp
And I'm sure you couldn't even
remember an ATM code if you tried.
&nbsp
All those... all those numbers.
It's only four digits.
Why is he still here?
&nbsp
Because we couldn't do it without him.
I thank you, Francisco.
&nbsp
Fran... Francisco?
Don't ask.
&nbsp
Yo, so what actually happened?
You fight some really
super-smart apes, or what?
&nbsp
Yeah. Yeah, we did.
And they were smart,
but today, at least,
&nbsp
we were a bit smarter.
How's he doing?
&nbsp
He's gonna be okay.
He's got some cuts and bruises,
&nbsp
but Caitlin said he just
needs food and a little sleep.
&nbsp
Okay.
Hey, I'm...
&nbsp
I'm sorry for being an
epic basket case lately.
&nbsp
My, um... my dad was kidnapped once,
and it turns your world.
&nbsp
You turn my world, Wally.
Look, I... I need you to
be honest about something.
&nbsp
Of course.
When my dad wakes up,
&nbsp
if I tell him that I love him
and I'll always be his daughter
&nbsp
but that I want to move to Earth-1,
what would you think about...
&nbsp
That's what I think.
I'm glad we think alike.
&nbsp
I see you're...
you took my love advice.
&nbsp
You know, when it comes
to scientific advice,
&nbsp
mine is sometimes specious,
but when it comes to
affairs of the heart,
&nbsp
well, I consider myself a genius.
Okay, yeah, we're gonna go now.
&nbsp
- Yeah.
Okay, great.
&nbsp
Congratulations. I'm happy for you.
Invite me to the wedding.
&nbsp
He's gonna be so pissed.
Caitlin.
&nbsp
Wait.
Listen, if I overstepped, then...
&nbsp
I apologize.
Just, after drinks the other night...
&nbsp
You were willing to
risk your life for me?
&nbsp
I've been doing a lot
of silly things recently.
&nbsp
I thought adding one more to
the list wouldn't do any harm.
&nbsp
I like you, Julian. I do.
And I like that you like me.
&nbsp
But I'm also afraid of my powers...
and not what they could do to me,
&nbsp
but what they could do to
anyone who gets close to me.
&nbsp
- Caitlin, I'm not afraid.
- You should be.
&nbsp
Fear me, Julian.
It's not a threat, just...
&nbsp
good advice.
Okay, fine.
&nbsp
I'll fear you.
You know what really
helps me when I'm scared?
&nbsp
What?
Just a good fillet steak...
&nbsp
bit of béarnaise on the side,
mashed potatoes... does
the trick ever time.
&nbsp
- Really?
- I promise.
&nbsp
I think we should find
a local steak house
&nbsp
and be terrified together.
Sure. Together it is.
&nbsp
- Well...
- Hmm.
&nbsp
- We did it.
- You did it.
&nbsp
No, uh, we all did it.
We changed the future
without changing who we are.
&nbsp
If we can keep doing this,
we can stop Savitar.
&nbsp
Wherever he is, however
he's gonna come at us,
&nbsp
I can stop him.
I know it now.
&nbsp
How do you do that?
Do what?
&nbsp
Stay positive in the
face of overwhelming odds.
&nbsp
Because I plan on living
a long life with you,
&nbsp
and nothing's gonna
take that away from me.
&nbsp
Good.
So does that mean no more nightmares?
&nbsp
You're finally gonna
get some sleep tonight?
&nbsp
Well... that last part
is entirely up to you.
&nbsp
Oh.
Like I told Flash,
&nbsp
always think ahead.
Now you will open the breaches
&nbsp
and very soon,
Central City will fall before Grodd.
&nbsp
Synced and corrected by Aaronnmb
www.addic7ed.com
&nbsp