My name is Barry Allen,
&nbsp
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world, I'm an
ordinary forensic scientist,
&nbsp
but secretly, with the help of
my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
&nbsp
I fight crime and find
other meta-humans like me.
&nbsp
In an attempt to stop the
evil speedster Savitar,
&nbsp
I was accidentally
thrust into the future,
&nbsp
and I saw him murder
the woman that I love.
&nbsp
But I won't let that happen.
I'm gonna do everything in my power
&nbsp
to change the future,
and I'm the only one
&nbsp
fast enough to keep her alive.
I am The Flash.
&nbsp
Previously on "The Flash"...
Grodd. He's got my dad.
&nbsp
Harry's my friend. I'm not
gonna just abandon him.
&nbsp
I'm going back to Earth-2.
Now I am the ruler of Gorilla City,
&nbsp
and all the gorillas will
follow anything I order.
&nbsp
Grodd the gorilla, he's
talking through Wells?
&nbsp
Yeah.
Who is this gorgeous intruder?
&nbsp
Her name is Gypsy.
She's a Collector.
&nbsp
Open a breach!
Time to warp out of this madhouse.
&nbsp
You will open the breaches,
and Central City will fall before Grodd.
&nbsp
Barry?
- Good morning.
&nbsp
You're in a good mood for
6:30 in the morning.
&nbsp
Yes, I am.
Was I too loud?
&nbsp
I did make breakfast.
We got pancakes and waffles,
&nbsp
some French toast,
bacon and sausage, perfectly cooked.
&nbsp
And I picked up some of that
dark roast that you love so much.
&nbsp
Barry Allen, what has gotten into you?
Being with you makes me want
to do things like this.
&nbsp
Come here.
I love you.
&nbsp
Um, so do you actually
want any of this, or...
&nbsp
Um, yes.
And some of the food too.
&nbsp
Yeah.
Whoa-ho-ho-ho, nice.
&nbsp
What...
are you doing?
&nbsp
I'm decorating!
Look at this place! Hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo!
&nbsp
You're decorating the Speed Lab?
Yes, I'm decorating the Speed Lab.
&nbsp
You know, 'cause Francisco, you know,
he wouldn't let me decorate the cortex,
&nbsp
'cause I made it look
oh-so-jolly for Christmastime.
&nbsp
What are the balls for?
Do you know what those are? Lanterns.
&nbsp
You know what I always say,
a fella that can't tell
&nbsp
the difference between
balls and lanterns
&nbsp
is in trouble when the lights go out.
Ohhh...
&nbsp
You go front to back.
Toothbrushing. You go front to back?
&nbsp
'Cause I'm a small circles kind of guy.
I wonder how the other
Wells brushes his teeth.
&nbsp
- The murderer?
- I'm fascinated
&nbsp
by the subtle differences
between us, you know?
&nbsp
- And the not-so-subtle ones.
- Like what?
&nbsp
Like the fact that I'm a genius
and you're a moron.
&nbsp
Okay.
See you at the party.
&nbsp
Sync and corrections by btsix
www.addic7ed.com
&nbsp
Wow. What a transformation.
Again!
&nbsp
So this is H.R.'s
contribution to the team?
&nbsp
Being Martha Stewart?
Guys, he's just trying
to do something nice.
&nbsp
Heads up!
I'm not really good with
this kind of thing.
&nbsp
You know what I got to do?
I got to take some lessons
&nbsp
from that guy in the green elf suit
over there in Star
City, what's his name?
&nbsp
Green Arrow. Hey, what is all this?
Friend's Day!
&nbsp
Ba-da!
- What?
- Yeah.
&nbsp
- Friend's Day.
- Friend's?
&nbsp
Oh, it's my Earth's equivalent
- of Valentine's Day.
- Valentine's Day.
&nbsp
And I thought, like, after, you know,
our success with the gorillas,
&nbsp
that we should, like,
celebrate the love.
&nbsp
Was all this necessary?
Yeah, Joe. Speaking of, where is your...
&nbsp
Your lady friend? 'Cause
I would like to...
&nbsp
No, you wouldn't like to do anything.
She's at work, which is
where I should be going.
&nbsp
Yeah, I...
Look what I have, ladies and gentlemen.
&nbsp
I have your own personal
Friend's Day card.
&nbsp
- Wow.
- For yours truly, Ms. West.
&nbsp
- Thank you, H.R.
- Captain.
&nbsp
- Thanks, H.R.
- Leader of the ship.
&nbsp
- Thank... thank you.
- You're so welcome.
&nbsp
Oh, hi, Jesse "So Quick"
Yeah, I also made one for
your grumpy old dad.
&nbsp
Ah, you know what I like?
- Yo' vibe.
- Thank you.
&nbsp
Caitlyn.
Oh! I forgot the coffee!
&nbsp
"You have sped into my
heart, Jesse Quick."
&nbsp
Oh, well, I guess that makes two of us.
Wow, H.R. is nothing like my dad.
&nbsp
He's so sweet and thoughtful
and understanding.
&nbsp
We should tell him.
Tell your dad about you moving here?
&nbsp
- Yeah.
- Um, now?
&nbsp
Yeah, I mean, H.R. said there'd
never be a perfect time.
&nbsp
Just got to rip the Band-Aid off.
- Yeah.
- Okay, let's do it.
&nbsp
H.R. does make a good point.
Yeah, what's that?
&nbsp
It was a really big win for
the team, beating Grodd.
&nbsp
I mean, we stopped a gorilla
attack from happening.
&nbsp
Yeah, look at you, changing the future.
We're all changing the future,
&nbsp
one headline at a time.
Look, I don't know what
the future's gonna bring,
&nbsp
but I hope every day is with you.
Which is why I wanted to ask you...
&nbsp
Barry Allen,
will you be my friend?
&nbsp
Always.
- Hey.
&nbsp
H.R. made this for you.
H.R. is an idiot.
&nbsp
So there's something I've
been meaning to tell you.
&nbsp
- Okay.
- So I-I'm just gonna say it.
&nbsp
I think that's wise.
I'm gonna move to Earth-1.
&nbsp
What?
- I'm gonna stay here.
- Why would you do that?
&nbsp
Grodd is no longer a threat.
No, it's... it's not that. Uh...
&nbsp
I want to be with Wally.
This whole thing has made us realize
&nbsp
that we have no idea what's
gonna happen, you know, and...
&nbsp
And if we're gonna go through something,
we want to go through it together.
&nbsp
Yeah.
This guy?
&nbsp
You like him?
Yeah.
&nbsp
He makes you happy?
Dad...
&nbsp
Okay.
That's it?
&nbsp
You're not gonna yell?
You're not gonna throw that over there?
&nbsp
Your happiness is what matters to me.
You're both adults.
&nbsp
I respect your decision.
Don't screw it up.
&nbsp
Okay, that was weird.
I guess that this means that
we gotta find you a place.
&nbsp
Me? More like us.
You know, sometimes it
seems like everybody else
&nbsp
gets to have their love doughnut.
Where's my love doughnut?
&nbsp
- Oh, love is complicated.
- Mm.
&nbsp
So, uh, where's Julian?
He's taking care of some
family matters in London.
&nbsp
Just so you know,
we are just friends.
&nbsp
Yeah, the friend zone. I know it well.
Pretty sure I have a
permanent residence here.
&nbsp
You know, maybe I should
just swallow the pill.
&nbsp
Maybe my game just ain't strong.
Your game is so strong!
&nbsp
For what it's worth,
I think Lisa Snart was totally into you.
&nbsp
Lisa Snart.
Not that I would actually
let you date her.
&nbsp
Cisco, I promise, there is a beautiful,
intelligent woman out there
who's gonna challenge you
&nbsp
to be your best version of yourself.
In fact, she could be
right around the corner.
&nbsp
Gypsy!
Oof!
&nbsp
Who the hell is this?
Where am I?
&nbsp
Ohh...
Why am I locked up?
&nbsp
Oops.
My powers don't work in here.
&nbsp
Yeah, it's kind of the
point of the cell.
&nbsp
What happened?
I thought we were all on the same page.
&nbsp
I spared your life, and you
said you'd go back to Earth-19
&nbsp
and tell everyone you killed H.R.
That's exactly what I did.
&nbsp
I told the council you were dead.
I don't believe you.
&nbsp
I didn't come here to take you back!
I'm telling you!
&nbsp
Then why are you here?
I don't know.
&nbsp
The last thing I remember,
I was on Earth-2...
&nbsp
hunting down another breacher.
Wait, you were just on Earth-2?
&nbsp
Where?
In the African jungle,
&nbsp
where I saw...
Let me guess, a gorilla?
&nbsp
Super tall? Anger management issues?
Grodd must have taken control of her
&nbsp
and sent her here to kill us.
Yeah, but she's on a
different Earth than him,
&nbsp
and Grodd's telepathy can't
cross dimensions like that.
&nbsp
Grodd said he always thinks ahead.
Just like the Reverse-Flash.
&nbsp
He didn't have you to open a breach,
so he used Gypsy instead.
&nbsp
So that means...
Grodd's here.
&nbsp
Something tells me he's not alone.
Any sign of him yet?
&nbsp
Not since you asked 30 seconds ago.
Okay, he's a giant gorilla,
&nbsp
who's probably leading an
army of giant gorillas.
&nbsp
- How can you not find him?
- He's probably figured out a way
&nbsp
- to scramble our satellites.
- Satellites.
&nbsp
We're talking about a
genius super-ape here.
&nbsp
And a master strategist
who successfully fooled us on my Earth.
&nbsp
We Wellses, we don't fool
easy, do we, hard hat?
&nbsp
Don't call me "hard hat".
We have to find him before
he hurts somebody else.
&nbsp
Don't worry, Barry, we will.
Every time I think we've beat him,
&nbsp
he comes back stronger, smarter,
and more dangerous.
&nbsp
He's evolving.
I keep trying to fight him the same way.
&nbsp
Okay, guys, look, we
just have to come up
&nbsp
with a different way to beat him.
What we need to do is get
ahead of him for once.
&nbsp
We can. You've seen the future.
You know there's an attack.
&nbsp
If we just figure out where
that attack happens,
&nbsp
we can launch a preemptive
strike against Grodd.
&nbsp
We can stop the attack
before it ever starts.
&nbsp
And fortunately, we have someone
who can foresee future events.
&nbsp
Before they happen.
Okay, okay, there's only one problem.
&nbsp
I can only vibe what Barry saw,
and a ticker on the side of a bus stop
&nbsp
doesn't give us a whole lot of info.
What if we widen the scope of your vibe?
&nbsp
Then you can see more of the future.
Yes. I can do that.
&nbsp
Just need to borrow your vibe gear.
- Harry, that's my only pair.
- I'll be careful.
&nbsp
- It's my only pair.
- West, come with me.
&nbsp
- You have an engineer's mind.
- Yeah, sure.
&nbsp
Happy to help.
We're gonna need all
the help we can get.
&nbsp
Can you talk to Joe, see
if he can rally CCPD?
&nbsp
Yeah, yeah, I'll let him know that
an army of sentient gorillas
is about to storm the city.
&nbsp
- He's gonna love that.
- Yup.
&nbsp
What about Gypsy? She's
a really powerful meta.
&nbsp
Yeah, but how do we know she's
not a Grodd sleeper agent?
&nbsp
She's not. I checked her out.
Can you convince her to help?
&nbsp
Bro, she won't say no to me.
No way.
&nbsp
You've got three
speedsters, an ice queen,
&nbsp
and a guy who vibes
almost as well as I do.
&nbsp
You don't need my help to stop Grodd.
Need I remind you, you're the one
&nbsp
who brought Grodd here
in the first place.
&nbsp
Not by choice!
I was chasing a fugitive
from my world on Earth-2
&nbsp
when Grodd ambushed me
and turned me into his damn puppet.
&nbsp
Okay, so then this is
the perfect opportunity
&nbsp
for payback, right?
Don't tell me you're gonna
run away from this.
&nbsp
I never run.
Then stand and fight with us.
&nbsp
We need you.
You need me?
&nbsp
Are you trying to Luke Starkiller me?
What if I am?
&nbsp
Is that what it's gonna
take to get you to stay?
&nbsp
Here's a bonus, you get to spend
extra time with this face.
&nbsp
And look at this face. Come on.
Who doesn't want to get to spend
extra time with this guy?
&nbsp
What?
The things I saw,
&nbsp
when Grodd was in control of my mind,
the horrors in that monster's head,
&nbsp
I can never un-see them.
What horrors?
&nbsp
The city in ruins.
People in pain. Death everywhere.
&nbsp
That's what Grodd wants,
what he's planning.
&nbsp
I'm sorry, Cisco.
This is your fight.
&nbsp
Not mine.
Now, if you don't mind,
&nbsp
I still have a fugitive to catch, so...
Okay.
&nbsp
I understand.
Take care of yourself, Cisco.
&nbsp
Admit it.
You are so into me.
&nbsp
West.
How are we coming along with that gear?
&nbsp
I've made all the
adjustments you asked for,
&nbsp
so we should be good to go.
Good. Thank you.
&nbsp
Yeah.
Great.
&nbsp
Um, how exactly is this gonna
help Cisco vibe any differently?
&nbsp
Ah, simple science.
We just broaden the overall
harmonic resonance
&nbsp
of Cisco's vibrational frequencies
all while focusing them on
a fixed temporal locus.
&nbsp
Couldn't be easier.
Yeah.
&nbsp
You know, I got to admit, Harry,
I was super surprised
at how cool you were
&nbsp
with Jesse staying on this Earth.
I thought, for sure, you
were gonna freak out
&nbsp
and throw something
or throw someone.
&nbsp
Well, my daughter's happiness
is of the utmost importance to me.
&nbsp
And you make her happy.
I'm gonna do everything in my
power to keep it that way.
&nbsp
I appreciate that, West.
I'm sure Jesse will too, after I'm...
&nbsp
gone.
We're gonna come visit
you on Earth-2 a bunch,
&nbsp
so you don't have to
worry about that, Harry.
&nbsp
Yeah, right.
Uh, well, means the world to me,
&nbsp
seeing as I don't know how
much time I have left.
&nbsp
Wait, y-you're sick?
I'm not as well as I once was.
&nbsp
Have you seen a doctor?
Yes.
&nbsp
I have seen a doctor, West.
Is it serious?
&nbsp
Oh, man, Harry.
Man. Um...
&nbsp
- I'm sorry.
- Me too.
&nbsp
Does Jesse know?
Appreciate you keep this between... us.
&nbsp
She doesn't know, and we
wouldn't want to upset her.
&nbsp
Hey, SWAT's ready to
roll whenever y'all are.
&nbsp
We find Grodd yet?
We're about to.
&nbsp
Cisco, you ready?
Harry, this thing, if
it fries my brain...
&nbsp
"It's an improvement."
- Was that "Rocky"?
- Yeah, Burgess Meredith.
&nbsp
Yeah, I'm ready.
Word of warning. Vibing blind,
&nbsp
it's like surfing a monster wave.
You need to stay above
the temporal flow,
&nbsp
otherwise your consciousness
can get sucked under.
&nbsp
And then what happens?
I don't know.
&nbsp
Guess we'll find out.
Wait, what?
&nbsp
Where are you, Ramon? What do you see?
I'm at an intersection.
&nbsp
State and Oakhill.
I think this is where it goes down.
&nbsp
That's a block away from the bridge.
That leads right to the heart of town.
&nbsp
If those gorillas get
over that bridge...
&nbsp
They'll overrun the city in no time.
Not if we stop them first.
&nbsp
Eyes wide, everybody.
Grodd's army could be here
any second, all right?
&nbsp
There's no sign of them.
You sure this is the right place?
&nbsp
According to Cisco, this is it.
Was it the right time?
&nbsp
We're too early.
No, Flash.
&nbsp
Too late.
- Grodd.
- I remember,
&nbsp
this human is important to you.
Now...
&nbsp
he's all mine.
No! Hey!
&nbsp
Do not hurt him. I'm the one you want!
- Right?
- I warned you, Flash.
&nbsp
And now I'm here on First Earth
to make good on my promise.
&nbsp
And when I'm finished, this city
and all the puny humans
&nbsp
will die.
No!
&nbsp
Joe!
Are you okay?
&nbsp
I think so.
I don't get it.
&nbsp
How is attacking Detective Joe West
a part of Grodd's plan?
&nbsp
- It wasn't.
- Then what was it?
&nbsp
A distraction.
I don't care if Senator
Ford is having doubts.
&nbsp
If the secretary doesn't
approve that budget
&nbsp
first thing in the morning, we're gonna
have to make some serious cuts...
&nbsp
The hell was that?
That damn gorilla almost
got me this time.
&nbsp
Shouldn't even have a scar.
Do you remember anything
&nbsp
from when Grodd was controlling you?
Not really. Just some flashes.
&nbsp
Flashes of what?
They were, like, these images...
&nbsp
places I've never seen before.
It was like I was seeing
what he was seeing.
&nbsp
Gypsy said the same thing.
Uh-oh, here we go. I know that look.
&nbsp
That's the "I have a genius idea" look.
A couple years back on my Earth,
&nbsp
there was a neuroscientist
that was able to achieve memory recovery
&nbsp
using transcranial magnetic
simulators on brain-damaged...
&nbsp
We use that here but more
as a depression treatment.
&nbsp
Well, in this experiment,
the neuroscientist
&nbsp
focused all the energy
on the occipital cortex
&nbsp
of the patients,
allowing them to achieve
&nbsp
almost full memory recollection.
So you think the
connection Grodd creates
&nbsp
in the brains of those he mind-controls
goes both ways?
&nbsp
Could be.
Maybe we could use Grodd's memories
&nbsp
that he left behind in Joe to
figure out what his plan is.
&nbsp
We'd just make some TCM simulators.
- All it takes is some...
- Magnets.
&nbsp
Throw together some magnets,
make a helmet out of 'em.
&nbsp
Hold on. Y'all want to
put a bunch of magnets
&nbsp
against my skull to look into the mind
of a psychotic, murderous ape?
&nbsp
Yeah.
Fine.
&nbsp
Let's make it happen,
before Grodd tries to
kill somebody else.
&nbsp
It's gonna be okay.
Hey.
&nbsp
Is everything okay?
Just tired of seeing the
people I care about
&nbsp
be put in harm's way.
Yeah, but like always,
&nbsp
we're gonna work together
and come up with a plan.
&nbsp
We're gonna stop Grodd, Barry.
And then what?
&nbsp
We just send him back?
He's just gonna come her again.
&nbsp
We have to end this once and for all.
Wait. What?
&nbsp
You want to kill Grodd?
Why not?
&nbsp
That's how their society
in Gorilla City works...
&nbsp
Kill or be killed.
That's why he wanted me to kill Solovar.
&nbsp
And you know what? I should have.
I showed too much mercy.
&nbsp
No, you did what was right, Barry,
as you always do.
&nbsp
That's what makes you a hero.
Oliver has killed.
&nbsp
He's still considered a hero.
Yeah, and he lives with the
weight of that decision
&nbsp
every single day.
I think that sometimes,
the only way to stop
&nbsp
bad things from happening
is to just get rid of
what's causing them.
&nbsp
What is this really about?
Grodd or what happens to me?
&nbsp
I kill Grodd, his attack never happens,
that changes the future, and...
&nbsp
you live, yeah.
Your humanity, showing mercy,
&nbsp
that is what separates
you from everyone else.
&nbsp
That's the reason that
everyone looks up to you.
&nbsp
Don't compromise who you are...
ever.
&nbsp
Losing what makes The Flash The Flash...
My life isn't worth it if
that's the cost to save me.
&nbsp
There you are.
Hey, you know your dad's
gonna be all right.
&nbsp
What's wrong?
Look, I've been thinking, and I...
&nbsp
I don't think you should stay here.
I think... It was a bad idea.
&nbsp
Um...
Wally, you asked me.
&nbsp
Yeah, and I shouldn't have.
I think you should go back to Earth-2...
&nbsp
spend as much time with
your dad as you can.
&nbsp
Spend as much time with my dad as I can?
Wally, what are you talking about?
&nbsp
Your dad is sick, Jesse.
He's really sick.
&nbsp
He doesn't have much time left.
Did he tell you that?
&nbsp
I'm so sorry.
He is...
&nbsp
unbelievable.
So all you have to do is concentrate
&nbsp
on your memories of Grodd, okay?
Yeah, that won't be a problem.
&nbsp
All right.
Hey, dead man.
&nbsp
- Seriously?
- Hm?
&nbsp
You told Wally you were dying?
- Dying?
- You're dying?
&nbsp
I didn't say I was, uh...
I-I said I didn't know how
much time I had left.
&nbsp
- None of us...
- Okay, what is wrong with you?
&nbsp
- Um...
- Is there seriously nothing
&nbsp
you won't say to get me
to stay by your side?
&nbsp
- I don't...
- Look, whatever.
&nbsp
I'm moving here, whether
you like it or not.
&nbsp
So all you have to do is concentrate
- on your memories of Grodd.
- Yeah.
&nbsp
- You ready?
- Waiting on you, dead man.
&nbsp
Mm-hmm.
Hey, if I start to Grodd
out at any point,
&nbsp
cut the power off immediately.
Of course.
&nbsp
All right, Joe, you ready?
- Yeah.
- All right, then.
&nbsp
So here...
we...
&nbsp
go.
Joe?
&nbsp
I didn't know he could draw.
Well, that's the thing.
Anybody can actually draw.
&nbsp
It's just that some have
more developed visual cortex
&nbsp
and manual ability, as you know.
And right now, these magnets are
taking that part of his brain
&nbsp
and lightin' it up.
Well, it worked.
&nbsp
Now we have a new problem.
We have to figure out
who the hell this is.
&nbsp
Good evening, General.
Color and number of the day.
&nbsp
Purple 246.
Are you all right, sir?
&nbsp
Sick.
_
&nbsp
Good.
General.
&nbsp
_
Great.
&nbsp
Yo, Rocky.
How you doin'?
&nbsp
Yeah, I'm fine. I just...
No matter what I do to stop Grodd,
&nbsp
he just keeps finding
new ways to attack,
&nbsp
new ways to destroy, and I...
Iris doesn't think I should,
&nbsp
but the only way this
ends is if I kill him.
&nbsp
Kill him.
That might be the most idiotic thing
&nbsp
I've ever heard you say.
- Wait, what?
- Iris is right.
&nbsp
If you don't want to listen, go ahead,
keep being an idiot.
&nbsp
I don't understand.
Don't. Kill. Grodd.
&nbsp
Harry, you of all people
should understand.
&nbsp
I mean, you would have
killed to save Jesse.
&nbsp
You were gonna kill Zoom.
Barry, there's a thousand things
&nbsp
I've done that I'm not proud of.
Some of them recently.
&nbsp
Every time I do one of those things,
it makes it easier to
do it the next time.
&nbsp
I look at you, out there
battling the darkness,
&nbsp
with honor and hope, and I'm reminded
there's always another way,
&nbsp
always.
Killing Grodd is not your answer.
&nbsp
Saving one life doesn't
justify taking another.
&nbsp
Find the other way.
Guys.
&nbsp
We need you in the cortex.
What's up, Cisco?
&nbsp
We've got a behemoth of a problem.
Terrific.
&nbsp
So we ran our John Doe image
through every database.
&nbsp
And it was tough. I mean,
the guy's a ghost.
&nbsp
We've been calling him Jason Bourne.
But then H.R. noticed something.
&nbsp
Well, at first, it was
a real brain-twister,
&nbsp
but then I remembered a quote
from a renowned poet from my
Earth, Alfred Yankovic...
&nbsp
Are you talking about Weird Al?
Why? 'Cause of the hair?
&nbsp
Get to the point already,
if you have one.
&nbsp
I can, hard hat. It's his hair.
Standard military cut.
&nbsp
So we ran the image through
the Department of Defense database,
&nbsp
and, as Cisco would say, "Yahtzee."
I would say that.
&nbsp
Nice work, H.R.
I know.
&nbsp
DoD has him listed as
Air Force General Matthew McNally.
&nbsp
General Matthew McNally, and
I'll give you one guess...
&nbsp
Just guess... What he's in charge of.
I know you're gonna
say military weapons,
&nbsp
but I really hope you don't
say military weapons.
&nbsp
It's worse, Barr.
Nuclear missiles.
&nbsp
McNally has the highest clearance.
He can have a rocket in the
air in less than ten minutes.
&nbsp
So are the satellites
back to functional?
&nbsp
We ran a full diagnostic.
Any nuclear weapon that's
authorized to fire,
&nbsp
- an alarm will sound.
- Okay, good.
&nbsp
Does it sound like that?
That's an alarm.
&nbsp
Yeah, it's that alarm, H.R.
Okay.
&nbsp
Short-range ballistic missile
authorized to fire from Fort Reynolds.
&nbsp
How much time do we have?
Minutes.
&nbsp
Grodd, what have you done?
Can we stop it from here?
&nbsp
Military weapons are basically analog.
I mean, they still use floppy disks.
&nbsp
I'm going after it.
Guys, no, look, I appreciate it,
&nbsp
but I need you to stay here, okay?
If I can't stop it,
&nbsp
I need you to get everybody
to safety, okay?
&nbsp
_
All right, I'm with the missile.
&nbsp
Barry, to access the
keypad, remove the panel
&nbsp
at the base of the missile vehicle.
All right.
&nbsp
All right, that's done. What's next?
Well, the good news is, this missile
&nbsp
has a built-in five-digit kill code.
Great. What is it?
&nbsp
That's the bad news. We don't know.
For real? Ah, well, then
what am I supposed to do?
&nbsp
You have to try every
combination, Barry.
&nbsp
It's okay, with this type of launcher,
you won't set off the nuke.
&nbsp
Barry, simulators are projecting
that hundreds of thousands will die.
&nbsp
Yeah, let's hope not.
Come on.
&nbsp
Five digits. How many combos is that?
- I'm guessing it's about...
- Precisely 90,000,
&nbsp
which you would know
if you weren't a moron
&nbsp
and you were an actual genius.
Two missiles are locked on target.
&nbsp
Guys, we need something
else. This isn't working.
&nbsp
Plan B, anyone?
Work!
&nbsp
How much time does he have?
15 seconds.
&nbsp
Guys, I need something!
This isn't working!
&nbsp
Something else!
You just got to keep going, Barry.
&nbsp
You just... just got to keep trying.
Six missiles are locked on target.
&nbsp
It worked.
It worked! We did it!
&nbsp
We did it!
Oh, thank God.
&nbsp
Flash stopped the weapon.
But he can't stop us all.
&nbsp
Attack!
Found them.
&nbsp
They're right outside the city.
Heading for State and Oakhill, fast.
&nbsp
Which leads right into downtown.
- All right, so what do we do?
- Barry, I know we're
&nbsp
speedsters and everything, but
we are way outnumbered here.
&nbsp
Yeah, I mean, he's right,
how are the three of us
&nbsp
gonna take on all those gorillas?
We have to.
&nbsp
As much as I hate these gorillas,
especially Grodd, if you kill him,
&nbsp
the other ones might stand down,
but you might not be able to
come back from this, Barry.
&nbsp
- You know that, right?
- I know.
&nbsp
But there's another way.
It's not gonna come to that.
&nbsp
Cisco, I'm gonna need your help.
Tracked her down on Earth-2.
&nbsp
Breach is taken care of.
Thank you.
&nbsp
Risky move coming to an Earth
where interdimensional travel
is punishable by death.
&nbsp
Especially when I'm the one
who's supposed to uphold that law.
&nbsp
I need to talk to you.
I don't do long-distance relationships.
&nbsp
Don't get me wrong, this is something
I'd love to talk about in more detail,
&nbsp
especially if distance
is your only hesitation.
&nbsp
But I'm here to talk about Grodd.
Okay, I see you don't
take no for an answer.
&nbsp
Gypsy, please.
He's gonna destroy my city.
&nbsp
And he's gonna hurt the people I love.
I told you before,
that's not my problem.
&nbsp
Look, just go back to Earth-1
before someone sees you
&nbsp
and I have to do something
that I don't want to.
&nbsp
You know, you told me I could
do things with my powers
&nbsp
I'd never even imagined,
and you're right,
&nbsp
'cause I'm not just
vibing people anymore.
&nbsp
I'm vibing what they feel.
And you know what I'm getting from you,
&nbsp
right here, right now?
You're more than this. You're like me.
&nbsp
You want to do something good.
Look, we need something to stop Grodd,
&nbsp
and I'm gonna need your help getting it.
Please, be the hero I
know you want to be.
&nbsp
Wells, how long do we have?
Two minutes, Barry.
&nbsp
Two minutes? Ten seconds!
Can you not even tell time?
&nbsp
That's what I said. Ten seconds.
So got any pointers on
how the three of us
&nbsp
are gonna save everyone and
stop a few hundred gorillas?
&nbsp
Go for the legs?
Just try not to get caught,
&nbsp
'cause, trust me, they won't let go.
Well, that was not the
start we're looking for.
&nbsp
Because...
How long do they have to last?
&nbsp
Hopefully not much longer.
Your city will fall, Flash.
&nbsp
There's only one way to end this.
You kill me.
&nbsp
But you won't do that.
All you care about is mercy.
&nbsp
Yeah, you're right.
Except I'm not the only one
that wants to stop you.
&nbsp
Solovar!
I challenge you, Grodd!
&nbsp
And you will fall again!
Good-bye, Grodd.
&nbsp
Stop! Stop...
Death isn't the way.
&nbsp
He betrayed me.
I know, so leave him
here, where he's from.
&nbsp
We won't let him go back to
Gorilla City ever again.
&nbsp
Just spare his life,
like I spared yours.
&nbsp
Send us home...
all of us.
&nbsp
How long is it gonna take
to put 100 gorillas through a breach?
&nbsp
We're gonna be here all night.
You know what I ought to do?
&nbsp
Whip us up some cappuccino...
Ho, ho, ho, ho, ho!
&nbsp
All the gorillas are back on Earth-2.
And Grodd?
&nbsp
I called Lyla. He's with A.R.G.U.S.
Good. I don't know about y'all,
&nbsp
but I don't ever need to see
a super-smart, telepathic gorilla again.
&nbsp
I'm with you.
Not that Grodd didn't have
&nbsp
some justification for
mistrusting humans.
&nbsp
Whatever good was in Grodd is gone.
As far as I'm concerned,
they can throw him
&nbsp
in the same cage as King Shark.
Mm, I'd pay money to see that fight.
&nbsp
All right, well, if the city
doesn't need my help anymore,
&nbsp
I'm gonna head back to Earth-19.
Oh, really?
&nbsp
So you did all this for the city, huh?
'Cause I'm pretty sure
there's a different reason
&nbsp
you chose to help us.
That's right, I was the only one
&nbsp
who knew where Solovar was.
Oh, right, yeah.
&nbsp
How could I forget?
- Mm.
- Don't front.
&nbsp
You're into me.
Look, Cisco, I mean,
&nbsp
even if I was...
You couldn't handle me.
&nbsp
Bye, guys.
- Bye.
- Mm-hmm.
&nbsp
I'll marry that woman.
Yeah.
&nbsp
Okay, I better get this story
in before I lose my job.
&nbsp
Okay.
You sure you still don't
want to look into the future
&nbsp
and see what's changed?
No.
&nbsp
Think I'm done with that.
- Good.
- I'll see you at home.
&nbsp
Okay.
Hey, I'll walk out with you.
&nbsp
I got a date with Cecile.
Oh.
&nbsp
Come on, guys. Let's go find Harry.
To review, this is my daughter.
&nbsp
There's nothing more important to me.
So you do right by my daughter,
&nbsp
or there is nowhere in the multiverse
I won't find you.
&nbsp
Dad.
They'd have to kill me.
&nbsp
Bye.
Bye, Jesse Quick.
&nbsp
Always another way, Flash.
Always.
&nbsp
Babe?
Is that Grandma Esther's noodles?
&nbsp
Mm-hmm.
And there's mint chocolate
chip in the freezer.
&nbsp
And these are for you.
What is all this?
&nbsp
I've been really busy recently with...
trying to avoid the future.
&nbsp
And I forgot that there's
always another way.
&nbsp
What is that?
Making the future...
&nbsp
our future.
My great-grandfather gave
this to my great-grandmother
&nbsp
after World War II.
He wanted to propose
before he was shipped out,
&nbsp
but he... he didn't have the money.
And he bought this three years later
&nbsp
when he was stationed in London.
Fought his way across France,
all the way to Berlin,
&nbsp
and this ring...
around his neck with his dog tags.
&nbsp
And when he got back, she was
waiting for him on the dock
&nbsp
of the Brooklyn Navy Yards.
He proposed on the spot.
&nbsp
After my mom passed away,
Joe held on to this for me...
&nbsp
until tonight.
- Barry...
- Iris West,
&nbsp
will you marry me?
Inside of us, we both know
you belong with Victor.
&nbsp
You're part of his work, the
thing that keeps him going.
&nbsp
If that plane leaves...
Okay, I'm so confused.
&nbsp
Is it supposed to be about
the War of the Americas?
&nbsp
Do you not like it? 'Cause
this is my favorite movie.
&nbsp
No, no, I didn't say that. Um...
I guess we just have
more wars on my Earth.
&nbsp
Well, we can just watch something else.
Or we don't have to
watch anything at all.
&nbsp
Mm.
You know what I could go for?
&nbsp
Big Belly Burger.
Wow!
&nbsp
Wow, ow.
Um, I'll be right back.
&nbsp
Thank you.
Sync and corrections by btsix
www.addic7ed.com
&nbsp