My name is Barry Allen,
&nbsp
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world, I'm an
ordinary forensic scientist,
&nbsp
but secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
&nbsp
I fight crime and find
other meta-humans like me.
&nbsp
In an attempt to stop the
evil speedster Savitar,
&nbsp
I was accidentally
thrust into the future,
&nbsp
and I saw him murder
the woman that I love.
&nbsp
But I won't let that happen.
I'm gonna do everything in
my power to change the future,
&nbsp
and I'm the only one fast
enough to keep her alive.
&nbsp
I am The Flash.
Previously on "The Flash"...
&nbsp
The Philosopher's Stone has
been the key to everything.
&nbsp
So we destroy the Stone,
and Savitar is gone for good.
&nbsp
There's only one thing
we can do with it.
&nbsp
Throw it into the Speed Force.
I have to do what I can to help.
&nbsp
I'm the guy who avoided
his dying mother for weeks.
&nbsp
I have a whole lot to make up for.
I like you, Julian, but
I'm also afraid of my powers
&nbsp
and what they could do to
anyone who gets close to me.
&nbsp
I didn't ask for these powers,
just like you didn't ask
to be used by Savitar.
&nbsp
I think we should be terrified together.
Sure. Together it is.
&nbsp
It's crazy how fast I've
gotten in such a short time.
&nbsp
And I'm gonna need you
to get a lot faster.
&nbsp
I'm not gonna save Iris
from Savitar; you are.
&nbsp
Iris West, will you marry me?
_
&nbsp
And Wally just beat his personal best.
Oh, Barry's putting him
through the wringer today.
&nbsp
Excuse... Barry? Excuse me?
Uh, yeah, I suppose it could be Barry,
&nbsp
or it could be his genius
coach, whose sole purpose
&nbsp
on this Earth is milking epic greatness
from those around him.
&nbsp
Thank you very much.
- It could also be Jesse.
- What?
&nbsp
Come on, Wally doesn't want
to get beat by his girlfriend.
&nbsp
Also, please, just refrain from...
using "milk" as a verb
from now on, please.
&nbsp
I'm getting kind of dizzy.
You're supposed to get dizzy, Wallace!
&nbsp
You're supposed to get
exhausted on this route.
&nbsp
It's supposed to simulate
the stress that you're gonna feel
&nbsp
when you finally confront Savitar,
so my suggestion to you
is, suck it up, buttercup!
&nbsp
Milking epic greatness.
Yeah, no kidding.
&nbsp
Why don't you take it
down a little, tiger mom?
&nbsp
Barry and Jesse are at the final mark.
Get ready.
&nbsp
Wally's at the home stretch.
Come on...
&nbsp
- Guys?
- 0.21 seconds.
&nbsp
0.21.
Just fast enough to
save Iris from Savitar.
&nbsp
You did it.
- You did it.
- We did it.
&nbsp
- You did it!
- You did it.
&nbsp
You okay?
Uh, yeah, yeah.
&nbsp
I'm just... happy.
We all are, Wally.
&nbsp
We all are.
Synced and corrected by Aaronnmb
www.addic7ed.com
&nbsp
Julian. Hi.
- Ah, Caitlin, how are you?
- How are you? It...
&nbsp
You've come straight from the airport?
Uh... yes, yes, uh...
&nbsp
Barry said he had something
to tell me. Is he here?
&nbsp
He'll be here any minute, I'm sure.
- Shall we? Yeah?
- Yes, we shall.
&nbsp
We shall.
- Look who I found.
- Hey, guys.
&nbsp
Oh!
- How are we doing?
- Julian.
&nbsp
It's good to see you.
Good to see you all.
&nbsp
Jesse, I thought you were
heading back to Earth-2.
&nbsp
I actually decided to stick
around for a little while.
&nbsp
Hey, does anybody know what's going on?
I mean, I got a mountain of
paperwork back at the office.
&nbsp
No, not the foggiest.
I was gonna ask you.
&nbsp
Ah. Welcome home, James.
Can I brew you a proper cup of tea?
&nbsp
And a robust pick-me-up for you, mate.
No need. We hit Jitters on the way.
&nbsp
Got everybody something. You guys are...
I thought you were on deadline.
&nbsp
I am.
You ready?
&nbsp
- For you.
- Here.
&nbsp
Okay. What is going on with you two?
- Uh, do you want to?
- Mm-mm.
&nbsp
This is all you.
- Okay, here goes.
- Mm-hmm.
&nbsp
Um...
No!
&nbsp
Congratulations! That's so exciting!
Thank you. Thanks.
&nbsp
- Hey, thanks, man.
- Wow.
&nbsp
You did it. This is...
this is fantastic.
&nbsp
Well done, Joe. Congratulations.
Dad, say something, please.
&nbsp
My baby girl.
You have grown into a beautiful woman.
&nbsp
You're marrying the best man I know.
Thanks.
&nbsp
You two bring me nothing but joy.
- I'm so happy for you.
- Okay.
&nbsp
This cuteness right here, I cannot...
- Congrats.
- Thanks, man.
&nbsp
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
&nbsp
And speaking of, um,
best man...
&nbsp
I'll do it. Of course.
When Barry and I first met...
&nbsp
- H.R.
- You mean him.
&nbsp
Okay, good.
I...
&nbsp
I'd be honored. Really.
I mean, as long as I
can get that plus-one.
&nbsp
'Cause, you know, me and Gypsy,
we about to tear up the
dance floor for you guys.
&nbsp
Barry.
- Can I talk to you for a second?
- Yeah, yeah.
&nbsp
Now, I wanted to be sure that
you heard what I said in there.
&nbsp
I couldn't be happier.
Okay, right.
&nbsp
So...
why didn't you ask my permission?
&nbsp
I mean, I told you the story
of me asking Francine's
dad's permission,
&nbsp
like, a hundred times.
At least, yeah. And
that's a great story.
&nbsp
Eh, but you missed the point?
I... yeah, I...
&nbsp
I don't... it was spontaneous.
I knew you'd say yes, and
I wanted to surprise you.
&nbsp
Yo. There's a three-alarm
fire in the Raab building.
&nbsp
Fire department is evacuating it now.
Jesse is a little
preoccupied with the ring,
&nbsp
- so it's just you and me.
- Okay.
&nbsp
- What you two waiting for? Go.
- Yeah.
&nbsp
Wallace...
Wallace West.
&nbsp
Wally...
What the hell?
&nbsp
Wally.
Hey.
&nbsp
What's happening? What's wrong?
Where'd he go?
&nbsp
Who?
Where is he?
&nbsp
Who? Where is who?
Savitar.
&nbsp
I feel fine.
So now Savitar's mind-punking you...
&nbsp
Oh, boy.
This never stops never stopping.
&nbsp
How long has this been going on, Wally?
- Like a week.
- A week.
&nbsp
Wally, why didn't you
say anything before?
&nbsp
Because I didn't know what this was.
I thought that this was
just maybe in my head.
&nbsp
You know, I wasn't looking at it
like I was keeping it to myself.
&nbsp
That's exactly what
you did, though, Wally.
&nbsp
You did keep it to yourself,
and with Savitar, that's
not something we can do.
&nbsp
This is Iris' life we're talking about.
- Yes, I know that.
- Do you, though, Wally?
&nbsp
- Yes.
- Uh, okay.
&nbsp
Until now, you only saw him, right?
Yeah, this was the first
time it was physical.
&nbsp
What... he wasn't there!
Okay? You weren't fighting him.
&nbsp
He was messing with your head.
- It was all in your mind.
- I've been there. Done that.
&nbsp
It's miserable.
Okay, why don't I run
a brain scan on Wally,
&nbsp
see if he was similarly affected
to when Julian was possessed?
&nbsp
Yeah, that's fine. Why don't we do that?
Wally shouldn't be in here anyway.
&nbsp
- What?
- Barry, he knows he messed up.
&nbsp
That's not what this is
about, okay? Look, it's...
&nbsp
if Savitar's using Wally
the same way he used Julian,
&nbsp
how do we know he's not spying
on us through Wally right now?
&nbsp
Wally, we don't know how this works.
How do we know he can't see
and hear everything we're doing?
&nbsp
Look, you're out.
- I'm out?
- I'm sorry, Wally.
&nbsp
Yeah, you don't sound real sorry.
All right, fellows,
let's take a quick ten.
&nbsp
We're all still the
"Four Amigos" here, right?
&nbsp
What?
You don't have that movie on this Earth?
&nbsp
- I'll go talk to him.
- Yeah, talk some sense into him.
&nbsp
- All right.
- So what now?
&nbsp
Well, we know from the future
that Savitar gets out of wherever he is,
&nbsp
but for now, he's still trapped, so...
- I need to talk to him again.
- No, I knew you were thinking this.
&nbsp
All right? And I won't do it.
I'm not gonna be your
personal walkie-talkie to him.
&nbsp
Guys, we can't. We don't have the Stone.
Actually, we can.
&nbsp
We still have Savitar's
spatial frequency
&nbsp
from when we plugged
in Linda Blair here,
&nbsp
so I think we could
work without the Stone.
&nbsp
Julian, I'm sorry, man. We
don't really have a choice.
&nbsp
Oh, we do have a
choice. I have a choice.
&nbsp
And I choose to decline.
I'm sorry.
&nbsp
- We're starting to fray.
- Well, we can't. All right?
&nbsp
Everybody just needs to trust me.
I know what I'm doing.
&nbsp
Come to talk me into it, then?
No.
&nbsp
Barry's lost his
bloody mind if he thinks
&nbsp
I'm gonna volunteer
to be... abused again.
&nbsp
He's just trying to protect Iris.
We all are.
&nbsp
But... not like that.
Is the reason you don't
want to do this because...
&nbsp
you don't want me to see it?
I just think...
&nbsp
hearing his voice coming out of me, I...
it just makes it impossible
for you to see me as a normal...
&nbsp
Hey.
I've had somebody else's
voice coming out of my mouth,
&nbsp
and you were still
able to see the real me.
&nbsp
How about trusting that
I can do the same thing?
&nbsp
Sorry.
I just wanted to do that,
&nbsp
in case you changed your mind later.
Quite all right.
&nbsp
Julian, you're gonna be okay.
You know the drill.
&nbsp
Just let your mind go blank.
We'll take care of the rest. Okay?
&nbsp
Just let Savitar back in
the driver's seat once more.
&nbsp
- Brilliant.
- Thank you.
&nbsp
Let's just get this over with, yeah?
Bow before my greatness.
&nbsp
Be in awe, as you are in
the presence of the Almighty.
&nbsp
Enough with the... religious nonsense.
You were just a man. Like me.
&nbsp
I'm nothing like you, Barry.
You're cruel, you're selfish.
&nbsp
From my perspective, you're the big bad.
Stupid.
&nbsp
Still here, pretender?
Still trying to find your place?
&nbsp
I found my place.
It's standing here with these people,
&nbsp
against you.
You know, the sad
thing is that you live.
&nbsp
You survived my wrath.
The coward.
&nbsp
- Irony.
- Where are you?
&nbsp
You said that I trapped
you in the future, where?
&nbsp
The only place that you could think of.
The only place that could hold me.
&nbsp
How long have you been imprisoned?
Long enough to lose my
mind several times over.
&nbsp
It's only my will that keeps
me on this side of sanity.
&nbsp
You know, it's funny,
when I think of sanity,
&nbsp
I don't necessarily think of Savitar.
Well, that's because
you're small, Cisco.
&nbsp
You've always been small.
Reverb told you that you
could have been a god.
&nbsp
But instead, you'd rather
work as... tech support.
&nbsp
You want to tell me why we're enemies?
Because we had to be.
&nbsp
Only one of us could live.
You thought that Thawne and Zoom
&nbsp
were your biggest foes, but...
but it's me.
&nbsp
It's always been me, Barry.
Man, what did we ever do to you?
&nbsp
You took everything from me!
I never asked for any of this, Joe.
&nbsp
I am only this way because of you.
All of you!
&nbsp
When do we meet?
Not long now.
&nbsp
You're there when I become who I am.
You're saying I caused
you to get your speed?
&nbsp
- I created you?
- Oh, no.
&nbsp
I created myself, Barry.
Only I can bring out my greatness.
&nbsp
Your greatness?
Well, you're still trapped,
&nbsp
wherever you are,
and I don't know how
you're gonna escape.
&nbsp
I mean, we got rid of
the Philosopher's Stone.
&nbsp
Did we?
I am closer to my freedom
&nbsp
than I have ever been.
Every step, every move that you make,
&nbsp
it only brings me nearer to it.
I only need one more thing.
&nbsp
Man, do you love to hear yourself talk.
Iris, trying to show
that you're not afraid?
&nbsp
But I know you are.
I'm sorry that you have to die.
&nbsp
But it's you or me.
And despite your feeble
efforts to change the future,
&nbsp
you can't,
because I am the future, Flash.
&nbsp
Barry, you've had to
suffer worse than anyone.
&nbsp
You've endured pain your whole life.
Your mother,
&nbsp
your father...
Trust me,
&nbsp
you'll never get over this.
Well...
&nbsp
Well?
Good chat, was it?
&nbsp
I-I don't know if I can take another
one of those séances.
Anyone else with me?
&nbsp
I almost filled my drawers.
Okay, so other than Savitar taking
&nbsp
scaring-the-bejeezus-out-of-us
to a whole new level,
&nbsp
did we actually learn anything?
- Please say yes.
- Maybe.
&nbsp
When I mentioned the Stone,
he questioned whether or not
&nbsp
we'd really gotten rid of it.
We did. We threw it
into the Speed Force.
&nbsp
That's like throwing
it into outer space.
&nbsp
Uh, maybe we didn't. I mean,
maybe there's more to it.
&nbsp
- A second Stone?
- Or maybe the Stone
&nbsp
that we had was part of a larger piece.
How about the Acolytes?
&nbsp
Maybe they know something we don't.
- Hey, what about that one guy?
- Craig?
&nbsp
Yes, the Acolyte that you dropped in on
when you went all cold?
&nbsp
His car's GPS has him located
somewhere near... Mount Buccelato.
&nbsp
Buccelato, that's miles away.
What... what would he
be doing over there?
&nbsp
There's one way to find out.
Talk to us. What do you see?
&nbsp
Some serious "Temple of Doom" stuff.
They have a box.
&nbsp
God of Speed, soon
your enemies will fall
&nbsp
and you will rise once more on Earth.
It looks just like the last
one that held the Stone.
&nbsp
- You were right, Barr.
- What are you gonna do?
&nbsp
I'm gonna go see what's in it.
What exactly were you
guys doing up here?
&nbsp
Worshipping His Greatness.
Let's see how far he gets without this.
&nbsp
He's ten steps ahead of you.
There's no stopping Savitar.
&nbsp
If I were you...
I'd move up the wedding.
&nbsp
So far... not so good.
Can't get any readings off of it.
&nbsp
It's the same as the last time.
Are we sure this isn't the same box?
&nbsp
Well, it can't be. I mean, I threw
the other one into the Speed Force.
&nbsp
Yeah, but you said the
explosion sent you to the future.
&nbsp
What if it did something
to the box too, you know?
&nbsp
I hate to say it, Barry, but,
after all my years of research,
&nbsp
I've never heard or come
across another box or Stone;
&nbsp
I think this is it.
If that's true, we need
to consider the possibility
&nbsp
that Savitar has that Stone.
I'm gonna check for radioactive isotopes
&nbsp
or gravimetric force residue,
'cause if it's the
same as the last time...
&nbsp
We're in big trouble.
You can go faster than that, Wally. Run!
&nbsp
And...
time!
&nbsp
Yeah. Yeah. That was, uh...
good.
&nbsp
We need to go again.
But I don't understand. I
was fast enough this morning.
&nbsp
Now all of a sudden, I'm too slow?
You're in your head. You gotta
get out of your head, man.
&nbsp
You gotta just run, you gotta
push everything else to the side.
&nbsp
Yeah, I'm trying, H.R. I can't do it!
- Okay. Okay.
- All right?
&nbsp
All right. Why not?
I don't know.
&nbsp
I do.
You're afraid.
&nbsp
Which is... I totally understand.
I mean, if I were in your
shoes, I'd be terrified.
&nbsp
But...
you can't run from a
place of fear, all right?
&nbsp
Nobody can do anything effectively
coming from a place of
fear. Trust me, I know.
&nbsp
Savitar can get inside my head.
What am I supposed to do
&nbsp
if he does that at the wrong time?
It sure would be a lot easier if I just
&nbsp
knew exactly how that night went.
Would it ever.
&nbsp
Are you picking up
what I'm putting down?
&nbsp
Uh-huh.
Let's go.
&nbsp
No way. I'm not gonna vibe you there
for you to watch your sister die.
&nbsp
Okay. Cesco, Cesco, Cesco...
th-this is to help Wallace...
&nbsp
to help him see what happens
so he knows what to do in the moment.
&nbsp
Come on, Cisco, please.
If Savitar's coming back and I'm
the only one that can save Iris,
&nbsp
I have to do everything I
can to make sure that happens.
&nbsp
And you're sure you want to do that?
Because this is not something
you can unsee, Wally.
&nbsp
If this is gonna help
me save my sister, yeah.
&nbsp
I have to see it.
Please.
&nbsp
Okay, if you have to see it...
come on down, be my guest.
&nbsp
H.R., you know how to work this, right?
I know how to work this, yeah.
&nbsp
Anything goes wrong, you
get Caitlin down here stat.
&nbsp
I know what I'm doing.
I was here the last time.
&nbsp
I saw what you did. All
I got to do is do this.
&nbsp
- The other one.
- It's the other button.
&nbsp
Bit of a lighter touch
next time, please, H.R.!
&nbsp
- Copy. Lighter touch.
- This way.
&nbsp
Don't!
This is it.
&nbsp
Okay.
So that's the distance I need to cover.
&nbsp
Don't do this!
Now, finally, I am free of you!
&nbsp
Barry, I love you.
No, don't say that, all right?
You're gonna be all right.
&nbsp
Hey, I'm begging you, I'm begging you!
- I'm beg...
- Barry?
&nbsp
You lose, Barry.
No!
&nbsp
Iris?
Iris, Iris.
&nbsp
Look.
Come on.
&nbsp
What... what'd you see?
Was it good? Did that... did that help?
&nbsp
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
&nbsp
It helped a lot.
Wally...
&nbsp
Why does nobody ever listen to me?
You're so full of it.
&nbsp
- What?
- Railing at me
&nbsp
for not telling everyone about Savitar?
What about what you're not
telling everyone, Barry?
&nbsp
- What are you...
- Cisco vibed me...
&nbsp
into the future. I saw what happened.
Tell my sister why you
asked her to marry you.
&nbsp
Go on, tell her the real reason, Barry.
What is he talking about?
&nbsp
Barry.
The night that Savitar kills you,
&nbsp
you didn't have a ring on your finger.
We weren't engaged yet.
&nbsp
So you thought that if we were...
That it might change the future.
&nbsp
Iris...
Iris, wait.
&nbsp
Iris, hey. Come on.
Hey, hey, I love you, okay?
&nbsp
I love you more than anything.
That part has never
changed. It never will.
&nbsp
Barry, we moved in together
after some rash decision
&nbsp
that you made at Christmas,
and then a couple weeks
later, you proposed.
&nbsp
You didn't even ask
for my dad's permission.
&nbsp
I know. I don't know...
I guess I got caught...
&nbsp
I got caught up in the moment. I...
That is exactly what I am afraid of.
&nbsp
- Iris, please...
- Barry, I just...
&nbsp
I need time to think.
Hey.
&nbsp
You okay?
I'm worried.
&nbsp
Yeah, I understand.
I keep coming back
to the thought that...
&nbsp
I could be the cause of all this.
What do you mean?
&nbsp
Savitar's prophecy.
"One will betray you"
&nbsp
You may well have invited
Judas into the group, Caitlin.
&nbsp
It's not you.
It's impossible to tell.
&nbsp
Savitar could be controlling me,
and none of us would know about it.
&nbsp
None of us, not even me.
But this time, we know who it is.
&nbsp
How?
Because...
&nbsp
I'm the one who betrayed everyone.
How long have you had this?
&nbsp
Ever since you threw the
box into the Speed Force.
&nbsp
It's such a small piece.
I didn't think it would really matter.
&nbsp
Why would you even risk it?
Because...
&nbsp
I thought I could use it
to get rid of my powers.
&nbsp
And... can you?
I don't know. I haven't been able
to figure out how to use it yet.
&nbsp
Okay, well, look, gang,
I think we can all agree
&nbsp
that this is a simple
case of the other side...
&nbsp
Killer Frost side of Caitlin
clouding her better judgment, so...
&nbsp
No, H.R. This wasn't her.
It was me.
&nbsp
I'm really sorry, guys.
Right now, we just need to
figure out where Savitar is.
&nbsp
Yes, I think that's a fantastic plan.
How are we gonna do that?
&nbsp
Uh...
- No.
- One more time.
&nbsp
- No.
- No, no.
&nbsp
You want to summon Savitar again?
I am not a human Ouija board, Barry.
&nbsp
- You can't just keep...
- It's the last time, all right?
&nbsp
And only long enough to see
if maybe we can track his location.
&nbsp
- Is that possible?
- No. No.
&nbsp
Julian, we gotta end
this, for everybody's sake.
&nbsp
- I'll see you downstairs.
- Oh...
&nbsp
Okay, well, you guys can
count me out, all right?
&nbsp
'Cause I didn't bring an endless
supply of boxers to this planet.
&nbsp
Julian, please.
I should have told you.
&nbsp
I can't believe that you
would keep part of that Stone.
&nbsp
Do you not remember what
Savitar had me do with that?
&nbsp
Yes, I do.
But you're not concerned, are you?
&nbsp
You just want your own
personal meta-human specialist
&nbsp
to try and find you a cure.
Julian, I don't want these powers.
&nbsp
I can't spend the rest
of my life wondering
&nbsp
if or when I'm gonna lose this battle
and become Killer Frost.
&nbsp
I thought you more than
anyone would understand that.
&nbsp
You know... you know what I understand?
I understand the real reason
that you invited me on this team.
&nbsp
That's not the only reason.
Yeah, I wish I could believe that.
&nbsp
Dad.
I heard what happened.
&nbsp
Thought you might need a pick-me-up.
Worked like a charm when you were a kid.
&nbsp
Smaller problems.
Yeah.
&nbsp
So...
- you wanna talk about it?
- I don't know what I want, Dad.
&nbsp
Iris...
whatever you may be feeling
right now about Barry,
&nbsp
that man does love you.
That... that kind of love is rare.
&nbsp
Dad, I wish it were that simple.
Simple.
&nbsp
Look, only you know...
what's good for you.
&nbsp
But with the kind of lives...
that you two have,
&nbsp
that love between the two of you,
that is the one thing...
&nbsp
that should stay simple.
Baby girl.
&nbsp
We'll be here if you need anything.
Okay.
&nbsp
Back to worship me once again?
We just wanted to let you know
that we're gonna defeat you.
&nbsp
Unlikely.
You told us that you're trapped,
imprisoned for all eternity.
&nbsp
You're never getting out of wherever
my future self locked you up.
&nbsp
You'll never know freedom again.
All will be revealed soon, Flash.
&nbsp
You will face my wrath.
You will beg for mercy,
&nbsp
and you will get none.
- Did it work?
&nbsp
Yeah. We got a hit.
It's just that that hit
is all of Central City.
&nbsp
That's not a hit. The whole city?
- Yeah.
- God. Well...
&nbsp
can we get a little more specific?
Pinpoint a location at
least... uh, something?
&nbsp
I think maybe we can get
a little bit more precise,
&nbsp
but I'm gonna have to give
it the old meta-human try.
&nbsp
Okay.
It's Iris. All right.
I'll be right back, but...
&nbsp
just let me know if you
get anything, all right?
&nbsp
All right.
Hey.
&nbsp
You going somewhere?
Yeah, I just wanna get back
to S.T.A.R. Labs and train.
&nbsp
Seeing as how you exploded
on Barry in front of everyone,
&nbsp
might want to wait on it.
Well, the truth had to come out, so...
&nbsp
Yeah, it did.
Just maybe not that way.
&nbsp
I mean, we all have to help each other,
not point fingers.
&nbsp
You're right. I...
I'll make it up to them. It's just,
&nbsp
this whole thing is
messing with my head.
&nbsp
- Don't let it.
- You don't get it, Jesse.
&nbsp
When you got your powers,
you were walking down the street.
&nbsp
Me? I touched the Philosopher's Stone,
I got trapped in some cocoon, and...
&nbsp
I just feel, because
of all of that, I...
&nbsp
there's something wrong with me.
I feel like Savitar has some kind of...
&nbsp
hold on me.
Look, I know.
&nbsp
Okay? But you're strong, Wally.
You can fight this.
&nbsp
You know, all I ever
wanted was to have powers.
&nbsp
To do some good.
But now, now I'm...
I'm the one responsible
&nbsp
for saving Iris' life.
I don't know if I'm gonna be
fast enough to save her, so...
&nbsp
Okay, Wally. You're not alone.
Okay.
&nbsp
She's right, Wally.
You're not alone.
&nbsp
Mom.
You're never alone, Wally.
&nbsp
- I've missed you so much.
- I missed you too.
&nbsp
Wally?
I'm so proud of you.
&nbsp
Of what you're trying to become.
That's all I want.
&nbsp
I just want you to be proud of me.
Wally, you're really freaking me out.
&nbsp
I am, son. I'm so very, very proud.
But you have to stop.
&nbsp
What? Why?
You're working so hard.
&nbsp
You don't see how dangerous it is.
Son, you're not fast enough.
&nbsp
You never will be.
But I can't... I can't
stop. I have to save Iris.
&nbsp
- I have to.
- Wally.
&nbsp
You're in my head again.
You were always so smart.
&nbsp
Weren't you, Wallace?
But not smart enough.
&nbsp
I have what I need to
escape my hell, Wallace.
&nbsp
No, not everything.
We still have a piece of that Stone.
&nbsp
Not for long.
And once I have it,
&nbsp
you and everyone you love
will perish.
&nbsp
- Wally?
- I have to go.
&nbsp
I can't let him get out.
- What are you talking about?
- Savitar.
&nbsp
- You need to tell Barry, okay?
- No. I can do this by myself.
&nbsp
Jesse, please, just wait here.
- Hey.
&nbsp
I got your message.
Yeah. Come, sit down.
&nbsp
Iris, uh...
- I know you're mad, but...
- No, Barry, that's not it.
&nbsp
I just want you to listen. Okay?
I need you to...
&nbsp
let me say what I need to say.
Okay.
&nbsp
I'm not angry... at you.
I understand that you...
&nbsp
you want to keep me safe,
and us getting engaged
could change the future.
&nbsp
I... I get all of that.
Barry, when you proposed to me...
&nbsp
I said yes because...
I love you more than anything.
&nbsp
And I want to be your wife.
But I thought that you were
asking me purely out of love,
&nbsp
not fear.
And, Barry, whether
you realize it or not,
&nbsp
now there's always gonna be
a part of us that's tainted.
&nbsp
Iris, I'm trying to save your life.
I know, and that's the problem.
&nbsp
I want to be your wife, Barry.
I don't want to be...
&nbsp
someone that you're trying to save
for the rest of eternity.
&nbsp
Eternity.
- Can't see anything.
- Give me those.
&nbsp
- Are those things even working?
- Yep.
&nbsp
Stop it!
- I just wanna see if they're working.
- What are you doing?
&nbsp
- What do you see?
- I'm seeing these white...
&nbsp
- flashes, it's like...
- Flashes?
&nbsp
Yeah, it's like Savitar
speeding through, like, a storm.
&nbsp
No, it's not a storm.
It's the Speed Force.
&nbsp
He's in the Speed Force.
That's why only speedsters
were able to see him.
&nbsp
Why is Savitar hiding
in the Speed Force?
&nbsp
He's not hiding.
That's where the future you trapped him.
&nbsp
That's right.
And that's why Savitar only
appears for a few moments at a time,
&nbsp
because the Speed Force just sucks
him back in. That makes sense.
&nbsp
But we threw the Philosopher's
Stone into the Speed Force.
&nbsp
And we gave him the very
thing he needed to escape.
&nbsp
Except, he said he
still needed one thing.
&nbsp
I don't think he can come out
because he doesn't have the whole Stone.
&nbsp
Guys... Wally went after Savitar.
- What?
&nbsp
He started hallucinating.
He thought he was talking to his mom.
&nbsp
No, that's... that's
not her. That's Savitar.
&nbsp
- Where'd he go?
- I don't know.
&nbsp
Okay. He was freaking
out. He said that...
&nbsp
he needed to stop
Savitar from getting out,
&nbsp
and he sped off.
The Stone.
&nbsp
- It's gone?
- It's gone.
&nbsp
- Barry, we gotta find Wally.
- Yeah.
&nbsp
If Savitar gets ahold
of the Stone, then...
&nbsp
He'll escape for sure.
I can't find him. He turned
off the suit's telemetry.
&nbsp
Oh, come on!
Poor Wallace.
&nbsp
Can't even open a portal.
You can't get rid of
that Stone, Wallace.
&nbsp
Like you can't get rid of me.
Oh, shut up, shut up.
&nbsp
You know it's true.
You're not fast enough to
throw it into the Speed Force
&nbsp
by yourself.
Shut up!
&nbsp
I'm going to get out of here, Wallace.
And then I'm gonna come for you...
&nbsp
and Barry and your sister,
and I'll kill everyone you love.
&nbsp
No, you're not real!
You're just in my head, just...
&nbsp
Oh, I'm real,
and I know the limits of your speed.
&nbsp
After all, I'm the
one who gave it to you.
&nbsp
And that...
giving me speed...
&nbsp
that was your biggest mistake.
- There's a massive power surge.
- Where?
&nbsp
The old Kob Factory.
Pulling up security footage.
&nbsp
Oh, my God.
Wally.
&nbsp
No!
Aah!
&nbsp
No!
No! Help me, Barry!
&nbsp
Aah!
I am free!
&nbsp
Ground.
Air...
&nbsp
I can feel again.
I can breathe again.
&nbsp
I've beaten you, finally.
Where's Wally?
&nbsp
What just happened to him?
Like the Greek myth of Atlas,
&nbsp
who could not put down the sky
until someone took his place,
&nbsp
Wally has taken my
place in the Speed Force.
&nbsp
You know me. I love a good myth.
He took your place. What...
&nbsp
When you created Flashpoint,
you unwittingly provided me
with the means for my return.
&nbsp
Wally...
You gave me the idea to turn Wally
&nbsp
into Kid Flash,
to make him fast enough to replace me
&nbsp
in your prison.
His youth and ego were my allies.
&nbsp
So taken with his fame and speed,
he never saw he was
running right into my trap.
&nbsp
How do I get him out?
- Wally's gone.
- How do I get him out?
&nbsp
Suffering in an endless
void for all eternity.
&nbsp
Another victim Barry
Allen failed to save.
&nbsp
No!
I'm gonna kill you!
&nbsp
If you had the strength to end my life,
you would have done it in the future.
&nbsp
But Barry Allen doesn't kill.
He's the good guy.
&nbsp
The boy Joe raised. The man Iris loves.
You have everything.
&nbsp
And deserve none of it.
I'm going to destroy this
city like I did in the future,
&nbsp
so you can see the truth, Barry.
And then, you'll treat me like a god.
&nbsp
You're not a god!
Who are you?
&nbsp
I am the future, Flash.
Show your face.
&nbsp
I want so badly to kill you,
and I will.
&nbsp
But you have to live
a little while longer.
&nbsp
Long enough to see Iris die.
The blade didn't hit your organs,
&nbsp
but it did shatter your clavicle.
Hang in there, man, hang in there.
&nbsp
- We have to take it out.
- Do it!
&nbsp
Any medicine I give you your
metabolism will burn through.
&nbsp
All right. Just do it, okay?
- Just do it.
- Hold him down.
&nbsp
Okay. Gonna be okay,
mate. You're gonna be okay.
&nbsp
Bite down on this.
I'm so sorry.
&nbsp
Three, two, one.
- How long was I out?
- Not long.
&nbsp
Are you in much pain?
I might be able to do
something with this.
&nbsp
Joe.
I'm sorry.
&nbsp
Not your fault.
Where is he?
&nbsp
I mean, is he in pain? Is he...
"One will suffer a
fate worse than death."
&nbsp
Jesse,
I...
&nbsp
I'm not like your dad. I don't really...
know what the right words are...
&nbsp
What are we gonna do?
We have to bring him back.
We have to save him...
&nbsp
I can't lose Wally, Barry.
I'm sorry.
&nbsp
I'm gonna work on this.
Yeah.
&nbsp
I'll see you soon.
I'm sorry.
&nbsp
I should have never...
- I was afraid.
- I know.
&nbsp
Believe me, I know.
Fear makes us do a lot of
things that we shouldn't.
&nbsp
My fear's the reason for all of this.
Synced and corrected by Aaronnmb
www.addic7ed.com
&nbsp