My name is Barry Allen,
&nbsp
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world, I'm an
ordinary forensic scientist,
&nbsp
but secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
&nbsp
I fight crime and find
other meta-humans like me.
&nbsp
In an attempt to stop the
evil speedster Savitar,
&nbsp
I was accidentally
thrust into the future,
&nbsp
and I saw him murder
the woman that I love.
&nbsp
But I won't let that happen.
I'm gonna do everything in
my power to change the future,
&nbsp
and I'm the only one fast
enough to keep her alive.
&nbsp
I am The Flash.
Previously, on "The Flash"...
&nbsp
The night that Savitar kills you,
you didn't have a ring on your finger.
&nbsp
We weren't engaged yet.
So you thought that if we were...
&nbsp
That it might change the future.
Now there's always gonna be
a part of us that's tainted.
&nbsp
Why is Savitar hiding
in the Speed Force?
&nbsp
That's where the future you trapped him.
- That's right.
- I have what I need...
&nbsp
... to escape my hell, Wallace.
Not everything; we still
have a piece of that stone.
&nbsp
- It's gone?
- If Savitar gets ahold of the stone...
&nbsp
He'll escape for sure.
You can't get rid of
that stone, Wallace.
&nbsp
You're not fast enough to
throw it into the Speed Force
&nbsp
by yourself.
Wally has taken my
place in the Speed Force.
&nbsp
We have to bring him
back. We have to save him.
&nbsp
My fear is the reason for all of this.
Savitar was right.
&nbsp
This is all because of me,
because of my weakness.
&nbsp
Flashpoint.
And because of it,
everyone's lives have changed.
&nbsp
Everyone I love is suffering.
This has to stop.
&nbsp
I can't let anyone hurt
anymore because of me.
&nbsp
No one else should
have to pay for my sins.
&nbsp
And they won't.
Ever again.
&nbsp
Cisco.
Get the breach room ready.
&nbsp
Okay, for what?
I'm gonna save Wally.
&nbsp
How exactly are you going to do that?
I'm going back into the Speed Force.
&nbsp
Synced and corrected by Aaronnmb
www.addic7ed.com
&nbsp
I'm just trying to wrap my mind around
you going into the Speed Force again.
&nbsp
The Savitar said he was there for years.
You said it was like being in space.
&nbsp
- I know.
- So what are you gonna do?
&nbsp
You gonna run in there and
run around till you find him?
&nbsp
- It's endless.
- I know.
&nbsp
And this is the only way to save Wally.
Yeah, yeah, I just... we need a plan.
&nbsp
I... I...
I don't wanna lose both my sons.
&nbsp
Look, gang, I don't
understand the Speed Force,
&nbsp
but there are plenty of
people in this room who do.
&nbsp
Am I correct in assuming
there's a point coming?
&nbsp
My point is why can't
you use your knowledge
&nbsp
to fashion some kind of safety
precaution for young BA right here,
&nbsp
so that, while he's in the
Speed Force, he doesn't get lost.
&nbsp
Oh, so you're saying I can just whip up
some kind of inter-dimensional tether
&nbsp
to just anchor him to the Universe?
Yeah.
&nbsp
- That's exactly what I can do.
- Yeah!
&nbsp
Now we're cooking with helium.
Yes, and I can... I can
add a biological component
&nbsp
that will measure his vitals
when he's in the Speed Force.
&nbsp
- That's a great idea.
- Thank you, Caitlin.
&nbsp
Because if we can
monitor Barry's vitals,
&nbsp
we'll know if they fluctuate,
and we can pull him out.
&nbsp
You mean "pull us out."
Yeah, if you're going in
there to save Wally, so am I.
&nbsp
Jesse, you're gonna stay here.
Because if your father finds out
you're lost in some negative world,
&nbsp
the first person to get
a broken schnoz is me.
&nbsp
- There's a negative world?
- Yeah, negative world.
&nbsp
Really? They have
Super Mario on Earth-29?
&nbsp
Oh, yeah, challenge me.
Barry, you need my help.
Your shoulder is still broken.
&nbsp
It's okay. It's almost healed.
No, look, I can do this.
&nbsp
I know, but I need you to stay here.
Keep the city safe while I'm gone.
&nbsp
And this is something I
have to do alone, okay?
&nbsp
Fine.
Thank you.
&nbsp
Okay, let's go to work.
Can I talk to you?
&nbsp
Yeah.
I'm gonna find Wally.
&nbsp
Whatever's holding him,
whatever's keeping him trapped in there,
&nbsp
I'm gonna get him back.
- Okay.
&nbsp
Iris...
did I lose you?
&nbsp
Bar.
What's going on?
&nbsp
Nothing, nothing.
I'm just trying to make her...
&nbsp
not worry so much.
About Wally or you?
&nbsp
Joe, now's not the time, all right?
Look, you...
&nbsp
are about to risk your life
to save her brother.
&nbsp
I think now is the perfect time.
She's having doubts about us.
&nbsp
About marrying me.
Did she call off the engagement?
&nbsp
Guess I changed the
future one too many times.
&nbsp
I think that's gonna do it.
We should be able to use this
to keep track of Barry's vitals.
&nbsp
He'll play astronaut,
and we'll play Houston.
&nbsp
Right, but how exactly are
you gonna track his location
&nbsp
when he's in the Speed Force?
Well, this is just a simple modification
&nbsp
from what we used to
get Barry out last time,
&nbsp
so the electrode halo?
Julian wasn't part
of the team last time.
&nbsp
- Not yet.
- Oh, right.
&nbsp
You know that thing we
used to talk to Savitar?
&nbsp
Yes.
Meet the electrode halo.
&nbsp
So basically these two are
linked electromagnetically
&nbsp
- via Goldtooth.
- Goldtooth?
&nbsp
Yeah, it's kind of the Cisco Ramon
inter-dimensional
equivalent of Bluetooth.
&nbsp
Kind of proud of it.
Anyway, it gives us all the
relevant locus information
&nbsp
no matter what corner of the
multiverse Barry's stuck in.
&nbsp
And, if Barry needs our help,
it'll stimulate Cisco's
prefrontal cortex.
&nbsp
And I'll open a breach and...
send him back in.
&nbsp
Good Lord, multiverses, breaches, halos,
easy bloody peasy.
&nbsp
By George, I think he's got it.
Cisco, you about ready?
&nbsp
Born ready.
Okay.
&nbsp
Here's winging it.
Winging it? Wait, what do you mean?
&nbsp
Well, I mean, I don't really
have a map of the Speed Force,
&nbsp
so when I vibe Barry into it...
You have no idea where I'm gonna land.
&nbsp
But the good news is, if he gets stuck
on the wrong side of the
tracks, now we can fish him out.
&nbsp
Find my boy.
I'm gonna do whatever it takes.
&nbsp
Thank you.
I love you, Iris.
&nbsp
I love you too.
Are we ready?
&nbsp
Good to go.
To infinity... and beyond.
&nbsp
Okay, once I let go, you're on your own.
Do it.
&nbsp
Good luck.
Wally?
&nbsp
Hello?
Hey, Bar.
&nbsp
Why are you here?
Why did you come back to this place?
&nbsp
I'm here to save Wally West.
Ever the hero, huh, Barry?
&nbsp
It's my fault that he's trapped here.
Is it?
&nbsp
Where is Wally West?
He's not exactly here, per se.
&nbsp
He's in the prison you created.
Well, your future self, that is.
&nbsp
How do I get him out?
I think you'll find we're not gonna be
&nbsp
as accommodating as we were
the last time you visited us.
&nbsp
What the hell does that mean?
It means things have changed.
&nbsp
We gave you your speed
back because you said
&nbsp
you'd come to terms
with your mother's death,
&nbsp
but you lied to us.
- I...
- You went back in time,
&nbsp
and saved her.
And, in doing so, you
created Flashpoint.
&nbsp
Zoom had just killed my father.
We know, and we understand,
&nbsp
which is why we allowed you to do that,
but choices have consequences.
&nbsp
And I'm afraid we can't let you
make any more choices like that.
&nbsp
Wally is just a kid.
He's a Flash.
&nbsp
He made his choice.
Now he has to live with it,
&nbsp
just like you do.
I'm not going anywhere
until Wally's free.
&nbsp
Then be prepared to
spend an eternity in here.
&nbsp
Why would you order a single espresso?
It's gotta be at least
a double espresso.
&nbsp
I can go triple.
- Doesn't affect me at all.
- Frightening.
&nbsp
I can have a quadruple, a sextuple.
Oh, there you are. I'm
gonna get us all coffees
&nbsp
'cause we got a lot of
work to do, you know?
&nbsp
A lot of... a lot of stuff to do.
It doesn't affect me though.
It doesn't affect me at all!
&nbsp
Okay.
- He scares me.
- Yeah.
&nbsp
I was wondering, do you
think you could use this
&nbsp
to track Savitar's location?
That's not a bad idea.
&nbsp
You know, I couldn't before
because he was in the Speed Force,
&nbsp
but, now that he's out of it,
feeling footloose and
fancy-free, I'm sure...
&nbsp
I'm sorry, you know what?
That was insensitive of me.
&nbsp
- It's fine.
- Okay, so...
&nbsp
let's say I find Savitar, right now.
What are you gonna do about it?
&nbsp
I'm gonna go after him.
Jesse, are you out of your mind?
&nbsp
No, okay? I can't just sit here waiting.
You can, and you will.
&nbsp
We all will. And, soon enough,
Barry's gonna get Wally
out of the Speed Force.
&nbsp
You don't know that, okay?
We don't know anything.
&nbsp
The only thing we actually know
is that Savitar is out there,
&nbsp
and, if we can, we have to find him
and send him right
back where he came from.
&nbsp
You're staying here.
_
&nbsp
Iris.
I wrote that article.
&nbsp
That used to be my byline, but...
not anymore.
&nbsp
Well, 2024 is a long ways away.
Things could still change.
&nbsp
What if it's too late?
What if some things can't be undone?
&nbsp
You having second thoughts?
I guess I'm just worried that...
&nbsp
I made the wrong decision.
And what?
&nbsp
You think that calling things off...
sent Barry running into the Speed Force?
&nbsp
Please, we both know
that he was gonna go
save Wally no matter what.
&nbsp
Yeah, that's just the
kind of hero he is.
&nbsp
Sweetheart, I know... I
know how you're feeling.
&nbsp
You can't figure out which
way's up right now, can you?
&nbsp
Do yourself a favor.
Look deep inside that big,
beautiful heart of yours.
&nbsp
You'll find the answer
you're looking for.
&nbsp
Eddie Thawne's life
was almost so different.
&nbsp
Iris was about to be his wife.
Joe was about to be his father-in-law.
&nbsp
But things didn't turn out
that way, did they, Barry?
&nbsp
Instead of that life being his legacy...
this is.
&nbsp
So the only reason you
came back is to save Wally.
&nbsp
Yes.
There's no other reason?
&nbsp
No.
All right then, Bar.
&nbsp
If you want Wally, all you need to do
is go through those doors.
&nbsp
But you're gonna have to
outrun that thing first.
&nbsp
Time Wraith.
♪ Hush, little baby, don't say a word ♪
&nbsp
♪ Mama's gonna buy you a mockingbird ♪
Caitlin.
&nbsp
♪ And if that mockingbird don't sing ♪
♪ Mama's gonna buy you a diamond ring ♪
&nbsp
That baby...
is she...
&nbsp
Beautiful.
Just like her mother.
&nbsp
Ronnie.
Hello, Barry.
&nbsp
We need to talk.
Perhaps some sort of new metal
akin to a Luttinger liquid?
&nbsp
What do you think?
Man, I don't know what this is.
&nbsp
All I know, it just came off the armor
of some Hindu speed god, so...
&nbsp
It's like the box the
philosopher's stone came in.
&nbsp
It simultaneously
exists and doesn't exist.
&nbsp
Like Schroeder's cat.
Remember Schroeder?
&nbsp
Guy with the cat in the
box both dead and alive
&nbsp
at the same time, dun,
dun, dun, which, by the way,
&nbsp
seems like cruelty for
animals half the time.
&nbsp
Okay, I think you're thinking
of Schrodinger, maybe?
&nbsp
- Schroding... no.
- Yeah, 'cause Schroeder's
&nbsp
the guys from "Peanuts."
- I don't think so.
- Yeah, the one with the piano.
&nbsp
- Yeah.
- The...
&nbsp
Charlie Brown has the piano on my Earth.
That's the whole gag 'cause
he can't play the piano.
&nbsp
- He's terrible.
- No.
&nbsp
Oh, my God, who cares
about cats or pianos
&nbsp
- or the freaking "Peanuts"?
- It's not "The Peanuts."
&nbsp
It's just "Peanuts."
You have been studying
this thing for hours.
&nbsp
Can we or can we not
use it to track Savitar?
&nbsp
Okay, all right, wind it in.
As far as we can tell, the shard is
made of near-frictionless material
&nbsp
that's in a constant state of flux.
So while it's utterly
motionless on the outside...
&nbsp
It's constantly moving on the inside.
Yes, it's as if it's being affected
by some sort of external source,
&nbsp
much like the tides are affected
by the phases of the moon.
&nbsp
Okay, okay, then it has to be Savitar.
I mean, this was part of his armor.
&nbsp
Maybe it's trying to reconnect
with its other pieces.
&nbsp
That's it.
It's just like "The Iron Giant."
&nbsp
If this is true, then this
shard could lead us right to him.
&nbsp
That's an idea.
Okay, all right, so
what are we waiting for?
&nbsp
Let's...
Hold your roll, Jesse Quick.
&nbsp
This hesitation that you
feel, on behalf of the group,
&nbsp
is our realization that
this "go for broke" attitude
&nbsp
is the very attitude that
got Wallace in his predicament
&nbsp
in the first place. Am I right?
I can't believe I'm uttering the words,
&nbsp
but I actually agree with H.R.
- Ditto.
- Thanks, boys.
&nbsp
A lone speedster...
it's just no match for Savitar.
&nbsp
- Yeah, but...
- Jesse, we're gonna find him.
&nbsp
When?
When the real Flash gets back.
&nbsp
That came out wrong, um...
Wow.
&nbsp
Put my foot in it.
Jesse, Jesse!
&nbsp
Oh, Jesse, hey, Jesse, quick question:
Merlot or Cabernet?
&nbsp
What?
What wine do you think would go best
&nbsp
with a big, old men's size
11 shoe stuffed in his mouth?
&nbsp
- H.R.?
- Yeah?
&nbsp
- Just leave me alone.
- I get it, I get it.
&nbsp
I get... Savitar...
Savitar hurt the one you love,
&nbsp
now you wanna hurt Savitar.
Yeah, bet your ass, I do.
&nbsp
No, I get it. I... I love it.
I respect it. I'm a
little worried though
&nbsp
that, in your zeal for
payback, you might be the one
&nbsp
who ends up getting hurt.
- On my Earth...
- Yeah.
&nbsp
- I am the real Flash.
- I know.
&nbsp
That's why I...
I should've said what I said.
&nbsp
No, no, you shouldn't have, okay?
'Cause I've fought
plenty of monsters before.
&nbsp
Yeah, absolutely.
Like Savitar, though?
&nbsp
'Cause, look, here's the thing.
If your father were here, he would...
&nbsp
He would do everything in
his power to stop Savitar.
&nbsp
And that is exactly what I'm gonna do.
Okay, okay.
&nbsp
I mean, hats off to you.
You really are Hard-Hat
Harry's little girl, aren't you?
&nbsp
Yeah, I am, and you're not him.
So just do us both a favor
and stop trying to be.
&nbsp
This troubles you.
Another life that could've
been and never was.
&nbsp
Caitlin and Ronnie should've had that.
A family, a future.
&nbsp
The future doesn't always
turn out as we want it to.
&nbsp
I see what you're doing.
First Eddie, now Ronnie,
&nbsp
showing me all of the people
who sacrificed themselves
for the greater good.
&nbsp
No, Barry, their
sacrifices were for you,
&nbsp
as was Wally's when he
attempted to stop Savitar.
&nbsp
No, Savitar tricked Wally.
And now he's trapped.
&nbsp
Wally doesn't belong in the Speed Force.
You have to let me take his place.
&nbsp
And that's why I'm here.
Or the other reason, Barry.
&nbsp
I wanna sacrifice myself for Wally.
- We can't allow that.
- Why not?
&nbsp
Because where Wally's
gone is a hell all his own.
&nbsp
Savitar said, "One will suffer
a fate far worse than death."
&nbsp
And it's not for you.
Leave, Barry, while you still can.
&nbsp
No.
Whatever hell Wally's trapped
in, I'm gonna set him free,
&nbsp
and I'm not leaving here until I do.
Very well, but you were warned.
&nbsp
Hunter Zolomon.
Come on, come on.
&nbsp
- Is it Barry?
- Did something happen to him?
&nbsp
We don't know. One second, the
telemetry was perfectly normal, and...
&nbsp
Then his vitals, they
just started crashing.
&nbsp
We warned you.
Why are you doing this?
&nbsp
You speak of sacrifice,
yet you still let others
&nbsp
bear the burdens that
should be on your shoulders.
&nbsp
Okay, okay, you're right.
You're right.
&nbsp
I never should've asked
Wally to save Iris.
&nbsp
It should've been me.
Please, let me save him.
&nbsp
There's only one way to free Wally West
from his eternal torment.
&nbsp
You must free yourself first.
I love you, Iris.
&nbsp
No.
- Cisco, is he...
- I don't know, I don't know.
&nbsp
Find out!
I can't.
&nbsp
- The tether's gone.
- What?
&nbsp
That was him and Wally's
lifeline out of the Speed Force.
&nbsp
How are we gonna get them back?
I don't know that we can.
&nbsp
Hello?
Wally?
&nbsp
Wally, Wally!
I'm gonna get you out, okay?
&nbsp
Just hang on.
Visiting hours are over, Flash.
&nbsp
So...
that's not yours.
&nbsp
- Get out of my way.
- I can't do that.
&nbsp
Not if you're planning on using
that to fight Savitar. I can't.
&nbsp
You're not gonna talk
me out of this, okay?
&nbsp
- I already told you you're not...
- ... Not your dad.
&nbsp
That message was
received loud and clear.
&nbsp
Now hear mine.
Taking on Savitar all alone
&nbsp
is not gonna bring Wallace back, Jesse.
It's just gonna get
you killed, and that,
&nbsp
my friend, that is not happening.
Not on my watch.
&nbsp
You done?
Yeah, said my piece.
&nbsp
And guess what?
I'm still not...
&nbsp
moving...
That was oddly satisfying.
&nbsp
What's happening to him?
Wally West is caught in
an endless temporal loop,
&nbsp
just like Savitar after you
imprisoned him here in the future.
&nbsp
No wonder he hates you.
What's he seeing?
&nbsp
He's reliving the single most
painful moment of his life...
&nbsp
over and over again.
His mother's death.
&nbsp
Wally.
He doesn't deserve this.
&nbsp
Let me guess. You do?
I know what my hell is.
&nbsp
I've already seen it in the future.
You don't like the future, Flash?
&nbsp
- Change it.
- I can't.
&nbsp
Don't you get it? I can't!
I'm not fast enough. He is.
&nbsp
That's why you have to
let me take his place.
&nbsp
Wally can save Iris.
Not learning your lesson, Barry.
&nbsp
You keep telling us one
thing and then doing another.
&nbsp
You wanna know what
inspired Leonard Snart
&nbsp
to sacrifice himself?
It was you, Barry Allen.
&nbsp
You inspired him to be better.
You inspired him to be selfless,
&nbsp
to sacrifice himself for others,
to be a hero,
&nbsp
just like you.
I'm no hero.
&nbsp
Not lately.
So what?
&nbsp
You've had enough, Scarlet Speedster?
Time to hang up the
cowl and give it all up?
&nbsp
Well, if you're out...
you're out.
&nbsp
I'm done fighting.
We know, and that's exactly the problem.
&nbsp
You think seeing Iris' death is hell?
You ain't seen nothing yet.
&nbsp
Let's get you out of here.
Okay, you stupid piece of metal,
&nbsp
take me to your leader.
Gotcha.
&nbsp
Jesse Quick.
I knew you would come for me.
&nbsp
How'd you know I was coming here?
Because I know everything that happens.
&nbsp
I've already lived it.
- I'm not afraid of you.
- You should be.
&nbsp
Jesse.
H.R.?
&nbsp
It's a little late to
talk me out of this, okay?
&nbsp
I'm not gonna try and talk you out
of anything. I learned that lesson.
&nbsp
You have something that belongs to me.
I need a little help here, H.R.
&nbsp
- Bum, bum, thinking.
- Think faster.
&nbsp
What do we got? We're fighting Savitar.
Savitar is a speed god. He's omnipotent.
&nbsp
He's invulnerable.
Then why does he need a suit of armor?
&nbsp
Jesse, he's vulnerable
somewhere under the suit.
&nbsp
Find a gap, find an
opening, and go for it.
&nbsp
I have such plans for you
in the future, Jesse Quick.
&nbsp
And I have plans for you too.
This is for Wally.
&nbsp
Ahh!
Yeah!
&nbsp
Jay.
Yeah?
&nbsp
Is this really you,
or is this...
&nbsp
just another Speed Force test?
Yeah, kid, it's really me.
&nbsp
How?
As soon as the team
lost contact with you,
&nbsp
Cisco came to my Earth and
told me what was happening.
&nbsp
I came here to help.
Let's get Wally.
&nbsp
'Fraid I can't let you do that.
Getting a little slow in your
golden age there, Garrick.
&nbsp
- Stop.
- Can't do that either.
&nbsp
Enough!
I'm taking Wally.
&nbsp
We can't let you do that, Barry.
Yeah? Try and stop me.
&nbsp
Wally?
Hey, Wally.
&nbsp
Hey.
Barry, Jay.
&nbsp
- I saw my mom.
- I know,
&nbsp
- I know.
- My mom.
&nbsp
I know. Look at me now, okay?
It's over.
&nbsp
You're free now, okay?
We're going home, all right?
&nbsp
It's okay.
We're going home.
&nbsp
Jay, let's go.
Sorry, kid,
&nbsp
this is where I stay for a while.
What? What are you talking about?
&nbsp
We both know that a speedster
needs to take Wally's place.
&nbsp
That's why I'm here.
No, no, Jay, you already lived your hell
&nbsp
when you were Zoom's prisoner.
And you set me free,
and I owe you for that.
&nbsp
- Jay...
- I've run a hell of a race,
&nbsp
but every marathon has a finish line.
Time's finally come for
me to cross it, but you...
&nbsp
you, Barry,
need to put an end to
this once and for all
&nbsp
and stop Savitar.
How?
&nbsp
Do what you do best.
Be The Flash.
&nbsp
Cisco said that he could
use this to track you...
&nbsp
and bring you home.
I'm gonna get this back to you again,
&nbsp
when I break you out of here.
See you soon, Flash.
&nbsp
What's happening?
Do you think you can reel them in?
&nbsp
I don't know.
I've never felt this
much harmonic feedback.
&nbsp
It feels like the Speed
Force is about to...
&nbsp
- Wally!
- Barry!
&nbsp
Oh, my God.
Are you okay?
&nbsp
We will be.
Hold on a second.
&nbsp
Three speedsters go in,
and only two come out.
&nbsp
Jay...
Jay stayed back...
&nbsp
to save Wally.
Come on, Wally, let's
get you checked out.
&nbsp
I thought I lost both my boys.
- Thanks for bringing him back.
- You're welcome.
&nbsp
Thank you.
I thought I'd lost you too.
&nbsp
I'm right here.
The Speed Force.
&nbsp
And it just appeared to you
in the form of Eddie Thawne?
&nbsp
- And Ronnie?
- And Snart.
&nbsp
All to teach me another lesson.
Which was what?
&nbsp
Saving Iris is my
responsibility and mine alone.
&nbsp
It's why the Speed Force didn't
let me take Wally's place,
&nbsp
why Jay sacrificed himself to do it.
So I could finish this.
&nbsp
Jay,
hero among heroes.
&nbsp
Yeah.
We can't just leave him in there.
&nbsp
We won't.
I'll beat Savitar. We'll get him out.
&nbsp
Good, 'cause it seems
to me the Speed Force
&nbsp
is a little bit of a crazy place.
Just ask Wallace.
&nbsp
Yeah, yeah, what...
what Wally saw...
&nbsp
it's gonna haunt him for a while.
So until he can get past
it, and he's really ready
&nbsp
to go back out there, Kid Flash is...
gonna need to take a break for a while.
&nbsp
Hey.
You okay?
&nbsp
Are you?
Right.
&nbsp
You should see the other guy.
Caitlin said I'll be fine.
&nbsp
Jesse, I can't believe you
went after Savitar by yourself.
&nbsp
What were you thinking?
The same thing you were when you did it.
&nbsp
Yeah, that was a mistake.
One that I will never make again.
&nbsp
Yeah, yeah, me either.
Not on this Earth, anyway.
&nbsp
Wait, what? You're going
back to Earth-2 already?
&nbsp
- Earth-3, actually.
- But you just got here, Jesse.
&nbsp
I know, I know, and
I want to be with you.
&nbsp
It's just Savitar said he had
plans for me in the future.
&nbsp
I can't let that happen.
Besides, until Barry can get
Jay out of the Speed Force,
&nbsp
Earth-3 needs a Flash to protect it.
I love you, Jesse.
&nbsp
I love you too.
You show those villains on Earth-3.
&nbsp
Nobody messes with our Jesse Quick.
- That's right. You give them hell.
- You know I will.
&nbsp
We're here if you need us, all right?
- Safe travels.
- Thanks.
&nbsp
Sorry for the, uh...
Yeah, yeah, me too.
&nbsp
- Good left-hook.
- Thanks.
&nbsp
I shouldn't be surprised. Us Wellses...
we are forces to be reckoned with.
&nbsp
That we are.
Thank you, H.R.
&nbsp
For what?
Just being a friend.
&nbsp
Thank you.
Yeah.
&nbsp
- You ready?
- Yeah.
&nbsp
This isn't good-bye.
No, it's more like "see you later."
&nbsp
I can't wait.
So, fun fact...
&nbsp
uncovered by our intrepid Jesse Quick,
in her latest dust-up with
the so-called "God of Speed,"
&nbsp
guess who feels pain.
What... what exactly are you saying?
&nbsp
Are you saying that underneath
the suit of armor that's he's...
&nbsp
Yes, James. He's not a god.
He's just a man, baby.
&nbsp
- A man?
- Yeah.
&nbsp
Hey.
Thank you for saving Wally.
&nbsp
Of course.
Um,
&nbsp
so, I just...
Look, you told me that you
only wanted to marry someone
&nbsp
because they love you
and not because they
were trying to save you,
&nbsp
and I get that.
I just...
&nbsp
you know, I've lived
with a lot of death,
&nbsp
tragedy in my life,
and seeing you die...
&nbsp
it's impossible not
to be consumed by that.
&nbsp
Yeah, no, I get that.
I do.
&nbsp
It just...
it made me question
if you were asking me
&nbsp
for the right reasons, you know?
If it was out of love or...
&nbsp
responsibility.
But, look,
&nbsp
while you were gone,
I realized something.
&nbsp
I don't have to doubt
why you wanna marry me.
&nbsp
It's the same reason
that I wanna marry you.
&nbsp
Mm-hmm.
I wanna be your wife, Barry.
&nbsp
Um...
I love you.
&nbsp
But,
uh...
&nbsp
you were right.
I proposed...
&nbsp
because I thought it would save you.
I thought Wally would save you.
&nbsp
I...
I was wrong.
&nbsp
I alone have to save you in
the future, and I'm going to,
&nbsp
but not by changing it.
By embracing it.
&nbsp
Okay, um...
what... what does that mean?
&nbsp
It means that...
I-I think we need
some space for a while.
&nbsp
I'm sorry, but I-I don't...
I don't know how we can...
&nbsp
move forward like this, with...
Um...
&nbsp
okay.
I guess I'll go to my dad's.
&nbsp
No, you stay here. I'll...
I'll stay with Cisco.
&nbsp
Synced and corrected by Aaronnmb
www.addic7ed.com
&nbsp