Previously on "The
Flash" and "Supergirl"...
What just happened to him?
Wally has taken my
place in the Speed Force.
It's okay, we're going home.
What Wally saw, it's gonna
haunt him for a while.
I proposed because I
thought it would save you.
- What does that mean?
- I think we need some space.
I owe you the truth. My name is Mon-El.
I'm the former Prince of Daxam.
I deserve better than being lied to.
I've been looking for you.
Toodles!
♪ I'm singin' in the rain ♪
I told you.
Everything's better in song.
When you speak, it's just words.
But when you sing, you open up your soul
and let who you really
are shine through.
Thanks, Mom.
Hmm. I love you, my beautiful boy.
I love you too.
♪ I'm happy again ♪
♪ I'm laughing at clouds ♪
♪ So dark up above ♪
This...
again?
What, are you gonna spend
the rest of your life
sitting around on the couch? Come on.
You've been doing this for
days. Let's do something.
- Let's go out.
- No, man, I'm sorry.
I... I don't feel like going out.
What is it with you and
musicals these days anyhow?
Everything's better in song.
Listen, dude,
I know you've been going
through a tough time
since Iris broke off the engagement,
- or, I guess...
- What?
... technically, since you
broke off the engagement.
Whoever broke off the engagement,
it doesn't matter, I just...
I don't know, man. I want to help.
Nothing you can really do.
Really? I guess I'm
just gonna have to let...
Mr. Gene Kelly take over
'cause, Lord knows, I can't
do anything about that.
- It's H.R.
- Yeah.
B.A.,
someone's coming through.
Could be Gypsy.
Could be, or it could be...
Supergirl?
Kara...
- What happened to her?
- We don't know,
but whoever did it
has come to this world.
Synced and corrected by Aaronnmb
www.addic7ed.com
Her vitals are low.
How long has she been like this?
A few hours.
Okay, we need to find
whoever did this to Kara
and punch him repeatedly
until he reverses
whatever spell he put on her,
and I get to punch him first.
Who are you exactly?
My name is Mon-El.
I'm... I'm Kara's...
friend.
We're more... more than friend.
We've been kissing a lot.
Oh, she never mentioned
she had a boyfriend.
It's a recent thing, so...
I thought you two broke up.
Shh...
I tell you what, I know
enough not to mention
the break-up between Barry and... uh...
- H.R.
- Sorry.
Look, hey, whatever's going
on between me and Kara,
I cannot leave her like this, okay?
- I need to get her back.
- We will, I promise.
So what happened to her?
An alien prisoner escaped our custody.
He did something to her, put
her in some kind of a coma.
And then he disappeared.
We tracked him here and followed.
Okay, but why would
he come to this Earth?
Well, we believe... for you.
- Me? Why?
- We don't know.
But his last words before he disappeared
were about finding
the fastest man alive.
Okay, well, clearly, we're
talking about a breacher here.
And if there's one thing I can do,
it's find breachers.
So what else can you
tell us about this guy?
Not much.
It's like he just
materialized out of thin air.
You mean like this clown just did?
I'm gonna go.
Wallace...
I understand what you've been through.
Stuck in the Speed Force,
things you saw... I get it.
I also know that sometimes,
the old adage is true.
When you get bucked from the horse,
best thing you can do...
get right back on the damn thing
and ride, Wallace.
Ride!
Hello, Barry Allen.
- How do you...
- Know your name?
I know a lot of things.
And I can do a lot of things too.
Whoa-ho-ho!
Wally West made it here too.
This is exciting.
It's good of you to join
the party, Kid Flash.
I'm happy to have you.
What do you want with Supergirl?
Same thing that I want with both of you.
To teach you all a lesson.
Is that all you got, Kid Flash?
I mean, you look a little scared.
And you're too slow.
Ooh.
Nighty-night, Flash.
- ♪ Moon... ♪
- What the hell?
♪ River ♪
♪ Wider than a mile ♪
♪ I'm crossing... ♪
Kara?
♪ You in style someday ♪
♪ Oh, dream maker ♪
♪ You heart breaker ♪
♪ Wherever you're going ♪
♪ I'm going... ♪
♪ Your way ♪
♪ Two drifters ♪
♪ Off to see the world ♪
♪ There's such a lot of world ♪
♪ To see ♪
♪ We're after ♪
♪ The same... ♪
♪ Rainbow's end ♪
♪ Waiting 'round the bend ♪
♪ My huckleberry friend ♪
♪ Moon river ♪
♪ And me... ♪
What a singer, huh?
- Yeah.
- You know her?
Yeah, I do.
Ladies and gentlemen...
- Barry?
- Hey!
Barry! It's you, thank Rao!
Oh, wait, it's really you, right?
- Yeah, this is me, yeah.
- Good.
What is... where the hell
are we? What's going on?
I was hoping you could tell me
or maybe explain to me why I
just pulled an Audrey Hepburn
and sang in a nightclub.
- Maybe we're dreaming?
- The same dream?
Yeah, that's... What's
the last thing you remember
before you got here?
I was at the D.E.O.
They had just brought
in an alien prisoner.
He got loose, and...
it was really weird.
He had this, um, red...
- ... Pocket handkerchief?
- Yes!
I saw you on my Earth.
You were in a coma.
Your boyfriend brought you to us.
He is not my boyfriend.
He... he's just a boy.
Who is not my friend.
- He's my nothing.
- Okay.
All right, uh, well, whoever he is
said that this guy whammied you,
and then he escaped to my Earth,
he showed up at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I went after him to try to
get him to wake you up...
- And then you got whammied.
- Yeah.
- So where are we?
- I don't know.
I mean, it could be a
parallel dimension, or...
maybe just some elaborate illusion.
We just need to figure a way out.
I guess I could click my
heels together three times.
- Yeah...
- I was kidding.
Okay, all right, well...
Come on. Let's...
You're a really good singer, by the way.
Hey, thanks. My sister says
I put the "Kara" in "karaoke."
There you are!
Merlyn...
- Who?
Malcolm Merlyn. Former head
of the League of Assassins.
The what of the what?
What the hell you talking about, kid?
My name's Cutter Moran, I own this club,
and both of you work for me.
We what now?
I pay you to sing, not
pepper me with questions.
And I hope you got something
better in your songbook
than what you were belting
out up there, blondie.
Hey! Don't call me blondie.
Hey, look, I don't know who you are...
obviously you're someone
who's quick with a knife.
You have to excuse my friend.
He doesn't think before he talks.
Yeah, I had a cousin like that.
I had to slit his throat too.
Oh.
Grady! Get these two set up.
And nothing I've heard before.
I want something original.
Barry, I don't have my powers.
Me neither.
Winn!
Winn, you're here too?
Ah! Who's Winn? The name is Grady.
I tickle the keys around here.
Say, you realize how he got the
nickname "Cutter," don't you?
- No.
- Because he likes to cut people.
You ask me, I think he's all talk.
Cisco... not Cisco. Hello.
I pray that, one day,
you do not find out
how very, very wrong you are, Pablo.
- Now go do your job.
- All right.
You see, Grady doesn't
know this, but one day,
I'm gonna be somebody.
I'm gonna be somebody,
and it's gonna happen
right there on that stage.
You'll see. I just need my one shot.
It's just curiouser and curiouser.
Yeah, yeah, it's like
"The Wizard of Oz."
- Yeah.
- "And you were there,
- "and you were there...."
- Except, it's not really them.
They're all playing characters in a...
... Musical.
Barry, where are we?
I don't know.
Well, you know what they say...
the show must go on!
Ah...
Supergirl, I loved your
rendition of "Moon River,"
such a beautiful song.
You were a little flat in places,
but I'm willing to let it slide
just because you're so cute.
- Hold on. What did you do to us?
- Oh, nothing much.
Just put a little song in your heart.
Put a little...
Why did you bring us here?
I didn't bring you anywhere.
We're inside your heads.
You created this world.
And we got lucky because it
could have been a war movie
or a... a space opera,
but thanks to your love of musicals,
with the countless times you
watched, um, "Wizard of Oz"
- with your adoptive parents...
- How did you know that?
And, you, all those rainy nights
watching Fred Astaire and
Frank Sinatra with Mom.
Well, where else would we be?
All right, all right.
Whoo!
Ooh! Swing and a miss.
I didn't tell you.
I'm not really here.
See, I'm out there in the real world.
Central City's mine for the taking.
- Ah. We're gonna stop you.
- Yeah!
You're welcome to try that.
If you can get out of here.
How do we get out of here?
You're in a movie musical.
So all you have to do
is just follow the...
The Yellow Brick Road?
No, the... the script.
- Oh, yeah.
- Script...
Reach the end of the plot,
and, presto chango, you get to go home.
One little detail,
though, I should mention...
if you die in here, you die out there.
Lovely.
I've reached my limit
with magical creeps.
In the meantime, I
hope you're both ready
to get the rust off
those pipes of yours.
- We're not singing for you!
- No.
Uh, any... anymore, I mean.
Come on, now, maybe just one little
- fun opening number just to...
- Leave your jacket on.
- ... kick things off!
- Where did it go?
♪ Think of your fellow man ♪
- Stop that.
- It's not happening.
♪ Lend him a helping hand ♪
- It's not gonna work.
- We're not singing!
♪ Put a little love in your heart ♪
♪ You see it's getting late ♪
♪ Oh, please don't hesitate ♪
♪ Put a little love in your heart ♪
♪ And the world ♪
- ♪ The world... ♪
- ♪ Will be a better place ♪
- ♪ And the world ♪
- ♪ The world... ♪
♪ Will be a better place ♪
♪ For you ♪
♪ And me ♪
♪ You just wait ♪
♪ And see, yeah ♪
♪ If you want the world to know ♪
♪ We won't let hatred grow ♪
♪ Put a little love in your heart ♪
♪ And the world ♪
♪ Will be a better place ♪
- ♪ For you ♪
- ♪ And me ♪
♪ You just wait and see ♪
♪ You better take a good look around ♪
♪ Oh, if you're looking down ♪
♪ Put a little love in your heart ♪
♪ And the world ♪
♪ Will be a better place ♪
- ♪ All the world ♪
- ♪ For you ♪
- ♪ And me ♪
♪ You just wait and see ♪
♪ Put a little love in your heart ♪
♪ Put a little love, put a little love ♪
♪ Put a little love ♪
♪ Put a little love in your heart ♪
♪ Come on and... ♪
♪ Put a little love... ♪
♪ In your heart... ♪
Where'd he go?
I don't know.
Come on, let's find him.
- He's gone.
- Yup.
- So what do we do now?
- I don't know.
I mean, I guess we just...
we do what he says, right?
We have to figure out what
the plot of the musical is,
- and we follow the story.
- Okay, uh, so...
what do we know so far?
We're singers.
And apparently we work for a gangster.
Yes, who wants us to perform for him.
I mean, honestly, it's
pretty straightforward.
- Right?
- Yeah.
Hello.
Hi! I miss being bulletproof.
- You're coming with us.
- Says who?
Says me.
Barry, are you okay?
Oh, please stop yelling.
I'm not yelling.
Wait, where are we?
I don't know.
All right, well, I'm sure
everybody at S.T.A.R. Labs
is working on getting us out of this.
Yeah, I'm glad they
brought me to your Earth.
Mon-El seems like he
really cares about you.
Mon-El only cares about himself.
He lied to me about who he really is
- for nine months.
- Hmm.
I can't shake it.
I thought it was gonna
be something special
like what you have with Iris.
That is...
off track.
I'm sorry.
I asked her to marry me.
You did? That's great.
Did she not say yes?
Oh, she said yes, but I guess I did it
for the wrong reason,
and, I mean, I love her,
but I was trying to change the future.
Then I pushed her away so
I could focus on saving her,
and it's just a mess now.
Everything's so simple when I'm running.
Or flying.
Shut up!
Both of you.
Stein?
Who... who's Stein?
Right.
- This them?
- Yeah.
Hmm.
Do you know who I am?
Not Joe West, I'm guessing.
Digsy. Digsy Foss.
I run this town.
So you're the mayor?
The mayor may have gotten the vote...
but I got the power.
I got a situation...
that you two are gonna help me with.
- We would love to help you with it.
- Really love to.
My daughter, Millie...
she's missing.
Last she was seen,
she was heading into
Cutter Moran's place.
Have you seen her in there?
- Millie, did you say?
- Yeah. Why?
We haven't seen her. I haven't seen her.
- I haven't seen her.
- Yeah, we...
She's the only thing
that is good and decent...
about my life.
If anything happened to her,
this town will run red with blood.
Starting with yours.
We wouldn't want that, now, right?
So, um, how can we help you?
You two sing for Cutter.
- We sure do.
- Yes, we do.
You could poke around and
see if you can find her.
Mm-hmm.
So are you gonna do this for me?
What do we do?
Follow the script.
- Hey!
- Hey.
- We're gonna find her... sir.
- Mm-hmm.
Good.
Okay.
This is the place.
Apartment 4B.
This is where we can find Iris?
- Millie.
- Millie, right.
Yeah, she's in there, all right.
Now, you two listen to me.
Don't you go telling
anyone I showed you this.
Oh, yeah, we promise.
Word to the wise.
You go digging around in this dirt...
you might not like what you find.
Okay.
Okay, so remember, she
might look like Iris,
but she is not Iris.
I know. This is gonna be weird.
Yeah, tell me about it.
I'm glad we haven't seen
someone that looks like Mon-El.
I'd probably just punch him
in the face for the fun of it.
Oh, my God!
That's her.
Sounds like she's in trouble.
Here, stand back, I'm
gonna kick the door in.
You stand back, I'll kick the door in.
Well, I didn't mean,
like, a gender thing.
- I just wanted to kick it in...
- Barry!
All right, together. All right?
- One, two...
- Three!
What the hell is going on?
All right, you caught us.
We're in love.
Ugh, gross.
Guys, we have a problem.
Well, another problem.
The Speed Force levels in Barry's cells
have been severely depleted,
as has the amount of solar
radiation in Kara's body.
What exactly does that mean?
They're being drained.
The guy who did this to them...
I think he's stealing their powers.
Power up.
We gotta bring him in.
No, not we... me.
I'm the reason Barry got whammied.
We win and we lose as a team.
I'm coming with you.
I'm coming too.
Look, J'onn, uh,
I respect this whole special
agent situation you got going on,
but this problem right
here needs someone with...
green skin and sick-ass cape.
Call me the Martian Manhunter.
I think you'll find that
J'onn's a lot more than...
just a pretty face.
Guys!
Hello.
Also, Barry and Kara's
vitals are all over the place.
Let's go.
All right.
Hello, friends!
Kid Flash.
Oh, I'm so glad you
could join the party.
I'm such a huge fan of your
work, but I have to say,
recently, your work's been a bit off.
You know what I'm talking about?
I think maybe it's just that
you're a little scared...
from what happened in the Speed Force.
Is that it?
No,
and I'm not afraid of anything.
Prove it.
Uh, Cisco, they're headed
towards 4th and Aspen.
Got it.
This way.
All right, J'onn,
how do you feel about
a little one-two combo?
I'm gonna open a breach,
you be ready to hit something
really hard on the B-side.
Hitting hard, I can do.
Wally, get ready to do the
same thing on the ground level.
Copy.
Now!
Ah...
Nighty-night.
Hey, who are you?
Your names, now.
I'm Kara. This is Barry.
We're singers at your dad's nightclub.
Yeah, Millie, your dad
thinks you've been kidnapped.
Well, clearly he's mistaken.
He really wants you to come home.
- Listen, I am never going back there.
- Mm-mm.
Why not? There's no place like home.
Tommy Moran...
is my home.
And besides, if our geezers
ever caught wind of this,
they'd go to war.
It'd be the end of
more than just us, huh?
Yeah, Tommy's right.
Our fathers hate each other.
Our love is forbidden.
This is just like "West Side Story."
I was thinking more
"Fantasticks," but...
Look, the point is...
we ain't telling nobody nothing.
And neither are you, capisce?
"Capisce."
- Can you give us a second?
- Oh, uh...
Sure.
Okay, look, he says we
need to follow the script.
- Uh-huh.
- Right? We're in a musical.
So I think if we convince them
to tell their fathers
that they're in love,
maybe that'll get us out of here.
And back home to being...
single, yay...
At least we'll be single together.
Has saying that ever
made anyone feel better?
Debatable.
Okay, so look...
your fathers aren't perfect, right?
Love isn't perfect.
No, but you can't let
your love for somebody
cause you to be afraid
of what might happen.
You gotta take the good
with the bad, no matter what.
- Right.
- And that includes...
telling your fathers how you
two feel about each other.
All right, you make
a convincing argument.
- You do.
- We'll do it.
We'll tell them about us, right?
Well, we should go now.
- Gee, thanks, kid.
- Okay.
- For you.
- Thank you.
Wow.
Okay, uh...
convincing people in musicals is...
- ... really easy.
- Yeah.
Let's hope getting out
of one is just as easy.
Digsy!
She's back!
- Oh...
- Hmm.
Thank God you're safe.
Oh, of course I'm safe.
Barry and Kara told me that
you sent them to find me.
We were concerned.
Dads, there's no reason to be concerned.
"Dads"?
You got a problem with that?
No.
I love musicals, so...
Okay...
Look, Dads, there's something that...
I need to tell you.
Mm-hmm.
I'm in love!
Who is the, uh... the lucky boy?
Um...
Tommy Moran.
You... you mean Cutter Moran's kid?
Dad, look, we're in love.
- The hell you are.
- He's a hooligan!
His father's a hooligan.
- His mother is...
- Hey!
Not in front of the girl.
And you're not loving that boy.
Have you lost your mind?
She is the daughter of my enemy.
Digsy Foss is a dirty, rotten scoundrel,
and the apple doesn't
fall far from the tree...
Dad, if you just let me explain.
There's nothing to explain, Tommy.
I knew you were keeping
something from me.
I never imagined it
was something like this!
She isn't your little girl anymore.
Well, she isn't.
She's an incredibly brave, strong woman.
One look, and you can see that.
And she wants to be with him.
No matter how scared
she was to tell you,
no matter how dangerous
it is to be with him,
all that matters is, they're together.
And when you find a
love like that, well...
you gotta hold on to it.
No matter who's trying to stop you.
That's clear to me now.
I think you're being a
little tough on your son.
Excuse me?
Well, it's obvious why he
didn't tell you right away.
I mean, look at the way you're reacting.
Maybe if you just listen
and... and hear his reasons
and try to see things
from his point of view...
maybe... maybe you'd understand why
he didn't tell you...
before now.
Baby doll, it's just...
you'll never understand
what it means to be a father.
Millie, my darling, we've
always taken care of you.
We just want you to be happy.
♪ Velvet, I can wish you ♪
♪ For the collar of your coat ♪
♪ And fortune smiling... ♪
♪ All along your way ♪
♪ But more I cannot wish you ♪
♪ Than to wish you find your love ♪
♪ Your own true love ♪
♪ This day ♪
♪ Mansions, I can wish you ♪
♪ Seven footmen, all in red ♪
♪ And calling cards upon a silver tray ♪
♪ But more I cannot wish you ♪
♪ Than to wish you find your love ♪
♪ Your own true love ♪
♪ This day ♪
♪ Standing there ♪
♪ Gazing at you ♪
♪ With the sheep's eye ♪
♪ And a licorice tooth ♪
♪ Music I can wish you ♪
♪ Merry music while you're young ♪
♪ And wisdom when your hair ♪
♪ Has turned to gray ♪
♪ But more I cannot wish you ♪
♪ Than to wish you find your love ♪
♪ Your own true love ♪
♪ This day ♪
♪ With a sheep's eye ♪
♪ And a licorice tooth ♪
♪ And the strong arms ♪
♪ To carry you away ♪
♪ Away ♪
♪ And the strong arms ♪
♪ To carry you... ♪
♪ Away ♪
Thanks for telling us the truth, baby.
I love you both so much.
We love you.
Thanks.
Okay...
So what do you want to do?
Gather up the boys.
- We're going to war.
- I had a feeling.
I appreciate your honesty, son.
- Thanks, Dad.
- Come here.
Get the boys.
We are going to war.
Well, well, well...
if it isn't the two people
I was hoping would visit me the most.
Fix them. Now.
I'm sorry. I can't.
If you ever want to
get out of that cell,
that's exactly what you're gonna do.
You don't get it.
You don't understand, big guy.
That's just not how it works.
My powers don't work that way.
What do you mean? You're
the one who did this to them.
Yes, but...
they are the only ones
that are in control
of what happens to them now,
as are the two of you.
Us? What does that mean?
How much...
do you love him, Iris?
And you, Mon-El, how
much do you love her?
So the question is:
is that strong enough to save them?
You want Kara and Barry back
from the world they're in,
you can go get them yourselves.
You have that power.
How?
Ah, I can't tell you. Sorry,
you gotta figure it out yourself.
Now, if you don't mind,
I'm gonna just chill
in this wonderfully decorated
little cell of yours.
Bye, guys!
Good luck. Love will find a way.
You can do it. Power
of love and all that.
What do we do now? We got...
we got Millie and Tommy
to tell their fathers
that they're in love.
Which, I know we're in
a musical and everything,
but seeing Mon-El in love
with someone else was...
It was hard to watch. I know.
Anyway, I mean, what are we...
supposed to do? What
do you think this...
Music Meister needs us to do now?
Uh...
Ah, there you are!
You two ready?
Ready for...
For rehearsal, you dolt.
Mr. Moran told me that you got
more songs in your repertoire.
- Ah.
- We have to finish the musical.
- Yeah.
- Uh, do you...
do you happen to know anything original?
As a matter of fact,
I've been working on something all day.
Wow.
- Things really are easier in musicals.
- Yeah.
All right.
♪ At times like these ♪
♪ When life is getting me down ♪
♪ And the world seems
like it's gonna end-ship ♪
- Mm-mm?
- ♪ There's at least one power ♪
♪ That we both still have ♪
♪ And that's the power of... ♪
♪ Friendship? ♪
Yeah, that's exactly
what I was gonna say.
Yeah, it's an easy rhyme.
♪ I'm your super friend ♪
♪ Your super friend ♪
♪ I'll be there in the nick of time ♪
♪ If you're ever in a spot ♪
♪ And if you're not there in time ♪
♪ You can just go back in time ♪
♪ And give it another shot ♪
I'm actually not supposed
to do that anymore.
Oh, okay.
Sing!
♪ I'm your super friend ♪
♪ Super friend ♪
♪ When you need a compliment ♪
♪ I can rattle off a dozen ♪
For instance, I have to
say, I'm not impressed...
♪ By your more famous cousin ♪
Thank you! No one ever says that.
Oh, he's all, like, "I'm Superman.
Whoop-di-whoop-di-whoo."
- That's a really good impression.
- Thanks.
♪ I'm your super friend ♪
♪ Super friend ♪
♪ When it comes to buddies,
pal, you're the best ♪
♪ I love you more than
the lightning bolt ♪
♪ I wear on my chest ♪
♪ If you're ever sad... ♪
♪ I'll bring you flowers ♪
♪ And you can list soprano
as one of your powers ♪
- ♪ If you're ever broke ♪
- ♪ I've got the cash ♪
- ♪ On my couch ♪
- ♪ You're welcome to crash ♪
♪ And if you ever need a hand ♪
♪ I'll be there in a flash ♪
- Barry!
- That was funny.
♪ I'm your super... ♪
♪ That has a double meaning ♪
♪ Friend ♪
Hello, my friend.
It will be a cold day in hell
before our daughter
marries any son of yours.
Like he said. A cold, cold day.
You took the words
right out of my mouth.
Come on.
Stop!
Agh!
Barry!
Oh, my God.
Agh!
- What's wrong?
- I think we're losing them.
- Can you stop it?
- Not if I don't know why.
- What are we gonna do?
- Um...
We need to go to
whatever world they're in.
How are we gonna do that?
Look, he said, if we loved them enough
that we could save
them, wherever they are.
Cisco, you can vibe us there.
I don't think it works that way.
You sent me into the Speed Force.
You sent Barry and
Wally into the future.
- You can do this too.
- What is she talking about?
- What's a vibe?
- I'll explain later.
Come on, just... grab
on to my shoulders.
Let's hope this works.
Barry, Barry...
Kara...
Barry!
Kara!
- Oh, no.
- No.
Hey, it's me.
It's Iris, I'm here. Hi.
Stay with me. I'm gonna get you out.
There's no time.
We have to go.
We have to get them out!
Come on, Barry. Barry!
No!
I'm so sorry I lied to you.
I forgive you.
I love you.
No, Barry, Barry, you're gonna be okay.
No.
I love you.
Iris?
Mon-El?
- Hey.
- Hi.
They're back!
Bravo! Round of applause!
Standing O. That was so good!
I loved it. That was a hell of a show.
And you two...
I guess your love really
was strong enough after all.
Beautiful.
Man, how did you get out of the cell?
Cisco, do you really think that cell
is gonna just, like, hold me?
No, I'm sorry... what's going on?
Why did you do this to us?
I did it because I
believe in the good guys.
I told you when we first met.
It was to teach all of you a lesson.
'Cause I see everything,
and I saw two people...
with two broken hearts.
So the lesson was...
Love, Supergirl.
Love is about...
letting yourself be saved.
It's not just about saving other people.
Even if you are superheroes.
Anyway, I'm sorry that I had to,
like, mess with you a little bit.
I was just trying to
get you to play the game,
do the song and dance.
Are you, like, from another...
Earth-multi-verse...
universe, something?
Yeah, you...
you wouldn't even
understand where I come from.
Wait, I'm sorry, that's it?
You're just gonna teach
somebody else a lesson?
Yeah, that's exactly what I'm gonna do.
Oh.
♪ Think of your fellow man ♪
♪ Lend him a helping hand ♪
♪ Put a little love in your heart ♪
Wait, so, let me get this straight.
You got whammied by some guy named...
Music Meister.
Damn, Barry, I'd have paid good money
to see you singing and dancing.
No.
Well, he's holding out on you
because Barry has an amazing voice.
- He does!
- Uh-uh.
I've actually seen him sing.
What? You have?
How have we not made a GIF of that?
Well, technically, I'm not even
the only one here who can sing.
Thank you, B.A.
What? I was talking about Kara.
Wait, shh... oh, you too?
Kara. Of course Kara can sing.
Well, her name is Supergirl.
It's kind of implied, right?
Well, we better be getting going.
I promised Kara's sister we'd
get her back in one piece.
We couldn't have done this without you.
- Thank you.
How are you guys doing?
Yeah, I think we'll be okay.
Although, if you lie to me again,
I will drop a mountain on you.
Wow. You mean figuratively?
- No, I mean, geologically.
- Okay.
What about you guys?
We'll see.
You didn't change anything
when I moved in with Cisco.
I, um, couldn't bring myself to do it.
You know, we've been through
a lot these last three years,
but, um...
getting stuck in a musical?
Music Meister...
said that, you know, it
could've been anything,
that I created that world because...
You were watching them.
Because of us.
My mom used to always say
that musicals have the power
to make everything better.
Did it work?
Um...
♪ Can't say how the days will unfold ♪
♪ Can't change what
the future may hold ♪
♪ But I want you in it ♪
♪ Every hour, every minute ♪
♪ This world can race by... ♪
♪ Far too fast ♪
♪ Hard to see... ♪
♪ While it's all flying past ♪
♪ But it's clear now ♪
♪ When you're standing here now ♪
♪ I am meant to be ♪
♪ Wherever you are next to me ♪
♪ All I want to do ♪
♪ Is come runnin' home to you ♪
♪ Come runnin' home to you ♪
♪ And all my life, I promise to ♪
♪ Keep runnin' home to you ♪
♪ And I could see it ♪
♪ Right from the start,
right from the start ♪
♪ That you would be ♪
♪ Be my light in the
dark, light in the dark ♪
♪ Oh, you gave me... ♪
♪ No other choice ♪
♪ But to love you ♪
♪ All I want to do ♪
♪ Is come runnin' home to you ♪
♪ Come runnin' home to you ♪
♪ And all my life I promise to ♪
♪ Keep runnin' home to you ♪
♪ Keep runnin' home ♪
♪ Home to you ♪
♪ Can't say how the days will unfold ♪
♪ Can't change what
the future may hold ♪
♪ But I want you in it ♪
♪ Every hour, every minute ♪
Iris West,
will you marry me?
Yes.
Synced and corrected by Aaronnmb
www.addic7ed.com