My name is Barry Allen,
&nbsp
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world, I'm an
ordinary forensic scientist,
&nbsp
but secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
&nbsp
I fight crime and find
other meta-humans like me.
&nbsp
In an attempt to stop the
evil speedster Savitar,
&nbsp
I was accidentally
thrust into the future,
&nbsp
and I saw him murder
the woman that I love.
&nbsp
But I won't let that happen.
I'm gonna do everything in my power
&nbsp
to change the future,
and I'm the only one fast
enough to keep her alive.
&nbsp
I am The Flash.
Previously on "The Flash."
&nbsp
I'm free!
- Who are you?
- I am the future Flash.
&nbsp
I can't spend the rest of my life
wondering if I'm gonna
become Killer Frost.
&nbsp
I understand the real reason
that you invited me on this team.
&nbsp
You just want your own
meta-human specialist
&nbsp
to try and find you a cure.
- That's not the only reason.
- I wish I could believe that.
&nbsp
I'm Cisco, by the
way. You must be Gypsy.
&nbsp
- You're into me.
- Even if I was, you couldn't handle me.
&nbsp
I'll marry that woman.
Iris West, will you marry me?
&nbsp
Yes.
Looks like we may
need to find a new job.
&nbsp
Heard Stagg Industries
may be getting bought out.
&nbsp
By who?
Doesn't really matter now, does it?
&nbsp
All I know is we got
millions of dollars of tech...
&nbsp
like whatever that thing is...
that no one's using.
&nbsp
Then surely you gentlemen won't mind
if I abscond with some of it.
&nbsp
This piece in particular.
How did you get in here?
&nbsp
Believe me, that's the least
impressive of my tricks.
&nbsp
Hands up, pal
Do it now, or I'll shoot.
&nbsp
Stop!
How the hell did he do that?
&nbsp
Maybe you can figure out how I did it,
but... I doubt you'll have time.
&nbsp
Synced and corrected by Aaronnmb
www.addic7ed.com
&nbsp
It's just beautiful.
You know what, it matches
the sparkle in your eyes.
&nbsp
Aw, thank you.
Barry, your grandfather had
really good taste in jewelry.
&nbsp
- Mm-hmm.
- Yeah, he did.
&nbsp
Okay, so, break it
down. How did it happen?
&nbsp
Um... we were at the apartment,
and, um,
&nbsp
Barry sang to me.
And then he proposed.
&nbsp
Oh, my God, that's so romantic.
- You sing?
- Not as good as Joe.
&nbsp
Shut up, Barry.
Well, okay, that reminds me,
&nbsp
my sister has four tickets
that she can't use...
&nbsp
- ... to "Hamilton."
- "Hamilton"?
&nbsp
On the house. I thought that maybe
we could make it a double
if you guys were interested?
&nbsp
Uh, yeah, we're interested. When?
First weekend in July.
&nbsp
Um, July.
Y... does that not work for you guys?
&nbsp
Um...
No, that works great.
&nbsp
We'll be there, all of us.
Don't! Don't do this!
&nbsp
Please? I'm begging you! Just...
Barry!
&nbsp
You lose, Barry.
No!
&nbsp
Well, everything's the same.
The future has not changed.
&nbsp
All right. Well, we have two months
to make sure that it does.
&nbsp
Okay, well, we should approach this
the same way we approach
any other problem...
&nbsp
start with what we know.
Problem can't be solved
if it's not understood.
&nbsp
Therein lies the rub. I
feel like we can't understand
&nbsp
any of this until it actually happens.
It's like Savitar's prophecies.
&nbsp
Precisely, and just like
the newspaper headlines.
&nbsp
- Well, all bar one.
- _
&nbsp
It's a crime scene. We gotta go.
- Stagg Industries?
- All right, no.
&nbsp
Hey, Julian, before you go,
there was an envelope delivered for you
&nbsp
from the Central City Opera.
Yes, you'd mentioned that
you'd never gone before, so...
&nbsp
well, I got them for us
a while back, but now...
&nbsp
just go with whoever you'd like.
Huh.
&nbsp
Looks like things between you and Julian
are a little frosty, huh?
&nbsp
It's too soon for the cold puns?
- Yeah.
- Yeah. Thought so.
&nbsp
He still doesn't trust me after I lied
about taking a piece of
the Philosopher's Stone.
&nbsp
You did what you felt you needed to do
to get rid of your powers.
&nbsp
I know that and you know that, but he...
He'll come around. Watch.
&nbsp
I don't know that he will, Cisco.
Hey, Bar. Anything?
&nbsp
Nothing yet.
How the hell did this
thing get filled with water
&nbsp
and those poor dudes
get trapped in here?
&nbsp
Beats me.
There's no water access
in the entire wing.
&nbsp
Instead of sprinklers, every floor uses
a halon gas system that
absorbs all the oxygen
&nbsp
if there's a fire.
What about the security cams?
&nbsp
None of them either.
Apparently, the Stagg geniuses
&nbsp
don't want any of their "secrets"
- to get out.
- Yeah.
&nbsp
Julian, please tell
me you found something.
&nbsp
Nothing yet, Detective.
No fingerprints, no DNA,
&nbsp
just two rather plump looking corpses.
What about the stolen tech?
&nbsp
Nothing. No one's saying a thing.
Everyone is incredibly
tight-lipped about it.
&nbsp
Of course they are. Look,
I'll make some phone calls,
&nbsp
see if I can pry those
lips open, all right?
&nbsp
Okay. I'll keep working on it.
This is the last thing we need
to be dealing with right now.
&nbsp
I feel the same way, but
we can't just do nothing.
&nbsp
Iris ain't gonna let
us get away with that.
&nbsp
I know, Joe, but we're
running out of time.
&nbsp
That's why you and me need
to solve this case fast.
&nbsp
Yeah.
Sometimes... I wish you hadn't
told me what was gonna happen.
&nbsp
Yeah, I know.
Hold on. Hey, what's up?
&nbsp
Looks like we got a robbery in progress
over at Kord Industries.
&nbsp
Great, thanks. Now Kord Industries.
That's two in one day.
&nbsp
That's two in under 12 hours.
Yeah, I'm gonna make
sure it's the last one.
&nbsp
I don't think that's yours, pal.
Flash.
&nbsp
You didn't think I'd want to come meet
the newest resident of Iron Heights?
&nbsp
No, I assumed that you'd show.
I just didn't expect you to be so young,
&nbsp
Barry... Allen.
Now, how do you know who I am?
&nbsp
I'm from the future.
You don't believe me?
Let's see, uh, 2017.
&nbsp
Hmm. How are things going
with your doomed love,
&nbsp
Iris West?
Or your greatest foe, Savitar?
&nbsp
You know Savitar.
I know everything about him, and you.
&nbsp
What the...
Gypsy.
&nbsp
Still seeking revenge, I see.
I'm gonna get it this time.
&nbsp
We'll see.
No!
&nbsp
He calls himself Abra Kadabra.
As in hocus pocus?
&nbsp
He's certainly got a lot of tricks.
Yeah, we think he has
some sort of nanotechnology
&nbsp
built into his body...
allows him to do some
extraordinary feats.
&nbsp
Teleportation, telekinesis, you name it,
and believe me, I have seen it all.
&nbsp
So that card trick he played on Barry,
the water tank at Stagg,
&nbsp
that's all some futuristic
tech that he's masking as magic?
&nbsp
Well, it's Arthur C. Clarke's third law.
"Any sufficiently
advanced technology is...
&nbsp
"... indistinguishable from magic."
Before you showed up, he
said he was from the future.
&nbsp
The future?
He is, 64th Century.
&nbsp
Great, another criminal from the future.
Haven't we had our fill of those guys?
&nbsp
64th Century.
What exactly are you after him for?
&nbsp
He's at the top of the
collectors' most wanted list.
&nbsp
Showed up on my Earth a few years back,
did a string of robberies that ended
&nbsp
with a lot of people losing their lives.
Showed up again a couple weeks ago,
&nbsp
looted some tech companies, came here.
To do the same thing? Why?
&nbsp
He must have needed our
Earth's tech for something.
&nbsp
Well, whatever it is, we can
definitely help you figure it out,
&nbsp
'cause I don't know about you guys,
but ever since last time you were here,
&nbsp
I've been looking forward
to some Gypsy-Vibe action.
&nbsp
- That's way too much.
- Embarrassing.
&nbsp
Yeah, I just want to catch
him so I can bring his ass
&nbsp
back to Earth-19 and put him down.
Don't worry. We can help you do that.
&nbsp
We should check and see if
Julian's gotten anything.
&nbsp
I'll go ask him.
In the meantime, we can figure out
&nbsp
where this guy disappeared off to.
- Lend me a hand?
- Stupid.
&nbsp
I know that look.
What is going on inside
that head of yours?
&nbsp
This guy knew what was going on
with you and me and Savitar.
&nbsp
If he knows something
about Savitar, then...
&nbsp
He might be the key to saving you.
This is the first
real lead we've gotten.
&nbsp
But, guys, what about Gypsy?
I mean, if she gets ahold of him,
&nbsp
she's gonna take him back to Earth-19.
We can figure that out later.
&nbsp
Right now, we just need to find him.
I got nothing.
&nbsp
Why can't I find you?
I told you, this guy is smart.
&nbsp
You can't just vibe Kadabra's location.
Whatever he's doing, it
renders him invisible to us.
&nbsp
Okay, well, if we can't vibe him,
then I guess we'll have to
find him another way, right?
&nbsp
What are you doing?
I'm putting some search parameters
into the S.T.A.R. Labs satellite
&nbsp
to see if anybody vibrates
at a different frequency
&nbsp
than Earth-1 folk.
Wish we had a satellite that
could do that on my Earth.
&nbsp
Wish I had a bunch of this stuff.
Oh. I could hook you up, girl.
&nbsp
How about this,
I spend a few days on Earth-19,
&nbsp
and set you up with
something state-of-the-art.
&nbsp
You know, the only thing is,
I would need a place to crash, so.
&nbsp
- Cisco...
- Gypsy.
&nbsp
That kiss, that wasn't
"I'll see you around."
&nbsp
That was like,
"That needs to happen again, real soon."
&nbsp
Or did I misread that?
I-I-I've been preoccupied.
&nbsp
Is that the only reason?
Great timing!
&nbsp
Looks like David Copperfield's
not too far from us.
&nbsp
He's at one of Mercury
Labs' satellite offices.
&nbsp
- Another tech company?
- The techiest.
&nbsp
Let's grab the speedsters and go.
Man, you just can't
help yourself, can you?
&nbsp
You brought the whole team this time.
- Mm-hmm.
- That wasn't very smart, was it?
&nbsp
Oh, this guy sucks.
I can see why you want to
bring him down so badly.
&nbsp
Do yourself a favor, give it up.
There's nowhere for you to go.
&nbsp
You can't out-trick all of us, Kadabra.
I think I just did.
&nbsp
He's a hologram.
Upon further inspection,
&nbsp
there was some rather
odd particulate residue
&nbsp
found at Stagg Industries.
Yeah, that's the nanotechnology
&nbsp
that Gypsy was talking about.
But what's it made out of?
&nbsp
Not exactly sure.
It's definitely organic,
but it seems to have
&nbsp
some sort of metallic
hydrogen properties.
&nbsp
Frankly, it's...
Beyond your understanding.
&nbsp
You make a move, you'll regret it.
Do you know how many times
I've heard that, Detective?
&nbsp
Told you.
Damn it.
&nbsp
Go, go, go!
Guys, move to the side.
&nbsp
Now... I can get what I came for.
Everybody okay?
&nbsp
Magic or tech, doesn't matter.
You're not getting out of these.
&nbsp
Maybe not.
You let me go, I will tell
you Savitar's greatest secret.
&nbsp
It's the key to defeating
him, the key to stopping him.
&nbsp
- What secret?
- I know who he is.
&nbsp
I know his name.
Hand him over!
&nbsp
Why'd you lock him up?
I'm taking him right back to my Earth.
&nbsp
Okay, but I need to talk to him first.
Fine. Get what you need from him,
&nbsp
but when you're done, he's mine.
You are gonna die for all
the things you've done.
&nbsp
I cannot wait to see
you be put to death.
&nbsp
Uh, I'm gonna talk to her.
Gypsy, darling?
&nbsp
You said you know who Savitar is.
I know everything
about the God of Speed,
&nbsp
hallowed be his name.
Like what?
&nbsp
That he's unstoppable,
that he was the first speedster,
&nbsp
and that you defeat him,
but not until after he takes
what matters the most to you...
&nbsp
Iris West.
Tell us who he is, now!
&nbsp
I don't think so.
It's frustrating, isn't it,
&nbsp
knowing that you're going to die
unless I give The Flash what he wants.
&nbsp
All that power, all that speed,
and yet you're still too slow.
&nbsp
This isn't a game or a trick.
This is about my daughter's life.
&nbsp
And it's my life
if you hand me over to that collector.
&nbsp
It's simple.
Let me out, and I'll
tell you who Savitar is.
&nbsp
Give me to Gypsy, and Iris dies.
The decision lies with you, Barry.
&nbsp
Guys, we can't let Gypsy take him
before we find out who Savitar is.
&nbsp
No, we cannot.
Then what are we supposed to do?
&nbsp
I don't know.
What is it with you and this guy?
&nbsp
It's like you're hell-bent
on taking him back with you.
&nbsp
He killed a lot of people on Earth-19.
He's killed people here too.
&nbsp
No one you know or care about.
Did he take somebody from you?
&nbsp
Hey.
Is that what this is about?
&nbsp
What this is about, Cisco,
is he needs to be brought to justice,
&nbsp
and I am not gonna
let anything or anyone
&nbsp
prevent me from doing that.
You're lucky.
&nbsp
This could've been a lot worse.
I'm fine, really.
&nbsp
It's merely a flesh wound,
as the "Monty Python" boys would say.
&nbsp
Anyway, thanks for patching me up.
Of course.
&nbsp
Listen, I've been trying to find
the right time to say this, and...
&nbsp
now seems to be as good a time as any.
I was so focused on not hurting you...
&nbsp
as Killer Frost...
that I forgot that I could
hurt you as Caitlin Snow,
&nbsp
and for that I'm very sorry.
So I understand...
&nbsp
if you don't trust me anymore, but...
maybe you can find it in
your heart to forgive me?
&nbsp
You're good to go.
Thank you.
&nbsp
We're gonna figure this out, Barry.
A guy like Kadabra,
&nbsp
he should have no say
whether you live or die.
&nbsp
How do you even know that
he's telling the truth?
&nbsp
I mean, he's done nothing
but tricks since he got here.
&nbsp
I mean, maybe... maybe
this is one of them.
&nbsp
It's not, Iris.
So... what, you want to let him go?
&nbsp
I mean, it just feels
like our only move.
&nbsp
He's a murderer.
I know he's a murderer,
&nbsp
but I mean, how many murderers
have we put in prison?
&nbsp
How many bad guys have we taken down?
I mean, don't we deserve one win
&nbsp
after everything that we've done?
Life doesn't keep score, Barry.
&nbsp
You should know that better than anyone.
Look, even if Kadabra hadn't showed up,
&nbsp
we'd still be in the same
place we are right now.
&nbsp
But he did, and if he knows
who Savitar is, he's gonna tell us.
&nbsp
- Barry...
- Iris, he can save your life.
&nbsp
No, you can save my life.
Not him.
&nbsp
Trust me, I want to
find out who Savitar is
&nbsp
just as badly as you do.
But I don't want to let someone
who has caused so much pain
&nbsp
walk free just to save my life.
And you know, deep down,
&nbsp
I don't think you want that either.
I knew you'd come.
&nbsp
'Cause you're the only
person who's willing to do...
&nbsp
anything.
What do you want?
&nbsp
To be set free.
Murdering people, stealing smart tech.
&nbsp
You came here for something.
Told you before, Detective,
&nbsp
it is beyond your understanding.
This is about my daughter's life.
&nbsp
It's as simple as that for me.
You tell me who Savitar is,
&nbsp
and I will let you go.
You don't, you're going with Gypsy.
&nbsp
A leap of faith for us both then.
Open the door.
&nbsp
If you take one step before you tell me,
I will blow you away. Understood?
&nbsp
But you do not know this guy.
Great timing!
&nbsp
What is that?
- No.
- Gypsy!
&nbsp
Give me the name.
The name, now!
&nbsp
Savitar... is...
No! What the hell are you doing?
&nbsp
He was about to tell me who Savitar is!
Damn it!
&nbsp
- Kadabra's on the loose!
- He's somewhere in the building!
&nbsp
And there we are.
Thank you, Doctor Wells.
&nbsp
Joe, he's headed for the elevator!
We had a deal.
&nbsp
Your freedom for Savitar's identity.
I've altered the terms of our agreement.
&nbsp
It appears that you have as well.
Move!
&nbsp
Caitlin! Caitlin, are you all right?
- You all right?
- Yeah.
&nbsp
- Come on.
- I'm okay.
&nbsp
Okay, I'm okay.
Okay, okay, easy.
&nbsp
Easy.
Come on. Gentle, gentle.
&nbsp
Yeah, yeah, yup.
The, um, the... hand
me the X-ray machine,
&nbsp
- grab it for us, would you, please?
- Yup.
&nbsp
Here, here.
Okay, good. remove it.
&nbsp
- How bad is it?
- Uh, it's bad.
&nbsp
It's bad, there's quite a few
pieces of shrapnel inside you,
&nbsp
and they look deep enough
to pierce your kidney
&nbsp
if they're not removed immediately.
Guys, we have to get her to a hospital.
&nbsp
We can't, they're
gonna ID her as a meta.
&nbsp
And not just any meta.
Yeah, one that we have a
file on for attacking CCPD.
&nbsp
Then what are we going to
do? None of us are doctors
&nbsp
and she can't operate on herself.
We do have another option.
&nbsp
What is it?
When Caitlin goes
meta, her metabolic rate
&nbsp
offsets cold tissue destruction.
She can regenerate?
&nbsp
No, we're not gonna
take off my necklace.
&nbsp
I don't need a hospital.
All I need is a mirror
and a steady set of hands.
&nbsp
You were a field medic
in the Royal Army, right?
&nbsp
What? No, I-I-I've never
operated on anyone before.
&nbsp
That's okay, I'll walk you through it.
Caitlin, you're talking
about staying awake
&nbsp
during your own surgery.
I'm putting my life in your hands.
&nbsp
I trust you, Julian.
What the hell were you thinking?
&nbsp
Now is not the time, Gypsy.
You know, you got a really
messed up sense of justice
&nbsp
for a cop?
Watch yourself.
&nbsp
I took two oaths in my life.
One, to uphold the law. The
other, to protect my family.
&nbsp
Guess which one takes priority?
That was my prisoner.
&nbsp
He was my prisoner too,
and you're on my Earth.
&nbsp
He has information that
could save Iris's life,
&nbsp
so I don't give a damn!
It's because of you he's on the loose.
&nbsp
Because of me? No, no, because of you.
You opened that door! You let him out!
&nbsp
That is on you, Detective!
How much of that did you hear?
&nbsp
I heard enough.
This is my friend.
&nbsp
It's the man's daughter.
I mean, wouldn't you do that
for someone you cared about?
&nbsp
I am doing that, you idiot!
Okay, what does that mean?
&nbsp
For who? Who are you talking about?
I used to have a partner.
&nbsp
Like, a "partner" or...
like a partner?
&nbsp
Both.
It was a long time ago, Cisco.
&nbsp
It's not like I'm burning
a candle for the guy,
&nbsp
but he did mean something to me.
It's been three years since
Abra Kadabra shot him dead.
&nbsp
I'm sorry.
I have been searching
for him ever since,
&nbsp
and he finally showed back up.
Ten minutes ago, I
had him dead to rights,
&nbsp
and then your friend messed it all up.
So yes, I do know what it is like
&nbsp
to care about someone so
much that you break the rules.
&nbsp
That's why I have to find
this guy, no matter what,
&nbsp
and when I do, he is
gonna pay for what he did.
&nbsp
No more delays.
- Ready?
- Ready as I'll ever be.
&nbsp
Okay, let's start with the
shrapnel on the surface.
&nbsp
Okey-dokey.
Just let me know if I do
&nbsp
any... thing wrong, okay?
Okay, that's the first bit. Well done.
&nbsp
Okay.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa.
&nbsp
Is there supposed to be this much blood?
It's normal for the shrapnel to cavitate
&nbsp
and displace tissue, but
if I lose too much blood,
&nbsp
I'll start hemorrhaging.
Okay.
&nbsp
Oh, my God.
Okay.
&nbsp
All right, nearly done, nearly
done, hang in there, hang in there.
&nbsp
Okay, well done. Well
done, that's all the pieces
&nbsp
of shrapnel from the surface gone.
Okay, great. Now it's
time for the hard one.
&nbsp
But you're doing great.
- You got this, okay, Julian?
- Yes.
&nbsp
It's wedged between my kidney
and my inferior vena cava,
&nbsp
and it's surrounded by
some major blood vessels.
&nbsp
If you hit them, there's a good chance
- I'll go into shock.
- Shock?
&nbsp
But it's okay. You've got this.
Okay. All right.
&nbsp
Heart rate's increasing.
Okay, I think I've got it.
&nbsp
Great, pull it out.
I can't, Caitlin, it's stuck.
&nbsp
Then turn it.
Guys, it's getting up there.
&nbsp
It might be a tendon in the way.
If it's not a tendon...
&nbsp
Then I will rip this necklace off.
No! I would rather die.
&nbsp
Caitlin, this is going to hurt.
- Ahh.
- Ohh!
&nbsp
Can you please stitch me up,
because I think I need to pass out?
&nbsp
Yes, yes. Of course, of course.
Well done, well done.
&nbsp
She's gonna be all right.
Thank God.
&nbsp
That really was amazing, Julian.
Seriously. Julian Albert, MD.
&nbsp
Hey, I think I know why Abra
Kadabra's been stealing all that tech.
&nbsp
- Why?
- Build a time machine.
&nbsp
He's trying to get back to the future.
Presto.
&nbsp
What is that thing in his hands?
Everything Kadabra's been stealing,
&nbsp
these are the exact
components I used to build
&nbsp
Evil Wells's time sphere two years ago,
but I could never figure out
what he used for a power source.
&nbsp
I think this is it.
So that's what he took
from the time vault,
&nbsp
its power source?
Last thing he needs to
return to the 64th century.
&nbsp
Well, we need to find his ass
before he pulls another
disappearing act.
&nbsp
If Kadabra's plan is
to "Marty McFly" himself
&nbsp
back to the future...
He's gonna have to open
a temporal wormhole first,
&nbsp
- and when he does...
- We can nail him.
&nbsp
Mm-hmm.
No, he's mine.
&nbsp
I look forward to
showing him the same mercy
&nbsp
he showed my partner.
Hey, Gypsy.
&nbsp
You can't go after him alone.
Sure I can.
&nbsp
You want justice for all
those people that he's hurt,
&nbsp
for your partner, right?
Right now we're trying
to prevent someone we love
&nbsp
from getting hurt, but we
can't do that without your help.
&nbsp
I don't trust you guys anymore.
Kadabra's already given
both of us the slip.
&nbsp
He does it again through time,
I don't think we get
this opportunity back.
&nbsp
Only way we catch him is together.
Guys, Abra Kadabra's
heading south on Ninth.
&nbsp
He opened up a wormhole.
What do you say?
&nbsp
We can't let him get past us.
We're not gonna do that.
&nbsp
Catch me if you can.
Where's he at?
&nbsp
He's on State and Main!
We're on it!
&nbsp
You shall not pass!
Ah!
&nbsp
Okay, now he's on Thurlow and Eighth.
- We're gonna lose him.
- No, we're not.
&nbsp
He's on Seventh, and he's moving fast!
You gotta stop this guy.
&nbsp
Time to go home.
Bar, he opened up another wormhole!
&nbsp
Yes! He did it, he got him.
Thank God.
&nbsp
So much for your disappearing act.
No!
&nbsp
By the laws of Earth-19,
I hereby collect you
&nbsp
for the crime of mass murder.
Let her take me.
&nbsp
You'll never find out what I know.
And Iris dies.
&nbsp
You've come to see me off.
I'm really touched.
&nbsp
What are we gonna do here?
You're going with her.
&nbsp
I'm not gonna stop her.
Then you'll never find
out what you want to know.
&nbsp
I have nothing to offer you.
No reprieve.
&nbsp
No escape for what you're facing.
You've done some terrible things.
&nbsp
But you are still a man.
You have a family,
&nbsp
friends, people that you care about.
Somewhere inside of you there must be
&nbsp
a glimmer of light, of hope.
It's that part of you that I'm asking.
&nbsp
I'm begging.
Help me save her.
&nbsp
Flash.
Begging.
&nbsp
See, here it is.
In the future, you and I
have been enemies for years.
&nbsp
Oh, there have been others, of course.
There was Thawne, Zoom, DeVoe,
&nbsp
but none of them hurt you like Savitar.
He truly broke you.
&nbsp
I have to be honest.
I was always a little bit jealous.
&nbsp
But now, it's like I
get to kill her too.
&nbsp
If you'll excuse me, I
have my execution to attend.
&nbsp
Where does this leave us?
I don't know.
&nbsp
Cisco, I...
Hey.
&nbsp
I'm still here.
Yeah.
&nbsp
Wasn't gonna let you go that easy.
Kadabra?
&nbsp
He's gone.
He's gone for good, apparently.
&nbsp
Sorry.
My palm's are sweaty.
&nbsp
It's quite all right.
Honestly, my stitch work may leave
&nbsp
quite a lot to be desired, so.
It's okay.
&nbsp
I was never much of a
two-piece bathing suit
&nbsp
kind of gal anyway.
I cannot believe what you did, Caitlin.
&nbsp
I mean, staying awake
during your own surgery,
&nbsp
that's one thing, but
talking my clumsy hands
&nbsp
through it, that's quite the other.
You are immensely brave.
&nbsp
You fought through the pain
like I've never seen anyone before.
&nbsp
You did all the hard work.
Hardly.
&nbsp
You going soft on me, Julian?
Yes.
&nbsp
Absolutely.
I'm so terribly sorry.
&nbsp
That's most clumsy of me.
Some bedside manner you got there.
&nbsp
I'm working on it.
Just rest.
&nbsp
Here you go.
Thank you.
&nbsp
Easy.
Sorry.
&nbsp
I should've been stronger.
You think you should've shot Kadabra?
&nbsp
Dad, I think you showed true
strength by letting him go.
&nbsp
I try to be strong for you guys,
for you and Wally and Barry.
&nbsp
Dad, you have been,
and it makes me stronger too.
&nbsp
When you were a baby, I was...
I was terrified
&nbsp
that you might die in
the middle of the night.
&nbsp
I just didn't sleep.
I would just...
&nbsp
sit in your room...
and watch you sleep.
&nbsp
I put my hand on your chest,
just to make sure you were breathing,
&nbsp
and then I...
I would just sit there
there, praying that...
&nbsp
you'd just keep breathing.
That's how I feel right now.
&nbsp
I don't know what I can do to save you.
I know how to save her.
&nbsp
What?
I know how to save her.
&nbsp
Kadabra, Savitar, Thawne.
You know, they're always
one step ahead of us...
&nbsp
for one reason...
they know what's gonna happen.
&nbsp
So every move we make,
every trap we try and set,
&nbsp
it's all just history to them.
They're armed with the future.
&nbsp
Well, not anymore.
What does that mean?
&nbsp
If the answers that we need
to stop Savitar and save you
&nbsp
are in the future, then
that's where I need to go.
&nbsp
I'm gonna run to the future.
- Mmm.
- No more strawberry.
&nbsp
What do you mean, there's
no more strawberry?
&nbsp
I just bought some, like, a week ago.
Yeah, well, I may have eaten some,
&nbsp
slash... all.
- Cisco.
- Do you want me to go out
&nbsp
and get you more strawberry Jell-O?
I will get you more.
&nbsp
No, it's fine,
but next time I operate on you,
you're getting bupkes, mister.
&nbsp
Mm, next time you operate on me,
maybe you can...
&nbsp
fix my broken heart.
I'm sorry it didn't work
out with you and Gypsy.
&nbsp
If two metas from
two different universes
&nbsp
with the same vibrational powers
can't make it work, then...
&nbsp
what hope is there?
There you guys are.
&nbsp
I've been looking all over for...
what are you doing in bed?
&nbsp
- It's a long story, H.R.
- I have a long story.
&nbsp
Yeah, how about you tell
us where you've been?
&nbsp
Her name is Rhonda, and
she's into new positions.
&nbsp
- We had the...
- Okay. Oh, my God.
&nbsp
Stop talking. You
gotta let somebody know
&nbsp
next time you decide to
go on a two-day love romp.
&nbsp
Who was worried about me?
He was. I'm touched.
&nbsp
You'll be touched in
the face with a hammer
&nbsp
the next time you pull
something like that.
&nbsp
Guys, stop it.
Don't make me laugh, or
I'll bust my stitches.
&nbsp
Is that lime Jell-O?
It's all you, H.R.
&nbsp
Are you serious?
Ah, ha ha ha ha!
&nbsp
I... love the lime.
I love the lime!
&nbsp
You were really worried
about him, weren't you?
&nbsp
Just promise me that
you'll never ever tell him.
&nbsp
Cross my heart and hope to...
Caitlin?
&nbsp
Hey!
Caitlin? Caitlin? Somebody help!
&nbsp
W-w-what happened? What happened?
I don't know, she just started seizing.
&nbsp
Hold her down, hold her down.
Hey, H.R., grab her legs. Hold her down!
&nbsp
What... what's happening?
She's not breathing.
&nbsp
We have to get an
ambulance in here right now.
&nbsp
H.R., grab the crash cart.
Cisco, grab the oxygen.
&nbsp
Wheel it over here!
Slow and steady, over her mouth.
&nbsp
Okay, good.
Come on, slow and steady, that's it.
&nbsp
- That's it.
- What's happening?
&nbsp
She may have threw a
blood clot, I don't know.
&nbsp
- Julian!
- Charge the paddles!
&nbsp
- Okay...
- Give me the paddles!
&nbsp
- Charging, you're good.
- Okay, give me the...
&nbsp
Give it here. Clear.
All the way, turn it up to the top!
&nbsp
- All the way up!
- Okay, you're ready.
&nbsp
- Clear.
- Clear, clear, clear.
&nbsp
Char... go.
Keep going.
&nbsp
Come on, Caitlin, come on!
Keep going, just keep going.
&nbsp
Uh, here, take this.
Here we go, she's coming back.
&nbsp
She's coming back.
Yes, she is.
&nbsp
Come on. Here she comes.
Come on! Don't stop.
&nbsp
Please.
Please don't stop.
&nbsp
She's gone.
Stop! That's not what she wanted!
&nbsp
I don't care!
I'm not gonna sit here
and watch her die, okay?
&nbsp
Okay?
It's all right, mate, it's okay.
&nbsp
It's okay.
Caitlin?
&nbsp
Huh.
Caitlin.
&nbsp
Synced and corrected by Aaronnmb
www.addic7ed.com
&nbsp