Previously on "The Flash"...
&nbsp
Despite your feeble efforts
to change the future,
&nbsp
you can't.
Everything's the same.
The future has not changed.
&nbsp
If the answers that
we need to stop Savitar
&nbsp
and save you are in the future,
then that's where I need to go.
&nbsp
Caitlin. Somebody help!
She's gone.
&nbsp
- Stop. That's not what she want...
- I don't care.
&nbsp
2024.
According to the future
article in the time vault,
&nbsp
I'm still in Central City.
There's no mention of Savitar.
&nbsp
I'd probably trapped him
in the Speed Force by then.
&nbsp
That's the time I need to travel to.
2024.
&nbsp
If I trapped him, I must've
figured out who he was, right?
&nbsp
Iris?
What are you doing?
&nbsp
Um, sorry, I was just thinking.
About what?
&nbsp
Same as you. The future.
And my dad.
&nbsp
What about him?
I need you to make me a promise, okay?
&nbsp
If things don't go our way...
- if Savitar kills me...
- He won't.
&nbsp
- if he does...
- He won't.
&nbsp
if he does, Barry,
promise me that you
will be there for my dad.
&nbsp
Don't let him push Cecile away.
Don't let him spiral out of control.
&nbsp
Make sure that him and Wally...
Stop, okay? We're not
gonna talk about this.
&nbsp
You're not gonna die.
I told you, I have a plan.
&nbsp
Barry, I need you to promise me, okay?
I'm serious.
&nbsp
Promise me...
that you're gonna make
sure that my dad is okay.
&nbsp
I promise.
S.T.A.R. Labs.
&nbsp
We, uh... we should go.
- You think?
- Yeah.
&nbsp
Oh, probably should've
made that out of carbyne.
&nbsp
Rookie mistake.
You do not want to hurt me, Caitlin.
&nbsp
You know, you probably should've spent
a little more time finding
a cure for what ails me.
&nbsp
I care about you, Caitlin.
Show me.
&nbsp
- Julian!
- Come on, come on!
&nbsp
Oh, boys...
where are you?
&nbsp
- What are you doing?
- Buying us some time.
&nbsp
♪ Swing low ♪
♪ Sweet chariot ♪
&nbsp
♪ Coming for to carry me home ♪
Shh!
&nbsp
Hey, dummies.
My palm scan still works.
&nbsp
I don't want to have to do this.
I know you don't.
&nbsp
But I do.
Stop!
&nbsp
Aw, come to save the day?
Good, now I can get rid of you, too.
&nbsp
Caitlin, you can fight this.
I know. But I don't want to.
&nbsp
Anything?
I searched the whole
building. She's gone.
&nbsp
Synced and corrected by Aaronnmb
www.addic7ed.com
&nbsp
Hey, Julian, how about
next time you decide
&nbsp
to release my friend's inner ice demon,
you do it sometime in July?
&nbsp
I know you're not being serious.
I was trying to save her life, Cisco.
&nbsp
Iris was right. Even H.R. was right.
- We should've taken her to a hospital.
- Brilliant idea, yes.
&nbsp
Expose her meta-human
status to the world.
&nbsp
That would've been great, wouldn't it?
Hey, guess what? She's
gonna do that anyway.
&nbsp
Guys!
Arguing isn't gonna help us find her.
&nbsp
Maybe we should just take five.
Yeah.
&nbsp
Yeah, probably right.
I'm gonna do this.
&nbsp
I'm gonna run to the future.
Wait, what?
&nbsp
- You want to do this now?
- Mm-hmm.
&nbsp
Barry, Caitlin is still out there.
I know, but we're running out of time.
&nbsp
If I can find my future self,
I can find out who Savitar is...
&nbsp
how we defeated him.
Besides, I can run to the future
&nbsp
and be back like I never even left.
All right, what do you need us to do?
&nbsp
Just keep everybody else
away from the pipeline.
&nbsp
Barry, last time you went to
the future, it was by accident.
&nbsp
How are you supposed to get there now?
With your help.
&nbsp
You sure this is gonna work?
I calculated the force
from the explosion
&nbsp
that propelled me to
the future last time.
&nbsp
At your fastest speed, you can
create three times that force.
&nbsp
It's more than enough to
get me where I want to go.
&nbsp
All right.
Just run as fast as you can.
&nbsp
I'll try to keep up.
Good luck, man.
&nbsp
2024.
I made it.
&nbsp
What is it, throwback Thursday?
Haven't seen that outfit
in a while, have we, honey?
&nbsp
Haven't seen him in a while, either.
Guess we get to...
&nbsp
relive the past.
Kick his ass like we used to.
&nbsp
You've been gone for a while, so...
let me remind you...
&nbsp
this is my town.
Our town, baby.
&nbsp
That's right.
Our town. My mistake.
&nbsp
Not anymore.
What was that?
&nbsp
Did you say something, Flash?
You're in for a world of pain.
&nbsp
You better run, Flash.
Next time, we're gonna
put him in something
&nbsp
he can't get out of.
I knew it was you.
&nbsp
Cisco.
Barry Allen.
&nbsp
How did you know I was here?
I had a feeling.
&nbsp
A feeling I have not
felt in a long time.
&nbsp
And so I hacked into
the security cameras,
&nbsp
and I saw you fighting
Top and Mirror Master
&nbsp
in your O.G. suit
with the white emblem...
&nbsp
2017 edition, of course.
Being here...
&nbsp
this is no accident, is it?
I came here for some information.
&nbsp
And then I'm... I'm going back.
What's the information?
&nbsp
Oh.
Time travel.
&nbsp
Yeah, yeah.
You say something, you might
mess something up, right?
&nbsp
Don't worry, my powers
of deduction have improved
&nbsp
since 2017.
2017...
&nbsp
Savitar.
I need to talk to me.
&nbsp
Do you know where he is?
So H.R. stopped the
S.T.A.R. Labs museum?
&nbsp
H.R. went on to other things.
What about Caitlin?
&nbsp
Once she became Killer Frost,
she never stepped in
this building again.
&nbsp
So I shut down this place?
My friend, you shut everything down.
&nbsp
S.T.A.R. Labs, Team Flash...
you didn't want us around.
&nbsp
- So you pushed us away.
- Why?
&nbsp
You said it was because
of what we represented.
&nbsp
That we were a constant
reminder to you of what you lost.
&nbsp
But you weren't the only
one who lost something.
&nbsp
Are you sure he's here?
He never leaves this place.
&nbsp
Well, what are you doing?
Aren't you gonna come with me?
&nbsp
Man, I shouldn't even be here.
Look, just get what you need,
&nbsp
but don't leave without saying good-bye.
All right.
&nbsp
Why are you here?
I need your help.
&nbsp
You're from before she dies, aren't you?
You can't save her.
&nbsp
Yes, I can. And I'm going to.
No, you can't. Go home.
&nbsp
Just tell me who's in the suit.
All right? That's all I need.
&nbsp
You tell me that, we'll
be able to track him down.
&nbsp
We'll learn his weakness.
We'll stop him before he even tries.
&nbsp
Just tell me who Savitar is.
I can't.
&nbsp
What are you... why?
Because I don't know the answer.
&nbsp
Sorry you ran all this way for nothing.
You want some advice, go home.
&nbsp
Spend as much time with Iris as you can.
Because pretty soon...
&nbsp
you'll never see her again.
You sure you can't stay?
&nbsp
I'm not gonna get what I came for.
- Look, we could really use you.
- Cisco...
&nbsp
I mean it. Mirror Master and Top
are not the only villains in the city.
&nbsp
Barry, we don't have a Flash here.
- Not anymore, okay?
- Well, Cisco...
&nbsp
I can't.
I'm sorry.
&nbsp
Look, it's good to see you in any time.
All right?
&nbsp
Yeah.
You too.
&nbsp
You okay? What's wrong?
I don't know.
&nbsp
A portal won't open. I can't get back.
I can't get back to the past.
&nbsp
- What's happening, Cisco?
- I don't know.
&nbsp
Why can't I open a portal?
Wasn't I running fast enough?
&nbsp
Well, I'm not sure. We don't
have the telemetry for the suit.
&nbsp
Okay, well... we got to figure
this out. I have to get back.
&nbsp
We're gonna get you
back home. Not to worry.
&nbsp
Look, good news... good
news, you can always go back
&nbsp
to the exact time in which you left,
no matter how long you stay here.
&nbsp
Yeah.
Maybe it was Scudder or Dillon.
&nbsp
They seemed a little different
than the last time I fought them.
&nbsp
I mean, look around you.
Everything's different.
&nbsp
Except you.
Maybe this means we can
get the team back together.
&nbsp
- Why haven't you done that?
- I've tried.
&nbsp
Believe me, I've tried.
But you see, Caitlin's not the
only thing Killer Frost took.
&nbsp
Aah!
No hands, no vibes.
&nbsp
And without my powers...
without you...
&nbsp
What... what about everybody else?
Julian, Wally?
&nbsp
Joe?
It's been a while, gentlemen.
&nbsp
Especially you, Flash.
More than you know.
&nbsp
Allen?
Yeah, it's me, Julian.
&nbsp
From the past.
2017.
&nbsp
The year it all began.
I'll assume you're here for
some answers then, are you?
&nbsp
Something like that.
Well, you brought him
to the wrong place, mate.
&nbsp
I just wanted him to understand.
Julian...
&nbsp
can I see her?
I tried to find her
something more humane, but...
&nbsp
this is the best I could do.
Caitlin?
&nbsp
It's me.
Barry Allen...
&nbsp
- I'm...
- From the past.
&nbsp
I can tell.
There's no hate in your eyes...
&nbsp
yet.
So to what do we owe the
pleasure of your visit?
&nbsp
Come to see how things
turn out for Team Flash?
&nbsp
I wanted to see what
happened to my friend.
&nbsp
I am not your friend, Flash.
I'm so sorry I did this to you.
&nbsp
I should have saved you.
I'm glad that you did this to me.
&nbsp
Caitlin wasn't.
I failed her.
&nbsp
But I won't when I go
back. I'm gonna find you.
&nbsp
And I'm gonna help you.
You're no match for the God of Speed.
&nbsp
Oh.
You didn't tell him, did you?
&nbsp
Well, secrets always were
our thing, weren't they?
&nbsp
When I became Killer Frost,
Savitar appeared to me
and showed me the way.
&nbsp
We made one hell of a team.
Why would you help him?
&nbsp
Because he gave me the
thing that you couldn't:
&nbsp
the cure to my illness,
embracing who I really am.
&nbsp
You know who he is.
Who is he?
&nbsp
Tell me who he is.
I'll never tell.
&nbsp
You are gonna be so
surprised when you find out.
&nbsp
You know, I think your protégé
went toe-to-toe with Savitar.
&nbsp
Maybe he can help you out.
I need to see Wally.
&nbsp
Hello?
Hi, um, I'm looking for Wally West?
&nbsp
I recognize you from Joe's photos.
- You're Barry, right?
- Bar... Barry, yeah.
&nbsp
- Uh, this is Cisco.
- Hey, Beth.
&nbsp
Hey, Cisco. I'm Beth.
Come on in.
&nbsp
I'll be upstairs if you need anything.
And stay as long as you like.
&nbsp
We don't get very many visitors.
Hey, buddy.
&nbsp
I brought a friend.
Wally?
&nbsp
Hey, it's me.
It's Barry.
&nbsp
Hey.
Can you hear me?
&nbsp
What happened to him?
Iris died, and that...
&nbsp
sent him into this rage.
And, uh, he went after
Savitar by himself one night.
&nbsp
Joe found him the next day
with a shattered spine.
&nbsp
No one knows what he saw that night,
but whatever it was...
&nbsp
he's been like this ever since.
I'm so sorry.
&nbsp
Listen, Barry, you and Joe...
Where is he?
&nbsp
Well, he's not here,
which means there's only
one other place he can be.
&nbsp
Hey, Joe.
Why are you here, Barry?
&nbsp
I just wanted to see you.
Just wanted to see how you were doing.
&nbsp
Now you want to know?
After all this time, now?
&nbsp
Uh, Joe, um...
I'm doing my best.
&nbsp
What happened to us?
My daughter's life was taken.
&nbsp
My son's.
And then you left me, Barry.
&nbsp
The last piece of who I was...
left.
&nbsp
Turned his back and ran away.
I wasn't there for you?
&nbsp
Why start now?
I'm gonna need you to leave, Barry.
&nbsp
Please.
You promised.
&nbsp
You promised her that you
would be there for Joe.
&nbsp
You don't understand.
I don't understand what?
That you abandoned him?
&nbsp
That you abandoned
him and everybody else?
&nbsp
- You made a promise!
- That I couldn't keep!
&nbsp
Not after everything I lost.
I was just as broken as Joe was!
&nbsp
- I don't care.
- You will!
&nbsp
You will.
You want answers, Barry?
&nbsp
How's this?
You will go back.
&nbsp
You will do everything that
you can think of to save her.
&nbsp
You're even gonna create
time remnants of yourself,
&nbsp
but he's gonna kill them all, mostly.
And then on the night of May 23rd,
&nbsp
Iris West will die in your arms.
- No.
- And in that moment
&nbsp
that she takes her last breath,
it'll feel like an eternity.
&nbsp
And it will break you.
She's the love of your life, Barry.
&nbsp
She was the love of my life.
There'll be nothing left
at all but stopping Savitar.
&nbsp
So no, you won't be there for Joe.
You won't be there when
Caitlin becomes Killer Frost.
&nbsp
When Savitar destroys Wally.
You won't be there for any of them.
&nbsp
But then one day, you'll stop him.
You'll lock him in the
Speed Force forever.
&nbsp
But at that point...
he already won.
&nbsp
Because everything that
you've ever loved is gone.
&nbsp
Including you.
Go home, Barry.
&nbsp
There's nothing for you here.
Cisco.
&nbsp
Did you figure out
what's keeping me here?
&nbsp
I need to go home.
What?
&nbsp
You're leaving? Now?
He's... he's...
&nbsp
he's not gonna help
me, man. He's broken.
&nbsp
And if Caitlin's working with Savitar,
I need to get back. I need...
&nbsp
before she's lost to us forever.
What about everyone else?
&nbsp
- Don't you want to help them?
- I can't help them.
&nbsp
I should've known.
No matter what I do,
&nbsp
you're gonna abandon
the ones close to you.
&nbsp
Cisco, it's not like that.
I just... I can't stay here.
&nbsp
But you want me to.
To get the team back together.
&nbsp
It wasn't Mirror Master or
Top that did something to me.
&nbsp
It was you, wasn't it?
Yeah.
&nbsp
What did you do?
You know the resonance field
you create when you run?
&nbsp
This disrupts that.
I might not be able to use my powers,
&nbsp
but I still know something about tech.
Why would you keep me here?
&nbsp
'Cause I miss my friend.
Cis...
&nbsp
If you want to go,
I'm not gonna stop you.
&nbsp
I don't know why I expected you
to be the same Barry Allen I remember.
&nbsp
That guy still had
some fight left in him.
&nbsp
You were right.
This isn't the future that I wanted.
&nbsp
I can't go back knowing
I let it stay like this.
&nbsp
You want to help me try to fix it?
I thought you'd never ask.
&nbsp
Well, let's get the team back together.
Even H.R.
&nbsp
Continuing with the H.R. Romance Series,
"The Streak vs. Mr. Reflecto."
&nbsp
"Just as the villain was about
to go in for the fatal blow,
&nbsp
"Florence felt strong
hands around her waist...
&nbsp
"lifting her like she was a feather."
Sss.
&nbsp
"She was whisked away,
"the wind blowing through her hair,
&nbsp
"as her mystery hero
finally set Florence down
&nbsp
"on a mountaintop."
I love that part.
&nbsp
I was in the zone.
- Uh-huh.
- _
&nbsp
_
"She, uh..."
&nbsp
"Florence was, um..."
And the mountaintop.
Back to the mountaintop.
&nbsp
"I have to have you..."
Okay, you know what?
&nbsp
We, uh, we should threesome...
do someone... something else.
&nbsp
I think...
Julian, H.R.
&nbsp
What the hell is going on?
I would like to know
the very same thing.
&nbsp
I was about to check one
of the most important boxes
&nbsp
a man can check in his life.
And who... who brought us here?
&nbsp
I brought you all here.
Oh, it's you again.
&nbsp
Bar?
You... you look...
&nbsp
Young?
He's from the past, Detective.
&nbsp
2017, to be precise.
I knew something felt
weird in the cemetery.
&nbsp
You hadn't visited Iris in years.
Yeah, that's what I've heard.
&nbsp
Cisco told me, or showed me,
that you all haven't been
a team in a long time.
&nbsp
And I know that I'm the reason for that.
Iris's death shouldn't have
driven me away from you all.
&nbsp
I mean... I mean, it
should've driven me closer.
&nbsp
This isn't what she would want.
But I'm here now to tell you that...
&nbsp
no matter what happens in the past,
I will not abandon you.
&nbsp
- What's that?
- It's a meta-human app.
&nbsp
Mirror Master and Top are at it again.
Let's get 'em.
&nbsp
Us, as in Team Flash?
Guys, we have a chance to put some hope
&nbsp
back into our lives.
And I...
&nbsp
I really need it right now.
I think you do, too.
&nbsp
So what do you say?
You ready for Team Flash to
take down the bad guys again?
&nbsp
Team Flash.
On three.
&nbsp
One, two...
Thank you.
&nbsp
Baby, you're a rock star.
Just like to shine for my man.
&nbsp
Yeah, I don't know.
It looks a little tacky from over here.
&nbsp
But I am old-fashioned.
We told you to stay away, Flash.
&nbsp
Yeah, well, I try not
to listen to criminals.
&nbsp
Or stupid people.
You guys hearing me all right?
&nbsp
Yeah, Bar, I can hear
you loud and clear.
&nbsp
Man, it's good to be back.
Well, that's... what the...?
&nbsp
Wh... what are you doing?
- Just... I had a...
- What are you looking for?
&nbsp
I just... I found... oh.
Now I'm ready.
&nbsp
Should've done as you were told.
Flash, it's two versus one.
&nbsp
Odds aren't in your favor.
I'll take that bet.
&nbsp
Give him a little ride.
With pleasure.
&nbsp
Okay, that's new.
He can't move.
&nbsp
They're using their
powers at the same time.
&nbsp
- What are we gonna do?
- Can't he phase or something?
&nbsp
- That doesn't work on these guys.
- Well, what will?
&nbsp
Give me that thing in your hands.
The other thing.
&nbsp
That makes more sense.
I can rejigger this to
mimic the resonance fields
&nbsp
from Scudder's portals,
make it so Barry can
manipulate the mirrors.
&nbsp
- But what about Top?
- This will also restore
&nbsp
whatever rarefaction
effect she's causing.
&nbsp
Yes, that's good. That's brilliant.
But without opening another breach,
&nbsp
how can we possibly get
it into his hands in time?
&nbsp
I'll take it to him.
I saw what you were
doing from the time vault.
&nbsp
You need help.
Give it to me.
&nbsp
Go.
Thought it was about
time I did something.
&nbsp
Cisco made it.
Now her powers won't affect us.
&nbsp
We can go anywhere he does.
The odds seem pretty even now, huh?
&nbsp
Go.
You mind?
&nbsp
Be my guest.
Gotcha.
&nbsp
In a bizarre twist, and
the first sighting in years,
&nbsp
eyewitnesses claim not one
but two Scarlet Speedsters
&nbsp
were responsible for
apprehending Sam Scudder
&nbsp
and Rosalind Dillon,
AKA Mirror Master and Top.
&nbsp
I'm sure I speak for all
residents of Central City
&nbsp
when I say this:
Flash, if you're watching,
&nbsp
it's good to see you again.
Ladies and gentlemen,
&nbsp
- Team Flash, back at it again.
- Yeah!
&nbsp
Yeah.
Yeah, I think this was
a good first step, Cisco,
&nbsp
but yeah, we have a ways to go.
Especially me.
&nbsp
I heard what you said.
And you were right.
&nbsp
Iris wouldn't have wanted this.
She would have wanted
us to stay a family.
&nbsp
I broke that promise to her...
to all of you.
&nbsp
You made me realize, even
though Savitar's gone,
&nbsp
I've... I've still been letting him win.
I was wrong to do that.
&nbsp
If you're all willing to...
try to be a family again...
&nbsp
I think I can, too.
I don't know which...
&nbsp
which one of you to hug first.
Him.
&nbsp
Well, I don't know
about you, but... I'm in.
&nbsp
H.R.? What do you say?
Yeah, I got a lot of coffee
tastings and some book readings...
&nbsp
lot of women left to
charm, but I... I'm in.
&nbsp
You know what?
Free coffees for the
gang at H.R. Jitters.
&nbsp
Maybe 10% off. On me, let's go.
Thank you.
&nbsp
- Thank you.
- I know how hard this must be.
&nbsp
No, you don't. Not yet.
That's the problem.
&nbsp
And neither of us can
change what's gonna happen.
&nbsp
I wish I could help
you, believe me, I do.
&nbsp
But you trapped Savitar
in the Speed Force.
&nbsp
Just tell me how you did it.
I had help.
&nbsp
- Help from who?
- A physicist.
&nbsp
Her name's Tracy Brand.
She made the Speed Force trap for me.
&nbsp
Why wouldn't you tell me this before?
Because she didn't
figure out the technology
&nbsp
until four years ago.
Four years after Iris died.
&nbsp
Mm-hmm.
Hang on.
&nbsp
I don't know where she is.
And I don't understand
anything that's on here.
&nbsp
But that's got all
her information on it.
&nbsp
Maybe when you go back,
you can find her and...
&nbsp
I don't know, she can
decipher it for you.
&nbsp
I hope so.
But if not...
&nbsp
just make some good memories with Iris.
Hold onto 'em as tight as you can.
&nbsp
Good luck.
Weird, it feels just
like "Back to the Future."
&nbsp
Which would make me Doc Brown.
You're not gonna give me
some kind of letter, are you?
&nbsp
No, I will not.
I'm gonna do something to fix that.
&nbsp
You're too good of a
superhero to lose those powers.
&nbsp
Hey.
You know you're my BFF, right?
&nbsp
You too, man.
Whoa. Wait, did you...
&nbsp
Did it not work? Do
we need to try again?
&nbsp
No, I went. I'm back.
You're back?
&nbsp
I went to the future.
How far?
&nbsp
Eight years from now.
I needed to talk to myself
and find out who Savitar was.
&nbsp
Did you?
No.
&nbsp
But I got a lead. Something we can use.
Something that'll help us stop him.
&nbsp
Barry, did you learn
anything about Caitlin?
&nbsp
She aligned herself with Savitar.
Why would she do that?
&nbsp
I don't know.
But we need to find her,
before she's lost to us forever.
&nbsp
All right, I'll get to CCPD.
Yeah, and we'll, uh...
&nbsp
we'll dive in here, right?
Right, team? Team Flash.
&nbsp
On three.
Okay. Okay.
&nbsp
Joe.
I love you.
&nbsp
I love you, too.
- You okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
&nbsp
I just...
I just want you to know
that no matter what happens,
&nbsp
I'm always gonna be there for you.
I know that, Bar.
&nbsp
I know.
Thank you.
&nbsp
What was that about?
I'm just keeping that
promise I made to you.
&nbsp
I've been waiting for you.
Fear not, my child.
&nbsp
I have come only to
offer you what you desire.
&nbsp
And what's that?
Salvation.
&nbsp
You want to cure me?
Turn me back into Caitlin Snow?
&nbsp
No.
I want to make sure Caitlin...
&nbsp
never returns.
Why should I trust you?
&nbsp
What do you need me to do?
Synced and corrected by Aaronnmb
www.addic7ed.com
&nbsp