When I was a child,
my brother would tell me
a bedtime story...
about the man
who murdered our father.
Who stabbed him in the back
and cut his throat.
Who sat down on the Iron Throne
and watched
as his blood poured onto the floor.
He told me other stories as well.
About all the things
we would do to that man...
once we took back the Seven Kingdoms
and had him in our grasp.
Your sister pledged
to send her army north.
She did.
I don't see an army.
I see one man, with one hand.
It appears your sister lied to me.
She lied to me as well.
She never had any intention
of sending her army north.
She has Euron Greyjoy's fleet
and 20,000 fresh troops.
The Golden Company from Essos,
bought and paid for.
Even if we defeat the dead,
she'll have more than enough
to destroy the survivors.
"We"?
I promised to fight for the living.
I intend to keep that promise.
- Your Grace, I know my brother...
- Like you knew your sister?
He came here alone, knowing full well
how he'd be received.
Why would he do that
if he weren't telling the truth?
Perhaps he trusts his little brother
to defend him,
right up to the moment
he slits my throat.
You're right.
We can't trust him.
He attacked my father in the streets.
He tried to destroy my house and
my family, the same as he did yours.
Do you want me to apologize?
I won't.
We were at war.
Everything I did,
I did for my house and my family.
I'd do it all again.
The things we do for love.
So why have you abandoned
your house and family now?
Because this goes
beyond loyalty.
This is about survival.
You don't know me well,
Your Grace.
But I know Ser Jaime.
He is a man of honour.
I was his captor once.
But when we were both taken prisoner
and the men holding us
tried to force themselves on me,
Ser Jaime defended me.
And lost his hand because of it.
Without him, my lady,
you would not be alive.
He armed me, armoured me,
and sent me to find you
and bring you home
because he'd sworn an oath
to your mother.
You vouch for him?
I do.
You would fight beside him?
I would.
I trust you with my life.
If you trust him with yours,
we should let him stay.
What does the Warden of the North
say about it?
We need every man we can get.
Very well.
Episode 2 - A Knight Of The Seven Kingdoms.
Thank you, Your Grace.
Either you knew Cersei was lying
and let me believe otherwise,
or you didn't know at all.
Which makes you
either a traitor or a fool.
- I was a fool.
- Not for the first time.
Cersei still sits on the throne.
If you can't help me take it back,
I'll find another Hand who can.
I suspect one of you will be
wearing this before it's all over.
Coal's coming through.
Don't you have something better to do?
You make my weapon yet?
Just as soon as I'm done
making a few thousand of these.
You should make mine first.
And make sure it's stronger than this.
It's strong enough.
It's going to be safer
down in the crypt, you know.
Are you going to be
down in the crypt?
- No, but...
- But you're a fighter.
I've done my share.
You've fought them?
I did. Some of them.
How many?
A few.
That was enough.
What are they like?
Bad.
Really bad.
"Really bad"?
Even a smith's apprentice
can do better than "really bad."
What do they look like?
What do they smell like?
How do they move?
How hard are they to kill?
Look, I know you want to fight.
And I know you're not scared
of rapers or murderers or...
This is different. This is...
This is death.
You want to know what they're like?
Death. That's what they're like.
I know Death.
He's got many faces.
I look forward to seeing this one.
- My weapon?
- I'll get right on it.
I'm sorry for what I did to you.
You weren't sorry then.
You were protecting your family.
I'm not that person anymore.
You still would be, if you hadn't
pushed me out of that window.
And I would still be Brandon Stark.
- You're not?
- No.
I'm something else now.
You're not angry at me.
I'm not angry at anyone.
Why didn't you tell them?
You won't be able to help us
in this fight
if I let them murder you first.
What about afterwards?
How do you know
there is an afterwards?
Next up.
Put a marker in the ground!
Bring it up to the wall!
Up onto the wall. All right.
- All right.
Well, here we are.
Yes, here we are.
Together again.
And the masses rejoice.
How do they feel
about their new queen?
She's your new queen too.
They remember what happened
the last time Targaryens
brought dragons north.
They'll come around
once they see Daenerys is different.
And she is? Different?
She is.
- You're sure about her?
- I am.
She didn't seem sure about you.
It's hard to blame her.
I made a mistake
common to clever people.
- I underestimated my opponents.
- Hmm.
Cersei told me the pregnancy
had changed her.
A chance for you both to start again.
And I believed her.
Was she lying about the baby too?
No, that part is real.
She's always been good
at using the truth to tell lies.
I wouldn't be too hard on yourself.
She's fooled me more than anybody.
What?
She never fooled you.
You always knew
exactly what she was,
and you loved her anyway.
So...
we're going to die at Winterfell.
Not the death I would've chosen.
I always pictured myself
dying in my own bed,
the age of 80,
with a belly full of wine and
- a girl's mouth around my
- A girl's mouth around your
At least Cersei
won't get to murder me.
I'm sure I'll feel some satisfaction
denying her that pleasure
while I'm being ripped apart
by dead men.
Maybe after I'm dead...
I'll march down to King's Landing
and rip her apart.
You will see
the Army of the Dead.
Good.
Yes, aim.
Don't rush.
Come forward.
- Come on.
- Ser Jaime.
Lady Brienne.
He's come a long way.
- He's all right.
- One more time. Come on.
- Still has a lot to learn.
- I'm sure you'll teach him.
Better, better.
I've been told you're commanding
the left flank.
I am.
It's, uh... It's good ground.
It is.
The rise, it should give us
some advantage.
If we can keep a tight formation,
we might be able to beat them back.
Yes, I think you're right.
- What are you doing?
- What?
- I think you know.
- I truly don't.
We have never had a conversation
last this long
without you insulting me. Not once.
You want me to insult you?
- No!
- Good.
I came to Winterfell because...
I'm not the fighter I used to be.
But I'd be honoured to serve under
your command, if you'll have me.
I better get back.
Forgive me, Khaleesi.
Have you done something to offend me?
Many things.
Long ago and long forgiven.
But you did forgive,
despite my failures.
When I heard you'd named Tyrion
your Hand,
it broke my heart.
When I named him Hand, I didn't
know if I'd ever see you again.
You made the right choice.
I wasn't under the impression
you liked him very much.
I didn't.
His mouth hardly stopped moving
between Volantis and Meereen.
It was all I could do
not to throw him in the sea.
But the mind behind all those words...
He's made mistakes.
Serious mistakes.
As have we all.
He owns his
and learns from them.
You're advising me to forgive
the man who stole your position?
I am.
And one other suggestion,
if you'll allow me.
The moment we can get the last
infantryman out onto the field,
we should shut the gates.
Keep them open
for as long as you can.
There are still people coming in
from the countryside.
Lady Sansa, I was hoping
we could speak alone.
I thought you and I were
on the verge of agreement before.
About Ser Jaime.
Brienne has been loyal to me, always.
I trust her more than anyone.
I wish I could have
that kind of faith in my advisors.
Tyrion is a good man.
He was never anything but decent
towards me.
I didn't ask him to be my Hand
simply because he was good.
I asked him to be my Hand
because he was good, and intelligent
and ruthless when he had to be.
He never should have trusted Cersei.
You never should have either.
I thought he knew his sister.
Families are complicated.
Ours certainly have been.
A sad thing to have in common.
We have other things in common.
We've both known what it means
to lead people
who aren't inclined
to accept a woman's rule.
And we've both done a good job
of it, from what I can tell.
And yet, I can't help but feel
we're at odds with one another.
Why is that?
Your brother.
He loves you, you know that.
That bothers you?
Men do stupid things for women.
They're easily manipulated.
All my life, I've known one goal:
the Iron Throne.
Taking it back from the people
who destroyed my family,
and almost destroyed yours.
My war was against them.
Until I met Jon.
Now I'm here, half a world away,
fighting Jon's war alongside him.
Tell me, who manipulated whom?
I should have thanked you
the moment you arrived.
That was a mistake.
I'm here because
I love your brother...
and I trust him...
and I know he's true to his word.
He's only the second man in my life
I can say that about.
Who was the first?
Someone taller.
And what happens afterwards?
We defeat the dead,
we destroy Cersei.
What happens then?
I take the Iron Throne.
What about the North?
It was taken from us,
and we took it back.
And we said we'd never bow
to anyone else again.
What about the North?
Apologies, my lady.
Your Grace...
What is it?
My queen.
Your sister?
She only has a few ships,
and she couldn't sail them here.
So she's sailing
to the Iron Islands instead,
to take them back in your name.
But why aren't you with her?
I want to fight for Winterfell,
Lady Sansa...
if you'll have me.
My lord, we're not soldiers.
You are now.
Look, I made it through
most of my years
without ever getting near a fight,
but then I survived
the Battle of the Bastards.
Right outside these walls.
If I can live through that,
you can live through this.
They'll outfit you with weapons
at the forge.
Right that way.
Thank you.
When the time comes,
you'll be down in the crypts.
They're the safest place to be.
Through that archway
right over there.
Thank you.
Hey, hey, who's next, lads?
Thank you, sir.
Which way should I go?
Which way do you want to go?
All the children will be going below
when the time comes.
But both me brothers were soldiers.
I want to fight too.
That's good to hear.
I'm going to be in the crypt
with my son,
and I'd feel a lot better
with you down there to protect us.
I'm sure a lot of people would.
All right.
I'll defend the crypt, then.
Riders coming in!
- My little crow.
- I thought we'd lost you.
Almost.
Put them in the stables.
How did you find each other?
We met up at the Last Hearth.
The dead got there first.
The Umbers?
Fighting for the Night King now.
We had to travel around them
to get here.
Whoever's not here now
is with them.
How long do we have?
Before the sun comes up tomorrow.
The big woman still here?
They're coming.
Next.
We have dragonglass
and Valyrian steel.
But there are
too many of them.
Far too many.
Our enemy doesn't tire.
Doesn't stop.
Doesn't feel.
We can't beat them
in a straight fight.
So, what can we do?
The Night King made them all.
They follow his command.
If he falls...
Getting to him
may be our best chance.
If that's true,
he'll never expose himself.
Yes, he will.
He'll come for me.
He's tried before, many times,
with many Three-Eyed Ravens.
Why?
What does he want?
An endless night.
He wants to erase this world,
and I am its memory.
Well, that's what death is, isn't it?
Forgetting.
Being forgotten.
If we forget where we've been
and what we've done,
we're not men anymore.
Just animals.
Your memories don't come from books.
Your stories aren't just stories.
If I wanted to erase the world of men,
I'd start with you.
- How will he find you?
- His mark is on me.
He always knows where I am.
We'll put you in the crypt,
where it's safest.
No.
We need to lure him into the open
before his army destroys us all.
I'll wait for him in the Godswood.
You want us to use you as bait?
We're not leaving you alone
out there.
He won't be. I'll stay with him.
With the Ironborn.
I took this castle from you.
Let me defend you now.
We'll hold off the rest of them
for as long as we can.
When the time comes,
Ser Davos and I will be on the walls,
to give you the signal
to light the trench.
Ser Davos is perfectly capable
of waving a torch on his own.
You'll be in the crypt.
Your Grace, I have fought before,
I can do it again.
Alongside the men and women
risking their lives.
There are thousands of them
and only one of you.
You can't fight as well as they can,
but you can think
better than any of them.
You're here because of your mind.
If we survive, I'll need it.
The dragons should give us
an edge in the field.
If they're in the field,
they're not protecting Bran.
We need to be near him.
Not too near,
or the Night King won't come.
But close enough to pursue him
when he does.
Dragon fire will stop him?
I don't know.
No one's ever tried.
We're all going to die.
But at least we die together.
Let's get some rest.
Your Grace.
Do you need help?
No.
You've had a strange journey.
Stranger than most.
I'd like to hear about it.
It's a long story.
If only we were trapped
in a castle...
in the middle of winter,
with nowhere to go.
Hello.
When Daenerys takes her throne...
there will be no place for us here.
I am loyal to my queen.
I will fight for her
until her enemies are defeated,
but when the war is over
and she has won...
do you want to grow old
in this place?
Is there nothing else you want to do,
nothing else you want to see?
Naath.
I'd like to see the beaches again.
Then I will take you there.
My people are peaceful.
We cannot protect ourselves.
My people are not peaceful.
We will protect you.
Have you told her yet?
No.
Mmm-hmm.
Being careful.
Biding your time.
Waiting for the perfect...
And now our watch begins.
Gilly? Little Sam?
They'll be safe down in the crypt.
If you want to join them...
To protect them.
Everyone seems to forget that I was
the first man to kill a White Walker.
- I've killed Thenns.
- Thenn.
I've saved Gilly more than once.
I stole a considerable number
of books from the Citadel library,
survived the Fist of the First Men.
You need me out there.
Well, if that's what it's come to,
we really are
Well, calling you,
wouldn't be strictly accurate.
Samwell Tarly.
Slayer of White Walkers.
Lover of Ladies.
As if we needed any more signs
the world was ending.
Think back to where we started.
Us, Grenn, Pyp.
Now it's just us three.
Last man left, burn the rest of us.
I wish Father were here.
I would love to see
the look on his face
when he realizes his two sons are
about to die defending Winterfell.
That would be something to see.
I remember the first time
we were here,
the first time I saw this hall.
- Mmm.
- You were a golden lion.
I was a drunken whoremonger.
It was all so simple.
It wasn't so simple.
I was sleeping with my sister
and you had one friend in the world
who was sleeping with his sister.
I was speaking in relative terms.
- Do you miss it?
- Of course I miss it.
Well, my golden-lion days are done,
but mongering
is still an option for you.
It's not.
Things would be easier if it were.
The perils of self-betterment.
Oh!
My lady.
Oh, we didn't mean to interrupt.
We were just looking for
somewhere warm to...
To contemplate your imminent death.
You've come to the right place.
You want some of this piss?
It's not bad.
- It's not good either.
- Thank you, my lord.
I don't think that's wise.
The battle might start at any moment.
Half cup.
- And you?
- No, thank you.
I should try and get some sleep.
You really think any of us
are going to sleep tonight?
Join us.
All right.
Just a bit.
Well, what do we have here?
Ser Davos, join us.
No, none for me, thanks.
Came here for this.
I figured I could wait to die
freezing my balls off out there
or wait to die nice and warm in here.
It could be our last night
in this world, you know.
Yes, well, I'm glad you're here.
Here fighting with us.
Glad you survived Eastwatch.
Would you like a drink?
Brought my own.
They call you "King Killer."
I'm sure someone does.
They call me "Giantsbane."
Want to know why?
I killed a giant when I was 10.
Then I climbed right into bed
with his wife.
When she woke up,
you know what she did?
Suckled me at her teat
for three months.
Thought I was her baby.
That's how I got so strong.
Giant's milk.
Mmm.
Maybe I will have that drink.
You never used to shut up. Now you're
just sitting there like a mute.
Guess I've changed.
What are you doing up here?
What's it look like?
No, I mean,
what are you doing up here?
You joined the Brotherhood.
You went beyond the Wall with Jon.
You're here now. Why?
When was the last time
you fought for anyone but yourself?
I fought for you, didn't I?
Oh.
May as well be at a bloody wedding.
My lady.
It's good to see you again.
I'm sorry we parted the way we did.
Was he on your list?
For a little while.
That's all right.
The Lord of Light
has brought us together all the same.
This is his moment.
- When light...
- Thoros isn't here anymore,
so I hope you're not
about to give a sermon.
Because if you are,
the Lord of Light's gonna wonder
why he brought you back 19 times
just to watch you die when
I chuck you over this wall.
Where are you going?
I'm not spending my final hours
with you two miserable old shits.
Hmm.
That for me?
This'll work.
Last time you saw me,
you wanted me to come to Winterfell.
Mmm. Took the long road, but...
What did the Red Woman want with you?
She wanted my blood
for some kind of spell.
Why your blood?
I'm Robert Baratheon's bastard.
I didn't know until she told me.
She tied me up, stripped me down,
put leeches all over me.
Was that your first time?
No, yeah, I've never had leeches
put all over my
Your first time with a woman.
What?
I... I didn't... I wasn't with her.
Were you with other girls before that
in King's Landing?
Or after?
You don't remember?
- Yes, I was.
- One?
Two?
- Twenty?
- Well, I didn't keep count.
Yes, you did.
Three.
We're probably going to die soon.
I want to know what it's like
before that happens.
Arya, I...
I'm not the Red Woman.
Take your own bloody pants off.
It's strange, isn't it?
Almost everyone here's fought
the Starks
at one time or another.
And here we are in their castle,
ready to defend it.
Together.
At least we'll die with honour.
I think we might live.
I... I do.
How many battles
have we survived between us?
Ser Davos Seaworth.
Survivor of both the Blackwater
and the Battle of the Bastards.
All without a shred
of combat ability.
Mmm.
Ser Jaime Lannister,
fabled hero of the Siege of Pyke.
Fabled loser
of the Battle of Whispering Wood.
Hear, hear!
Ser Brienne of Tarth.
Defeated the Hound in...
Pardon me, Lady Brienne.
She's not a ser?
You're not a knight?
Women can't be knights.
- Why not?
- Tradition.
Tradition.
I don't even want to be a knight.
I'm no king.
But if I were,
I'd knight you 10 times over.
You don't need a king.
Any knight can make another knight.
I'll prove it.
Kneel, Lady Brienne.
Do you want to be
a knight or not?
Kneel.
In the name of the Warrior,
I charge you to be brave.
In the name of the Father,
I charge you to be just.
In the name of the Mother,
I charge you to defend the innocent.
Arise, Brienne of Tarth...
a knight of the Seven Kingdoms.
Ser Brienne of Tarth!
Knight of the Seven Kingdoms!
We have all we need
to win this war.
I have trained my men,
women and children.
I have fought before.
I can fight again.
Please, listen to me.
You're the future of our house.
I don't need you
to remind me of that.
You'll be safer in the crypt.
These things we're fighting...
I will not hide underground.
I pledged to fight for the North,
and I will fight.
I'm meant to relieve you.
You got it?
Yeah, I got it.
Oh, I'm sorry, I didn't mean to...
It's all right.
We're done here.
I wish you good fortune, cousin.
Thank you, my lady.
- My lady.
What have you got there?
It's called Heartsbane.
It's my family sword.
You still have a family.
Yes. And I'd love
to defend them with it.
But I can't really hold it upright.
Your father,
he taught me how to be a man.
How to do what's right.
This is right.
It's Valyrian steel.
I'd be honoured if you'd take it.
I'll wield it in his memory...
to guard the realms of men.
I'll see you when it's through.
I hope we win.
- We'd better get some rest.
- No, let's stay a bit longer.
We're out of wine.
How about a song?
One of you must know one.
- Ser Davos?
- You'll pray for a quick death.
Ser Brienne?
- Mmm-hmm.
- Hmm.
High in the halls
Of the kings who are gone
Jenny would dance with her ghosts
The ones she had lost
And the ones she had found
And the ones
Who had loved her the most
The ones who'd been gone
For so very long
She couldn't remember their names
They spun her around
On the damp old stones
Spun away all her sorrow and pain
And she never wanted to leave
Never wanted to leave
Who's that?
Lyanna Stark.
My brother Rhaegar...
everyone told me
he was decent and kind.
He liked to sing.
Gave money to poor children.
And he raped her.
He didn't.
He loved her.
They were married in secret.
After Rhaegar fell on the Trident,
she had a son.
Robert would have murdered the baby
if he ever found out,
and Lyanna knew it.
So the last thing she did...
as she bled to death
on her birthing bed
was give the boy to her brother...
Ned Stark...
to raise as his bastard.
My name...
my real name...
is Aegon Targaryen.
- That's impossible.
- I wish it were.
Who told you this?
Bran.
- He saw it.
- He saw it?
And Samwell confirmed it.
He read about their marriage
at the Citadel
without even knowing what it meant.
A secret no one in the world knew...
except your brother
and your best friend.
Doesn't seem strange to you?
It's true, Dany.
I know it is.
If it were true,
it would make you the last male heir
of House Targaryen.
You'd have a claim to the Iron Throne.
Form up!
Get yourselves back!
High in the halls
Of the kings who are gone
Jenny would dance with her ghosts
The ones she had lost
And the ones she had found
And the ones
Who had loved her the most
The ones who'd been gone
For so very long
She couldn't remember their names
They spun her around
On the damp old stones
Spun away all her sorrow and pain
And she never wanted to leave
Never wanted to leave