Your singing wakes the world.
Your colors adorn the sky.
You are the gift of God.
O', dear birds!
Greetings.
We have come from
Excel Engineering College.
The robotics research students.
We have an appointment
to meet Dr. Vaseegaran.
Please, come in.
Excuse me. You are...
I'm Dr. Vaseegaran's assistant.
Oh. Your name?
Nila.
- Beautiful!
Thanks.
Nila, blue...
- What?
You know, both the sky
and the water are blue.
So?
- Should I fly away or drown?
Can I have your number?
11423879.
Look what he's...
Stop licking your tongue
as if she's a piece of meat.
Hi!
Hello.
- Hello, sir.
Hello, sir.
- Hi, sir.
Please sit down.
Doctor, we are the students
of mechatronics.
Professor Mitra told us that
you've built a new humanoid robot.
Can we have a look at it?
Sure.
This is the robot I've built.
Project Nila.
Nice, Intelligent, Lovely Assistant.
Humanoid X12 2018 Model.
Quantum core millenia.
X12 5D Extreme Processor.
Unlimited cloud memory
at one terahertz speed.
Built-in simulated Amygdala.
This is Nila's MPU.
Memory and Power Unit.
It works just like a human heart.
Synthetic skin.
MPU... MPU...
- Ultra...
Should you fly away or drown?
Whoa!
What about the phone number?
- My IMEI number.
So, is this one also like Chitti?
- No.
It's a domestic purpose robot built
adhering to Asimov's Law.
Being a secretary, a friend,
or a caretaker,
it will serve people
in every way possible.
Does it have feelings, too?
- Of course.
Pre-programmed, customizable,
controlled feelings.
Will Chitti ever return, Doctor?
Every invention of science
was initially considered dangerous.
In the past, people
fiercely opposed it.
But in times of necessity,
they accepted them.
One day, people of this city
will need Chitti. Dot!
Hey, Nikita...
- Go to hell!
Flew away, then drowned!
Nikita, listen to me...
I was flirting with her
out of scientific curiosity.
It was obvious that
she was a robot.
'Shut up, liar!'
My Barbie!
My Snow White Princess!
'Hey, joker! Hang up!'
#GodSwear.
I will gift you an Apple Watch
for your birthday... Hey!
'Unknown calling'
Sushma, Moksha has got
a new collection today.
Be back after lunch. Okay?
My flight has delayed.
Inform the clients.
I'll be there by...
After coming from office,
I sit and talk with my family.
We spend quality time, you know...
Hey, idiot!
Harith, give me the phone.
I have to make an important call.
Give me the phone.
What the... Here you go.
I haven't done anything!
If I can get 20 this month...
Make rice, lentils and potatoes
for dinner...
Grandpa?
Manu, I am telling you,
this is our Principal's conspiracy.
Hello, where are you?
Will you come to the terrace...
Mom!
What's wrong?
The project manager and that
'Papaya' girl has a special deal.
He promoted her and sent her
on-site... Hey, my phone!
He went to call the technician,
still no sign of him coming.
Tomorrow is "Mahavir Jayanti".
All shops will be closed.
Buy all the items by tonight.
It supports 4G, Wi-Fi, Bluetooth
and also has dual SIM capacity.
I came to see girls,
but there are only boys here.
Danger, girlfriend calling.
Hi, Sana.
'Wow, sir. You managed
to answer my call today!'
Sorry, Sana.
- 'I called you so many times!'
'Why did you receive this call?
You are quite busy, right?'
'For your sake,
I've come 10,000 kilometers,'
'studying like a lunatic.'
'And under the pretext of a project,
you are flirting with Nila?'
She's just a toy, Sana.
- 'Toy?'
'But she's a doll, too.'
- Come on, honey.
'112 missed calls.'
What if I give 112 kisses
for the 112 missed calls?
'Forget 112,
just give one kiss properly.'
Mmm... Huh?
Flying kiss?
Sir, my phone is missing!
Where to file a complaint?
That is why there is this long queue!
Go and stand behind.
Cell phones flew away?
How is this possible?
Where did they go?
Who is behind this?
Is it a single person
or a whole gang?
I am scared.
This is a sign of
the world's destruction.
The hole in the sky
has turned into a black hole.
All our cell phones
are going up there.
What are you saying? Is there
a drainage system up there?
I work in the share market.
Without the cell phone, I'm gone.
Life seems meaningless
without WhatsApp and selfies.
I took my phone with me
when going to the bathroom.
Now I don't even feel any pressure.
He is in Kuwait now. Our relation
is maintained by the cell phone.
I saved my Mom's number.
Where will I get
her landline number now?
My bank account, ATM pin,
password, all are saved in it.
What should I do?
It has photos and videos of me
with my girlfriend.
What if someone puts them
on the Internet?
Excuse me, is there a separate
section for iPhones?
Yes, there is one beside
the mental hospital.
Go there.
Sir, it's a very special phone.
You want me to take this
as a complaint? Back off!
I tied my cell phone
to my wedding necklace.
That's too gone.
It was of pure gold.
No nagging of wife, no mobile bills
to pay, just relax.
Sir, someone has given a curse.
Let's start worshipping
to bring the phones back.
What nonsense!
The commissioner has called me.
Okay, sir, I'll look into it.
Thank you.
Sir, the Telecom Minister
is on the line.
Sir, even the Chief Minister
lost his phone.
Yes sir, your PA is right
in front of me. I'll see.
Sir, the Minister's phone...
Sir, it had diamonds
on its back.
0.25 caret, sir.
There were 526 stones.
Sir, it costed two crores.
Please, find it at any cost.
Understood.
Sir, he's the BSNL Chief
Technical Officer, Ramsubramaniam.
Please.
Did you find anything
via SIM card tracking?
Sir, not only BSNL,
even other networks are unable
to track their SIM cards.
All the cell phones are switched off.
All cell phones in the city
have gone missing.
How did all of them
get switched off?
How is it even possible?
'Greetings. Breaking News.'
'Cell phones fly and vanish.
People are going crazy.'
'Police department left helpless.'
'Specialists attend a meeting
with the Chief Secretary.'
So Doc, I think you know
the situation.
What is this?
What is this phenomenon?
This is strange.
I have studied all reports
from NASA and Interpol.
Such a thing has never been
recorded anywhere before.
Giving a scientific explanation
to it is impossible right now.
We can see it very clearly.
This is a terrorist attack.
They are planning something big.
This is our defense system, sir.
When something beyond understanding
takes place, we blame terrorists or God.
Could this be an alien invasion?
No, sir. I've read reports from ISRO.
No such alien movements or activities
have been detected in space.
An international company working
in this field may have a hand.
I mean, they want to destroy
our cell phone technology
and replace it with something new.
This is a public display.
As far as I know, there is
no technology in the world
that can make all cell phones
in the city fly away like birds.
Maybe... Someone here
once built a nonsense robot?
A crank scientist like him must be
doing this in the name of novelty.
Who is he?
He is the son of Bohra,
the former AIRD director,
Dhinendra Bohra.
Brilliant scientist.
He too is a director of AIRD.
This is a visualization of
the combined data
of INSAT 3D weather satellite
and GSAT-16 communication satellite
from the day the cell phones
disappeared.
These tiny dots are our cell phones.
After coming a particular distance,
they suddenly disappear altogether.
The cell phones did not cross
the troposphere,
which means they are within
10 kilometers from sea level.
They haven't crossed a radius
of 200 kilometers from Chennai.
All the cell phones are
within these boundaries.
We know of only four forces.
Gravity, electromagnetic, strong nuclear
and weak nuclear.
None of these can attract
only cell phones.
I believe, this can be explained
scientifically.
Dot.
All phones broke the glass
and flew away. - Really?
When will the container lorry arrive?
'It has crossed Nagari.'
You scoundrels! You haven't crossed
the Andhra borders yet?
Hello! I've already made an announcement
of sales here.
There isn't a single cell phone
in the city.
The queue to buy cell phones
is as long as that of the devotees
seen in front of Tirupatti temple.
'I know, sir. It will arrive
before 4 AM.'
I was promised a delivery
by this evening.
'Welcome To Tamil Nadu'
Brother, what is this sound
coming from behind?
Nowadays, songs sound like this.
Brother?
Brother, someone is banging the
container with an hammer from inside.
What are you saying?
There are only cell phones inside!
Call me when the container arrives.
Sure, sir.
Will police protection be here
tomorrow?
I have paid the money, sir.
They'll be here tomorrow morning.
- Okay.
But sir, what if the new cell phones
too fly away like this?
Then understand we are in
for a nightmare.
Not only you and me,
all of us.
Hail Lord Hanuman!
Please protect me.
Hey, what is this sound?
'Sir, the container has arrived.'
Who is this speaking?
'This is Mohan, sir. You told me
to call when the container arrives.'
'It has arrived.'
Where is it?
- 'In your house, sir.'
Sir, please give us more details.
- Please, move back and give way.
Hello, sir.
- Commissioner Rajendranath called me.
Please come in.
There are no traces of any human
presence in Jayanth Kumar's murder.
But he's a wholesaler of cell phones.
Maybe that's our clue.
His family is out of town.
He was alone at home.
We didn't find anything
about any domestic help.
There isn't a single fingerprint
or footprint.
He exploded into pieces.
But no traces of explosives either.
A sale of mobile phones was
to be delivered to his showroom.
The container lorry met
with an accident last night.
All cell phones disappeared
from inside.
We are clueless, sir.
Someone is having problem
with cell phones.
This contains silicon, enamel
and polycarbonate dust
from a lot of cell phones.
They were manufactured by different
brands on different dates.
What if I say Jayanth Kumar
was murdered by cell phones?
Cell phones murdered him?
What are you saying, sir?
So, what were the cell phones
doing here?
Where they came from
and where they went,
that's what I need to find out.
Dot.
'Wow, sir! What a miracle!
You managed to call me today!'
Sana, it's a long story, this is
the only cell phone in the city.
To find out where all the cell phones
are going, I've fixed a tracker in it.
'So I am the lab-rat of your experiment?'
It's not about that.
That day, the phone flew out
of my hand when giving the kiss.
So I thought I'd do it today.
'You remembered it three days later?
Why?'
'What happened to your landline?
Couldn't you use that to call me?'
The landline was busy, Sana.
'Don't lie. Just admit
you forgot my number.'
'Out of sight, out of mind!'
'Nila is everything for you now, right?'
Hey, she's just like a laptop.
"Oh, I'm a laptop!"
'Now she's singing you a song?'
Shut up!
- 'Shut up?'
Now I'm telling you the truth,
and you're telling me to shut up?
Sana, this phone may fly away anytime.
Kai Po Che!
Hey! No more films for you.
Nila, activate EMR.
'Activating EMR'
What are they doing?
Are they trying to locate
a bomb or something?
You search that side.
- Okay, boss.
Thanks, Nila.
- Why thank a laptop?
I was supposed to submit this
by 7 o'clock.
Sir, the Minister is already
discussing this issue.
Sir, Onicell owner Manoj Lulla
has come.
Oh, dear. He will create
a problem.
Greetings, sir. Come.
Is he inside?
- Yes, sir. Come, sir.
2G!
Okay, you find it out. Oh!
Come, sit.
Drop the formality.
What are you doing?
Is there a government or not?
Look, Mr. Lulla.
Just as God is, so are we.
If you believe we exist, we do.
If you don't, we don't.
But you are everywhere
while collecting money.
There isn't a single
cell phone tower of mine.
It has uprooted all of them.
Destroyed the microwave emitters.
This isn't only your problem.
All towers and microwave emitters
in the city have been destroyed.
All the other vendors
are facing this problem.
They too are scratching their heads
like you.
What are you saying?
My loss runs in millions.
If this continues, I'll be soon
begging in the streets.
We will check all your sites first.
That won't be enough.
We've given a lot of money
for you and your party.
If necessary, you'll have
to become a tower.
Don't worry.
Everyone's in the same situation.
Nothing like this happened before.
We don't know how we will
manage all this.
We've asked the Cabinet
for military help.
We will send the army
to protect the towers.
You can't fool me like you fool
the public.
I am giving you one week.
Everything should be fixed by then.
I must restart my business.
Otherwise, the next upload
in WikiLeaks will be yours!
'Fifth force.'
Science is researching
on this fifth force.
We don't know about its properties
and how to measure it.
Maybe this fifth force
is attracting the cell phones.
But with today's technology,
we cannot study it.
And we don't have the power
to control it.
That's why we've asked
for military help.
Sir, it's a huge force.
I've seen it with my own eyes.
If we bring in the military
to deal with this,
there will be an enormous
loss of life.
So what should we do?
To fight against it,
we need a superpower.
With exceptional intelligence
and extraordinary strength.
Who cannot be killed.
One who won't die...
Is there anyone like that?
Chitti. The robot.
We need to get it from
the museum. Dot.
I'm waiting.
No! Impossible!
It's illegal!
That robot has been banned.
It has been dismantled.
Has everyone forgotten
how it went out of control?
Many people lost their lives,
many properties were damaged.
If we bring it back,
it won't die,
but it will finish us all.
We also know for whom
that robot had changed.
That mistake won't be repeated.
It's my responsibility.
Sir, this is all a conspiracy
of Vaseegaran.
He is using this critical situation
for his own advantage.
He wants to market his killer robot
to multinational companies.
Now you decide, are we here
to find a way to save the city,
or for Vaseegaran's advertisement?
Okay, then you give us
a solution.
We will think about it.
Th-That's why we are here.
Sir, we are in grave danger.
This is just the beginning.
We don't know what happens next.
We have no option other than Chitti.
Mr. Vaseegaran, we can't act
against the court's order.
The process is very long.
An ordinance must be passed
in the Parliament,
the opposition parties
should cooperate.
Not possible.
- It's possible, sir.
Has any minister seen
this kind of situation?
We will convince the court
why we took this step.
Such a rule exists.
What if the robot kills someone?
Who will shoulder the responsibility?
Me? Or the minister?
It won't happen, sir.
Why not?
It is a machine.
Can you guarantee that
it won't lose control?
If it creates a mess,
the blame will be on me.
Let's forget Chitti.
Suggest some other option.
The military is the only way, sir.
That's right.
Release the request and order today.
Do the needful.
Hello.
So, plan collapsed?
Dhina, what is all this?
You know how science works.
What is all this for?
I know.
But I won't spare you.
I won't let you bring that Chitti back.
Why are you so mad at me?
You murdered my father.
Me?
Chitti is your alter-ego.
That is also you.
Murderer!
'Hey, Lulla!'
'This is the minister speaking.
I have erected all your towers.'
'Have you seen on the road?'
'All phones in the city
have started working again.'
'Go, restart your business.'
Where are you speaking from?
'From here.'
Nila, go.
Hack it open, Nila.
Boss, if I hack this,
won't I be breaking the rules?
This is an ethical hacking.
An exception. Now do what I say.
Absolutely, boss.
A lie that benefits someone
is not called a lie.
Hey, where are you learning
all this from?
For me to understand people,
you've embedded virtual emotions
and adaptive programming in me.
Basically, people have interest
in four topics.
TV, cinema, food,
gossip. Easy!
"My eyes met your eyes."
"A new desire blossomed in my heart."
Shut up!
'Leaving from airport.
Battalion 121 proceeding to spot.'
The whole state is right now
under military control.
There's nothing to panic.
Everywhere, technology related
to cell phone network
is being attended to
on a war-front emergency basis.
With military protection in place,
we are taking necessary steps
to restart the sales of cell phones.
Soon, people can start using
cell phones like before.
Balu.
- Yes, sir?
Ask for military protection
for us first.
Sir, there are four police vans
outside.
The sight of the rifles they have
won't scare even street dogs.
We need AK-47.
Manoj Lulla was hale and hearty
until yesterday.
When he got killed last night,
we didn't even find his body.
Who signed the order to restart
cell phone services immediately?
Oh, God, no.
I don't want to be found dead
like a chewed-out mango.
Go and call the military
immediately.
Juice for you, dear.
Are they on position?
- Yes, sir. We've assigned two men.
Enough security at the main gate?
- Yes, sir.
'Attack in Porur,
company on high alert.'
Sir!
Sir! Sir!
- What happened now?
The cell phone gang has uprooted
the tower in Porur.
They wiped out
the entire battalion there.
No one knows where
they will go next.
They've reached Porur too?
- Yes.
Tell them to double
our protection.
All companies are on high alert.
Close all gates and doors.
Shut all the windows too.
Don't keep a tiny hole open.
Sir, everything's been closed,
even the computer's Windows too!
They are pelting stones at us!
Sir, it's not a stone,
it's a cell phone!
Your missing cell phone.
Come and see.
All the stones are still intact!
I am a Minister.
Technology is in my hands.
That's why they got scared
and returned my phone to me.
Who is this "Unnikrishnan" calling?
It's an unknown number.
Go and tell the military
to shoot this sparrow.
Hey, get out!
'Alpha come in. Alpha.
Jupiter is reaching.'
Sir, this way please.
How is Vairamoorthy?
- Critical, sir.
He is unable to breath.
Something is stuck in his windpipe.
- What?
What is it?
- No idea at all, sir.
His PA is also not
in a state to speak.
Did you scan his body?
- We did it first, sir.
All reports are clear and normal.
Yet he is unable to breath.
What happened, Doctor?
He's no more.
What?
Phone... Give me a phone!
Sir, the phone flew away
in front of you.
Landline, man!
Hello? - I am the Home Minister
Vijay Kumar speaking.
Activate that robot Chitti
immediately.
Today! Right now!
How can you say that
as if it is very easy?
What will you tell the court, sir?
I can't break the law like this.
I will handle all of that!
First get Chitti ready!
How can it be done so quickly?
You need to pass an ordinance
in the Parliament.
The opposition parties
need to cooperate.
The process is very complicated.
There are 40 MPs in the Parliament.
I'll deal with them.
It's a machine, sir. What if
it breaks something or kills someone?
Who will shoulder the responsibility?
You? Or me?
Hey! It is not the right time
to get back at me.
The phone flew into
our Telecom Minister's mouth.
What if it enters my body
through another orifice?
I will shoulder the responsibility.
Dot!
I came here at 5 o'clock.
At least 30 people were
already here.
I haven't even got the phone yet,
And they're telling me to recharge.
Losing the cell phone felt like
losing so many pages from my life.
Oh! So what if the cell phone
flies away like a bird again?
I am very sharp, bro!
How will it go off?
What is this?
A leash for your mobile phone?
Brother, without a cell phone,
I spent the last few days better.
No annoying ringtones...
I could see the world properly.
I could talk to my children.
I could meet my friends.
It felt so good.
- Then why are you here?
What should I do?
Cell phones are like wives.
Trouble if you have them,
trouble if you don't.
Yes!
Chitti, you're back!
I was falling so fast,
I felt like I would die.
Thank you, Chitti.
Holy crow!
Chitti to control.
- 'Control to Chitti.'
Assemble at TTK road junction.
What place is this?
Integral Space Research Centre.
This space research centre
is not currently active.
No research is conducted there.
Two technicians stay there,
just for show.
In 1964, the leader of
the atomic commission, Dr. Homi Bhaba
inaugurated this research center.
Call Dr. Sam.
Hello, Sam here.
Dr. Sam, it's Vasee.
I need an information now.
Urgent.
About the space center
at Sector 2, Phase 14.
Vasee, keep this confidential.
Does intelligent life exist
on any other planet besides ours?
To find the answer,
we transmit signals into space
from different points
of the world.
Our signals are sent from there.
What is the frequency mode
of the signal?
There is a probability that
an evil force may receive the signal.
So, we are transmitting
positive signals
from our side.
We have generated
such a frequency for the signals
that only positive forces
can receive.
Thank you very much, Sam.
Chitti, play the visual
in Kirlian mode.
Look at that! The cell phones
are trying to avoid
the positive signals
from the emitters.
Because a negative force
is controlling the phones.
Negative force?
You mean, from another planet?
Freeze it!
No. This negative force
originated on this land.
That's a human face!
I have seen this face somewhere.
Nila, give me reports of
all recent abnormal events,
especially deaths,
that took place there. ASAP!
Doctor, these look like
the emitters at the space center.
Exactly.
- Why are you making this?
You know very well.
You tell us why.
Maybe the negative force controlling
the cell phones belong to a human,
which does not have a body.
It is made of the aura
that surrounds the body.
What is aura?
Every cell of the human body
is made of protons and electrons.
The waves they emit, known as
micro photons, make up the aura.
It is attached to the body
like a thin layer.
When alive, the aura of a person
is positively charged.
When a person dies, his aura
becomes negatively charged.
We need to destroy
the negative charge.
One way to do this is to send
more powerful positive charge
toward it and neutralize it.
After death, the aura consists
of micro photon minus.
We will release micro photon plus.
The sum of plus and minus
is zero.
Am I right, Doctor?
Exactly, Chitti.
This is a photon synthesizer.
It will generate micro photon plus.
See?
I've put the positive waves
the space center emitted in it,
which is ten times stronger than
the negative energy of a human body.
We will use this device and completely
neutralize that negative energy.
Wow! Great.
- Boss, I have the details ready.
73 people have died in that area
in the last year.
17 unnatural deaths, 13 murders
and 4 suicides have been reported.
Does any of these cases have
any connection to cell phones?
One died in an accident while talking
on the phone while driving a lorry.
A girl drank poison because
her private photos got leaked.
One hanged himself from a cell tower.
Date?
- April 7th.
The cell phones started disappearing
from the next day.
Oh, my God.
I understand everything now.
Chitti, install this
on the AIRD bus immediately.
We are going there.
Doctor, we got it.
All the phones are here.
'Nila, bring the bus
behind the house.'
Chitti!
Nila, fix the cryostat.
Quick!
My God.
It's Pakshirajan!
Nice DP.
This war is between
me and mankind.
You are not a human being.
So don't interfere.
Run away!
The command "run away"
is not in my programming.
I may not be a human, but I have
been reactivated to save humans.
To eliminate you is
my primary task.
Pakshirajan, why are you
so upset on mankind?
Why are you doing all this?
What do you want?
This is the Pied Cuckoo.
Its biological name
is Jacobin Cuckoo.
It is said that monsoon comes in
North India after this bird arrives.
If it does not come,
it does not rain that year.
Why? It's a mystery,
nobody knows why.
In old text books, it is
called the "Varsha Pakshi".
Why don't you research on this?
Sure, sir.
Wow! Sir, your photograph
is on the cover page.
Yes, it came about a year ago.
Sir, how did you get interested
in birds?
To tell the truth,
birds were interested in me.
'When I was born,
I couldn't breath.'
'My body turned blue.'
'The doctors had given up.'
We tried our best,
but we couldn't save him.
Let's complete the formalities
and prepare the death certificate...
'Maybe it was a coincidence,'
'but everyone said
it was a miracle.'
'My grandmother firmly believed
that God Himself had come'
'in the form of a sparrow
to give me life.'
'I still remember
when I was a child,'
'a sparrow used to enter
my room through the window'
'and fly around.'
"The morning rays come to me
through your eyes."
"As the world ends the day,
your chirps put it to rest."
"As if an artist is drawing
on the giant canvas of the sky."
"Teach me how to fly,
otherwise I have no friends."
"O', tiny little being!"
"May you sing your songs forever."
'That's when I decided to dedicate
my life only to birds.'
"O', tiny little being!"
"May you sing your songs forever."
"O', lovely little birdie!"
"This is my only prayer to God."
"No limits in the world,
no borders in the world,"
"you make no divisions,
O' innocent little bird!"
"Your sky is limitless without
borders and boundaries."
"Every leaf of every branch is yours."
"You adore the entire world
with your mellifluous voice."
"My heart wants to go with you,
O' dear birds!"
"My heart wants to fly with you,
"Take me on your wings,"
"then let's fly away..."
"Let's fly away from this land..."
So I studied ornithology and became
a professor of ornithology.
"Pon ulagaleero,"
"bhuvanam muzhudhaleero,
nannaya pullinangal."
This is an ancient Tamil song.
It means,
"O' birds, you are all over this world."
"You have spread your wings
right up to heaven."
"Our earth and our skies
abound in these birds."
The total weight of all the birds
in the world
is 100 times the weight of
all the human beings.
Birds eat a thousand times more
than humans do.
If they didn't eat insects,
there wouldn't be a single leaf
anywhere.
There will be no food for us.
Because the number insects is
100 times the number of birds.
If humans must survive,
then it is important
for birds to survive.
Sir, the number of birds that
come to Vedanthangal every year
is decreasing.
What is the reason, sir?
When we were children, we would
wake up to the chirping of sparrows.
Nowadays, there are no traces
of sparrows in the city.
Cell phones were introduced in India
in 1996.
Since then, the number of birds
has dwindled.
Especially sparrows.
This is called the Arctic Tern.
This small bird weighs only 50 grams.
Every year, it flies 12,000 kilometers
and comes to Vedanthangal,
then goes back after a while.
It does not have a map
or a radar.
Its brain can read the waves in
the sky using cryptochrome formation,
leading it to the right direction.
This is the bird's speciality.
Now we have filled the skies with
the radiation from cell phone towers.
For this, the cryptochrome formation
in the birds' brains
is slowly getting destroyed.
They get lost.
And they are going extinct.
Because of this radiation,
the eggs of birds become flaccid,
weak and soft, lacking a shell.
When the bird sits down to warm
the eggs, they break.
To tell the truth, even men too
suffer from such problems.
We may be diagnosed with cancer,
concentration may be reduced,
abortions may increase.
Moreover, there is depression,
schizophrenia, Alzheimer...
Mental diseases like these
are on the rise.
All the symptoms
are now clearly visible.
Mr. Pakshirajan,
tell us what the solution is.
What do we use cell phones
mostly for?
To chat and gossip.
We can control that.
Why so many cell phones?
Why so many towers?
We will reduce them.
There should be a law about
who uses cell phones, for what,
and for how long.
He seems to have lost it.
Instead of today's high frequency
technology,
we will make a different technology.
- Hello?
Until then, 90 percent
of the cell phone towers
in our country will
remain shut down.
Good idea.
Sir, please excuse me.
Sir, since morning I haven't...
Save birds, save earth!
- 'Save birds, save earth!'
Don't kill, don't kill!
- 'Don't kill birds!'
Save birds, save birds!
- 'Save birds, save birds!'
Don't kill, don't kill!
- 'Don't kill birds!'
'Stop, stop!
- Radiation, pollution!'
'Save birds, save earth!'
Don't they have any other work?
As soon as the sun rises, they start
holding placards defending animals.
Why don't you crack down on them?
I asked them to leave, sir.
But they said they won't leave
without meeting you.
Tell me...
What's your problem?
What is the frequency rate
allowed by TRAI?
And what is the frequency rate
on your towers?
You are endangering the birds
flying in the sky...
Hello, hello, mister, listen.
We are strictly following
the regulations of TRAI.
Subscribers often complain,
"No signal in bathroom",
"No Skype in the lift",
"No connectivity in the basement"...
Do you know, in the last 3 months
2000 subscribers switched networks.
Do you know that?
- Don't lie.
To retain your subscribers in this
disgusting competition of yours,
you flout the rules.
Now you have gone well
above the limit.
Due to this radiation, an entire species
of birds is going extinct.
Are you aware of this?
You are exaggerating.
There is no scientific proof
that birds die due to
cell phone radiation.
You know that?
Alright.
Go and stand for 24 hours
under one of your towers.
My point will be proven.
You get out.
You wanted scientific proof,
I am willing to give it to you.
Get lost.
Write a letter to the media,
or protest holding placards
in the scorching sun.
I don't care. Out.
But...
- Get out!
Nonsense.
Stop!
What are you doing?
Stop all of this! There are
houses around here.
Birds too come here.
Stop all of this!
Hey old man! We are not building
an atomic center here.
We are just building
a cell phone tower.
Now you will get
better connectivity.
Now move, go away!
What happened?
Ramaswamy, I have told you many times
how so many birds are dying.
You too felt bad about it.
But what is this?
- What do I do?
Agriculture is no longer
profitable.
Insects have destroyed my crops.
Buying insecticides,
I have become a pauper.
The reason for that too
is the death of birds.
Birds eat insects.
The less birds there are,
the more insects there will be.
Maybe you are right.
But I don't have the strength
to be a farmer anymore.
This is the only way
I can earn using this land.
So should you sell your land
to someone who kills birds?
People here are dying from hunger,
and you are worried about birds?
Go, stop pestering me.
- Move it, move!
'Ladies and gentlemen,'
'stop using cell phones!'
Each of the cell phones
you are using right now
is encased with the blood
of thousands of birds!
Every cell phone is a bird's coffin!
'Save birds...'
Come here.
Who is that man,
pestering our customers?
Take him away from here.
- Okay, sir.
Hey...
Stop using cell phones!
Take these...
Let me go!
Sir, I've filed many petitions
in all levels.
But no one took any action.
Oh! This is why we don't see
sparrows nowadays.
When I was a little child,
there were so many sparrows.
I used to play with them.
And when I grew up,
I caught and ate them.
So tasty!
And the medicine made from them...
Very tasty!
Now we don't see much around...
What's this, sir?
I'm talking about saving them,
and you're talking about eating them!
So should I mourn them?
Let's start a welfare center
for birds.
I'll put you in charge of it.
First, take action against
all network companies
using frequency rate
more than necessary.
Cancel their licenses.
Then?
Allow only two networks to operate
following regulation rules strictly.
Nonsense!
India is a country
of 1.25 billion.
We need to reach so many people.
Shouldn't all areas receive
signal properly?
At present, cell phones are
the driving force of life.
Without them, the whole world
will come to a standstill.
Cell phones save our time.
They increase efficiency.
People will lose jobs.
A hungry person cannot
amputate his hand and eat it.
This is the kind of progress
we make by killing birds.
If even a tiny sparrow
cannot live because of us,
what kind of development
and technology is this?
America is many times
bigger than India.
There are only four
or five networks.
China is the most populous country
in the world.
There are only three networks.
And here?
Ten!
By taking bribes, you give them
permission to operate.
Mind your tongue!
You look well-educated
and well-mannered,
so I have kept quiet.
And you start blaming me?
Then listen, everything is going
according to the framework.
We are allowing cell phone service
following the state's rules.
Go and file a case in the court
if you want. Get lost!
Sir, don't be angry.
Please listen to me.
How much more will you make us listen?
Go, go to the court!
Explain whatever you want to
to the judge.
The PM tells us to listen
to the public.
And we have to deal with morons
like this.
Listen, court officials are coming
to check radiation frequency.
Keep it within the limit.
The test reports clearly shows
that all providers have set
their emitters within legal range.
Also, it has not been proven
that birds are affected
by cell phone technology.
As a result, the court finds
Pakshirajan's PIL to be baseless.
Pakshirajan, all your points are valid.
But killing humans is wrong.
When they killed so many sparrows,
was it not wrong?
Is a bird's life so valueless
than a human life?
Will you punish the innocents
for the mistakes of a few?
Whom are you calling "innocent"?
Each and every cell phone user
is a murderer!
I screamed at the top of my voice.
I ran along the streets
and begged.
I pleaded to everyone
not to use cell phones.
Did a single person
listen to me?
People read about this on newspapers
and watch the news on TV.
And after that...
They say, "Even birds die
because of cell phone radiation!"
"Poor birds!"
They express their sorrow
for five minutes,
then they share the articles and
video clips on WhatsApp and Facebook.
They think they have
fulfilled their responsibility,
then again they start
talking on their cell phones.
I won't spare them.
I won't spare
a single cell phone user.
Just watch me do such a thing...
from now on cell phones will be
the noose around their necks!
People will run the hell away
as soon as they see them.
You just wait and watch.
Pakshi, your game is over.
The bus is ready.
Chitti!
Thanks.
- Welcome.
Hey! What's this?
Why did you fix your MPU
in me?
Oh! My mistake.
Now I understand
how my core memory got corrupted,
and punch dialogues, "Comedy Nights
with Kapil", "Kum Kum Bhagya"
and "Karela Kofta" made their way
into my MPU.
Come, lie down.
I'll fix it.
No. Let it be for now.
Aura.
Every human, every animal...
Every object, every place
has an aura.
It's not something about religion.
It's a matter of science.
Auras have been detected
through the use of Kirlian camera.
An ordinary person's aura
is three to four feet thick,
whereas the aura of a sage
may spread up to 50-60 feet.
Russian scientist
Dr. Frank Baranowski has proven this.
Pakshirajan's aura is vast.
It is not the aura
of only a single human,
but an enormous one combining
the auras of thousands of dead birds.
A giant ball of negative energy
with a mind.
A very angry mind.
Maybe this is the fifth force,
that had been snatching
only our cell phones.
The city would have been destroyed.
It is because Chitti returned
that we were saved.
Thank you, Chitti.
Heartfelt gratitude to all of you
who have supported me so far.
In every textbook,
it is said that
to protect us from the evil,
God takes avatars
and comes to Earth.
Now God Himself has taken
the form of a machine
and come to save us.
When a soldier fights
at the border,
doesn't his shadow fight too?
When he kills the enemy,
doesn't his shadow do the same?
So, do we pay respect to the shadow
instead of the soldier?
He is the real soldier,
I am his shadow.
All thanks to the God
who created me.
Thank you.
There is someone else
who must be acknowledged.
Had she not given me
her heart at the right time...
I mean, if she hadn't fixed
her MPU in me,
then we might not have been
able to defeat that force.
That is...
Nila.
And at this wonderful moment,
another good news awaits us.
This creation of Dr. Vaseegaran,
Chitti,
has been approved
by our government.
This morning, an order
has been passed
to make 500 robots like Chitti
for the Indian army.
Thank you.
Hi, scientist.
May I come in?
O' irresponsible people!
Throw away your cell phones.
Take this as your last warning,
or death is imminent.
Dad, I was talking to my boss,
not to some girl.
Hey! Didn't you listen?
I always wear "Victoria's Secret",
you know, including the latest...
Nila, is photon synthesizer set?
- Yes.
All clubs are closed
after 12 o'clock.
Let's go next week...
Doctor, what are you doing?
What is all this for?
Come, my beloved toy!
Alas! I am not your doctor anymore.
'Nila, turn on the neutralizer!'
No.
Nila, stop it!
You can't do anything to me, Chitti!
Now I have a body.
Dr. Vaseegaran's body.
To destroy me,
you'll have to destroy
your creator as well!
Go on, turn on that toy of yours.
Show me your technology.
Turn it on.
Turn it on and show me!
Chitti, don't think.
Turn it on.
Both of us will be destroyed
together.
No, Doctor. I can't do that.
Chitti, don't risk all of
humanity for saving me.
Destroy me to eliminate him.
Kill me!
- Sorry, Doctor.
The human emotions of the MPU
won't allow me to do so.
Oh, you fool! This is my order!
Kill me!
No! Hold fire.
This bullets will only
kill Vaseegaran.
Pakshirajan won't be affected.
Chitti, what are you doing?
Let them shoot me!
No.
Chitti! Chi...
Nila, turn on the synthesizer.
Come on! Quick!
Nila, no! Don't do that!
Shut up! This is my order!
Turn it on!
Stop being silly, Chitti.
Your call is disconnected!
Chitti...
What a pity!
Chitti? Chitti!
Chitti...
Nila, you go and...
"I will cause a ruthless destruction!"
"Pakshirajan is terribly personified.
He is the new name of fear!"
"I have come to destroy you."
"Your spirit screams the hell out
as you see me."
"I am omnipresent!
Where will you run from me?"
"Pakshirajan!"
"I am omnipresent!
Where will you run from me?"
"Pakshirajan!"
The joy of coming back to life
after death feels so good.
Pakshi!
You won't be able to fly anymore.
Hey, Nila!
How was it?
Nila, the Lucky Woman, huh?
Come, come, come, come...
Come on, baby!
Wow.
The best two of
Vaseegaran's creations...
One is me,
the other is you.
What are you looking at?
Come on! Give a beautiful kiss
to your great king, Nila.
Stop the play, Chitti.
First defeat Pakshi.
He is more powerful than you.
And he is causing more destruction
than you.
He has beaten and broken you
into pieces.
Now he is the world's No. 1...
not you.
Hey! Number 1, number 2 is
all a child's play.
I am the only one.
Super one!
No comparison. Understand?
I understand, Chitti.
Make him understand this.
- Absolutely!
The king of birds!
The battle is on!
Left! Right!
Head!
Activate command mode.
Command mode activated!
What is this?
It's me.
Mini me!
So cute!
'What a game!
What a game we've had till now!'
'And now it's half time
at the IFL finals.'
Hey, your phone is ringing.
Dear subscribers,
you are going to be
out of coverage from now.
Because, all of you will die now.
This is not an ordinary death...
Radiation death!
You will die the same way
birds died in flocks.
Did you get it?
I will combine the radiation
from all the cell phones you use
and direct it against you.
Want to see a demo?
Hey you!
Excuse me...
Can you choose someone else?
I'm... I'm on your side.
- How?
I was the one who freed you.
Spare me for that at least, please?
So what?
You, too, are a cell phone user.
"Your spirit screams the hell out
as you see me."
"I am omnipresent!
Where will you run from me?"
You all will be burned to ashes
like this.
'In five seconds, 70,000 people
died in Hiroshima.'
'It was the world record.'
Today, 80,000 people!
A new record!
You are going to be
a part of a historic moment,
dear subscribers!
Dear subscribers,
no need to panic.
You are not the ones to die.
A small bird...
What are you looking at, Pakshi?
I am Chitti, reloaded.
Version 2.0!
Doctor, you?
Did I shoot you?
I tried to kill you?
Oh, no. I was about to commit
a grave sin!
Doctor, don't do anything to me.
You are my creator.
Don't rip me apart with your own hands.
Forgive me and let me go.
Please!
Take this.
Vasee!
Come, my selfie lovers!
I will set your screens on fire.
Zero balance!
Shoo that sparrow!
Hey, birdman!
I am Iron Man!
Please, don't kill me.
Let me go!
Pakshi, you better fly away,
or I will pluck every feather
from your body.
Stupid machine! Why are you
fighting for these selfish people?
Once you've served your purpose,
they'll break you into pieces.
What's happening?
Hey, angry bird!
Did you not recognize me?
I am Chhotu, the microbot.
Version 3.0!
If you disturb my boss,
I shall kill the dove!
"I am the grandson of Isaac Asimov!"
"I only look small!"
"We will burn this monstrous bird"
"and celebrate Diwali!"
Hey!
I have heard that
birds have 360-degree vision.
Pakshi, won't you look around?
Microbots!
No!
No, no!
No! Spare them!
Pakshi, now I know your weakness!
Go!
"Let's drag it away..."
Pakshi, the radiation will
burn the stadium,
but first these doves
will be roasted!
Microbots, go.
"I have many tricks
up my sleeve..."
"I may look tiny, but I am
a pocket-sized dynamite..."
"Beware of my cunning! Or you will
end up in the graveyard!"
A lion can do nothing
to a mosquito.
But thousands of mosquitoes
can send a lion to his doom.
Good job, 3.0.
Thank you, Commander.
Microbots positioned?
- All set.
Pakshi!
Have a blast!
Hey, hey!
Do you want all birds to die?
Hey, beep, follow me!
Come on, bots.
Vroom!
"We will burn this monstrous bird"
"and celebrate Diwali!"
"Hey, foolish bird!"
"Your place in Hell awaits you!"
"Let's finish this!"
"It is a nightmare
born out of an egg!"
Hey! Who are you?
Who let you in here?
This is a restricted area.
Get out!
Once again, we are alive
because of you.
You took a big risk
and saved us.
Technology is there to save us,
but we are misusing technology.
The true purpose of technology
is to eliminate diseases,
eradicate poverty,
promote education.
If we use it selfishly,
we will lose control over it,
and we will be wiped out.
You think Pakshirajan will return?
He is no more.
But if we don't correct ourselves,
then someone else will rise.
Pakshirajan's actions were wrong,
but what he said was true.
The existence of humans
depends on other animals as well.
We must control radiation,
reduce network companies.
There should be a rule
to ensure that our technology
doesn't harm other living beings.
This land is not our property.
Every animal in the world
has equal right to it.
You're right.
We should save birds.
At least, we can provide them
with water during summer.
This should be the definition
of humanity.
All this will happen, Vaseegaran.
This should be brought
to the Parliament's attention.
I'll make sure this happens.
Thank you, Vaseegaran.
Thanks, Nila.
- Who thanks his own shadow?
Oh God!
We need to remove the red chip
from Chitti!
Don't worry, boss.
I had activated an auto-eject
program for safety.
Smart!
Good to see you alright, Doctor.
Me too, Chitti.
Doctor, we robots have to report
to the Delhi headquarters.
Can I leave, Doctor?
Hmm.
Take Nila with you.
Doctor, I can't leave you
in this condition...
I'll handle it myself.
- Is this love?
Go!
Thanks, Doctor.
"O' my love! You are my battery,
the current of my breath."
"O' my battery!
Don't be discharged ever."
"O' mechanical beauty, listen..."
"I was awakened by your current."
"You got transferred into
my heart like data."
"O' my digital beauty!"
"Let me touch your silicon cheeks..."
"Your firewall-like hair stops me..."
"Let's travel around the world
on Wi-Fi..."
"I am a superconductor!"
"O' my love! You are my battery,
the current of my breath."
"O' my battery!
Don't be discharged ever."
"O' my love! You are my battery,
the current of my breath."
"O' my battery!
Don't be discharged ever."
"O' mechanical beauty, listen..."
"I was awakened by your current."
"You got transferred into
my heart like data..."
"O' my digital beauty!"
"You are the sensor
that awakens feelings..."
"You are the cable
that passes energy..."
"You are the disc
and also the drive..."
"You are the software
that quenches my thirst."
"My CPU beats on your RAM."
"Come, log into me
without password."
"In this electromagnetic
relationship,"
"how did love come in the way?"
"O' Alpha! You are my beginning."
"O' Mega! You are my end, too."
"I love you from zero to infinity."
"O' my love! You are my battery,
the current of my breath."
"O' my battery!
Don't be discharged ever."
"O' my love! You are my battery,
the current of my breath."
"O' mechanical beauty, listen..."
"I was awakened by your current."
"You got transferred into
my heart like data..."
"O' my digital beauty!"
"Let me touch your silicon cheeks..."
"Your firewall-like hair stops me..."
"Let's travel around the world
on Wi-Fi..."
"I am a superconductor!"
"O' my love! You are my battery,
the current of my breath."
"O' my battery!
Don't be discharged ever."
"O' my love! You are my battery,
the current of my breath."
"O' my battery!
Don't be discharged ever."
Hello! Sana, darling!
'So many things happened
and no one even called me!"
'I am dying of worry here...'
Hello, Sana, listen...
'And where is that Nila of yours?
She is your assistant, right?'
'Couldn't she call at least?'
- Can't this phone fly away now?
Hey, big guy! Are you stunned?
A strong blow came slowly!
Hey! Who are you?
I am Chhotu, compressed version.
3.0!
Your grandson!
"We will burn this monstrous bird"
"and celebrate Diwali!"
"Hey, foolish bird!"
"Your place in Hell awaits you!"
"Let's finish this!"
"It is a nightmare
born out of an egg!"
"We will scramble that egg
and eat it up!"
"I am the painter of the strange
rainbow above your head."
"I am as powerful as Lord Rama."
"I am the painter of the strange
rainbow above your head."
"I am as powerful as Lord Rama."
"I am a Lilliput who has never
heard the name of any disease."
"I am a Lilliput
who has an iron fist."