Dedicated to Bollywood Friends of Persian Language Www.Bollycine.org
..Svpr Star Rajan Kant
Robot 2 (Second Edition)
The dream of flying like you "" I'm in heaven
"Fly, Fly"
.Balyvvd cinema proudly presenting the Www.Bollycine.Info
IMPORTANT NOTE: The main language of the Tamil movie. After the songs have been translated for Tamil version
Hello
Hello, we are students. With our doctor appointments Wasi
Please go ahead
! Brother, what Dafyh
excuse me, who are you?
I am a resident doctor
Oh your name?
unbroken
Beautiful, thank you -
Blue, blue
Yes?
Your name after a fun name
for what?
! I do not know, or I should eat his name
I can hold Shmarhtvn?
Zbvnt say it was the same monkeys coming out.
Hi hi -
Hi, come in -
Gettin 'our doctor from the School of Engineering Mzahmtvn
So did you see that you just wanted humanoid robot
Are methionine showed us this?
Necessarily
Here's the robot
New unbroken
An assistant, beautiful, lovely and clever
2018 model robot who is blind Kvantvn
With unlimited storage and speed of a Terra
Here's Aslyshh engine looks like a heart operation
Here's a fun name for the human form -
! Mybrysh or Mykhvrysh
His telephone number?
Number build my car
Model Chytyh? Not -
This is a model that helps your people to turn their
It feels like? Programmable for Kntrlshh -
Is Pinto doctor comes back in the day?
Translation expertise of our cultural and artistic media Translators: Byngsa and Mystic
..Drsth not now
But when needed, people will accept it.
Pinto is certainly needed when he comes back
Is Naکata
get lost
Took her
Listen, I just dribble Las way I was; I did not mean
Shut Up liar
My Doll, Let's Go Coffee shop
I do not want to
I wanted to really know your birthday! I'm a handset Apple Gift
Collection comes on, let's eat and sharp
OK
... to tell the customer. I
A place the whole family phone talking ..darn
Give my phone
Not
I'm an obligatory phone! Give the phone
! What Dad! Take
! Me what Dad
...Father
... Hello, dear
It ..rh
Daddy
So that to me, it hits me with my ..hrf
Look, I need us
Dear ..alv
Yeah everyone! Mom
what happened?
I was the project manager ..dyg·h promotion work
..Bh Dad and say hello Bresson
Four of the Zen fay! Carling Chi darh
: Instagram, Telegram our official media @BollyCineOfficial
Doctor, like Dkhtrtvn ring out!
Chuck Senate
Wet citizens, stole Qur'an answer?
Sorry Senate
How was working on a project called .. All cards
I beg you dear
Because of a missed call and now I bus 112 to
112 to face one wanted to leave right now
Hah
! Kiss the Air
! It is not clear what happened
All Phone fly out
These people will do a double or a band
We were very scared
This marks a sort of huge destruction
I saw the destroyed
If I die Gvshym Brngrdh
Vatsp and Iniesta are you not live without
Now everybody has a phone No, what I mean -
what do I do?
Now I Pydashvn How should I?
All information passing and my bank was in it.
General personal photos and videos luggage
sorry
Excuse me what to write?
..Qrban, my phone
..Qrban, where it Hکaatnamh
I went to find out ..gvshy
Whatever is sign up
All Tlfna go if Dad just -
Sound Commissioner OVERSEAS
Thankful
Minister are
Yes, sir. I'm being followed
You see, sir, my phone has been carats of diamonds two and a half
Twenty million cost was
A help it, sir, OK -
Sir, expert of the single
Khvastyn your SIM card through the phone's location dying
So what happened?
All the SIM card and the phone is totally out of our orbit are available
! I can not understand is Mvqytshvn
All calls shutdown
Find out the hidden phones, the City Mission
Then all off Mission
Well, how is it possible?
I think the conditions Vzyh you know what?
Very strange! I've got all the evidence and investigate the strange things past
This is quite rare, and any wonder
I can not be the perfect answer for this incident and I find conclusive scientific
Obviously this is a Trvrystyh attack
They're planning a big attack OVERSEAS
We can not for whatever happens in this world ..kh
We do not know the answer and let it sync linked to terrorism or an act of God
Is it a coincidence work might be extraterrestrial beings?
No sir, I read the reports
You're nothing special space creatures come from the existence of land we do not have
It should also be borne in mind that becomes an international company that is in their interests
As far as I know
Phone technology that could give the town like a bird flight did not come into existence
It is possible that this is a new experience for a scientist is a fool
Who is this?
Son of former science and technology minister, Mr doctor Dyrndr one of the best scientists now
Director of science and technology
The three-dimensional map or core product images Mahvarhhayyh three of which are on the circuit
The three little dots are transmitters for satellite
Current images tells us that the phone is turned to a high point
This means that the phone is more than 10 kilometers above sea level going
If Bkhvayym the formation of a circle of sync
Phone should be inside a fence 200 kilometers away in Chennai
..Jazbh, electromagnetic, nuclear radiation
I'm sure this happening can be explained scientifically
All Phone Glass break up and go out
Complaints were made? Not -
Even a whole town knows you left the phone
Who wants me now answer the people?
Tomorrow afternoon myrcene
! You said you this afternoon myrcene
The voice of society, what comes back?
The sound track! These days, all the rhymes Aynjvryand
Bro, bro
That's what's going on inside? Interior someone?
what are you saying? She just phones Mvbaylh
This was the container Call me
Khvastyn from the security police? Yes -
Tomorrow the
If tomorrow, sir Display Driver Model Tlfnay New Bern, then what?
After days without Bdmvn goin
! Not just us, but all of us
You brush Dadmvn
What's going on here.
Qurban tonne container
Who speaks it?
I derogatory, you were told you were containers Call
Yeah
Hello sir, I am Commissioner Rajendar Sharma
The sides
You Ayshvn murder is not a trace of man
Perhaps this is a clue to the type of work you get into the phone Ayshvn helpful
The absence of loved ones
There is no sign of footprints or fingerprints room
Ayshvn was supposed to come once the phone
Ayshvn was released today after your mobile phone
Gvshyshvn shipping container and left it all handsets vanish from it.
Really do not know what's going on
The murder of handsets
... These are many of the components you
Some mobile phones such as silicon and are ...
Cellphones with different models and different release dates
Kumar Jynd phone 'killing
Killing off the phone?
What do you say, sir?
If not then what phones they were here?
!tip
What a surprise! Today miracle! You whip phone
Senate very good. I can take this call
This is the last corner of the city you there
All handsets vanish
There, I got this phone connect a tracer
Therefore I actually Shmam mice
It's the Senate
I wanted to kiss her on the phone to send the ball went flying
So I thought why do I do today
That's not going to work
Nokia jumped
At that meeting Lab! Now are you with that girl
Hey, this is exactly like a laptop will stay the only one Dstgahh-
Shu the lightweight
What ? Shut yo?
Listen to the Senate, the phone was ..prvaz every moment possible, mark the oovoo
Why did not guess honor? -
tyrwḵạzhwḵwndrạm
MRI MRI of the active O activated -
This is what gives The oil trail are they doing?
You're left to look Yes, sir -
mmnvnm unbroken
Thanks a laptop Wants
Sir, listen mail!
Lula coming
Or God, we
Were you want to say? - Yes -
Sit Ad
No excuse not acceptable
Noble What are you?
! You state here, there or not.
See Lula Here's the same God who is everywhere
Notes that good when I am with sharp teeth
Ydvnh healthy I left the cell towers
Your problem is not just the quick removal of all poles
Even towers rest of the company
This is how he saw the same people who sit out for
Why are you saying nap?
I saw billions in losses
If it goes to three months in another way I have my tent street
We had to consider the rest of your problem
Just a week Noble
Before the election the gang guys have money Chmdvn Chmdvn
If you need to be yourself I'm mast
, Come on! A rare accident happened Have?
We do not know how to control this situation we
We are doing everything that is necessary to save the towers we
I. Of the people you can not concentrate Mymaly
I rub the juice
A week from today till then everything must be right
I must start again
If Nyfth my way, you will be the next bomb Wikileaks
But overall survey tracked
Several handsets are coming under control and this has become
We can not be controlled with today's technology it
Because of this, we got ready we left Artshmvn
That's too much power, sir.
If we put in front of his army Bzarym
They get a couple missed Jvnshvn
So what to do?
We need a superpower to fight with him
Those who have many skills
Someone who has no one to kill his kick
SOMEONE kick die?
Plaintiffs, Rabat
We should feel really needs to get out of the museum, points
I am waiting
No way! I disagree
Where illegal کar
How many people really remember that they killed for him.
Was and how much damage?
He who dies with Brgrdvndnsh but we must die
Who shifted to the robot? Ino everyone knows
This time I did nothing wrong, I guarantee happining
Sir, these people all this chopping the poor bastards plot
He is critical of this position took advantage of the coming Abuse
For he could face international companies attracted by ticks
You decide
Are we here to save the city gathered
Or to advertise the Gran Vessey?
Okay, if you want to say you have strategy
A. We think about it.
We have gathered here for
Sir, we'll have big risks
This was the first stage we have no idea and do not have a plan to prevent future incidents
We have no way other than pinto sir.
Mr. Vessey Gran; we can not stand in front of the verdict of the judiciary
Agrm Bkhvayym take the decision it takes time
Must request to parliament sync
Have a high number of seats
Bring to a vote and suspensions up! Nammknh
Maybe, sir, have you ever seen something like this minister?
We do this because it was obvious Mykhvayym
Therefore, can we convince the court the way it is
If the robot to kill someone then who will be in fault?
! My fault or Secretary
Also not happen, sir.
Why happining?
The A-device
What guarantee is there that can not get out of control?
If I happen to be responsive
Pinto No, I have another way
Do not worry sir's Army
it's true! So today we publish requests and orders
!So what up with u
What's Going On? You consider yourself a scientist, why?
! I know, but let's do this,
Let him come back pinto
Why are you so upset with me?
! I ship my father
From?
This tiger precise self misconception
!the murderer
Oh brother, I
Poles all the way Dydyshvn not correct?
All phones in this town again began to work
Go start your business now
!Where to start
At this point
unbroken bad
Hksh now open again
Sir, if I hack I put my foot on the law
Case no?
Where legal Hک
An exception, not always
The mean true, a lie which is a good thing to happen to him
! He's not lying, right?
Nila, and you learn these things from the learned Where are you?
.. I should be able to understand people's
There, you learn the name of a specific system for me ..yh
And Play, boudin implemented
I realized that most people focus on the things you have four
Money, cinema, food and lust! So easy
"We have a heart made of iron."
"About Love comes first Sraght?"
"About Love comes first Sraght?" Shut up -
Each unit is ready to be
You do not need to control the city Artshh people Btrsn
Everywhere all means of telecommunications systems are repaired Mission
The protection of the army, we're going
Use the phone all again soon
Tell me more protection they
But sir, this Alansh four men out to Van blades to protect you Vaystadn
That's my dog ​​Dstshvnh them with the weapons Nmytrs·h
Tell them subdue AK-47
Yesterday telecommunications company owner ..rv so threatening to kill and destroy
! Has been found that Jnazshm
Who signed cell towers on the Setup tab again?
! I'm miserable.
No, not like that someday I'm going like these become a
Go say they increased the number of personnel
Ad
According to a report of an assault attack
Sir, sir.
what happened?
I heard there was an attack where the towers were hitting right now
Everywhere was destroyed
You see I told you, I would have said 'no protective doubles
I was doing it, sir.
Come close the doors closed, keep the windows
Sir, do not worry everything under controlled
Sir, this is your phone Ad
Diamond is not Tvryshvn
I'll come back with his own leg
I've minister, okay? I'm punching technology
You see exactly how the phone! Up after me.
! Contact Anonymous
By Anonymous
Collection Go, Go, Go out of here
go out
Sir
How is their situation?
Many victims Vkhymh Tnfsysh the ruins
Why? what happened?
I do not know! The Shock entered them.
Could not speak.
Beautifully scan did you, not the case? Yes sir -
We got her whole body MRI
No items
But still very hard breath comes and goes
! What the doctor sadly died -
..Tlfn, phone
The phone before you flew away
! I mean permanent line
Hello
I am the interior minister
The robot's pinto immediately Rush noble
Already today, right now
LOL! how is it possible?
You'll also if you say you restaurant! No order lunch Midi
What do you want to tell the court?
This is how we can not violate the law Bzarym
I think everything Ono row
You just bring it out pinto
But how is it possible?
Parliament should you sync request
Much to her seats in the body
It's a long process clamp
40 seat there I am! And it me
! She is a one-device
If you break something up or kill someone, what?
Tzmynsh Who's the lead? You or me?
Argh! He tore the phone from the mouth of the abdomen and came out
It is not clear tomorrow! Handset from where I go Tu
I'm Tzmynsh, the
!Point
! How busy here.
Do not come NL's phone and thats questions about the charge OVERSEAS
I want a fresh new model I
eh! If the phone again, but the bird wants to fly and lambs what?
Look here, my brother very Personal
! How wants to go
, You just close your pants, bras
Since the phone are not very good
I'll go anywhere there is a phone ringtone I come back, I spoke with my kids
I talk with my friends! How much good.
So what did you come here for?
As the phone like Adam's wife will stay the
Msybth you do not have an open're a disaster in another
!Yeah
! Pinto you back
thank you! I just thought I tat - thanks Pinto -
Pinto center
! Center in Pinto
Send a car path
.Batry weak
In search of power was .yaft
: Instagram, Telegram our official media @BollyCineOfficial
Where is here?
This is a weather research center Fzayyh
The center is not active anymore
So long closed
2 technicians only way I got here today
I 1965, the center was built on the orders of doctor Homi bavra
Call the doctor Sam
Yes, Sam I am
Doctor Sam, I'm wide Gran
I'm a bit of information immediately
About a research center which Phase I was 14
Vessey this information Mhrmanhst
Did you just land our galaxy, creatures with reason and intelligence 's?
To find out whether they are creatures boilers
We have a point in space, we'll send you signal ground
That's exactly the sound that Indian visitors Mrkz·h
! Frequency property which countries?
There is a possibility that the signals are received by a power eagle Mission
We therefore send positive signal from our side
This means that the galaxy if you're positive balance
They could only make our signal received
Thank you, doctor
! Pinto images that throw the curtain
He could see his effort home to get away from the positive signals
That's because the negative energy from within after it
Negative energy that is a another world?
Keep it
No, this energy wealth is here
This is people! Ino I saw somewhere
Nila, the list of those who die quickly! Associated with the phone having the check
Doctor Research Center were in front of the transmitter why?
! Accurate
so why?
! Also you say you do not know if you say
They might be the negative energy emitted by a person
The body may not have the time
But their negative aura and energy still in this world
Him again?
The human body is composed of neutron and electron s
By combining the two energy radiated an aura gets a name
This energy is always present in humans
If a man carries this energy alive
The energy always remains positive
However, if one die
The same energy or aura comes into negative
... to eliminate this negative aura
We need much stronger than the negative positive energy to send his post
The aura of the work happen
To do this we must use rods of light transmitters
When you send a positive light on the negative side
It reduces negative
Must be low enough to score zero
I like that she goes away on its own, just tell the doctor?
! It pinto
The device produces a positive light beams into the Look
Type the energy of the Research Center were sent I got reproduce
Of these, ten times the power of a positive radii of Mrdhst
With the power that the device is
We can not parse it and eliminate negative energy
What good! The supreme sacrifice -
The information requested boudin
Your recent times about 34 people mysteriously die
Among them, 17 have been declared natural death Tash
13 people are murdered each other 4 to suicide
Of these deaths which one the phone to evolving?
People are talking on a phone while driving in the accident
Because a girl naked pictures to've had several people committed suicide
A man hanged himself from a telecommunications tower
What a day
7 vryl
Exactly the same day, the phone starts to vanish off
!My God! Has everything becomes clear
! tiger
Ino's face-mounted devices now have to Shim
! We find her doctor, all handsets inches
Blue Fly crying Community slash
Plaintiffs
Nila, fixed now try again
! Oh my! Rajan Shopping Cart
! Photos Profile Bahalyh
The war between me and men
You're not human intervention Wants
!do not interfere
I no such thing as losing the software is not defined
I woke up mankind may be saved
I should not kill you
Rajan delete it, why people hate so much?
Why are you doing it?
What do you want?
This is a Kvkvyh
The name of the biology of this Jykvbynh say
The birds Mansvr after this type of migration to India between
You south India, these people came after the rainy season comes
If this does not show up, it means that the rain will not happen
Because nobody knew who this secret?
Your ancient history of this bird told they rain
Why do not you take on this study?
Be sure to master! Professor society! You see the magazine printing
This! Outnumbered year
! Sir, How are the birds you are getting interested
If I want to tell the truth, my favorite bird, wild,
When I was born, self Nmykshydm
My body was bruised doctoral could not work effectively swift
In the earlier procedure
Translation expertise of our cultural and artistic media Translators: Mystic and Byngsa
Maybe it was something happens to say it's ok but all Mjz·hst
My grandmother said that a bird came face God to give me life
I remember today
When I was a kid
A sparrow every day from coming inside the window ..ataqm
And flew
"You're the golden light of life"
"Ballerina shake you go"
"Sit on female gazelle"
"With his arms to sleep Spoke"
"Nhyft quiet walk with his feet."
"A great Kvlam as you go"
"Its Achtyakyi Medhi"
"I have a dream of flying like you in heaven"
"fly"
"Do I listen to your voice."
From that day on I vowed that my life belongs to the birds. All OK
"Hey flock"
"Do I listen to your voice."
I pray that voice. "" Chirp you hear
.. "Without Zbana"
.. "Without Aiana"
"Wherever you live?"
.. "Without Zbana"
.. "Without Aiana"
"Wherever you live?"
.. "every little thing to eat."
"Things yours"
.. "where"
"The atmosphere also make a wing"
"You're human courage."
"That he lives"
"The spirit of, Azizm"
"I would like you heart"
"The world will be extinct."
"Your love will save from extinction"
"Fly, Fly"
"Beyond a Boundary Fly"
So I chose my own field biologists
And became Professor
The bird that will fly on the whole world.
From here to the south everywhere this Prndganh
It's an old adage: In the Tamil language were the
The bird that will fly on the whole world.
From here to the south everywhere this Prndganh
All birds hundred times the weight of the weight of all humans on the planet
So that people eat thousands before him eat the birds
..Agr they Nkhvrn cream
Even a green leaves you the rest of the world will Monde
People will not have anything to eat
Because worms on the earth one hundred times the world's birds you
Sing it if people continue to Hyatshvn the earth, birds must stay alive
What happened that was so low Jmytshvn?
Qblna we were awakened by the sound of birds and bird from
But you now and into the cities, not the bird has no name
The first mobile phone was invented in 1996
After that, the number of birds getting less
This name is Artyklr
Little bird, weighing 50 hot
Every year thousands of kilometers away and here comes 12
And then comes back
This bird radar map or not
The bird's brain power that could get your route
And he could not find her own path
The effect of this Prndhst
We came to the cell towers, all of the signals we are facing in the air
Because of these frequencies, the brain powers of these birds had gone slowly
They get a couple of Qdrtshvn the wild, and they die slowly of
Because of the low frequencies wild birds eggs and soft Mission
Birds Sing it every time Bshynn method
For breeding, and break eggs for fertility Valadi again!
, The truth is that this problem is a problem of all mankind
With so many problems, even people going to happen
Psychiatric illness, schizophrenia, Alzheimer's disease, anxiety, and stress is getting more and grows.
Gradually it becomes clear that Lamtash
Mr Rajan delete it, how to make the problem was solved?
What is the phone for you?
! To prattle! This must be controlled
Why all phones or masts?
What Nyazyh? This pair should be shortened
How and how much to use phone
To this must be a law
! This guy crazy
Instead of a strong frequencies are today's make it happen
Technology will have to find replacements
Until then the country should turn off cell towers 90 percent jump
! Good idea
Save the earth, save the bird saw saw
! Do not kill
! Do not, do not throw the bird
Save the earth, save the bird saw saw
These people do not have work and life?
The mark attorney morning! .. a bunch of dogs and cats and birds
I said, sir.
Said no meeting place where you will not go anymore
Begin, What understand your problem?
Telecommunications frequencies limit how much?
Frequencies you now, is it?
You're birds in the sky from the mid-air between Mybryn
Hey .. Sir, listen to
We telecoms rules, we run the exact verbatim
Customers have also complained that Alansh
You do not signal apartment you do not have an elevator signal
Basement unbeatable service
Your past three months, about two thousand of our users to change the wireless Kartshvn
LIE! Keep your filthy competition increasing in a puttin '
And each company will take as much as he loves the high frequencies
The frequencies other than cross the red line radiation risk
These rays reached for generation of birds to extinction
You got the news?
! It is no exaggeration else are you
"Because birds are extinct rays Mission" This letter was no evidence of
Okay, you yourself just 24 hours on a cell towers Stop
Then I prove that I
go out
Did you remain anonymous document? I am I'll give you another
Go out and write letters to the media
Stop signs every day and take the company forward
I do not care, go out
Go out and listen to -
! Nonsense says
Vaysyn! Noble What are you?
The people here around the house, the bird
You finish this construction
Hey man, we do what we are doing?
Just have a mast, rather.
From now on, the more comfortable you'll receive comes signals
what happened?
How many times have you explained that birds die?
You're hurt by them but still no let Midi
what do I do? Kshavrzym underlying the worm struck, destroying Tmamshvn
He also destroyed the Prndganh
The birds eat worms
..Prndhha how little you hear
Worms Hmvnqdr going to jump
It really is
But I can not farm
This is another way of income except I do not
So do you want the bird to those who are Mykshn land for mast bad?
When people are hungry die
I have a meeting and thought the birds?
Do not bother me
Go along with
..Ladies and Gentlemen
Let me next to mobile phone use
Every phone you make use scrolled
The blood of a bird Ghshthst
Use a pay phone that lives in your hands Prndhst
Come here, Who is that? Yes -
Since when he gives Ferrari customers
Bndazynsh out the eye -
..Ladies and Gentlemen
...listen
Sir, I'm here to say I have a job for you
Aha! Because of this newly found no cry could not
When I was little sparrow overall the sides and across the Myplkyd
I played with them
When I grow up I roast them
And with a bit of salt and pepper ate! How delicious went
! Now that I do not know Where are Gnjshka
If the first and we ate fried
What Hrfyh sir?
I am talking about .. I live it up
You are about to frying them
what do I do?
I sit and lament or you feel responsible?
You get a couple proliferation against companies that have frequencies higher than the limit, no more action
Revoke the work permit them
after that?
And 2 to companies that are in accordance with the rules OVERSEAS let me continue to turn their website
What winks and Prtayy! India country with 1 billion and 250 million Jmyth
This signal is needed to cover people or not?
The phone is a huge necessity
Phone, such as water, human life is not disrupted if there would be.
Phone, we are saving time comes into
Can you handle the work and life of the people doing it do Myaftn
If someone Grsnhsh is coming off his hand and hard?
Quality control is exactly the kind of endangered birds
If a sparrow can not for the life of himself to trust us and gave 30 g
So how do these jobs going! To help human life
US from India several times bigger
There are only 3 or 4 companies OVERSEAS telecommunications activities
China is the world's largest population
There are only 3 companies OVERSEAS telecommunications activities
And here?
! Ten
And all of the company's issued permits are you
! Stop else
It seemed like a nice guy ..and educated
There, I had the honor to talk to you
What do you know about politics?
You telecoms law is any law that we practice it, we
If you think it is not filed Go you now
Sir, you'll Why are you sad? Listen to
I do not command you go, go court
The judge said if I'm answering mark
The courts are rolling in for inspection frequencies
So bring on the frequency extent permitted by law
The reports showed that it was obvious that all companies are subject to the country's telecom rules
Here's also been proven that it really ..bkhatr communication frequencies
Birds are Anqrazh generation! Or harm they bear
For this reason, the Court of Rajan's petition unfounded minutes of pure, end of session
The mean you just delete Rajan
But killing people is not the right thing
Kill every one of sparrows was the right thing?
The value of all bird life! Are you under some chopping the poor bastards June
Do you want a bunch of people you betrayed your revenge from innocent people to take big?
What innocent?
Any person who is guilty of an interesting mobile phone
How I shouted?
I went every alley and street
Gave anyone a favor
I learned not to use the phone placard
; Two would not listen to me even a
Every day you can see all TV and magazine
The communication frequencies dangerous birds for life
Then say community! The rays phone! Birds do die? eh?
! Poor
Five minutes after giving upsetting punch
After the example, an article or a news story about you .. This issue Vatsp or Facebook
Share finished putting all our responsibility
After hours Myshynn foot again talking to Gvshyshvn
do not tell me
I Ydvnh of what pass is Hmrahshvn phone
Let's survive
I see the work now
Everyone's phone, he had to see her fear take over
Delete your game Dead
By ready
! tiger
My CPU is damaged
! Oh, my.
thank you
you're welcome
eh! what happened?
I followed him because I connect you to yourself you do?
Oh, my mistake
I realized that I lost because of internal memory
And now, a handful of TV shows and movies blades in it.
Come to make it
Not for now, let me stay
Everything that lives is with people is what animal ..chh
He called himself a certain energy with him
This is a religious word or quote is not quite Seminary
Some scientists even they could see of him also forgive
A zombie aura about one or one and a half meters distance he had Mobility
A Russian doctor named Frank Baranowsky prove it has
Ora migrant Rajan Richmond qvyh
This aura is not a person
The combination of hundreds of thousands of his Prndhst
A big aura! A giant aura of negative energy with a negative mind
! Very negative
Maybe it's just something that will take him to the phone
The city was destroyed opportunity to convert
We're saved because of this Pinto Back
Thank Pinto
And who gave permission to do that, Mr. Minister
..Tv all the old legends is
Which is to save lives
God comes to earth in the form of an avatar
People saved
This time, that God came among us with the face of a machine
And saved us, pinto
If one country's borders to Myjng·h
Is that a shadow that accompanied him Myjng·h?
If the enemy soldier's foot on a bench
Shadow soldiers did exactly the same thing anything?
We honor the soldiers we take, not the shadow of the
What are the doctor and I could shadow
The main task facing Ayshvn do
thank you
Here's someone else who should thank him too
If the heart at the right time that I did not
I mean, I did not have to wake up Oy
Perhaps he could not miss the giant'll get
This person unbroken hst
The government announced ..amrvz
Pinto made a completely legal activity Wasi doctor
And the government, to design another goal for the Army ordered 500 to Pinto
Thankful
!the danger! The request was rejected
! Status: be neutral
Release
: Instagram, Telegram our official media @BollyCineOfficial
Hi scientist
I can to come inside?
Remove throw out all the Gvshyhatvn
This is the last warning for you or destroy you close
Save the birds
You heard?
... yeah Victoria's Secret
Nila neutralizing device ready?
Yes
Is just ... just
The doctor, what am Noble?
Cara What do you mean by this?
I came pretty toy?
What bad I'm not your doctor
Nila turn the machine on
No blue, which qtsh
You can not do something to me, pinto
I've got another body
S citizens, namely body
I ruined my ...
God, are you destroyed Khvdtm
hurry up
Turn up your gaming rig
Tknvlvzhyt Show
Turn, Turn, see
Pinto not think clearly now
I do everything! We both destroyed Gettin '
No doctor, I can not do this, the
To save me, do not destroy the rest
If you kill me, he's gone
I pull Excuse me doctor -
I can not do this, the controls set up to do
Dyvvnhay! Kill me this is my command
Fired Thank You
Because of this bullet may Wasi Gran Away
Bzarym doctor should be Tvrysh
Pinto, what are you doing?
They let me shoot me
Not
Tiger, tiger
Nila soon turn the machine on
Blue, No Cry clans aynkar
Blue, NA Way curt
Pinto, I wish my words! Listened
! Haha
God Excellency connection was interrupted
Plaintiffs
! Alas
Tiger, tiger
Plaintiffs
So bad unbroken avnja
Performing the second edition
The aim was to identify
2.0 .nskhh complete
Notre death was his pleasure
Delete, today you can not fly anymore
Nila, what are you doing there? come here
Aowov
Come on baby
! Else Khfny Could just be me and you.
Now let's kiss was pretty great king
Pinto, after another stop
First, delete the Destroy
He loves you more power
Power is more than you exterminators
You've got the pieces
! Ole world that you now do not you
The first and second these people them all! Kids game.
I Mnhsrbfrdm, Super First
! Not to compare nine games
! You do not understand Pinto
Not
Must explain to her
totally
! Shah wars, the war started
left right
Over 360
Right again
Active obedience is activated -
Where چah?
This is me
!Just me
, Very funny
What's the grand finale was going to Bbynymm half
Dear viewers
You will not be available anymore
Because all of you are going to die
Death is not simple
! But a painful death
Like a bird will be killed one by one, you understand?
You all handset that you use
I will gather them all x
And I use on your own
Want to see?
You ..hy
sorry
Select another one
How?
I'm a fan Shmam
Grand?
I'll open up my
Because of this I am just asking
What difference does it make? Finally you are being a spectator
you're welcome
All components of the ash
* Not * in only five seconds out -
Hiroshima, killing thousands of people, you will get the greatest record
But today, killing guys will mark a new record
You, dear audience .qrarh be part of this historical moment
Dear audience, do not worry
Not going to die
What do you have to look at pure are you? ! Little Bird
I've Pinto redesigned, version 2.0
Gran Wasi your doctor?
I wanted to shoot you myself! What a great sin
!sorry! I was wrong
You are my God.
I do not destroy
Please do forgive me; Bylaaaaaakh
.Halt was magnetically active
All lovers futures, forward to you guys, let's Btrkvnm
Head Khraba zero
You'll never get a bird's
! Hey, I'm Iron Man
Is, is, is Esa
Delete, flying up and escape from here now! Otherwise I Tykht piece
! Any idiot Machin
Why do people help you? ..Ayna to pass the bridge Khrshvn
! Again you have pieces
Version 3.0 has been sent to activate .pyam
*Warning! On the eve of radiation penetrating *! What was happening
This bird khshmgyn
I introduce
I Kvtyam, version 3.0
..Ag·h after injury to the head, the dove
"Noha Isaac Azimovh"
"Little size, but the same sun"
"Rajala, Tu Dioanhi"
"Today if Dyvalyh"
She is the
I can look at you 6 different directions at the same time
Baby, rest of the guys are rolling
Vice-admiral
No, no Vlshvn now
! Oh delete it, you're finally tamed
Go
Pure, the radiation that's coming true stadium Mysvzvnh
But first melting the bird looks
: Instagram, Telegram our official media @BollyCineOfficial
Manerbadtha, Mail
A lion can not get some flies from her disposal
But a few flies almost a milk subdue
Nice job
Thank commander
All the Jashvn are?
Yes
Paliz
Be the explosion
Are, are, are
Sand want me to stand?
Hey, Come after me
Yala
"Rajala, Tu Dioanhi"
"Like you're Diwali"
"Rajala"
"You're the party of hell."
"I am .. from SRM Chlogh"
"Blew up, boom, bang."
Hey you who you are?
How Avmdyn inside? Barin out
: Complete archive of film and TV India Www.Bollycine.org
If we are alive still because of your sacrifices
You got a big risk because you hold our neck
We rescued technology
We make mistakes, but we use it.
... do the right technology: diseases of poverty
Poverty, illiteracy and such over Chyzast
If we Bkhvayym of it for personal profit
Stone rocks for us again repeat such incidents would not give in and strap up
Rajan delete it again comes back you you think?
He's dead, but we still were not changed
I know that was wrong, but his pure word was quite right
Bird life on Earth guarantees OVERSEAS
We rays and frequencies must be reduced
The telecommunications companies should be low
We should not easily happen because of human life at risk
Law must be
This earth is not our father's property
Therefore, this beast that lives ..hr Korea
So far we have just as much right to live on
You are right
We take to save our birds
One also can water them at least Bzarym to eat
Then our future will be better than today
All this will happen
I'm dying to parliament
I guarantee that the state's strict laws in this area
thank you
mmnvnm unbroken
You do not have to thank me
!Oh God
Pinto would have needed to have this system configuration
Do not worry, active security program
! Intelligent
Presented by reference Bollywood cinema Www.Bollycine.org
Are you glad to see that all right, President
Me too
Doctor should screen you can make a report?
! Unbroken co mytvnh
Doctor, are you sure?
Sawing, you do not? -
Go
Thank you, doctor
You are my life, my life, ' "my battery
"do not leave me"
"Do not kill a bit damp"
Translation expertise of our cultural and artistic media Translators: Byngsa and Mystic
"Hey beautiful world car"
"'Ve got the numbers Mybary"
"You play with my engine."
"Hey mate letter"
.. "on the species without blood"
"I can kiss."
"Java Clay New"
"I can fly?"
.. "Ettelaat Salem Ru"
"I can eat?"
"It is, Blait Jmaکn Atobostm"
You are my life, my life, ' "my battery
"do not leave me"
"Do not kill a bit damp"
You are my life, my life, ' "my battery
"do not leave me"
"Do not kill a bit damp"
"Hey beautiful world car"
"'Ve got the numbers Mybary"
"You play with my engine."
"Hey mate letter"
"You feel and feed safety sensor"
"You're my data cable you"
"You are my keys."
Fish are that you "" I filled the neural network
"You're my posts, you're my password"
"You're my exclusive laptop, you are my King."
"You're hot iron"
"Come sure fused together and Shim"
"Pia .. Pia Awa"
"Pia Mگa"
"Mega, Mega Mlkham come up."
"Zero love you"
"Ta were expressed"
You are my life, my life, ' "my battery
"do not leave me"
"Do not kill a bit damp"
You are my life, my life, ' "my battery
"do not leave me"
: Complete archive of film and TV India Www.Bollycine.org
"Hey beautiful world car"
"'Ve got the numbers Mybary"
"You play with my engine."
"Hey mate letter"
.. "on the species without blood"
"I can kiss."
"Java Clay New"
"I can fly?"
.. "Ettelaat Salem Ru"
"I can eat?"
"It is, Blait Jmaکn Atobostm"
You are my life, my life, ' "my battery
"do not leave me"
"Do not kill a bit damp"
You are my life, my life, ' "my battery
"do not leave me"
"Do not kill a bit damp"
First Edited - Farsi Version
01.04.2019 - By BeingSa
Copyright© Bollycine.Org