'O birds, you are all over this world'
'You have spread your wings
right up to Heaven'
'Our earth and our skies
abound in these birds'
'Feathered creatures of our world!'
Any idea what to ask?
'Vanakkam'
We are from Excel Engineering college
Robotic research students
We've got an appointment
to meet Dr Vaseegaran
Please come in
Dude, soooper hyperbola!
Excuse me
You are-
I am Dr Vaseegaran's assistant
- Your name
- Nila
- Beauuuutiful!
- Thanks
Nila...moon!
What?
It's a lie to say
there's no gravity in the moon
- Why?
- You are such a magnetic force!
Your laughter can be my ringtone!
Can I have your number?
11423879
Enough! The whole floor is slippery!
Hello, sir
Please sit down
Doctor, we are mechatronic students
Professor Mithra told us you have
created a new humanoid robot
- Can we take a look at that?
- Sure
This is the new robot I have created
Project Nila
Nice, intelligent, lovely assistant
Humanoid X122018 model
Quantum Core Millenia
X125D Extreme processor
Unlimited Cloud memory
1 Tera hertz speed
Built in simulated Amygdala
This is her MPU
Memory and Power Unit
Works like our heart
MPU!
Synthetic skin
Ultra realistic humanoid
You are such a magnetic force!
What about that phone #?
That's my IMEI #
- Is she also like Chitti, doctor?
- No
Created adhering to Asimov's laws
this is a domestic purpose robot
You can treat her as your friend,
secretary and caretaker
She will be of help to mankind
in all ways and always
Does it have feelings, doctor?
Yes, pre programmed,
customizable, controlled feelings
Is there any chance for Chitti
to resurface again, doctor?
All our present scientific inventions
in the beginning were opposed as dangerous
And labelled as null and void
Bound by time
It became a necessity
in the ensuing years
Chitti will also be a pre requisite one day
Dot!
- Hey Nikita
- Go to hell!
Bulb! Serves you right!
Nikita, hear me out
I acted as if I was flirting with her
just to make you see red
- As if I didn't know she's a robot?
- 'Get lost, liar!'
My Barbie doll
My Snow White princess!
'Shut up and hang up!'
Believe me, I've booked
an Apple watch for your birthday
Sushma, Moksha has got
a new Collection today
You eat and then I'll come over, okay?
My flight was delayed
Inform the clients, I'll be there by-
When I get back from work
I chat with my family nonstop!
We spend quality time you know
You bloody swine!
Harith, can I have my phone?
Daddy has to make an important call
Give me the phone
Don't cry...here
I didn't do anything
What is the bid today
in our chit fund?
Can get Rs 3000
What is this?
Make 'rasam' and potato curry
for dinner, enough
Grandpa!
'Residing in all of that as Me'
'So that Me through this Me'
'Talking to Me'
Dude, this must be
our principal's handiwork!
Where are you, dear?
Coming to the terrace?
What happened?
Our project manager and
prickly 'Jackfruit' Asha
...are hand and glove in this
That's why he promoted her
and sent her abroad on site
He went to get the bore-well man
No sign of him still
Tomorrow is Mahavir Jayanthi
All the shops will be closed
Buy our stuff tonight, okay?
This phone has 4G, Wifi, Bluetooth
plus dual Sim capacity
I'm in Ranganathan street,
jam packed with men all around
Danger
Girlfriend calling
- Hi Sana
- 'Hi scientist sir'
'Wonder of wonders
You picked my call?'
- Sorry, Sana
- 'How many calls?'
'Can't you even pick my call?
Are you that busy?'
'Just for your sake I'm 10,000 km away
and studying here like a lunatic'
'Under the pretext of working on
your project, are you flirting with Nila?'
That's a robot, Sana
'But a female doll, right?'
Don't be mad at me, honey
'I called you 112 times!'
I'll accept your punishment
and kiss you 112 times
'No need 112'
'Just 1 phone-kiss, let me see'
Mua-
Flying kiss?!
Sir, where should I complain
to retrieve my mobile?
All of them are waiting too!
Go and stand in the queue
How can a cell phone fly?
And where will it go?
Who is behind all this?
What is the reason?
'Is a whole gang behind this
or just an individual?'
'This is scary'
Is this a sign our world
will perish as people claim?
Like the ozone hole there is
a black hole in the sky it seems
It has sucked all the phones I believe
Yov! Shut up, man
You're talking as if it's a drainage hole
I'm in the share market
My job is dependent on cell phones
Life is absolutely boring
without WhatsApp and selfies
As soon as I wake up
I take my mobile to the loo
I feel I've lost my hand now!
My husband is working in Qatar
Our long distance romance
is only through cell phone
I've saved my mom's # as 'Amma'
I don't even know her landline # now
I've stored my bank account #,
ATM pin #, password, the whole works
It has personal videos and photos
of my girlfriend and me
What if they are uploaded
on an adult site?
Excuse me, is there a separate section
for Android phones?
For sure! It has been opened
in Parthasarathy temple, go there
Sir, I'm very sentimental
about this cell phone
Do something, sir
How can I take this as a complaint?
- Get lost!
- Sir, please
I had hooked my wedding chain
on my mobile, sir
I lost that too
10 sovereign
Pure gold, sir
No wife to nag, no phone bills
to pay, why don't you relax?
God will be appeased if you do
a redemption ritual in Thirunallar, sir
You and your silly superstitions!
Commissioner sir asked me to meet you
I'll take care, sir
Thank you
Telecom minister is on the line
Sir, even our chief minister
has lost his mobile
He is on another line
Your secretary is right here
I'll handle it, sir
Sir, minister's phone-
I've embedded precious stones all over
0.25 karat, sir
526 stones, sir
Cost 20 million, sir
Somehow retrieve it for us, sir
Okay
He's chief technical officer of BSNL
Ramasubramaniam
I heard you're tracking with Sim card
- What happened, sir?
- It isn't our Govt network alone
All the other networks too
are unable to track even 1 phone, sir
All the cell phones
have been switched off
Every single phone in the city is missing
How can all of them
be switched off?
How is this possible, sir?
'Vanakkam
Headlines'
'Cell phones vanish into thin air
People in panic mode'
'Police department puzzled'
'Chief secretary calls
a special panel to discuss'
'So, doc, I think
you know the situation'
What is this?
What is this phenomenon?
This is strange
I've checked all the NASA studies
and Interpol records
No one has recorded such an event
anywhere in the world
There is no scientific explanation
so far for this rare occurrence
It is so obvious
This is a terrorist attack
They are planning something large-scale
If we can't come up with a reason
...it's our habit to blame
either God or terrorists, right?
Can it be the handiwork of aliens
from a different planet maybe?
No, sir
According to ISRO reports
...no new movements or alien activities
have been recorded in space
Can it be a conspiracy by some
international company in the same field?
I mean, wipe out the present
telephone technology
And bring in a new
scientific know-how
This is a public display
In just 2 days, all the mobiles in the city
flying in mid air like sparrows
There isn't any technology
like this as far as I know
May be someone we know here
who botched up a lousy robot earlier
Some crank scientist
...is messing up with some other invention
in the name of novelty, who knows!
Who is this?
Late Mr Bohra
AIRD director
His son
Dhinendra Bohra
Scientist, he's also in AIRD
as senior director
On the day all the cell phones went missing
...data from INSAT 3D weather satellite
And GSAT 16 communication satellite
This is the visualization
All these dots are cell phones
After a certain distance
the dots vanish into thin air
Cell phones haven't crossed
the troposphere
That is, not crossed
10 km above sea level
If you take the distance into account
...not crossed a radius
of 200 km beyond Chennai
They are all missing
within this sphere somewhere
We are aware of only 4 forces
Gravity, electromagnetic,
strong nuclear, weak nuclear
These 4 won't attract mobile force
I believe this can be
explained scientifically
Dot!
I believe all the phones in this shop
broke the glass panes and flew out
Where is the lorry
with the consignment?
- 'Crossed Nagari'
- Doomed!
Not yet crossed Andhra border?
We've advertised
tomorrow's sale
No one has a cell phone in the city
They will make a beeline to our shop
like devotees in the temple at Tirupati
'Don't worry, it will be
delivered at 4:00 a.m'
You've been saying this
like a broken record!
"I am a modern girl with wanderlust"
Bro, what is that deafening sound?
Songs nowadays are only like this!
Bro...?!
Someone is digging
with a crowbar in our van
We have only cartons
with cell phones in there
Call me, as soon as
the truck reaches here
Have you asked
for police protection?
Paid them, the cops will
be here by 5:00 a.m
What if all the cell phones we get
for our sale tomorrow fly away?
It means we are jinxed
beyond redemption
Not only for us
For the entire city
Lord Muruga
Fountain of knowledge
Bless everyone with Your grace
Wha...what is that noise?
'The truck has arrived, sir'
Who is that?
'Arumugam, sir'
'You asked me to call you
as soon as the truck arrives, right?'
- Where?
- 'To your house of course'
Please cooperate
Go back
- Commissioner Rajendran asked me to come
- Please come in
There is no evidence of human presence
in Jayanth Kumar's murder
As the deceased is a cell phone merchant
...he wanted you to check for clues
His family members were on a pilgrimage
He was all alone
The servants are not aware of anything
No fingerprint or footprint
He died exploding
to minuuute pieces
But there is no evidence
of explosives whatsoever
He had advertised in the papers
about his Mobile Sale in his shop
The truck carrying the load
met with an accident
The entire load went missing
Nothing makes sense, sir
Someone or something doesn't like
the presence of cell phones here
This is silicon, enamel and
polycarbonate dust of 1000s of mobiles
Different brands
manufactured on different dates
Will you believe me if I say
Jayanth Kumar was killed by cell phones?
A cell phone is an assassin?
What do you mean, sir?
All the missing cell phones
have landed here
How did these phones come here?
Where did they go?
We should find out
Dot!
'Hello scientist, what a surprise!
You've called of your own accord'
Sana, I think you would've heard of
all the cell phones disappearing here
To trace them, I've fixed a tracker
in my old phone and I've activated it
'Oh! So am I the guinea pig?'
Not like that, Sana, my phone flew away
before I could send my kisses!
That's why, I thought
I could specially-
'After 3 days, huh?'
'What happened to your landline?
Why didn't you call from that #?'
Phone was engaged, Sana
'Don't pull a fast one'
'Accept you don't remember my # '
'Out of sight, out of mind!'
'Now your whole world is Nila'
She's just like a laptop
'You bet she's on your lap
and you're coddling her 24x7!'
- 'A duet on top of all this!'
- Shut up!
'If I speak the truth,
should I shut up?'
Stop nagging me
This phone may also fly away!
Mu-
Gone with the wind!
Hey! You're watching too much TV!
Nila, activate EMR
Activating EMR
What is happening?
Are they looking for a bomb?
- You search that side
- Okay, boss
Thanks, Nila
Why thank a laptop?!
They are discussing about
your issue inside, wait
Sir, Onicel owner Manoj Lulla is coming
He's such a pain!
Good morning
- Is he in?
- Yes, ji, go in, ji
2G...!
Talk to you later
- Please sit down
- I don't need any pacifying
What are you up to?
Does a Govt exist or not?
Look, Mr Lulla
Govt and God are one and the same
If you believe, they exist
If not, they don't
But you ensure your palms
are greased promptly, eh?
Without exception it has snatched
all my cell phone towers
Destroyed all the microwave emitters
Not just yours, sir
Microwave emitters of all other
networks have been destroyed too
Uprooted the vendors' towers
they had rented as well
Everyone is in a state of shock
You saw them, right?
What should I see?
My loss runs in millions
If this continues, in 3 months
I'll be in the streets
We are watching
from all angles
Not enough if you just watch
We've paid through our nose for you
and your party during the election
You should be standing out in the open
with your arms stretched like a tower
Don't get tense
This isn't your problem alone
It concerns our national security
Everybody is perplexed
and in a state of panic
Yesterday in our cabinet meeting
we've requested military aid
Even if you need a battalion
to guard each tower, we'll do it
Don't worry
Don't think you can appease me
like how you tackle the general public
I give you 1 week grace time
By then things should
go back to normalcy
I must start my business again
Otherwise the next upload in Wiki Leaks...
...will be yours!
5th force
The scientific world is still into
extensive research about this force
The way it works
How to measure it
Our knowledge is zilch
This could be the 1st evidence
for the existence of the 5th force
We can't explain this force based
on our knowledge of science
Using the amenities at our disposal
...we can't combat it either
That's why we've requested
our military to step in
Sir, it's a huge force
I saw it with my own eyes
If you ask the military
to combat it
...you will only face
enormous loss of life
What should we do then?
To combat it effectively
we need a super power
We need exceptional intelligence
We need a man with
the boon of immortality
A man who will never die?
Does a person like that exist?
Chitti
The Robot!
We must reactivate him
Dot...!
I'm waiting
No...impossible
It's against law, sir
Our court has banned that robot
Has been dismantled too
It went out of control
and killed many lives
Immense loss of property as well
You are all well aware
...if we bring it back
...it won't die
It will massacre all of us
Everyone is aware who was responsible
for that robot's drastic change
This time I'll ensure
such a blunder does not occur
Sir, this is Mr Vaseegaran's conspiracy
He wants to use this critical situation
and reactivate his invention
He wants to make money by
selling it to multinational companies
Now you decide
Have we assembled here
to save the people?
Or for Vaseegaran's advertising?
Okay, so you come up with a solution
Let's...think about it
That's why we are here
Sir, my suggestion is based
purely on good intentions
This is the start
of an apocalypse
If we don't prevent it now, we'll be
wiped out en masse, only Chitti can save us
Mr Vaseegaran
We can't flout a court order blatantly
The process required
to do so is very tedious
I must pass an ordinance
in the Parliament
Opposition parties should cooperate
- Not possible
- It is possible, sir
A minister can easily take
some emergency decisions
We can convince the court
by explaining in detail later
Such a rule exists
But if that robot kills some people?
Who will take the responsibility?
Should I?
Or our minister?
- Such a situation won't arise, sir
- Why not?
That's a machine
We can't predict
when it may screw up
If it does something drastic
I'll be held responsible
Let's forget Chitti
Suggest some other option
Military is the only other feasible option
Let's go ahead with that
Request and the order
will be released by today
Do the needful
Hello...?
So
Plan collapsed?
Dhina, what is all this?
You are a scientist
You are well aware
Of course
But I won't let it happen
I'll never allow you to bring
that nitwit Chitti back to life
What do you have against me?
You murdered my dad
Me...?
That Chitti
Your alter ego
That is also you!
I'll never forget it
'Yov! Lulla'
'I am the minister, I say'
'Your tower is back in its place
You saw it on the way, right?'
'All the phones are back in the city'
'You can go back
to your business, man'
Where are you speaking from?
'Right here'
I got drenched to the skin
No phone to even call Gopal
Even I got stranded
near Taramani-
Nila, go up
Hack it open, Nila
Boss, according to my rules
hacking is illegal
Isn't this wrong?
This will come under ethical hacking
Exception...do what I say
I understand, boss
'If a handful of people benefit'
'...nothing is wrong', right?
Where did you get
this 'Nayagan' dialog from?
I should know all that humans like
As per your adaptive learning
you've programmed in me
Human beings have
only 4 preferences
TV, Cinema, food and gossip
Easy!
"Iron heart sprouting for the 1st time?"
"Is it an invitation of first love divine?"
"Iron heart blossoming for the 1st time?"
Shut up!
'Leaving from airport
Battalion # 121 proceeding to spot'
Entire state is under military control
People need not panic
Technology related to cell phone
networks in all the places
...is being attended to
on a war-front emergency basis
With military protection...
...arrangements have been made
to restart sales of cell phones
Very soon, people can start
using their cell phones as usual
- Hey, Balu
- Sir...?
Call the minister and ask him
to provide us military protection
We have 4 police vans
round the clock stationed here, sir
If you look at the 303 rifles they have
even street dogs won't be scared
We need AK 47, man
You saw how Manoj Lulla whom we met
2 days ago was squeezed like juice, right?
I was the one who signed the order
to revive cell phone service in the city
Looking at the current situation
looks like I'll be the next juice!
Call for the military immediately
Juice for you, my dear
- Is security in position?
- We've assigned 2 men, sir
- Enough strength in front?
- Yes, sir
'Attack in Porur
Company on high alert'
SIR!
Sir...!
Aiya...!
What happened?
That cell phone gang uprooted
all the towers in Porur
Wiped out our military force it seems, sir
No one knows where
that horde has vanished now
Yov! Porur is quite close to this place
Double the protection
round our house
A whole battalion is alert, sir
Ask them to shut all gates,
doors and windows
Not even the smallest hole
should be exposed
Sir, everything has been closed
Including the computer's Windows!
They are throwing stones at us
Sir, this isn't a stone
It's your cell phone
Your missing cell phone
Come and see for yourself
'True that!'
All the precious stones are intact
How can you underestimate a minister?
Technology is in the palm of my hands!
That's why it has got scared
and returned only my mobile!
Who is this 'Unni Krishnan' calling?
It's an unknown #, sir
Good morning
Yov! Call the military
- Ask them to shoot this sparrow
- Okay, sir
Go...go...go
Get out!
Sir, this way please
- How is Mr Vairamoorthy?
- Critical, sir
He's unable to breathe
- Something is blocking his windpipe
- What is it?
Don't know exactly, sir
His secretary is equally dumbfounded
- Did you scan his body?
- We did, sir
All the reports are normal
But he is unable to breathe, sir
- What happened, doctor?
- He is no more
Whaat?!
Phone...phone
All the phones flew away, sir
Landline, man
Hello, I am Home minister
Vijay Kumar speaking
Activate that robot Chitti immediately
Today
Right now
How can you ask as if you're ordering
'idli' and 'vada' as Take away?
It is a ban by the court, sir
I can't flout the rules of the court
I'll handle all those formalities
1st activate Chitti at once
How is it possible immediately?
An ordinance has to be
passed in the Parliament
'The Opposition has to cooperate'
The process is extremely complicated, sir
40 members of the Parliament
will favor us, sir
I'll handle all that
It's a machine, sir
We don't know when it will malfunction
Who will shoulder the responsibility
if it kills someone? You or me?
Yov! Don't seek revenge
oblivious of time or situation
It went into our Telecom minister's mouth
God knows which part of me it will target
I'll take all the responsibility
Satisfied?
Dot!
I came here at midnight
There was a queue right then
I haven't got the phone as yet
and she wants me to top up!
Without cell phones, our life is like
'A Few Pages Missing In The Middle'
Okay, what if the cell phones
fly away again?
I'm as sharp as a needle, you see
Take a look
You've fixed it like the chained tumbler
in the railway station!
Sir, for a while I was
so relaxed without cell phones
No ringtones to bug me daily
I'm lifting my head to see the world
I talk to my children
I visit my friends face to face
- Great feeling, eh?
- Then why the hell is he here?
What to do?
A cell phone is like one's wife
Damn if she exists
Darn if she doesn't!
Become a habit!
Yes!
Chitti, you're back?
The way I fell I thought
my skull will blow to bits
Thank you, Chitti
Holy crow!
Chitti to Control
- 'Control to Chitti'
- Assemble at TTK road junction
What is this?
Integral space research centre
That space research centre isn't active now
Research is no longer
conducted there
Only 2 technicians are left
In 1964, head of Atomic Commission
Dr Homi Baba inaugurated this centre
Call Dr Sam
Hello, Sam here
Dr Sam, I'm Vasi
I need this information now, urgent
What is that space research centre
in sector II Phase XIV?
Vasi, keep this confidential
To find out if life exists
in other planets just like us on earth
...signals are sent from many parts
of the world to outer space
That is one such place
from where signals are sent
What kind of signals are being sent?
There are good forces and bad forces
co existing in this world
We send only positive signals
to outer space
Because only positive energy
present in space
...should be aware
of our presence here
Thank you very much, Sam
Chitti, play that visual
in Kirlian mode
Look at that
If that cell phone bird is scared
of the positive signals from the emitters
...there is some negative force
embedded in it
By negative force
you mean from another planet?
Freeze it
No, this is some negative force
present only on our earth
This is a human face
It looks very familiar to me
Nila, I want all the recent
abnormal events in Thirukazhukundram
Most importantly
details of the deceased a.s.a.p
Doctor, this resembles the emitter
we saw in that space research centre
- Exactly
- What is your plan?
You know by now
You tell me
If it is a human negative energy
that is creating the 'mobile' force
...it has no physical form
But only the aura
that surrounds the human body
Aura...?
Atoms in a human body
consist of neutrons and electrons
The micro photon particles
that emanate from it is called aura
It is a thin layer around the body
not visible to the human eye
Aura of a person who is alive
is charged positive
A dead person's aura
will be charged negative
We must destroy that negative charge
The only way to succeed is to send
a more powerful positive charge towards it
And neutralize its energy
Aura of a deceased person
is micro photon minus
We must send micro photon plus
Add plus to minus
it becomes zero
- Am I right, doctor?
- Exactly, Chitti
This photon synthesizer
generates micro photon plus
See
I've created the same positive rays here
similar to the Research centre
This is 10 times stronger than
any negative energy known to mankind
We can neutralize
the negative energy for sure
Wow! Great
Boss, here are the details you asked for
73 people died last year
in Thirukazhukundram
Only 18 unnatural death
2 murders
4 suicides
Is any death connected to a cell phone?
A lorry driver died in an accident
using his mobile while driving
Because her 'hot' photos
went viral through her mobile
...a girl consumed poison
One man died hanging himself
in a cell phone tower
- Date?
- April 7th
The next day cell phones started vanishing
Oh my God!
Now I'm getting a clearer picture
Chitti, immediately
install this in AIRD bus
We are leaving for Thirukazhukundram
Doctor, we got it
I found all the phones
Nila, bring the bus
to the rear end of the house
CHITTI!
Nila, fix the cryostat, quick!
My God!
Pakshi Raja...!
Nice DP
This is a war between
the entire mankind and me
You are not a human being
Don't interfere
- Run away
- Running away isn't in my software at all
I have been reactivated
only to protect human beings
My primary task is to destroy you!
Pakshi Raja, why are you
so furious with the human race?
Why are you behaving like this?
What do you need?
This is a pied cuckoo
Biological name is Jacobin cuckoo
In Northern India...
...the monsoon season starts
only when this species migrates
If this species doesn't show up...
...there will be no rainfall
in that year for the entire region
Till date no one knows
the mystery behind this
Even in our mythology
it is referred as 'rain bird'
Carry out research on this
Sure, sir
Wow...!
Sir, your photo is
on the cover page
It was published a year ago
Sir, how did you get
interested in birds?
Actually the other way about
The birds evinced interest in me!
'When I was born
I wasn't breathing'
'My body had turned blue'
'Even the doctor gave up hope
and said the baby is dead'
I'll sign and you finish
all the formalities
Get the death certificate
and take the baby
'Don't know if it was an accident
or something else'
'But everyone exclaimed
it was a huge miracle'
'My grandma used to say'
'God came in the guise of
a sparrow and resurrected you'
'I still remember'
'When I was young, early in the morning
the tiny sparrow will fly into my room'
'...keep chirping cheerfully
and going around the fan in a circle'
"To the sun's ray at dawn that glitter
a warm welcome your wings you flutter"
"As the sun slides down yonder deep
you caress the branches to sleep"
"With your pitter patter dainty feet
'kolam' you draw as an aesthetic treat"
"Today you make me yearn
To fly like you I want to learn"
"Flock of birds in flight"
"I stood listening
to your musical chirping"
'I decided right then'
'My life will be dedicated
to birds and only birds'
"Flock of birds in flight"
"Oho! A flight of birds in sight"
"I stood listening
to your musical chirping"
"A host of sparrows
A flight of swallows"
"I wish to hear
your tweet and twitter"
"No language or religion, you fly at ease
Any place is your home, as you please"
"No language, no religion, you roam
You affirm any place is your home"
"You claim even weeds to be
your kith and kin in reality"
"You form a swing in mid-air
to play with the wind out there"
"You make a deep impact in people
to whom laughter isn't easy or simple"
"My precious life, my cherished creed
A heart like yours is needed indeed"
"Even if the world is wiped out extensively
an urge to protect you surges effusively"
"Swiftly on a flying spree
in the skies carefree"
"Fly without any boundary"
That's why I studied
ornithology with passion
I became an ornithology professor too
'Pon ulagaaleero'
'Bhuvanam muzhudhaleero'
'Nannaya pullinangaal'
These are lines from
Nammazhwar's Thiruvaimozhi
This is the meaning
O' birds, you are all over this world
You have spread your wings
right up to Heaven
Our earth and our skies
abound in these birds
When compared to the weight
of the human race on earth...
...weight of the birds en masse
is almost 100 times more
Birds eat 1000 times more food
than what humans consume
If they didn't feed on worms
...not even 1 green leaf
will be left on earth
Human beings won't
get any food at all
Because insects are
1000 times more than birds!
So if human beings have to
survive on this earth...
...birds also should be alive
Sir, of late birds flocking to
the bird sanctuary in Vedanthangal
...has dwindled
What is the reason, sir?
When I was young, we used to wake up
only to the chirp of sparrows
'You don't get to see any sparrow
in the city nowadays, sir'
'Only in 1996...'
'...cell phones were
introduced in India'
'In a gradual and continuous process
birds have decreased only after this'
'Particularly sparrows'
It is called Arctic Tern
This small bird weighing just 50 gm
...migrates every year
from the Arctic region
...flying 12000 km
to our Vedanthangal
...and returns
A bird doesn't have a map or radar
From within its head, it absorbs
all micro rays from the sky
And using cryptochrome formation
...it steers in the right direction
'That is the bird's sole strength'
Now we've filled the sky with radiation
from numerous cell phone towers
So the cryptochrome formation
in the bird's head is shattered
And eliminated completely
'Not knowing where they are heading'
'...birds lose their way and
their entire species is becoming extinct'
'To the birds, it is equal
to losing their sanity'
In addition, because of the radiation...
...shells aren't being formed
on the eggs of these birds
Their eggs resemble a layer of skin
The eggs break when
the mother bird is incubating
In reality, men also suffer
from these repercussions
Many get afflicted by ******
********* may be on the rise
******** will increase
Above all
Depression
Schizophrenia
Alzheimer's etc-
Higher % of mental disorder
All these symptoms
are obvious right now
Mr Pakshi Rajan
What is your solution?
Why do we use cell phone now?
Just gossip and trivialities
Let's control that
Why do we need so many
cell phones and towers?
Let us reduce that
Let us pass a law as to who, why and
for how long a cell phone can be used
Has this chap lost it?
Is he mad?
Instead of the current high frequency
cell phone technology
...let us invent
a safer technology
Until then let us shut down
90% of the cell phone towers in India
Please speak a little loudly
Sir, please excuse me
'Save bird, save earth'
'Save bird
Save earth'
'Don't kill, don't kill'
'Don't kill birds'
'Save birds save birds'
'Save birds
Save earth'
'Don't kill, don't kill'
'Don't kill birds'
'Stop...stop'
'Radiation
Pollution'
'Stop...stop'
'Radiation Pollution'
'Don't kill'
Are they all jobless?
When the sun rises, they swing placards
defending dogs, cats, crows and sparrows
Can't you chase them?
'Refusing to leave, sir
Very insistent about meeting you'
Tell me
What's your problem?
What is the frequency rate
permitted by TRAI?
in your towers at present?
Birds flying in the sky are being
destroyed in their fetus stage by you
Hello mister, listen
We strictly follow the rules of
Telecom Regulatory Authority of India
Already subscribers complain
'No signal in the bathroom or basement
Skype doesn't work in the lift'
Do you know in these 3 months
2000 customers have...
...switched to other networks?
Don't lie
In your disgusting competition
just to retain your subscribers
...you are increasing the frequency rate
to suit your needs as you wish
Now it is well over the danger limit
Because of the heavy radiation
the entire species of birds
...the bird kingdom is dying
without a trace
You aren't one bit bothered
You are exaggerating
Birds becoming extinct
due to cell phone radiation
...has no scientific proof or backing
You know that?
If that is so
come with me
Stand under your cell phone tower
for just 24 hours
I will prove it!
You get out
You asked for scientific proof, right?
I'll provide it
Get out, man
Write to the Press & Media
Hold placards and
protest in the hot sun
I don't care
Out
Get out!
Nonsense!
Move it a little bit upwards
Hey...listen!
What is this, sir?
Stop it
I'm telling you
There are houses nearby
Many birds flock around
- Stop everything
- Hey, old man
Are we building a nuclear plant here?
It's only a cell phone tower
Hereafter you'll get good signal
on your phone, move aside
Come on...come
- What is it, sir?
- Ramasamy
I repeatedly told you
about birds dying
You were also worried
- But now...?
- What can I do, sir?
Agriculture is no longer profitable
Insects kill all my yield
I became a pauper
buying insecticides
Primary reason for that is
the increased death rate of birds
Only birds eat insects
If birds die...
...insects will increase
beyond control
Whatever the reason, I don't
have the strength to be a farmer
This is the only income
I can get from this land
Why should you sell your land
to a man who kills birds?
People are dying
of starvation here
And you're bothered
about birds dying!
Don't pester me
Attend to your work
Move aside
'Ladies and gentlemen'
'Stop using cell phone'
Every cell phone used is encased
with the blood of thousands of birds
Each cell phone is a sparrow's coffin!
Save birds
- Come here
- Yes, sir
Who is this man?
Disturbing all our customers
- Chase him away
- Okay, sir
What happened?
Ladies and gentlemen
Don't use cell phones
Here...read this
Aiyaiyo!
I have given many petitions
in many levels many times
'No one has taken any action'
Oh!
Is this why we don't see
any sparrows at all?
When I was a kid
...they used to flock around my house
It was a feast for sore eyes
I've played with those birds
When I grew up, I have
even fried and feasted on them
A real treat for the taste buds
- Crispy, like quail fry
- Super, sir
And that concoction made with it
What an aphrodisiac!
It isn't available nowadays
What is this?
I'm talking of ensuring birds live
and you're relishing killing them
What else do you want me to do?
Shall we start a Sparrow Welfare Board?
You can be elected as the chairman
1st take strict action against networks
which exceed their allotted frequency
Cancel their license
Then?
Grant permission only 2 networks
following regulations to the T
What are you saying?
We boast of a population of 1.3 billion
Shouldn't we reach all of them?
Shouldn't every area receive signal?
Cell phone is the foundation for everything
The world will come to a standstill
if mobiles don't work for an hour
How much time is saved
because of this gadget?
Business has developed
Industries have prospered
Because he's hungry will anyone
chop his own hand and eat it?
Same holds good for the progress
we attain by killing birds
If a 30 gm sparrow can't live
depending on us
...then how can we boast of
this technology and progress?
America is a bigger nation than India
It has only 4-5 networks
China is the most populated
country in the world
Only 3 networks are used
But here?
More than 10
You accept ****** from everyone
And allow networks to flourish
flouting all the rules
You're letting your tongue run, eh?
You seem educated
I was lenient because you're a big shot
You're analysing politics, huh?
Okay, let me counteract
We work based only
on rules and regulations
Only by adhering to international rules
cell phone service is allotted
File a case in court
if you have any doubts
Clear out now
Don't get angry
Please listen to me
I was patient for so long, eh?
Go...go to court
You'll get a verdict after many years
Prime minister says
I must meet the common man
'And I get caught
with such crackpots'
Court officials are coming
to check radiation frequency
Make sure it is well within the limit
'From multiples tests conducted
it has been found...'
'...only adequate radiation
has been channelized into cell phones'
'It has not been proved scientifically
that birds are affected by cell phones'
'Therefore Pakshi Rajan's case
has been adjourned'
Pakshi Rajan, whatever you say
is just and right
But killing humans is wrong
They killed countless flocks of birds
Isn't that a crime?
You'll label human life differently
In what way are birds' lives inferior?
Why do you kill innocent people
for the fault of a handful of men?
Who is 'innocent'?
Every individual who owns
a cell phone is a murderer
How I yelled my throat hoarse
How many streets
I would've walked begging
How many feet I fell
pleading not to use cell phones
Did even a single soul
pay heed to my pleas?
They read about this in newspapers
Watch the News on TV
And then...
...exclaim 'oh'!
Do sparrows die only due to
radiation from cell phones?
'How sad!'
'Poor things, no?'
Just for 5 minutes
make clucking sounds
Share that article and video clipping
in WhatsApp and Facebook
Thinking their duty is over and
it was their good deed for the day
They go back to
their cell phones, blockheads!
I won't let this go
I won't spare even a single person
who owns a cell phone
Hereafter
Cell phone is everyone's Yama!
Just watch, people should panic and
run for their lives as soon as they see it
Pakshi, you've reached your stop
Get into the bus
Chitti!
Oh my God!
- Thanks
- Welcome
Hey! What is this?
You've fixed your MPU in me
Oh! By mistake
I was wondering why
my core memory was corrupt
Punch dialogs
Vadivelu comedy
'Vani Rani' episodes
Banana flower fritters!
# star-darling and dance-king
All kinds of stuff
Come, lie down
I will fix it
No need
Let it be
Aura
Every human, beast,
inanimate object
Even every place has an aura
This aura invisible to the eye pertains
not only to spirituality but science too
With the help of a Kirlian camera
we can take photos of an aura
Ordinary people have an aura
3 to 4 feet thick
Some sages have an aura
spreading over 50 feet
Russian scientist
Dr Frank Baranowski has proved this
Pakshi Rajan's aura is enormous
It isn't the aura of
an individual man alone
Aura of 1000s of birds
which were destroyed
A giant ball of negative energy
With a mind
A very angry mind
This maybe a form of 5th force
It has controlled all the cell phones
It would've destroyed
our city given a chance
We succeeded only because
of Chitti's reappearance
Thank you, Chitti
I thank all of you
who have been a source of support
In our ancient classics
...we have heard many stories of God
descending on earth to destroy demons
Lord Shiva Himself came as a robot
to save us from a fate worse than death
I invite that Iron warrior Chitti
on to the dais to share a few words
When a warrior fights
his shadow battles along with him
When the warrior pierces and kills
the enemy, the shadow will follow suit
So will we praise and
garland the shadow?
He is real
I am his shadow
All glory and praise to
that God who created me
Thank you
At this juncture I must thank
and mention a specific name
At the right moment
parting with the heart
I mean, giving the MPU
...if I had not been activated
I couldn't have destroyed the evil force
The name is...
Nila
At this wonderful moment
a piece of good news for you
Chitti who has been created
by Dr Vaseegaran
...has been approved by our Govt
An order has been passed this morning
...to create 500 Chitti robots
for our Indian army
Thank you
Hi, scientist
May I come in?
Irresponsible people
Trash your cell phones
This is your last chance
Otherwise...
...death is certain!
I'm not the Mahesh
who got tagged in # MeToo, dear!
Check your phone properly
Why don't you-
Didn't you hear what I said?
I always wear Victoria Secret, you know
Including the latest one-
- Nila, is photon synthesizer set?
- Yes
'Hey! Pub closes at midnight'
'Let's go tomorrow'
'Hey! Stop...stop'
Doctor, what happened to you?
Why are you behaving like this?
Welcome, my dear 'nuts & bolt toy'
I'm not your doctor!
Nila, turn on the neutralizer
No...!
Nila, stop it!
You can't do anything to me, Chitti
I have a body now
Dr Vaseegaran's body!
If you destroy me...
...it is the same as
you killing your God!
Now...
...can you turn it on please?
Show off your technology
Turn it on
Switch it on, damn you!
Chitti...!
Don't hesitate
Turn it on
Destroy me
He'll be destroyed along with me
No, doctor
I can't do that
Chitti, thinking you are saving me
don't exterminate the entire human race
Kill me
Destroy him
- Kill me
- Sorry, doctor
Human emotion fed by you
is stopping me
Moron! This is my order, kill me
No, hold fire
If you shoot, only Vaseegaran
will die unnecessarily
Can't kill Pakshi Rajan
Chitti, why are you stopping them?
- Let them shoot me
- No
Chitti
Aiyo! Chitti
Nila, turn on the neutralizer
'Come on, quick!'
Nila...NO!
'Don't do that'
Shut up!
This is my order
Switch it on
Aiyo!
What you've done
is really foolish, Chitti
Your 'call' is disconnected!
Chitti...?
What a pity!
Chitti...Chitti
Chit-
Chitti
Nila, go right now and-
"Earth shattering cyclone blows
today right now"
"He's gonna break, break, break
Break it down!"
"Pakshi Raja gonna destroy everyone"
"As quick as a stride
destruction of a different kind"
"Illusionary tricks galore
Danger! Caution all the more"
"He's going to eat you alive"
"Run for your life"
"I am a bird of prey waiting to eat you
Feather-man who got into you head to toe"
"Pakshi Raja!"
"King of birds...Pakshi Raja"
"I have the souls of birds many
to seek revenge, flocking within me"
"King of birds...Pakshi Raja"
Unique feeling of real joy
to die and get reactivated!
Pakshi
Unlike your name
you can't fly any longer!
Hey, Nila...!
Why are you standing right there?
True to your name,
Nila should orbit the earth, eh?
Come...come...come
Come on, baby
Wow...!
Only 2 tasks of Vaseegaran
in his research are worthy of praise
One is me
The other is you!
What are you looking at?
Come on
Give a beautiful kiss
to your great king, baby
Stop the play, Chitti
We must 1st destroy Pakshi
Because he is even more powerful than you
He's committing atrocities multi-fold
He was able to shred
even you into million parts
Now...
...he's number 1 here
Not you
Hey, this # 1 and # 2
are all child's play
I am the only one
Super one!
No comparison, understand?
I understand, Chitti
We must make him understand
You bet I will
The king of birds
The battle is on!
Left
Right
Head
'Kamoshka'
Activate command mode
Command mode activated!
What is this?
It's me
Mini me!
So cute
'What a game!'
'And now it's Half time
at the IFL finals'
'We'll handle that later
Attend to your call'
Dear subscribers
You are going to be
not reachable from now
'Because...'
...all of you will die now
'By no means an ordinary death'
'Radiation death!'
You will all die in groups
like how the sparrows collapsed
'Don't you get it?'
I'll combine the radiation
from the cell phones all of you use
I'll download it on all of you
Want to see a demo?
Hey, you...!
Ex...excuse me
Why don't you select someone else?
Why?
I'm on your side
How...?
I was the one who released you
At least for that reason
let me go please
So what?
You are a subscriber too, man
Don't hurt me please
"He's going to eat you alive"
"I am a bird of prey waiting to eat you
Feather-man who got into you head to toe"
"Pakshi Raja"
You will meet your end in this way,
a fate worse than ordinary death
"Pakshi Raja"
In just 5 seconds, 70,000 people
were killed in Hiroshima
Till date that was the world record
Today...80,000 men and women
A new record!
You are going to be part
of a historic moment
Dear subscribers!
Dear subscribers
Don't panic
You are not the ones
who are about to die
A small bird
What are you looking at Pakshi?
I am Chitti
Reloaded
Version 2.0!
Doctor, is that you?
Did I shoot you?
Did I try to kill you?
My God! I was about
to commit a grave sin
Doctor, please don't harm me
You are my creator
Don't rip me apart with your own hands
Forgive me and let me go
Please
Fat hopes!
Vasi...!
Come, you selfie bots!
I will set your screens on fire
"I bow down to like, no man
I bow down, I say, 'no damn' "
"I stand tall, alone I stand
I cow down like, 'No man' "
"Are you ready?
Take a shot"
"I am the only one"
"There is no comparison
'cos I am Super Super one"
"I'm out to get you
Let ya wreck ya self"
"See me coming out"
"10000 fighters by my side
I'm about to shoot 'em down"
"I'm the only one you see"
Zero balance!
Shoot that sparrow
Hey bird man!
Iron man!
I'm just a driver
Let me go
Pakshi!
You had better scatter
and scoot from here
Otherwise I'll pluck
every single feather out
You moron of a machine!
Why are you fighting
for these ungrateful men?
When you've served their purpose
they will rip your nuts apart!
Hey! What's happening?
Yayayay...angry bird!
Why are you staring?
I am Kutti!
The microbot
Version 3.0
If you disturb my boss
your dove will be
Dodo!
"I am Isaac Asimov's grandson, buddy"
"I am a warrior, size of a turkey berry"
"O bird of prey
You're a goner, I say"
"It's 'Festival of lights' for us today"
It is said a bird can look
in 6 different directions
Pakshi, won't you see?
Microbots
No...no
Hey! Don't do this
Maintain that same panic
"Birdie got caught-o?"
Bow bow
"Feathers fell apart-o?"
"3.0"
"Swarmed all over you?"
Pakshi, if you breach this stadium
with your radiation
...1st victims will be
only your birds!'
Microbots, go
"3.0"
"I am a cannon 6" tall
You're a radish, that's all"
"I am an automated masterpiece
I tricked you with zetabyte-ease"
"I am the evil mosquito Ranguski
Ready to send you to the cemetery"
"Itsy-bitsy, I'm snuff powder heady
I'm into your nostril, deal with me"
A lion can't touch a mosquito, big birdie!
But if mosquitoes set their minds
they can chase the lion to its doom
Cuckoo!
Good job, 3.0
Thank you, commander
- Microbots positioned?
- All set
Pakshi
Have a blast!
Should these doves also explode?
Hey beep
Follow me
Come on, bots
"O eagle, you're a goner, I say"
"It's 'Conquest of good over evil' today"
"Bird of prey
It's a jolly day"
"You are a guest in hell any which way"
"People's favorite
'Podimas' minuute"
"If I burst, it will be a wrecker
like a boom-boom cracker"
Hey! Who are you?
What are you doing here?
This is restricted area
Get out!
You are the reason
we are alive today, Vaseegaran
What an enormous risk you've taken
and saved all of us!
Technology saved us
But we are the ones
misusing technology
We should eliminate poverty
with the help of technology
Eradicate diseases
Promote education
If we use it for personal comforts and
fuelling our greed, it's only doomsday
Will...will that Pakshi Rajan reappear?
He is dead and gone
But if we continue this way
another 'evil force' will erupt
Even if Pakshi Rajan's actions were wrong
...there was truth in his words
If human beings should live on earth
birds should also co exist
Control radiation
Reduce networks
Pass a rule, no technology should affect
any living thing, human, bird or beast
This earth doesn't belong only to us
Everyone should realize it belongs
to all the living creatures here
You are right
Ensure birds are not destroyed
At least provide water for birds
to drink during our scorching summers
That's enough to refresh
and revitalize your minds
All this will happen, Vaseegaran
I'll bring this to the notice
of our Parliament
I'll make sure this happens
Thank you, Vaseegaran
Thanks, Nila
Why are you thanking your shadow?
Oh God!
We have to remove
that red chip from Chitti
Don't worry, boss
To be on the safe side I activated it
after doing an auto-eject program
Smaaart!
Good to see you alright, doctor
Me too, Chitti
Doctor, all the robots and I have to report
in the headquarters at Delhi today
Can I leave, doctor?
Take Nila with you
subtitled by rekhs
assisted by harini & pradeep
Doctor, how can I leave you like this and-
I can take care of myself
'Respect for love?!'
GO...!
Thanks, doctor
"My love, my life, my battery
Don't go away from me"
"My sole soul friend, my battery
Don't decrease even a bit, dearie"
"O' damsel from the world of machinery
You shower love through numbers binary"
"You lean on my engine-body
and please me in rhapsody"
"Hey! My exquisite electric wifey!"
"Shall I kiss your bloodless cheeks, miss?"
"And make a new Java rose bloom in bliss?"
"Shall I feed you
with data brand new?"
"Hey! I am your 'bus conductor' true"
# My magic metallic heart, my battery
Don't ever leave me #
# My sole soul mate, my battery
Don't decrease even a bit, dearie #
# My gripper, my gears, my battery
Don't go away from me #
# My wonder wheels, pistons, my battery
Don't decrease even a bit, dearie #
"Metal maiden from the world of machinery
You embrace me with numbers binary"
"You throttle my engine to flirt with me"
# Hey! My wifey animated by electricity #
# You are my sensor's sense
Plus its food and essence #
# You're the data miracle
spreading through my cable #
# My engine is driven by your magic spell #
"My every neuron cell
is your 'mass' and moon as well"
"My username is you
My password too"
"You're my genie
special laptop Rajini"
# My dear iron flower, steel sweety-softy"
"Shall we melt to unite today, hottie?"
# You're my Alpha, my beginning #
# You're my Omega, my ending #
# Love you from zero to infinity #
# My love, my life, my battery
Don't go away from me #
# My sole soul friend, my battery
Don't decrease even a bit, dearie #
# My gripper, my gears, my battery
Don't ever leave me #
# O' angel from the world of machinery
You shower love through numbers binary #
"You lean on my engine-body
and tease me in rhapsody"
# Hey! My ravishing robot-wifey! #
# Shall I kiss your bloodless cheeks, miss? #
"I'll make a new Java rose bloom in bliss? #
# Shall I feed you
with data brand new? #
# Hey! I am your 'bus conductor' true #
# My wires, my world, my battery
Don't ever leave me #
# My cyborg companion, my battery
Don't decrease even a bit, dearie #
# My beloved bot, my battery
Don't go away from me #
# My bold and beautiful bot, my battery
Don't decrease even a bit, dearie #
Helloooo, Sana sweetie
'So much has happened
Why didn't anyone tell me?'
- 'Not even 1 phone call, text or e-mail'
- Sana, listen to me
'I am almost dying in fear
Where did that wretched Nila disappear?'
Can't this phone fly away now?!
Hey senior!
Why are you so dazed?
Were you scared?
Just for laughs!
Hey! Who are you?
I am Kutti
Compressed version
3.0...!
Your grandson
Muah!
"O eagle, you're a goner I say"
"It's 'Festival of lights' for us today"
"Bird of prey
It's a jolly day"
"You are a guest in hell any which way"
"People's favorite
'Podimas' minuute"
"If I burst, it will be a wrecker
like a boom-boom cracker"
"Boss, I am a microbot"
"If you get caught
dude, you're kaput!"
"3.0"
"I am a cannon 6" tall
You're a radish, that's all"
"I am an automated masterpiece
I tricked you with zetabyte-ease"
"I am a cannon 6" tall
You're a radish, that's all"
"I am an automated robot
I conned you without a doubt"
"I am the evil mosquito Ranguski
Ready to send you to the cemetery"
"Itsy-bitsy, I'm snuff powder heady
I'm into your nostril, deal with me"