Previously on "The Flash"...
&nbsp
Next time you decide to release
my friend's inner ice demon,
&nbsp
you do it sometime in July.
I was trying to save her life, Cisco.
&nbsp
When I became Killer Frost,
Savitar appeared to me
and showed me the way.
&nbsp
If the answers that
we need to stop Savitar
&nbsp
and save you are in the future,
then that's where I need to go.
&nbsp
You trapped Savitar in the Speed Force.
Just tell me how you did it.
&nbsp
- I had help.
- Help from who?
&nbsp
A physicist. Her name's Tracy Brand.
I know who you are.
&nbsp
Synced and corrected by Aaronnmb
www.addic7ed.com
&nbsp
- Whew!
- _
&nbsp
Cecile?
Most people quit...
&nbsp
their New Year's resolutions by now.
Uh-uh. Central City
Marathon is in two months,
&nbsp
and I gotta shave... ooh!
I still got half a minute
I gotta take off my time.
&nbsp
- You?
- A lot more than 30 seconds.
&nbsp
Look, I am going to wait for you...
at the end of the marathon.
&nbsp
No, you're not pulling
out of this thing.
&nbsp
I am not as easy with running
as some other members of my family.
&nbsp
Mm, I'm gonna let it
slide. I'm gonna let it.
&nbsp
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
&nbsp
Are you getting mad?
I would never get mad.
&nbsp
I love you too much to be mad.
Uh, um...
&nbsp
that, uh... I, uh...
- I didn't really mean to...
- No, absolutely...
&nbsp
I was looking at you,
and then it just came
out, and I didn't want you
&nbsp
- to feel uncomfortable or...
- I'm sorry. Hold on.
&nbsp
Sorry. I gotta take this.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Go for it.
&nbsp
Yeah? Okay. I'm on my way.
Yeah.
&nbsp
All right, sorry.
I gotta head out.
&nbsp
Her name is Tracy Brand.
She's one of the world's
top theoretical physicists...
&nbsp
you know, or at least she will be.
No kidding. Girl Scout
earns her merit badges.
&nbsp
2021 Nobel Prize, Copley Medal,
presidential commendation.
&nbsp
She's a genius, but what's that to us?
She's the key to stopping Savitar.
&nbsp
Future me said that four years from now,
Dr. Brand invents the technology
&nbsp
that traps Savitar in the Speed Force.
Four years too late.
&nbsp
Yeah, but if she invents the tech then,
then maybe she's working
on the prototype now.
&nbsp
That's exactly right,
so we should find her.
&nbsp
Agreed.
Sorry...
&nbsp
why are we not looking
for Caitlin again?
&nbsp
Easy, Romeo and Juliet.
None of us have forgotten about Caitlin.
&nbsp
Right, but future
Flash already confirmed
&nbsp
that she teams up with Savitar.
We should be doing
everything in our power
&nbsp
- to stop that from happening.
- We know.
&nbsp
Right, so what is Wally doing
swanning off to Earth-3
to be with his girlfriend?
&nbsp
He could be here right
now looking for her.
&nbsp
It's like no one's doing a thing.
No one's doing a thing?
&nbsp
Barry and Wally searched
the city half a dozen times.
&nbsp
No one's doing a thing?
Every chance I get,
&nbsp
I try to vibe where she is.
We're using facial
recognition technology.
&nbsp
We're using the meta-human
app, the satellite.
&nbsp
We're doing everything we can.
I just want her back, okay?
&nbsp
Yeah, well, if you
wanted her here so badly,
&nbsp
maybe you shouldn't have
ripped off that necklace
&nbsp
- and turned her into a killer.
- Okay, okay.
&nbsp
- All right.
- Just saying.
&nbsp
We got a hit.
Tracy Brand, currently enrolled in
CCU's Theoretical Physics program.
&nbsp
So our hopes of defeating
an evil speed god
&nbsp
- hinge on a grad student?
- Yup.
&nbsp
Could be worse. B.A.,
Cisco, let's do this.
&nbsp
Let's go.
Ahh, the soul-sucking
fluorescence of academia.
&nbsp
Yeah, this is exciting, though.
It's like meeting Norbert
before he was Einstein.
&nbsp
- Albert.
- Norbert Albert?
&nbsp
Do you guys smell that?
Toast?
&nbsp
Holy...
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
&nbsp
What are you doing?
You mean save you from
a painful, fiery death?
&nbsp
I had it under control.
- Come on!
- Aah!
&nbsp
Okay! You know what?
Let's put this down...
&nbsp
while you still have your eyebrows.
Did you set the fire on purpose?
&nbsp
Yes, I'm burning everything.
- W... ev...
- What?
&nbsp
- Everything? What...
- My work.
&nbsp
Well, I don't know why
they call it "work,"
&nbsp
because none of it works.
This isn't exactly what I expected.
&nbsp
- Me neither.
- Um, Dr. Brand?
&nbsp
Oh, no. Just Tracy.
I failed my dissertation.
&nbsp
Nothing like ten years down the drain
and a pile of debt as a legacy.
&nbsp
Tracy, uh, w-w-we were just hoping
that you'd have a moment to talk.
&nbsp
Oh, no. My bus leaves in five minutes.
Oh, please tell me I
didn't burn my bus ticket.
&nbsp
- Uh...
- Yeah, that's hot.
&nbsp
Your bus? Where... where are you going?
Big Belly Burger. I hear they're hiring.
&nbsp
What? You're seri...
Well, what about all your research?
&nbsp
Oh... you mean my...
"unsubstantiated and
transactional" inquiry
&nbsp
into the "purely suppositional" nature
of extra-dimensional energy?
&nbsp
- Yes?
- Yeah?
&nbsp
A waste of time, or,
as Dr. Hersh puts it,
&nbsp
"A total misapplication of
the university's resources."
&nbsp
I might as well start practicing,
"Do you want fries with that?"
&nbsp
- Yes.
- No.
&nbsp
- B.A.
- Stop.
&nbsp
Look, don't let the
naysayers get you down.
&nbsp
Your doubts, they're traitors.
Don't believe them. Your
mind is too fine to waste
&nbsp
turning tubers into finger chips.
Finger... chips?
&nbsp
- Finger chips. There's, like, a...
- He's from out of town. H.R!
&nbsp
Stop. Look, look,
look. You can't give up.
&nbsp
Your work on relativistic
quantum mechanics
&nbsp
and its application
to inter-spatial theory
&nbsp
to manipulate matter
on a subatomic level,
&nbsp
it's groundbreaking.
I haven't shared that
hypothesis with anyone,
&nbsp
other than my therapist.
- Who are you?
- We're therapists.
&nbsp
Yeah.
Admission here is so easy.
&nbsp
Get her out of here. Go.
So...
&nbsp
you've gone full-on Killer Frost, huh?
New threads and everything.
&nbsp
No more pencil skirts for me.
I don't want to hurt you.
&nbsp
You won't.
But I will hurt her.
&nbsp
Cisco! Hey!
- Hey, you good?
- Yeah.
&nbsp
- That's gonna leave a mark.
- Come on, come on.
&nbsp
- Caitlin's after Tracy.
- Yeah.
&nbsp
That means she's working with Savitar.
That's definitely her, Detective.
&nbsp
Icy eyes and all.
Yup, that's her.
&nbsp
So I'm gonna spread this around
so everyone knows to look for her.
&nbsp
- Uh, can you give me one second?
- Mm-hmm.
&nbsp
Uh, so if Caitlin wants Tracy dead,
I guess what you saw
in the future was true
&nbsp
and she's teamed up with Savitar.
I just didn't think it
was gonna happen this soon.
&nbsp
It certainly makes
things more complicated.
&nbsp
Makes what more complicated?
Uh... t-there was a meta attack at CCU,
&nbsp
and we just don't
have much to go off of.
&nbsp
Really? It's a college campus.
- Isn't there video footage?
- Uh, no.
&nbsp
It got... erased.
Uh, well, I'm sure you
two will figure it out.
&nbsp
Joe, can I, um...
- Yeah.
&nbsp
So I'm feeling weird about this morning.
Uh...
&nbsp
Look, when I told you that I loved you,
I-I didn't mean to
make you feel pressured.
&nbsp
No, no, no, no, I-I
didn't feel pressured.
&nbsp
Okay. So...
we're good?
&nbsp
- We're great.
- Great. Okay.
&nbsp
Um, in that case, uh...
good luck with your meta.
&nbsp
Um, so I totally heard that.
- Do you want to talk?
- No. Hey, where are you going?
&nbsp
Oh, uh, nearest bus stop.
Uh, no, you should stay here,
&nbsp
um, with Detective
West for a little bit.
&nbsp
Why? That sketch artist was
like freaking Michelangelo.
&nbsp
- I mean, you've got your woman.
- Not yet.
&nbsp
And until we do, you could
be in a lot of danger.
&nbsp
You really think Jack Frost's
sister wants to kill me?
&nbsp
- I'm no one.
- In my experience,
&nbsp
if she's come after you once,
she's likely to do it again.
&nbsp
Look, this whole witness
over-protection thing
&nbsp
is totally unnecessary.
It was just a random attack.
&nbsp
Oh! The bus is coming.
I gotta go.
&nbsp
We need to keep an eye on her.
Yeah, we do.
&nbsp
She got away.
I told you exactly where she'd be.
&nbsp
Barry and Cisco were
there when I arrived.
&nbsp
As I told you they would be.
Maybe there's more
Caitlin Snow inside you
&nbsp
than you led me to believe.
Are you saying I let her go on purpose?
&nbsp
Did you?
You call yourself Killer Frost,
&nbsp
but you haven't actually
killed anyone yet.
&nbsp
You and I can both be gods,
free of the pain and suffering of man.
&nbsp
All you have to do...
is kill the girl.
&nbsp
Okay. Look, I might not have any cash.
But I have one of
those, um, Jitters cards
&nbsp
that has ten stamps on it,
which means you owe me a free drink.
&nbsp
Okay?
Allow moi to help out
a damsel in distress.
&nbsp
I will pay for myself and the lady.
I will have a triple-shot,
no-whip mocha Flash,
&nbsp
and anything this young lady desires.
Yeah, I, um... I need
to calm down, so a Zoom.
&nbsp
- A Zoom?
- Mm-hmm.
&nbsp
Never heard of it.
- Oh, it's on the secret menu.
- Secret menu?
&nbsp
Triple espresso with a shot of cayenne.
Marry me.
&nbsp
Hey, wait. You were at
the college this morning.
&nbsp
No... oh, this morning? Oh, yeah.
No, I remember you now.
&nbsp
Yes, I was. H.R.
Wait, what is it with you people?
&nbsp
Did the CCPD send you to find me?
No, no, no, no. The
reason I'm here is...
&nbsp
my team and I...
are very interested in your research.
&nbsp
- Really?
- Yes.
&nbsp
You're interested in my
theories on quantum mechanics?
&nbsp
Your ideas of wave-particle duality,
your quantization of energy,
&nbsp
and your time-symmetric formulation
of quantum theory and...
&nbsp
... How the boundary conditions
lead to principle causality
&nbsp
and the psychological arrow of time.
And the psychological arrow of time.
&nbsp
You really know your stuff.
Well, je suis...
&nbsp
smart.
Lay off the French, and lay
off the improv too, please.
&nbsp
Just keep her talking.
Ah.
&nbsp
Thank you, Mischa.
Please. The Zoom.
&nbsp
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
&nbsp
Let's zoom.
Mate, was it just me,
&nbsp
or did it sound like
H.R. was trying to flirt?
&nbsp
Hmm. Didn't notice.
Listen, the, uh, security
footage today from CCU,
&nbsp
the stuff that we wiped to
protect Caitlin's identity?
&nbsp
I-I saw it.
As in, I-I saw the two
of you squaring off.
&nbsp
Okay.
Well, from the angle that I saw,
&nbsp
it looked like you had
a pretty clear shot.
&nbsp
Okay.
You had a clear shot, Cisco,
and you didn't take it.
&nbsp
- Why?
- Julian, I'm trying to focus
&nbsp
on what we're here to focus
on. I suggest you do the same.
&nbsp
Gents, how we doing?
Uh, all good.
&nbsp
I don't know about this one, Bar.
H.R. isn't exactly our best closer.
&nbsp
Ah, he'll be fine.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
&nbsp
- Just...
- Cecile?
&nbsp
She's just... she caught me off guard.
Mm-hmm?
&nbsp
Just didn't think we were there yet.
Well, obviously she is.
&nbsp
- Are you?
- I-I care for her a lot.
&nbsp
It's just with everything going on
with Iris and Savitar
&nbsp
and now Caitlin, I just feel like I...
lie to Cecile all the time.
&nbsp
Then maybe you should stop.
You're gonna have to
tell her about Wally
&nbsp
and me and all this
at some point, right?
&nbsp
So why not now?
Well, just so you know,
&nbsp
you don't have to keep
her in the dark for us.
&nbsp
If you love her, you
should be honest with her.
&nbsp
At least that's what
you'd tell me to do.
&nbsp
- Okay, so...
- Mm-hmm?
&nbsp
here's the thing that I could
never get them to understand
&nbsp
at the university. See...
- I've been studying speedsters.
- Oh.
&nbsp
And so you know how,
when they run, they generate a trail...
&nbsp
- of lightning behind them?
- Light... lightning.
&nbsp
I don't think all of that
is generated by them running.
&nbsp
- I think...
- No?
&nbsp
... some of it comes from somewhere.
- Mm-hmm.
- Like, it's some sort of a...
&nbsp
like a... hmm.
Speed Force?
&nbsp
Yeah.
- Wait. That is a great term for it.
- Well...
&nbsp
- Speed Force.
- Thanks.
&nbsp
Anyway, so I've been
doing some calculations.
&nbsp
Mm-hmm?
I think there might be
a way to manipulate it.
&nbsp
Mm-hmm?
Maybe even...
&nbsp
control it.
Maybe even turn it into a prison.
&nbsp
Maybe. Um, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
&nbsp
I mean... just a random thought.
How do you think one
would accomplish that?
&nbsp
- See, I don't know...
- Okay.
&nbsp
because the university
wouldn't fund my research.
&nbsp
Ahh, mm-hmm.
Why are you so interested in this?
&nbsp
Because everybody thinks I'm a crackpot.
I certainly don't
think you're a crackpot.
&nbsp
I...
What's wrong?
&nbsp
We should go.
- Wait. What?
- I think we should go. Yup.
&nbsp
Guys, guys, we need a little help here!
We got a little trouble here!
&nbsp
- Hey.
- Flash?
&nbsp
- Where is she?
- Right here!
&nbsp
- Her again?
- Caitlin! Caitlin, stop!
&nbsp
- Get her out of here!
- What? What?
&nbsp
What did I ever do to you?
So what?
&nbsp
You're Savitar's lackey now?
More fun to reign in hell and all that.
&nbsp
All right, I'm gonna get
her to head back this way.
&nbsp
When she does, you gotta
knock her out, okay?
&nbsp
- Okay?
- Yeah.
&nbsp
Now, Cisco!
Savitar says I'm not
allowed to kill you,
&nbsp
but I can't have you
following me around.
&nbsp
It was the left leg last time, right?
Right.
&nbsp
Scar tissue's a lot more
sensitive than regular tissue.
&nbsp
This isn't you!
It is now.
&nbsp
Cait! Cait!
This is where the
Flashy Flash goes down?
&nbsp
It's not exactly what I
imagined, but it's cool.
&nbsp
So I always wondered
how you kept the friction
&nbsp
from building up a lethal
dose of static charge.
&nbsp
Yeah, that's vulcanized Teflon.
It neutralizes any electron imbalance.
&nbsp
Okay, and the... the White Witch?
I'm guessing you know
why she's after me.
&nbsp
Well, she's teamed up with an
evil speedster from the future,
&nbsp
and apparently you developed
the technology to trap him
&nbsp
for an eternity, so...
You can't be serious.
&nbsp
Totally serious.
An evil speedster?
&nbsp
He calls himself Savitar.
Savitar? And he's from the future?
&nbsp
- Yup.
- And I build a trap for him?
&nbsp
- Me?
- You.
&nbsp
He wants to kill you
before you build it.
&nbsp
That's why he's sending
Killer Frost after you.
&nbsp
Killer Frost? Her
name... is Killer Frost?
&nbsp
- Yeah.
- We know it's a lot to take in.
&nbsp
Well, to be fair, you're
basically telling me
&nbsp
I'm Sarah Connor in "Terminator."
- Well...
- Uh, more like...
&nbsp
- Miles Dyson.
- Yeah,
&nbsp
- but good effort, though.
- So wait.
&nbsp
You're telling me my
ideas about the, um...
&nbsp
The Speed Force.
Speed Force, being able to control it,
&nbsp
manipulate it, all of that...
I'm right?
&nbsp
It appears so.
That's me?
&nbsp
Nobel Prize?
All of that?
&nbsp
In the future, yeah.
Look, Tracy.
&nbsp
We need your help.
We need you to build this trap now.
&nbsp
What happens if I don't build the trap?
Someone very important
to us is going to die.
&nbsp
I'm sorry.
Excuse me.
&nbsp
Uh, I know that, uh,
normally one of you fellas
&nbsp
goes out for the chat, but, uh...
I got this one.
&nbsp
Tracy!
Oh, Tracy!
&nbsp
I'm working.
I can see.
&nbsp
I thought you'd like to be informed
that H.R. has managed
to talk Tracy around.
&nbsp
Ah, perfect. That means
we can get to work.
&nbsp
Yeah, there's one thing
I need to know first.
&nbsp
Outside Jitters earlier,
you could've stopped
Caitlin with a vibe.
&nbsp
But just like CCU, you didn't.
I'm not doing this again.
&nbsp
No, no, no, no, no.
You are.
&nbsp
I need to know, Cisco.
Tell me why you couldn't do it.
&nbsp
Get out of my way.
Caitlin could be home now.
&nbsp
Had you stopped her, she would be here.
But you didn't! You couldn't!
&nbsp
Tell me why!
Because I'm afraid!
&nbsp
- Afraid of what?
- Afraid of killing her!
&nbsp
I'm walking around with
two loaded guns here,
&nbsp
ready to go off.
What if she's hurting
Barry or Joe or you...
&nbsp
and I have to save you and
I can't control my powers
&nbsp
and I end up killing her?
She's my best friend.
&nbsp
And I'd rather it be me than her.
Hey.
&nbsp
How's Tracy holding up?
Ah, we'll see.
&nbsp
Um...
Have you told Cecile about us yet?
&nbsp
Cecile is the only thing...
normal I have in my life right now,
&nbsp
and I like having something normal.
If I tell her about all this...
&nbsp
that goes away.
But if you don't tell her...
&nbsp
- There may not be an "us."
- Mm-hmm.
&nbsp
Joe, there's no such thing as normal.
Love is the only thing that
makes the fight worth it,
&nbsp
and it's the only thing
that's gonna get us through it.
&nbsp
Guys. Guys, there you are.
We got a big problem.
&nbsp
Tracy's gone.
I checked CCU, her
apartment, and Jitters.
&nbsp
Tracy's not in any of them.
I'll bet you Savitar and Killer Frost
&nbsp
are hunting her down as we speak.
H.R., you were with Tracy last.
&nbsp
- How did she seem?
- Rattled, Miss West.
&nbsp
Rattled, but I gave her a
rousing and reassuring pep talk,
&nbsp
- so I think she's okay.
- Oh, that's why she left.
&nbsp
That's not why... look,
I will have you know...
&nbsp
my book on motivational speeches,
"All's Wells that Ends Wells"...
&nbsp
- Tracy is in danger.
- You're right.
&nbsp
- Iris! Focus!
- What?
&nbsp
- We need to find her. Now.
- Yeah, we gotta find her.
&nbsp
Where else could she be?
Oh!
&nbsp
Why don't we start with
her future hologram, right?
&nbsp
That's... that would give us insight
- into her psyche, no?
- Of course, yeah.
&nbsp
- That's pretty good.
- Thank you.
&nbsp
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.
&nbsp
- She's cute.
- This is creepy, right?
&nbsp
- Yeah.
- I find her charming.
&nbsp
Do you think you could
screenshot a hologram?
&nbsp
Go back to that last one.
Yeah, there's another one like it.
&nbsp
Whoa, whoa, look at that.
- Zoom in.
- Yeah.
&nbsp
Eppur si...
Eppur si muove.
&nbsp
Tracy, you blessed paramour of science.
Gang, I know exactly where she is.
&nbsp
Eppur si muove.
"And yet it moves."
&nbsp
Galileo's famous
statement uttered moments
&nbsp
after being forced to recant
his theory that the Earth
&nbsp
revolves around the sun.
"And yet it moves."
&nbsp
Mocha Flash for me.
- A Zoom for milady.
- Thank you.
&nbsp
You're very welcome.
How did you know I was here?
&nbsp
Um, I might have done a
bit of holographic stalking.
&nbsp
I stalked you holographically.
You mean, in the future,
I'm still obsessed
&nbsp
with a 500-year-old Italian polymath?
Yes, it would appear so.
&nbsp
I'm sorry I ran off.
- I just...
- No.
&nbsp
just needed to clear
my head and think...
&nbsp
- Of course.
- ... and this is where I do it best.
&nbsp
Well, I can see that. That statue
is nothing if not inspiring.
&nbsp
Concrete beard, foreboding, smart.
- Totally inspiring.
- Yup.
&nbsp
You know,
Galileo's peers thought
he was a crackpot too.
&nbsp
- Is that right?
- Yeah.
&nbsp
And I used to find that comforting.
- Oh.
- But then when your team
&nbsp
showed me the future...
and showed me that my crazy ideas
&nbsp
aren't so crazy after all,
I just felt more intimidated than ever.
&nbsp
Well, I can see that.
It's like you're sitting
in the shadow of greatness.
&nbsp
- Your own greatness, right?
- Exactly!
&nbsp
It's like I've failed so many times.
That's all I know how to do.
&nbsp
I don't know how to be that...
brilliant woman in the hologram.
&nbsp
But you wouldn't understand.
You are a born genius.
&nbsp
Yeah, about that.
Um, I'm not...
&nbsp
technically a genius.
That was a cheap thing to
do. I'm sorry I misled you
&nbsp
about me being a genius.
The point is, you...
&nbsp
are... a genius.
You are. I know it.
&nbsp
I can... I can feel it.
It's right there. It's right there,
&nbsp
just brimming just below the surface.
- It is?
- Yes, absolutely!
&nbsp
Yes, it is, Tracy.
And you can defeat Savitar.
&nbsp
All you need is to just
believe in yourself.
&nbsp
And for what it's worth...
I already do.
&nbsp
- Hi.
- Hey.
&nbsp
I didn't know you were dropping by.
Yeah, well, if you had read
any of my texts, you'd know.
&nbsp
Yeah. Um...
- I'm sorry.
- I know.
&nbsp
It's why I'm here. Look, I...
You know, it doesn't
take a detective to see
&nbsp
that something's not right.
Look, Cecile...
&nbsp
Is it because I said, "I
love you," this morning?
&nbsp
Because, Joe, it's... it's okay
if you're not ready to say it back.
&nbsp
No, no. It's not about that.
No? Well, then what's going on?
&nbsp
'Cause you've been acting weird all day.
I mean, not just with us this morning
&nbsp
but at work with that meta case.
You gotta give me something, Joe.
&nbsp
All I can say is...
that part of my life
is very complicated.
&nbsp
And if you were to become part of that,
your life would be very complicated,
&nbsp
and it would change us.
And I mean change us forever.
&nbsp
That's not a bad thing, you know.
It's called growth.
&nbsp
And then I was thinking about...
what you said this morning, and...
&nbsp
it told me where you were.
It also showed me where I was, and...
&nbsp
and you add those complications,
and I think we should
stop seeing each other.
&nbsp
Really?
That's what you think we should do?
&nbsp
I-I-I think it's the
best thing for both of us.
&nbsp
Here I was, thinking that being together
was the best thing for both of us.
&nbsp
I guess I'll, uh...
I'll see you around the station, Joe.
&nbsp
- Cecile!
- Joe!
&nbsp
- No!
- Joe!
&nbsp
Guarantee you I'm faster.
Caitlin...
&nbsp
we can talk about this.
I'll talk. You listen.
&nbsp
In an hour, you're gonna get
a message with an address.
&nbsp
Bring me Tracy Brand,
or I will kill your little sweetheart.
&nbsp
Joe.
Wait!
&nbsp
So you're saying that
if we don't turn Tracy
&nbsp
over to Killer Frost...
She's gonna kill Cecile.
&nbsp
Correct me if I'm wrong,
but Tracy is our key to
finding Savitar, right?
&nbsp
Yes, but what are we gonna do?
We gonna just let Killer Frost
&nbsp
live up to her name and kill somebody?
Not if I have anything to say about it.
&nbsp
All I'm saying is,
we need to do whatever
it takes to save her.
&nbsp
No one's gonna die, all right?
We're gonna get her back. I promise.
&nbsp
That's them.
They're at the old Dressler Factory.
&nbsp
Okay, we know where they
are. That's something.
&nbsp
So what do we do?
I have a plan.
&nbsp
Cisco, can I have a quick word?
- Not now, Julian.
- Listen, please, mate.
&nbsp
Just... just hear me out.
I know you're terrified of losing her.
&nbsp
So am I.
I know you're... you're worried
&nbsp
about not being able
to control your powers,
&nbsp
but I know you can.
I don't think your abilities
have ever come from a place
&nbsp
of... of negativity or... or hate.
They come from somewhere good.
&nbsp
They come from love.
And if you can find
it in you to stop her,
&nbsp
then I really think we can save her.
Cheers, mate.
&nbsp
Hi.
Yeah, you know how I said, you know,
&nbsp
we were gonna keep you safe?
Um, yeah.
&nbsp
So, um, now I need to ask you
to do something dangerous.
&nbsp
Cecile!
- Are you all right?
- Joe!
&nbsp
I'm okay. She didn't hurt me.
That's because killing you...
&nbsp
does nothing for me.
Killing you, Tracy? That's everything.
&nbsp
Hand her over.
You don't have to do this.
&nbsp
- Yes, I do.
- Why?
&nbsp
Because Savitar commands it?
He's not a god.
&nbsp
He's just a man that's using you.
- Come on, you're one of us.
- One of us?
&nbsp
- We're family.
- We're family?
&nbsp
We protect each other till the end.
How are you doing that?
&nbsp
Savitar told me everything you'd say.
You two are more alike than you realize.
&nbsp
You see, that's how
Savitar knows every move
&nbsp
you're going to make.
He's always one step ahead of you,
&nbsp
because this is all history to him.
That's how I know Cisco's
in the rafters right now.
&nbsp
Oh, no.
It's over, Caitlin.
&nbsp
Caitlin is dead.
Not to me.
&nbsp
Go. Go. Go. Go.
Caitlin.
&nbsp
You're alive.
I'm sorry.
&nbsp
I had to stop you to save you.
My ascension is nearly at hand, Flash.
&nbsp
As I rise, you will fall.
How do we keep surviving these things?
&nbsp
Because we're in control of our fates.
And how did she know I
was up in the rafters?
&nbsp
Is she psychic now too?
And that thing where you guys
were talking at the same time?
&nbsp
How do you think she was doing that?
I don't know. She said Savitar told her
&nbsp
what was gonna happen.
No way, man. This wasn't just
brushing up on days to come.
&nbsp
This was precise. Scary precise.
- Like Savitar was there.
- Mm-hmm.
&nbsp
What I don't understand is why Savitar
wouldn't kill Tracy when he showed up.
&nbsp
I mean, why would he
choose to rescue Caitlin?
&nbsp
He needs her for something.
We gotta figure out what that is.
&nbsp
Agreed.
Thanks to Cisco, we now
have a sample of her blood
&nbsp
when she was fully
mutated as Killer Frost.
&nbsp
This?
It could be the key to reverse
engineering a cure, so...
&nbsp
it's good work, mate.
You too.
&nbsp
Oh, there you are.
I brought us some coffee treats.
&nbsp
Unfortunately, we were
all out of cayenne.
&nbsp
- Careful, that's hot.
- Ah!
&nbsp
Yeah, hot, hot, sorry.
How are you? Oh! Ha! Whoo!
&nbsp
- Careful.
- Ah, how are you holding up?
&nbsp
- Whew, it's hot.
- Well...
&nbsp
- I'm processing.
- Mm-hmm.
&nbsp
That was really...
I mean, the voice...
&nbsp
And the "whoom!"
- Pshh!
- Killer Frost? Savitar?
&nbsp
You know some people
with really scary names.
&nbsp
Eh, but is it too much?
All of us here would understand.
&nbsp
Personally, I just...
I just wanna make sure
&nbsp
that, you know, you don't get hurt.
As a matter of fact, I was thinking...
&nbsp
- I was thinking too.
- Yeah?
&nbsp
- About Savitar.
- Mm-hmm?
&nbsp
The way the light reflects off his suit,
it's unlike any other metallic
compound I have ever seen.
&nbsp
Hmm, you and I were thinking
about different things.
&nbsp
- What do you think it is?
- In Fermi liquid theory,
&nbsp
any sort of non-Fermi liquid
- is called "strange metal."
- Mm-hmm.
&nbsp
It's a theoretical compound
capable of dispersing heat
&nbsp
at high temperatures.
I think Savitar travels so fast
&nbsp
that he needs that suit
to neutralize the charge
&nbsp
he builds up around him.
Huh. Interesting.
&nbsp
So without the suit, he's just a dude
with a bad case of static cling.
&nbsp
Yeah. So if we could build a device
capable of harnessing that power,
&nbsp
theoretically, we could use
his own velocity against him.
&nbsp
And trap him in the Speed Force.
Tracy, you are indeed a genius.
&nbsp
- I'm getting there.
- Well, yes, you are.
&nbsp
That means you're
gonna stay and help us.
&nbsp
Is that what that means?
If I do, does that mean
the future's changing?
&nbsp
I think it means mine certainly has.
- Hey.
&nbsp
Thanks for seeing me. Come on in.
So how are you doing?
&nbsp
Joe, I'm fine. I just...
you know, I wish that you would've
told me what was going on with you.
&nbsp
Although I... obviously
have some idea now.
&nbsp
It was my fault that you
got caught up in all this.
&nbsp
I'm so sorry, Cecile.
Joe, me too. Look, I...
&nbsp
When you told me that you
loved me this morning...
&nbsp
- I froze.
- Yeah.
&nbsp
I knew that it meant
that we moved up a level
&nbsp
in our relationship.
And... for me,
&nbsp
that level comes with a lot of baggage.
Like Killer Frost and The Flash?
&nbsp
Yeah.
So you thought that pushing
me away was the thing to do?
&nbsp
I thought that I was protecting you.
Clearly I was wrong,
&nbsp
because not only did I lie to you.
I lied to myself.
&nbsp
And you know what?
I'm done with that.
&nbsp
And I'm done with this.
Thank you for not making a big deal
&nbsp
about me wearing this.
Cecile Horton...
&nbsp
I love you.
I love you with all my heart.
&nbsp
And I'm sorry that I
was dishonest with you.
&nbsp
And from now on,
there will be no secrets
&nbsp
between us.
- Okay.
- Mm.
&nbsp
I should have told you a long time ago.
But it's not bad.
&nbsp
- Wally!
- Hey, Dad.
&nbsp
Hey.
How was it?
&nbsp
It was... yeah, it was
great. Jesse says hi.
&nbsp
- So you talked to Cecile?
- I did.
&nbsp
Told her everything.
Told her I love her.
&nbsp
I told her that you were The Flash
and that Wally was Kid Flash.
&nbsp
Don't worry. She promised me...
that she wouldn't tell Joanie.
&nbsp
What changed your mind?
You. All of you.
&nbsp
I mean, love's the only
thing we got in this world.
&nbsp
Without it, nothing really matters.
Hmm.
&nbsp
And who knows what we'd become
if we didn't have it?
&nbsp
- How was Earth-3?
- Yeah, um,
&nbsp
hanging out with Jesse was awesome.
I mean, love's the only
thing we got in this world.
&nbsp
Without it, nothing really matters.
And who knows what we'd
become if we didn't have it?
&nbsp
You did this to me, Barry.
- I created you?
- I created myself.
&nbsp
You're even gonna create
time remnants of yourself,
&nbsp
but he's gonna kill them all.
Savitar told me everything you'd say.
&nbsp
You two are more alike than you realize.
Savitar knows every move
you're going to make.
&nbsp
He's always one step ahead of you.
This is all history.
&nbsp
This wasn't just brushing
up on days to come.
&nbsp
This was precise.
Like Savitar was there.
&nbsp
Who knows what we'd become
if we didn't have it?
&nbsp
One step ahead of you.
All history.
&nbsp
I am the future Flash.
- One step ahead of you.
- Barry?
&nbsp
Barry!
Are you okay?
&nbsp
Yeah.
Uh, I'm sorry.
&nbsp
I'll be... I'll be
right back, all right?
&nbsp
I'm here!
I know who you are.
&nbsp
It's about time.
Yes, it is.
&nbsp
Everything with you is
about time, isn't it?
&nbsp
The past, the present, the future...
you know all of it, right?
&nbsp
And you know everything about me!
About Joe!
&nbsp
About Wally.
And Iris!
&nbsp
You know our strengths.
You know our fears.
&nbsp
You know how much we love each other.
And you know how to use
that love against us.
&nbsp
All this time, we thought
that we couldn't stop you
&nbsp
because you were one step
ahead, but that's not it!
&nbsp
You don't just know
what's gonna happen to us.
&nbsp
You were there.
You lived it.
&nbsp
You remember...
when you were me.
&nbsp
Like I told you from the beginning...
I am the future Flash.
&nbsp
Synced and corrected by Aaronnmb
www.addic7ed.com
&nbsp