If you think I look at you like a trophy,
you're wrong. You're not good enough.
Vilde, you're super pretty.
-But not pretty enough.
If you really want to get rid of me,
go on a date with me.
Remember when I said you weren't good enough?
That was bullshit.
Okay.
Why is it so hard to understand people
can be friends with their ex?
It's William.
He wants to talk to you.
If you go out on a date with me,
I'll stop using Vilde.
Hi. Hello.
-Hi?
We were wondering if you know Jonas.
From the first year.
I think he's in 1STD.
Eh, yeah..
-Do you know if he's together with someone?
No, I don't think so.
What about the girl with the Head jacket?
Eh, Eva?
-Yes, Eva!
No, she's not his girlfriend.
Okay, great. Thanks!
Hello.
-Hi!
What's up?
I didn't do my homework.
Have you talked to Jonas?
Yeah, why?
What actually happened on Friday?
His phone died.
So.. Did he have fun at
the Elvebakken party?
They never even got there. They went to a
third year party. Do you know whose?
Apparently it was really awesome.
Lots of people from school were there.
We should've known and gone there.
Did he hook up with someone?
I don't think so. Don't know. Why?
It seems like the only thing you two talk about
is who he has hooked up with.
That's not the only thing we talk about!
Also about who I hook up with.
You haven't hooked up with anyone since
you've broken up, have you?
But if I had..
-Maybe you should.
Hook up with someone?
-Hm-hm.
I'd gladly hook up with someone,
but I just haven't hit on anyone.
What about Tinder?
-Tinder?!
Okay.. what happened to you?
I think it'd be good for you to get out
there a little.
I'm not on Tinder.
-Why not?
Are you on Tinder?
-Me? No. Oh my god.
But you, Noora.. Why don't we ever talk
about your love life?
We have Spanish now. Clock is ticking,
and you haven't done your homework.
(Why are you changing the subject?)
Who did you hook up with last?
I'm just saying we have Spanish now.
Stop talking about hooking up.
It's the only thing you care about.
I've never heard you talk about anything else.
It's really sick.
Maybe you should get some help.
With Spanish or hooking up?
-Both!
Should we just be wallflowers then?
It's not about being wallflowers.
It's about how we present ourselves.
We shouldn't be perceived as
sexual objects.
I don't want to be sexual objects,
I just want us to look pretty.
You use red lipstick.
Because it looks pretty on you.
That's not why I do it.
It's because I think it's nice.
I don't do it for guys.
-What's the difference?
[You're really pretty today. Happy Women's Day.
Looking forward to Friday.]
It's going well. We got "Brun og Blid"
as a sponsor.
How did you do that?
-I've been doing a little research after school.
I'm not really sure if we should have them
as our sponsor.
Because I don't think I want us to present
ourselves as sexual objects.
That's really important to me.
But at the same time I want us to be seen
as beautiful individuals.
Above all we will emphasize
our femininity.
I think that "Brun og Blid" is
good for that.
Why is everyone staring at Jonas?
-Didn't you hear?
No.
There are rumors that he got
a third year to come.
Come to what?
Cum-come..
He slept with a third year?
He went down on her.
Huh?
-He licked her.
But Eva, you said Norwegian guys didn't..
Hello.
Happy Women's Day.
What course do you guys have now?
-Eh, Norwegian! Yeah.
Me too. Should we just go now?
It's difficult for Tinder to know that.
It should be in the bio. 14 centimeter.
Hey you! Look who's on Tinder.
Tinder?
-Yes, Tinder! You have to come with me.
Why should I come with?
Excuse me? Check his friends.
They are fucking handsome.
They are second years at Handels.
His name is Adam. Adam.. Eva..
It's perfect!
Then you can go with her!
-I'm going to Stavanger.
You?
-I have basketball camp.
It's my cousin's birthday.
Noora! Come with me, please?
You said I needed to
meet more guys.
I can't though. Sorry.
-You can't, really?
Hey, Noora?
I'll just ask you straight out.
Are you lesbian?
There's nothing wrong with being lesbian.
-No, no no no!
Vilde..
It's not weird that I think so! You don't have sex
and you don't want to talk about sex.
Just because I don't go around talking about
being keen on having sex..
.. doesn't mean I'm lesbian.
But what are you doing tomorrow?
It's Eskild's birthday.
Is he having a big party?
-No. A small celebration.
Not even a real celebration. Just..
Maybe we can meet up later
if you're going out?
Who was that?
-Her name is Jamila Bikarim.
Do you know each other?
She's engaged to my brother.
-Engaged?!
How old is she?
-She's 17.
Is it an arranged marriage?
-Huh?
Why would you get married when you're 17?
Because they want to have sex.
That is great.
Hello.
You're so pretty. Where are you going?
-I'm not pretty.
Okay..
I got a Facebook message
from Eva. Your friend.
She wrote: Happy birthday!
You didn't say that it wasn't your birthday?
-Huh? Not yet.
You can't say that. I had to say it was your
birthday because I have a date.
You have a date? With who?
-An asshole called William.
William? As in Vilde's William?
He's not Vilde's William.
-Okay. Drama.
He really isn't Vilde's. And you wanna know something?
I'm doing this for Vilde's sake.
You're going on a date with William for Vilde's sake?
-Yep.
Okay, how is that related?
He told Vilde she wasn't good enough.
I have to go on a date with him,
to get him to apologise to Vilde.
So you're not going on a date with William because
you want to, but to not hurt Vilde?
Yes!
She won't be hurt when she finds out you're
dating him behind her back?
[Outside.]
I'm not dating William. I'm going on one
date to get rid of him.
And anyway, she'll never find
out about it.
Because you won't tell Eva that it's
not your birthday, okay?
Hi.
-Hi.
Are you ready?
Ready for what?
Are you coming out,
or are you just going to sit here?
Really cool to just sit there
and be pissed.
Cocoa?
Do you see that church down there?
My grandparents lived to the right of it.
In a really big and creepy house.
They had paintings on every wall possible.
My brother said the paintings came alive
and walked around at night.
There was just one room that I liked, the TV room.
Grandma called it the Blue Room.
Walls were blue.
Chairs were blue.
Pillows were blue.
Vases were blue.
You know the wall-to-wall carpet?
Where the carpet covers the entire floor?
Yes I know what wall-to-wall carpet is.
That was blue, too.
You're fucking with me, or what?
Hm? What?
Do you think I fall for that stuff?
What?
Everything here.
With the view, cocoa, carpet, and then you
come with that damn childhood story.
Did you see it in some high school movie
and took note of it, or?
Wow..
You're really cold.
I mean it.
Okay..
I won't talk about my childhood
stories anymore.
What do you want to talk about?
I don't want to talk about anything.
I don't want to get to know you.
I don't even want to be here.
Why are you here then?
Because you pressured me.
I actually didn't pressure you.
How did I pressure you?
Because you sent Vilde messages and you called her,
just to get to me.
How is that pressuring someone?
Because she shouldn't think there's
something between us.
You're not just saying that?
That there's nothing between us.
You're twisting it. It's much more
complicated than that.
It's not that complicated.
You're lying to a friend and you blame me.
The point is that I'm not
interested in you.
And I never will be.
Why not?
You're controlling,
and selfish.
And you use people to get your way.
You're cold,
and selfish..
You already said selfish.
And that time in the school yard when you
said Vilde wasn't good enough.
How can you say something like that?
I didn't want her to like me.
Couldn't you have said it in a better way?
Why should I have said that in a better way?
-To not hurt her.
Hurt her?
There's no point in not hurting her..
.. when I don't want her to like me. It's better to be clear
so there won't be any doubt.
And destroy her self-image?
Do you really think that's how it works?
-What?
It's not possible to destroy her self-image with one comment.
In that case, I think her self-image had already
been destroyed before that.
But if you saw it from my side..
It was Vilde who came to me.
She was keen on me.
She wanted to sleep with me.
I didn't promise her anything.
However, you called me out in the
middle of the school yard.
Does that make you good?
Does that make you fair?
Shouldn't you have warm cocao?
-No.
I like the cold.
Then it tastes like chocolate milk.
It's good that you apologised about telling Vilde
she's not good enough.
Is it?
-Hm-hm.
Okay.
I hope it was a smart plan,
because now she likes me again.
I don't like her.
So then we'll end up in the same place,
won't we?
Hello?
Where?
Where are you?
We have to go.
What's up?
-I'll drive you home.
But just so that we're clear,
so that there won't be any misunderstandings.
I've made up for it now.
I don't owe you anything.
No, you don't owe me anything.