William likes girls who are model thin.
If it's true that Williams dating someone,
I'm sure she's super skinny.
Gum?
[Drama between Vilde and William.
Vilder is crying in the bathroom.]
What did you say to Vilde?
She wanted to hook up with me,
but I wasn't interested.
What's going on here?
You like me.
-No I don't.
Yes you do.
You like me.
SKAM
Easter special
You said it was in Hemsedal!
I said it was just outside of it.
According to Google Maps it's an hour
and a half away. That's not just outside of it.
It's shorter from Oslo to Hemsedal.
Are you kidding me? What are we going to
find here? It's in the middle of nowhere.
Who is he?
Hi.
I've made the cabin ready for you.
Eh, okay. Ready how?
The only thing is that..
the electricity is a bit unstable.
Just be careful.
So you help grandmother with the cabin?
Yes.
Okay.
Bye.
My name is Kasper.
Okay.
What a creepy guy!
It's good that he helps grandma with the cabin.
-But he's a bit weird.
Just because people are different outside
of Ring 3.. (=road that can be seen as Oslo's border)
.. doesn't mean he's creepy.
So he said: "Vilde, you are
really sweet, but I have to stop you."
So I said: "Is it because you like someone else?"
And he said: "It's because I'm not interested."
I don't understand it. He's hot and
then he's cold. Then hot, then cold.
We should've been in Hemsedal now.
So you could've gotten a rebound hook up.
What's this?
It looks similar to that Kasper who we met.
Maybe Kasper's up for a rebound hook up.
Maybe there's someone on Tinder.
-Nobody measures up to William anyway.
All are like 20 kilometers away.
Maybe there's someone on Jodel?
There's nothing on Jodel.
I'm not kidding.
This is the first time I've experienced this.
-We've lost contact with the world.
I wrote: "Hi! Can anyone hear us?
Is there no one out there?"
I wonder what William
is thinking about now.
Do we really have to talk
about guys the entire time?
What else can we do?
There's nothing to do here.
We're in a cabin! We have to play games,
or something.
Are there no games here, Chris?
TP? (Trivial Pursuit)
No, not TP.
Do you actually have to
wear your hijab all the time?
Why? Are you stressed out by it?
No but, we're just with girls here.
You're not forced to wear it.
Vilde, no one is forcing me to
wear it. I wear it because I want to.
Okay, I have something better than a game.
I have an Ouija board.
-What's that?
It's fucking fun. You can ask spirits
questions and they'll answer you.
For example, what is William thinking of now?
Yes, we'll play!
I'm going to lie down.
-Why?
Are you superstitious, Sana?
Night, Vilde.
Okay, let's play!
Dear spirit who's here now,
does Jonas still have feelings for me?
Nothing's happening.
Are you doing this, Chris?
-I swear it's not me.
Fuck. I knew it.
This really sucks.
Why does it suck?
-We can't be friends if he still has feelings for me.
You should have seen him at William's party.
He was so jealous.
-Okay, but now it's my turn.
Dear spirit, what's William thinking
of right now?
Someone here? But who?
No, now it's my turn Vilde.
Can you ask who?
-Eh, no.
Why not?
Because I'm not curious what William's thinking
about. I want to know something else.
Dear spirit, why didn't Sana want
to play with the Ouija board?
Psychic.
-I knew it!
I knew there was something
strange about her.
For example, that she wears her
hijab all the time.
What does that have to do with it?
That's really mysterious.
Your turn, Chris.
Can you ask who William's thinking of?
-No, I'm not gonna ask about your man.
I'm gonna ask about my man, okay?
Spirit, let's talk about Isak.
Why is he even together with Sara?
[Do you miss me?]
Hom?
Gay?
These spirits are smoking crack.
What's going on?
Let's take a break now. -No, now it's my turn
and I want to ask who William's thinking of.
We can just take a break.
-No! I've waited all round.
We can take a break after
I've asked my question.
I don't think the spirit is very serious if
it says Isak is gay.
Eva!
Okay, who's fucking around now?
Huh?
Is it you?
-No, what's up?
Someone has replied on Jodel,
and it says:
"Does Jonas still have feelings for me?"
"What is William thinking of right now?"
"Why is Sana not playing with the Ouija board?"
Are you joking?
2016..
Spirits are on Jodel.
From "very close".
Is it you?
-No, I promise!
You had your phone just now.
You're the only one who could've done it.
It wasn't me!
-Show your phone.
Why should I show my phone?
To see if it was you.
I'm telling you it wasn't me!
Why are you so scared
to show your phone?
What just happened?
It was like a light went on for me.
William is now a Russ. (graduate)
And once someone's a Russ, they don't want a girlfriend.
Everyone knows that.
So even if he has a lot of feelings for me,
I can't fulfill them.
Because he knows it's better to reject me now
than to hurt me during Russetiden.
I'm not saying he has feelings for me,
but when the spirit said..
he thought of someone here,
I thought it was noteworthy.
Vilde, do you want bread?
-No, thanks.
Why not?
Because I'm allergic to gluten.
You don't have a gluten allergy.
Yes, I do. I have all the symptoms.
Which ones?
Skin problems, hair loss,
acne, and itchiness.
I'm tired and weak all the time.
It still doesn't work?
I sent my grandma a message
asking for Kasper's number.
Maybe it was Kasper who replied
to us on Jodel at night?
What reply on Jodel?
-Someone on Jodel wrote everything we said.
Is that him?
What is it?
A message from my grandma.
"Kasper who? There's no guy helping
me with the cabin."
Should I write "who are you" on Jodel?
-Yeah, do it.
You're not going to get any answers.
Sana?
Can I ask you if you're psychic?
Why would you ask that?
I was just wondering.
-There's no bus before tomorrow.
Are you kidding me?
Hello people, can we relax a little?
You don't seriously think Kasper
is out to get us?
Say that's the case, what is he going to do?
We're with five, he's by himself.
And he's really small, too.
We're stuck here anyway.
Let's at least have a good mood here.
If you clean up a little here,
we can go and make some food.
Vilde, are you coming?
Why?
Because we're in a cabin.
Everyone has to help.
Can you peel these and then slice them?
What are we making?
-Tortilla.
Do you need potatoes for tortilla?
-Yes.
I'm actually not fond of potatoes.
-Why not?
I just don't like them.
And they're really unhealthy.
No Vilde, potatoes aren't unhealty.
Your body needs potatoes.
Do you know what's so
good about potatoes?
Potatoes have a lot of starch.
That's really good for you.
Because you said you're tired
and weak all the time.
And then there's Vitamin C.
-That's good for a cold.
Vitamic C is like an antioxidant..
To get rid of potentially dangerous chemicals.
Those chemicals aren't good.
-It can actually cause cancer.
And old skin, Vilde.
Completely true. But vitamin C fixes that,
isn't that cool?
Yeah.
So then we'll have eggs.
Eggs are full of protein.
If you want to be strong
when you do sit ups..
.. and if you want to have abs,
you need protein.
Eggs pretty much have
all eight amino acids..
.. you need if you want to have a toned body.
Did you know that eggs
increase your metabolism, too?
No.
How do you know so
much about food?
Has anyone done a self defense course?
-Just cooking courses.
I'm not going to be able to fall asleep.
-If we sleep tonight..
So girls.. Whatever happens,
we can't split up.
That always happens in horror movies,
and then they die.
I don't understand what he wants.
-He wants to have sex.
That's the only thing men want.
You want that too.
-Yes, but not with him here and now.
We won't talk about guys now.
-Perhaps another time. But I don't have time for that.
What should we do?
We just have to think a little.
If your mom doesn't answer soon,
we have to call the police.
She doesn't answer.
-The police can't do anything.
Of course they can!
There's a person stalking us.
That's what the police are for.
Put your phone away.
There's something I have to tell you.
But you can't freak out.
-I can't be freaked out more than I already am.
Vilde?
-Yeah?
Remember when you asked me why
I never take off my hijab?
Yes.
The hijab makes sure..
I don't know how to explain this.
But I wear it..
.. so I can see things no one
else can see.
Are you psychic?
Call it what you want.
But ever since we got here..
I've seen images..
Of Kasper..
What kind of images?
Images from another time.
-Fucking hell.
Are you kidding me?
I see him right now.
He's standing behind that door.
Fucking hell.
I'll start crying soon.
What does he want?
He wants to be seen.
He says we have to see people like him.
-People who are a little different.
That was really sick.
Look, I'm shaking.
I can't do this without you.
You have to be with me.
Be with you for what?
We have to see him.
That's the only way we can make him disappear.
You don't have to be scared.
I'll go in front.
My hijab will protect us.
Are you guys ready?
He's standing back there!
Fucking hell!
-Are you kidding me?
Oh my god!
Fuck!
That's badly done.
I hate you! Fuck!
Dont cry.
I'm not crying!
Yes you are!
"I'm shaking. I'm shaking."
What about you?
You went: "We have to accept death."
You should've seen your face when Sana
said she was psychic because of her hijab.
It wasn't that weird that
I believed it.
You know that it's just an ordinary scarf?
But then what's the deal with Kasper?
Kasper's just a guy from the electrician
who helps my grandma with the cabin.
Are you joking? -Why do you think he was outside
when the power came on?
Fucking hell, oh my god.
-Everything was bullshit?
Yeah! Sana told me it was her who fucked
with us on Jodel yesterday.
Was that you?
-Yeah!
We decided to continue fucking with you,
because it was so much fun!
It worked good as hell!
You're really sick!
You can't do this to people!
Don't take it so seriously.
But what about the Ouija board?
-Was it real that William was thinking of me?
Vilde, it also said Sana was psychic
and Isak was gay.
So don't take it seriously.
[Heard your friend's little hipster ex got together with
isabel from my class. That's sick.]
But it also said Jonas still has feelings for me.
[Heard your friend's little hipster ex got together with
isabel from my class. That's sick.]
And I know that's true!
[Heard your friend's little hipster ex got together with
isabel from my class. That's sick.]
So it's not completely false.
[Heard your friend's little hipster ex got together with
isabel from my class. That's sick.]
And the Ouija board didn't directly say Isak's gay.
[Heard your friend's little hipster ex got together with
isabel from my class. That's sick.]
And the Ouija board didn't directly say Isak's gay.
[Sick that he got with a 97'er.]
[You should try it.]
Fucking hell!
Are you still in shock?
[You should try it.]
Best female actress goes to.. Sana!