He's the most unsympathetic, selfish person I've ever met.
I would never touch him.
And you shouldn't either.
You like me.
You should've seen him at William's party,
he was so jealous.
[I heard that the little hipster ex of your friend
got together with Isabel from my class?]
Oh my god, look at this.
Looks good? You think it looks good?
It's hideous.
Can you picture a girl in this?
Yeah, maybe in Syria.
But like, in Norway? No.
Hey welcome back, Noora.
I didn't know you were coming back this afternoon.
This is Lito.
My name is Lito.
We're just going through some of your clothes
to see if there's anyhting you don't need.
Like this, for example?
Eskild, what are you doing? You can't take
my clothes without asking me first.
Oh I'm sorry, are we imposing?
No, no. Don't be silly.
She never uses clothes like this.
Yeah, we're just going through
your clothes as I said because..
.. as you know there's a big crisis
in Syria right now.
There's a lot of Syrian refugees
that need your help.
So I was just thinking you
could donate some.
Okay..
Yes, I guess. But maybe just not that top.
Because it has meaning to me so..
What meaning?
-It's from when I lived in Madrid.
Isn't he handsome?
I think he's gay.
Eskild, what are you doing? You can't
just give away my clothes..
.. to a Syrian refugee just to
check him out.
He's not a Syrian refugee.
He studies in Norway.
His father is the Turkish ambassador.
Lito has taken leave from university.
To help the refugees full time.
Sexy?
Sexy? There's nothing sexy about the refugee
crisis. It's incredibly serious.
It's incredibly serious, and you say stuff like:
"Oh no, not that top. It has meaning to me."
See, here she comes. A saint!
Little princess here is rising.
Very good!
Tennis racket, we have a CD player, Rubik's cube.
Lots of hoodies and sweatpants.
Don't know if it's clean.
-Thanks so much, Linn.
You know what Noora,
you're actually a bit stingy.
There are many people who need it
so much more than you.
I'm not stingy.
I care a lot aobut the refugee crisis.
You can't just come into my room and-
Is everything good?
Yes.
Yeah it's all good.
-Everything's fine.
Yeah, it's okay. It's just like..
she loves this top, so..
Yeah but I mean, we got a lot of clothes
and stuff, don't we?
If I take this and this,
you can take the rest.
I'll take this top here, Noora.
You don't need it.
Excuse me?
-Noora, don't be so stingy.
I love dresses with pockets.
It looks hot.
It starts to sing when you have your
cellphone in it.
But this is ugly.
No, nothing is ugly.
But it's a little..
Bye bye.
That one was nice.
I don't wear it. I can't go in white.
I'll get make-up on it and I'll
spill while eating.
You should wear it.
Do you want it?
No, we have to give stuff away.
-Yeah, you need it more than me.
We have to show that we care.
-I care!
You know Eskild..
He said that I don't care.
I do care about the refugee crisis.
It's Eskild who doesn't care.
He's just trying to get with
that Lito guy.
He's convinced that he's gay.
Though he's not.
I don't understand why people who are gay
just assume everyone else is gay too.
What's the deal with that?
Did you happen to hear that it's
over between Isak and Sara?
No.
I think she who broke
up with him.
Oh!
This is from Jonas.
I have to give it back to him, right?
It's not that nice, so..
Have you talked to Jonas since
we've come home?
Eh, no. I've tried but I feel like
he's trying to ignore me.
Oh? - I think he's a little embarrassed
about what happened at William's party.
But if he still has feelings for me,
we have to be able to talk about it.
I want us to be friends.
I don't want it to get in the way.
I think it's important that you
guys talk to each other.
Yeah I will. He can't ignore me when
school starts again.
How's it going with you and William?
There is no me and William.
No, I know. I was only joking.
I know that. Vilde would have a
breakdown if she knew.
I've never seen someone so obsessed
with another person. Have you?
No..
You don't think she's going to pay
to hook up, right?
What hook up?
Didn't you see the Penetrator stuff? They're
having a fundraiser. You didn't see it?
No?
Are you kidding me?
Okay, I have to show you.
It's really sick.
During Easter they trashed
a cabin in Trysil.
They got a bill of
300 fucking thousand Kroner.
It's so sick.
So now they're having a fundraiser.
Look: Help the Penetrators.
They're selling sweaters and
there's an auction to hook up with someone.
Hooking up with William starts
at 1000 Kroner. So sick!
They will have a charity party on Friday.
Hello, this is prostitution.
It wouldn't suprise me if Vilde ends
up paying to hook up with William.
Hi.
Willhelm!
Fucking hell, it's
lovely to see you.
Did you miss me?
-No!
Not even a little bit?
-I didn't.
Did you have a good Easter?
Yeah. Did you?
Good, yeah. Just a little wild.
I saw your event on Facebook.
Charming stuff.
You have to come.
-No!
Why not?
Because it's the dumbest thing I've seen in
my entire life.
Hook up auction? Seriously?
You know it's actually illegal? It's prostitution.
Are you jealous?
No.
Because I'll hook up with someone else?
That's why you're
being so grumpy.
I'm not grumpy. And I'm definitely not jealous.
I just think the entire event is horrible.
Europe is in a state of emergency.
Twelve million Syrians are fleeing.
People are dying of hunger.
What does it have to do with this?
-It has everything to do with this!
You guys trashed a cabin
for 300 thousand!
While the world is starving.
Imagine how much people are willing
to spend to hook up.
How high will they go?
Ten thousand Kroner to hook up with someone? No!
Think of... William. It's sick!
-Those people are stupid.
They'll fail to raise it all
on Friday anyway.
There's the hooking up, the sweaters,
partying on their bus with them.
They make a lot of effort.
They care about both-
Hello!
-Hi!
I brought lunch for you as well.
Oh, yeah.
Will you ask Noora, Vilde?
-Yeah!
We were talking about helping the
Penetrator-boys, out of solidarity.
We can use some of the money from our
bus budget for their bus.
But it's a bit boring to just donate money.
So we discussed participating in the hook up
auction. It's for a good cause.
Vilde, what world do you live in?
You know that millions of
refugees are starving?
And you think this is a good cause?
You think that we should give money
to a bunch of asshole kids?
Guys who just got themselves drunk
and trashed an entire cabin?
You don't always need to be so uptight.
Try to have a little humor.
It's a social event that gets the entire
school together. It's not just for fun.
It helps the refugees more than when we
sit at home and be sad for them.
If you used half of the energy you use
to think about William..
.. to think of refugees instead,
it might have helped a little bit.
So no hook up auction then?
-No, Vilde.
What about the party?
-Of course we're going to the party.
Are you guys serious now?
-Come on, Noora!
If even Sana thinks it's fun! She knows a litte
bit more about being a refugee than you.
[Since it's so important to you, I've decided we'll donate
10% of all the funds we raise tomorrow to the refugees.]
Why do I know anything about being a refugee?
[Since it's so important to you, I've decided we'll donate
10% of all the funds we raise tomorrow to the refugees.]
I was born in Norway.
[Since it's so important to you, I've decided we'll donate
10% of all the funds we raise tomorrow to the refugees.]
[But only if you come to the party.]
Because you're from another culture.
No.. I'm from the same culture as you.
[But only if you come to the party.]
[You know you're sick in the head right?]
You're a muslim.
Eh, yeah?
[You know you're sick in the head right?]
Muslim is another culture.
Islam is a religion, Einstein.
What's up today? Is it the pick-on-Vilde day?
[It's you who's sick in the head if you don't come.
Think of the refugees.]
Why are you all ganging up on me?
[It's you who's sick in the head if you don't come.
Think of the refugees.]
Have you thought about how much of my soul I put into this project?
[It's you who's sick in the head if you don't come.
Think of the refugees.]
[20%]
It's not to be popular, but to be with you guys.
It's you I love.
Can you not try to give back a little?
I'm giving you everything. Everything!
[Deal. But then you should be bloody sweet at the party.]
Can you not try to give back a little?
I'm giving you everything. Everything!
[Deal. But then you should be bloody sweet at the party.]
Yeah alright!
We're going to the party. Okay!
And.. the hook up auction?
No, Vilde.
Do you want to pay to
hook up with William?
Yes.
You know it's illegal?
It's prostitution.
Not if there's no sex.
It's hooking up.
Sex doesn't fall under hooking up.
Everyone knows that.
[And you've already won the hook up auction.
So you no longer have to be jealous.]
[I'm not jealous and I'm not joining the auction.]
[Yes you are.]
You see that? They care about refugees.
They're not a bunch of assholes.
Hey, there's Jonas!
Yeah..
There's something I have to tell you.
-Yeah?
I had hoped Jonas would
have told you himself.
Jonas is together with Isabel.
They got together on Easter.
Perhapes I should've told you..
.. but I thought it would be best
if you heard it from Jonas.
But he never said it, so..
What are you thinking?
I'm fine.
Sure?
-Yeah, yeah!
Eva, you're allowed to be upset.
He's your ex-boyfriend.
I'm not upset. I'm fine, really.
I think it's only good that he moved on.
We really are just friends.
It's fine.
You sure?
Yes, I'm totally sure.
Come, let's party now.
I think he's terribly in love with her.
They say you can see it in the way
he looks at her.
When he looks at her
when she's not looking at him.
He looks so.. He smiles at her
in a certain way.
Not really smiling, but you see
something in his eyes.
That he.. I don't know.
Do you think she's prettier than me?
Huh?
She is. Much, much prettier than me.
Eva, you have to stop now.
She's not prettier than you.
I just don't understand why
he didn't say anything.
He just pretends like it's nothing.
He has to say he has a girlfriend.
He has to introduce me.
They're going to announce who won
the hook up auction soon.
Where did you see that? -The girl who will
make out with William has paid 3000 Kroner.
You know what? If he hadn't thought
of introducing us to each other..
.. then I'll do it myself.
Hi! Isak!
-What's up?
I've missed you.
We never hang out anymore.
You know what?
You're so sweet.
Jonas has a girlfriend!
Did you know? She's a third year.
I've really missed you.
It's so good to see you.
No.
-What?
We'll just drop it.
Don't you want to make
out with me? Huh?
No, we'll just drop it.
Is it because you like guys?
He doesn't want to
make out with me.
We should go drink some water.
.. who has won the hook up auction?
The girl who won is..
What are you saying?
I can't hear what you're saying.
I'm not going to say it.
-You're not saying it?
Vilde! Take care of Eva.
She should have water.
Vilde..
-Hi.
I love you.
Should we get you some water?
Isak doesn't want to make out with me.
-No, he doesn't?
But.. Hi!
Do you want to make out with me?
There you are.
What's this stuff about the announcement
of the hook up auction?
And you're pissed as usual.
I mean it.
Have you gone around telling
people bullshit? -Bullshit?
You have to relax a little.
Have some faith in me.
Faith? Why should I have
faith in you?
You don't care about anyone
but yourself.
I care. 20% of the funds
goes to the refugees.
Because I'm here.
They don't care why
they're getting money.
You don't care about them. Not for real.
I care about you.
For real.
No. You don't.
If you really did you wouldn't have pressured me
to come to the party like this.
You don't have to be here
if you don't want to.
Yes, I do! How else will the
refugees get their money?
The refugees will get their
money anyway. So relax.
Yeah, but eh..
I have to be here and watch Eva.
So she doesn't do something stupid.
How do you think that's going?
I think I have to puke.
-You have to puke?
You have to puke?!
You can't puke here.
Aren't you getting tired of this game soon?
What game?
Pretending as if you don't like me?
That's not a game.
I'm not pretending.
Okay. This is what we'll do.
Look into my eyes.
And tell me you don't like me.
That's the dumbest thing I've heard.
Look at me.
Say you don't like me,
and I'm gone.
I swear.
I don't like you.
You don't have the right
to be pissed at me.
I'm not pissed at you.
I'm just trying to do what's
right here. What you're doing is shit.
As long as you get your way.
Okay.
You're insanely selfish, manipulating,
and self-involved.
And spoiled.
That's why I don't like you.
Was that all?
No!