Nikolai. William's brother.
She's not my girlfriend,
and she's leaving now.
I wonder how many girls William
will sleep with during Russetiden.
You're going to be sleeping around.
-Then you know more than me.
I won't hurt you.
And if you really want to meet my brother..
.. then I'll introduce you to him.
I don't think it's you Isak has feelings for.
Are that Chris and Isak?
Isn't that a little strange?
My phone battery is..
It's so bad.
-Yeah I know. Same with mine.
The Riot Club? Isn't that a bit of a weak concept?
-I don't know.
Russ concepts are not really my specialty.
Looks like they had fun at
the release party.
What are you looking at?
-Chris' instagram.
I saw something strange yesterday.
What?
Isak and Penetrator Chris were together.
What? Together how?
No. Isak got into the car
of Penetrator Chris.
Are you kidding?
-No!
Where was that?
-On the right side of school.
Imagine if they're in a relationship!
How crazy would that be?
Yeah but you don't have to be in a relationship
if you sit in a car together.
It's still a bit weird, you know?
-Because it seemed like they were trying to hide it.
Hide what?
-Nothing.
Say it!
Hey, tell me Noora.
Hide what?
Huh?
-Nothing!
Did you tell Eskild about Isak?
-No.
Who is Isak?
-No one.
Eva, don't start.
Don't say anything to Eskild. You don't
know what he's capable of.
Eva. Eskild
Friends!
She's just pissed.
Don't try to come between us.
It's jealousy.
Eva, say it to Eskild.
Cutie!
I can't hold it in!
Okay, we have a friend
who we think is gay.
Who is it?
Isak.
He's always together with a lot of girls
but we found gay porn on his phone.
Eh.. he's gay!
Excuse me, you think that everyone's gay Eskild.
I do not.
-You do!
Let me see pictures of him.
Give me some visuals.
I'll find one.
Okay, look at this.
Isakyaki? Okay.
Yeah, he's gay. I chatted with him
on Grindr last week.
Seriously?
I'm messing. He looks sweet thouhg.
Pouty, handsome.
So nice that he's gay!
He isn't gay.
You don't know..
We don't even know if he is.
I'm gonna find out.
Eskild!
You won't find out anything.
You're not a part of this.
I can chat with him if I want to.
You don't own Instagram. Jesus!
Do you know what you've started, huh?
I have to hurry..
for English.
Can't have more absences.
Hurry then.
See you after school?
Tomorrow. I have bus stuff tonight.
Maybe I can stay at your place.
Okay.
What is it?
-I can't leave now.
I have a hard-on,
so we have to stand here for a bit.
Don't be delicious.
It's physically impossible for me
to not be delicious, so..
True.
Say something that will turn me off.
When will I meet your brother?
Before the weekend, maybe.
I got a message from Vilde.
She was wondering if you guys could
party on our bus with us on Friday.
Are you keen?
No.
Why not?
William, I can't be on that bus
with you and Vilde.
Well okay. I have to go.
Don't touch me.
I heard you can get
chlamydia in your eye.
I don't want to..
-Oh, I get it.
I don't want to have
chlamydia in my mouth.
Tell me if you get it,
so we don't spread it.
Maybe we have it in our mouths.
-You think so?
I don't know. From Jonas?
Hello!
What is it?
Your lipstick is just a bit smudgy.
Oh yeah. I just ate, so..
Ate? Ate what? Dick?
Vilde has arranged that we can party on
the Penetrators bus on Friday.
The Riot Club.
-To me they'll always be the Penetrators.
We were talking about
who we want to hook up with.
Who do you want to hook up with?
Eh, no one.
-No..
Noora, it just so happens that we get
to go on the bus.
The situation there is a little different.
It's give and take.
[Now Vilde's saying that we're partying
with you guys. You have to stop it.]
The situation there is a little different.
It's give and take.
[Now Vilde's saying that we're partying
with you guys. You have to stop it.]
We have to give something back.
Vilde, that's the dumbest
thing I've heard.
There's no need to hook up with anyone.
I don't have to..
What about Julian? He's kind of your
type. He's the sweetest.
A little bit.. feminine?
What are you talking
about now, Vilde?
I'll fix it. You, Noora Amalie Saætre,
will get hook a up.
No, Vilde!
-I'll fix it, okay?
Yeah, so this is my room.
This is your room?
-Yeah.
Nice.
Thanks.
Remember when you said you
wouldn't have sex before you got married?
Eh, yes. I remember that.
That was really funny.
Yeah, but it wasn't a joke.
No..
No.
-No.
Yeah, same for me.
I think it's cool to wait.
Do you mean that?
No.
Okay..
Eskild! You can't just come into my
room whenever it suits you.
Who's that?
William. Eskild.
Eskild, William.
William, Eskild.
-I see.
What do you want?
I was chatting to that Isak guy.
He's not gay.
Eskild!
What?
Is it a secret that he
isn't gay, or what?
Fucking hell.
She's so uptight.
Can you do something about it?
Believe me, I'm trying.
You need dick, Noora. Dick.
Eskild!
[Now I know who you can hook up with.
Maksin! He's so handsome!]
Hey you.
Vilde still thinks that we're going
to party on your bus.
And.. you have to stop it.
Yeah but the guys are excited about partying
with a muslim, so it's still on.
Sana?
Yes.
Why?
Why not?
Okay, but you know I can't be on
that bus with you and Vilde.
We know this isn't going
to go well.
Then you'll stay home.
[I know I promised you'd meet Nico, but he's gone back
to Stockholm. You'll meet him in the summer.]
So what exactly did Eskild say?
[I know I promised you'd meet Nico, but he's gone back
to Stockholm. You'll meet him in the summer.]
He just said that he chatted with him,
and that he really wasn't gay.
How does he know he's gay or not?
I don't know. They have their
own language or something?
Did you ask what they talked about?
Eh, no.
I was just relieved that Eskild wasn't convinced,
or he would have started stalking him.
There's Chris.
Oh my god. They're gonna
talk in secret characters.
Did you see that?
Eh, yes!
That was the call-me sign!
That was such an obvious sign!
They're in a relationship.
It's not certain that they are.
-It is! What else?
You know what?
I will try to hook up with Chris
in the bus on Friday.
If he doesn't want to hook up with me,
then I'm convinced.
That's the plan.
Noora, this here is Julian.
He has been in Madrid.
She's a virgin.
Virgin!
Hi. Noora.
So you've been in Madrid, huh?
-Yeah.
Noora! Do you know what happened?
I hooked up with Chris, and his
phone started ringing.
"Isak calling" is what it said on the display.
So then he just pulled away.
Fucking hell, really!
What's going on?
Just stay here.
Okay?
Okay..
You promise?
What are you going to do?
Just stay here.
What's going on?
We have to stay here.
It's the Yakuza guys.