Nikolai. William's brother.
She's not my girlfriend
and she's leaving now.
I need some space!
I can't think properly
when I'm with you.
If nothing feels more important
to you than being with William..
You have to try to make it work.
Hi. Noora, wasn't it?
Some girls believe he's good deep down.
They believe he's going to be better for them.
You're standing here, while he's out there
somewhere sleeping with someone else.
[Fuck I lost my phone between the bus seats yesterday, and
only found it today. I'm in Lillehammer but it's shit and I miss
you so much. Can we please be done with the space stuff soon?]
[Love you.]
[Alcohol poisoning]
[Drugged?]
[Rape and sexual assault]
[Hi. What happened on Friday?
I don't remember anything.]
I blacked out.]
What's up? Have you locked your door?
-What is it?
William's outside.
Say that I'm not home.
-That'd be weird since I already said you're home.
Say that I'm sleeping or something.
Or that I'm sick.
He's really insistent. Can't you
just go out and talk to him?
Can't you just find an excuse, Eskild?
Okay.
Are you ok, or?
-Eskild! I..
I just want to be alone, okay?
Is that impossible for you to understand?
Okay, that's fine.
Noora. Noora!
Two seconds.
I have a friend who's a journalist at Aftenposten.
They want an article from a young voice.
I showed him the article
you wrote last week.
He liked it a lot. I suggested
you could write the article.
Isn't that cool?
Yeah.. I'm just not sure I can.
If I have time now.
There's a week left. Don't you want
to become a journalist? You have to do this.
Yeah, okay. I can try.
-Cool. I'll e-mail you then.
You tried to call me on Friday?
Wrong number.
Six times?
What's going on?
What's going on is that..
I said I want some space!
I asked for it, you have to give me space.
Whose locker is this?
Sana's.
What does it mean?
Whore.
Fucking hijab police.
They want war,
they'll get war.
Hello sunshine. What's up?
-I'll just have some food.
Should we go see Paradise afterwards?
Was it you who took my fishcakes?
Were those your fishcakes?
For fuck's sake, Eskild.
I can buy new ones in the morning.
I get my salary tomorrow.
I don't need fishcakes tomorrow,
I need fishcakes now!
I would've eaten two
fishcakes at five!
Now I don't have
anything to eat.
I can make something else
that's nice for you..
You can't make something else!
You can't even cook, Eskild!
The only thing you can do.. You can't shit
other than benefiting from people!
She's kind of right.
What the fuck, Linn?
Are you serious?
Oh my god.
How did the talk
with William go?
I dropped it. I don't think
we fit really well together.
What happened?
We logged into my brother's computer, copied all
the kinky messages with Jamilah, and posted it on his wall.
Are you joking?
What did she say?
-She hasn't said anything.
Did you bring me lunch today?
No, I forgot.
Want to borrow some
money to buy something?
No, no. I'm fine.
Hey, Sana?
-What?
I think we really got ourselves into shit now.
What is it?
Allah9753 commented on a Riot picture:
"Good click yesterday, guys."
What does that mean?
It means the hijab
police is not behind the hate account.
I'm sure it's one
of the Riot guys.
Fuck, it's the asshole
from the bus party.
Eh, Sana?
Oh no.
-They're coming this way.
What do we do?
-Honestly, run!
Huh?
-Run!
[Hi Noora. Didn't see your message til now. Nice to hear from you.
Don't worry. Absolutely nothing happened. Just a party. Nikko.]
William, we have to go.
William! We have to pick
up the bus in 30 minutes.
What's going on?
We have to talk.
I have to talk.
I know I shouldn't have smashed that
bottle on the Yakuza guy's head.
But there isn't anything
we can do about that now, okay?
He has terrorised half of Oslo
and beat up innocent people.
Including my best friend.
I'm just really angry and
frustrated that they were beaten up.
It was me who Yakuza was really after.
It's me they were going to take.
Chris and the guys are the
only one who have been there for me.
Because I don't even
really have any family.
You don't?
Dad's a workaholic and mom's going
around taking valium with wine.
My brother is a complete psychopath.
Psychopath?
He's just really manipulative.
That's why I was such an
asshole that morning. In the kitchen.
Had he found out
that I have feelings for you..
He would have
tried to fuck it up.
That's just how he is.
He doesn't tolerate that
others have something he doesn't.
I've taken a lot of shit from Nico.
That's because he's the only brother I have.
He's pretty much the only family I have.
But if he had tried to
fuck it up between the two of us..
.. I would've killed him.
I would've killed him.
I have to be together with you.
Say that we should be together.
Don't be so sad.
Fucking hell William,
we have to go.
I love you.
[No way! Fucked up! Just found this picture on my phone,
and then remembered EVERYTHING! You were so horny.
Haha! Behaved yourself like a little whore.]