If the answers that we need
&nbsp
to stop Savitar and save
you are in the future,
&nbsp
then that's where I need to go.
You're from before she dies, aren't you?
&nbsp
You trapped Savitar in the Speed Force.
Just tell me how you did it.
&nbsp
I had help. Her name's Tracy Brown.
She made the Speed Force trap for me.
&nbsp
You're telling me my ideas
about the Speed Force...
&nbsp
- I'm right?
- In the future.
&nbsp
We need you to build this trap now.
Caitlin's after Tracy.
&nbsp
That means she's working with Savitar.
- So you talked to Cecile?
- Told her everything.
&nbsp
Told her I love her. I told
her that you're The Flash.
&nbsp
Like I told you from the beginning...
I am the future Flash.
&nbsp
It's like looking in a mirror.
Well... not quite.
&nbsp
You're not so scary without your armor.
What can I say?
&nbsp
I outgrew red.
I know what you are.
&nbsp
You're a time remnant.
A temporal duplicate...
&nbsp
created when you run back in time
and meet yourself.
&nbsp
You brought a remnant to
life last year to defeat Zoom.
&nbsp
Your duplicate died,
saving the multiverse,
&nbsp
and you continued
your happy little life.
&nbsp
And it would've stayed that way,
but then you decided to play God.
&nbsp
You created Flashpoint
and changed everything.
&nbsp
I went to the future.
My future self told me that
&nbsp
he created time remnants to stop you.
But you slaughtered them all.
&nbsp
All but one.
Me.
&nbsp
I lived.
But a funny thing happened
&nbsp
when I did.
You. Joe.
&nbsp
Wally, Cisco.
You all shunned me because I
wasn't the true Barry Allen.
&nbsp
I was an aberration.
A disposable hero.
&nbsp
Future you failed to
mention that, didn't he?
&nbsp
How did you become Savitar?
I was broken...
&nbsp
and alone.
I wanted the pain to end.
&nbsp
And that's when I
realized the truth, Barry.
&nbsp
God feels no pain.
All I had to do was become one.
&nbsp
And I only need two more things:
for Iris to die
&nbsp
so that you are driven
so far into the dark
&nbsp
that I can be born.
And the other?
&nbsp
It may sound ironic
given who I'm talking to,
&nbsp
but I'll keep that one to myself.
What happens if I kill myself?
&nbsp
If I die, then you'll never be created.
Cause and effect's a tricky thing.
&nbsp
Didn't work so well for Eddie, did it?
Shot himself in the chest...
&nbsp
Thawne's still kicking around.
See, that's the thing
about time travel, Barry.
&nbsp
The more you do it, the
less the rules apply to you.
&nbsp
But us having this conversation now...
we're changing the future.
&nbsp
Are we?
My ascendancy is nearing.
&nbsp
When I have control of all of time,
it will be you who is
abandoned and forgotten.
&nbsp
You're gonna die right here!
I forgot to tell you...
&nbsp
my suit's cooler than yours.
Synced and corrected by Aaronnmb
www.addic7ed.com
&nbsp
It's impossible.
I don't understand. How
could Savitar be you?
&nbsp
He's not me. Not really.
He's all the worst parts of you.
&nbsp
It's like in "Star Trek"
when the transporter
&nbsp
splits Kirk into good Kirk and bad Kirk.
Please tell me you at least
have "Star Trek" on your Earth.
&nbsp
- "Voyager."
- I hate spinoffs.
&nbsp
That explains why Caitlin
was willing to follow him.
&nbsp
- He has a face that she trusts.
- Half of one anyway.
&nbsp
So when the Legends found
that message in the Waverider
&nbsp
from old you saying
"Don't trust Barry Allen,"
&nbsp
it was talking about
Savitar Barry Allen.
&nbsp
It's all coming together...
in the worst way.
&nbsp
You said you made Savitar?
- How?
- Peep this.
&nbsp
Four years from now,
future Flash creates...
&nbsp
a time remnant to fight Savitar.
But Savitar lets that remnant live
&nbsp
so that it can later become Savitar.
So once Savitar is
imprisoned in the Speed Force,
&nbsp
this remnant starts to go crazy.
And he goes back in time to the past...
&nbsp
and becomes Savitar.
Creating the lie that he
was the first speedster,
&nbsp
spreading the myth and recruiting
acolytes throughout the ages.
&nbsp
That doesn't make any sense.
Which came first, Savitar
or the time remnant?
&nbsp
It's a closed loop.
No beginning, no end.
&nbsp
It's just one endless cycle.
Classic chicken and the
egg scenario, I think, eh?
&nbsp
A time remnant, it's, um...
it's like a duplicate of you, right?
&nbsp
So it has your feelings, your memories.
So why would he want to hurt us?
&nbsp
Why would he want to kill Iris?
H.R., how's Tracy coming
with the Speed Force trap?
&nbsp
Good, yeah, good. Slow.
Get her to speed up, all right?
&nbsp
I'll do that now. Can do.
If Savitar is a version
of Barry from the future
&nbsp
and he remembers
everything that Barry does,
&nbsp
how are we ever going to come
up with a plan to stop him?
&nbsp
What was he like?
Broken.
&nbsp
You know...
all this time I thought
that Savitar is this...
&nbsp
monster.
It's hard to picture
what might happen, and...
&nbsp
it being you that...
I... I know it's not you. I'm...
&nbsp
Part of him is.
He said it was like looking
in a mirror, and he was right.
&nbsp
But not just the way that he looked.
It was...
&nbsp
it was his eyes.
The pain that was inside them.
&nbsp
I've seen that in myself.
When I think about...
&nbsp
how my parents died so violently...
sometimes I want to repay that
violence with more violence.
&nbsp
I want to make someone else...
hurt as much as I do.
&nbsp
But you don't ever do that.
You're not him. You're a good person.
&nbsp
But it's in there,
you know. That's in me.
&nbsp
That power, that pain,
that's where Savitar
comes from. From loss.
&nbsp
From losing you.
You're not going to lose me.
&nbsp
Do you hear me?
And we are going to stop Savitar.
&nbsp
You are not alone. He is.
And he is not a god.
&nbsp
Jay told me that we're not gods.
He was wrong.
&nbsp
We could be.
Any speedster, and
it wouldn't take much.
&nbsp
When the love that we feel in our hearts
is drowned in anger...
&nbsp
when the bad memories
outweigh the good ones.
&nbsp
What am I going to have
to become to stop him?
&nbsp
Hey! Oh, bad time?
No, man, what's up?
&nbsp
I just came up with the best idea ever.
Either that or it's the worst idea ever.
&nbsp
- But...
- It's an idea.
&nbsp
It's an idea!
You want to give me a perm?
&nbsp
It's not for your hair, Steel Magnolia.
This is for your brain, okay?
&nbsp
I want to stop you from
making new memories.
&nbsp
What are you talking about?
Savitar knows everything we're gonna do
&nbsp
because he remembers doing it.
He's a future Barry. So...
&nbsp
what if Barry can't remember
what we're doing now?
&nbsp
You want to mess with his brain?
Just a little bit.
&nbsp
It's a minimal procedure.
It'll still be the same
Barry you know and love,
&nbsp
except he just won't be able
to retain new information.
&nbsp
There's two types of memory,
Allen. Short-term and long-term.
&nbsp
- Long-term is where you...
- Okay, Julian, just stop.
&nbsp
This is my presentation;
I'm the expert here.
&nbsp
This is the part of your brain
that retains new information
&nbsp
before sending it to the
cortex to be stored forever.
&nbsp
So what if we block that chain...
with a magnetic disruption?
&nbsp
So Savitar won't be able to remember
whatever strategy we come
up with to defeat him.
&nbsp
Which means he can't be two
steps ahead of us anymore.
&nbsp
With any luck, we'll actually
put him one step behind.
&nbsp
Beautiful.
Cause and effect.
&nbsp
Barry, what do you think?
Let's do it.
&nbsp
Wait, wasn't Caitlin the
expert on brains around here?
&nbsp
She was.
But this is something we'll
have to do without her.
&nbsp
I trust you.
You won't feel a thing.
&nbsp
Okay, let's get this show on the road.
The disrupter is attached
to your hippocampus.
&nbsp
So, it's ready.
Okay, ready for zapping.
&nbsp
Can we not call it "zapping"?
Ready to activate.
&nbsp
In three...
two...
&nbsp
one.
- Sweet dreams, my beautiful boy.
- Way to go, slugger.
&nbsp
Run, Barry, run!
I have watched you be
in love with Iris...
&nbsp
Maybe we were meant to be together.
Okay, that should do it.
&nbsp
All right.
Right. How do you feel?
&nbsp
I feel fine.
You see? He feels fine.
&nbsp
Barry...
Barry?
&nbsp
Barry.
Who's Barry?
&nbsp
Not fine.
Who are all of you?
&nbsp
What's going on?
Seriously, who are you guys?
&nbsp
- Okay, Barry, stay calm.
- Who's Barry?
&nbsp
- Cisco!
- Slight miscalculation.
&nbsp
Slight wouldn't be a word I'd use.
Where the hell am I?
&nbsp
Is this a dentist office?
No, no. This is S.T.A.R. Labs.
&nbsp
St... Labs? A laboratory?
St... a laboratory? What are you?
&nbsp
- Are you guys experimenting on me?
- No one is ex...
&nbsp
Well, yes, technically, yes.
But... but it was consensual.
&nbsp
- You were? You...
- Yes.
&nbsp
Why can't I remember anything?
Why can't I remember my name?
&nbsp
Your name is Barry.
My name's not Barry.
&nbsp
I don't know what my
name is, but my name's...
&nbsp
"Bartholomew Henry Allen."
- That's not a good name.
- Look, Barry...
&nbsp
Are you sure I don't
go by "Bart"? Can...
&nbsp
"Bart" feels more natural to me.
- Can we go with Bart?
- Bart's kinda cool.
&nbsp
- Okay.
- Wally!
&nbsp
Okay, hey. Let's just
get you back in the chair.
&nbsp
No! No, no, no. I'm not...
- I'm not getting in the chair.
- Just get in the chair...
&nbsp
No, how do I know you
didn't kidnap me here
&nbsp
to do some weird brain surgery on me?
Or maybe you're like those criminals
&nbsp
who trick people into hotel rooms
so they can steal their kidneys.
&nbsp
Do I still have my kidneys?
We don't want your kidneys.
&nbsp
Okay, Barry...
look at these photographs.
&nbsp
We're your friends.
Your family.
&nbsp
We just want to help you, okay?
That's a nice ring.
&nbsp
Who's the lucky guy?
You are, Barry.
&nbsp
Look, I know you're scared, okay?
You can trust us.
&nbsp
Cisco.
- A minute.
- Yes, sir.
&nbsp
I'm gonna be right back, okay?
- Wally, stay with him, okay?
- Me?
&nbsp
So how do we know each other?
Oh, I'm your brother.
&nbsp
There is no sign of any...
permanent structural damage.
&nbsp
Then why can't he remember anything?
Julian?
&nbsp
He appears to be suffering
from some sort of...
&nbsp
- psychogenic retrograde amnesia.
- ... Amnesia.
&nbsp
What if we didn't account for
Barry's increase neural velocity,
&nbsp
due to his super speed?
Wait, do we think he
knows he's The Flash?
&nbsp
That he has super speed?
Hey, Barry. Catch.
&nbsp
Sorry.
Oh, my Lord.
&nbsp
- He's, like, god-awful.
- He's pathetic.
&nbsp
Can't we flip a switch... undo it?
Okay, we are not
flipping any more switches
&nbsp
until we figure this thing out.
It's Cecile. Hey, babe.
&nbsp
An emergency?
All right, bye.
&nbsp
Okay, Cecile needs Barry at CCPD,
like, right now. She says it's urgent.
&nbsp
He can't possibly go
out in that condition.
&nbsp
Okay, um, my dad and I
will take Barry to Cecile.
&nbsp
You and Cisco figure out a
way to get Barry's memory back.
&nbsp
And fast.
Yeah?
&nbsp
Okay.
You don't want to work?
&nbsp
Well then, I don't need you!
Um, am I to infer then... that, uh,
&nbsp
you've hit a little speed bump
in your quest to build a device
&nbsp
to trap Savitar in the
Speed Force? The... the...
&nbsp
Accelerated matter
microgenerator projectile.
&nbsp
No, I know. It doesn't
exactly roll off the tongue.
&nbsp
No, it doesn't.
How about...
&nbsp
we call this fancy device of yours...
- You know, you probably shouldn't...
- ... call it the...
&nbsp
Speed Force Cannon.
Speed Force Bazooka.
&nbsp
Speed Force Gun.
Speed Force Bazooka. Is better, yeah.
&nbsp
But if the Speed Force Bazooka
doesn't start working soon,
&nbsp
we're gonna have to start calling it
the Speed Force Epic Fail.
&nbsp
- Why? What's the problem?
- Okay. The accelerometer.
&nbsp
It sucks a hell of a lot of air watts,
- which is measured...
- Alright. Stop talking science!
&nbsp
You need to take a step back...
from the Speed Force Bazooka.
&nbsp
- There's not time.
- There's always time!
&nbsp
Because sometimes, to move forward,
you have to take a step back.
&nbsp
Step... back.
You see? Yes.
&nbsp
Shake a little...
Shake out those
shoulders. I feel like...
&nbsp
Oh, oh, my gosh.
The tension in your shoulders...
&nbsp
Think of something that calms you.
- Coffee.
- Co...
&nbsp
Oh, yes.
But not just any coffee. Piping hot...
&nbsp
- Indonesian dark roast with...
- Yep.
&nbsp
Raspberry and coriander...
I've never met another person
&nbsp
who uses copious amounts
of caffeine to chill out.
&nbsp
I've never met another person either.
I... I-I-I'm relaxed.
&nbsp
Are you relaxed?
- Mm-hmm.
&nbsp
You, uh...
- And I'll... okay.
- Yeah.
&nbsp
I mean... okay.
Yeah.
&nbsp
Good morning, people.
Hi. I'm Barry Allen.
&nbsp
- You can call me Bart.
- O... kay.
&nbsp
So you said there was an
emergency. Where's the fire?
&nbsp
Ah, it's funny you
should put it like that.
&nbsp
- Lucious Coolidge.
- Who?
&nbsp
- Heat Monger.
- The worst arsonist Central City's seen
&nbsp
since Mick Rory went off the grid.
That is, until Flash here stopped him.
&nbsp
What's Flash?
Uh, ah, so what... what is the problem?
&nbsp
Judge Hankerson. He's got
an opening in his docket,
&nbsp
so he moved Coolidge's
probable cause hearing
&nbsp
up to this afternoon.
Barry was the CSI on the case.
&nbsp
So I need him to testify
in order to hold
Coolidge over for trial.
&nbsp
Uh, yeah, no.
Barry can't do that.
&nbsp
Why not?
Uh...
&nbsp
What do you mean he has amnesia?
Bar, what's her name?
&nbsp
Um... Felicia?
Oh, my God.
&nbsp
Is this... is this like a...
like a Flash thing?
&nbsp
Was he battling a super villain
who used his evil powers
to steal Barry's memory?
&nbsp
Um...
no, we sort of accidentally did this
&nbsp
to him ourselves.
Why?
&nbsp
That doesn't matter. What does matter...
is you stalling that judge.
&nbsp
Barry is in no condition
to testify in court.
&nbsp
Joe, if Barry can't testify,
Coolidge walks.
&nbsp
And then God help us all.
Okay. We'll figure out something.
&nbsp
Please do.
It was nice meeting you.
&nbsp
Oh. Yeah.
You too... Bart.
&nbsp
I got some friends
down at the courthouse.
&nbsp
I'm gonna go down there
and see if we can delay
&nbsp
this whole Coolidge
situation, all right?
&nbsp
I'm sorry.
For what?
&nbsp
I don't know. It just
seems like everybody's upset
&nbsp
and it feels like it's my fault.
No. No, not at all.
&nbsp
Look, we just want you
to get back to normal.
&nbsp
That's it, okay?
Well, I would, if I could
remember what normal is.
&nbsp
I mean, what have you
and I been doing lately?
&nbsp
Are we planning the wedding?
Like, are we sending
out wedding invitations
&nbsp
or picked a honeymoon destination, or...
Am I a warm weather guy
or a cold weather guy?
&nbsp
Actually, we've been a
little busy lately, so...
&nbsp
With what?
Um, nothing that you
need to worry about, okay?
&nbsp
Okay. You know what's weird?
I know we just ate, but
I'm already feeling hungry.
&nbsp
Yeah, let's get some food in you.
- All right.
- Okay.
&nbsp
What's that saying?
"Man plans and God laughs?"
&nbsp
Well, men are planning.
And what's the God of Speed doing?
&nbsp
Kneeling.
Brooding time is over.
&nbsp
You revealed yourself.
Now what?
&nbsp
Any idea what to do
with Flash and Friends?
&nbsp
Because we are getting pretty close
to your big becoming,
&nbsp
and if we don't take them down,
neither one of us gets what we want.
&nbsp
Hello? Anybody home?
What are you doing?
&nbsp
Who are you?
What's wrong with you?
&nbsp
Who... am... I?
- Science club.
- Yeah.
&nbsp
- Key Club...
- Mm-hmm.
&nbsp
- Astronomy Club...
- Yup.
&nbsp
- Yearbook?
- Yeah.
&nbsp
- And anime club?
- Oh, yeah.
&nbsp
You loved... loved... "Dragon Ball Z."
I don't know what that is.
&nbsp
Yeah, I couldn't
explain that show to you
&nbsp
- even if I wanted to, so...
- Okay.
&nbsp
- Sorry.
- I definitely had...
&nbsp
quite the nerd thing going on, huh?
Yeah, a little bit.
&nbsp
I thought you said we were
best friends in high school.
&nbsp
Yeah, we were.
Then why didn't you give
me some advice, help me out?
&nbsp
Oh, believe me, okay? I tried.
- Really? You did?
- Yes.
&nbsp
Okay, because I have evidence
that you did not.
&nbsp
Um, I don't remember any of this,
but even I can see how
wrong that look was.
&nbsp
This is visual terrorism.
I won't look at it anymore.
&nbsp
What?
Uh, you just...
&nbsp
You're so different. You're so light.
What do you mean?
&nbsp
I don't know, it's
like you're not carrying
&nbsp
the weight of the
world on your shoulders.
&nbsp
So, what, I was like...
brooding all the time before?
&nbsp
- Sometimes.
- Yeah?
&nbsp
- Yeah.
- Really?
&nbsp
I don't know, it's just...
it's really nice to
see you smiling so much.
&nbsp
I mean...
how could I not,
&nbsp
knowing I'm gonna be with
you for the rest of my life?
&nbsp
- Uh-oh.
- What?
&nbsp
I got to get to the courthouse.
Oh, yeah, of course.
&nbsp
- Yeah, I got to...
- Hey, yeah.
&nbsp
Um...
I'll... yeah, later. Okay.
&nbsp
Okay.
Docket number CC-15-204.
&nbsp
Evidentiary hearing for Central
City versus the defendant,
&nbsp
Lucious Coolidge.
- I see the city wishes to file...
- Cutting it real close, guys..
&nbsp
- ... felony charges...
- You ready to testify?
&nbsp
No. No, I'm not.
Yes, he is. He just
needs one minute, please.
&nbsp
The prosecution may proceed.
Too late. He's up.
&nbsp
Here. Just take these.
I wear glasses?
&nbsp
You will now. Just put 'em on.
- You'll be okay.
- Just don't get them wet.
&nbsp
- Your Honor, I, uh...
- What? Wh...
&nbsp
I call Barry Allen to the stand.
Raise your right hand, please.
&nbsp
You swear to tell the
truth, the whole truth,
&nbsp
and nothing but the truth?
I do, yes.
&nbsp
Thank you. Miss Horton?
- Mr. Allen...
- Can I sit?
&nbsp
Please, just...
You are a crime scene investigator
&nbsp
for the Central City
police department, correct?
&nbsp
Uh...
oh, this is so cool.
&nbsp
Well, I'm so glad you enjoy testifying,
but please just answer the question.
&nbsp
Of course.
Uh, yes, I am a CSI
&nbsp
at the CCPD under the expert
direction of Julian Albert.
&nbsp
Smiley face.
Want to cut it out with the emojis?
&nbsp
Mr. Allen,
can you tell me...
&nbsp
in your expert opinion,
what substance do you
see in this photograph?
&nbsp
Uh, shellac flakes.
Shellac is a resin
secreted by female lac bugs
&nbsp
found in large quantities
of the trees in Thailand...
&nbsp
that's too fast, that's too...
Mr. Allen, are you all right?
&nbsp
Yes, I'm sorry. I'm fine.
I just, um...
&nbsp
it's getting hot in here.
What else is unique
about shellac flakes?
&nbsp
It's the fire accelerant
used in all of the arson cases
&nbsp
associated with Heat Monger.
Such an embarrassing name.
&nbsp
I like it. I think it's great.
And how would you know when
shellac flakes have been used?
&nbsp
We calculate flame
temperature and burn patterns,
&nbsp
and a telltale sign is
when shellac is burned
&nbsp
into potassium perk-er-lorate
or ammonium perchlorate,
&nbsp
which is considered a
high-temperature accelerant fire.
&nbsp
Hmm. So, then...
would you say the fires in these photos
&nbsp
would be considered high-temperature
accelerant fires?
&nbsp
Uh, yes,
because...
&nbsp
Ow!
Uh-oh.
&nbsp
- Um...
- Mr. Allen?
&nbsp
Can you continue?
Yes, I can... I can continue.
&nbsp
The... uh, yes, the fires were...
high-temperature accelerant fires,
&nbsp
because the flames...
were, were...
&nbsp
very yellow.
Very yellow?
&nbsp
And that's your expert
opinion on accelerant fires?
&nbsp
Mr. Allen?
Ms. Horton, if Mr. Allen
is unable to elaborate,
&nbsp
I'll have no choice but to dismiss.
Mr. Allen?
&nbsp
That's... um...
Dismissed.
&nbsp
How'd it go?
Marvelous. They let the pyro go.
&nbsp
- What went wrong?
- Everything.
&nbsp
Barry's memory loss is
starting to become a problem.
&nbsp
It sure is.
For more than just him.
&nbsp
I don't have my speed.
Not anymore. And I know why.
&nbsp
If you want to fix this and help Barry,
you are gonna do exactly as I say.
&nbsp
Now this Heat Monger's
gonna go free because of me,
&nbsp
and I feel awful.
Barry, it's not your fault.
&nbsp
It's just that now there's
a bad guy on the streets,
&nbsp
and I can't do anything about it.
What? Is that not something
I would've said before?
&nbsp
That is exactly something
you would've said before.
&nbsp
There's just something about
you that always wants to help.
&nbsp
This is our place?
How do we afford to live here?
&nbsp
Wow.
You have great taste.
&nbsp
Uh, actually, this is all you.
I find that hard to believe.
&nbsp
Is that me?
Yeah.
&nbsp
Who are these people?
They're your parents.
&nbsp
You don't remember anything
about what happened?
&nbsp
Why, did something bad happen?
They died.
&nbsp
It was unexpected, but...
they died peacefully.
&nbsp
That's why you came to
live with Joe and me.
&nbsp
And that's when we met?
Uh, no, actually, we
were friends before then.
&nbsp
I remember the first
time that I saw you.
&nbsp
You were the happiest
boy that I'd ever met.
&nbsp
I have a feeling that's
because you entered my life.
&nbsp
It's okay.
What the...
&nbsp
Barry! Are you okay?
What just happened to me?!
&nbsp
These powers are so cool.
I can literally feel electricity
&nbsp
coursing through my body.
I mean, is it always like
this? This is amazing.
&nbsp
We just walked into a buzzkill.
My presence usually dampens the mood.
&nbsp
- Joe, don't.
- You fire, I'll fire.
&nbsp
What the hell is she doing here?
- She wants to help.
- Help?
&nbsp
- With what?
- With the fact that I lost my powers.
&nbsp
Barry, why don't you give us a minute?
Sure, yeah. Are you
like a super villain?
&nbsp
Just asking. Okay.
How did this happen?
&nbsp
You got rid of Barry's memories.
What Barry remembers, Savitar remembers.
&nbsp
So Savitar's lost his memories too?
Savitar loses his memory,
he doesn't go along
&nbsp
with the plan to give Wally powers.
Cause and effect.
&nbsp
But if you let me help you figure out
how to get Barry's memories back,
&nbsp
everything goes back to the way it was.
- Kid Flash runs again.
- And Savitar survives.
&nbsp
And Iris dies.
Life's full of difficult choices.
&nbsp
Or it isn't.
If Savitar gets his memory
back, what's in it for you?
&nbsp
That's my business.
You think that Barry
can become The Flash?
&nbsp
Yeah. He can learn.
I still know how to do
everything. I can teach him.
&nbsp
Okay.
Maybe this is how you defeat Savitar.
&nbsp
But there's still a lot
of villains in this city,
&nbsp
and no Flashes to protect it.
Is that really a chance
you're willing to take?
&nbsp
- Hi.
- Ah!
&nbsp
- I'm still here.
- Yeah, you are.
&nbsp
Because when you left, I stayed.
We gotta talk about the
elephant in the room.
&nbsp
But you know what,
I... I have a job to do.
&nbsp
We have to build that device.
We've got to focus on the task at hand.
&nbsp
Do you understand what I'm saying?
- I totally understand.
- From here on out,
&nbsp
whenever I look into your azure eyes,
flecked with gray,
like a summer rainstorm
&nbsp
coming to kiss my lips,
the only thing I'm
gonna be thinking about
&nbsp
is how I can best inspire that...
beautiful, sexy brain.
&nbsp
Sparks.
You felt them too.
&nbsp
- No.
- No?
&nbsp
- No, I mean yes, obviously.
- Oh, okay.
&nbsp
Sparks. Jumping between
two parallel wires...
&nbsp
a modified high-voltage climbing arc.
I guess my work here is done.
&nbsp
You should never have
tried this without Caitlin.
&nbsp
Well, we didn't really have
much of choice, now, did we?
&nbsp
Also, don't refer to
yourself in the third person.
&nbsp
It's Caitlin. It's you.
It's the same person.
&nbsp
It's just confusing.
Hand me the girard processor.
&nbsp
It'll help me prime his neocortical
and medial frontal lobes.
&nbsp
What?
Nothing.
&nbsp
Oh, golly. Look at us.
Just three musketeers working away.
&nbsp
Just like old times, huh?
Hey, Julian, did Caitlin
ever tell you about our time
&nbsp
working on the Particle
Accelerator with Ronnie?
&nbsp
No. No, she did not.
There was this one time
&nbsp
we had this very strict deadline,
and Dr. Wells was super hard on us.
&nbsp
- All of us, even Hartley.
- Who's... who's Hartley?
&nbsp
Oh, he was this guy we used
to work with. Such a dick.
&nbsp
You actually reminded me a lot of
him when you first came onboard.
&nbsp
Anyway, so we were working
on the iridium plating for the, um...
&nbsp
What was it called again?
The synchrotron, that's what it was.
&nbsp
So anyway, we were struggling,
and we were burning the midnight oil,
&nbsp
and we could not get
the dubnium capacitor
&nbsp
to hold a single charge.
And so all of a sudden...
&nbsp
Ronnie just loses all his chill.
He turns beet red,
&nbsp
and he starts yelling at the thing like,
"Come on, you dumb-nium capacitor!"
&nbsp
"Take charge."
Yes!
&nbsp
Yes.
Oh, my God.
&nbsp
I think about all the
memories I cherish most, and...
&nbsp
and you're in every single
one of them, Caitlin.
&nbsp
Let's figure this out.
I don't want to be here
any longer than I have to.
&nbsp
Suit yourself.
Okay!
&nbsp
Guys, I still can't
believe I have these powers.
&nbsp
They're amazing.
I mean...
&nbsp
I think that I could be a superhero.
All right, well is it
cool if I run some more?
&nbsp
- Have at it.
- All right.
&nbsp
I haven't seen him this
happy in a long time.
&nbsp
Try ever.
It's the first time he
hasn't been weighed down
&nbsp
by the tragedies of his past, you know?
First time he's actually
been free of them.
&nbsp
You don't want his
memory restored, do you?
&nbsp
Dad, I...
I can't say that seeing
him happy and light
&nbsp
isn't something I have wished for him,
because... yeah, it is.
&nbsp
Sweetheart,
I wish that for him, too. But you
didn't fall in love with The Flash.
&nbsp
You fell in love with Barry Allen.
Dad, I know this is a
different version of him,
&nbsp
but he's...
he's still Barry.
&nbsp
No, he's not, honey.
Look, until yesterday,
&nbsp
Barry had 28 years of
experiences to define him,
&nbsp
and some of those memories were
bad, but some were good, too.
&nbsp
But without those memories,
the Barry Allen we know and love...
&nbsp
is gone.
Whoo-hoo!
&nbsp
I don't know, Dad.
You know, part of me can't help but...
&nbsp
think that this is some
sort of gift, you know...
&nbsp
that this is the life that
he was supposed to have.
&nbsp
Maybe the city doesn't need The Flash.
Hey, everybody!
&nbsp
Happy Friday!
So I am a superhero?
&nbsp
Yeah.
- A real good one.
- Huh.
&nbsp
You're The Flash.
You sure The Streak isn't
a better name, maybe?
&nbsp
Turn on the TV.
Uh, okay. Yeah.
&nbsp
Eyewitnesses say the man who
set the fire to the offices
&nbsp
is none other than Lucious
Coolidge, AKA Heat Monger.
&nbsp
That's the guy that
went free because of me.
&nbsp
At this rate, it won't be long
before the whole thing burns down.
&nbsp
There's hundreds of
people who work in there.
&nbsp
We need to stop it.
How? I mean, you can't right now.
&nbsp
No, but I can.
Barry, you don't know
how to use your powers.
&nbsp
- Bar...
- You just said I'm a superhero.
&nbsp
And a good one, right?
I mean, memories or
not... I can't stand by,
&nbsp
and watch people die
if I can prevent it.
&nbsp
Um, forgot the suit.
Barry? You okay?
&nbsp
Uh, yeah, I'm good.
Stopping's hard.
&nbsp
How do I save everybody inside?
You just run them out of there.
&nbsp
I barely got here myself.
How am I supposed to
run with someone else?
&nbsp
There's gotta be something we can do.
There is something we can do:
&nbsp
jump-start his brain using that thing.
We have not done a test run.
&nbsp
- There's no time to test it now.
- What is that thing?
&nbsp
This can send electrical charges
through the transmitters in his suit
&nbsp
and theoretically,
should jolt his memory.
&nbsp
You want to electroshock his brain?
Won't that fry it even more?
&nbsp
If we don't do that, all
those people are gonna die.
&nbsp
Life's a game of chance.
Okay, Barry, you're
gonna feel something.
&nbsp
Might hurt, might sting, might suck.
- Wait, what?
- Probably all three.
&nbsp
Okay, here we go.
Barry?
&nbsp
Uh, yeah, I still don't remember.
Why didn't that work?
That was supposed to work.
&nbsp
We kick-started his temporal lobe.
Now he just needs to access it.
&nbsp
Gas is in the tank, we just
need to turn the ignition.
&nbsp
We need a visceral
memory to spark his brain.
&nbsp
Okay...
okay.
&nbsp
Barry?
I need you to remember.
&nbsp
- I can't!
- Yes, yes, you can. Okay?
&nbsp
Okay, listen to me.
The night that your mom died,
&nbsp
I didn't want to tell you how,
but she didn't die peacefully.
&nbsp
- She was murdered.
- What?
&nbsp
And you came to live with us.
My dad brought you inside, and...
&nbsp
you were in shock...
you weren't even crying.
&nbsp
And later that night, a sound woke me,
and I crawled out of my bed,
&nbsp
and I realized that the sound
was coming from downstairs.
&nbsp
I peered over the banister, and...
I found you crying alone.
&nbsp
I knew I had to go to you.
I sat next to you, and...
&nbsp
you put your head in my lap,
and I held you while you cried.
&nbsp
And I didn't know it
then, but now looking back,
&nbsp
I realize that that was the
night that we fell in love.
&nbsp
That was the night that we realized
how much we needed each other.
&nbsp
And look...
I so wish...
&nbsp
that I could take your
dark memories away.
&nbsp
I wish...
that I could make all
of that pain go away,
&nbsp
but I can't.
Okay? But what I do know, what I know,
&nbsp
is that for every bad memory,
there is a good one...
&nbsp
that will get you through it.
Run, Barry, run!
&nbsp
Barry?
I remember...
&nbsp
I remember.
I remember everything.
&nbsp
I remember everything!
Now for this fire.
&nbsp
I don't think I can
put this fire out alone.
&nbsp
You don't have to.
Yes!
&nbsp
Looks like you remembered
how to save the day.
&nbsp
Like riding a bike.
- Your mother's maiden name.
- Thompson.
&nbsp
CODIS is an acronym for what?
Combined DNA Index System.
&nbsp
Okay.
In the third grade, you
renamed the class hamster to...
&nbsp
Alexander Ham Bell.
I was eight years old.
&nbsp
So you got your memories back.
Now we can all focus our attention on...
&nbsp
stopping Savitar.
Good luck with that.
&nbsp
Please tell me we're not gonna
just let her walk out of here.
&nbsp
- Now you want to fight?
- We don't want to fight you.
&nbsp
Can't really avoid that now, can we?
Yeah, we can. You can stay here with us.
&nbsp
We're your friends. Your family.
Caitlin, I can fix you.
&nbsp
You already tried.
Well then, I'll try harder.
&nbsp
I don't care what it takes.
I don't care what I have to do.
&nbsp
I swear to you, I will find you a cure.
Caitlin, I love you.
&nbsp
I don't love you, Julian.
I never did.
&nbsp
I never loved any of you.
She's gone?
&nbsp
Yeah.
Maybe too far gone now.
&nbsp
We'll figure out a way to get her back.
Just like we figured
out how to get you back.
&nbsp
You sure this is the me you want?
With all the baggage?
&nbsp
Seeing you without the weight
of everything that's happened,
&nbsp
seeing you happy, like you were
before your mother was killed?
&nbsp
Without all of that
darkness haunting you,
&nbsp
you were finally free.
It was nice.
&nbsp
I did the same thing months ago.
What do you mean?
&nbsp
That freedom? I had that.
When I was with my mom and
dad again in Flashpoint,
&nbsp
and I could've let it stay like that.
I could've let the memories
of this timeline fade, but...
&nbsp
if I'd done that, I would've lost Joe,
and Cisco, and Wally,
and Caitlin, and you.
&nbsp
Pain and darkness... it's a part of me.
You know, I need it to fuel me,
&nbsp
to push me to be a better person,
to be a better hero.
&nbsp
To keep me from ever
forgetting who I am.
&nbsp
Now that...
is the Barry Allen I know and love.
&nbsp
Hey, you guys... okay!
You guys, you got to come see this.
&nbsp
Y-you got to come see this.
What is that?
&nbsp
This is the Speed Force Bazooka.
- Good, right?
- And that's gonna trap Savitar?
&nbsp
There is a tiny little problem.
- What's that?
- It's, uh...
&nbsp
In order to generate enough power...
to magnetize Savitar's radial field
&nbsp
and keep him in a state
of perpetual stasis...
&nbsp
- Stasis.
- ... inside the Speed Force,
&nbsp
- we need by my calculations...
- By calculations...
&nbsp
3.86 terajoules of energy.
I'm guessing that's more
energy than in a AAA battery.
&nbsp
Yes. That's more energy than in the sun.
Guys, where are we gonna
find something like that?
&nbsp