Why don't you want to talk to me?
I think I was raped by William's brother.
Is there no one else you can ask?
Someone who was at the party?
There was a girl from our school. Mari.
Tell me you didn't sleep with my brother.
I don't know.
Yes?
Hi.
Are you up for a visit from a friend?
What are you doing?
I'm just throwing
out a lot of shit I don't need.
You had such long hair.
When is this from?
Ninth grade.
Have you heard something from William?
Eva talked to Penetrator Chris,
and he said William has gone to London.
His father lives there.
I'm sure it's just for the weekend.
They have exams next week.
He has to take the exam.
I will talk to Mari tomorrow.
You will?
I sent her a message asking if we could talk.
We'll just cross our fingers hoping she's a little cool.
Just not so cool that
I would've slept with her as well.
What do you want to find out?
Are you hungry?
Eh, no.
I've made something nice for you.
Vilde, I've already eaten.
Do you like tortilla?
What's so good about tortilla,
is that it's made from potatoes.
And your body needs potatoes.
Because potatoes have
lots of starch, which give you energy.
And vitamin C,
which is a antioxidant.
Antioxidants help you
so you don't get old skin.
You don't want to have old skin
when you get together with William again.
Then we need to eat tortilla!
[He didn't show up to his exam today. Chris says he
can't reach him either.]
What's up?
Hi.
Thank you for wanting to meet me.
-Of course.
You're paranoid about
Nico's party?
Yes.
Don't be. You were just sweet.
Do you know if I slept with William?
No.
You don't know.
No, you didn't.
Are you sure?
Yes.
But... oh my god. Okay.
But did I sleep with someone else?
-No.
You were really stressed out, weren't you?
Yeah, I woke up naked!
-You undressed yourself!
I got undressed?!
You seriously don't remember anything?
No! Can you just explain everything now?
Okay. Do you remember
throwing up on the sofa upstairs?
No..
You threw up on the sofa upstairs.
I took you to the toilet.
You threw up again,
so we drank some water.
Then you said you wanted
to lie in William's bed. Remember that?
No..
You were really obsessing over William.
How so?
You said you loved him..
.. and that he wasn't good because he was an asshole. You didn't
want to be that girl who falls for such a guy.
You smelled his pillow and said it
smelled like him. You wanted to sleep in his bed..
.. and you began to undress yourself completely.
You said last time you were in his bed,
he said that all your clothes would be off within two weeks.
You said it wasn't going to happen,
but that he had meant it.
But that really deep inside
you hoped he was right.
Now he had been right in a way.
Then you passed out.
But I woke up in bed next to Nico.
Yeah, but he came in much later.
But how do you
know he didn't do anything?
Because when Nico came, I was awake. I asked him to go
lie somewhere else. But then he passed out and fell asleep.
But maybe he did
something while you were sleeping.
Noora..
Nico was really fucked up. He wouldn't have even
managed to get a boner.
Just forget it, really.
I would have noticed if
someone had sex next to me.
You didn't sleep with Nico.
I'm totally sure.
But he took pictures of me.
What kind of pictures?
Naked pictures. While I was asleep.
Are you kidding?
I reported him.
Nico, poor guy.
Poor guy? Seriously?
I remember when I was little,
I used to be scared of him.
I'm not scared of him any longer.
I think I just pity him.
But not like that. It was right
of you to report him.
Did you know him when you were little?
I went to kindergarten with Amalie,
his little sister. She was my best friend.
Oh yeah?
I know Nico hasn't had an easy life.
He has a different father than William and Amalie.
His real father never wanted anything
to do with him. Neither did William and Amalie's father.
And their mother is
just really cowardly and weak.
When Nico was little he got
these really sick tantrums. He snapped completely.
Instead of trying to calm him down and
understand him, his mom would lock him in his room.
Music at full blast, so no one would hear him. She went
around smiling nervously and pretending nothing had happened.
It was really intereseting to
have dinner there, so to speak.
After the accident she just
really abandoned both her sons.
Just left them to the au pairs.
I know Nico doesn't have any contact with her.
I don't think William has, either.
If he does, it's not much.
Accident?
When Nico was eleven..
.. he stole his stepdad's
car and crashed it into a cliff.
With William and Amalie in it.
It wasn't his intention.
He was just a kid.
But Amalie broke
her back and died.
Fucking hell..
Yeah, it's quite dark.
They were eight years old.
After that pretty much
the whole family was fucked up.
But William is a good guy.
I understand you think he's an asshole,
but he's actually really sensitive.
He just keeps everything inside.
Does it sting?
-It itches.
It stings when I touch it.
You can't touch it.
That's why you got it.
-Huh?
If you touch there, you get it there.
What are you talking about?
-You can't touch it on your fiffi.
Fiffi?
It Swedish for vagina.
[Hello. I was down in our basement and it looks like someone is living and sleeping
there. There's a mattress, a duvet, pillows and stuff on the floor. Do you know anything about it?]
On (pocketdoctor.com) it says you can get chlamydia in your eye.
[Hello. I was down in our basement and it looks like someone is living and sleeping
there. There's a mattress, a duvet, pillows and stuff on the floor. Do you know anything about it?]
How did I get chlamydia in my eye?
[Hello. I was down in our basement and it looks like someone is living and sleeping
there. There's a mattress, a duvet, pillows and stuff on the floor. Do you know anything about it?]
[No.]
Don't touch me!
I promise it's not chlamydia.
(These texts won't fit on the screen, try to put it through Google Translate lol.)
But who did you have sex with?
Had sex with?
-Yeah, you said you had sex with him.
(These texts won't fit on the screen, try to put it through Google Translate lol.)
After the party.
Vilde, I didn't say we had sex.
I just said..
.. that he fingered me a little
on the taxi. We didn't have sex.
William's at school! He went into
the headmaster's office.
Excuse me, I was just wondering..
Is William..
You haven't replied to my messages.
My phone was dead.
I didn't sleep with your brother.
Can we talk?
I'm moving..
.. to London.
Listen up.
William Magnusson.
You're a smart guy.
So you ought to understand..
.. that I would never just
let you move to London.
Not before we've talked.
So if you really want to get rid of me..
You should meet me for a talk.
Stop feeling so
damn sorry for yourself.
Okay.
I'll text you.
[I'm outside of your apartment now. You
wanted to talk? I don't have much time.]
You weren't kidding when
you said you don't have much time.
Plane leaves at six.
You want to talk?
Why do you have to go to London?
Because I want to.
How long will you be there?
I think the rest of my life.
What about us?
Is it just over?
Yes.
Just like that?
I'm not in love with you.
You are..
You are in love with me..
That's why you're being so cold.
No, Noora.
I'm cold because that's how I am.
I always wondered why you're so smart.
Just to defend your asshole
behavior to yourself?
You just tell yourself that's how you are?
Is it because your mom is a cunt?
Because you had a tragic childhood?
Is that what you say to yourself? That you're so sorry
for yourself that you just can't fault your own behavior?
Anyway, it's not true.
People experience horrible things every day,
and they still manage to be nice to others.
Being an asshole is not something
you're born with, or something you become.
It's a choice.
It's also a choice to let
Nico destroy what there is between us.
What's the plan?
Were you just gonna go around London being
an asshole, because your brother is mean?
Because your girl lied to you?
Are you never letting anyone in
again because you might get hurt?
Believe me..
You don't want that.
It's really lonely.
Because people..
.. need people.
I love you.
And you love me.
We have to be together.
Tell me we should be together.
I have to go.
Eva?
William has left.
William broke up with me.
William has left to London.
Fuck, he left to..
He came here. We were going to meet.
He came here..
.. in Chris' car. He said he wasn't in love with
me anymore, and his flight would leave at six.
No, he said he
wasn't in love with me anymore.
Because he wanted to..
Can I come to you?