He's the most unsympathetic, selfish
person I've ever met.
I would never touch him.
I told you I won't
have sex before I get married, right?
Jesus!
My brother is a complete psychopath.
Psychopath?
Tell me you didn't sleep with my brother.
I don't know.
You didn't sleep with Nico.
-But he took pictures of me. Naked pictures.
I reported him.
What's the plan?
Are you gonna go around London
being an asshole because your brother is mean?
Because your girl lied to you?
We should just lie here today.
Okay.
What's wrong?
Don't stop.
I need some space, okay?
You don't need space.
Dead serious.
I respect you.
Now you have to respect me.
I had.. sex when I was thirteen.
And the guy I had sex with
behaved really shitty afterwards.
So in the spring..
It was not just because of that.
Lots of stuff.
But then I got kind of..
.. sick.
So I'm probably just..
.. scared that something
like that will happen again.
Hey you..
I'm really damn sorry..
.. for what Nico has done.
But it wasn't your fault.
Nothing serious happened,
and he'll be convicted.
Isn't that good?
We have a legal system in Norway.
We just have to trust
that the legal system is fair.
So you don't have to kill him.
You didn't kill him, did you?
I haven't seen him.
I went to London.
Is he in Oslo?
Don't know.
I haven't been to the apartment.
Is it you who has
been living in our basement?
There really is someone
who's living in our basement.
So damn creepy.
I know!
I stayed with Chris.
I'll continue to stay wiht Chris.
You can live here, too.
But you have to..
.. go back to the apartment sometime.
I can't meet Nico.
I can come with you.
I'm not scared of him.
Hello?
He's not here.
What do you wanna do now?
Leave again.
Don't you want to be here for awhile?
-Why should I?
You have to take back your apartment.
I can't live here.
You..
You need to give in now. You can't
run from your brother for the rest of your life.
You just have to face him.
You have to look him in the eye
and tell him he's a fucking loser.
Be done with it.
That's not how it works.
I don't know what I
would have done if I had met him now.
Where will you move to?
I'll buy a new apartment.
You have money for that?
It'll work itself out.
So your solution
is to buy a new apartment?
Yes.
Do you want to move in with me?
Say yes.
William..
Can you not for once stop giving a damn about
what's wright and wrong, and just do what you want?
Okay.
We'll move in together!
We'll move in together.
Don't stop.
You don't need to.
What's that?
William!
Summon for interrogation.
Friday, 3rd of June. At 3 o' clock.
Why?
Because I smashed a bottle on that
guy's head. There's a video of it.
Why did you guys stop
talking when I came?
Have you received a letter from the police?
No.
Have you?
We've been summoned for questioning about the
fight on the night of the bus party. They called our parents.
Mom snapped completely.
-Mine too.
Why was I not summoned?
Probably because you left
before the police arrived. They took our names.
They came across the video on the internet.
The police has reported the case themselves.
But it's good that you weren't summoned.
It prevents you from having to testify against William.
Will you guys testify against William?
What should we do?
We can't lie to the police.
We can refuse to say anything.
Yeah, we have the right to remain silent.
They can't convict him based
on just that video anyway.
The quality is bad and it's unfocused.
We really have to think this through carefully.
He could go to prison for six months. I googled it.
This all started when William did something good.
-How so?
In the winter William beat up a Yakuza guy
for calling Iben, Chris' ex-girlfiriend, a cheap whore.
To avenge himself he beat up three
Penetrator guys. And William did nothing.
They beat up Jonas. Then Chris and Isak
planned to beat up Yakuza on the night of the bus party.
William didn't know anything about it.
But he ended up having to take it.
Can't we tell them this story?
I don't think that's how it works. They're only interested
in who threw the bottle at someone's head.
Why did William
smash that bottle, Noora?
Why?
-Yes.
He smashed it because
he felt it was his fault.
That Yakuza beat
up his best friend.
He's extremely loyal
to the ones he loves.
So he did it because..
He doesn't entrust this responsibility
with adult people, because..
There has never been an
adult who has taken responsibility of him.
He also has a little trouble controlling his mind.
It'd be great if you said that, too.
I say we shut our
mouths at the questioning.
I agree.
Okay, let's do it.
Do you think Isak
and Jonas will say anything?
No, it was William who helped them.
Jonas doesn't even like the police.
The only thing that could fuck
up everything, is if Yakuza testifies against him.
Eskild?
Eskild!
What?
I don't know who you've got
living down in our basement..
But it has to stop. We've gotten
complaints from our downstairs neighbors.
I don't know anything about it.
It's not me.
Is it Tito?
Or Nito?
I don't know anything about it.
It could be Linn.
It's your bedding.
No, it's not.
You know what bedding is mine? Stalker.
Eskild, I'm the only
one who washes bedding in this house.
Had it not been for me,
your bedding would be full of stiff, old cum.
What's this?
Did you just say
stiff, old cum?
Wow!
Way to go, girl!
Dirty.
Eskild, don't change the subject now!
It's because of William.
No, it's not because of William!
Yes, it is. I can see it in you.
You think in a more sexual way.
Good job, William. Applause!
From one guy to another.
He got them juices flowin', Willy!
Fuck, Eskild. Shut up!
Did you guys have sex?
No!
You're gonna have it now!
You're so horny now, help!
Didn't you see the video?
Are you kidding me now?
"Skogtur". On Google. Search for "Skogtur".
You can watch it with William. Foreplay.
-Bye, Eskild.
Stop having people live in the basement.
Eskild!
Yes? "Skogtur"
Say hi to Tito and tell
him to find himself a new place to live.
Yeah.
But let me know if you're going to watch
that video. It's been a long time since I've seen it.
It's quite cool to watch it together.
-Bye!
[Who did you get the number from?]
[Eva got it from Iben who got it from the guy's ex.]
[Okay. Wish me luck.]
Hey you..
-Hm?
Why do you actually
write Noora with two O's?
No one else does it.
Eh, you know Vilde..
Yes. I know Vilde..
Yeah..
She just sent me the
number of the Yakuza guy.
Okay, what are going to do with it?
No, I just thought that..
.. maybe you could call him.
Why should I?
So that you could've asked him if
he couldn't say anything in the interrogation.
No.
William!
Seriously!
Please.
Forget it.
Yeah but listen!
Everyone is keeping their mouth shut.
Your guys, Isak and Jonas, and my friends. Everyone!
If you don't say anything about all that they did,
they won't say anything about what you did either.
Noora..
No.
Forget it.
Done.
He refuses to call, so that's fucked.
[Seriously? Guys are such idiots. Why doe he have to be so proud?
We're talking about six months in prison.]
[Ik] I know?
[But you can call him..]
Do you want to read to me?
Ibsen?
Please?
Why?
Because I'm excited
to hear Ibsen's story.
Story? The story of Ibsen?
Yes.
-The Ibsen of the story?
There's nothing here.
-There's lots of pages here.
Just read 'em.
Read 'em words?
A Doll's House.
A Doll's House?
[Insert Norwegian puns that I don't understand.]
Who cares?
Three-act play.
-1879.
No..
You're cute.
Yeah, that's true.
[Hi. You don't know me, but I was there during the fight on the 29th of April.
I just wanted to say that none of the Riot guys or anyone else who was there
will say anything about what happened. As long as you don't say anything.]
[Hi. You don't know me, but I was there during the fight on the 29th of April.
I just wanted to say that none of the Riot guys or anyone else who was there
will say anything about what happened. As long as you don't say anything.]
[We won't say anything.]
Hello.
How did it go?
It went fine.
Yeah, but you were there for four hours.
What did they say?
Did you get the impression
they have a lot of evidence against you?
I confessed.
Why did you.. You can't..
Why did you do that?
Hell, do I know?
Maybe it's because of what you said.
What I said?! I said you shouldn't say shit.
That's what I said.
The stuff about Nico. That we should
believe in and trust that we have a fair legal system.
I chose to trust it.
Alternatively..
I could have chosen to not trust it..
.. and just kept my mouth shut about it.
But then I'd nearly killed Nico.
If you get what I mean.
But what will happen now?
I have to go to court in a few weeks.
I might have to go to prison.
What do you want to do now?
While you're still free?
What do I want to do now?
I know what I want to do.
-What?
What I want to do now,
is to have a really big party..
.. where we get completely wasted.
We'll just crawl around.
Okay.
Yeah.
-Yeah.
Where do you think that's gonna happen?
At my place?
We may as well go
back to that damn apartment.
I'm ready to order. If there's someone else
who wants to..
Eva!
You have to meet Isak!
-Hi! Eskild. -Isak.
And Jonas.
-Hi! Eskild.
I live with him.
We live together.
-No we live in a house with roommates.
[Jonas talking about Noora's story of the BJ action.]
Huh?
-Yes!
What BJ action?
What day? On Saturday?
No! It was a really long time ago.
I can't remember
everytime I get sucked off.
It's true. If we have fun,
I won't think about it anymore the day after.
Isn't that a good philosophy?
Do your thing!
-Yeah!
Speaking of that jacket..
I know she..
I know she's not the one
who created it, but she sews at the factory.
I met her when I was in Asia.
You look so cool!
-Thank you.
[I like that you're standing there looking at me.]
[You actually hate parties, don't you?]
[I don't HATE it.]
[We don't have to be here.]
[Go to your house and chill?]
[No. That's not what I want.]
[What do you want?]
Chris. Out.
Are you serious now?
Out. Now.
Bro!
I know I should ask you
if you're ready, but I don't care now.
So shut up.
Oh my god!
Kasper!
Is there no life here?!
I think I did something stupid.
What do you mean?
I sent a message to the Yakuza guy.
I knew you were going to do it.
You're not mad?
I would have done the same.
What will Eskild and Linn
say when you tell them you're moving out?
I'm scared to say it.
You have to say it.
Okay.
My god, it'll go well for sure.
They just have to find
someone else who can live in the room.
Oh, cool belt!
Is it?
Are you taking the credit for that belt?
Is it yours?
-Yes, it's Isak's.
Ah, I see.
All his coolest clothes are actually mine.
SKAM LOVES YOU