Four years from now,
&nbsp
Dr. Brand invents the technology
that traps Savitar in the Speed Force.
&nbsp
This is the Speed Force bazooka.
And that's gonna trap Savitar?
&nbsp
I know what you are.
You're a time remnant.
&nbsp
You all shunned me...
because I wasn't the true Barry Allen.
&nbsp
I was an aberration.
How did you become Savitar?
&nbsp
I was broken and alone.
God feels no pain.
&nbsp
All I had to do was become one.
_
&nbsp
Iris.
You know what I'd love right now?
&nbsp
Anything you want.
Caviar.
&nbsp
- Caviar?
- Mm-hmm.
&nbsp
Okay. Well, it's just a little late,
so it might be hard
for me to find a place
&nbsp
that's open that has it.
But I'll find an assortment.
&nbsp
Thank you.
Just stay with me, okay?
&nbsp
The whole team's working on this.
And we can accomplish a lot in 24 hours.
&nbsp
I know we can.
I'm fine, Barry. Really.
&nbsp
Get some caviar...
Hi, Barry.
&nbsp
Um...
there's something that
I need to say to you.
&nbsp
Synced and corrected by Aaronnmb
www.addic7ed.com
&nbsp
Hey, Cisco.
What?
&nbsp
Where?
All right, I'll come pick you up.
&nbsp
- What is it?
- Ah...
&nbsp
Really good news.
Lyla.
&nbsp
Hey.
Gentlemen.
&nbsp
- Ah...
- It's a wee bit chilly.
&nbsp
Wanna take this inside?
Every square inch of
that building is bugged.
&nbsp
Figured it was better to talk out here.
Okay. Yeah, I love the breeze...
&nbsp
- Yeah. Yeah.
- ... on days like this.
&nbsp
So, I got your message.
But, you're gonna have to run me through
&nbsp
- exactly what you need again.
- Yeah...
&nbsp
- So, we're building a cannon...
- Right.
&nbsp
... bazooka... thing.
It's a sort of trap.
&nbsp
In order to turn it on, we
need something to power it.
&nbsp
Something extremely
powerful and regenerative.
&nbsp
- Okay.
- Yeah, so,
&nbsp
I tasked our satellite to look for
anything that might have our
specific power requirements,
&nbsp
and... wouldn't you know it...
we found something that
has exactly what we need.
&nbsp
And it's right there in that building.
Crazy, huh?
&nbsp
I really don't think you
should be spying on me, Cisco.
&nbsp
Is it spying if we're friends?
But he's right, isn't he?
You have something, don't you?
&nbsp
It's a piece of the
Dominators' technology.
&nbsp
We got it from the ship
that crashed in Central City.
&nbsp
- That's great.
- You can't have it, Barry.
&nbsp
- What?
- Lyla...
&nbsp
we've searched everywhere.
This tech is the only
thing that we can use.
&nbsp
I can't do it.
Is this because of baby Sara?
&nbsp
Look... I'll admit, it's
been hard not to wonder
&nbsp
what it would have been like to
have a daughter instead of a son,
&nbsp
but this is less about what happened
than why it happened.
&nbsp
I made a big mistake.
Exactly my concern.
&nbsp
Barry, this is the kind of
tech that wars are fought over.
&nbsp
If something happens and it
gets into the wrong hands,
&nbsp
people could die. Millions.
And frankly, I don't know if
I can trust you to have it.
&nbsp
Director Michaels.
I gotta go.
&nbsp
Lyla, if we don't use this,
Iris is going to die.
&nbsp
Tonight.
I'm sorry, Barry.
&nbsp
I can't help you this time.
You'll have to find another way.
&nbsp
- Are you serious?
- Yeah.
&nbsp
Yeah, if Lyla won't let us
have the Dominators' tech,
&nbsp
then we are gonna break into
ARGUS, and we're gonna steal it.
&nbsp
Wally and I will phase
through the walls.
&nbsp
We'll be in and out of there
before anyone even gets off a shot.
&nbsp
Uh, hello? No, you won't.
- Yeah, we...
- What is that?
&nbsp
That is a meta-human power dampener.
And it's all over the building, so
you can't use your powers inside.
&nbsp
Can we use anything else
to power this Speed Force gun?
&nbsp
- Speed Force bazooka.
- Bazooka.
&nbsp
Nothing else.
Manipulating extra-dimensional
energy requires,
&nbsp
well, a ridiculous amount
of energy,
&nbsp
and the Dominator tech's the
only thing that can do that.
&nbsp
Hey, I have... I have an idea, gang.
What if we just put you...
&nbsp
- put Iris on a plane to Paris...
- No.
&nbsp
... or somewhere far away?
There's nowhere on Earth that
Savitar wouldn't find her.
&nbsp
Guys. Stealing this Dominators'
tech is our only option, all right?
&nbsp
Barry. ARGUS is more
secure than the pentagon.
&nbsp
If your powers don't work in there,
how are you gonna get past security?
&nbsp
Okay.
This is what we're dealing with:
&nbsp
- surveillance cameras.
- I'm out.
&nbsp
- Eye scans.
- Nope!
&nbsp
- Palm prints. Heat sensors.
- Whoa!
&nbsp
- What?
- Laser sensors.
&nbsp
They really thought of
everything, didn't they?
&nbsp
That's just the first floor.
So, you're saying this is
the most fortified structure
&nbsp
in the history of fortified structures,
they can't use their superpowers,
&nbsp
and we have less than 14
hours to steal the thing.
&nbsp
And none of us are master thieves.
No.
&nbsp
No, we're not.
_
&nbsp
Hello, Flash.
I need your help.
&nbsp
Barry Allen. The hero of Central City.
This is Siberia in the year 1892.
&nbsp
We're a little out of your jurisdiction.
Yeah, hear me out.
&nbsp
I wanna recruit you... for a mission.
I'm already helping a
bunch of idiot do-gooders.
&nbsp
Sorry. I'm up to my
fuzzy hood in teamwork.
&nbsp
Would it help if I said please?
No. And you already have a bunch
&nbsp
of superhero types in your life.
Why ask me?
&nbsp
Well, you have a...
particular set of skills.
&nbsp
Great movie. Last time we
tried to be buddy-buddy,
&nbsp
it didn't work out so well...
for you.
&nbsp
Why trust me now?
Spit it out, or I'm
gonna step onto that ship
&nbsp
and pretend like this
conversation never happened.
&nbsp
Iris.
- Oy. The girlfriend.
- Fiancée.
&nbsp
Mazel tov.
What about her?
&nbsp
If you don't help me, she's gonna die.
True love.
&nbsp
That's your pitch.
It's all I've got.
&nbsp
And I assume saving your girlfriend
requires us doing something...
&nbsp
less than lawful?
We need to break into ARGUS
and steal an alien power source.
&nbsp
The Flash, a thief?
That's my kind of
mission. One condition:
&nbsp
my rules.
Your rules.
&nbsp
I know we don't have a plane.
We steal a plane, okay?
We'll put it back. All right?
&nbsp
And we parachute out of the
plane, and land on the roof...
&nbsp
gotta land on the right roof, all right?
And then... right down the air ducts.
&nbsp
Mission: Improbable style.
- Easy.
- Easy?
&nbsp
- Yes.
- What about...
&nbsp
the counter-terrorism missiles?
- What?
- Yeah.
&nbsp
Hello, Joe! Cisco.
Iris!
&nbsp
Love the ice. Sparkly.
Captain Cold.
&nbsp
Snart, what the hell are you doing here?
Snart's gonna help
me break into ARGUS...
&nbsp
get the power source.
- Huh?
- Awkward.
&nbsp
I can see you all have
a lot to talk about.
&nbsp
I'll be down in your lab,
getting everything ready.
&nbsp
Barry, are you out of your mind?
I thought he was with the Legends.
&nbsp
- He is.
- No, he dead.
&nbsp
- Well... Yeah.
- You time-traveled again?
&nbsp
That's what got us in this
mess in the first place.
&nbsp
I thought you said you
would never do that again.
&nbsp
I also said I would do
whatever it takes to save you.
&nbsp
That hasn't changed.
And I'm pretty sure you all
feel the same way, too. Right?
&nbsp
Look, I'm not changing time.
I will put him back,
&nbsp
right where I found him.
After we get what we need.
&nbsp
Fine. You say we need Snart's
help, we need his help.
&nbsp
So what's the plan?
What are you doing?
&nbsp
Flash...
damaged my suit in our fight.
&nbsp
Pretty badass.
Very godlike.
&nbsp
Well, dress for the job you want.
We're a team, right?
&nbsp
Barry and Caitlin, at it again.
You're not Caitlin.
&nbsp
And I'm not Barry.
You sure you're gonna
go through with this?
&nbsp
- What?
- Killing Iris.
&nbsp
You're gonna take her
to Infantino Street,
&nbsp
and ram a metal spear through her back?
Well, it's either her or me.
&nbsp
If she doesn't die,
I'm never born.
&nbsp
Right, but...
behind that pretty little face of yours,
&nbsp
you still remember
everything that Barry does.
&nbsp
So you remember growing up with Iris,
falling in love with her, kissing her.
&nbsp
You sure you're ready to end her life?
What I remember...
&nbsp
is being created as a disposable life.
Something to be... thrown away
&nbsp
when Barry Allen was done with me.
He didn't care about me.
&nbsp
Why should I care about his love?
You're not having
second thoughts, are you?
&nbsp
Good.
Because you know what you need to do,
&nbsp
and when the time comes,
I expect you to be ready.
&nbsp
What is it?
Barry went back in
time to get Snart's help
&nbsp
with stealing the
power source from ARGUS.
&nbsp
Power source? For what?
Oh...
&nbsp
it doesn't matter.
- Well, should I stop them?
- No.
&nbsp
Let them take it.
No speed gun can stop a god.
&nbsp
My guess is the power
source is most likely here.
&nbsp
Why there?
Because it's the deepest
part of the facility,
&nbsp
and if it's as valuable
as you say it is,
&nbsp
then the deepest
recesses of any facility
&nbsp
are usually the most secure.
Hm. Smart, Snart.
&nbsp
- "Smart, Snart."
- Mm-hmm.
&nbsp
I'm gonna keep hackin'
away and find out for sure.
&nbsp
Do you have any idea what
else might be down there?
&nbsp
Don't matter. There are only
four rules you need to remember.
&nbsp
Make the plan, execute the plan,
expect the plan to go off the rails...
&nbsp
throw away the plan.
Follow my lead and you'll be fine.
&nbsp
I'm trusting you.
We all are.
&nbsp
Just don't sit me at the single's table
at the wedding reception.
&nbsp
Just out of curiosity,
you have a plan for getting in there?
&nbsp
I've got that covered.
Oh, ah... here, hold that
for a second. Yeah, okay,
&nbsp
- and... kay... and don't look.
- What?
&nbsp
Hey, Flash.
Superhero.
&nbsp
Cowl on, please? We got
civilians in the house.
&nbsp
It's okay. H.R., we're
trusting Tracy with our lives.
&nbsp
We can trust her with this.
- Good point.
- Yeah.
&nbsp
- Okay, I'll put my hands down now.
- Okay.
&nbsp
- Oh!
- Yeah.
&nbsp
- Totally should've figured that out.
- Yeah.
&nbsp
- I...
- What...
&nbsp
- Well, carry on.
- All right.
&nbsp
Okay...
All right, Joe. I need you to take Iris
&nbsp
some place far away from here.
Far away from me.
&nbsp
- Barry.
- I can't know where.
&nbsp
If I know, then Savitar knows.
I'll get Wally.
&nbsp
We'll keep her safe, don't worry.
So here we are.
&nbsp
This is not good-bye.
Yeah.
&nbsp
Look...
I know you're gonna do
whatever it takes to save me,
&nbsp
but don't lose yourself
in the process, okay?
&nbsp
_
Hello.
&nbsp
Harry.
Kid, Joe.
&nbsp
Iris.
What brings you folk to this
section of the multiverse?
&nbsp
What's that?
It's how much time we have left.
&nbsp
Before what?
Before we lose.
&nbsp
We're prepping the chopper
for San Francisco now.
&nbsp
Copy that, sir...
Director Michaels. I thought you
were en route to San Francisco.
&nbsp
Plans changed.
I received an unexpected
gift from the Flash.
&nbsp
Captain Cold?
Always nice to meet a fan.
&nbsp
I'm taking the prisoner to lock-up.
Of course. We'll just need your ID.
&nbsp
_
Spent so much time
on that ARGUS fake ID.
&nbsp
That thing's a masterpiece.
Your eye scan?
&nbsp
_
You boys really dot the
"I"s and cross the "T"s.
&nbsp
And finally, Director Michaels:
Elvis, banana.
&nbsp
- What the hell?
- Search me.
&nbsp
Elvis, banana...
it's word association.
&nbsp
Barry must have to come up with the
next correct words in the sequence.
&nbsp
Like "peanut butter, bacon."
- Yeah, Kevin Bacon.
- Mellow, yellow.
&nbsp
- James Brown, split.
- Okay.
&nbsp
Barry, you're gonna have to stall.
I repeat, ma'am. Elvis, banana.
&nbsp
My, my, my.
Getting rather violent
in your young age.
&nbsp
Yeah, what were you doing?
Magic.
&nbsp
Neat trick.
Was a neat trick, yourself.
&nbsp
Transmogrifier from H.R.'s Earth.
Here you go.
&nbsp
Cisco, where to next?
Okay, you will take the...
&nbsp
East elevator?
They should do the west elevator.
&nbsp
- I agree with Tracy.
- Barry, take the west elevator.
&nbsp
I used to watch you do that as a kid.
I thought you were so cool.
&nbsp
What'd I tell you?
Guns aren't cool,
&nbsp
- they're just for protection.
- Right.
&nbsp
Dad, look, I know this
is hard for everyone,
&nbsp
but I feel like it's hardest for you.
Dad, can I tell you something?
&nbsp
Yep.
When I was 16,
&nbsp
um...
Barry and I switched rooms,
&nbsp
so that I could sneak out
of the window past curfew.
&nbsp
- It's true.
- Wait a minute.
&nbsp
You...
you told me that it was because
&nbsp
Barry didn't like the
noise from the street.
&nbsp
Yeah, no.
But in my defense, my
curfew was 8:00 p.m.
&nbsp
- Yeah, I was a little strict.
- A little?
&nbsp
Okay, since...
since we're confessing, remember...
&nbsp
when I told you guys
that we couldn't eat out for a month,
&nbsp
because I was saving money
for yours and Barry's college tuition?
&nbsp
Yeah.
I took some of that money,
&nbsp
and I went on a blues cruise.
Junior Walker was playing.
It was just for three days.
&nbsp
- Dad.
- Hm.
&nbsp
- Oh, that reminds me.
- What, um...
&nbsp
what was that song you
used to sing all the time?
&nbsp
You don't remember?
I don't remember.
&nbsp
- "What Does It Take."
- "What Does It Take"!
&nbsp
♪ I tried, I tried ♪
♪ In every way I could ♪
&nbsp
♪ To make you see how much I love you ♪
♪ I hope you understood ♪
&nbsp
- I love you.
- I love you too, Dad.
&nbsp
Take this for me, please.
Just in case.
&nbsp
Make sure you give it back to Barry.
Okay.
&nbsp
Who's Grodd?
Telepathic gorilla.
&nbsp
Spared his life on another Earth,
so he could invade Central City.
&nbsp
That's what mercy gets you.
_
&nbsp
This must be where Waller
kept her suicide squad.
&nbsp
I think this is it.
Come on.
&nbsp
Cisco, we found it.
Cisco?
&nbsp
Barry!
- Hey, Cisco, can you read me?
- Loud and clear.
&nbsp
Hey. Uh, so, we found it.
Jackpot!
&nbsp
But there seems to be
some kind of signal interference
at the end of the hall,
&nbsp
and the lock is the Montgomery 3000.
- The Montgomery 3000.
- Wait, is that bad?
&nbsp
Well, we're looking at a 25-ton door
that can withstand a
30-megaton nuclear blast.
&nbsp
And aside from being
completely bombproof,
&nbsp
the Montgomery 3000 can only be unlocked
by a voice-recognition
system necessitating
&nbsp
three different pass-codes
from three different people,
&nbsp
and as if that weren't already enough,
the thing costs $10 million to build.
&nbsp
37 seconds.
I must be out of practice.
&nbsp
Well, ARGUS should ask
for their money back.
&nbsp
Wait!
Make the plan, execute the plan.
&nbsp
Expect the plan to go off the rails.
I've seen a lot of things,
&nbsp
but a half-man, half-shark
takes the cake.
&nbsp
I can't believe ARGUS turned
King Shark into a guard dog.
&nbsp
King Shark. That's adorable.
Give me your cold gun.
&nbsp
So you can do what, exactly?
Snart, there's only one way
that tech's getting out of here.
&nbsp
Oh, I see.
You didn't just recruit me
&nbsp
for my skills as a thief, did you?
You wanted a partner who wouldn't mind
&nbsp
if you got all murder-y.
I told you what I'm up against.
&nbsp
All right?
Give me the gun.
&nbsp
Open the door.
Open the door!
&nbsp
Have you seen "Shark Week," Barry?
Me, I can't get enough of it.
&nbsp
Good thing the Waverider has cable.
What's your point?
&nbsp
Most sharks are cold-blooded,
but the great white shark,
like our friend in there,
&nbsp
is partially warm-blooded.
- He's susceptible to cold.
- Never strays into water
&nbsp
colder than 53.6 degrees Fahrenheit.
If we lower the temperature
in that room to 53.5 degrees,
&nbsp
King Shark should fall asleep
like a little baby.
&nbsp
Or, you can go ahead and kill him,
and prove what a badass you are.
&nbsp
Your choice.
Throw away the plan.
&nbsp
Ho-ho-ho.
Tracy Brand, you know,
&nbsp
it's moments like this I'm
reminded that S.T.A.R. Labs
&nbsp
is so much more than a haven
for beautiful minds, it's...
&nbsp
- It's a miniature Jitters.
- It's a... oh, yeah. Uh!
&nbsp
Raspberry and coriander.
Mmm!
&nbsp
Yes, it is... it's a home...
- Yeah.
- ... is what it is. You know what?
&nbsp
It's my home. It's my...
It's my family. Although, I...
&nbsp
you know what, I will say...
I have to tell you,
I haven't always felt
&nbsp
- I belong completely.
- What?
&nbsp
Yeah, lacking a clear
sense of purpose sometimes.
&nbsp
- But then you arrived.
- I did?
&nbsp
- Oh, yeah, I did.
- Oh, yeah, you did.
&nbsp
Here you are. Yeah. And with you here,
I understand... my purpose.
&nbsp
It's us. You and me.
That meeting of the mind that
we have, it's just so powerful...
&nbsp
But H.R., you're from another Earth...
- Yeah, I... yeah...
- I'm... I'm a unemployed,
&nbsp
former grad student, who...
Come work at S.T.A.R. Labs with me.
&nbsp
Okay? I mean, it doesn't pay much.
- How much?
- Ah, it pays next to nothing.
&nbsp
But you know what? It wouldn't matter.
We'd be together.
Imagine: me inspiring you,
&nbsp
and you applying that inspiration,
and us changing the world together.
&nbsp
And drinking so much coffee!
Tracy Brand.
&nbsp
Will you do me the honor...
of joining Team Flash?
&nbsp
With you? I'd love to.
By all means, you first.
&nbsp
Thanks.
Reminds me of "Jaws."
&nbsp
They didn't show the shark
because they couldn't afford
&nbsp
to make it look good.
How long do you think he'll stay asleep?
&nbsp
I like "Shark Week." I'm
not a marine biologist.
&nbsp
Snart!
Barry!
&nbsp
This place is gonna be
crawling with ARGUS agents
&nbsp
in the next two minutes.
Look on the bright side, Barry.
&nbsp
This is your chance to show
how ruthless you really are.
&nbsp
Sometimes you gotta
make a tough call, Barry.
&nbsp
Cisco?
We need your help.
&nbsp
I have the energy source, but...
Snart's trapped inside
the cell with King Shark.
&nbsp
You gotta open the door.
I can't hack into the mainframe.
&nbsp
Hurry, all right?
Cisco's working on it.
&nbsp
Whatever you do, don't look behind you.
If Cisco saves my life, tell him I'll...
&nbsp
put in a good word with my sister.
Come on...
&nbsp
Bam!
Come on, come on!
&nbsp
Come on, come on! Come on, come on!
- I got you!
- Barry!
&nbsp
I got you, I got you!
Hang on!
&nbsp
Now, Cisco, now! Close it!
Ouch.
&nbsp
Been there.
Okay...
&nbsp
Flash!
Let's get out of here.
&nbsp
Lyla.
Barry.
&nbsp
I told you I couldn't give this to you.
- Yeah.
- And you snuck in here anyway?
&nbsp
To save Iris' life, Lyla.
Yeah. I'll do anything.
&nbsp
Not anything.
I saw the whole thing
on the security monitors.
&nbsp
You could have left Snart to die.
But you risked your freedom
and Iris' life to save him.
&nbsp
You're just gonna let me have it?
I couldn't let Iris die knowing
that that could save her.
&nbsp
And I know you'd do
the same thing for me
&nbsp
if it were John's life on the line.
Thank you.
&nbsp
Now go. Do it.
And get this guy back
to wherever he belongs.
&nbsp
Took the words right out of my mouth.
Tell me, Snart, did you
think I had it in me?
&nbsp
To leave you behind?
I wasn't sure.
&nbsp
Always known you had the potential to be
as ruthless as they come.
&nbsp
Your history made sure
of that, same as mine.
&nbsp
Who knows, maybe
that's why we get along.
&nbsp
You see the good in me.
I see the bad in you.
&nbsp
- Maybe.
- Piece of advice:
&nbsp
stop trying to beat
Savitar at his own game.
&nbsp
Your goodness is your strength.
And call me sentimental...
&nbsp
I think the Flash should remain a hero.
Take care of yourself, Snart.
&nbsp
No strings on me.
No strings on me...
&nbsp
We did it!
We got the Dominator tech.
&nbsp
Yes, yes!
- Where's Iris?
- Ah, Iris...
&nbsp
safely stashed away on
Earth-2 with ole Harry Wells.
&nbsp
No.
Barry! Savitar knows where Iris is.
&nbsp
Savitar's coming.
- What?
- Now. Joe.
&nbsp
Iris, stay behind me.
He gets to you through my dead body.
&nbsp
- Harry, Wally.
- Yeah.
&nbsp
I got him.
Oh, God.
&nbsp
It's really true.
Yes, it is.
&nbsp
Aim that gun at me and I'll kill you.
Listen to me.
&nbsp
- You were my son once.
- Oh.
&nbsp
Whatever I did to make
you feel this way...
&nbsp
I'm sorry.
Please, Barry.
&nbsp
No.
That's not my name.
&nbsp
- Barry.
- That's not my name!
&nbsp
Please! Stop, okay?
I will go with you, just
please, do not kill them.
&nbsp
I'm not gonna kill them now.
They...
&nbsp
need to watch you die first.
- Baby, no.
- Dad, it's okay.
&nbsp
Oh, look, Joe.
She's accepted her fate.
&nbsp
You should too.
He took her.
&nbsp
He...
_
&nbsp
- I'm sorry, Barry. I'm so sorry.
- It's okay.
&nbsp
No, it's not. It's not okay, Barry.
I should have been there for her,
&nbsp
- I should have protected her...
- Look, you did everything you could,
&nbsp
All right?
You trusted me, and I let you down.
&nbsp
- Listen to me. Listen to me!
- I let you down.
&nbsp
There's no way you
could ever let me down.
&nbsp
You've become the hero I
always knew you could be.
&nbsp
I'm gonna go get our
girl back, all right?
&nbsp
- B.A., I'm so sorry.
- It's okay.
&nbsp
I screwed up. I'm so sorry.
So, what now?
&nbsp
Now we go to Infantino Street.
We know exactly where
Savitar's gonna be and when.
&nbsp
Is the bazooka ready?
I've loaded the power
source into the device,
&nbsp
which should deliver the
necessary amount of energy
&nbsp
to trap Savitar in the speed force.
We'll be on standby in case it fails.
&nbsp
It won't fail. It
won't fail. It's ready.
&nbsp
You didn't have that the last time,
- so we have the upper hand now.
- Mm-hmm.
&nbsp
All right.
You guys figure out what your plan is.
&nbsp
I can't be here to know any of it.
You know where I'll be.
&nbsp
Gauntlets, check.
Goggles, check.
&nbsp
Super powers?
Check.
&nbsp
Locked and loaded.
Don't stress.
&nbsp
- Tracy's bazooka...
- Yeah.
&nbsp
- ... it's gonna work.
- Tracy's bazooka?
&nbsp
- Yeah, you helped.
- I didn't... I didn't...
&nbsp
- I didn't help.
- Yes, you did.
&nbsp
- You inspired her.
- I didn't inspire her. I...
&nbsp
I didn't do anything inspiring.
You know what's inspiring? Barry.
&nbsp
A hero among heroes. You're all heroes.
And you've all given me so...
&nbsp
so much, you know?
You've given me a home,
you've given me a purpose.
&nbsp
Now you've led me to
the woman that I adore,
&nbsp
that I wanna spend my future with,
and through it all, what have I done?
&nbsp
What have I done? What
have I contributed except...
&nbsp
some fair-to-middling drumming,
and lead Savitar directly to Iris.
&nbsp
- That's not fair.
- It's not fair?
&nbsp
It's not fair for you to
say. Savitar tricked us.
&nbsp
Us? Me.
I'm the one who opened
his big, fat mouth,
&nbsp
and now we're all in
trouble, and especially Iris,
&nbsp
'cause I couldn't keep my mouth shut!
Hey! That coulda happened to me, okay?
&nbsp
Easy. I mean it. That
coulda happened to me,
&nbsp
that could happen to any of us.
H.R...
&nbsp
You gonna hold down the fort?
Yeah.
&nbsp
Of course you are.
'cause that's what you do.
&nbsp
You show up.
You're ready.
&nbsp
Dependable when we need you the most.
You hear me?
&nbsp
I hear you.
All right.
&nbsp
Till next time.
Oh, Cisco.
&nbsp
Time for a little chat.
Cisco?
&nbsp
I just had a vibe.
What? What'd you see?
&nbsp
Killer Frost.
I saw this coming.
&nbsp
What are you talking about?
Ever since Caitlin got powers,
&nbsp
I've had vibes of us
fighting in a forest.
&nbsp
This whole time I've been fighting it.
I didn't wanna face
the fact that one day,
&nbsp
she'd be this far gone.
Then go now.
&nbsp
Keep her from making the
biggest mistake of her life.
&nbsp
What about you? You're
gonna need my help.
&nbsp
Savitar won't be with her right now.
This is our best chance to help her.
&nbsp
Go save Caitlin.
I'll save Iris.
&nbsp
News announcer: In other legal news,
the highly publicized
trial of Jared Morillo,
&nbsp
AKA Plunder, comes to a close.
Morillo was found guilty of grand theft
&nbsp
and aggravated assault after
he was caught by Kid Flash
&nbsp
robbing the Central City
Museum earlier this year.
&nbsp
Please don't fail, please don't fail.
Everybody,
&nbsp
stay on alert.
Here we go.
&nbsp
I know you're here!
Come out and face me like a woman.
&nbsp
I didn't think you'd actually show.
That's 'cause you don't
know anything about me.
&nbsp
Or Caitlin, for that matter.
Savitar's right.
&nbsp
In order to join him as a god,
I have to cure myself of Caitlin.
&nbsp
This has to happen.
I don't wanna fight you.
&nbsp
I don't wanna fight you, either.
I wanna kill you.
&nbsp
Flash. This is it.
Now the moment is upon us.
&nbsp
My ascension to become a god.
- Not tonight.
- Show me you're the hero.
&nbsp
Let's see what happens.
I'm gonna stop you.
&nbsp
Ha!
It's working.
&nbsp
- What?
- It didn't work.
&nbsp
What... what?
Why didn't it work?
&nbsp
I spent an eternity in
a trap just like that.
&nbsp
You think I didn't
know how to prevent it
&nbsp
from happening again?
The philosopher's stone.
&nbsp
It's made of calcified
Speed Force energy,
&nbsp
and you gave it to me.
No... guys... guys!
&nbsp
I failed.
Joe!
&nbsp
You stuck me in the Speed
Force for an eternity of hell.
&nbsp
Now, welcome to yours.
No. Don't do this.
&nbsp
Don't do this!
Now, finally, I am free of you.
&nbsp
- Barry.
- I'm begging you, just...
&nbsp
Barry!
You lose, Barry.
&nbsp
No!
Hi, Barry. Um...
&nbsp
there's something that
I need to say to you.
&nbsp
I love you.
And if something happens,
&nbsp
I need you to hear this.
I, Iris Ann West,
&nbsp
take you, Bartholomew Henry Allen,
to be my lawfully wedded husband.
&nbsp
To have and to hold,
from this day forward.
&nbsp
In sickness and in health.
To love and to cherish.
&nbsp
Until death do us part.
Iris. Iris.
&nbsp
Iris!