This season on "The Flash"...
I went back in time and
created an alternate timeline,
a whole new existence.
I created Flashpoint
and changed everything.
- Who are you?
- Savitar. The god of speed.
You said that I trapped
you in the future. Where?
The only place that could hold me.
The Speed Force.
- Iris West, will you marry me?
- Yes!
Dr. Brand invents the technology
that traps Savitar in the Speed Force.
- Good luck with that.
- We don't wanna fight you.
We're your friends. Your family.
- Caitlin, I love you.
- I never loved any an you.
Caitlin is working with Savitar.
- Caitlin is dead.
- Not to me.
I know who you are.
I am the future Flash.
When I have control of all of time,
it will be you who is
abandoned and forgotten!
And I only need for Iris to die
so that you are driven
so far into the dark
that I can be born.
I'm gonna stop you.
It didn't work.
You lose, Barry!
No!
Iris!
Oh, no.
Iris?
B.A.?
What?
B.A.
H.R.?
Dad.
Baby?
Yeah.
I don't understand.
It was H.R.
Till the next one.
H.R.
Hi.
Let's get you out of here.
Where is everybody else?
I couldn't tell...
Barry, or Savitar,
would know I was coming.
- Let's get you out of here.
- Okay.
Get her.
- We can't outrun them.
- No, we can't.
What are you doing?
I'm the reason Savitar found you.
- I need to remedy that.
- Not like this.
Give me that. Oh!
Don't! I'm the one he wants.
Okay? Please, don't hurt him.
H.R.!
- Tracy.
- No.
- No. No.
- It's... it's okay.
Why are you doing this?
I couldn't be a coward.
I'm not a coward.
We just found each other.
I know.
Our story would be brilliant.
You will be brilliant.
You will be glorious, Tracy Brand.
You will be.
I've seen... seen it with my own eyes.
I love you.
Oh, B.A.?
- B.A.
- I'm right here.
Will you tell Cisco...
please tell him...
Will you tell him that?
For me?
- Yeah.
- Good.
Now...
go stop Savitar.
H.R.
Savitar took the Speed Force bazooka.
Bye-bye, Vibe.
Keep him alive.
What? Why?
Because I need him to
build something for us.
"Iris West-Allen."
It changed back.
- Does that mean what I think it means?
- Yeah, Joe.
The future's ours again.
Savitar?
- Something's wrong.
- What is it?
She's... not dead.
How is that possible?
H.R.
He took her place.
I thought you said H.R. lives.
Not anymore!
If Iris doesn't die...
That means the future's changing.
So is yours.
Synced and corrected by Aaronnmb
www.addic7ed.com
What?
H.R.'s dead? I... I can't believe that.
- Is Tracy all right?
- Not good.
She just wants to be alone.
There'll be time to mourn.
Right now, we need to
figure out our next move.
So for the millionth time,
I'm lost on all this time travel stuff.
What happens now? With Savitar?
Iris didn't die. So that
changes things, right?
I mean, since Iris didn't die,
future me never goes
down that same dark path.
I never create time
remnants to fight Savitar.
And if future you never
creates these time remnants,
then Savitar himself is never born.
Precisely. Once the time paradox
catches up with him, then...
he'll be erased from existence.
But I saw him. He didn't disappear.
- Not yet.
- But he will, Joe.
Any guesses how long that's gonna take?
Maybe a few hours?
He can do a lot of
damage in a few hours.
Well, guys, we can't just sit around
and wait for Savitar to disappear.
But Savitar won't become
Savitar if he's erased.
Not unless he pulls off
whatever he's got in mind,
before the paradox hits him.
- He stole the bazooka for a reason.
- Yeah, why?
I don't know, but remember,
he's been planning this for centuries.
He wants to be a god.
He must need the bazooka,
and Caitlin, to achieve his goals.
Anybody got any good news?
Actually, uh, voilà.
- What is that?
- This, Detective,
is the cure for Caitlin.
You're kidding. You figured it out?
Not by myself. With the help of...
Caitlin's mother.
This is experimental gene therapy.
This? This will rewrite
Caitlin's meta-DNA.
This will bring back...
Caitlin.
I searched the forest.
Savitar and Caitlin were gone.
So was Cisco.
Savitar has 'em both.
Oh, you better have a plan B,
'cause I don't think your
plan A worked out too well.
Fix this.
Fix what? The Speed Force bazooka?
Hey, I didn't name it.
If I didn't name it, I didn't make it.
And if I didn't make it,
I don't know how it works.
Oh, you know enough about
it to alter what it does.
Oh, I see. You want me to alter it.
Well, what do you want
me to alter it into?
Like, a hair dryer? Or a waffle maker?
Oh, I know. Maybe something that's gonna
fix that thin-crust
pizza you call a face.
An intradimensional quantum splicer.
A splicer.
I do have a plan B.
I open a time portal,
exposing the Speed Force,
you shoot me with that,
and I become fragmented
throughout all of time.
The past, present, future.
After that, the paradox can't reach me.
You wanna splice
yourself throughout time?
Exist in every single
moment there ever was?
All of us aware and connected
through one consciousness.
I'll be everywhere...
every hour, every minute.
And then,
I will rule from the Big Bang
until the end of the world.
You wanted us to build this thing.
Well, why do you think
I let you idiots live?
Tracy Brand trapped me in
the Speed Force in the future.
All I had to do was get her
to build this a little earlier
and have my best friend
make all the adjustments.
I'm not your friend.
Get...
to work, Francesco.
How about I sit on my ass
and let you obliterate
permanently from existence?
How's that sound?
That's your plan?
Do it or you'll Reverse-Flash me?
Not you.
Her.
You know what I'm remembering?
Julian just got back to S.T.A.R Labs.
He has the cure.
He can turn her back.
You can have her back. You're so close.
But not if she's dead.
So put that mechanical
genius to good work.
Make me what I need.
And I will let you both go.
I hated Thawne...
and Zoom.
They took so much from me.
And I've hated Savitar
for threatening to take
you away from me too.
But he didn't.
I know.
There is strength in anger.
I've used it before.
And so we sit here, with our anger,
trying to think of a way to hurt Savitar
or maybe kill him.
And I just don't think that
hate's gonna get it done this time.
What do you mean?
Something that Snart said to me...
that the Flash should
stay a hero, all the way,
and sometimes that it's not
about who can punch the hardest
or run the fastest.
So what are you gonna do?
The last thing he'd expect.
I wasn't sure you'd come.
Must be an odd sensation,
getting new memories.
You having an uncertain future.
What do you want? I'm busy.
Doing what?
Getting erased from existence?
We will see which one of us gets erased.
Are you still planning
on becoming a god?
Cisco and Caitlin are still alive.
If that's what you're worried about.
Oh, I know. You need them, right?
To pull off your grand ascension.
Look, Barry,
if I wanted to talk to myself,
I could have done that, back at my lair.
What... do you want?
I wanna help you.
- Really?
- You don't have much time...
before the paradox reaches you.
Come back to S.T.A.R Labs.
Let Cisco and Caitlin go,
and let us figure out a way to save you.
You really think I'd trust you?
You showed up.
So you remember me coming here.
Did I have any tricks up my sleeve?
Was I... was I planning
on blindsiding you?
I don't know, Barry.
Maybe I get off on watching you grovel.
No, I don't think that's it.
I think you're hearing me.
I'm still in there.
Deep down, buried beneath
the scars and the pain,
that part of you that...
it must feel so lonely.
But it also knows what
it's like to have a family,
to have friends.
You can have all that back.
We can stop hurting each other.
I remember when I was six, and, uh...
I begged Mom and Dad
to let me go to the
Science Expo in Midway.
And, uh, well, we got a flat
tire on that dirt road, no spare,
so we were towed to that garage
in a tiny, one-street town.
Of course, we were stuck there all day.
Then we got ice cream
and French fries with gravy
at that little diner.
And then that night, we watched
the local fireworks show, and...
Actually, it turned
out to be a great day.
And it's my favorite
memory of Mom and Dad.
What was the name of that town?
Masonville.
I'm still in there.
Come home.
You make a move toward Iris...
He won't. Killing Iris...
won't save him now, not anymore.
Where is Cisco? Where's Caitlin?
- They're safe.
- I was asking him.
Show me that you can help me.
Then I will tell you
where your friends are.
You tell us now, or you go up in smoke.
This is bloody insanity.
- Can't believe this.
- What is he doing here?
- He's a monster.
- Hey! Hey! Stop! Guys.
It's okay.
Everyone, just...
Iris, stay away from him.
Look at me.
It's okay. Look at me.
We're gonna help you, okay?
Thank you.
Right. Well, since our guest here
has both of our resident
scientists hostage,
what temporal problem
can we help you with?
Tracy built the Speed Force trap.
Maybe she has an idea.
Tracy's our best bet.
Am I?
So... you're Savitar.
I hear you're about to
have a really bad day.
Good.
Tracy...
He stole my future.
Why does he deserve one?
I shouldn't have come here.
No. We'll get her to help us.
I think I know someone who might be able
to get through to her.
Uh... I'm not H.R.
My name is Harrison Wells.
I'm from a different Earth.
In the multiverse...
how to explain this?
You're... his doppelganger?
Yeah.
Something like that... look.
These people...
they're good people.
And they need your help.
By helping the bad guy
that I spent weeks trying to stop?
No. I won't do it.
The only reason I agreed
was because of H.R.
H.R. needs your help.
H.R. is dead.
That's why you need to stay.
Because of what Savitar took from you,
because of what Savitar
took from H.R... everything.
H.R. paid the price that he did
because he loved these people.
Because he loved you.
And when the moment came,
H.R. didn't run.
Strange being back here.
You remember S.T.A.R Labs?
I remember everything.
This is where we came up
with the cerebral inhibitor
to use against DeVoe.
Who?
You haven't gotten there yet.
So how's this gonna
work? Where will I live?
What do you mean?
Are Wally and I gonna be bunk-mates?
Am I supposed to just rejoin Team Flash,
fight some Rogues?
What kind of life were
you thinking I'd lead?
I hadn't gotten that far yet.
How do we explain me at the wedding?
And do I sit bride-side or groom-side?
Ah, look, I mean, we
don't have all the answers.
You know, we're gonna figure it out.
Together.
No.
Not together.
Love and hate, they're so close.
It's easy to mistake one for the other.
You're gonna spend the
rest of your life with him.
But I remember giving you the ring.
Singing to you.
Asking you to marry me.
I can't do this.
No, yes, you can. Okay?
I will be here for you.
I tried to kill you.
I killed H.R.
And you are going to
have to live with that.
But we won't give up on you, okay?
That is not what we do.
There is a way through
this for all of us.
Where are Cisco and Caitlin?
I'll bring them home.
What is it?
There's energy radiating
from the breach room.
And it's not breach energy.
It's the philosopher's stone.
It's releasing all its energy.
Savitar.
It looks like it's gonna blow.
Wally. Get everybody out.
Is it finished?
Yeah. It's finished.
Fantastic.
You know Savitar's gonna
turn on you one day.
No, he won't.
A bad guy like Savitar
always turns on his partners.
Not this time.
Wake up!
You're only saying that because
he needs something from you.
Once he's done with
that, it's over for you.
- How'd it go?
- As I expected.
I was a fool to think otherwise.
Where did he go? What did you do?
I got rid of a problem.
A few of 'em.
Now I can fix mine.
- Are we ready?
- Yes.
Do it.
Caitlin...
Listen to me.
He'll do it.
He'll kill you.
I'll take my chances.
Gypsy! No, wait. No!
You don't care that they got away?
No, it doesn't matter.
It's time.
Ow!
I had that. I was
getting through to her.
You were almost killed.
Maybe that's how it looks
to the untrained eye.
These eyes are highly trained.
And I know you were in danger because
I vibed it across the multiverse.
I can't believe this is the
thanks I get for saving you!
This isn't thanks! This
is the opposite of thanks!
Wait a minute.
How did you vibe that I was in trouble?
Because we are connected.
Jackass.
Guys?
Oh, my God.
I thought something
happened to you guys.
Two-Face told me you guys were dead.
We're okay. Gypsy...
- Gypsy.
- Guys.
Gypsy.
- Harry.
- Here to help.
Good.
I know what he's up to.
We have to hurry.
I must become immortal
before the paradox reaches me.
Today, I become a god.
This is why I brought you here.
The Speed Force doesn't like it
when speedsters mess with time.
Get ready.
See ya later, Hunter.
The one thing Black
Flash can't fight... cold.
Finally! To be a god!
What?
No!
I've been waiting a
long time to do that.
Garrick!
- How did you...
- He didn't.
I did.
By changing the polarity
of the climbing arc,
I changed your Speed Force splicer
into a Speed Force skeleton key.
Didn't think I was
actually gonna let you
become a god, now, did you?
Let's end this.
Go!
Go ahead, Cisco. Go bad.
No. I never will.
But I will give you a choice.
You wanna be Caitlin again?
Here's your chance.
Look out!
You'll pay for what you did!
And you can die the same way twice.
I knew you didn't have
it in you, Caitlin.
I only have a few minutes left.
I can feel it.
But before I go,
I'm gonna kill Joe.
And Wally.
And Iris.
If I am going to die,
then everything you
love is going to die too.
No!
How's it feel...
to get so close to your ascension,
and end up on the ground?
Now I see.
- It's written.
- Nothing's written!
Do it!
You kill me, you become me.
Either way, I live.
I'll never let the pain,
the darkness, determine who I am.
I will never be you.
All these months, you were
trying to save me from him.
Look at that. I saved you.
_
When I think of H.R.,
I'm reminded of...
a story that John Lennon once told.
When Lennon was five years
old, his teacher asked him to...
write down what he wanted
to be when he grew up.
Lennon wrote, "Happy."
His teacher said that he didn't
understand the assignment, and...
Lennon said that they
didn't understand life.
H.R. understood life.
He wasn't a genius, and
he didn't have super speed.
But when we needed him
the most, he was our hero.
He was my hero.
Mine too.
Good on you, mate.
Thanks for believing in me, H.R.
Hey, I've been looking for
the right time to tell you.
Tell me what?
Right before H.R. died,
he asked me to give you a message.
Tell... tell Cisco...
this took strength,
and he gave it to me.
I know that you've had a connection
with every Wells that we've met, but...
I don't know. Something
about this Wells...
Yeah...
Something.
I'll be right back.
Well, well, well.
At least you're not shopping
at Villains "R" Us anymore.
I'm sorry about H.R.
I'm sure he would have
appreciated you coming.
Why did you come?
I don't know.
Maybe you wanted to come home.
I don't have a home.
Yes, you do, Caitlin.
You do. With your friends.
With me.
I'm sorry, Julian.
I'm not Caitlin anymore.
You're not Killer Frost.
No, I'm not.
I'm something else.
And I need to figure out what that is.
On my own.
Hey.
Cisco.
Let me go.
- Stop it.
- It's not funny.
- I know.
- Why are we laughing?
We should not be laughing.
Today, of all days.
I think H.R. would have approved.
Probably.
Are you okay? I mean...
with what you did.
I'm sure one day, it'll hit me.
In the future,
which... I have again.
We have.
Every day of it.
♪ Every hour, every minute ♪
I think we have the song picked out
for the dance at our reception.
Oh, yeah, that reminds me.
I can officially mail these.
What are these?
Save the date cards for our wedding.
On one of my braver
days, I filled them out.
I never mailed them,
not knowing if I would...
live to see the ceremony, but...
but now I guess it's safe to...
Delivered.
I wasted a lot of money on stamps,
thank you very much.
Are you...
ready to be Iris West-Allen?
I've always been Iris West-Allen.
I've always been yours.
What was that?
Oh, my...
There's never been an
earthquake in Central City.
That wasn't an earthquake.
You found something?
Everything's barbecued.
I'm gonna try to establish
an up-link to the satellite.
That's not good.
Hey, Wally, can you reverse the polarity
- on the neutron flow?
- On it.
Central City University
just reported an earthquake
of 6.6 on the Richter scale.
- That's not an earthquake.
- Then what was it?
Earthquakes come from down below.
This... this is something else.
It's gettin' bad out there.
Emergency services will
soon be overwhelmed.
Guys. 7.2, that last one.
- Cisco.
- Yeah?
We're on! Guys.
What is that thing?
- That's definitely not a breach.
- Holy plutonium.
What even emits that many kilojoules?
The Speed Force.
But Savitar's dead.
That's the problem.
It's the Speed Force prison.
It needs an occupant.
When you freed me, we emptied it.
- Without a prisoner...
- It goes unstable.
And now it's bleeding
energy onto our Earth.
Okay, so how do we stop this?
By giving it what it needs.
Which is what?
The Speed Force is unbalanced.
I have to stabilize it.
- What? How?
- By running into it.
No, you can't. Barry, you'll
be trapped in there forever.
If I don't go, the whole city,
maybe even the entire
planet, could be destroyed.
Cisco.
There's gotta be another way, right?
Barry, Central City needs The Flash.
And they'll have one.
They'll have one.
Right?
Yeah.
Mate...
Do you mind sticking around?
- Anything for you.
- Barry.
Wally and Jay said they were in hell.
Barry, it's your mother.
That's the Speed Force.
Barry isn't going to hell.
But like all runners must eventually,
he's reached his finish line.
His race is over.
You can't take him with you.
She's not taking me anywhere.
I have to go.
Why? Why are you being punished?
This, all of this, it
started with my mistake,
with Flashpoint.
This is... this is my penance.
This is my redemption.
My beautiful boy.
It's time to rest.
- Don't mess it up with her.
- I'll do my best.
They're all gonna look to you now.
I'm not a hero like you.
You've always been my hero.
All this time we were
trying to save Iris,
you're telling me that...
we should've been
trying to save you too?
You did save me, Joe.
You took an 11-year-old
boy with a broken heart,
and you gave him a home
and so much love.
No son ever felt more
love from a father.
No father ever felt more proud of a son.
Barry.
It's time.
This isn't fair.
I know.
We were supposed to
have our happy ending.
I'm ready to be Iris West-Allen.
And you always will be.
But you need to keep living your life.
Keep growing.
Keep loving.
Keep running. For me.
Promise me you'll run, Iris.
I promise.
I gotta go.
Synced and corrected by Aaronnmb
www.addic7ed.com