Hey, Jimenez.
Do you think
the Special Forces guys killed him?
If he can even be killed, that is.
What do you mean?
What are you talking about?
I don't know.
But I heard they shot him 20 times.
They pumped him full of lead first.
Then they burned his body
and spread his ashes all over Medellin.
And they say that
he rose from the ashes,
and he went to the houses
of each of the men who had shot him,
and he killed them as they slept.
Bullshit.
Quiet! Someone's coming.
We're soldiers from the National Army!
Stop and identify yourselves!
We're well armed!
Mr Escobar.
I'm sorry, but we've been ordered
to not let you through.
We have to take you into custody again.
I'm sorry, son...
But unfortunately,
I can't allow that to happen.
If you'll excuse me.
Not a word of this to anyone,
understood?
This...
is an embarrassment for Colombia,
gentlemen.
So...
- How will we proceed?
- Mr President...
Escobar will surely attempt
to re-establish himself within the city,
and we can't allow him or his sicarios
to move freely.
So my recommendation, Mr President,
is that we occupy Medellin.
Flood the streets with officers.
Conduct searches.
Close down the streets.
Establish vehicle checkpoints.
Pressure him until he appears.
And who would conduct
such an operation?
Colonel Pinzón, sir.
- He should begin immediately.
- Of course, sir.
- Are you injured?
- No, I'm OK. I'm not hurt.
You know I couldn't talk to him.
I couldn't negotiate with Escobar.
- I understand.
- Why did you go inside?
I don't know.
I sensed something was off.
Ariza said his orders were only
to secure the perimeter.
Well, he lied. I gave the order myself.
Go home and get some rest,
but come back soon.
You know you're the only person
I can trust.
Yes, sir.
It's all right, Tata. I'll be right back.
Excuse me, Doña Hermilda.
Boss.
- Good to see you.
- It's great to have you back.
Very good to see you.
He's here. It's him.
- Praise the Lord. I knew it. I knew it!
- How are you, brother?
Pablo!
Thank God.
- Oh, my son!
- How are you?
- I'm fine.
- You're OK?
- How are you?
- I'm fine.
- You're all right?
- I am.
- I did everything I could, Dad.
- I know.
I know.
I'm very proud.
I love you very much.
It's Dad.
...you and your family. May he always
protect you in his holy glory.
Thank you very much.
You're great boys.
- Monitor the police frequencies.
- Yes.
And don't bother me
unless it's necessary.
As you wish, boss.
Very good.
Very good, gentlemen.
Please take the things out of the car,
put them over there.
I felt I'd lost you.
You're never going to lose me.
And what now, Pablo?
What will we do now?
I did what I had to do, Tata.
I'll take care of it.
We'll be fine, and content,
and happy, and together, and united.
But...
Always.
- Tell me you'll never leave me.
- Never.
Promise me.
I promise.
I promise, my love.
I understand, you're from the DEA,
but I have to ask Colonel Pinzón first.
Wait one moment.
Gentlemen, wait here for a moment.
We'll let you in once the area
is secured, understood?
We're going to have to move everything.
- What do you mean by "everything"?
- Everything. The labs...
the offices, the hideouts, the deposits...
we're moving everything.
Boss, even the labs?
They're well-guarded.
There's no problem.
Come on, don't you know
what's going on at La Catedral?
The cops are going through the maps
and documents you idiots left behind.
Now we can't trust anyone,
you bastards.
Who are you calling a bastard?
We are. Moving. Everything.
- Right?
- Yes, sir.
Yes, Don Pablo.
We're also going to need more men.
Last night we lost a lot of brothers.
- May they rest in peace.
- Amen.
And one last thing.
I'm going to need a good driver with a
clean record to drive me around the city.
He needs to be smart,
fearless and determined.
- Done, boss.
- Boss, I'm sorry, but...
You can't risk yourself like that.
Yes, Don Pablo, I agree with Velasco.
I want people to know that
Pablo Escobar doesn't hide like a rat.
Because we...
are the Medellin cartel, motherfucker!
Pablo, no!
You believe whatever the fuck
you want, you son of a bitch!
- This again? Stop obsessing. Relax.
- Relax? What do you want me to do?
To sit here and wait for Pablo
to walk through that door
and kill me and my daughter?
He's going to come and kill you, too.
- How about that?
- Pablo won't be killing anyone.
Jaime, what country do you live in?
If he hasn't killed anyone yet,
he's planning on it.
Haven't you noticed, Berna?
Judy, haven't you noticed?
Gaviria's got this city
swarming with cops.
There's a cop
on every fucking corner.
Pablo can't move.
Then we have to find and kill
the bastard before the police finds him.
Judy, listen.
Listen to me! Listen!
Pablo, right now, is like a caged rat.
Understand?
Jaime.
Despite everything, you still don't know
what Pablo's like?
- He's someone we can't underestimate.
- You said it, Berna.
They shouldn't underestimate us either.
Pablo's running out of allies,
and you know it.
Pablo will always have allies.
Berna, I want everyone to know
what happened to Kiko.
It should be crystal clear
that being loyal to Pablo
will only earn you a bullet in the head.
They'll know what side
they should be on, right?
Judy...
what shall we do with the labs?
What do you suggest?
I think we shut down the labs,
at least for a while.
We have to lay low
until Pablo is killed or captured.
That's bullshit, Berna.
Tell me how that makes any sense.
A lot of other people stopped
paying Pablo at the same time as us.
Let's join forces with them.
There's the Priscos, for example.
Last night I met with Ricardo.
I'll talk to him.
Jaime, be very careful
with those people.
- Hello?
- OK?
- Nice.
- One moment.
Ricardo?
Don Pablo.
Of course there was
no decision to make.
You know that
you can always count on us.
Sweetie!
Fag!
How's it going, Limóm?
- Son of a bitch.
- How's it going, brother? Good or what?
Quica, my love, come give me
the best 20 minutes of my life.
What are you doing here?
Are you going in?
No, brother.
I didn't come to see the whores.
- Then what?
- I came to see you, brother.
And from what I can see,
you're still driving whores everywhere.
You know. I have to pay rent.
Listen, Limón,
why don't you make good money?
Doing what?
- The same thing, brother.
- Driving who?
Pablo Escobar, brother.
- Eat shit, you bastard.
- Limón, I'm serious.
Come here.
The boss asked us to find someone...
you know, someone clean,
who the police don't know.
He would go in the trunk.
- Where would I have to take him?
- Wherever he says. You don't ask.
What do you think, brother?
There's cops everywhere.
Why don't we put a girl in the back
so no one gets suspicious?
- Which one of the whores do you trust?
- They're whores.
Then who, brother?
- No!
- No?
- Thanks.
- Why not?
- No.
- What's wrong with it? Nothing.
- I'm very busy, Jhon.
- That doesn't matter, Maritza.
Yes?
Ask one of the girls
you drive around all day.
- I can't.
- Move.
Maritza... I need you to do it.
It'll be the easiest money
you've ever made.
You'll be able to quit your second job,
understand?
To take care of your daughter.
Haven't I always done right by you?
I've always helped you and your family.
80? Right?
You're a son of a bitch, you know?
So?
- And who's that?
- He's a friend. He's trustworthy.
What's up, Quica?
This is the girl I told you about.
Let's go.
Take care, skinny!
- All good?
- All good, brother.
I'll follow you, brother.
- Who's that bitch?
- Close your fucking legs, Rosa.
You'll kill all the flowers.
You shit-eating bastard.
This pussy smells great.
Now you buy your whores
at the market?
Don't get pissy.
If you're in a better mood
when I come back this afternoon,
you'll get to fuck me.
Fucking Quica.
Shut up! Go inside! Watch yourself!
Ready? Close your eyes.
All right.
It's a little bunny, my love.
She's very delicate.
Boss?
Look, Don Pablo...
this is the guy
I've been telling you about, Limón.
He's Guarazapo's cousin.
Limón! Come here, brother.
Come on!
Pleasure to meet you, sir.
Don't worry, boss.
We've known each other for a long time.
Besides, the police don't know
who he is. He's clean.
And where are you from, son?
I was born in Envigado, sir.
My mother lives in the barrio
you built for us.
I'm very glad.
- What about the girl?
- She...
She's a friend, boss.
We went to school together in Envigado.
I know her well
and I know where she works,
so she's someone we can trust, boss.
Listen, Limón...
Do you know what it means
to work for me?
It's an honour to work for you,
Don Pablo.
You've done so much
for the poor in Medellin...
if I have to lose my life for you...
I will, boss.
All right.
Open the trunk.
Don't worry, brother. Everything's good.
All yours.
Where are we?
- What the fuck are we doing here?
- Get down and hide.
- Jhon, I don't...
- Shit, Maritza,
I don't have time to give you
explanations. Just do it, all right?
Don Pablo.
- Hello.
- Welcome.
Thank you. No, don't get up.
Don't get up.
- How are you?
- Very well.
Great, I'm very glad.
- Rojas.
- Don Pablo.
How have you been?
Good, yourself?
I wasn't expecting you.
- I'm well.
- Guys, please.
Yes, sir.
Do you want anything to drink, sir?
- A coffee?
- No, thanks.
- Anything?
- Thank you, I'm fine.
- How are you?
- I'm well, sir. Everything is well.
- How is Maribel?
- Maribel is well, sir. Thank you.
Good, brother.
What's going on with the deposits?
They're looking a bit low.
Well, after everything
that happened with...
with Mr Gateano
and Mr Moncada, well...
people are nervous, you understand?
This woman, Judy Moncada,
has been saying things...
So people don't want to pay.
- That's it?
- That's it, sir. I thought you knew.
- I told them to tell you...
- Calm down. Don't worry about that.
We'll fix that problem soon.
Yes, sir.
In the meantime...
I want you to move
to the offices in Laureles.
It's no longer safe here.
- Done, sir. Whatever you say.
- Good.
And fill this up, please.
Don Pablo!
- Sir, how are...
- Is that you?
- How are you, sir?
- Sweetie! Sweetie!
Sweetie!
Don Pablo is in front of our house.
Don Pablo?
- Don Pablo!
- Ma'am, how are you?
Fine, and you?
- It's him, old man.
- Sir, how are you?
- How is your health?
- It's good. Very good!
Good. Good. How are all of you?
Good? Good?
- How are you, Don Pablo?
- Good.
It's him.
In the flesh?
- Good?
- Boss, we should get going.
Let them see me. Let them see me.
I never thought I'd meet you in person.
I'm well, Ma'am, how are you?
- Here, boss, behind you.
- Here. Let's see.
- Generous as always, Don Pablo.
- For you.
- Thank you, Don Pablo.
- For the doctor, sir. For the doctor.
- Take care of yourself.
For you, Ma'am.
For you too, sir.
There's a girl on line three.
She wants to talk to an American.
- What's wrong, brother?
- Suck my dick, please.
- DEA Agent Peña.
- Pay attention.
I know where you can find
one of Escobar's little men.
Oh, yeah? Which one?
There's a reward, right?
Yes, there's a reward.
What's your information, miss?
Who are you talking about?
La Quica.
La Quica?
You know La Quica?
He came to the brothel on 23rd street.
He left with a man in a taxi,
said he'd come back later.
Do you work there?
Yes.
How long ago was this?
A couple of hours.
All right, we'll look into it.
It would be worth investigating, Colonel.
We're not asking much.
Did you close the lab?
Jesus Christ.
No, Berna, I haven't and I won't
because it's not necessary.
- Listen to me, Jaime...
- No, you listen to me. Enough of this.
I already spoke with
Ricardo Prisco, right?
He's with us. He supports us.
Everything's good.
What else could we want?
I told you to be careful
with those people, Jaime.
Pay attention to me.
First, these guys have been with us
since Pablo killed Kiko, right?
Second, Ricardo knows
that being loyal to Pablo
means a bullet in the head.
And third, and to ease your mind,
they're sending us men, for security...
What?
So you gave these people
the address to the lab?
Don't be an idiot.
How else would they get here?
Jaime, listen to me.
Get out of there now.
Get moving and come here right now!
Listen to me, Berna!
Stop with the paranoia!
Jaime! Jaime! Come here now!
- Now!
- Come play, motherfuckers!
Jaime! Jaime!
Get out now!
What's going on, Ricardo?
You're fucking up, man.
Ricardo, put that shit down, brother.
Ricardo, put it down.
Pablo is weak, brother.
You know this.
The city's filled with cops.
Pablo can't move, brother.
Ricardo, put the gun down.
Hello, Jaime.
Jaime.
- Berna, how have you been?
- Who's this?
This is Pablo speaking. I imagine
you want to talk to Jaime, right?
Berna, help me, man.
Berna, talk to Pablo.
Explain everything, Berna! Help me!
Pablo, no! Wait!
And now, you fat bastard...
we're coming after you
and that bitch you protect.
Pablo, you've just made
the biggest mistake.
Tell the others...
Who is it?
...that Pablo Escobar is to be respected,
you son of a bitch.
That son of a bitch!
His entire family, understand?
I want everyone
in his fucking family dead!
That fat fuck!
Son of a bitch!
Listen, Judy...
I'm very sorry about Jaime,
and about all of these deaths.
We have to accept
that we lost this time.
But you know what?
I'll be with you until the end.
And if you want to go head on
against Pablo, just say so.
We'll find strong allies. And people.
A lot of people.
Yes.
You're right.
I think we have to see things
for what they are.
The truth, just as it is.
And this is the truth, Berna:
I know of someone who's very powerful.
Someone who wants to kill Pablo
as much as I do.
- You sure it's not a trap?
- I'm not sure of anything.
Hello, Fernando.
You did very well, sister.
Look... you don't just get two,
you get three.
You have a special talent, that's why
you get not two, but three green ones.
What are you doing tonight, sweetie?
I know of a nice calm place.
We could have fun.
I can't.
I have to take care of my daughter.
- Bitch. Give me 30 minutes, Limón.
- All right, brother.
I'm going to fuck one of them.
Sweetie...
Thank you, Maritza.
Bastard.
Excuse me! Excuse me! Excuse me!
Right here, to the right.
It's the next right.
Know the area well, don't you, Peñita?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah? You like that? Yeah?
There's the taxi. Park on the left. There.
Calm down! Calm down!
OK, let's go.
All right. Wait for me here.
- Trujillo!
- Go around! Go around!
Move! Move! Move!
Brother!
Goddammit. What?
- Quica! Quica!
- What's going on?
Let's go, brother. Hurry up!
Brother! Hurry, Quica!
They're cops, brother! Run!
Stop looking.
This is the best place to eat.
The situation is that...
your escape has left us without...
We don't have a lot of options.
If I hadn't escaped,
they would have killed me, Fernando.
Or I'd rot in an American jail.
- You will tell Gaviria...
- Gaviria is being crucified by the media.
I think it's not a good time.
You will tell Gaviria...
I'm willing to go back to La Catedral
to finish my sentence.
As you wish.
- In the morning, I'll return to Bogotà.
- No, no, no, brother.
We can't... leave for tomorrow
what we can do today.
Right?
Mr President,
Mr Fernando Duque is on the line.
- I have nothing to say to him.
- I'll handle it. You go ahead.
Mr Duque.
- Eduardo Sandoval speaking.
- Mr Vice Minister,
I have an important
message from Mr Escobar.
He says he's willing to negotiate the
conditions for his return to La Catedral.
Turn on the television.
- What did he say?
- He told us to turn on the TV.
Good evening, compatriots.
In the last year and a half, we've
enjoyed the peace we'd been waiting
for over a decade.
Now we can go to work,
drop our children off at school,
and enjoy life's small pleasures...
without the threat of violence
looming around every corner.
This peace is now threatened
by Pablo Escobar's escape.
Escobar has been named the bloodiest
narco-terrorist of all time.
This history... changes today.
But I need your help.
We must come together as a people,
as a country,
so his reign of terror comes to an end
here and now.
This is why I'm before you now...
offering a reward of 1.4 million dollars
for whoever gives information
leading to his capture.
It is my hope
that through this reward...
the day will finally come
when our country is free of his grip
and ceases to be held hostage
by terror, intimidation...
and murder.
I want to make it very clear...
that under no circumstances...
will I negotiate with Pablo Escobar.