Get down!
One!
Rosa!
Tell me who talked to the police!
Who talked to them?
It had to be that whore in the market.
Please, Quica!
Thanks for accepting the invitation.
Forgive me for the hood.
It's for security reasons.
- I hope you understand.
- I understand.
Can I offer you something?
Coffee, water?
No, I'm fine, thank you.
Let's begin, then.
- Do you regret going to jail a year ago?
- Absolutely not. In fact...
what I regret least is having escaped.
The Special Forces came in
and opened fire.
I put my life at risk, right?
However...
I hope this interview
makes it clear to the president...
I'm willing to return to any prison
in the District of Antioquia.
The most modest
and the most humble.
But I have to check the conditions
they're going to put me in
because it would be easy, for example,
for someone to rig a car bomb
that would explode when I arrived.
It turns out that my problem
turned into a political problem.
It appears I'm very important
to the re-election
of the president of the U.S.
I'm ready to pay for my mistakes
by accepting the most humble cell
as long as my rights are respected
and they guarantee me that I will not
be transferred anywhere for any reason.
Do you acknowledge that
you've committed crimes in the past,
or that you ordered someone's death?
That answer I could
only give to a priest.
In a confessional.
Marietta.
- What's up?
- What happened?
They killed them.
I think there were six or seven girls.
Who would do something like this?
Are you, by nature, violent and proud?
Those who know me
know I have a great sense of humour.
I consider myself a happy man.
I've always been happy,
always optimistic.
I've always had faith in life.
I always sing in the shower.
How do you think the story
of Pablo Escobar will end?
Well... one can never assume.
I always hope for the best.
I would like to die on my own two feet.
In the year 3047.
Look behind you.
Watch out for that guy.
That's it.
Smash the telephone booth.
Get the pipe.
I already know, Dad.
You have to get it.
And what's that, a woman?
I'm about to fight a woman or what?
- Her name's Nora.
- Oh, yeah, what's her name?
Nora.
Boss, excuse me. I have
to interrupt you one second.
How do you...?
What about the laboratories?
It's been difficult
to find the Moncada laboratories, boss.
And the ones that we find,
we can't get inside.
There are police checkpoints
everywhere.
This morning we lost four men
trying to get through one.
Bastards.
And what about Judy Moncada?
We can't find her anywhere.
Or Don Berna.
Find her.
Yes, sir.
And you, boys?
Everything is good, boss.
- How are you, Limón?
- Very good, sir.
- How are you feeling?
- Very good.
- Comfortable?
- Thanks. Very good.
Good.
I'm going to teach you something.
There is nothing lower than a rat.
And if we let the rats run free,
the streets will be filled with them.
- Understand me?
- Yes, boss.
Give me one second.
One second.
Boss, excuse me. It's Fernando.
Tell me, Fernando.
Your interview worked,
Don Pablo.
Palace wants to meet with me
right away.
You heard that, brother?
- We have to finish our little job.
- But we already finished it, right?
No, brother, there's still one left.
But you already killed all the whores.
I'm not talking about whores, brother.
Why her?
- She did everything we told her to.
- Someone talked to the police.
Yeah, those fucking whores.
She's someone we can trust, man.
You can trust her, but I can't.
Move it.
Quica.
I'm not going to tell you again.
Let's go, we've got shit to do.
Good day.
I have a meeting with the president.
I'm Fernando Duque.
Your meeting is not
with the president, Mr Duque.
How's that?
- With the vice minister, then?
- No, sir.
This says you're meeting
with the attorney general.
My apologies, Mr Duque.
Mr Duque...
I believe that everybody
has the right to a fair trial.
Pablo Escobar has the same rights
as any other Colombian.
If he has committed a crime,
he must be judged and indicted,
not hunted and killed like an animal.
Mr De Greiff,
everything you're telling me I find...
fascinating.
However, I don't...
I don't buckle under the pressure
of the Americans...
like Gaviria, Mr Duque.
Then that means that...
you would consider...
making a deal with Pablo.
I'm saying that Colombia...
has been at war far too long.
Of course.
The Americans
are bringing in new people.
Different faces but, ultimately,
the same motivation.
They are using us
to advance their political agenda.
Yes, maybe.
But the reality is we have to accept help
wherever it comes from.
The thing about the gringos
is they're limited
to Carlos Holguin
and the embassy.
On the other hand, Escobar is gaining
ground, gathering more support.
Everyone supports him in Medellin.
- Along manhunt plays into his hands.
- Let's talk about Medellin.
Colonel Pinzón basically
has Escobar surrounded.
Do you think we'll succeed?
Tip line. What do you want to report?
Agent Peña?
Faggots!
Attorney General De Greiff.
They told me that you met
with Mr Fernando Duque.
That's right.
The president was very clear
that no one was to communicate
with Escobar's people.
Unfortunately for the president,
I don't work for him.
I work for the people of Colombia.
Well, the president and I also work
for the people of Colombia.
And should all work together
in a united front against Escobar.
- Not in a war...
- Are you afraid of what I might find
if I speak with him, Mr Sandoval?
- Excuse me?
- Tell me something.
Why did you need to be there
that night at La Catedral?
Why was the presence of
the vice minister of justice necessary
to transfer a prisoner?
Because we're not talking
about any prisoner.
We're talking about Pablo Escobar.
Besides, I was only following
the president's orders.
I don't think that's true.
Are you insinuating something?
- Are you accusing me of something?
- No, I'm not accusing you of anything.
At least, not yet.
But I'm going to open up
an investigation.
About the allegations...
that, possibly,
you helped Pablo Escobar escape.
You know what, Attorney General?
Eat shit.
- What the hell are we doing here?
- Running an errand.
- What errand?
- For Don Pablo, brother.
Hello.
Hello, gentlemen, can I help you?
Of course. We're here to pick up
a package, under the name Alvarez.
Yes, sir. Right away, with pleasure.
Go ahead.
Brother... let's give up on the girl.
She's not coming back.
Are you afraid or what, Limón?
Close your fucking mouth
and do what I say.
Mr Alvarez!
Quica!
It's the best in the market.
You really know your shit.
Brother!
This is fucking great, brother.
Good.
Put it in the car.
We've got stuff to do.
I'm going to take her eyes out
and make her eat them, that rat bitch.
- What number?
- Room three. I already told you.
Bastard.
You told me she'd be here.
I don't know, brother.
I think this is where she lives.
She's not there.
Let's come back tomorrow,
or later.
Fuck that, brother.
Quica!
Over there, brother.
I got something, brother.
That bitch. I'm going to rip out
her tongue and shove it up her ass.
I told you she wasn't here, brother.
At this hour, she's at work.
- This is bullshit, brother.
- She's not here.
We'll come back later, then.
If the president
doesn't want to negotiate,
then we haven't won anything. Right?
Pablo, we have found
a very good option.
Definitely.
If you let me negotiate with De Greiff,
create some dissension in his ranks...
Oh, Fernando.
That's not what I pay you for,
Fernando.
You pay me to strategise
and that's exactly what I'm doing.
Pablo, you have to understand...
The position
that Gaviria is in right now...
La Catedral was
a humiliating failure for him.
Right now, he's thinking
that capturing you is his only option.
And he's not at all thinking
about trying negotiate, but...
De Greiff, he is willing to talk.
And he has the autonomy
to make deals.
Fine, OK.
Let's do it.
You're not going to believe it,
but the attorney general
supports the legalisation of drugs.
- Don't bullshit me.
- It's true.
Trust me, Pablo, little by little.
With patience, with time...
What we don't have is time, Fernando.
Fernando, excuse us.
- Yes, sir.
- Thank you.
- Blackie.
- Yes, sir.
Thank you very much, Fernando.
- Thank you very much.
- Yes.
Excuse me.
What's wrong?
We can't live like this, Pablo.
Running from one place to another,
hiding,
hoping the government will negotiate.
Gaviria is going to negotiate, Tata.
He's too intelligent and too weak not to.
How are you so calm?
Pablo, if Gaviria doesn't want you in jail
then we both know what he wants.
I think it's time for us
to leave Colombia.
I know we said we'd never leave,
but things have changed.
No, nothing has changed.
My love, we have everything we need.
Let's get the children
and go to some other place.
A place where we don't have to hide.
We're not going
to spend our lives hiding.
I promise you that.
Ortiz, don't let him
out of your sight. Over.
They saw La Quica buying a toilet.
Guess which one he bought.
The same one that Pablo had
at La Catedral. A Kohler.
We need more.
- But what else, Peña?
- Where did they see him?
Going toward the hills
on San Isidro Avenue.
Baby, when are you coming?
You left me all alone.
I can't right now. It's too dangerous.
But you said you were coming.
Let things calm down a little bit.
I'll show you a good time.
Correct me if I'm wrong...
In the last raid,
your two men managed to capture
the president of the United States,
George Bush.
That was based on many different calls
from the tip line.
This is the voice of Velasco.
Ms Messina, apparently
you think my men work for you.
You are mistaken.
I don't work for you.
I decide how we are going
to work together. It's different.
I know what happened
to the last man that worked with you.
Colonel Carrillo.
He was exiled to Spain.
Colonel, General Silva is on the phone.
Excuse me, Colonel.
General?
Move your asses!
The police are coming!
Get the guns, the cars and the money
ready, now! They're close!
Boss!
Boss, forgive me, it's urgent.
Boss.
It's the police.
They're coming up the hill.
We have to leave right now, boss.
Pablo. Pablo!
Bastards.
They're coming from
the other side too.
- What happened?
- We have to leave.
The police are coming.
- Get the cars ready.
- Yes, boss.
- Wait at the back.
Pablo!
Go get the kids.
We have to leave right now.
Come this way. Hurry up!
Hurry. Over here, through the tunnel.
Surround the house! Let's go!
They're gone, sir.
Colonel, nobody's in the house,
no signs of life, sir.
Fuck.
At ease.
Go ahead, come in.
The bedrooms...
they're on the right.
Everything is OK, Tata.
No, Pablo.
This time everything is not OK.
Sweetheart, if Pablo says it's OK,
is because it's...
Was I talking to you?
I'm talking to my husband.
That was very close, Pablo.
And tomorrow, what?
Do you want the children
to watch those men kill you?
No one is going to die, Tata.
I'm dealing with it.
How, Pablo?
Tell me how.
Negotiating?
Yesterday, they nearly killed you
for negotiating.
If you are going to fix it,
fix it for good.
Don't worry.
Ready.
Boss, we're ready.
What's the order?
Do it.
Yes, sir.
- What's up?
- Ready.
All right.
We're ready, sir.
Come.
Step on it!
Do it, brother.
It's cold, you fucking fag!
Finish him! Do it, bastard!
Kill him!