Good morning.
Good morning, Mum.
- Your cat bit me again.
- You stole my pencils.
- Why are you fighting?
- Because he stole my pencils!
- She's making it up.
- Stop fighting.
- Let's see.
- Let's go, sweetie. What time is it?
- 6:40a.m.
- God, I'm late again.
Remember to ask your brother
what we talked about.
- Tell him school starts next week.
- Yes. I'll ask him, all right?
I still have to buy the books, everything.
I told you I'll ask him, my love,
all right?
And you still haven't tied your shoes.
80, like I taught you, right?
We have the rabbit ear,
we go around the tree, and...?
And it goes in the hole.
That was a loud one.
LUIS LODOÑO WHITE,
SERVILE FRONT MAN
AND INITIATOR OF KIDNAPPINGS
FOR PABLO ESCOBAR
Sit him there.
Over here.
Look at that ugly son of a bitch.
One... two... and three.
This family is the only thing
I care about.
- You're the one that...
- Me? Me, ma'am? Me?
- We shouldn't leave, Tata.
- All of this is your fault.
If you'd listened to Pablo,
my brother would still be alive.
Because you do that so well?
Do you listen to him?
When you're always criticising him,
doubting him, worrying.
I would never put this family in danger.
Tell her, Pablo.
Tell her it's not my fault, Pablo.
- I know, Mom.
- This isn't my fault. Tell her, Pablo.
It's not your fault. I know.
It's not your fault.
Everything's all right, Mum.
It wasn't your fault.
Look at these smiling faces.
We didn't want to make you
uncomfortable, Judy.
How considerate of you.
So that's why no one called me?
Because this lab belongs
to the Moncadas.
So I was supposed to be notified
when it was taken back.
- That wasn't made clear to us.
- I'm making it clear now, Carlos.
- What are we going to do with that?
- All the cocaine is going to Cali.
That is my cocaine.
Look, Judy, we decided that not a single
kilo of cocaine will be moved in Medellin
until Pablo Escobar is dead.
That's our strategy. To asphyxiate him.
That's the Cali cartel's strategy?
To keep making money
while the rest of us go hungry?
- You know we can't trust them.
- No. Not them or any of you.
We don't trust any drug trafficker.
Well, let's not get personal, Carlos.
All right?
We all need friends.
Sir, would you like some?
Go!
Sir?
Are you all right?
- We're done working together.
- What's bothering you?
The killing of innocent civilians,
for starters.
Whether they're innocent or guilty,
I don't decide.
That's what priests are for, no?
The Castaños are crazier than ever,
and that wasn't part of the plan.
But it's working.
Not if I stop providing you intel.
For what it's worth, I'm on your side.
I don't like what's happening.
Medellin is my home
and I love it very much.
As far as the methods
of the Castaños go,
well, those are the methods that
have Pablo's people hiding like rats.
Including that gonorrhoea of a lawyer,
Fernando Duque.
Our guys fired a whole fucking clip
at him, point blank.
Can you believe that these sons of bitches
didn't hit him once?
I need you to help me find him.
He's Pablo's mouthpiece
and his connection to the government.
What we want is
to exterminate this rat.
That way, we'll get to Pablo
and we can end this madness, Peña.
I've told you! You have to...
What are you doing?
You have to bring the passports.
Juliana... they're trying to kill me.
We have to get out of here.
I think you're the one
who needs to leave.
Can I see Simon, at least?
- Where... Simon!
- Stop, Fernando!
Simon is at school.
Besides, this isn't even your week.
So, please... leave.
- Oh, what's going on?
- How are you?
- Bye, Anda!
- Bye!
Where's Mum?
Why do you have her car?
Get in.
Come in.
Go on, son. Sit down.
So, you're being reassigned.
You will be moved into the intel unit
that was formed a couple of months ago.
You'll be all right there.
You're sending me to an office
because I made a mistake?
Anything else?
Yes, sir, Colonel.
How are you, Papa?
And you?
- How long will we be there?
- Not long.
Just long enough for me
to get some things figured out here.
Do you remember when we went
to the United States?
It's going to be an adventure,
just like that.
Do they have Disney World there?
I don't think so.
Listen to your mother
and your grandmother. All right?
I made more than one reservation
so no one will know what flight you're on.
I spoke to Fernando
and he said it's perfectly legal.
You have every right
to leave the country.
- It's like a normal trip.
- A normal trip?
Confess. Do you regret it?
Marrying me, or what?
Not for a second.
They may separate us...
...but they'll never be able
to destroy us.
Go.
The little bunny.
I'll take care of him, all right?
Give me a kiss.
Sergeant. Private Hugo Martinez Jr.
at your service, sir.
The colonel's son.
He said you have some
technical background.
I took a couple
of engineering classes, sir.
And I built a ham in my parents' house.
Great. What do you know about RDF?
The basic concept, sir.
The basic concept.
All right.
Get acquainted.
We go out tomorrow afternoon.
And don't worry.
Unlike Carlos Castaño,
this won't hit back.
What's going on?
I'm gonna freeze to death out here.
That's Bogotà. What do you expect?
Hey! What the fuck is wrong with you?
Why are you not working?
Get to work.
I'm not paying you with candy.
- Okay, okay.
- Pass me the phone, boy.
Make some fucking bombs.
You need an invitation to start working?
Hurry, boy! You get to work too!
And don't smoke near the gunpowder.
Hey, boss.
I just came back from the airport.
Miss Tata, the kids and your mother
are on the plane, boss.
Thank the Virgin Mary.
That's the most important thing.
They're flying now.
One more thing.
We hit those fucking drugstores
pretty hard.
You tell us.
Should we come home or...?
No. Stay put. We're not done yet.
I may need you again.
Copy that, boss.
Thank you, Blackie.
Figure out... what time it is in Germany.
On it, boss.
Boss!
Peña.
Any word on our friend?
Did you find him?
- Peña?
- Not yet.
What's up, Peña?
Are we getting a beer or what?
Another day, brother.
See you tomorrow.
No. What are you doing, Simon?
Leave it where it is.
I'm listening to the news.
What are we doing here?
I told you. We're going on a trip.
And what's happening?
Where's my mum?
Simon... calm down.
I already spoke to your mother.
You got yourself into trouble,
didn't you?
It's because you work for Pablo Escobar.
That's why this is happening.
You're his lawyer.
What are we going to do now?
I have a plan. Calm down.
You don't have a plan, Dad.
You're a son of a bitch. A fucking thief.
Did you say "son of a bitch"? "Thief"?
I'm a lawyer. I'm a good lawyer.
All the money this family has,
we have because I've been a good lawyer.
- I do my job.
- I want to call my mum.
You want to call your mum?
Do you want to call your mum,
or do you want to behave like a man?
Are you going to be a pussy
and call your mum? That's a great idea.
Let's call her so she can tell you where
all the money for your toys came from.
Your room full of toys.
Where do you think it came from?
You didn't complain during the Christmases
or the birthdays
or when I bought you a motorcycle.
But now you're complaining. Very well!
Very well. It's over.
It's over! Now that they're
going to kill me, it's over.
I'm sorry... Simon.
I didn't mean to say that.
Forgive me.
Everything will be all right.
Was it a heart attack or what?
You fainted, Pablo.
How many of those are you taking?
I've had a terrible headache.
Those aren't any good, Pablo.
You shouldn't put so much shit
in your body.
You're better off... taking these drops.
They're homeopathic.
Three drops under your tongue
in the morning and two at night.
Have you ever been to Disney World?
I haven't.
It's beautiful.
It's very organised. Very clean.
What's wrong with me, Ricardo?
Stress.
Stress is dangerous.
How's the weed working out?
I haven't been smoking a lot.
The first man who smoked marijuana
was a Chinese emperor.
He burned the plant because
he was attracted to its smell.
But when he inhaled the smoke,
he saw a blue jay.
And the bird told him
to conquer his neighbouring empires.
And that's what he did.
All right.
With you until death, Don Pablo.
Thank you.
I'd like to stay and stand guard.
All right. Thank you.
Let's see, darling.
Colour inside the lines.
There it is.
This is our stop.
- What's going on?
- What's happening?
- Can you give me back my passport?
That money is ours.
- Pablo, they're not letting us in.
- No, no! They can't do that.
- That's what they're doing.
- They can't...
Listen, Tata, that's illegal.
That's illegal. Don't worry.
Don't worry, because...
Do what you need to do to get us
into Germany. I have to hang up.
Don't touch me! I'm asking you
not to touch me. Let go!
No!
Fernando Duque.
Javier Peña.
It took me one day to find you.
If you don't want them to kill you,
you need to start doing things better.
Please... get me out of here.
Please get me out of Colombia.
You know who I work for... worked for?
Well, our help isn't free.
We need full cooperation.
Dad!
Hey, Simon, it's all right.
It's all right. Go back inside.
I'll come up soon.
It's my son. He's... He's scared.
First, we'll get you to Holguin.
You'll be safe...
No! No, we're staying here.
There are cops working
for Los PEPES everywhere.
It would be better if you get us
to the United States at once.
I'll cooperate with you.
Anything you want.
Please get us out of Colombia.
Is that a deal?
Do as I say.
Start by hiding your fucking wife's car.
Hello, German embassy.
First of all, I'll kill every last German
son of a bitch that lives in Colombia.
Then I will bomb Frankfurt, Munich...
I'm going to shove bombs up your asses,
you bastard motherfuckers.
Nazi, racist gonorrhoeas.
I'm going to kill all of you. You hear?
I'm going to kill all of you!
I once heard you say that I had the same
rights as any other Colombian citizen.
I imagine that also applies
to my family, correct?
The government hasn't done anything
to stop Los PEPES.
Those terrorists have attacked
my family and murdered my associates.
Is that how the Colombian government
ensures the rights of all its citizens?
The president is trying to prevent
my family from entering Germany
and yet you do nothing about it.
That man wants to dangle my family before
Los PEPES and use my children as bait,
and you, who call yourself a man
of principle, do nothing about it!
There's a lot of interference.
Yes. Medellin has too many
electrical wires, phone wires, antennae.
- That must be why.
- What's your success rate?
To be honest,
we haven't located a signal yet.
Not one?
Not one.
Here's what we're going to do, Morales.
Let's both start here: L9.329.
There it is.
I was talking to my police contact and
you won't guess who's hiding the lawyer.
None other than that son of a bitch, Peña.
What do you think about that?
Who's your contact?
Who he is isn't important.
The important thing is that I trust him.
Know what the worst part of this is?
We can no longer trust Peña.
Then we'll have to put a bullet in him.
No.
We can't kill DEA agents.
Oh, no? Why not?
If it were up to me,
I'd feed him to the crocodiles.
Berna, look...
Schedule a meeting with Peña,
just as you have been.
We'll take care of the rest.
COURTESY OF LOS PEPES
Córdoba recovers,
we'll have a goalie in place.
Leonel Alvarez can do his thing
and move the ball along.
Did you follow me to the hotel?
You told Berna?
Let go.
Tell me, asshole.
- Let go! It's all right.
- What's the problem?
I'll catch up. Everything's fine.
What's going on, Peña?
Playing the fucking American?
Did you see what they did to his son?
How many families has Pablo Escobar
destroyed, Peña? Do you know?
You don't decide who lives and who dies.
Don't be fucking stupid.
This is how we do it.
I understand that you're trying
to prevent Escobar's family
from entering Germany.
Let's make something clear.
If you've come to plead for them
as part of some deal, the only...
No, Mr President.
I haven't come to plead for them.
I've come to plead for you.
For me? How so?
I know that you want Escobar dead.
And while I don't agree with that,
I understand it.
But this... this I can't understand.
This isn't just wrong.
It puts you, the president of Colombia,
in league with a death squad.
Call the German chancellor.
Tell him to let the family in.
Mrs Escobar, I'm sorry to inform you that
your entry into Germany has been denied.
I know my rights, sir.
But you don't understand.
My children are in danger.
Send me any place other than Colombia.
Tell him the children are under age.
We just want to live in peace...
No.
Tell him that's all we want to do.
To live in peace.
Get the children and your belongs.
Please.
They kick us out of the country and
on top of everything, they keep the money.
I know. I'm going.
What's this?
Why are we being treated this way?
Let's go.
Pardon me.
I hope you enjoyed Germany.
- How much for this?
- Two thousand pesos.
Thank you.
Ladies.
Stop! National police!
It's all right, ma'am, we're with
the national police. Come with us.
The attorney general asked us
to put you under protective custody.
Don't worry. Everything will be all right.
Come with us. You'll be safe. Let's go.
- Come with us.
- Let's go. Quickly. Let's go!
How can I help you, boss?
I want this faggot of a president
to know what happens
when you're on the side
of those bastards, Los PEPES.
I want to see blood.
I want the sky to burn with gunpowder.
I want you to put the biggest bomb
you can get your hands on
as close as you can
to the Presidential Palace. Are we clear?
As you wish, boss.
My love, let's go. Let's go.
Do you want one? Yes? How much?
One hundred pesos.
- Here.
- Thank you.
- Are we going that way?
- That way, darling.
You better be a doctor when you grow up.
This is very expensive.
Elena! Elena, let's go!
Lift him up carefully!