Here to the right.
Stop.
Stay here.
Who's there?
Relax, sir.
We come in peace.
Stay right there!
Relax.
How are the cows?
The cops came here...
a few months ago.
What did you tell them?
The truth.
That I haven't seen you in years.
You've gotten old, Pablo.
It happens.
You look younger.
Life in the country keeps you young.
Be careful, it's hot.
What's your name?
Limón, sir.
Don't give me that shit.
What's your real name?
-Jhon.
Do you know how to milk a cow, Jhon?
- No, sir.
- Well, you'd better learn.
All right, gentlemen.
I get up at 5:00am.
Good night.
Good night, Dad.
It is the state, not individuals,
that has justice in its hands
and the legitimacy to use arms.
Gilberto's no longer our partner.
I don't care what he thinks.
Have you seen the news?
They have issued
a statement without us.
Los PEPES is done.
That's only for show.
The Castaños are still in Medellin.
Hmm?
No one told me anything.
Listen to me, Berna.
If Escobar comes through that door,
we'll kill him ourselves.
We don't need anybody else.
Start moving this product now.
That's all fine, Judy.
But if Gilberto finds out, what then?
Did you know they're offering
$1.4 million for Los PEPES?
I know where they are.
Be careful what you say.
That's a dangerous thought, Judy.
I'm not interested in the reward.
I'm interested in my labs.
Then at least tell Gilberto yourself.
Sir?
Hello.
And to what do I owe this lovely surprise?
We're at the warehouse in Manrique.
This place is full of product.
What do you want us to do?
Where do we send it?
Keep it. Think of it as a contribution
to your great cause
against the communists in the jungle.
I'm sure you'll find its value
can be put to good use.
And what do we do about Judy?
Do whatever you think is best.
Well, Gilberto, if you say so.
Thank you very much.
Fidel. Gilberto said
we can keep all of it.
What? I thought
we were going home.
We don't know anything
about cocaine.
We'll learn.
If they can, why not us?
And what about Judy? Hmm?
Judy feels Medellin
is only big enough for one narco.
We'll let the Castaños decide which one.
- Fabian.
- Yes?
- Bring the Mercedes. Thank you.
- Yes, ma'am. Right away.
Hurry up, Berna.
Relax, Judy.
That meeting can't start without you.
How many people do we have
in the laboratories?
Forty-five in each one.
How many supervisors?
Three in each.
- We need twice as many shifts.
- Yes, ma'am.
Oscar, Luis! Get in the cars.
The boss is leaving.
Yes, sir.
- Peña.
- Javier.
- What do you want?
- Something happened, we need to talk.
- I'm busy. I can't talk.
- There 's been an attempt on Judy.
She's saying a few things
you might want to hear.
Give me time.
- Peña.
- Mr Peña has arrived.
Let's go. Search.
Kiko and I built all of this together.
This is all that is left for me.
What are the Castaños thinking?
That they can chase me out?
I'm not leaving.
They don't want you to leave,
they want to kill you.
And what about you?
You're in this with me, too.
Look...
You brought these guys here.
You got in bed with Cali.
This is all your doing.
This is a fight between narcos.
It's not my problem.
Don't call me again.
Berna, last I heard, leaking classified
intelligence is a federal offence.
Especially when it ends up
in the hands of a death squad
that's killed innocent people.
I'm sure some newspaper in America
might be interested
in hearing more about that.
Are you threatening me?
Yes, I'm threatening you.
You gotta be fucking kidding me.
What do you want?
You're a cop.
You know perfectly well
where Montecasino is.
Where the Castaños are,
and the Rodriguezes.
Arrest them.
And when you do,
accidentally shoot them in the head.
- It doesn't work that way.
- Oh, no?
Then how?
We'll do it my way.
So you want Judy to be a rat?
I don't agree with this, Javier.
We are narcos, but we have our honour.
Berna...
you're a fucking drug dealer
who sells poison by the kilo.
Fuck your honour.
Says you.
You've been happily working
with the information we've provided.
And what have you done?
If you have a better idea, go for it.
Otherwise, this is the deal.
Judy becomes a confidential informant
to the DEA.
She gives us Cali, everything she knows.
If you don't like it,
you can take on the Castaños alone.
We haven't heard anything
from him for weeks.
We don't even know where he is.
I don't know why you're letting
De Greiff come here.
He's coming to scare you.
And now you're losing faith in Pablo.
You don't understand, do you?
We don't have any more money,
Hermilda.
If they take our protection away,
we can't do anything else.
Pablo has many properties.
Don't be so dramatic, Tata.
You think someone
is going to invest in us?
They're going to give us their money?
No one is going to help us.
Everyone knows what that would mean.
Whatever he's doing...
wherever my son is,
he's doing it for his family.
Don't forget that.
Pablo? Pablo?
Can you hear me, Pablo?
Please answer.
Tata, can you hear me?
Tata?
Can you hear me?
That's a lot of product for men
who don't know how to run this business.
We have to be clear with them.
Their work isn't done.
Our donation to them is an advance.
Besides, we have to keep them happy.
Their connection with the Americans
is invaluable, brother.
What a fucking joke,
the CIA and their war
against the communists.
It's a joke, but that friendship
could save our lives one day.
What? Any news about Judy?
The Castaños took their first shot,
a bomb. But they didn't kill her.
Since when did it get so fucking hard
to kill someone?
What about her assistant?
The fat one, what do they call him?
Berna?
He's the one we should kill.
She's just a loud-mouth bitch.
Don Berna. Him we found.
Where?
Here.
Out front.
Don Berna!
Welcome to Cali.
Gilberto, thank you, brother.
Forgive us, but we weren't expecting you.
Don't worry about it.
I'm here to speak to you all.
Very well, brother.
It's about Judy.
Thanks. You won't regret it.
Tata, are you there?
Can you hear me?
There's no signal here.
I don't know why you keep trying.
Why don't you come and drink with us?
I'll be right there.
There's coffee in the Thermos.
He's communicating to his wife via radio.
Those are the codes and frequencies.
What do you want, Lugo?
Money? Visa?
No visa, no money,
you understand?
Is that what he thinks?
That everyone wants to go
to the United States?
I don't want anything.
All I want is for this to end soon and you
to understand the family is in pain.
Find him and kill him.
What are you doing, Pablo?
You don't know how to tie a knot.
This is a cowboy's knot.
This is really good.
Wanted: Pablo Escobar.
Reward 2,700,000 pesos.
Call for free from any city
at 9-800-10-600.
In Bogotà, 222-50-12.
In Medellin, 461-11-11.
The kids would love to be here.
I've been thinking...
I could buy some land here next to you.
Some cows, maybe some sheep.
And have my own farm.
We could run it together.
What do you think?
We need to finish putting up the wire.
Do you remember when the soldiers
came to our village?
You were a tough little boy,
probably only seven or eight years old.
But even in that moment,
you were already the man of the house.
In the face of all that
violence and death, you were strong.
You are a survivor.
A man of action.
I knew that day you were destined
for great things, Pablo.
- Good evening.
- Colonel.
Sit.
So, did you decipher those codes?
Are they real?
Yes, Colonel.
I verified the frequencies.
The codes are the same ones
Escobar's wife is using.
He'll use them when he calls her.
Did you confirm it's Escobar?
Did you hear him?
No, Colonel, not yet.
Why didn't you answer me when I asked
about me coming here with my family?
I wasn't paying that much attention.
But you're paying attention
to me now, right?
So, what do you think?
- It's a nice idea.
- Yes, it's a nice idea.
It's a nice idea, now help me.
Put that bucket down here.
Now hold on to the pig.
Fuck!
Funny that you don't like blood.
How strange.
What are you trying to say?
Clean yourself.
You know what's funny?
That my dad...
has no fucking idea who I am.
I know very well who you are.
Did you know that I was
one of the world's richest men?
Is that right?
You know the President
of the United States knows who I am?
The United States? Disgusting.
I was elected to the
House of Representatives of this country.
Your last name is known throughout
the whole world because of what I did.
- So what? So what? So what?
- So what?
And what about you?
What about you?
An ignorant old man...
who lives alone.
On this shithole farm.
Who doesn't know his own grandchildren.
Not even one fucking picture
of them here.
So I'm nothing more than
an ignorant old man?
That's right.
Now tell me...
Tell me...
what you think of me.
- Who cares?
- I do.
It's important to me.
You wanted to come live on this farm
with your wife and kids.
But that's not possible, Pablo.
You chose your life!
Be in charge of it.
You want me to tell you
what I think of you?
I'm ashamed.
I think you're a murderer.
At last, the truth.
A truth...
that breaks my heart.
Leave me alone.
Limón.
Yes, sir?
You like it here, right?
Yes, boss.
It's a peaceful place.
Peaceful.
Kneel down.
A few kilometres from here, in a field,
you will find a big tree.
Under that tree
is a buried case of money.
Go and get it.
Are we leaving, boss?
Yes.
Go on.
That's correct, Mrs Escobar.
How long did you think
this arrangement was going to last?
Do you not realise that if
we leave here, they're going to kill us?
If you desire, you have the right
to contract private security services.
Tell us how. We don't have a dime.
That is not our problem.
Mrs Escobar, I'm sorry.
You're sorry?
Then help us find asylum
in another country.
I don't have an issue with you
leaving Colombia. But...
But you can't help us find asylum.
That's bullshit!
They're going to... kill us all.
Mama, what's wrong?
Nothing, my love.
I'm sorry, Attorney General...
but I don't know what else to do.
If you're in contact with your husband,
I advise you to express your concern.
Tell him to surrender.
The power of the law is your last hope.
Think about your children.
Shit.
- No.
- Yes, before you go to sleep.
- Do you like it? Yes?
- No. No.
Fuck.
Jhon. What are you doing here?
Where is the money?
The money we gave you. I need it back.
We spent it. It's gone.
Relax. I'm not going to hurt you.
You've already hurt me.
You've fucked up my life.
I want to put the baby in her crib.
Can I put her down?
Hang on, Maritza.
And this?
That's all we have, Jhon.
It's all we have. We need it.
Please, don't take it. Please.
It's for the baby, please!
You lying... bitch! Get off!
Motherfucker! Bastard!
I should turn you in for the reward!
You deserve it!
Sooner or later, they'll find you anyway.
What did you say?
Are you going to say something?
Are you going to rat on me?
I might! Why shouldn't I?
What? So now you're a killer?
Like your hero?
Jhon!
I know you! Get that shit out...
- Boss, I did what you asked.
- Show me.
But I have bad news.
- What happened?
- Look.
It's rotten, sir.
There was half a million dollars
in that fucking case.
This is what I could retrieve, sir.
There's about six thousand dollars
I counted, boss.
Get your things. We're leaving.
Remember, you and I
are partners in all this.
Everything's set.
We have to do this tonight.
Where?
It's a safe house in El Poblado.
We've used it before.
Berna knows Where.
I'll see you there.
Everything is ready, Judy. Get in.
Let's go, Flaco.
I know what you're thinking.
I'm making a mistake.
You'll be taken care of
like you've taken care of me.
The only thing that needs to happen
is to get rid of the Cali cartel.
Up here, Flaco.
I can't protect a rat.
I didn't think you'd betray me.
You were going to get yourself killed,
Judy.
So now, you're going
to get on that plane.
And if I don't, what?
What happens?
If you don't get on,
then you'll leave with the Castaños.
And I won't protect you anymore.
Tell me something.
Did Cali arrange this?
How much did they offer you?
At least tell me that.
It's a mutual understanding.
I'll work with the Castaños.
They don't understand our business,
- but they'll be useful in mine.
- So you fucked over your partner.
I was never your partner.
I only protected your life.
Relax. You'll have money.
The Americans said they'd make sure
you had everything you need.
- Where am I going?
- Doesn't matter.
Go. And never come back to Colombia.
Don't worry about a thing.
You'll still be a rat, but for the CIA,
instead of the DEA.
Tata?
Tata, can you hear me?
Pablo?
It's me, my love.
Finally, I can speak to you, my love.
I've missed you so much.
Where have you been, Pablo?
I had to do something very important.
But I'm back home, my love.
I'm home.