Tell her what you got.
Male, Caucasian, mid 40s,
appears to have been shot.
- Where?
- In his room.
- Very funny.
- O.K., O.K.
The wound's below the heart.
- Shot once?
- Seems to have been, yes.
First you said
appears to have been shot.
Mr. Turner.
Oh, Dr. Lappe, I'm sure
he'll be here any second now.
Really?
Mr. Turner's late again.
Get back to work.
We can dope it out in five minutes
and get back to work.
- Know whatJoey would say?
- He isn't the only mind in this place.
Come on. Uh, what kind of a slug?
- You're missing the point, Ray.
- What do you mean?
The machine will come back with,
"" Please express in other words.""
What should we feed in?
[Doorbell Rings]
[Buzz]
- Turner,Joseph. No middle initial.
- You're 1 7 minutes late.
Make it 1 2, will you?
I was bucking head winds.
Dr. Lappe, anything in
the early pouch for me?
- Dr. Lappe?
- Yes?
Nothing in response
to your report.
Please have the book I left on your desk
analyzed and on the computer by 4:00.
Yes, sir. Better get the telemias
moved closer to the light.
You're getting a blight
on the leaf.
At ease, Sarge. At ease.
Going to rain today. 1 0:20.
[Ray]
There's got to be more details.
[Harold]
I only read two chapters.
- No other clues?
- Not so far.
- [Janice] What time they find him?
- Early evening.
They never said
what the caliber of the bullet was.
- Apparently .38.
- There it is again-- ""Apparently.""
It made an entry wound characteristic of
a .38. They couldn't recover the slug.
Hey, we're getting somewhere.
You guys figure it out.
I have Far East journals to read.
Was the slug smashed
against the wall?
No. As a matter of fact,
there was no exit wound.
We're not getting anywhere.
Finish the book, Harold.
Hi. What we've got so far is--
Ice.
Instead of lead. Ice!
The murderer pours water
into a .38 caliber mold,
freezes it, and keeps it solid
until the crime.
Then he shoots the guy
with the ice bullet.
Cops show up, there's just
a few drops of water.
- No bullet, no ballistics.
- That's great.
- Hey.
- Yeah?
What is this?
Mmm. Calligraphy's
getting beautiful.
- What is it?
- Ten. That means heaven.
That's it? Nothing else?
Well, it can mean the best.
Tops sometimes. Why?
I'm not sure.
We're going to Sam
and Mae's tonight, right?
- Mm-hmm.
- Why don't you talk to Sam about it?
- About this?
- Mm-hmm.
I did. He says, ""That's interesting,
but it's not my department.""
Which means he doesn't think
there's anything,just like Dr. Lappe.
- And you.
- Well, there's not much.
- A mystery that's been translated?
- A mystery that didn't sell...
has been translated into
a very odd assortment of languages--
Turkish, but not French,
Arabic, but not Russian...
or German... Dutch.
Spanish?
Yes. Yes.
Hey, where'd you get that thing
about the ice? Dashiell Hammett?
Dick Tracy.
Are you sure about this ideogram?
Look at this face.
Could I be wrong about an ideogram?
It's a great face,
but it's never been to China.
- When can I get computer time?
- Dick Tracy?
- He was a very underrated detective.
- There's free time at 2:45.
Morning pickup.
No, no, no, no.
Stay on schedule. I'll get it.
- Four pieces, right?
- Right.
- Hold it. Hold it.
- Five.
- Affirmative. Fiver.
- Where is Mr. Heidegger?
- Called in sick, Dr. Lappe.
- He's probably hung over again.
This is extraordinary.
I was just checking the files...
and came across this carbon copy of an
inquiry he sent to Persian Gulf command.
He did that for me.
It never went through
my office.
I asked him to do some research for me.
I guess he didn't feel it was important.
I wish you people
would go through channels.
[Door Opens]
Uh, what's on your mind?
O.K.
[Buzz]
[Not Audible]
This was in the pouch
from New York Center.
HQ from Langley
said there's nothing...
from any other intelligence source
to support your theory.
-Gentlemen.
-This your idea of working on that book?
I'll have it on the computer
by 4:00.
We have people
to service these machines.
These things are simple.
They just look complicated.
Mr. Turner, I wonder
if you're entirely happy here.
- Within obvious limits, yes, sir.
- Obvious limits?
It bothers me
I can't tell people what I do.
Why is it taking you long
to accept that?
Well, I actually trust
a few people.
That's a problem.
I believe it's your turn
to bring in lunch.
What time is it?
- 1 1 :22.
- The rain's going to stop by 1 1 :30.
You can wait eight minutes.
Ah, yes. Yes.
Mr. Turner?
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Damn it.
It's not a proper exit.
He always goes out that way
when it rains. Saves him a block.
Personnel should enter and exit
the premises by authorized means only.
[Thunder]
Jimmy.
- Hey, Shakespeare, how's it going?
- Terrific.
I'm building up a great collection
of rejection slips.
Yeah, I know the feeling.
I always wanted to be Escoffier.
Maybe it's not too late. Van Gogh
was 30 before he started to paint.
- No kidding?
- There's no mayonnaise on Dr. Lappe's.
On the other hand, Mozart was 3
when he started playing the piano.
- He was composing at 6.
- Fast starter. It's probably better.
I don't know.
Van Gogh never sold a painting
in his lifetime. Mozart died a pauper.
- Where am I, the public library?
- That's a very bright man.
It's educational.
That's why I come in here.
You come in here to get sick
like everybody else.
- Come on.
- No butter on Ray's sandwich.
He get panicky about butter.
[Doorbell Rings]
[Buzz]
[Typewriter]
Give it toJennings in the back.
He'll sign for it.
- [Gunfire]
- Edwinna Rose.
[Clock Chimes]
Mrs. Russell,
was the Kirkus report in this--
Wait, wait, wait!
Aah!
Uhh!
Would you move from the window,
please?
-Pardon?
-Would you move from the window, please?
I won't scream.
I know.
A little breakdown
in the security there?
Well, what--
what are you doing?
What?
Wh--
Come here. Come on.
Harold.
[Horn Honks]
For Christ's sake!
What the hell you doin', Mac?
Do your sleeping
at night, will ya?
[Beeping]
- This is the Major.
- This is Joe Turner.
- Identification.
- What?
- My name's Turner. I work for you.
- Identify yourself.
- I-- I don't--
- What is your designation?
- Uh, Condor. Section 9, department 1 7.
- The section's been hit.
- What level?
- Level of damage.
Everybody. Dr. Lappe,Janice,
Ray, Harold. Harold was in the, uh--
- Are you on a company line?
- No, I'm in a phone booth.
I'm in the street.
You're in violation of secure
communication procedures, Condor.
Listen, you son of a bitch!
I came back with lunch.
The house was murdered.
Everybody is dead.
Has the incident been discovered
by anyone outside the company?
I don't-- I don't know.
I don't think so.
- Are you damaged?
- Damaged? No.
Are you armed?
I don't-- I have Mrs., uh--
I can't remember her code name.
Nightingale.
She kept a gun.
I've got the gun.
- Identify the armament.
- It's a .45 automatic.
Will you bring me in, please?
I'm not a field agent.
I just read books.
- Leave the area.
- All right. Well--
Do I come in to headquarters now?
- Negative. Find a secure location.
- Where?
Avoid any place you're known.
Do not go home.
Surface again in two hours.
And call the Major.
That'll be 1 430, your time.
Wait-- Wait a minute.
All right. 2:30, right?
Walk away from the phone.
Don't hang it up.
- Don't--
- [Click]
This is the panic officer.
Section 9-1 7 may have been hit.
Activate following procedures--
NY 1 27 DC 469er.
Replay on the report upcoming.
Stand by.
[Children Shouting]
Augie One
to New York Center.
New York Center.
Go ahead.
- Who am I talking to?
- Higgins, Deputy Director. Go ahead.
Hit confirmed. Maximum as reported.
Six cold items.
- The quality of work?
- Clean, fast, first-rate.
Did you say six?
Excepting Condor,
there should be seven.
Repeat. Six.
Here's a rundown on those items.
Lappe, Chong, Russell,
Jennings, Martin, Mitchell.
All right, Augie One.
Find seven.
Thank you.
[Door Closes]
Condor.
"" Researcher, tide pool.
Likes to read comic strips.''
[Street Band Plays
Good King Wenceslas]
[Buzz]
Who is it?
Jesus.
Hey, you.
You ring my buzzer?
- It was a mistake, buddy.
- Not you guys.
[Door Closes]
Hey. Hey!
Hey, who are you?
Hey, who the hell are you?
Augie Three here.
We found item seven.
Ralph Heidegger.
He bought it at home.
[Higgins] Button it up, Augie.
I'll send you more janitors.
- [Buzz]
- I need Langley right away.
- Yes, sir.
- [Telephone Rings]
- Garber speaking.
- This is Higgins, Deputy Director.
Let me have department 1 7.
Somebody took out
one of your sections.
- What?
- 9-1 7.
That's New York.
Somebody got mugged maybe.
They were hit.
- They're bookworms.
- They got seven out of eight.
We're on the shuttle
to La Guardia. 30 minutes.
- One of my people is O.K.?
- Condor. You know him?
- No. Can he say what happened?
- He was literally out to lunch.
- What does he say happened?
- He's not in yet.
- First call was a little wild, scared.
- Who's bringing him in?
- Higgins.
- Already booked on the shuttle.
- Wicks, O.I.C. department 1 7.
I want a chopper
fueled for New York now.
- Oh.
- Hello.
- They're waiting for you.
- What?
Your two friends.
They said you'd be home early.
They just got here.
Said you gave them the keys.
Mr. Turner?
[Helicopter]
- [Beeping]
- This is the Major.
- This is Condor.
- Stand by, Condor.
I'm routing you
to New York Center.
Condor on 1 -1 , Mr. Higgins.
- Hello, Condor.
- Who is this?
Deputy Director Higgins,
New York Center.
I'm controlling now, Condor.
Where are you?
How come I need a code name,
and you don't?
Where are you, Turner?
Here.
You all right?
Are you insane?
Everybody's dead.
Take it easy.Just take it easy,
and we'll bring you home.
Here's how we'll do it.
Do you know the Ansonia Hotel?
- Broadway and, uh...7 1 st.
- Broadway and 73rd.
There's an alley
behind the hotel.
One hour from now
at exactly 1 530,
enter that alley from
the 73rd Street side.
Will you be there?
The head of your department just came
from D.C. He'll bring you home.
- I've never met him.
- Don't worry.
He's studying your photos now.
Turner?
Turner!
I don't know you, either.
We'll meet.
He'll be carrying a Wall StreetJournal
in his left hand.
- There were two guys at my house.
- What were you doing there?
- You were told not to go there!
- I was homesick. Who were they?
- They were ours.
- What were they doing in my house?
I'm not going into any alley.
Fuck the Wall StreetJournal!
It's been a long day.
You've been under--
Damn right I've been under.
All right, Turner.
We'll bring along a familiar face,
somebody you know.
Who's left?
Got a friend in statistics
named Sam Barber.
Sam.
You guys are something.
- Will he do?
- Yes, Sam will do.
All right, Turner.
Stay well for 60 minutes,
and you're home.
Can I ask a question?
- Sure.
- What is happening?
I'll talk to you
in 60 minutes.
You've got 5 5.
This is ridiculous.
You're not a field agent.
It's standard procedure.
- To pick up a friend?
- What about you, Mr. Wicks?
- No, thanks.
- Side arm?
- Do you have a .45?
- You bet.
Here, let me
help you with that.
How long have you known Condor?
Who,Joey? I knew him before
he was a bird even.
We went to CCNY.
My wife Mae too.
Was she ever Condor's girl?
Here you go, Mr. Wicks.
Hey, can you tell me anything
about what happened today?
- When?
- This morning.
- Uh, those murders.
- What murders?
Sam?
Here he is.
Joe!
Hey, Sam.
Where-- Where's that other--
What are you doing?
That's him! It's him!
Joe!
[Siren]
[Store P.A. Plays
Silver Bells]
Um, Katherine Hale.
H-A-L-E.
08, 1 1 56,
1 72, 208, 87 5.
Amount, 51 .86.
Where's there enough snow
this early?
- Vermont. I hope.
- What's open now, Sugarbush?
I don't do downhill.
This is for cross-country.
Don't like the lift lines, huh?
- 47 4?
- Thank you.
[Sirens]
Kathy!
Kathy. Where have you been?
Let me give you a hand.
- W-wait a minute.
- Shh. Don't do anything.
Be quiet. Get in the car.
Don't make a sound. Don't be dumb.
Come on. Hurry up.
Get in.
Listen, please don't hurt me.
- Where do you live?
- Brooklyn Heights.
- Alone?
- I live with a friend.
Uh, you live alone.
Let's go.
[Door Buzzes]
Leave the stuff.
Hey, Kathy.
You should have said hello.
- Where is it?
- Here.
""Condor shot us both.""
That was the only statement
he could make
before they took him
into the operating room.
- And the other man, Barber-- he's dead?
- Before he hit the ground.
You should add that it was
a remarkable shot.
A half inch above
his flak jacket.
- I thought this guy--
- Wait a minute.
Was Condor qualified
with a handgun?
""Two years military service--
Signal Corps.
""Telephone lineman,
long lines,
""switchboard maintenance--
six months overseas.
""Separated 9/61 . Worked at Bell Labs
Communication Research.
College on the G.I. bill.''
The question was, Mr. Higgins,
is he qualified with a handgun?
No handgun, sir.
M-1 rifle and carbine.
Evidently, it was sheer luck.
- [Telephone Buzzes]
- Or else--
- Yes?
- Or else what, Mr. Higgins?
This Condor isn't the man
his file says he is.
- Where did he learn evasive moves?
- He reads.
- He r--
- What the hell does that mean?
It means, sir,
that he reads everything.
- But I don't understand.
- Yes. Very good.
- Has operations got anything?
- Absolutely nothing, sir.
- Extraordinary.
- It was very well executed.
Which requires planning,
communications, tracks.
I'm not asking for footprints,
but a blade of grass,
a broken twig--
- Something disturbed.
- Yes, sir.
- Wicks seems to be all we've got.
- Where do we have him?
We don't.
They rushed him to Guvenor Emergency
before we got word.
Maybe we should leak the name of
the hospital, make Condor make his move.
Of course, Len, don't expect
too many mistakes from this man.
He does seem
rather more interesting
than just another
of our reader/researchers.
For example, has he gone
into business for himself?
Was he turned around?
Does someone operate him?
Homosexual?
Broke? Vulnerable?
Could he be
a soldier of fortune?
Did he arrange the hit?
Is that why he's still
in flight?
Still, he...
may be an innocent.
But then, why didn't he
come in gently with Mr. Wicks?
- Tentrex Industries.
- It's a cover. I work for the CIA.
Oh,Jesus.
Your assignment for today
was to go out and kidnap a girl.
Look it up. Look it up.
Tentrex Industries.
Then look up the number
for the CIA.
They're listed,
like my Aunt Gladys?
Under "" U.S. Government Agencies.""
Go on.
So is this what you do?
This photography?
O.K., uh--
It's the same number.
You could have had the card made--
Yes, I could have,
but I didn't.
You really get into it,
don't you?
Sit down!
I told you I had a friend.
1 5 1 /2, 34.
- I dig 1 5 1 /2, 34s. What size are you?
- What are you, a clown?
- I'm scared!
- So am I!
- Why? You've got the gun!
- Yes!
Yeah, and it's not enough.
Listen.
I work for the CIA.
I'm not a spy.
I just read books.
We read everything
that's published in the world,
and we--
we feed the plots--
dirty tricks, codes
into a computer,
and the computer...
checks against actual CIA plans
and operations.
I look for leaks,
new ideas.
We read adventures
and novels and...
journals.
I--
I can--
Who'd invent a job like that?
I-- Listen!
- People are trying to kill me!
- Who?
I don't know,
but there's a reason.
There is a reason!
And I just need...
some safe, quiet time
to pull things together.
- Here.
- That's only fair.
- [Rat-A-Tat-Tat]
[Hiss]
Where's the guy
with the shirts?
He-- He's at a ski place
in the Green Mountains.
We just want to go
cross-country skiing
for a couple of weeks,
away from everything.
- When does the news go on, 6:00?
- 6:00.
40 minutes.
- Come here.
- No, please. Please don't.
Lie down.
Lie down against the wall.
Put this arm behind you,
and keep it there.
Now you listen to me.
I am tired.
I've got to close
my eyes for a while.
I can't think straight.
If you try and move
or climb off the bed...
I'll know it--
I'll feel it.
And I promise you
I'll hurt you.
Couldn't you let me
stay in the other room?
No.
I believe what you told me.
No, you don't.
I don't know if I do.
That includes Condor,
of course.
Yes. I owe you Condor.
- Otherwise--
- Otherwise does not exist.
Will Condor take long?
- Do you want an estimate?
- There is a time factor.
Always with you people.
Condor is an amateur.
He's lost, unpredictable...
perhaps even sentimental.
He could fool a professional.
Not deliberately,
but precisely because he is lost.
Doesn't know what to do...
unlike Wicks...
who has always been
entirely predictable.
The man Condor killed
in the alley.
Some friend of his.
- Close friend?
- I suppose. Why?
- It interests me.
- What was his name?
I don't know.
He was nobody.
[Speaking French]
Right.
What about Wicks?
You want the firm
to question him?
They will, you know.
We don't want that.
Cost you nothing.
I was careless with Condor.
Wicks will be done
for nothing.
- What time is it? What time--
- It's news time.
Get up.
Take a second now
Look up in the sky
Can't you
see the Blue Bird?
That's an Eastern plane
flying through the sky
Shouldn't that
be you there?
Suddenly you stop,
and you're wondering why
You're down there,
and they're up in the sky
You gotta believe
it's for you
dreams come true
You gotta believe
in lookin'up now
Eastern's lookin'up now
Look at us,
look at you
And you gotta believe
Lonely pictures.
- You can fly,you can fly
- So?
You can fly
Do what you want to
You're funny.
You take pictures of...
empty streets and trees
with no leaves on them.
-Fly Eastern
- It's winter.
Not quite winter.
They look like...
November.
Not autumn, not winter.
In-between.
I like them.
Thanks.
Eyewitness News continues
with an update--
- Sit down.
-...of the Ansonia shootings.
The shootings
behind the Hotel Ansonia
remain a complete mystery
at this hour.
The victims' identities
have not yet been revealed.
- Victims?
- Drugs were not involved.
- Did he say victims?
- Nor does it seem to be a robbery.
Lieutenant, can you tell us
about the possible motive?
- Not at present.
- Have you identified the victims?
- Employees of an insurance company.
- What?
Doing a routine inspection
for possible violations.
Did the victims know
their assailants?
- Absolutely not.
- Well, there you have it.
One man dead,
one seriously wounded,
in an alley on
the west side of Manhattan.
The man with the gun
still at large.
Stan Roberts, Eyewitness News,
New York.
Sam.
Jesus Christ.
Victims. What is he s--
What happened in that alley?
- I didn't shoot him.
- You said you shot somebody.
But not Sam!
Nobody in that alley
said anything about the CIA.
But--
But they were there.
Wait a minute.
You're telling me--
They had to have been
to change that story.
What did Higgins say?
He said he wouldn't be there.
He said the section chief
was coming in.
Wait a minute. He's--
Section chief would be
coming in from Washington.
He'd have to reach Sam.
Sam would call me.
[Woman's Voice]
Hello.
Hello?
- I need your car.
- That's called grand theft.
You don't want trouble
with the police.
This guy in Vermont-- What will he do
when you don't show up?
- Probably call. Very soon now.
- Will he show up here?
That gun gives you
the right to rough me up.
- It doesn't give you the right--
- Rough you up?
- Yes! You're in my house!
- Have I-- Have I raped you?
The night is young.
You don't believe anything
I've said.
I believe
you're in trouble...
danger...
but I don't know what kind,
and I'm not sure
how much of it is made up.
Real, but, uh...
Doesn't make any difference--
doesn't matter.
- Wait a minute. Will you--
- Forget it.
I'm trying to understand!
Aah!
Ow! What are you doing?
Let me go!
Ow! You're hurting me.
Wait a minute. You--
Oh! You bully!
Don't tie me up!
Come on, please!
This is... unfair!
I know.
[Doorbell Buzzes]
Oh.
Hi,Joey.
You're early. Come on in.
Hey, is Janice working late?
So is Sam.
[It Came Upon
A Midnight Clear Plays]
Hey, pour one for me,
too, will you,Joey?
It's their own fault
if we're zonked when they get here.
Hey, I've got it.
We'll give them an hour.
If they're not here,
it's you and me,
just like old times.
Joey.
What is it?
Hey, what is it,Joey?
What? What's wrong?
Mae, how do you know
Sam's working late?
What do you think he's doing?
- When did he call?
- I don't know. 2:00 or 2:30.
What did he say? Exactly.
He didn't exactly.
He had the center call.
- Who at the center?
- I didn't recognize his voice.
It wasn't that lady
that usually--
[Telephone Rings]
[Ring]
- Hello.
- [Click]
What is it?
- Third damn time tonight.
- Third time?
- Some burglar casing the joint.
- I want you to get out of here.
- I can't,Joey. I'm cooking.
- Do what I tell you.
- What about dinner?
- Go to Bill and Eileen's.
-Joey, what's going on?
- Please.
-Joey, you--
- Don't argue. Move! Move!
-Joey--
- Go upstairs and stay there.
Do what I'm telling you.
I'll call you. And stay there.
-Joey--
- I'll call you.
- Do what I tell you.
- What about Sam?
Yours?
No.
Happy birthday
to Grandpa
You're always
pushing the buttons.
Would you stop it, please?
Fifth floor.
Uh, ladies' underwear.
Kids.
Probably the same everywhere.
[Door Opens]
[Door Closes]
This is the second floor.
I do it all the time.
- After you.
- No. Go ahead.
All right.
Anybody here good
with a coat hanger?
- What?
- I locked my keys in my car.
- I'll give you money.
- How much?
You can't tell me
you've never busted into a car.
- So how much?
- 5 bucks.
5 bucks?
Can you give me a break?
- Do you mind?
- All right. 5 bucks. 5 bucks.
I'll be right back.
Come on, man.
Merde.
- The money.
- Wait a minute.
Gimme the money.
- Hey! Hey.
- Hey!
[Ring]
- [Ring]
- Ow.
I want you to answer
the phone.
I'm not going to
answer the--
Ow! I'm not answering any phone!
Answer it. Answer it.
You answer the phone! Tell him
what a brave son of a bitch you are.
Ow.
I want you to be
casual and nice.
[Ring]
- H-Hello?
- Where the hell are you?
- Ben?
- Who do you think it is?
-Ben.
-You were supposed to be up here by now.
- I know.
- You haven't even left yet.
I was held up.
That's no excuse.
Come on, what's going on?
Doesn't this trip
matter to you?
- It matters.
- Yeah, I'm sure.
No, it does.
This has happened
over and over again.
- Last minute, some excuse.
- No, this is different.
So, what?
- The car--
- What about it?
- Bro-- Broke down.
- What? What? What broke down?
- The g-generator went.
- Oh, Christ, the generator.
- That's going to take forever.
- Maybe not.
I-- I tried to call you
before, but--
The generator--
It's going to take too long.
Why don't you just--
forget about the car.
Take the bus up
first thing tomorrow.
I'll try.
Try?
What's-- What the hell
is going on?
Are you O.K.?
What-- What's...
No, I'm O.K. I'm fine.
You don't sound so fine.
I-- I wish you
would understand.
I do. I do, I do. It's just--
Goddamn it,
I'm just disappointed, that's all.
I really, uh--
I really wanted to be
with you here,
tonight, babe, you know?
I know.
- We'll have time.
- Yeah.
Look, get--
get the very first bus out
in the morning, O.K.?
All right.
- Good night, sweetheart.
- Good night.
[Click]
Listen, I'll be going...
in the morning.
Where?
Was it all right?
All right?
Outside-- Was it safe?
Wherever you went.
Oh.
I'm not sure.
Oh, God.
I wish I knew more.
About you.
About yesterday. Today.
I don't remember yesterday.
Today it rained.
Why did you tie me up
like that?
I mean, you thought
I'd call the police.
I wouldn't have.
Why?
Well, sometimes...
I take a picture
that isn't like me,
but I took it,
so it is like me.
It has to be.
I put those pictures away.
I'd like to see
those pictures.
We don't know
each other that well.
Do you know anybody that well?
I don't think I want
to know you very well.
I don't think you're
going to live much longer.
Well, I may...
surprise you.
Anyway, you're not
telling the truth.
What do you mean?
You'd rather be with somebody
who's not going to live much longer,
at least somebody
who would be on his way.
- I'm not--
- You take pictures.
Beautiful pictures,
but of empty streets
and trees with no leaves--
November.
Why haven't you asked me
to untie your hands?
H-How much do you want...
I just...
want to stop it.
For a few hours.
For the rest of the night.
And then I'll go.
Joe!
What was his name?
What is it Higgins said?
Was it--
The head of your department just came
from D.C. He'll bring you home.
I've never met him.
Anything in the early pouch?
Headquarters at Langley
says there's nothing...
from any other intelligence source
to support your theory.
Headquarters at Langley
says there's nothing...
from any other intelligence source
to support your theory.
Wicks.
- You didn't sleep well.
- You didn't?
No,you didn't.
You're up early.
Oh, I had--
I had some thoughts.
I've got a plan.
I don't know if it'll
work or not, but...
I'll need your help.
Have I ever denied you
anything?
Hey.
Well, when things
quiet down...
you're really a very sweet man
to be with.
You had bad dreams.
Talked in your sleep.
What did I say?
Who's Janice?
Well, was she a volunteer
or a draftee like me?
She was...
a friend.
She's dead.
Do I have permission
to take a shower?
You don't have to help,
you know.
No, I'll help. You can always
depend on the old spyfucker.
- O.K.
- I'm sorry.
- No.
- No, I didn't mean--
I didn't mean to say that.
I'm really sorry.
I'd like to help you.
[Heart Monitor Beeping]
[P.A. System]
...the Lord is come
Let earth receive her king
Let every heart
Prepare Him room
And heaven and nature sing
And heaven and heaven and...
[Monitor Flatlines]
- 1 8. Isn't that--
- Yes.
A.I.D. in I.C.U., 1 0-9-8.
[Doorbell Rings]
Yeah?
Insured package
for Katherine Hale.
Uh, could you leave it
out on the stoop?
Somebody's got to
sign for it.
Well, she's in--
She's not here.
It's O.K.
You can sign.
- Yeah?
- Her name on top. Yours on the bottom.
All right. Oh, wonderful.
Government pens.
Look, I don't have another pen.
I'll get one.
[Kathy]
Aah!
Don't-- Don't--
No, no. No.
Now listen.
You're O.K. You're O.K.
Now listen to me.
You're O.K.
Can you get dressed?
Please, hurry.
- [Ring]
- Stella Boutique.
Ex-Extension 1 -8-9-1 ,
please.
Pardon me?
Is--Is this 662-37 99?
- Yes. Who's this?
- There's no extension 1 891 ?
Are you kidding? We're lucky
if we have phone service at all.
Sorry.
- [Ring]
- Operator.
Operator, what's the area code
for Washington? D.C.
That's 2-0-2.
Kathy.
6-3-1 -1 .
CIA? Langley?
- Extension 1 891 .
- [Ring]
1 891 .
Let me speak to Mr. Wicks.
Um, he's not here just now.
May I ask who's calling,
please?
How do you feel?
You O.K.?
What did you do
to those people?
What people?
I don't know who they are.
I file a report.
A guy in Washington reads it.
He's supposed to--
He's my section chief.
He comes to New York
to shoot me.
- Did you know him?
- No.
Did you know the mailman?
No, but the guy
in Washington did.
- You won't know the next one.
- I'm not waiting for the next one.
- Has he gone double or dirty?
- I don't know, sir.
- You think he's still in New York City?
- I wouldn't be.
Question-- Is there
an intelligence network...
undetected by CIA linking...
certain Arabic-speaking countries
with Dutch and Spanish-speaking?
We're already visible.
Let's not become conspicuous.
If company agents aren't enough,
use freelance.
Use whatever it requires,
but end it.
O.K.
Let's get it
over with, O.K.?
Kathy.
Thanks.
[Horn Honks]
Applications here.
O.K.
See. Mr. Addison. Turn right.
First door on your left.
Mr. Marcus.
- Mr. Addison?
- No.
He's in clearance.
Passed it. It's on your left.
Oh. Sorry.
Uh, thank you.
Yep. I didn't get the job.
Looks good,
but, um, I have this friend,
and he asked me to
give you a message.
Quote--
"" Dear Mr. Higgins,
""This will introduce
a friend of mine, Sparrow Hawk.
"" Please accompany her
""to the Nassau Street exit
of this place.
Now.''
Personally, I'd do it,
because he has this huge gun,
and he's looking
at us right now.
I'll save this for you.
Shall we?
To your left, please.
O.K., sit up. Sit up!
All the way up.
Back up against the panel.
Take it easy.
I'm not armed.
They could be DF-ing us if you have
a transmitter hidden in your clothes?
- What's this?
- DF, huh? You do read everything.
Somebody or something
is rotten in the company.
You never complained
till yesterday.
You didn't start killing my friends
- Who's she?
- Who hit the Lit Society?
We had a big meeting about that.
Your name came up.
Five Continents Imports.
Ring a bell?
- Where'd you get that?
- The mailman.
- Mailman?
- The one you sent.
-With the uniform, pouch, automatic gun.
-We never use mailmen.
Are you familiar with a tall gentleman,
6'4"", blond hair,
strong like a farmer, not American,
accent, country near Germany,
maybe Alsace-Lorraine?
[Telephone Rings]
[Ring]
- Yes?
- Was the letter delivered?
The return receipt
has not arrived.
You should have
delivered it yourself.
A more complicated package
had to be handled,
but I might have underestimated
this one.
I was told you never make
that kind of mistake.
What will you do?
- Wait.
- For what?
People who move
leave word of change of address.
- I want to see that report.
- Do you know him?
- Professionally, yes.
- Professionally, he kills people.
Yes. Yes.
- He works for the company?
- He did once.
- He's a contract agent.
- Contract agent.
Freelance.
Where did you see him?
- Uh-uh.
- It would help if I knew.
- Who would it help? Who'd hire him now?
- Anybody.
Terrific answer.
- I wouldn't accept it, either.
- What's his name?
- When I knew him,Joubert.
- Come on, Higgins.
Who'd hire him? You don't look up
Joubert in the yellow pages.
That's right. It'd have to be
somebody in the community.
- Community?
- Intelligence field.
Community!Jesus, you guys are kind
to yourselves. Community.
I want to see
that report, Turner.
That report was sent to headquarters
and disappeared.
- Who read it?
- You mean besides Wicks?
You tell me.
I pick up traces of what I think's
an intelligence network
the company doesn't know about,
and I report it.
Now, why is that going
to make anybody mad?
Unless it was
the company's network
and you didn't want it blown,
even to your own guys.
Unless somebody is lying,
Higgins.
Come on.
Why is everybody so shy?
I'm not shy.
I don't know.
That's what worries me.
- I don't know.
- Ask Wicks.
Wicks died.
Someone yanked him off the life
support system at Guvenor Hospital.
Get me in, Higgins.
What good would that do if you're right,
and they are inside?
What good would it do
to bring you in?
What am I supposed to do?
I'm sorry.
You're sorry?
You're sorry.
Oh, I get it.
I get it.
You expect me to draw fire,
like one of those
penny arcade bears
that parades back and forth,
waiting for somebody,
somebody good,
to take another shot.
You'll pick him up
before he does it, or just after?
I'll try and find out
what's going on.
- Nice talking to you, Higgins.
- Now wait a minute.
- Have a nice day.
- Where will I find you?
I'll find you.
- Do you trust him?
- Trust.
Does he trust you?
He's in the suspicion business.
He can't trust anybody.
- How could anybody fool them?
- Maybe nobody did.
- Then--
- Maybe there's another CIA...
inside the CIA.
Hey, Sal.
Hey, the lights went off.
Come on over here.
The generator went off.
- It's a hotel room.
- What hotel?
There's no tag.
It's room 81 9, city of New York.
There's a code number
cut in the edge.
- You in the trade?
- I read about it in a story.
- Was the story about locksmiths?
- It's the lock manufacturer's code.
He can give you
the hotel name.
I don't want to read about you
in the paper.
Will you make the call?
[Ring]
Yes?
I'm doing a survey.
Do you believe the Condor's
really an endangered species?
- [Operator] Your room number, please.
- 81 9.
[Telephone Rings]
[Ring, Ring]
[Man]
Hello?
- Yes. I just had an interesting call.
- Who is this?
In reference to
an all-but-extinct bird-- the Condor.
- Have you had such a call?
- You're a fool to call me.
- You had no such call?
- No.
Must have been
the Audubon Society.
I assume they're still
located in New York.
[Ring]
Langley Computer.
State your program at the tone.
- [Beep]
- G.
Carriage return.
T-R-S. Tone.
Symbol for number.
Computer is ready.
[Beeping]
That number is
202-227-0098.
[Ring]
- CNA, Mrs. Coleman speaking.
- This is Harold Thomas, Mrs. Coleman.
Customer service,
requesting a CNA...
on 202-227-0098.
One moment, please.
That would be
a Mr. Leonard Atwood.
365 Mackenzie Place.
Chevy Chase, Maryland.
All right.
Cross-check this tape
against Wicks and hold any intersects.
Hat size.
Lucifer.
All right, run Lucifer.
Coming up.
I'll be damned.
[Beeping]
- This is the Major.
- Condor.
Find me Higgins.
Routing you, Condor.
Stand by.
Hello, Condor.
- The Holiday Inn, 57 th Street.
- Is that where you are now?
Room 81 9. You'll find
the Alsatian gentleman we spoke of.
Where are you, Condor?
Where are you?
Shh. Quiet down.
Hey, Higgins?
Yeah, I'm right here.
Who is Leonard Atwood?
Where are you, Higgins?
Ain't we pals anymore?
[Dial Tone]
- Something?
- Major?
- Got him.
- Let me see that.
What's he doing in Brooklyn?
Condor.
- We can get a unit--
- Wait.
- What's going on, Major?
- Son of bitch wired together 50 phones.
What?
Everybody in Brooklyn's
talking to each other.
I didn't know you smoked.
I quit three years ago.
- You're pale.
- It's the light in here.
What are you
going to do there?
- See a guy.
- More secrets.
Like those pictures you hide.
Yes.
Someday, I--
I'd like to show them to you...
if you live through this.
You could drive me
to Washington.
No, I couldn't.
You've-- You've a lot
of very fine qualities.
- But--
- What fine qualities?
You have good eyes.
Not kind, but...
they don't lie,
and they don't look away much,
and they don't miss anything.
I could use eyes like that.
But you're overdue in Vermont.
Is he a tough guy?
He's pretty tough.
What will he do?
U-Understand, probably.
Boy, that is tough.
Last call, train six.
Newark connects to Penn Central
to Baltimore, Washington, D.C.
All aboard.
- Kathy, I need time.
- Hmm?
Eight hours or so,
that's all.
Till noon,
to do what I have to do.
Do you understand
what I'm saying?
Are you going
right to Vermont?
Yes.
What I mean is don't
call anyone.
Don't stop, please.
Don't tell anyone about--
- Of course.
-Jesus.
Jesus.
I-- I didn't--
All aboard!
Hey.
You take care of yourself.
I'll do my best.
Do your best.
Why aren't you further along,
Mr. Higgins?
You mean with the company?
You seem perfect for it.
Are you perfect for it,
Mr. Higgins?
I've tried to be, sir.
You were recruited
out of school?
No, sir. Company interviewed
a few of us in Korea.
You served with
Colonel Donovan
in the O.S.S.,
didn't you, sir?
I sailed the Adriatic
with a movie star at the helm.
It doesn't seem like
much of a war now, but it was.
I go even further back
than that.
1 0 years after the Great War,
as we used to call it,
before we knew enough
to number them.
Do you miss that kind
of action, sir?
No.
I miss that kind of clarity.
[Intercom Buzzes]
Yes?
Thank you.
He's being held
at New York Center.
Mr. Higgins, you do understand
the company's position?
There's nothing in the way
of your doing this, is there?
And I want ya
right where I've got you
And I've got ya
right where I need you, baby
And I need you
right where I've got you
And I've got you
right where I want you, baby
And I want you
right where I've got you
And I've got you
right where I need you, baby
And I need you
right where I've got you
Yeah
Ow!
-Now you're funky...
- What is this?
What's going on?
[Music Stops]
Who are you?
What are you doing here?
I'm Condor.
Sit down.
What do you do for a living?
Don't be ridiculous.
What do you do...
exactly?
Deputy Director of Operations.
- What section?
- Middle East.
What are you working on?
What are you doing?
What's the secret worth murdering
everybody at the A.L.H.S. house?
- There's no secret.
- Wicks showed you my report.
What report? Yes.
It was your network I turned up.
Doing what?
What does operations care
about a bunch of goddamn books?
A book in Dutch.
A book out of Venezuela.
- Mystery stories in Arabic.
- Wait.
What the hell
is so important about--
Oil fields.
Oil.
That's it, isn't it?
This whole damn thing
was about oil.
Wasn't it? Wasn't it?
Yes, it was.
Don't turn for a moment.
Put your thumb in front
of the hammer.
Release it slowly.
Set down the gun
on the desk.
And don't move.
Back up.
You were quite good,
Condor, until this.
This move was predictable.
Hey!
What? What?
Did you touch anything
except the chair?
You're working for
the company again.
Yes.
I am.
Jesus. They took you back.
Just for this. For Atwood.
How-- Wha--
He's with the company. Why?
I don't interest myself in why.
I think more often
in terms of when,
sometimes where,
always how much.
I suspect he was about to become
an embarrassment.
As you are.
- So you're not finished.
- Pardon?
Oh, no. I have no arrangement
with the company concerning you.
They didn't know you'd be here.
I knew you'd be here.
But didn't you send
the mailman?
That was a business arrangement
with Atwood,
but you see.
Come on.
Come.
Tell me about the girl.
What about the girl?
She was chosen... how?
By-- By age?
Her car? Appearance?
At random. Chance.
Really.
Can I drop you?
[Sigh]
I'd like to go back
to New York.
You have not
much future there.
It will happen this way.
You may be walking.
Maybe the first sunny day
of the spring,
and a car will slow
beside you,
and the door will open,
and someone you know,
maybe even trust,
will get out of the car.
And he will smile,
a becoming smile.
But he will leave open
the door of the car
and offer to give you a lift.
You seem to understand
it all so well.
What would you suggest?
Personally, I prefer Europe.
- Europe?
- Yes.
Well, the fact is,
what I do is not
a bad occupation.
Someone is always
willing to pay.
I would find it...
tiring.
Oh, no. It's quite restful.
It's almost peaceful.
No need to believe
in either side or any side.
There is no cause.
There's only yourself.
The belief is in
your own precision.
I was born in the United States,
Joubert.
I miss it when
I'm away too long.
A pity.
I don't think so.
Is it any trouble to drop me
at the Union Station?
Oh, no.
It would be my pleasure.
For that day.
[Carolers]
Remember Christ, our Savior
Was born on Christmas day
To save us all
from satan's power
When we're gone astray
Oh, tidings of comfort and joy
Comfort and joy,
Higgins!
Oh, tidings of comfort and joy
Comfort and joy
Why'd you call so late?
We were worried about you.
Likewise. The car for me?
It's all right. It's safe.
You'll have a few hours of debriefing.
- Hey, Higgins?
- Yeah?
Let's say,
for the purposes of argument,
I had a .45
in one of my pockets
and I wanted you
to walk with me.
You'd do it, right?
Which way?
West. And slowly.
Stay in front of me
about three or four steps.
Where we going?
Wave them on ahead.
Do we have plans to invade
the Middle East?
- Are you crazy?
- Am I?
- Look, Turner--
- Do we have plans?
No. Absolutely not.
We have games. That's all.
We play games-- What if?
How many men?
What would it take?
Is there a cheaper way
to destabilize a regime?
- That's what we're paid to do.
- Walk on.
Go on.
So Atwood just took the games
too seriously.
He was really going to do it,
wasn't he? A renegade operation.
Atwood knew 541 2 would
never authorize it,
not with the heat
on the company.
What if there hadn't
been any heat?
Suppose I hadn't stumbled
on their plan?
Different ballgame.
Fact is, there was nothing wrong
with the plan.
The plan was all right.
The plan would've worked.
Boy, what is it
with you people?
You think not getting caught in a lie
is the same thing as telling the truth?
No. It's simple economics.
Today it's oil, right?
In 1 0 or 1 5 years-- food, plutonium,
and maybe even sooner.
What do you think the people
are going to want us to do then?
Ask them.
Now now. Then. Ask them
when they're running out.
Ask them when there's no heat
and they're cold.
Ask them when
their engines stop.
Ask them when people who have never
known hunger start going hungry.
Want to know something?
They won't want us to ask them.
They'll want us
to get it for them.
Boy,
have you found a home.
There were seven people
killed, Higgins.
- The company didn't order it.
- Atwood did.
Atwood did.
And who the hell is Atwood?
He's you.
He's all you guys.
Seven people killed,
and you play fucking games!
Right.
And the other side does, too.
That's why we can't let you
stay outside.
Well, go on home, Higgins.
Go on. They've got it.
- What?
- You know where we are.
Just look around. They've got it.
That's where they ship from.
They've got all of it.
What? What did you do?
I told them a story.
You play games,
Oh, you--
You poor, dumb
son of a bitch.
You've done more damage
than you know.
I hope so.
You're about to be
a very lonely man.
It didn't have
to end this way.
Of course it did.
Hey, Turner.
How do you know
they'll print it?
You can take a walk,
but how far if they
don't print it?
They'll print it.
How do you know?
Remember Christ, our Savior
Was born on Christmas day
To save us all
from satan's power
When we're gone astray
Ohh