You may go,
I will go by myself
Take out the car
Take out the car quickly
Will we go to hotel?
We will go to hotel but after this road
Put some load on accelerator
Come outside quickly
I will be at your house in 5 mins
Chatur called me
The silencer?
He is saying that Racho is coming
What are you saying?
He is saying that if you wanna meet rancho
then come at campus at 8 PM
come outside quickly
Ok
Suri I will be back in few minutes
i have found my friend
i will talk to you when i come back
wear your pant
we will go to hotel
but after Imperial college
i have forget to wear socks
you are talking about socks,
look you have also forget pant
you go to hotel but also drop
my brother to hotel
you have send the car to run way
where is Rancho?
Where is Rancho?
But look at this
not to my wife
look but the bunglow
behind her
why are you showing this to us?
You forget?
What is this?
Lets bet
we will come back after 10 years
right here
do you have guts?
Do you remember anything?
He left his pant
and you think he will come back
for your bet?
I know
then why you call us?
To meet Rancho
see where is Rancho now
so you know where is Rancho?
We have heard that life is race
i born at 5:15 AM
come
take the photo
dont worry when he will live here
for few days he will forget god
he will put nude girls photos
on the wall
then he will say give me this girl
Rs 2 per bag
keep the change
i also wanna give you tip
tonight wear underwear without hole
he is a he man
everybody was saluting
when we saw Rancho first time
whats your name?
Remove your pant
you wont understand?
Dont wear wet pant
what you said?
Then talk to him slowly
remove your clothes
if you wont come outside then
i will pee on your door whole semester
we have read it
but he applied it
everybody call him virus
virus is coming
with eggs
he call first stair downstairs
be quick
he daily take power nap
for 7.5 minutes
and listen to opera
he do all unprotected work
in this 7.5 minutes
what is this?
This is nest
whom?
A bird
bird never lie her egg in her nest
when her children grom up they
throw that nest
every year 4 lacs applications
come to ICA
but only 200 persons selected
my daughter also applied for 3 years
in space neither fountain nor
ink pen can be used
after spending million of dollars
scientists invented a pen
that can be used on any temperature
when you find extra ordinary student
like you
pass this to him
write on board
if fountain pen cant be used in space then
why they did not use pencil?
They could save million of dollars
whole day he tease teachers
if we live with him then we will
be in trouble
who will pay the fees?
Your father?
Just wear the uniform and go to school
here lots of population,
nobody will recognize you
and if we get caught then?
Change the uniform,
change the school
there was something special in him
why are you laughing?
I'am very happy to be in engineering college
no need to be happy
tell me the machine definition
anything that can make man's
work easy
we are stuck in machines
from pen to pant's zip
I'm telling you the definition
you will also write this exams
but i also said the same
if you like simple language then
go to arts and commerce college
you know more than book?
If you wanna pass then write from the book
get out
i forget something
what?
Can i take my books?
You cant this is simple language?
I told something in simple language
but you didn't understand
professors most of time
kept him outside class
whenever professors tell him to go outside
then he go to another class
he was different from us
we daily fight for bathroom
wherever he find water,
he take bath there
he loves machines
he always keepy screw driver
in his pocket
wherever he find machine he open it
some work and some dont work
i wanna know convocation dates
my dad wanna make reservation
call your dad
director sir wanna talk to you
this year your son wont be graduate
its my recommodation that
dont do reservation
please look at it
submit it
we will concentrate on it
did you leave eating for 2 weeks?
Did you leave bathing for 2 weeks?
Then why studies?
Please have a look
sunday afternoon my son died
and monday i was giving lecture
wireless camera on helicopter
i can be used as a security
dont tell it to Joy
we will give him surprise
we will fly it outside his window
you scare too much
there was a security guard in our village
he say at night
ALL IZ WELL
and we sleep comfortable
one night there was a robbery in our village
then we found that he was blind
on that day i knew one thing,
our heart is very coward
always keep him fool.
No matter what problem comes
no but you can have the power to
tolerate it
neither police knows,
nor Joy's father
everybody is thinking its a suicide
they are thinking he is died because
of tension
these engineers are very smart
its not a suicide.
Its a murder
you are blaming me for
Joy's suicide
I'm not blaming you
i'm talking about system
i have some statistics
India is on number 1 is suicide
in every 1.5 hour a student
commit a suicide
they die in suicide more
than disease
i'm running this college since 32 years
I bring this college to number one
they only talk about marks
aboutjobs in US
today he will teach us engineering
you have 30 seconds
you have to tell the meaning of
words written on board
you can also use the book
those who find the answers raise
his hand up
nobody found the answer?
Now rewind 1 minute of your life
and think
did anyone think?
Today we will learn something new
we will enjoy
if you win than what will you get?
Your knowledge will increase?
Only pressure will increase
its a college,
not a pressure cooker
these 2 are my friends names
i was just telling you that how
to teach
i wanna tell you that your son
are on wrong path
come inside
look that
we could only afford one A/C
i never buy a car
i still ride bike
did farhan took this photo?
He was in a mood to do photography
what was your percentage at that time?
You think its a joke?
I'm just saying that why are you making him
engineer? Make him wild life photographer
i beg you
dont ruin my son's future
lets eat
when next time you come,
eat with us
father did not give us food,
then we went to Raju's house
everything was old
small room with parallised father,
sick mother and single
his father was postman
Kamo is 28 years old.
People ask for Maruti 800 in marriage
if you dont study then how
will we marry her
if these letters come from college
then how will we eat?
You wanna eat cheese?
Leave it
then we decided leave his mother
and concentrate on food
not like your father
lets go somewhere to eat food
money is not necessary to eat food
bring 3 large vodka
we will be in trouble
bring all things in 2 plates
what people will say?
You will beat me with glass then my
head will be busted open
why i beat you?
I'm gonna give you free advice
what?
Dont marry that guy
he will tell you all his life the price
of all his things
do you wanna know what is the
cost of his shoes?
I wont ask him,
he will tell by himself
run away
these are my students
what they are doing here?
My dad wont allow me to break
the engagement
you explain very well
please explain to my dad too
where is your dad?
Run away
its a free advice
what are you doing here?
We will give envelope to bride
how many daughters you have?
I think you are from groom's side
we are from science
he explain very well
give the demo
there is a often electricity break down
in delhi
it creates a probelm in marriage
so i thaught that i will make inverter
that will make power from car batteries
design is ready
i can make inverter
i wanna meet you all in office tomorrow
what was your per plate cost?
We will pay in installments
we wont do it again
i wont marry
this is Rancho's father monthly income
2.5 crore
if we remove one or two zero than
it wont effect on him
and if you remove one more zero
this is your father's monthly income farhan
and if we remove one more zero than
its your family income Raju
change your room
if you live with Rancho you
wont be pass
please try to understand virus
is playing game with us
i want marks and he can give me marks
I'm making line because i
wanna support my family
mother's half salary spend in father's salary
my sister is not getting married
people want Maruti 800 in marriage
my mother haven't bought a single
saree in last 5 years
dont make fun of my mother
we will study but not only to
clear in exams
we will be top
Raju changed his train box
everybody calls him silencer
to make his mind sharp,
he eat some digestive tablets
then he farts
study hard or dont allow others to study
we have did many miracles here
to impress virus he write his speech
from librarian in pure english
ok i call him
your phone
director sir called you
now
you give this to chatur I'm coming
I'm talking from Lajpat nagar police station
listen to my instructions carefully
or you will die when you come out
from college gate
while he was talking,
Rancho changed some words from his speech
like miracle become rape
did you call me sir?
Who are you?
Ok hold down commssioner is
on the line
where was I?
When you come out from gate,
you will see a signal
when that signal become red then
all cars will be stop
these days heavy flow of traffic is on
the road
i told you that he remember you
if you study then you can save your life
for 4 years
and after 40 years you will get raped
what i did wrong with you?
Sorry dont take it personally
i will take it personally
enjoy the science
i'm not here to enjoy
so you wanna rape?
One day i will be successful with
my ethics
then i will laugh and you will cry
dont run after success
be a good engineer so that success runs after you
you catch your train,
i catch my train
we will come here after 10 years
then we will see who is more
successful
what happenned to him?
What he is writing?
Dont forget this date
then used to it
you change the speech?
Dont lie to me
what is your problem with my dad?
I dont have any problem,
i'm making inverter on his name
look at this
because he is running factory
there donkeys are manufactured
look there is your donkey
so what I tell him?
He can see profit in you thats why
he is with you
what the hell you think of yourself?
What do you mean Suhaas is not
interested in me?
She lost the watch
it costs 4 lacs
mine is only Rs 250 and it
shows the same time
you called him donkey on his face
its very noise here, she called me
thank you and i heard get lost
i said get lost
do you know you never love him?
Means when he comes infront of you do
you ever feel wind is blowing
moon has increased its size
it also happens in real life
if you love with normal man than
it will happen. Not with donkeys
ok I'm coming
you are medical student?
I need your help
i called ambulance 2 hours before
our country is very strange,
they give guarantee to reach in 30 minutes
you bring papa on scooter?
We have lots of exams but we have
only one father
please forgive me
I was scared
go and meet father and dont cry
scooter saved life today
how much it is?
Now you can wear your mother's watch anytime
your mother was very beautiful?
Yes
how do you know?
Have you seen your father?
Its 8:30 AM.
You have the exams at 9 AM
how you we leave you alone?
I'm here
doctors are here
he saw us like we asked him to give his
both kidneys
we kept writing and he was busy
in arranging papers according to role numbers
do you know who are us?
Do you know our name or role numbers?
What's your role number?
Where is that paper?
Today results was about to announce
everybody was praying with god
and your?
Rancho is not here
heartbeat was stop
because of not we came last
its because our friend was failed
he came second
who came first?
Move
on that day we know about human
behaviour
we friend fail we feel bad and when friend comes
first we will feel more bad
but 2 persons were more upset than us
do you have any problem?
Do you have any other way?
Yes i have
result cant be announce on notice board
why we tell weakness of someone
to all peoples?
I did not mean that
like i come first I'm sitting infront of you
my friends came last and they
are sitting at back
may be any company will give job to
peoples
they will get the job
he is responsible for global warming
you wait here i will buy a pant
where is this address?
If he is literate will he be selling peas?
Yes he lives there
I'm Ranchoredas
i dont know what is happenning?
Iook my secretary come here before
i checked telephone directory
how his face is changed?
Is he do plastic surgery?
You kept saying that bring me
to Haridwar
and i was waiting for highway tender to open
what are you saying?
Your degree is there
how dare you enter my properyt without
my permission?
I checked everything
this degree belongs to our friend
from where you get this?
I will kill you,
nobody will know this
I'm going to Haridwar with my
father's ashes
if you say then i will also bring your bones
i will count till 3
dont try to scare us.
Shoot us
raju flush it
we will go to hell but we will
bring your father with us
we bring the empty bowl,
its empty
we will empty it
I'm ranchoredas
he was my farmer's son
everybody called him Chote
he manages my house
he love to study
he wear my old uniform and comes
in school
whichever class he likes,
he sit in that class
i took benifits of him
he do my homework and exam papers
we got caught
papa was a rich man thats why Master Ji
told this first to papa
everybody respects me
he needs study and i
want only degree
let it happen as its going
make this boy engineer
i went to London for 4 years,
and he was studying in ICA under my name
after getting degree he will never
meet anyone from IC
i wont meet but one day 2 idiots
will come to meet me
then what will you do?
He really miss you both
i give you address
go and meet him
and dont tell my secret to anyone
which secret?
Where are we going?
To meet Rancho?
What we are doing?
We only go to college to
get degree
but he only came for study in college
after 2 month 26 companies will
come here to offer you jobs
it means you will have jobs
before your final exams
suppose if a student gets a job
and if he fail in finance for 2 marks
then he will getjob?
Is there anybody else who
is thinking the same question?
I will pray you whole life but
just take virus from this world
fry him in hot oil
shut up
every year you take photo with virus
i think we will move outside
from photo this year
do you know whats your passion?
What are you doing?
This is your passion
he write this letter 5 years before
but he never post that letter
leave engineering and become wild
life photographer
only do that work in which you
have talent
you love animals and going
to marry with machines
my girlfriend and wife both are engineers
because you are coward
but you do both things
you scare and also die
he loves Piya but scare to tell her
if you have dare then tell her
where are you joining the connections?
What will he say?
I dont scare
you both go inside, if anybody comes
then i will give you wireless aleart
dont make noise
listen to me for 2 minutes
you daily comes in my dreams
wearing bride's dress
and comes near to me to kiss me
nose comes between us and then
i wake up
nose never comes in between stupid
he took 4 years to say this
kiss him and tell him nose never comes
in between us
who is he?
Who are you?
But you only become what your heart says
whole night studying
thats why its looking like this
what you were studying?
Will you type a letter for me?
He is alive because he wanna
see me engineer
you had to think this before
ok remove your name from the letter,
and write Rancho's name
be my witness,
i wont throw out you from college
please dont cry infront of him
talk to him
make him happy
there is a good news for you,
your papa is fine now
new medicine worked
farhan wanna talk to you
maa has bought a new saree
tell me how I'm looking?
Her marriage is fixed
you know him very well
he loves animals alot
our farhan
farhan will marry your sister
so you are coming with me?
And i will go forjob interview
why i go to house?
You had promise for one thing
i dont think after reading it you
will go for interview
what is this?
Its a letter
he wanna make you his assisstant
or after 50 years you will be in hospital
and you will think that i could try it
why you buy so much expensive?
I dont wanna be a engineer
i dropped from the 3rd floor of that building
i did pee on director's office door
while i was drunk
Rancho is still playing with your
brain
I dont understand engineering
i will learn alot
people will laugh on you
Kapoor was saying that you are lucky
your son study in ICA
Kapoor never put AC in my room
it was you who did all this
it matters what you think?
I even dont know his first name
have you seen any film?
No i wont commit a suicide
he forced me to put your and mother photo
i will earn less money
i will have small house and car
i will do anything for you by true heart
i have always obeyed you
how much your professional camera costs?
Will it come by selling laptop?
If you want more money than ask from me
go enjoy your life
is there any special reason?
I was a bright student since birth
today i did not say god that give me this job,
i just told thanks to him about this job
we need a diplomatic person to
deal with clients
if you control your attitude than
something will happen
i got this attitude after so much
hard work
i cant
you keep yourjob
i keep my attitude
from where you have come?
It seems like someone has
removed my clothes
i wont say i lose
2 or 4?
For what?
To steal this?
We cant get married
why?
You love someone else?
Then why dont you propose me?
Are you imputent?
Then prove it?
I have her house number
where we can find her?
In hospital?
If we drive car fast then we will be
there on time
what do you say?
If we have think then do U turn
you take so much time
we have found Rancho
you still marry with this donkey?
You still love rancho
thats why you are eating it
now he dont talk about price
everyday this type of Sherwani
comes in our laundry. I will clean it
Piya we are getting late
dont shout people will kill me
go inside and send Suhaas
everybody will laugh.
Dont do suicide
people will do gossips for only
2 days
but because of people you marry
with this donkey
is Rancho is married or not?
I dont know
if he is married then?
We will again drop you
since yesterday i was a simple citizen
he was scared if Raju fails then he will
again go for high jump
we took swear that we will only
steal paper for Raju
where he hide it?
Until morning we wont find it
ask from piya
enjoy it.
Virus set this to fail you
i will be pass by myself
or i will be fail
i thought i will marry his sister
then i control my emotion
i wish i could give this key to my brother,
he would be alive
have you ever asked him what he
wanted to be?
You always put pressure on him
he prefered to die
piya what are you doing?
Brother wanted to be writer
that was murder
whole city is full of water,
we cant do anything
raju where is sister?
When there was no hospital on earth,
babies also born that time
you do the delivery of sister
farhan you take towels and scissors
she is tired
what is vacuum cup?
Why it is used?
How?
With vaccum cleaner
but vaccum cleaner pressure is very strong
is there vaccum cleaner?
If my grand son will be engineer then
i will rape him
you kick me.
You will become football player
be whatever you want
on first day of college you asked
a question from me
because pencil nip will be broken in space
i wanted to take that moments
in my camera
everybody hug each other
promise that we will be in touch
we will meet once in a year
nobody know that we are watching
Rancho for the last time
where is he?
Where we can find Ranchoredas?
Calm down and come with me
where is Rancho?
He has read all your books
look at this
raju he daily read your blogs
do you remeber your helmet?
That was stolen
who are you?
You remove your helmet
and come near to me to kiss me
why you did not inform me?
Did you marry?
No and you?
Listen to me
no you listen to me
you become teacher
we caught train together,
but your train went in reverse
stop non sense
he did non sense
i told you one day you will cry
and i will laugh
this is virus pen
how its with you?
Did you steal it?
Good news is that your name is
not Rachoredas