Yes?
What?
Hold on!
I'm fine.
You guys can get back to work.
I'll be on my way.
- Get the car!
- Mr. Dhillon?
Do you want me to get the name tattooed?
Get the car!
Let's go.
To the hotel, sir?
Yes, via Vasant Vihar.
Let's hurry up, dude!
Hello, Farhan.
Get ready.
I'll pick you up in five minutes.
What's wrong?
Chatur called me.
The "Silencer"?
Yes.
He knows where Rancho is.
Really?
He asked us to meet him near the tank
inside our college campus.
Hurry!
Okay.
Honey, I'll be back soon.
My shoes!
We found our buddy.
What?
I'll see you later.
You forgot your pants!
To the hotel now?
Yes, but via
Imperial College of Engineering.
I forgot my socks.
You forgot to wear your pants as well.
Oh, no!
Go and get my brother from the airport
and drop him at the hotel.
This is Mr. Dhillon.
Where the hell is my cab?
- Rancho!
- Chatur, where's Rancho?
Rancho?
Where's Rancho?
Some rum for you?
The same rum you guys used to have
back in those days.
Where is Rancho?
Have patience.
Look at this.
Check out the mansion
behind my wife, you idiots.
Why are you showing this to us?
Don't you remember?
Look at this.
5th September. That's today's date.
I challenge you.
We'll meet again after ten years.
Same day! Same place!
We'll see who's more successful.
Do you accept my challenge?
Do you?
Remember?
I had challenged that idiot, right here!
- Jackass!
- Hold on.
I got off the flight
and he forgot his pants
so that we could meet Rancho.
We searched for him for five years
and we have no clue where he is.
You think he'll show up
for your silly challenge?
I know he won't show up.
- I'm going to beat him up...
- Hold on, Farhan!
Why did you call us here?
I wanted to show you the huge difference
between my success and Rancho's failure.
Do you know where Rancho is?
Where is he?
Rancho.
Ranchoddas Shamaldas Chanchad.
He was as unique as his name.
We were always told that life is a race.
Run fast, or you'll be trampled upon.
Even to be born, one had to race
300 million sperms.
1978. I was born at 5:15 p.m.
At 5:16 p.m. my father announced.
My son will grow up to be an engineer.
No one asked me what my aspirations were.
I lived all my life
As if it were the life of another
For just one moment
Let me live as I am
I lived all my life...
Raju Rastogi.
Ranchoddas Chanchad.
What's your room number?
Come on.
I'm Man Mohan. MM.
The students here call me Millimeter.
I deliver eggs, bread and milk to them.
I also do the laundry
and help them with their
journals and assignments.
I'm the helper.
I charge a fixed rate, no bargaining.
Hold on, hold on!
Meet Kilobyte, Megabyte
and their mother Gigabyte.
- I see.
- You can click a picture.
They don't bite.
Check him out!
Another God-fearing soul.
I'm Raju Rastogi.
Don't worry.
A few days here and
he'll lose faith in God.
Then, there will be pictures
of naked babes on the wall.
He'll be praying to God
for a girlfriend like them.
Get out of here.
You owe me four rupees.
Two rupees per bag.
Here's five. Keep the change.
Thank you.
Here's a suggestion.
Wear your... best underwear tonight.
Why?
Your Majesty, thou art great.
Accept this humble offering.
It looks like He-Man's ass!
Here.
Pretty buttocks!
That's cute!
A campus tradition on day one.
Freshmen must pay their
respects to the seniors...
in their underwear.
This is when we first saw Rancho.
Spiderman.
Batman.
Fresh meat!
Greetings.
Drop your pants, get stamped.
- What's his name?
- Ranchoddas Shamaldas Chanchad.
What a mouthful!
It needs serious cramming.
Come on, take off your pants.
Don't be stubborn.
It's not good to wear wet pants.
Take them off.
What's that?
What did he say?
Please make him understand.
Hey, James Bond.
Make him understand.
Stop speaking in English!
Speak in Hindi.
Explain it to him slowly.
There's no hurry.
Feeling cold?
Please take your pants off.
Or else... he'll have a
urine related explosion all over you.
"Urine related explosion!"
A true linguist
in the land of engineers!
Spiderman.
Batman.
Hey, come out of there.
Come out!
Come out, or else...
I'll have a urine related explosion
all over your door.
By the count of ten...
if you aren't out...
I'll... urinate over your door
all through the coming semester.
One.
Two!
Three!
Four!
Come on!
Five!
Six!
Seven...
Eight!
Nine!
Ten!
We had studied about it.
He applied it, practically.
Dr. Viru Sahastrabuddhe
was the Director of ICE.
Students called him "Virus."
"Computer Virus" to be precise.
Virus is on the way, with eggs!
The freshmen are summoned.
Come quickly!
Virus was the most competitive man
we had ever seen.
He couldn't bear to see anyone
becoming more successful than him.
To save time, his shirts had Velcro.
And his ties had hooks.
He had trained his mind to write
with both hands simultaneously.
Every day at 2:00 p.m. he took
a seven and a half minute power nap
with an opera as his lullaby.
Govind, his valet, had instructions
to carry out all unproductive tasks
such as shaving and manicuring
during his nap time.
What is this?
- Whose?
- A koel bird's nest.
A koel never makes her own nest.
She lays her eggs in other nests.
And when they hatch,
what do they do?
They push the other eggs...
out of the nest.
And these are the eggs you smashed
to get into ICE.
- ICE gets 4,00,000 applications a year.
- "ICE gets 4,00,000 applications a year."
- And only 200 are selected.
- "And only 200 are selected."
And these?
My son tried for three years.
If you don't run fast,
you'll get trampled upon.
This is an astronaut pen.
Fountain pens and ballpoint pens
don't work in outer space.
So scientists spent millions
to invent this pen.
It can write at any angle,
in any temperature and at zero gravity.
I got scared.
When you come across an
extraordinary student like yourself...
pass it onto him.
For 32 years, I've been
waiting for that student.
Anyone here,
who'll strive to win this pen?
Shall I post it on the notice board?
I have a question, sir.
Sir, if fountain pens and ballpoint pens
didn't work in outer space
why didn't the astronauts
use a pencil?
They could have saved millions.
He zaps a senior's privates
and questions the director.
We should avoid that boy.
I'm glad you questioned Virus.
Your Majesty, thou art great.
Accept this humble offering.
Hey! Buzz off!
Go to school.
Who will pay for it? Your father?
- No wisecracks about my father!
- Relax.
You don't need money to go to school.
All you need is a uniform.
Listen!
Pick a school
buy the uniform
and slip into the class.
In that sea of kids,
no one will notice you.
- What if I get caught?
- A new uniform, a new school!
- See that?
- He was different.
He challenged conventions at every stage.
A free-spirited bird had
landed in Virus's nest.
We were like robots, blindly following
our professors' commands.
He was the only one who
was not like a machine.
Why are you smiling?
Sir, studying Engineering
was my childhood dream.
I'm very happy to be here.
There's no need to be happy.
Define a machine.
Anything that simplifies work,
or saves time, is a machine.
On a warm day, press a button
and get a blast of fresh air!
The fan is a machine.
Speak to a friend who lives miles away.
The telephone is a machine.
Compute millions in seconds.
The calculator is a machine.
We are surrounded by machines!
From a pen's nib to a pant's zip,
everything is a machine.
Up and down, in a second...
What is the definition?
I just gave it to you, sir.
"Up and down, in a second."
Is that what you'll write in your exam?
Wonderful!
But I said the same thing
in a simple manner.
If you prefer a simple manner,
join an Arts and Commerce college.
But it's important that one must
understand the meaning as well.
What's the point of blindly
cramming a bookish definition?
You think you're smarter than the book?
Mention the textbook definition,
if you want to pass the examinations.
But there are other books...
In simple terms, "Go away!"
Why are you back?
I forgot something.
What?
What do you mean?
Books, sir.
I forgot my books.
May I take them?
Couldn't you say that
in a simple manner?
I tried that earlier.
It simply didn't work.
Most of the times, the professors
kept Rancho out of their class.
When thrown out of one class,
he'd slip into another.
He believed that knowledge was
everywhere and we needed to grab it.
He was unlike any of us.
We fought for a shower
every morning.
He'd bathe wherever
he found water.
He loved working on machines.
Whenever he spotted a machine,
he opened it with a handy screwdriver.
Some, he could reassemble.
Some, he couldn't.
There was another boy, just like him.
Joy Lobo.
Mr. Joy Lobo!
Sir, I need to know the dates
for the convocation.
- Why?
- Dad wants to make train reservations.
I'll be the first engineer
from my village.
All my relatives want
to attend the function.
In that case, please call your dad.
The director wants to speak to you.
Joy!
Mr. Lobo, your son
won't graduate this year.
Why?
Mr. Lobo, I told you...
it's an unrealistic project.
I suggest you not to
book your train tickets.
Sir, please see it properly.
Submit it, and we'll consider it.
Sir, a small extension...
After dad had a stroke,
I couldn't focus on it for two months.
Did you stop eating for two months?
- No.
- Right.
- Stopped bathing?
- No.
Then why did you stop studying?
Take a look at it, please!
Mr. Lobo!
Sunday afternoon, my son
fell off a train and died.
Monday morning, I was here for my lecture.
I can give you sympathy.
Not an extension, I'm sorry.
I lived all my life
As if it were the life of another
For just one moment
Let me live as I am
I lived all my life
As if it were the life of another
For just one moment
Let me live as I am
This is an amazing design.
A wireless camera atop a helicopter!
This can be used for traffic updates
and security.
But Virus said that this is an
impractical design, it won't work.
We will make it work.
Don't tell Joy.
It will be a surprise for him.
We'll capture his reaction
through the window.
If we work on his project,
who will work on ours?
There are 42 exams per semester
including tests, oral exams and quizzes.
Don't be scared.
Place your hand over your heart
and say, "All is well."
Words of wisdom from
His Holiness Guru Ranchoddas.
We had an old watchman
in our village.
He used to say this
during his night patrol.
And we slept peacefully.
Once, there was a theft
and we learned that
he couldn't see at night!
He used to yell, "All is well"
and we felt secure.
That day I understood that humans
tend to get scared very easily.
You need to trick your mind.
No matter what the problem,
always tell yourself that all is well.
That solves the problem?
No. But you gain courage to face it.
Remember it, bro.
We are going to really need it here.
When life spins out of control
Just let your lips roll
Let your lips roll
And whistle away
When life spins out of control
Just let your lips roll
And whistle away
All is well
The chicken is clueless
About the egg's fate
Will it hatch or become an omelet?
No one knows
What the future holds
So let your lips roll
And whistle away
- Whistle away...
- All is well
Bro, all is well
Buddy, all is well
Confusion and more confusion
No sign of any solution
Ah, finally a solution!
But wait, what was the question?
If the timid heart with fear
Is about to die
Then con it with this simple lie
The heart is an idiot
It will fall under that spell
Let your lips roll
And whistle away
- Whistle away...
- All is well
Bro, all is well
Buddy, all is well
Blew the scholarship on booze
But that did not dispel my blues
Holy incense lit up my plight
And yet God is nowhere in sight
The lamb is clueless
About its destination
Will it be served on skewers
Or simply minced
No one knows what the future holds
So, let your lips roll
And whistle away
- Whistle away...
- All is Well
Bro, all is well
Buddy, all is well
When life spins out of control
Just let your lips roll
And whistle away
All is well
The chicken is clueless
About the egg's fate
That's right
Will it hatch or become an omelet?
No one knows
What the future holds
So, let your lips roll
And whistle away
Whistle away!
Eureka! Eureka!
All is well...
Bro, all is well
Buddy, all is well
Fly it up to Joy's window!
- Joy!
- Take it higher.
Look at that silly moron!
Such a jerk!
Joy, come out.
Joy!
Come to the window.
Joy, look outside!
Joy!
The police and Joy's father
have no clue.
Everyone thinks this is a suicide.
The postmortem report
mentions the cause of death.
All of them think that the pressure
on the jugular killed him.
What about the mental pressure
for the last four years?
That's missing in the report.
Engineers are a clever bunch.
They haven't made a machine
to measure mental pressure.
If they had, everyone would know that...
this isn't suicide, it's a murder.
How dare you blame me
for Joy's suicide?
If a student can't handle
pressure, is it my fault?
Life is full of difficulties.
Will you always blame others?
I don't blame you, sir.
I blame the system.
Look at these statistics.
India ranks number one in suicide cases.
As per statistics,
the suicide rates among students
has increased.
More students die of suicide,
than of diseases.
Something is terribly wrong.
I can't speak for the rest.
I've run this place for 32 years!
We were ranked 28th.
Now, we are number one!
What's the point, sir?
Here, they don't discuss
new ideas or inventions.
They discuss grades.
All of them want a job in the States.
You teach them how to get good scores,
not how to learn efficiently.
How dare you lecture me!
Here is a self-proclaimed professor.
He thinks he is better than
our highly qualified teachers.
Professor Ranchoddas Chanchad
will teach us Engineering.
You have 30 seconds
to define these terms.
You may refer to your books.
Raise your hand
if you get the answer.
Let's see who comes up
with an answer first.
No one got the answer?
Now, rewind your life by a minute.
When I asked this question,
were you excited? Curious?
Thrilled that you'd learn
something new?
No. All of you got into a frantic race.
What's the use of such methods,
even if you come first in such a race?
Will your knowledge increase?
No, just the pressure!
This is a college,
not a pressure cooker.
Even a circus lion learns to sit
on a chair in fear of the whip.
But you call such a lion
well trained, not well educated.
Just explain those two words.
Sir, these words don't exist.
These are my friends' names.
Farhan and Raju.
Is this how you'll teach Engineering?
Sir, I wasn't teaching Engineering.
You're an expert at that.
I was teaching you how to teach.
And I'm sure one day, you'll learn...
because unlike you, I never
abandon my weak students.
I regret to inform you
that your respective sons
Farhan and Raju
have fallen into bad company.
Please look into the matter,
otherwise their future will be ruined.
Virus's letters dropped on
our homes like atom bombs.
Just like Hiroshima and Nagasaki
our homes plunged into a gloom.
Our parents invited us
for a dressing down.
Come in...
Come in.
Do you see that?
We could afford only one air-conditioner.
We placed it in Farhan's room,
so that he could study comfortably.
I didn't buy a car.
I manage with a scooter.
I invested all my money
in Farhan's education.
We sacrificed our comforts for
Farhan's future. Do you get it?
And now after all this, I receive
a warning letter from the director.
Have you clicked these pictures, Farhan?
- Shut up.
- For a while, that was his passion.
He went around clicking
pictures of animals.
He wanted to become
a wildlife photographer.
Son, what was your score that year?
Did you hear that? A sudden drop
from 94 to 91 percent!
Do you find it funny?
No, I'm sorry.
I'm just amazed at the photos.
He should become a wildlife photographer,
not an engineer.
- He will...
- Shut up!
This is a humble request to you!
Don't ruin my son's future.
The food is on the table. Let's eat.
Let's go.
You should join us for a meal
the next time you visit us.
Dad denied us a meal.
But we were hungry,
so we went over to Raju's place.
Raju's house was straight out of
a 50s black and white movie.
A small, dingy room.
A paralyzed father.
An ailing mother.
And an unwed sister.
A torn up sofa with sprouting springs.
And a 24-hour water supply
from the leaking roof.
His mother was a retired school teacher
and a tireless complainer.
His father was once a postmaster.
He was bedridden due to paralysis...
and lost his job.
And Raju's sister...
Kammo has turned 28.
They demand a car in dowry.
You need to study and earn well,
so that we can get her married.
- Some okra?
- Yes, thank you.
Okra and cauliflower have
become very expensive.
They are looting us!
And to make things worse,
I got a warning letter from your college!
Mom!
- Cottage cheese?
- Yes.
Cottage cheese should be sold
at the jewelers, in velvet pouches.
- Cottage cheese?
- No, thanks.
Mom, please!
Alright, I'll shut up.
I earn for the family,
I slave like a maid
and then, I'm asked to keep my mouth shut.
I can't even share my
problems with my son.
Raju.
We were in a huge dilemma.
Were we supposed to comfort our friend,
or console his mother?
Anyway, we thought of focusing
on the cottage cheese.
Even his eczema cream costs 55 rupees!
Another roti?
- No, thank you.
- We've had enough.
"Okra and cauliflower..."
"They have become very expensive."
At least you were offered a meal.
Unlike your sadistic father.
Hitler Qureshi!
And your mother was feeding us
eczema induced rotis!
- Don't poke fun at my mom!
- Enough, you guys.
I'm famished. Let's eat out.
It's the end of the month.
We have no money to eat out.
To eat out, you don't need money.
All you need is a uniform.
Look!
- Come on.
- Let's go.
- Good evening.
- Hello, good evening.
- Good evening...
- Three large vodkas.
- Half soda, half water.
I'm afraid, we'll get caught.
- What's for starters?
- Get double portions of everything.
- Give it to me.
- Yes.
And play some peppy music.
Why are you wearing
this ancient piece of junk?
People will have a bad impression
about you, my fiancé.
You're going to be a doctor.
You shouldn't be wearing a cheap watch!
- May I hold your glass?
- Why?
So that you don't hit me with it.
Why would I do that?
For the free advice I'll now impart.
What?
Don't marry that ass of a man.
He's less of a human being,
and more of a price tag.
He'll turn your life into a
nightmare of brands and prices.
He'll ruin your life.
Want a demonstration?
Shall I find out the price of his shoes?
I won't ask.
He'll announce it himself.
What the hell!
Mint sauce on my 300 dollar shoes!
Run for your life!
It's free advice. Take it or leave it.
Dad, are they your guests?
My students! Why are they here?
Hold on, Dad.
These beans smell great.
- There's no room for the roti.
- Just pile it on.
Okay.
That was an eye-opener.
It was my moral responsibility.
Dad won't let me break up with him.
Could you please speak to my father?
You are good at it!
Certainly!
Raju, the mint sauce please.
- Where is your dad?
- Right behind you.
Run for your life! It's free advice.
Take it or leave it.
What are you doing here?
We'll hand these gift cheques
to the couple.
I'll do that for you.
It's my sister's wedding!
Sister?
Sir, what's the total number
of daughters you have?
Empty! No gift cheques.
Forgot the cheques, Raju? Farhan?
We didn't invite you.
I'm sure the groom's family invited you.
No, sir. We are here as
the emissaries of science.
Really?
He explains things very well.
I'm sure he will.
Won't you?
Well, Delhi has plenty of power cuts...
that disrupt wedding celebrations
in the city.
So I thought of making
an inverter that
draws power from guests' cars.
I see!
Where's the inverter?
Sir, the design is ready.
Where's the design, Farhan?
- I gave you the design.
- I gave it to Raju.
Never mind the design.
I'll show you the inverter!
You can only invent stories...
not an inverter.
No, sir. I'll make one.
And I'll name it after you.
After all, it was invented
at your daughter's wedding.
Farhan.
Raju!
I'll see you in my office tomorrow.
Sir, what was the cost per plate?
We'll reimburse it to you...
in installments.
- We'll never crash a wedding again.
- Not even my own.
In fact, I won't even marry.
Nor will he.
That's right. I won't get married.
Your parents shouldn't
have married either.
There would have been
two less idiots in the world.
This is Ranchoddas's father's
monthly income.
Two and a half crore rupees.
Couple of zeroes less...
and it is still a sizable income.
But erase another zero...
Isn't that your father's
monthly income, Farhan?
Now, take away another zero!
And that's your family income,
Raju Rastogi.
Take my advice.
And shift into Chatur Ramalingam's room.
The exams are near.
Stay with Rancho and you're sure to fail.
- Want a shave?
- No, sir.
Raju, don't worry.
This is Virus's move to split us.
- Don't worry...
- I have to worry!
He grades us, and I need
good grades for a good job.
Unlike you, I don't have a rich father.
Shut up, Raju!
Must we follow all his hogwash?
I won't follow him blindly, like you do.
- You're crossing the line.
- No, I'm drawing one!
I have a family to support!
Mom spends her entire salary
on Dad's medicines.
My sister is not getting married
because the boy demands a car in dowry.
Mom hasn't bought a single saree...
in five years.
Now don't get your mom's
wardrobe into the debate.
How many sarees can you afford, per year?
No wisecracks about Mom!
We'll study diligently.
But not just for good grades.
Here's quoting a wise one.
"Study to be accomplished, not affluent."
Follow excellence.
And success will follow you!
Who said that?
His Holiness Guru Ranchoddas?
Go, rot in the bogs!
Raju, don't stress. We'll excel!
Shove this back into the tube.
Raju shifted to another room.
His new roommate was Chatur.
Chatur was called "Silencer."
To sharpen his memory,
he popped pills from a local quack.
And then, he used to let off
silent but lethal farts.
Raju?
He always blamed others for it.
Silencer studied 18 hours a day.
On the eve of the exam,
he used to distract others.
He believed that there are only two ways
to excel in the examinations.
Elevate your own grades,
or try to lower your opponents' grades.
Rancho decided to subdue Silencer
and rescue Raju
with a master plan.
Our director...
has unceasingly served...
The meaning of served is...
I don't care what the meaning is.
I'll just memorize it.
Such a moron!
Chatur was the introductory speaker
at the Teacher's Day function.
To impress Virus, he got his
speech written by the librarian
in highbrow Hindi.
Hold on.
Chatur, there's a call for you.
Please collect the printout.
I'll be right back.
Oh, the things I have to do!
Mr. Dubey, the director wants to meet you.
- Really?
- Yes. Right now.
I'll see him right away.
Give this to Chatur.
Mr. Ramalingam?
I'm calling from the
Rajpat Nagar police station.
Are you from Uganda?
Your life is in danger!
Listen to me carefully.
Or else, you'll get killed as soon as
you step out of the college gate.
Why? What happened?
While Chatur was kept engaged,
Rancho altered a few words
in his speech. For example...
Served became screwed.
Yes, sir?
- Who are you?
- I'm Dubey, the librarian.
I'm a permanent staff member, sir.
Hold on a moment.
The chief is on the other line.
Yes... So, where was I?
You said that I may die
outside the gate.
Right!
As soon as you get out of the gate,
you'll see a traffic signal.
When it turns red,
all the vehicles will halt.
- Then?
- Then cross the road with great caution.
There's a possibility that you might die
by being hit by a vehicle.
You're safe, my boy. Well done!
Silencer, this is for you
from the librarian.
Chanchad!
The director said that
he didn't call for me.
Well, I suppose he must have forgotten.
Forgotten?
You rascals!
Distinguished guests,
respected chairperson.
Our chief guest,
the Honorable Minister of Education.
Respected teachers and friends.
ICE has now soared
beyond the stratosphere!
The credit goes solely to...
Dr. Viru Sahastrabuddhe.
Sir, I have written the speech.
For 32 years, he has...
unceasingly screwed the students
of this college.
He means, "served" the students.
I'm sure his endeavors will continue.
We are astounded at how a man,
in his lifetime
can screw so many people, so well.
With rigorous training,
he has built up his stamina.
He has spent every living minute
just screwing people around.
Let's replicate his methods.
Let him continue.
In the future, the students of ICE
will venture across the globe.
Wherever we go, we promise to screw
everyone and spread his legacy.
We'll hoist this screwer's flag
all over the world.
We'll show the world that
our capacity to screw
cannot be matched by any student
anywhere on the planet!
Cannot be matched by any student.
Good evening, sir.
You have given this institution
what it sorely needs!
- Boodle...
- Bosom!
It's "Boodle!"
Not "Bosom!"
Utter nonsense! That's insulting.
Everyone has a bosom,
but it remains pocketed.
No one offers it so readily.
That's ridiculous!
You have generously offered
your bosom
to this relentless screwer.
Now see how he makes it grow.
Is this what you teach here?
This is an insult to my stature!
Disgusting!
On this august occasion,
here's a Sanskrit verse.
Listen to the might of his fart
in a Sanskrit verse.
A good loud fart is honorable...
"Fart?" Go, Silencer!
A medium fart is tolerable.
"Tolerable?"
The softer windbreaks are terrible.
"Softer windbreaks..."
And the silent ones... are unbearable!
That's what mindless cramming
does to you!
Cramming may see you
through four years of college
but it will screw you
for the next 40 years.
He still doesn't get it.
"The medium fart is tolerable..."
You're a poet, Rancho!
That was fun!
He didn't know what hit him.
What did I ever do to you?
Sorry, man.
Don't take it personally.
I will!
Chatur Ramalingam
will never forget this insult.
Sorry, man. We just wanted Raju to
know that he shouldn't cram blindly.
Understand and enjoy
the wonders of Science!
I'm not here to enjoy Science!
You're here to screw Science?
Go ahead!
Laugh at my methods.
But one day these methods
will bring me a lot of success!
One day, I'll be successful
and you will be a failure!
You're wrong, buddy.
Don't chase success.
Become a good engineer
and success will chase you.
You do it your way,
and I'll follow my methods.
Ten years from now, we'll meet right here.
Same day! Same place!
We'll see who's more successful.
You... or me?
Do you have the courage
to accept my challenge?
It's a challenge!
Watch it!
What's wrong with him?
What's he writing?
Don't forget this date.
I'm not used to such
expensive gifts, Suhas.
Get used to them, Pia.
- You edited the speech?
- What?
Don't lie!
Yes.
- Do you have a problem with my father?
- No way.
I'm making an inverter
named after him. Look!
Oh, no!
Why are you harassing him?
He runs a factory, not a college.
Churning out asses!
Like that one.
She destroyed it, man.
How dare you call him an ass?
He is one!
He is an engineer, he studied MBA
and then he becomes
a banker in the States.
Because it rakes in more money?
Life for him is just
a profit and loss statement.
He sees profit in you,
that's why he is with you.
You are the director's daughter
and you'll be a doctor very soon.
He doesn't love you.
Who do you think you are?
How dare you say that he doesn't love me?
New watch? One moment, please.
You always need a demonstration.
Suhas!
Where were you?
She's looking for her watch.
Never mind. Get another one.
It is worth 4,00,000 rupees!
4,00,000!
Mine's a cheap one,
but it's just the same.
Now wear your ancient piece of junk
at dinner.
What are you staring at?
Here come the tears!
Stop crying and look for it.
Go and get yourself
another fiancé, you ass!
Hey, you're awesome.
Called him an ass to his face!
- It's too noisy here.
- Yes.
She was trying to thank me,
but I heard something else.
- I said, "Get lost."
- Don't get angry.
Actually, you never really loved him.
When you see him,
do the winds whisper a melody?
Does your scarf sway in the wind?
Does the moon appear gigantic?
That happens in movies, not in life.
It happens in real life too
if you love a person,
not an ass.
What?
Okay, I'm on my way. Bye!
You're a medical student!
I need your help.
Please come with me.
What's that oath you doctors take?
You'll never deny help to a patient.
Remember the Hippocratic oath?
Please help me, it's an emergency!
You gatecrash my sister's wedding,
break off my engagement,
my dad is popping BP pills
because of you...
and here I am, helping you!
I'm doing this only because
of the Hippocratic oath.
- Where's Raju?
- He's gone to get a cab.
I called the ambulance two hours ago.
In this country,
pizza gets delivered in 30 minutes
but an ambulance...
He needs urgent hospitalization.
Stop!
Move away!
Move away...
Keep this.
Raju is here.
What the hell!
You brought Dad on the scooter?
I should have sent him by post?
No wisecracks about Dad's profession!
Where is he?
Go, ask the doctor.
We would have lost him
if there was any delay.
I'm glad you brought him here
on the scooter.
Call me if there's any problem.
Rancho!
Thanking your buddies!
Is Silencer teaching you good manners?
Didn't he teach you anything
about friendship?
Go on, now.
You have an exam tomorrow.
That's okay.
His father's health is more important.
We won't budge from here
without your father.
Don't worry!
Rancho, forgive me. I was scared.
It's okay. Calm down.
Please forgive me.
Calm down.
It's okay, calm down.
Go, see your dad.
Don't go in there
with that weepy face.
Go.
Get going.
He was our dearest friend
Thank God for your scooter,
it saved his father's life.
It's a good one.
How much does it cost?
I'll tell you when you pour
some mint sauce over it.
It's not the 15th of August.
For you, it is! You are free
to wear your mom's watch.
No ass can say that it's
an ancient piece of junk.
How did you know that
it was my mom's watch?
At your sister's wedding,
you wore sparkling new clothes.
Only the watch was old.
What could that mean?
You really missed your mom
that day, didn't you?
Yes.
Your mom must have been really beautiful.
Yes. How do you know that?
Your dad is ugly.
The winds
Whisper a melody
The sky hums along
Time itself is singing
Zoobi do...
Param pum...
Zoobi doobi pum paara
Zoobi doobi param pum
My silly heart goes zoobi doobi
Zoobi doobi as it jives along
Zoobi doobi pum paara
Zoobi doobi param pum
My silly heart goes zoobi doobi
Zoobi doobi as it jives along
Leaves sing on their branches
Bees jam with flowers
Crazy sunbeams dance off petals
As birds yodel in the skies
Flowers, bold and brazen
Snuggle and cuddle
Whatever is happening right now
I've seen it happen in the movies
Zoobi doobi pum paara
Zoobi doobi param pum
My silly heart goes zoobi doobi
Zoobi doobi as it jives along
Zoobi doobi pum paara
Zoobi doobi param pum
My silly heart goes zoobi doobi
Zoobi doobi as it jives along
Let's learn how to make some mint sauce.
The all-powerful sauce that
exposes phony people.
- The mint...
- You have a bright future.
Shunning an ass,
you'll fall for a human.
The time is ripe for love.
The temperature in New Delhi
remains stable.
Clear skies.
But if in love, expect rain.
Pitter-patter go the raindrops
Whish-whoosh whistles the wind
Do-da-Dee waltzes the rain
Boom-boom echoes the sky
Drenched in rain and passion
You sway your hips on cue
Whatever is happening right now,
I've seen it happen in the movies
Zoobi doobi pum paara
Zoobi doobi param pum
My silly heart goes zoobi doobi
Zoobi doobi as it jives along
Zoobi doobi pum paara
Zoobi doobi param pum
My silly heart goes zoobi doobi
Zoobi doobi as it jives along
The gorgeous moon
Serenades the earth
A shooting star skips along
Crooning a ballad of love
The night is bright but lonesome
Come touch me, my handsome
Whatever is happening right now
I've seen it happen in the movies
Zoobi doobi pum paara
Zoobi doobi param pum
My silly heart goes zoobi doobi
Zoobi doobi as it jives along
Zoobi doobi pum paara
Zoobi doobi param pum
My silly heart goes zoobi doobi
Zoobi doobi as it jives along
Zoobi doobi goes my silly heart
My silly heart!
Hello, wake up!
- Is he dead?
- What!
No!
It's 8:30 a.m.
Your exam starts at 9:00 a.m.
But we can't leave him alone.
I'm here!
It's just a matter of three hours.
Take my scooter.
The watch looks really old.
- Sorry, we are late.
- It was an emergency!
Five minutes more, please.
We started half an hour late.
He glared at us like we had
asked for both his kidneys.
But we continued writing.
He continued arranging
the answer sheets.
I'm done!
You are late, I can't accept these.
Sir, do you know who we are?
Even if you are the minister's son,
I don't care.
Do you know
our names and roll numbers?
No.
Who are you?
He doesn't know us! Run!
Hey, what's your roll number?
Where the hell... are their papers?
O Lord, have mercy.
The results were going to be out.
It was time to pray to God.
Help me excel in Electronics,
I'll offer You a coconut!
God, help me excel in Physics,
I promise You a pint of milk per day.
God, help me excel in all the subjects.
God, I will stop behaving like a creep!
Watch over my results!
God, I'll offer hundred rupees
every month!
Hundred rupees is not good enough
to bribe a traffic cop,
let alone the Almighty.
Check from the bottom.
Your name appears at the end of the list.
What about you?
Rancho?
I can't see his name here.
We were sad.
Not because our ranks were low,
but because our friend had failed.
What is Silencer howling about?
- He got the second rank.
- Damn!
Who's first?
Rancho.
Rancho?
What the hell! Move aside.
We learnt a lesson
about human behavior.
If your friend fails, you feel bad.
But if your friend succeeds
exceedingly well, you feel worse.
We were sad. But two other
people were heartbroken.
Ranchoddas Chanchad.
Uday Sinha.
Alok Mittal.
Sahili Rao.
Sir, is it necessary to sit
according to your ranks?
Any problem with that?
Yes, this grading system is
like a caste system.
The A graders are treated like masters.
And the C graders are treated like slaves.
Are you suggesting a change?
Yes. The results should not be
displayed at all.
Why publicize someone's flaws?
If your iron count is low,
will the doctor prescribe a tonic
or air your report on TV?
I should go to each student's room...
and whisper it in their ears.
"You haven't done well."
"Oh, I'm so sorry, you have failed."
No, sir. That's not what I meant.
I'm sitting next to you
because I scored high.
My friends didn't score well,
so they are sitting out there.
At least, they are here!
If they spend more time with you,
they'll fail.
They won't pass their examinations
and they won't find a job.
They'll find a job, sir.
There are companies that prefer
hiring humans, not machines.
They'll be hired, for sure.
- Govind.
- Yes, sir?
Even if one of them gets a job
through the campus interviews...
shave off my mustache.
Okay, sir!
Jackass! You just farted, didn't you?
It smells like a septic tank!
Popping those pills again?
- Raju?
- Raju...
This is a familiar stink.
His farts have caused global warming.
Give me your wallet.
I'll buy a pair of pants.
Take Chatur's suit instead.
Rancho will recognize you
even in your underwear.
- Help us with this address, please.
- I wish I could read.
- He can't read.
- But he can speak.
Sir, do you know a man named
Ranchoddas Chanchad?
Yes, he lives up there.
He was free as the wind
Let's go!
CHANCHAD HOUSE.
Free like a soaring kite
Where did he go?
Let's find him
- Chatur, your pills.
- Thanks. Where were they?
In the pocket.
We are friends, we must share our things...
- Take them off!
- Stop it!
People will misinterpret it, you moron!
Let me go.
What happened?
MR. SHAMALDAS CHANCHAD.
Excuse me, where is Ranchoddas?
There he is.
Rancho.
We are looking for Ranchoddas.
That's me.
No, I mean...
Ranchoddas Shamaldas Chanchad.
That's me.
Ranchoddas, take care of yourself.
Ranchoddas Chanchad.
Raju.
I drove from Delhi to Shimla
without wearing any pants.
That too, for the wrong guy!
The same name, the same degree,
the same photo, but a different guy.
What's going on?
How did Silencer get Rancho's address?
Good question!
Chatur, come here.
Phunsukh Bangdu? Who's that?
It took me a year to get
an appointment with him.
Forget Wangdu.
How did you get Rancho's address?
He led me to Rancho, see this.
My secretary was here to get
an appointment with Mr. Wangdu.
She didn't get the appointment.
But I found Rancho.
I checked the Shimla city directory
and found Rancho's name.
What happened to his face?
Did he undergo a plastic surgery
in honor of your visit?
Only one man has the answer.
I couldn't fulfill your last wish.
You kept asking me to
take you on a pilgrimage.
But I waited for the initiation
of the highway tender.
You died as soon as the
tender was released.
No way!
You are an engineer.
You flaunt your degrees on the wall!
How dare you barge in?
I'll have you arrested.
You are the one who will be arrested.
We know the truth.
You use the degree to
clinch high-end contracts.
That's our friend's degree.
How did you get it?
This is a 150 acre estate.
If I kill you and bury your body,
no one would even notice.
I'm taking my father's ashes
to the sacred river.
Should I take yours as well?
Grab that!
Here, here!
Give it to me!
Tell us the truth, or your father's ashes
will be flushed down the drain!
- Hand it over to me!
- Down the sewer, I say!
Get it away from there.
If you pull the trigger,
I'll flush this down.
I'll count to three.
We are not scared of you!
Raju, scatter the ashes.
One.
Take us down, and your father's ashes
go down the drain as well.
- Two!
- You'll have to get the ashes out
of the gutter.
What is it, Raju?
We've got the wrong urn.
It's empty!
Empty?
- Empty?
- We'll empty it out!
No, no!
We'll empty it out!
No!
Tell us!
Who are you?
I am Ranchoddas.
Trust me, it's true!
I am Ranchoddas!
That was Chhote.
Chhote?
He was our gardener's son.
People called him Chhote.
He stayed with us
after he was orphaned.
He did odd jobs around the house.
Running the usual errands and
taking care of household chores.
He had a passion for learning.
He used to wear my old uniform
and slip into school.
And he used to attend any class he liked.
I made him do my homework,
and appear for the examinations
on my behalf.
It was going well, until one day...
our teacher saw a sixth grader
solving a tenth grade math question.
Which grade are you in, son?
What's your name?
We got caught.
My father was a powerful man,
so our teacher alerted him
before speaking to the principal.
You started it, and you will finish it.
People pretend to respect me.
But in my absence...
they make fun of me
because I am an illiterate.
I won't let that happen to my son.
This boy wants to study.
I want him to earn a degree for my son.
Let this continue.
Make sure he goes on to study Engineering.
And I'll have a degree in my son's name,
placed on that wall.
I went to London for four years,
and he went to college on my behalf.
He had promised Dad...
that he won't keep in touch with anyone
after he graduates.
But he always said to me...
"Two idiots will come looking for me.
That's for sure."
He misses the both of you.
I'll give you his address.
Go, meet him.
But please keep my secret.
- Trust us.
- Yes.
You got the wrong urn, sir.
Your father's ashes are in here.
Who was that guy?
It's a complicated story,
you won't get it.
- Ignore it.
- Where are we going?
Ladakh.
Ladakh!
To meet Rancho.
What is he doing... in Ladakh?
I don't know.
But I have the address of a school.
And look at him.
Next week I'll sign a multimillion
dollar deal with Phunsukh Wangdu.
And look at him.
Now, I respect Rancho even more.
Most of us went to college
just for a degree.
No degree meant no job,
no marriage
no credit card and no social status.
None of this mattered to him.
He was in college
for the joy of learning.
He was not obsessed about success,
nor afraid of failure.
Who was the first man on the Moon?
Who was the second?
Soon, 26 companies
will be here with job offers.
You'll have a job
even before your final exam.
Get ready!
Sir, if a student gets a job
but... he fails the final exam
by a tiny margin,
will he still have the job?
Anyone else with the same question?
Hurry up.
For the last four years
they've been our most
consistent students.
Consistently last in every exam!
Their brains will fetch a handsome price
if they were to be sold in the bazaar.
Because they are unused.
The exams won't affect their jobs.
Because no company
will hire them anyway!
They are very unique and their names
will be written in gold.
"Farhanitrate" and "Prerajulization."
He screwed us! Such an insult!
In front of everyone.
God, I'll give up on meat!
I'll light a 1000 incense sticks!
Do me just one favor!
I want You to kill Virus!
Let him burn in the fires of hell!
Make sure that he suffers!
You think God is a contract killer?
Shut up!
You're sitting next to Virus
in every yearbook photo.
We are always at the back.
This year I think we won't even
be a part of the photograph.
- Want to know the secret to my success?
- Yes.
I love machines.
Engineering is my passion.
What's your passion?
- That's my bag.
- Shut up.
What are you up to?
Damn it!
This is your passion!
You need to mail this letter.
What letter?
Five years ago he wrote this for
his favorite wildlife photographer.
- Andre...
- Istvan.
Yes! Istvan.
He wanted to go to Hungary
and be his student.
But in fear of his dad, the Fuhrer,
he never mailed the letter.
Quit Engineering and pursue photography.
Follow your heart, your talent.
If Michael Jackson's father
had forced him to become a boxer...
If Mohammad Ali's father
had pushed him to become a singer...
Imagine the disaster!
Do you get it?
He loves photography,
but he wants to get into Engineering.
Your Holiness Guru Ranchoddas!
Engineering is my passion
as well as my ambition.
- But I still fail. Why?
- Explain!
Because you are a coward,
you are scared of the future.
Look at this!
I see more holy rings than fingers.
One ring per fear.
Exam, sister's dowry and the job.
With such fear for the future,
how will you enjoy the present?
That is why you can't
focus on your studies.
Strange friends! One lives in fear,
the other in pretense.
You live in fear as well as pretense.
- No way.
- You're scared to tell Pia you love her,
so you pretend you don't.
That's rubbish!
It's easy to offer free advice,
tough to follow it!
If you have the courage,
go and talk to Pia.
- There's no connection here...
- There's a deep connection, Your Holiness!
Listen, if you tell Pia how you feel...
I'll tell Dad that I don't
want to be an engineer,
I want to be a photographer.
And I'll throw my rings away
before the job interview.
Deal?
Do you have the courage to do so?
His Holiness is speechless.
Let's go.
- Follow me.
- Where?
Where to?
- Let's go.
- Where?
Hey, Virus! I'm antivirus!
Is there a dog in here?
Cowards! Let's go in.
If there's any danger,
I'll let you guys know.
Come on.
We hate you, Virus!
Do you need a background score?
- Pia.
- Who is it?
Don't yell!
It's me, Ranchoddas Chanchad.
I have something to tell you.
I'll leave once I do.
'Cause I can't help
Falling in love with you...
-Pia
-Yes?
Those 22 minutes with you
on the scooter...
were the most enchanting
22 minutes of my life.
I could spend an eternity...
with you on the scooter.
Falling in love with you...
Every night you ride into my dreams...
on your scooter, dressed as a bride.
Instead of a veil,
you lift your helmet.
And you come closer to kiss me.
But we don't kiss each other.
Why?
Because our noses collide,
and I wake up.
The noses never collide, stupid!
I thought you were Pia.
I wish I was!
Mona! Why did you interrupt?
It took him four years to say this.
Pia, let him know that noses don't
collide when you kiss someone.
You have my permission, kiss him!
- Who is this?
- My sister.
Who are you?
When you were talking...
He? How do you know
it's a "he" or a "she"?
Dad asked the astrologer if we'd
be having an engineer or a doctor.
Why?
The boy grows up to be an engineer,
and the girl, a doctor.
Champ, better stay inside.
Out here, there's a circus.
Your grandpa is the ringmaster.
He'll crack his whip.
Run for your life!
He would want you to become an engineer.
But you should follow your heart.
If grandpa scares you...
put your hand on your heart
and say, "All is well."
Say it again.
He kicked again!
Pia!
Say it again.
Who is it?
You sent a "hate-mail" to Dad,
here's a "pee-mail" for you!
A "pee-mail" for you!
No...
Who is it?
Who...
- Who is it?
- Your future son-in-law!
And the wedding party.
Rastogi!
Guard, follow them.
Where is Raju Rastogi?
Where were you last night?
- He was studying all night.
- Studying?
He hasn't slept well,
that's why he looks scruffy.
Really?
What did you study?
The whole chapter.
Whole chapter?
Raju!
Mr. Rastogi!
Can you type?
Yes, sir.
Will you type a letter for me?
Please delete that.
This will kill my dad!
He lives just to see me
become an engineer.
You should have thought about that
before peeing on my door.
Sir, please give me one chance.
Okay.
Instead of your name...
mention Ranchoddas Chanchad's name.
I know he was with you last night.
Be my witness... and I'll spare you.
You can think about it
until I'm done shaving.
We won't let you die
The heavens may beckon you
But we'll take up arms against God
And it's not a fight we intend to lose
You may try your best to escape
Try with all your might
But there is no way we'll let you go
We won't let you die
Rancho, watch that monitor.
Raju.
His body is paralyzed with shock,
but his mind is alert.
He can see and hear us.
Please don't cry in front of him.
Speak to him normally, motivate him,
crack a joke, be happy.
Good news, Raju!
Your dad has recovered.
The new medicine worked.
Is this your family tradition?
As one male gets up,
the other conks out?
Come on, wake up.
Your dad wants Pia's scooter.
Should I give it to him?
I hope he knows how to ride it.
Raju, Farhan is live on the webcam.
Look! Virus has cancelled
your suspension order.
Wake up, now.
Everything is okay!
You hear that?
Rise and shine, buddy.
In this journey of few strides
On the path called life
Don't quit
Just celebrate the ride
Please listen to those who love you
Every dark night is followed by sunrise
Don't shut out those who love you
We won't let you die
Look! Your mother bought a new saree!
It costs 2,000 rupees. Look!
Wake up, now!
She bought ten sarees!
Look!
Hey, Raju!
Raju! How do I look?
Remember the letters mom would write
She always blessed you with eternal life
Don't let her be disappointed
Look at us now, don't turn away
Smile once to show you care
Wake up, don't torment us anymore
Did you hear about your sister?
She's getting married.
Without offering any dowry!
The bridegroom wants nothing at all.
He just wants to marry Kammo.
- You know who the bridegroom is?
- Yes...
Guess!
- You know him very well.
- Yes.
- He loves animals.
- What?
Yes! He's going to be a
wildlife photographer.
Quiet!
Didn't get it? It's Farhan!
Farhan will never take any dowry.
Farhan will marry your sister.
For free!
- Raju!
Raju!
He would've woken up even if we
were to offer vegetables for free.
Why put my life at stake?
It's decided!
Farhan will marry your sister.
Rancho!
Rascals! Stop lying.
Lucky escape!
We won't let you die
OKRA COSTS TWELVE RUPEES.
- Did you call for a taxi?
- I did.
Why?
I'm going for a job interview.
You're coming with me?
No. You're going home.
I'm going for the interview.
Why would I go home?
Remember... the promise?
Give me your tie.
Why?
I doubt you'll go for the
interview after reading this.
What's that?
- A letter.
- For you, from Hungary.
From a photographer called Andre Istvan.
You mailed my letter!
He loved your pictures.
He wants you to assist him.
You get to work in the
Brazilian rain forest, for a year.
He will pay you as well.
Dad will never agree.
Go, speak to him.
For once, dump your fears.
Otherwise you will regret it
for the rest of your life.
The letter is in your hand,
and the taxi is at the gate.
With a little bit of courage,
you can turn your life around.
Do you think he'll like it?
It's such an expensive gift.
Our son is getting his first job today.
Don't be stingy at
such a proud moment!
Farhan?
Don't you have a job interview today?
I didn't go there.
I don't want to be an engineer, Dad.
What happened?
I jumped down...
from the third floor of that building.
Because I was rusticated from college.
Why?
I was drunk and I urinated
outside the director's door.
Rancho is messing with your mind!
I don't enjoy Engineering.
I'd be a terrible engineer.
Rancho has a simple belief. He says,
"Make your passion your profession."
Then work will become play.
What will you earn in that jungle?
A small stipend, but I'll learn a lot.
Five years from now...
when you see your friends buying
cars and homes, you'll curse yourself.
Life as an engineer will bring
only frustration. Then, I'll curse you.
I'd rather curse myself, Dad.
People will laugh at you!
They will call you a loser
for quitting in the final year.
Mr. Kapoor says that you are
fortunate to be studying at ICE.
What do I tell him now?
Mr. Kapoor didn't provide me
with an air-conditioner.
It wasn't Mr. Kapoor who slept
in discomfort while I slept well.
He didn't take me around the zoo
on his shoulders.
You did all that, Dad.
How you feel, matters to me.
I don't care about Mr. Kapoor.
I don't even know his first name.
You think you're the hero
of a melodrama?
Enough, he's upset.
God forbid, what if he does
something crazy like Raju did?
So, the discussion is over.
Don't say a word,
or they will try to kill themselves.
No, Dad. I'll never attempt suicide.
I promise.
My friend Rancho, whom you detest...
forced me to place this picture
in my wallet.
He told me to look at it...
if a suicidal thought crosses my mind...
and imagine your pain
if you were to see me dead.
I want to convince you, Dad.
But not with a suicide threat.
Dad, what will happen
if I become a photographer?
I'll earn a little less.
I'll have a smaller house,
a smaller car.
But I'll be happy.
Whatever I do for you,
will be out of genuine love.
I've always obeyed you.
For once, let me listen to my heart.
Dad.
Please don't walk away.
Return this.
Son, what's the cost
of a professional camera?
Can the laptop be exchanged for it?
If you need more money, just ask for it.
Go, follow your dreams, my son.
Why are your grades consistently poor?
Fear.
I was a good student since childhood.
My parents hoped
that I would end their poverty.
That scared me.
Here, everyone is very competitive.
You don't count if you're not first.
My fear grew.
I slipped on holy rings over my fingers
and prayed frantically.
It was almost as if I was
asking God for favors.
16 broken bones gave me
two months to think and reflect.
Finally, some sense dawned on me.
Today, I didn't ask for anything.
I just thanked God for this life.
If you reject me, I'll have no regrets.
Because I'll still do something
worthwhile with my life.
Such frank behavior
is not good for our firm.
We need someone who is diplomatic
to handle clients.
You're extremely straightforward.
If you assure us
that you'll have some control
over your attitude
then... we may consider you.
It took me two broken legs
to build up this self-confidence.
It wasn't easy to get this attitude.
I can't change myself, sir.
You can keep your job...
I'll keep my attitude.
Wait.
I've interviewed countless candidates
for 25 years.
Everyone turns into
a yes-man to get the job.
You are unique!
Shall we discuss the salary?
Your Majesty, thou art great!
Accept this humble offering.
He was our dearest friend
He who touched our hearts and vanished
Where did he go?
Let's find him
Govind!
You had asked me to shave it off
when they get a job!
What have you done?
I feel naked without my mustache.
I've lost my dignity.
I won't accept defeat, Rastogi.
The job isn't yours until you
pass your final exam.
I'll make sure that the questions
are extremely tough to answer.
Rastogi, you're dead meat!
Why are you here?
Be careful.
- You've been drinking?
- Yes, I'm a little drunk.
Little? I think you're quite drunk.
- I needed courage.
- For what?
- For stealing this.
- What's this?
The duplicate key to Virus's office.
The question papers are
inside a red envelope.
Dad wants to make sure that
Raju fails in the examinations.
Go, get the papers!
That's cheating!
Tell me something.
Do you think that the noses collide
while two people kiss?
Wait a minute. Have some Dhokla.
You Gujaratis are very cute.
But why do your food items
have such dangerous names?
Dhokla, Fafda, Handwa,
Thepla, Khakhra!
The names sound like missiles.
Let's go.
"Today, Bush bombarded Iraq
with two Dhoklas!
400 dead, 200 injured!"
Let's go.
I can deal with the weird food names.
But not your last name.
Ranchoddas Shamaldas Chanchad.
I won't change my last name
after we get married.
Pia, I can't marry you.
Why?
Is there someone else?
No.
- Are you gay?
- No.
Then why don't you propose to me?
Are you impotent?
Stop, stop!
- What happened?
- We didn't inform Pia.
Are you in touch with her?
- No! But I have her phone number.
- Call her up, I'll stop the car.
Yes.
There aren't enough washrooms
in this country.
- Is Pia there?
- No.
Is she at the hospital?
Why would she be there?
She's getting married in Manali.
Too late! She's married.
Not yet. It's a six hour drive.
If we rush, we'll reach before the vows.
What do you say?
It's a no-brainier. Let's go.
We'll meet Rancho and return.
I have a meeting with Phunsukh Wangdu
this Friday.
Get into the car.
Do you know what will happen if I miss it?
Virus will have a heart attack.
We always crash his daughters' wedding.
Listen, I'll handle Pia.
Please deal with Suhas.
- Farhan!
- We found Rancho.
Is that for room number 107?
You are late!
Get lost.
We found Rancho!
I don't think you should marry that ass.
You still love Rancho.
You're still eating his favorite food.
He's incorrigible.
He is not the right man for you.
He doesn't speak about
brands and prices anymore.
My coat that costs 1,50,000 rupees!
How dare you do that?
- I'll sort it out, sir.
- How?
Our laundry specializes in
cleaning mint-stained suits.
I'll clean it in a jiffy.
Give me a minute!
- I'll clean it for you...
- How dare you!
Pia.
Let's go, Pia. We are getting late.
Pia, it's me, Raju.
Please don't react, they'll kill me.
Where is Suhas?
The housekeeping staff took my coat away!
Send Suhas here.
It's rude to leave the ceremony.
- Yes, Farhan?
- The car is ready.
Grab her hand and run!
Don't move.
- Sir!
- My coat?
- You're here!
- Yes!
- Who's at the altar?
- Altar?
Another couple of rounds,
and we'll be considered married.
I'm already married, Pia.
Let's go.
It's too late...
People will laugh at me.
How does that matter?
Rastogi!
People will gossip for a few days.
Then, they'll forget about it.
But if you get married
to the wrong person,
you'll regret if for life.
The car is at the gate,
we are about to meet Rancho.
You don't have to marry that ass
fearing people's judgments.
Pia, there's a minor issue.
What?
We're not sure if Rancho
is married or single.
- I'm sure he is single.
- What if he's married?
Then we'll drop you back.
Relax! Have some biscuits.
What's he doing here?
- Ignore him.
- The biscuits are very good.
I was a law-abiding citizen.
But in the last 24 hours,
I had grounded an aircraft...
laid a dead man's ashes on
the edge of a toilet seat...
and made a bride elope
from her own wedding!
All for the sake of Rancho.
But he had done a lot for us as well.
Like stealing the question paper
from the lion's den.
Envelope with the red seal. Come on.
He feared that if Raju failed, he might
try to commit suicide once again.
We were principled thieves,
stealing the paper only for Raju.
We were not even going to look at it.
Where is it?
We'll grow old searching for it!
Rancho, ask Pia.
Where were you?
- You need to answer my calls.
- Pia, your phone...
Brother-in-law, if you say "All is well,"
the baby kicks.
He kicked.
- Heard that?
- Pia, your phone...
I found it, Rancho.
I was expecting your call.
Quick, photocopy this.
Where was it?
Put it back.
Be careful.
- We are safe!
- Where were you?
- Here.
- What is this?
A gift.
Question paper.
Virus wants you to fail the examinations.
That's strange!
You taught me how to live without fear.
And now you are leading me
towards the path of shame.
No way!
If I succeed, it will be on my own terms.
If I don't, that's okay.
My buddy!
I was so happy at that moment.
I wanted to get a little more personal,
but I controlled my emotions.
To hell with you!
Wanted to change the education system?
- How dare you pee at my door!
- Sir, please stop it...
Scoundrel!
If all of you aren't out by morning,
I will call the police.
How did he get my office key?
I gave it to him, Dad.
I wish I had given this key to my brother.
He'd be alive today.
You think your son
fell off a train and died?
You wanted him to be an engineer.
Did you ever ask him
what he wanted to pursue?
You put a lot of pressure on him.
He chose death
over the entrance exam.
I don't understand...
Dad, go to your room.
What is wrong with you?
He wanted to study Literature,
he wanted to be a writer.
But all he wrote was
this suicide note.
Put that away, please!
No more cover-ups!
Just once...
you should have asked him
to quit Engineering!
You should have let him
follow his passion.
He would have been alive!
He didn't commit suicide.
It wasn't a suicide.
It was a murder.
Many city roads are completely submerged.
The traffic has come to a standstill.
Mona!
Please don't follow us.
I can do whatever I want to.
I need an ambulance!
Get it from another hospital!
The entire city is flooded, sir!
We are helpless.
No, Pia...
Mona, are you okay?
It's Pia on the line.
Rancho, it's impossible for you
to get here. So, do as I say.
Try to understand!
You don't get it...
They disconnected the call!
Mona...
Mona!
Be careful!
- Turn on the lights!
- Where to?
- To the table tennis table.
- Pia, we are in the common room.
Raju, turn the web camera on.
Sure...
- Hi, Piya.
- Raju! Where's Mona?
Yes.
Here, Pia.
Mona, don't worry. I'm with you.
Rancho, even when there
were no hospitals and doctors,
babies were successfully delivered.
You guys will help Mona
deliver this baby.
What are you doing!
Dad, stay out of this.
Farhan, get some towels and scissors.
Millimeter, get some clips
and a lot of hot water.
- Rancho, place a cloth over her.
- Yes...
Mona, try pushing.
- Push with all your might!
- Push harder!
- Push...
I can't do it!
Please check if there's
any crowning happening.
Crowning?
Get that diagram.
It's a process whereby the baby's head
starts to emerge.
Be quick!
Go, Rancho! Be quick!
There's no crowning.
Mona, please push harder.
Mona!
She's tired, Pia.
Wake her up!
She needs to push harder!
- They need a vacuum cup.
- Where will they get one from?
What's a vacuum cup?
How is it used?
If the mother is too fatigued to push,
a cup is placed on the baby's head.
Suction makes the cup
stick to the head...
and the baby is pulled out.
I can make this!
How?
- With a vacuum cleaner!
- Vacuum cleaner?
That would mean a lot of pressure.
- I'll control the pressure!
- Do you have a vacuum cleaner?
Yes, in my office.
- Farhan, hurry up and get it.
- Here's the key!
What happened?
What's wrong?
Hello, Pia!
- What happened?
- There's a power cut!
How will the vacuum cleaner work?
- Farhan.
- Yes?
Get the vacuum cleaner.
I'll switch the inverter on.
How?
Millimeter, take Virus out.
Be quick!
- Come on!
- No way...
Not him! I want you to get my
inverter which is named after him.
- Get that, quickly.
- Okay.
- Raju.
- Yes?
Ask the other students to help you with
car batteries, wires, and a vacuum gauge.
Emergency in the common room!
Where's Rancho?
Keep the batteries and the wires here.
Raju, switch everything off and
connect the inverter to the mains.
Farhan, get your lens cleaner.
Yes, get it.
Rancho, here's the blower.
Fix this to the gauge.
Rancho, I'm done.
- Are all the switches off?
- Yes.
Switch on the bulb and the computer.
Okay.
Raju, turn the computer on.
Connect it here!
Pia, come here quickly.
- Farhan, turn it on.
- Okay!
Pia, what's the rate of the suction?
Not more than 0.5!
- Cover it!
- Yes.
A vacuum cleaner baby!
Mother of all deliveries!
- Farhan, switch it off.
- Okay.
Push the baby down, like this.
Okay.
- Farhan, switch it on.
- Yes!
Come on, push!
Do it for Champ!
The baby is coming out!
Farhan, turn it off.
Okay!
Cut the umbilical cord using two clips.
Farhan, get me two clips!
- Get the scissors.
- Be careful!
Cut it and get me a towel.
Pia, the baby is not crying.
Rancho, rub the baby's back.
He is not responding.
Blow air into his mouth!
Calm down, Mona.
Tell yourself that "All is well."
He kicked.
What?
Tell yourself that "All is well!"
He wandered lonesome as a cloud
Yet he was our dearest friend
I was afraid he would ask the baby
to grow up and become an engineer.
But when he finally spoke,
we were stunned.
What a kick!
Do you want to be a footballer?
Follow your heart!
Follow your passion!
Wait! Where are you going?
You had asked me a question
on the first day of college.
"Why didn't astronauts
use a pencil in space?"
If the tip of a pencil breaks,
it will float around in zero gravity
and get into someone's eyes, or nose,
or inside the instrument panels.
This was an important invention!
My director told me...
that when...
an extraordinary student...
Excel in your exams and leave!
Ranchoddas Shamaldas Chanchad!
I wanted to capture all these memories.
That day, we hugged, we rejoiced, we cried
and promised to keep in touch.
We vowed to meet each other
at least once a year.
No one knew that we were seeing Rancho
for the last time.
Untie him.
Raju.
Only Rancho can establish
a school like this!
Where is he?
Don't pee out here!
Get lost.
- Don't pee out here.
- I'll smack you!
Bingo! That means he is somewhere around!
Excuse me, where is Ranchoddas?
- He's not Ranchoddas!
- Rancho...
Chhote... Dammit, what's his name?
Calm down.
Come with me.
- Where is he?
- Rancho!
Rancho!
Farhan, he has read all your books.
Look!
Raju, he reads your blog every day.
He shares it with the kids
with great pride.
Remember your helmet, Pia?
It was stolen.
Who are you?
How do you know us?
- Didn't you recognize me?
- No.
Well, I'm Millimeter.
I'm all grown up now.
Oh my God!
Look at you, handsome!
How did you get here?
I got a letter with a
train ticket attached.
It was an invitation for me to study here.
Rancho is unbelievable!
Where is that idiot?
Dorje, try it yourself.
Pum pum paara
Pum pum paara pum
Pum pum paara goes my silly heart
Every night you ride into my dreams
on a scooter, dressed as a bride.
Instead of a veil,
you lift your helmet.
And you come closer to kiss me.
Why did you leave without informing me?
No.
Are you married?
What?
No...
What about you?
So?
So what?
Do you love someone?
Zoobi doobi pum paara
Zoobi doobi param pum
See, the noses don't collide, you stupid!
Rancho, you jerk!
Screw you!
- Listen to me...
- No, you listen to me!
- I can explain everything.
- You asshole!
- Moron!
- Scoundrel!
Hit him hard!
Let him go.
On your feet, you scoundrel.
Hey, buddy!
Ranchoddas Chanchad!
How do you do, Teacher?
Wow, you're a teacher in a village!
We studied at the same college.
But you failed miserably.
Instead of becoming an engineer,
you became a teacher.
What's your salary, Chanchad?
Five thousand rupees?
My son's pocket money
is more than your salary.
- Cut the crap.
- Crap is what he gave us!
He wanted to change the education system.
He wanted to change the world.
Finally, what does he change?
Kids' diapers?
I am going to beat him up!
Just relax.
Remember what I had said?
One day, I'll be successful
and you will be a failure!
I need your signature.
Accept your defeat and
acknowledge my success!
- Chatur!
- He's a crazy guy.
Hey, this is Virus's pen!
Where did you get it from?
Forget it, man.
Here's what you can do when your
school needs help or donations.
- He hasn't changed at all!
- Ignore him.
- He is crazy.
- Yes.
The good news is that your name
is not Ranchoddas Chanchad.
I can't imagine myself being called
Pia Chanchad!
What is your real name?
Phunsukh Wangdu.
- Wangdu?
- Pia Wangdu!
- Yes...
You mean, you're a scientist?
- The one with 400 patents?
- Yes.
I won't change my name
after we get married.
- You're the man Chatur kept mentioning?
- Yes!
The Japanese are looking for you?
Are you a scientist,
or a teacher?
I'm a scientist,
but I also teach children.
You're the man, Phunsukh Wangdu!
Yes, I am!
- Silencer!
- Chatur, come back.
Wait a minute!
Wait, I'll have to call him up.
Mr. Wangdu,
I can't believe it's you.
I can't sign the deal
with your company.
Why, sir?
I can't sign it because
you took my pen away!
- The one in your hand! Virus's pen!
- Virus's pen?
- Mr. Wangdu?
- Yes, Chatur?
He's doomed!
He is screwed.
I hope our personal problems
won't affect this deal.
Chatur! Take that!
I always knew that
you would be successful!
You're lying.
I mean it!
Your Majesty, thou art great!
Accept this humble offering.
Free advice, Mr. Wangdu.
Run for your life!
- Let's go.
- Run!
Rancho, I'll lose my job.
I have kids to look after.
His Holiness Guru Ranchoddas
had correctly stated.
Follow excellence and
success will chase you!