More.
Another.
Careful, señor.
Hot day like today...
...too much oil in the machine...
...can cause it to blow a gasket.
There are two kinds of men
in this world.
Those who drink...
...and those who pour.
Shut up and fill my glass.
Hey, you two.
Yes, you.
I used to be just like you.
Worked dirt for the man
till my hands bled.
But no more.
Because I learned that a man
can never drink his fill...
...by waiting in line for the tap.
Listen to him.
He can teach you something!
Hey, how you doing, boss?
Good to see you, my friend.
You know, I never pegged you
for such a deep thinker.
I keep thinking I should write a book.
Maybe, maybe...
So, what brings you to this
burro's asshole of a town?
I knew I would find you here.
Don't you have something to deliver?
Cutting it close, aren't you?
Lots of time.
Tortuga may be slow out of the gate,
but he always...
Finishes first.
Yes, I know.
Just like your namesake.
I like the way you talk, Tortuga.
Yeah?
You've got such a way with words.
They flow like a waterfall.
I like that about you.
I'm so stupid.
I missed your birthday.
No, I feel terrible.
So bad I came all the way here
to this burro's asshole...
...to give you your present.
Present?
Come on, boss.
No need to go through the trouble.
Forget it, I wanted to.
I have it for you in the back.
- Back there?
- Yes. Come. Follow me.
It's perfect!
Do you really like it?
I love it!
What a great pet it will make.
Thank you, boss!
Excellent.
Let me sign it for you.
Let me sign it...
..."For the big talker."
Gentlemen. Welcome.
Thank you for coming.
Any difficulty at the border?
The day I can't get across the border
is the day I retire.
Please, come in.
I apologise that it's not
wheelchair accessible.
My apologies, Gustavo.
Of course,
you should have been advised.
It's your territory,
you had a right to bless the order.
We had no reason to believe
the man was of concern to you.
Indeed, he is.
So you're in business with
this Heisenberg.
I don't know him by that name, but yes.
I've made no secret of the fact that...
...I have always done business
with certain local manufacturers.
You and I,
we still make money together.
It's never affected our relationship.
Don Salamanca had a
nephew named Tuco.
Yes, I knew of him.
Then perhaps you know Don Salamanca
mentored him in the business.
Thought of Tuco as a son.
When Don Salamanca was no longer
able, Tuco took over for his uncle.
He was a key man in our
organisation north of the border.
He was loyal.
This Heisenberg, Walter White...
...he was one of Tuco's local suppliers.
Until he betrayed Tuco.
So now you see,
blood must be repaid by blood.
Tuco's cousins here...
...they have the right
to exact vengeance.
The Salamanca family, the cartel...
...everyone stands shoulder
to shoulder on this.
Don Salamanca.
Gentlemen.
I feel your loss deeply.
Please accept my condolences.
I have no issue with
your right to vengeance.
But I am presently engaged in
business with this man.
When our business is done...
...he will no longer be
of any concern to me.
Until then...
...I need him alive.
Excuse us.
I don't tell you how to
fry your chickens, Gustavo.
You should really leave matters
of my organisation's politics to me.
Do I not run my own territory?
Of course you do.
And I will advise them to be patient.
But I recommend you finish your
business with the man quickly.
Or you risk losing the
good graces of the cartel.
That would not be wise.
And those boys inside...
...I cannot guarantee
that they will listen.
They are not like you and I.