Why?
Why is this still under discussion?
I don't like him.
I don't care who he knows.
We're supposed to trust
him with our products.
Big man.
Big Generalissimo!
Big fry cook is more like it.
The "Chicken Man."
You will do what you want.
But you have my vote.
Never trust a South American.
Dirty, dirty people.
He broke my toy! He broke my toy!
He was just having fun.
You'll get over it.
No! I hate him! I wish he was dead!
Grab your old uncle a beer,
would you?
No, no. A cold one.
This is what you wanted.
Your brother dead. Right?
You're going to have to
try harder than that...
...if you want to save him.
How much longer do you think
he has down there?
One minute? Maybe more? Maybe less?
Family is all.
Finish him.
Too easy.