It came out of nowhere.
You gotta help us.
Look at all this damn water. Don't drink that.
Ain't no telling if it's gonna be poison.
Nothing ordinary.
How's Junior?
Exactly what I expected.
He hasn't said a word since we told him it was going back.
I spoke to the dealership, they didn't wanna take it.
What?
It's in perfect condition.
- It's got 17 miles on the odometer.
- I know.
I spent an hour sweet-talking the
manager down to a restocking fee.
Eight hundred dollars.
Eight hundred dollars? For two days?
Well, the law says they don't have to take it back at all.
All right, here's the registration,
the window sticker, the receipt.
Make sure you talk to the general manager.
His name is Glenn.
Glenn.
Call me if there's a problem. And please just don't -
Don't tangle with anyone.
Fine.
Walt.
Shit.
Yes, hello.
I need a cab.
Yes, thank you. The name is White.
I'm at the Pavilion parking lot on University.
Oh, yes, that's right. Just south of the airport.
Oh, that would be great, thank you.
How long do you think that would take?
No, I'm sure he'll see me.
Thank you.
Contrition?
Hey, there is total contrition here.
There's mountains of contrition.
"Fan-tan-tastic." I will messenger them over right away.
Oh, and about that other thing unrelated, yes, I can get you in...
...but I gotta warn you, the eighth hole is murder.
Oh, yeah. You wanna make it interesting?
Great. Tee time is 7 a.m. sharp.
Prepare to have your ass handed to you.
Okay. Bye.
He was headed for destruction of property.
Since it's your property...
...I sweated him down to misdemeanour trash burning.
Now, the only thing is, it's not gonna be free.
There's a 5 grand fine, 600 for towing and disposal...
...3 grand to steam-clean the blacktop.
So bottom line, your little joyride is gonna set you back...
...about 52,000 bucks.
So was it worth it?
I don't need to hear the blow-by-blow. Just tell me it's done.
Oh, I'm sorry. Did I wake you?
I caught this thing before it got into the system.
Your record stays clean, the wife never finds out.
I've been working magic here. I could at least get an attaboy.
Fine. Rebel without a cause, give.
What is it? Fring?
He will see me dead.
And there's nothing I can do about it.
All that's left is to wait.
And we're sure about this.
Because Pinkman says he needs you too much.
Pinkman says.
Unless...
...you could help me find a third party.
What third party?
Someone who can ameliorate the situation.
Let's ditch the thesaurus, all right?
You talking about a hitman?
Assuming that's still what they're called.
Wrong answer.
That's what the kids call "epic fail."
All I would need is a phone number. I'd do the rest.
Saul, there'd be a finder's fee.
A big one.
If you held my feet to the fire, I could come up with names.
One or two guys west of the Rockies who do this work.
But guess what. These guys?
They know Mike and Mike knows them.
Mike knows everyone who does this?
Who do you think gave me their names?
All right. Okay, plan B. Look, we go outside my network.
Craigslist. Soldier of Fortune.
Let's say we get lucky. I mean, incredibly lucky...
...and find a guy who's not a cop...
...or some kind of survivalist nut-job wannabe.
How good is good enough?
Whatever goombah we buy is gonna come head-to-head with Mike.
And Gus Fring?
Hey, just winging that guy is not gonna
"ameliorate" your situation.
Not by a damn sight.
I've tried to solve this, but I can't get anywhere near him.
You can't get near him?
Why don't you ask your partner?
Yeah, I saw him.
And you tell Saul before you tell me?
Look, he's my lawyer, same as yours.
Every time I go over there, Saul hassles me about Mike.
He's still scared the dude's gonna come break his legs.
So I give him the latest.
What happened exactly?
I was at a diner with Mike and he just shows up.
They send me outside and the two of them talk.
That's it.
So this is, like, a regular thing?
How close were you to him?
Close.
I mean, closer than you and me right now.
Did he speak to you?
It was over in 10 seconds.
Would you just answer?
He said, he sees things in people.
What things?
What people?
Me.
He said, he sees something in me.
A month ago, Gus was trying to kill both of us.
And now he pulls you out of the lab and employs you as what?
An assistant gunman?
A tough guy?
Does that make any sense to you?
He says, he sees something in you.
What kind of game is he playing?
Does he think you're that naïve?
He can't truly think that you'd forget -
Well, let alone Gale, let alone Victor...
...and all the horror that goes along with all of that.
What about this girlfriend of yours...
...and her little brother?
I mean, the man looked you straight in the eye...
...and told you, "No more children."
But that very night, that little boy...
...he just -
He winds up...
Gus can't possibly think that you'd forget that.
- Okay.
- All I'm just saying is that...
...is it possible that he would
think that you're that weak-willed?
Drop the sales pitch.
I'll do it.
You'll do what?
I'll kill him.
First chance I get.
Piña colada? More like stale bubblegum.
Does anyone want their car to smell
like the bottom of a 6th-grader's desk?
Okay. Hemp? Really?
I know. But you know what they say. "The customer's always right."
Speaking of customer, it's not too late to have a grand opening.
I was thinking huge party, balloons, bouncy house for the kids...
...you know, make a splash, get on TV.
Let people know they won't face the
eyebrows of doom when they come in.
Marie, how's Hank doing?
You know what? He's doing better.
- Really?
- Yeah. He -
Lately, his moods improved and he's like a maniac with his PT.
That's fantastic.
Yeah, don't get me wrong, he's got a long way to go, but he -
- Yeah.
- Oh, hey.
- Hey. Hi, Walt. It's good to see you.
- Hey. You too.
Hey, your cashier here is quite the salesperson.
She just talked me into something
called the Orbital Paste Wax Buff.
Oh, yeah, it's very important to maintain your clear coat.
Boy, once that's goes -
Oh, yeah.
Hi.
Bogdan was averaging 19 cars during rush hour...
...and we are already up to 22. Twenty-two actual cars.
Last night, I deposited $3800.
Jesus.
How much is that?
Two hundred seventy-four thousand dollars, give or take.
- Give or take?
- Yeah.
I haven't counted it.
Wait.
Two hundred and seventy-four -
And this is how often?
Every two weeks.
Thursday's good for a drop-off?
But, Walt...
...are you telling me you make $7,125,000 a year?
Seven and a half even, before expenses.
But I can't -
- This is too much.
- So it's more...
...than you thought...
...and this is somehow bad news?
No, that's not the point.
I mean, there's no car wash in the world...
...that could do this kind of business.
I mean, this is nine months work here, minimum.
Seven million? That could take years.
So set some aside. Save it for a rainy day.
Save it? Where? Save it where?
I can't go to the bank with it. I sure can't leave it here.
Wait a minute.
Is this all 50s?
- Who pays for a car wash with a 50?
- Skyler, I didn't ask you to do this.
I was under the impression that you had this under control.
I just didn't expect this amount of money.
- The 50s are gonna be a problem.
- That's what this is, problem solving.
This is a simple division of labour.
I bring money. You launder money. This is what you wanted.
I never wanted any of this.
I've gotta go.
If you want out, just say that you want out.
Okay, then.
You're telling me you made this in the lab?
Why not?
Making it in his own lab seemed appropriate.
There's not much of it.
We had more for Tuco.
It's enough.
This is still the best way.
You go after him with a gun, you'll never get out of it alive.
But with this?
You slip it into his food or drink.
There shouldn't be any taste or smell.
Thirty-six hours later...
A man his age, working as hard as he does...
...no one will be surprised.
What about Mike?
Mike can have his suspicions, but that's all they'll be.
Please, one homicidal maniac at a time.
I don't know when I'm gonna see Gus again.
I mean, if ever.
Keep it with you.
When you have the opportunity...
...be ready.
What if they search me?
Will they do that?
It's the wrong way around.
It's my lucky cigarette.
Well...
...whatever you do, don't smoke it.
You know they have a drive-thru, right?
No, this is good.
Could use the exercise, get the blood pumping.
Don't worry, you're not gonna have to pick me up.
Might take me a while, but I'll get there.
Jesus, ain't we a pair.
Hey, you must really like chicken.
V-8, 470 horses, 20-inch rims, satellite radio, Bluetooth.
Zero to 60 in 4.7 seconds.
Whoa, whoa, what do you mean, on a lark?
Spur of the moment, your dad ups and
buys you a brand-new Challenger?
Yeah, I barely got it around the block...
...and Mom said we couldn't afford it so they took it back.
Do you know how long I had it? Fifteen hours.
Well, hey, buddy, let me tell you something.
When I was your age...
...I'd have given my left nut to
drive a car like that for 15 minutes.
Seriously, how does that happen?
Well, we were looking at used cars and I kind of -
You guilted him into it. I know. I hear you.
You pulled the old, "Poor little me and my troubles," am I right?
- Maybe.
- You flew too close to the sun.
You'd let him buy you a clunker, you'd be driving now...
...instead of borrowing mom's hooptie.
Agent Schrader.
- How are you doing?
- Well, thank you. Good to see you.
Do you remember Mr. Fring?
- How are you?
- Well. Nice to see you again.
It's a pleasure to see you. You're looking well.
Yeah, well, you know, chalk it up
to clean living and vitamin pills.
I must apologise. If I had seen you come in...
...there'd have been no question of accepting your money.
In the future, feel free to ask for me.
A DEA hero should never have to pay for a meal at Pollos Hermanos.
No kidding? Well, I'll take you up on that, for sure.
And how are your mother and father?
They're good.
- The chicken is great.
- Thank you.
If ever you're interested in rewarding part-time work...
...perhaps something after school? My door is open.
Sounds good.
I don't know about this one. He might eat up all your profits.
I'll let you finish your meal. Can I get you anything else?
- A refill, perhaps?
- No, thank you. I'm good.
- Sure. Take a Diet Coke, thank you.
- Of course.
So where are we going?
Oh, big doings today.
The order of the day is eyes open, mouth shut.
What's up?
Test.
You got me?
Count off.
Let's go.
Right here. Leave the wrap on, please.
You know how to make coffee?
Sure.
There you go.
- You want a rundown?
- Please.
Three guys up at the gate, two visible, one in the blind.
We got five guys down here with a backup out of sight.
I got Tyrus down in the tree line with a Barrett. 50.
Planted him there last night, in case we had any early arrivals.
I don't have an extra holster.
Stick this in your pocket. Keep it out of sight.
If you're gonna be here today, you're gonna have a gun.
It's loaded?
I don't wanna see that in your hand unless you see me with mine.
Emergency only.
First car is coming.
All right, what's the order of the day?
Eyes open, mouth shut.
A lot of guns.
Nobody's asking you to give up yours.
You wanna sweep the place before you bring in your guys?
I am the guy.
All right, then.
Welcome.
Where is the rest of your party?
I am the only one coming.
And why is that?
My employers feel I can adequately represent their interests.
Please, sit.
This is my offer.
In consideration of our previous relationship...
...I will make a one-time payment...
...of 50 million U.S. dollars.
In return our business is concluded.
No further payments. No further contact.
An absolute severance.
You have no response?
Yes or no?
You know what the Cartel wants.
Anything else would be a waste of time.
Is it to be yes... or no?
A hard way to begin a negotiation.
This is not a negotiation.
You got something of mine?
Glove box.
Figure I better teach you how to shoot.
Could be things are gonna get hairy.
What is this?
I mean, you're giving me a gun...
...and now I'm, like, part of the team or whatever?
He said he sees something in me.
Like what?
If I had to put it in a word...
...I'd guess loyalty.
Loyalty.
Only maybe you got it for the wrong guy.
Jesse?
- Hey.
Long time, no see.
How you doing?
Yeah, you know...
- ...good.
- Good.
Good.
Okay, we're gonna get started. You coming in?
So the truth is, we can't change the past, what's done is done.
We've gotta own our actions, but putting ourselves on trial...
...acting as our own judge,
jury and executioner, it's not the answer.
A lot of the time, all that judging does...
...is just ensure that we're gonna repeat the cycle.
Right?
"I'm such an asshole.
It's totally hopeless, what's the point?
I think I'll have a hit."
Jesse...
...what's going on with you these days?
I went back to the crystal.
You sober now?
Yeah.
Four days.
Big whoop, right?
Hey, four days is four days.
You're here.
You still...
...working at the laundry?
How are things there?
Sucks ass.
Anything you wanna talk about?
A couple of weeks back...
...I killed a dog.
You hit it with your car?
No.
I put him down.
I watched him go.
I was looking him straight in the eye.
He didn't know what was happening. He didn't know why. He -
He was just scared.
And then he was gone.
He was suffering.
It was a kindness.
No, he wasn't sick.
No. He was just, like -
I don't know, like, a...
...problem dog.
What did he do?
Bite someone?
No, this dog never -
Never bit anybody.
You pick up the rock, you go right to the dark side.
Anything can happen.
It ain't no rock that made me do it.
What was the problem? Why did you kill him?
Watch the crosstalk, please.
Maybe it's not the details that matter, right?
How do you feel about what you did, Jesse?
I don't know.
Who cares how you feel?
What kind of person kills a dog for no reason?
Colleen.
Put an ad in the paper, drop him off at a shelter.
You don't just sit there and talk about
killing a helpless, innocent animal.
We're not here to sit in judgement.
Why not?
Why not? Maybe she's right.
Maybe I should have put it in the paper.
I should've done something different.
The thing is, if you just do stuff and nothing happens...
...what's it all mean?
What's the point?
Oh, right, this whole thing is about self-acceptance.
Kicking yourself doesn't give meaning to anything.
So I should stop judging...
- ...and accept?
- It's a start.
So no matter what I do...
...hooray for me because I'm a great guy?
It's all good?
No matter how many dogs I kill, I just,
what, do an inventory and accept?
I mean, you back your truck over
your own kid and you, like, accept?
- What a load of crap?
- Hey, Jesse.
I know you're in pain.
No, you know what?
Why I'm here in the first place?
Is to sell you meth.
You're nothing to me but customers!
I made you my bitch.
You okay with that?
You accept?
No.
About time.
Jesse.
Bring a light over here, will you?
Do you see any residue there?
- Where?
- Here. On the bottom, right there.
It's been a week. What's going on?
I haven't seen him.
I didn't think so. But I'll just give it another shot anyway.
- Hey.
- Hey, buddy. Look at that.
Graduated to doorman. Finally found your calling.
Oh, little whiskers, Marie.
What did you do?
Show your barber a picture of a dog's
ass and said, "I'll take that"?
Charming as usual.
Welcome back.
- Looking good, Marie.
- Thanks, Steve.
- Good to see you. How you doing?
- He's fine. We can take it from here.
- Yeah.
- If you wanna hold his elbow.
No, no, no. You keep your mitts off me. I'm good. I'm good.
Hey.
Good luck.
Let's go, we're running late. Come on.
Hank, seeing you walk in here,
I can't tell you what that means to all of us.
Your progress, it's incredible.
Yeah, well, chalk it up to clean living and vitamin pills.
- Steve tell you his news?
- What?
Finally got your period?
I made GS-14.
Wow, that's all right, man.
Next stop: Washington, D.C. Sitting behind a desk...
...papers piled so high, you can't see over them.
Hey, better you than me, buddy.
Seriously, congratulations, buddy.
Thanks.
Steve said you might have something for us.
Yeah, maybe. You guys are gonna have to tell me.
Remember my pal Tim Roberts?
APD detective?
Yeah, well, he's working on a murder case.
The victim's a 34-year-old male Caucasian...
...by the name of Gale Boetticher.
One night last month, Boetticher opens the door...
...takes a bullet to the face from a person or persons unknown.
Now, this Gale Boetticher is a bona fide chemistry genius.
I mean, he's got degrees up the wazoo, right?
And, well, as you might expect, he's a nerd's nerd.
Vegan, sandals and socks kind of guy.
As it turns out, he's also an A-number-one meth cook.
And what caught my eye is his speciality product is blue.
So, what are you thinking?
This is your Heisenberg?
No. What I think we got here is Heisenberg's former cook...
...and maybe a line on Heisenberg himself.
Anyway, lo and behold, amidst all the hippie-dippy nonsense...
...I find this.
Now, this here, I do a little Google-fu...
...and I realise it's a parts number specifically for this baby.
That there is a high-volume HEPA industrial air filtration system.
That's a 300,000-dollar gadget.
Perfect for a pharmaceutical plant or microchip factory...
...or maybe the biggest meth lab north of the border.
Okay.
So this little dingus here is manufactured...
Madrigal Electromotive.
I call their Houston office, I get through
to the nicest little 20-year-old temp.
I use the Schrader sweet-talk.
Before you know it, she's pulling files.
Six months ago, one of these systems
was shipped to a depot here in ABQ.
Who signed for it?
Gale Boetticher.
So I asked my new girlfriend,
"Who paid for it?" And she says, "Nobody."
They have no record that anybody actually paid for this thing.
So I go back and push more and before you know it...
...the temp's gone, there's no address.
I'm talking to some snot-nose lawyer
who's asking me for my badge number.
Brick wall.
So I take a peek into Madrigal Electromotive.
Now, Madrigal is based in Hanover, Germany...
...but they're what they call "highly diversified."
Industrial equipment, global shipping, major construction...
...and a tiny little foothold in American fast food...
...specifically a local chain.
Pollos Hermanos.
Okay. So what, right? Boetticher's dead.
I got no line on who's been bankrolling him...
...or where his lab was.
The whole thing's a snipe hunt, right?
But now I get this crazy idea...
...and I can't shake it.
I mean, I stay up nights staring at the ceiling...
...trying to make sense of it. That napkin.
I told you Boetticher's vegan.
We're talking this guy makes his own fermented lentil bread...
...or whatever the hell that is.
What's a vegan doing in a fried chicken joint?
Maybe he's meeting somebody.
Like who?
Well, like, maybe...
...this guy.
I mean, what do we know about Gustavo Fring, huh?
This whole friend-of-law-enforcement thing?
Could be a case of, "keep your friends
close but your enemies closer."
He's got the money to finance this operation.
Maybe he's got the connections too. Maybe, just maybe...
...he's our guy.
Hank, no offence, but I think you're really reaching.
If your guy had his meeting at KFC...
...you wouldn't immediately assume
he's sitting down with Colonel Sanders.
You know, I -
I couldn't agree more, guys.
Gustavo Fring, blue meth, you know.
The whole thing is off-the-map nuts.
I ought to be wearing a tinfoil hat, you know?
Except...
...I can't seem to wrap my mind around this one little thing...
...and that is, what are Gustavo Fring's fingerprints...
...doing in Gale Boetticher's apartment?