- Where are we?
- At the Dawn of Time.
- Ah!
- Well, look who's finally...
- Awake.
- Alex.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
- No, no, no, it's okay.
It's okay.
Are you okay?
Did you have a bad dream?
- I don't know.
I'm...
How did I get here?
- Well, you fell asleep
in front of the TV,
and you just looked so peaceful,
so I didn't have the heart
to move you to the bed.
- (WHISPERING)
The... the Dawn of Time.
Dawn of Time.
- Is that what you were
watching before you nodded off?
- Wait.
What is...
This isn't right.
Well, I mean, it's right,
but it's not right
because it's right.
- Uh-huh.
I see the White Martian
did a number on you last night.
- White Martian?
(WHISPER)
White Martian.
- Listen, I gotta run.
Kelly and I are trying out
a new indoor rowing class
in downtown, so are you... you
sure you're okay?
(QUIETLY)
- I'm fine.
(CLEARS THROAT)
I'm fine.
- Okay.
- Alex.
- Yeah?
- I love you.
- I love you too.
(SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC)
- (SIGHS)
(PHONE VIBRATING)
Nia.
- Kara.
- It's good to hear your voice.
- Well, it would be better
to see my face.
Where are you?
The ceremony's about to start.
- Ceremony?
- They're awarding
the Nobel Peace Prize
any minute.
Don't worry, I saved you a seat,
but that lady from the gazette
is giving me angry eyes.
If you miss this,
Andrea's gonna blow a gasket.
- (WHOOSHES)
- Please take your seats.
- Good timing.
- (CHUCKLES)
Hey, uh, I had a really weird
dream last night.
Could you maybe help me
interpret it?
- What happened?
- Oh, uh, the world ended,
but, like, all the worlds.
All of them.
- That's dramatic even for us.
- And now I'm proud
to introduce the winner
of this year's
Nobel Peace Prize,
Lex Luthor.
(APPLAUSE)
(FOREBODING MUSIC)
- Nia, Nia, am I still dreaming?
- I know, right.
It is so great when this award
goes to someone
who actually deserves it.
♪ ♪
(SPIRITED ORCHESTRAL MUSIC)
- We live in dangerous times.
Earth is a dangerous place.
I suppose that's why people
love superheroes so much.
The power, the chutzpah
of someone who can
fly faster
than a speeding bullet.
But that's what makes this
so special.
I don't have any powers.
I can't leap tall buildings
in a single bound,
but I have dedicated my life
to fighting
on the side of humanity,
and to be recognized for that
is more than I can
put into words,
so I will just say
I stand with mankind.
(APPLAUSE)
(FOREBODING MUSIC)
- I'm gonna throw up.
- Are you still feeling weird?
We should get you
to the med bay.
You did not seem okay
this morning.
- Oh, no, no, I'm fine.
I'm just disoriented.
The world is... what was Lex
doing up there?
- Well, they keep throwing
all these awards at him.
He doesn't usually
accept them in person,
but this one meant a lot to him.
- People think he's a good guy?
- Kara, we're talking about
Lex Luther.
He's the best guy.
- No, he's not.
He's a psychopathic lunatic.
- What?
No, he's the boss.
And he's your
number one supporter.
I mean, besides Lena.
And all the times that they
defended you to the president...
What has gotten into you.
- Hang on, what-wha... wait,
did you just say "boss"?
(SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC)
(FOREBODING MUSIC)
I don't...
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Alex, are we...
- Supergirl.
- J'onn.
- I know you must be confused.
I was too, but it happened.
It all happened.
- Why are we the only two
that remember?
- What are we that they are not?
- Paragons.
We helped Oliver
restart the universe.
- And this is the result.
I suspect there will be
more such changes
that are yet
to reveal themselves.
(ALARM BLARING)
- Well, there's something
happening downtown.
- I'll send a team.
- No, no, no, it's fine.
I need to punch something.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
(SCREAMING)
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
(SIRENS WHOOP)
♪ ♪
- Hey.
- Look who came to join the fun.
- I'm sorry.
Who are you?
- Weather Witch.
And you are no match
for my wrath.
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
- Oh, look, I'm having
not so great a day,
which is actually your bad luck.
- Ugh.
Ah!
- Sorry, she's one of mine.
- Well, what's she doing
on my Earth?
- What?
- Wait, wait, what are
you doing on my Earth?
Your Earth?
This is my Earth.
- I thought...
- Supergirl, Flash, I just
love it when you guys team up.
Would you sign this
for me please?
- Oh, sure, um...
- Wait, you know both of us?
- And it's normal to see
us together?
- Well, normally you'd also have
Green Arrow and a Legend or two.
Last year,
even Batwoman joined in.
Make that out to Marv.
M-A-R-V.
- Thank you.
- Marv, M-A-R-V.
You're welcome.
Marv, as far as you know,
how long have Supergirl and I
and all the rest of us
been working together
on this Earth?
- Uh, since forever?
♪ ♪
(SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC)
(INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER)
(EERIE MUSIC)
- The hell?
♪ ♪
Call for help.
Now!
♪ ♪
(EERIE MUSIC)
- How did I get back here?
(CAR HORN BLARES)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(PHONE RINGING)
Ray, where are you?
- Hey, Cap, over here.
- Ray.
Hey, hey.
- Hey, you okay?
Not that I'm ever one
to question a hug.
- What was the last thing
that you remember?
- Uh, portaling to this
location on your orders.
- You don't remember coming
here for trivia night
and being teleported
to an alternate Waverider
to stop the multiverse
from being destroyed?
- Wait, was there a crossover?
Were we invited?
Did we win?
- That's certainly how it looks.
- Did you just hear...
- It's good to see
you're both safe.
- J'onn, that's a neat trick.
- Wait, you know J'onn Jonnz
from Supergirl's Earth?
- Of course I know J'onn.
- Wait, go back.
Supergirl has her own Earth?
- Not anymore.
When we restarted the universe,
our worlds combined,
and only we Paragons know
it was ever any different.
- Okay, sorry, guy,
I'm a little lost here.
- Here, this'll be faster.
- Whoa, there was a multiverse.
It all got destroyed.
There's an evil Batman,
and there's a me
that's a super me?
- It'll take him some time
to assimilate
to this new paradigm.
I have been going
from city to city
restoring the memories of
our compatriots as best I can.
- And what about Oliver?
- There's been no sign of him.
(SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC)
- Hey, where are you going?
- To find my friend.
♪ ♪
Oliver!
- Sara.
- I need to talk to you guys...
- We already know.
We already know.
- Martian J'onn came by
and gave us
a splitting headache.
- It all happened, didn't it?
- He died twice, Sara.
- (WHISPERS) Yeah.
- I wasn't there both times.
Both times I failed him.
Dig, you...
- I'm so sorry.
It's okay.
I wasn't there.
He was my brother.
- I know.
Listen to me.
Look, we all... we all died,
the entire universe,
the multiverse.
Now we're back
that means, Oliver,
he might be back too.
- After the brain dump...
We had Felicity run
a global search.
I mean, nobody's better
at finding people,
but they've got to be here
to be found.
- You don't know.
Look, when Oliver died,
he became something else.
He... he called it the Spectre.
Then maybe, Felicity, she just
can't find him in that form.
Dig, she just can't find him
in this form...
- Sara...
Sara, gone is gone.
He's gone.
(MELANCHOLIC MUSIC)
♪ ♪
(DEVICE CLICKING)
- J'onn,
what are you doing here?
Is something wrong?
- Not anymore, no thanks to him.
- Do you know why
he's like this?
- And now so do you.
(EERIE MUSIC)
- Oliver!
- (SCREAMS)
- This is all his fault.
He's the one who released
the Anti-Monitor.
- He paid dearly
for his misjudgment,
but not as much as some others.
- Ah!
Ah.
What happened?
Where am I?
How did I get here?
- You nearly damned us
all to hell, Nash Wells!
- Well, that's an introduction.
Who the hell are you
and what are you talking about?
- You need to stay calm.
Your system's still recovering.
- (LAUGHS)
You... you need to calm down.
I'm not gonna stay here,
get lectured by
some government suit who...
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
God.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
- And so you should be.
This is all your fault!
- It is my fault.
But you... you solved it.
You and the others,
you saved the universe.
You fixed my mistake.
Right?
- Not entirely.
(FOREBODING MUSIC)
- It's true.
We all live
on the same Earth now.
Our Earths must have merged
when we helped Oliver
reboot the universe.
- I can't believe it.
- What are you guys doing here?
- I had to see if it was true.
The DEO, CatCo,
all of National City
is on this Earth now.
Even Argo's up there.
We did it.
We saved everyone.
- Not everyone.
(MELANCHOLIC MUSIC)
♪ ♪
- Oliver.
He didn't make it.
- Guess we just
have to face facts.
- No, that's not... that's...
- Why did he give everyone else
a fresh start but not himself?
- Maybe this was
the only way, Kara.
Maybe his sacrifice
made all of this possible.
Him for us.
(ELECTRONIC BEEPING)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
- What is that?
- We're being attacked.
- By who?
♪ ♪
- You wouldn't believe it
if I told you.
(PEDESTRIANS SCREAMING)
♪ ♪
It's a giant Beebo.
- Beebo hungry.
(ROARS)
- (GIGGLES)
- How the hell
did Beebo get here?
- Isn't the more
pressing question
why is there a giant Beebo
walking down the street?
- Well, this wouldn't be
the first time.
It's a long story.
- That's right.
Wally told us about
the time you guys used
those totems to turn
yourselves into a giant Beebo
to fight a time demon.
- I guess it's not a long story.
- Could that be
what's happening here?
- Ava, Nate, you there?
I need a twenty
on Behrad and his totem.
- Sara, are you okay?
Ray called us to tell us you
were on some special mission.
- But he's a little flimsy
with the deets,
so what's the haps, Cap?
- Yeah, we've been busy
saving the multiverse.
- You got shanghaied into
another crossover, didn't you?
- Hmm, yeah, kind of.
- Whoa, whoa.
Did they kidnap you?
- This is
a classic crossover move.
We tell 'em we're too busy,
they commit a felony.
- Guys, Beebo is rampaging
through Star City.
Does Behrad have his totem?
- Beebo?
That doesn't make any sense.
You would need all six totems
to make that happen,
and Behrad's definitely
still on the ship.
- All right, I gotta go.
- Wait, do you need help?
- No, stay in DC.
I don't want any more
of my people
getting roped into this mess.
- Well, here's the thing.
One of us is
kind of already there.
- Who?
- And who should I
make this out to?
- Doris.
I'm such a huge fan, Rebecca.
I mean, what should I call you?
- Rebecca's fine.
To Doris.
Thanks for the passion, love...
(BUILDING RUMBLES)
(CAR HONKS)
(PEDESTRIANS SCREAMING)
(RUMBLING CONTINUES)
- (GIGGLES)
(PEDESTRIANS SCREAMING)
- Fur ball.
- Oh my.
- (LAUGHING)
- Oh, man, I can't believe
Nate's gonna miss seeing Beebo.
He's gonna be so jealous.
- Here he comes.
- What's the plan?
- (LAUGHS)
Smile, Beebo.
- What?
Are you...
- Oh, sorry,
you guys don't wanna be in it?
Oh, bad timing.
- Is this seriously
happening right now?
- Well, maybe it's a good thing.
- Guess we could all
use the distraction.
- Right, compartmentalize,
focus on the work, good idea.
- Guys, Beebo's still
on the warpath.
Any suggestions on
how we take him down?
- Hey, what is that?
- That's a utility truck.
Why?
- Are you guys ready to do
a tag team trip up?
- Yeah.
What do you have in mind?
- All right, Supergirl,
Atom, keep him contained.
Flash, use those cables
to your left.
- Got it.
- All right.
- Can do.
(SPIRITED ORCHESTRAL MUSIC)
- Beebo want cuddles!
♪ ♪
- Is this actually happening?
- Is this what all
the crossovers are like?
- Yes and not exactly.
- I'm never letting my child
watch that show again.
- Done.
- All right, now get him moving.
- Die, fur ball!
- Mick?
- That blue bastard
ruined my book signing!
- Okay,
everybody get ready to pull.
- Here, take it.
Take it.
- Ow.
- The bigger they are...
- The harder they...
- Fall!
- Ah!
- Ugh.
- Whoa, whoa.
- Oh, thanks Supergirl.
- What the hell?
- (GIGGLES)
- Guys, something's off.
I'm not reading
any known elements,
nothing off the periodic table.
(DRAMATIC ELECTRONIC MUSIC)
- I don't think the rules apply
to 50-foot talking plush toy.
- Hey, hey, Kate's here too.
That's... uh, sorry.
What were you saying?
- (GIGGLES)
- It's unnatural.
- Alien?
- Hey.
- Or magic?
Sara, don't you
and the Legends deal with
that kind of stuff all the time?
- Or maybe it's just here
to keep us talking.
- A diversion.
- But for what?
- I know what I'd do.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
- It is finally time
for Sargon the Sorcerer
to claim his reward!
Oh, and buy that beautiful
timeshare in Bogota.
(WHIMSICAL MUSIC)
- Come on, man, Beebo?
Is nothing sacred?
- You know, it's a smart move.
Distracting all the fuzz
with giant fuzz, but someone
should have told you.
Beebo, he's off limits.
(SPIRITED ORCHESTRAL MUSIC)
♪ ♪
- Beebo!
- Oh!
- (LAUGHS)
Got him again.
- Pee-ew.
(UPBEAT POP MUSIC)
- So how normal
was that for everyone?
And don't say very.
- Oh, well, with this
new Earth, just may be.
- (CHUCKLES)
Well, dear God, I hope not.
- What is that?
- Alcohol.
- Mm.
- Rory, huh?
We had a Rory once on our team.
- We did.
(FOREBODING MUSIC)
- What's this?
- Was there a memo that went out
on how to infiltrate
our secret bunker?
- Why are you here?
- I'm here to warn you.
You see this?
This gauntlet is primed
to detect antimatter
of which there has been
a massive surge
in the Star City area.
- Okay, well, you're about
two hours too late.
- Yeah, already took care of it.
- Did you really?
My readings say different.
This thing ain't over.
As a matter of fact,
it's just beginning.
♪ ♪
(DEVICE HUMMING)
- Something's not right.
- That thing still working?
- Yeah, it's working.
I built it myself.
It's infallible.
- Yeah, but you're still
detecting traces of antimatter.
Then our fight
isn't done, is it?
- (SIGHS) No.
Or worse, it's starting up
all over again.
(FOREBODING MUSIC)
♪ ♪
- Hey.
- How'd you find me?
- You feel that gust of wind
a few seconds ago?
That was me.
I did a quick search
of the whole city for you.
When you didn't come back
for the post-Beebo celebration,
I got a little worried.
- Yeah.
(SIGHS)
See that tree over there?
My sister and I,
we used to race to the top
when we were little.
I'd win every time.
I used to think it was
because I was a better climber,
but now I think
Laurel let me win
'cause she knew
I was a sore loser.
A lot has changed since then.
I was an assassin.
(CHUCKLES)
I was dead, now I'm the captain
of a friggin' time ship.
One thing remains the same.
I'm still a sore loser.
(SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC)
- I know it's... it's hard
not having Oliver here with us.
But look at what
his sacrifice made possible.
Our world is... it's different...
But at least it's safe.
♪ ♪
- He was just the last tether
to my old life, you know?
And he was the only person left
who knew me
when I was just... me.
With him gone,
my connection to this world,
this place, to that tree...
It's gone.
- I know what it's like
to lose family.
My mom, my dad,
each death felt like
there was no moving forward,
like life
would never be the same.
And I was right
it's not the same,
but... somehow it's okay.
Family isn't just the people
that you grew up with.
It's the people you find,
the ones you love,
ones that make you crazy...
Make you smile.
- When did you get so wise?
- The Legends,
they are my family.
They have been for a while.
I guess I just... I always
thought there would be
at least someone who remembered
what I was like
before I got on that boat.
♪ ♪
(ETHEREAL WHOOSHING)
(SPIRITED ORCHESTRAL MUSIC)
♪ ♪
(ETHEREAL SCREAM)
- I thought we got rid
of all those things.
- Barry, Sara,
the shadow demons are back.
I believe we are being hunted.
- If they're hunting
the Paragons, that means...
- Ryan.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC)
(BABY CRIES)
(ETHEREAL WAILING)
♪ ♪
- (ROARS)
(BABY CRYING)
(SPIRITED ORCHESTRAL MUSIC)
- Sara?
What the hell's going on?
- You have to come with me now.
♪ ♪
- All right, Barry, J'onn,
Supergirl, and Batlady
are gathering the troops.
Those attacks were probably
just the first wave.
Assassins sent
to pick us off in pairs.
- How are the shadow demons
even still here?
Didn't Oliver destroy the guy
who controls them?
- Well, not according
to the surge
in antimatter energy
I'm reading.
- The Anti-Monitor is alive?
- But you said Oliver
sacrificed himself
to create this new world.
- Apparently, his sacrifice
didn't kill the Anti-Monitor.
- Well, then how do we do that?
- Well, let's just throw him
into the sun
and let the bastard burn.
- Oh yeah, let's throw him
in the sun
and cause
an antimatter explosion
that obliterates
the solar system.
You know what,
let's not do that.
- At least he's trying
to offer up a solution
instead of being
the cause of the problem.
- That's the solution?
Blow up the solar system?
- Guys, guys, we're all
on the same team, okay?
- No, Scrappy's right.
It's my fault
we're in this mess.
We gotta fix it.
Gotta fix it.
- It's just a little tricky.
The Anti-Monitor
is made of antimatter,
and, like its opposite,
it can neither be created
nor destroyed.
It can only...
- Change form
and move from place to place.
So what if we do just that?
What if we could set off
a chain reaction
that will destabilize his form?
Compressing his molecules
so he's essentially
shrinking for eternity.
- Is that kind of reaction
even possible?
- Sure it is.
I did it a bunch of times by
accident
when I was developing
my ATOM exosuit.
- So you think you can keep him
shrinking indefinitely?
- Essentially, we'd be
sending him to the "atomverse."
- I like to call it
the Microverse.
- Ah, that's better.
Possible trademark issues,
but that's better.
- He could get stuck there
for, like, ever.
- In theory
it could totally work.
But developing
a device in time...
- Leave that to me, D-League.
I just gotta get to STAR Labs.
Scrappy.
- Look, if this goes down
anything like it did
on Earth-38, then things
are gonna get messy.
Geek team, get on it.
Mick, go with 'em,
keep 'em safe.
The rest of us, we'll need to
hold back this incoming army.
(SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC)
♪ ♪
- Hey, this can work, Sara.
I know it can.
- That's what we thought
back at the Dawn of Time.
Here we are back at square one.
- This new Earth
isn't square one.
It's what Oliver gave up
his life to create.
We have to protect it.
If we're gonna go down...
We go down fighting.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
(ETHEREAL WHOOSHING)
- All right, listen up.
I got a ton of those
shadow things descending
on Gardner Pier.
- Copy, we're en route.
(FOREBODING MUSIC)
- This is new.
- New world, new look.
- Cut the chatter, they're here.
♪ ♪
(ETHEREAL WAILING)
- What the hell?
- Was that it?
(ETHEREAL WHOOSHING)
- It's not over yet.
(FOREBODING MUSIC)
♪ ♪
- Paragons, the universal
safeguard meant to thwart me.
It is time to meet your end!
- We'll need a reinforced core
to contain the reaction.
- Titanium?
- No, that's too heavy.
- What we need... what
we need is...
Depleted promethium.
- STAR Labs, I've got shadows
advancing on your position.
- On it.
- It's been a while, Frosty.
You look good.
- Thanks.
I read your book, Rebecca.
- Which one?
I'm very prolific.
- (ETHEREAL WAILING)
- Whoa.
- Do you wanna take this guy,
or should I?
- Ladies first.
- Age before beauty.
- Mm.
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLES)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
Who the hell are you?
- Guy who just saved your ass.
- We had that covered.
- Sure you did.
(ETHEREAL WAILING)
- Company's coming.
You ready?
- I stay ready.
- I am destiny incarnate,
inexorable and inescapable.
You are nothing.
Insects fated to be crushed
beneath my heel
without a moment's thought.
Fighting is useless.
Surrender.
(FOREBODING MUSIC)
- Not today.
Not ever.
- Oliver died so that we
could continue to fight.
He sacrificed everything
for this new world,
and we will not fail him.
We will not fail this world.
For Oliver.
- For Oliver.
- For Oliver!
(TOGETHER)
For Oliver!
(SPIRITED ORCHESTRAL MUSIC)
♪ ♪
- (SHOUTS AGGRESSIVELY)
(FOREBODING MUSIC)
♪ ♪
- The age of heroes ends now!
- Guys, we're gonna need
a bigger bomb.
- Sky team, with me.
- Ray,
how's that shrink bomb coming?
- Well, we could really use
some fast hands.
- Could we ever.
- Barry.
♪ ♪
- Supergirl, look out!
- J'onn!
(ETHEREAL MOANING)
- Where are you from, Sparkles?
- Don't call me Sparkles.
I'm from Freeland.
Martian came, got in my head,
told me y'all were caught up.
(SIGHS)
It's been a weird day.
- (ETHEREAL WAILING)
- That's an understatement.
- All right, what are we making?
- All right, so plans, right?
- Yep.
- Now, this is what
we have to build.
Now, these pieces are all
very volatile.
Be...
(NERVOUS MUMBLING)
- How's this look?
- Okay, that's good.
- Whoa.
- Love when he does that.
- That's perfect, actually.
Okay, so now all we have to do
is get it into direct contact
with the Anti-Monitor
once we've activated it.
- Okay, and to activate it
I just press this button?
- No don't touch that!
- Are you crazy?
- All right, okay, relax, relax.
All right, Ray,
you're coming with me.
- Oh, cool.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
♪ ♪
- No!
- Shadows are on the move again.
Pérez Landing.
- Yeah, we know.
We're here.
(ETHEREAL WAILING)
Barry.
- Bomb's ready.
Ray's running it
to the sky team.
- We're running
out of time here, Ray.
Hurry!
- Hurrying.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC)
♪ ♪
- (GRUNTS)
(SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC)
♪ ♪
- Hope I'm not too late.
- Ray?
- Hang on, Superman.
(DEVICE HUMS)
- (ROARS)
Throw it like a girl.
- Always.
(TRIUMPHANT MUSIC)
- How did you... no!
♪ ♪
- We did it.
We did it!
- Wait, but where's Kal?
- I'm right here.
- Whoa.
- Sorry about that, Superman.
Here you go.
♪ ♪
- Thank you, Ollie.
- My fellow Americans,
today our way of life,
our world,
almost came to an end.
An entity known as
the Anti-Monitor
attacked Earth
intent on its destruction.
Thankfully, we were saved
by Earth's greatest heroes...
- Hey, Sara.
- Hey, sweetie.
Baby, come over here.
Your brother wants
to play with you.
- Their unity and strength
should be an example for us all.
I'm told this assembly was led
by Star City's Oliver Queen
otherwise known
as the Green Arrow.
We give thanks
to these brave women and men
who, with great tenacity,
tireless work,
and the utmost courage,
put their lives on the line
for our country, our planet.
(COMMUNICATOR BEEPS)
- Hey, Lois.
- Clark, I need you to get
to Metropolis now.
It's the boys.
- The boys?
- Yeah, honey, your sons.
- While in
a hard-fought battle,
loss is expected.
It never gets any easier,
so it is with great sadness
that I must inform you
that Oliver Queen
sacrificed his life
for our world's survival.
He is known to us
as the first of our heroes,
and while this is
a devastating loss,
we can take solace in knowing
that he lived as he died,
with honor.
I ask all of you to join me
in a moment of silence
to honor him now.
(MELANCHOLIC MUSIC)
♪ ♪
- A grateful nation thanks you,
Mr. Queen.
May you finally find rest
in the hereafter.
God bless you,
and God bless
the United States of America.
Good night.
- In the end,
there was only one,
a single black infinitude.
Then the infinitude
found release.
(STIRRING ORCHESTRAL MUSIC)
♪ ♪
And finally, the darkness broke,
filling it with life...
♪ ♪
With the multiverse.
Every existence
multiplied by possibility.
And spread out before space
and time in infinite measure.
♪ ♪
Civilizations rose and fell...
And rose again across
reality's grasping expanse.
Life, a precious gift,
persevering
in the face of every obstacle...
Until, finally,
the age of heroes was born
- Thanks for saving us, Oliver.
The world has hope again.
I have hope again.
We'll never forget you.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
♪ ♪
- Thanks for believing in me
even when I didn't.
You had this way of bringing
out the very best in all of us.
I'm gonna miss you, man.
- I've lost a lot of people
that I love.
But I never imagined my life
without you in it.
You were always there for me.
And now...
Ollie, you changed my fate
for the better.
Thank you.
♪ ♪
- I never met Oliver, but he
must have been a good dude.
But why'd you choose
a condemned building?
- What?
No, this is not
a condemned building.
No, listen, this is an old
STAR Labs Research Facility
that nobody uses,
and what's even better,
no one knows it exists.
- Good for you.
- No, good for us.
I figure we could all
use this to gather
if anything ever happens again.
- It's a great idea, Barry.
- Thanks, Superman.
- It's a better option than
you all dropping by the DEO.
- Why do we even need it?
I mean, how often does the world
almost come to an end?
(CHUCKLES)
Oh, it's like that.
- Don't worry,
I was the new kid last year.
- All right, listen,
I haven't even shown you guys
the best part yet.
You ready?
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
- (CHUCKLES)
- Oh, nice.
♪ ♪
You should have
led with that, bro.
- Yeah.
- Not bad.
- I love it.
- It's perfect.
(MONKEY CHATTERING)
Sounds like we need
to call pest control.
- What was that?
("SUPER FRIENDS" THEME PLAYS)
♪ ♪
- Greg, move your head.