(Soldiers shouting)
(Swords clashing)
(Soldiers continue shouting)
(Both grunting)
(Screaming)
(Screams)
(Urging horse)
Man 1: Go, move out!
Soldiers: (Chanting)
Here comes the king in the north!
The king in the north!
Man 2: Here comes the king in the north!
Soldiers: (Chanting)
Here comes the king in the north!
The king in the north!
(All cheering)
(Men talking indistinctly)
(Both laughing)
Ser eldrick sarsfield
and lord Desmond crakehall.
What are you doing?
I have a list.
A list of people you mean to kill?
For laughing at me?
Do I look like Joffrey to you?
No, death seems a bit extreme.
Fear of death, on the other hand...
You should learn to ignore them.
My lady, people have been laughing at me
far longer than they've
been laughing at you.
I'm the halfman, the demon monkey, the imp.
You're a Lannister.
I am the disgraced daughter
of the traitor ned stark.
The disgraced daughter
and the demon monkey.
We're perfect for each other.
(Chuckles)
So how should we punish them?
Who? Whom?
Ser eldrick sarsfield
and lord Desmond crakehall.
Ah!
I could speak to lord varys
and learn their perversions.
Anyone named
Desmond crakehall must be a pervert.
I hear that you're a pervert.
I am the imp.
I have certain standards to maintain.
(Chuckles)
We could sheep shift lord Desmond's bed.
You cut a little hole in his mattress
and you stuff sheep dung inside.
Then you sew up the hole
and make his bed again.
His room will stink,
but he won't know where it's coming from.
Lady sansa!
My sister used to do that
when she was angry with me.
And she was always angry with me.
Why "sheep shift"?
That's the vulgar word for "dung."
My lady...
Well, you asked me.
(Both exclaiming)
That's him!
My lord, my lady.
Your father has called
a meeting of the small council.
Killed a few puppies today?
Show him.
Come on, show him.
Pycelle: Oh!
Apologies, my lord. Old fingers.
"Roslin caught a fine fat trout.
"Her brothers gave her
a pair of wolf pelts for her wedding."
Signed, "walder frey."
Is that bad poetry
or is it supposed to mean something?
Robb stark is dead. (Laughing)
And his bitch mother.
Write back to lord frey.
Thank him for his service and command
him to send robb stark's head.
I'm going to
serve it to sansa at my wedding feast.
Your grace, lady sansa
is your aunt by marriage.
A joke. Joffrey did not mean it.
Yes, I did.
I'm going to have it
served to sansa at my wedding feast.
Tyrion: No.
She is no longer yours to torment.
Everyone is mine to torment.
You'd do well
to remember that, you little monster.
Oh, I'm a monster.
Perhaps you should speak
to me more softly, then.
Monsters are dangerous,
and just now kings are dying like flies.
I could have your
tongue out for saying that.
Let him make his threats.
He's a bitter little man.
Lord Tyrion should apologize immediately.
Unacceptable, disrespectful,
and in very bad taste.
I am the king!
I will punish you.
Any man who must say,
"I am the king," is no true king.
I'll make sure you understand that
when I've won your war for you.
My father won the real war.
He killed prince rhaegar.
He took the crown
while you hid under casterly rock!
The king is tired. See him to his chambers.
- Come along.
- I'm not tired.
We have so much to celebrate.
A wedding to plan. You must rest.
Grand maester,
perhaps some essence of nightshade
to help him sleep.
I'm not tired!
Cersei: Come.
(Door opening)
Not you.
You just sent the most powerful man
in Westeros to bed without his supper.
You're a fool if you believe he's the
most powerful man in Westeros.
A treasonous statement. Joffrey is king.
You really think a crown gives you power?
I think armies give you power.
Mmm-hmm.
Robb stark had one, never lost a battle,
and you defeated him all the same.
Mmm-hmm.
Oh, I know.
Walder frey gets all the credit.
Or the blame, I suppose,
depending on your allegiance.
Walder frey is many
things, but a brave man?
He never would have risked such an action
if he didn't have certain assurances.
Which he got from me.
Do you disapprove?
I'm all for cheating. This is war.
But to slaughter them at a wedding...
Explain to me why it is more noble
to kill 10,000 men in battle
than a dozen at dinner.
So that's why you did it? To save lives?
To end the war. To protect the family.
Do you want to write a song
for the dead starks?
Go ahead, write one.
I'm in this world a little while longer
to defend the lannisters,
to defend my blood.
The northerners will never forget.
Good.
Let them remember
what happens when they march on the south.
All the stark men are dead.
Winterfell is a ruin.
Roose Bolton will be named
warden of the north
until your son by sansa comes of age.
I believe you
still have some work to do on that score.
Do you think she'll open her legs for me
after I tell her
how we murdered her mother and brother?
One way or another,
you will get that girl pregnant.
I will not rape her.
Shall I explain to you
in one easy lesson how the world works?
Use small words. I'm not as bright as you.
The house that
puts family first will always defeat
the house that puts the whims and wishes
of its sons and daughters first.
A good man does everything in his power
to better his family's position,
regardless of his own selfish desires.
Does that amuse you?
No, it's a very good lesson.
Only it's easy for you
to preach utter devotion to family
when you're making all the decisions.
Easy for me, is it?
When have you ever done
something that wasn't in your interest,
but solely for the benefit of the family?
The day that you were born.
I wanted to carry you into the sea
and let the waves wash you away.
Instead, I let you live.
And I brought you up as my son.
Because you're a Lannister.
(Door closes)
Sansa.
It's empty.
Let's find a place to sleep.
Hodor
(echoing)
don't, hodor.
Brandon: Maybe we shouldn't stay here.
You'd rather be out there?
There are a lot of
stories about this place.
Horrible stories.
I always quite liked the horrible stories.
So did I. Once.
You ever heard about the rat cook?
No. Who's he?
Just a cook in the night's watch.
He was angry at
the king for something, I don't remember.
When the king was visiting the nightfort,
the cook killed the king's son,
cooked him into a big pie
with onions, carrots, mushrooms, and bacon.
That night he served the pie to the king.
He liked the taste of his son so
much, he asked for a second slice.
The gods turned the cook
into a giant white rat
who could only eat his own young.
He's been roaming the nightfort ever
since, devouring his own babies.
But no matter what he does,
he's always hungry.
If the gods turned every
killer into a giant white rat...
It wasn't for murder
the gods cursed the rat cook
or for serving the king's son in a pie.
He killed a guest beneath his roof.
That's something the gods can't forgive.
"The late walder frey," old Tully called me
because I didn't get
my men to the trident in time for battle.
He thought he was witty.
Look at us now, Tully.
You're dead,
your daughter's dead, your grandson's dead,
your son spent
his wedding night in a dungeon,
and I'm lord of riverrun.
(Laughing)
The blackfish escaped.
An old man on the run with no allies.
I have tywin Lannister backing me.
Who does he have?
As you say.
They all laughed at
me, all those high lords.
They all thought they were better than me.
Ned stark, hoster Tully.
People snigger when I marry a young girl,
but who said a word when Jon
arryn married the little Tully bitch?
You'll be needing a new young girl.
Yeah.
Got that to look foward to.
Hmm.
And you, the warden of the north.
No more starks to bow and scrape to.
Must have been torture following
that stupid boy all over the country.
He ignored my advice at every turn.
If he'd been a trifle less arrogant...
Calling himself
the "young wolf." How's that for pomposity?
(Walder chuckles)
Well, here's to the young wolf!
(Howls)
Forever young.
(Both laughing)
Will you move to winterfell
now that the war's over?
At some point perhaps.
But winterfell's in ruins.
Yeah.
What happened up there?
I heard the greyjoy boy seized the place.
I heard he killed all the
ravens. And after that, nothing.
I sent my bastard ramsay to root him out.
Robb stark offered amnesty for the
ironborn if they gave us theon.
Oh. And?
Ramsay delivered the terms.
The ironborn turned on theon,
as we knew they would.
They handed him over trussed and hooded.
But ramsay, well...
Ramsay has his own way of doing things.
Well, the girls weren't
lying. You had a good-sized cock.
What?
Pork sausage. (Laughs)
You think I'm some sort of savage?
People talk about phantom limbs.
An amputee might
have an itch where his foot used to be.
So I've always wondered,
do eunuchs have a phantom cock?
Next time you think about naked girls,
will you feel an itch?
(Weeping)
Sorry.
I shouldn't make jokes.
My mother taught me
not to throw stones at cripples.
(Whimpering)
But my father taught
me to aim for their head.
(Softly) Kill me.
Sorry, what?
Kill me.
A little louder.
Kill me!
You're no good to me dead. We need you.
(Breathing shakily)
You don't look like a
theon greyjoy anymore.
That's a name for a lord.
But you're not a lord, are you?
You're just meat.
(Grunts)
Stinking meat.
You reek.
(Gasps)
Reek!
That's a good name for you.
What's your name?
Theon greyjoy.
(Groans)
What's your name?
(Stammering)
Theon greyjoy.
Please.
What is your name?
Reek.
My name is...
(Sobbing)
- (Distant panting)
- (Gasps)
Hodor
(distant pants echoing)
(Growling)
(Creaking in distance)
(Footsteps approaching)
(Eerie groan)
(Gasps)
(Yells)
(Panting)
- Don't kill me!
- Who are you?
- Sam! Sam!
Gilly. Don't hurt us.
Where are you going?
To castle black.
I'm a brother of the night's watch.
My brother, he's in the night's...
(Shushes)
- Who's your brother?
- Jojen: Doesn't matter.
(Summer growling)
You're Jon's brother.
The one who fell from the window.
No, I'm not.
I've been around ghost
enough to know a dire wolf when I see one.
And I've heard all about hodor.
Hodor
I'd be dead if it wasn't for Jon.
If you're his brother,
you're my brother, too.
And anything I can do to help you, I will.
Take us north of the wall.
What? Why in the world
would you want to go...
I don't want to. I have to.
How did you get through the wall?
Does the well lead to an underground
river? Is that how you came here?
Come with us.
There are steps carved
into the south side of the wall.
Hodor can carry you to the top.
We'll walk straight to castle black.
Come with us.
There's nothing north but death.
If Jon is alive,
then castle black's where he'll be.
It's the safest place for you.
There's nowhere
safe any longer. You know that.
Samwell: What I know is what I saw.
And if you saw it, too,
you'd run the other way.
You saw the white walkers
and the army of the dead.
How do you know all that?
The night's watch can't stop them.
The kings of Westeros
and all their armies can't stop them.
(Baby crying)
But you're going to stop them?
Please, Sam.
I have to go north.
I have to.
"Balon greyjoy, lord of the iron
islands and invader of the north.
"I give you until the full moon
"to order all ironborn
scum out of the north
"and back to those
shit-stained rocks you call a home.
"On the first night of the full moon,
"I will hunt down every islander
"still in our lands and flay them living,
"the way I flayed
the 20 ironborn scum I found at winterfell.
"In the box you'll find a special gift...
"Theon's favorite toy.
"He cried when I took it away from him.
"Leave the north now,
or more boxes will follow
"with more theon."
Signed, "ramsay snow,
natural-born son of roose Bolton,
"lord of the dreadfort
and warden of the north."
Get that out of my sight.
Theon disobeyed my orders.
The boy is a fool.
He cannot further the greyjoy line.
I will not give up the lands I have seized,
the strongholds I have taken.
Get this away from me.
He's your son.
Son?
He's not a man anymore.
He's your son. He's my brother.
He's a greyjoy.
Watch yourself.
I've made my decision.
And I've made mine.
I'm going to pick the
fastest ship in our fleet.
I'm going to choose
the 50 best killers on the iron islands.
Man: Get those ropes!
Yara: I'm going to sail up the narrow sea,
all the way to the weeping water.
I'm going to march on the dreadfort.
I'm going to find my little brother,
and I'm going to bring him home.
What is it?
Dragonglass.
We found them at the fist.
Someone buried them a long time ago.
Someone wanted us to find them.
Why? What are they for?
Killing white walkers.
How do you know that?
Gilly: The Walker came for my baby.
And Sam...
But no one's killed
a white Walker in thousands of years.
Well, I suppose someone
had to be the first.
Take it, hodor.
And the Archer.
I got lucky with one of them.
There are more.
Many more.
And for every one of them,
the dead men,
more than you could count.
I wish you'd come with us.
I wish I could.
I really do.
How are you keeping?
Great. Never better.
It was just a bit of blood.
I should have known.
Every time
a highborn asks my name, it's trouble.
We're not really people to you.
Just ways to get what you want.
I'm not a highborn.
She called you "ser."
I heard it.
A recent state of affairs.
I was born in flea bottom, just like you.
Sure, you were.
You're my friend. You're here to help.
I lived below the street of flour.
How far below?
How close to the red keep were you?
The shit that poured from their privy pipes
flowed down the side ofaegon's hill,
along Tanner's row
and right in front of my front door
- on gin alley.
- Gin alley.
The street of steel,
with your armor and your knights?
(Scoffs)
You lived in the fancy part of town.
And here we are now.
Two boys from flea bottom
in the castle of a king.
Yeah, we've come a long way.
We're all the same, really.
She went to great pains
to point that out to me.
If you mistrust fancy people so much,
why were you in such a hurry to trust her?
You're me.
Never been with a woman.
Never talked to a woman, really.
And then she comes at you,
big words, no clothes.
What would you have done?
She does know her way
around a man's head, I'll give her that.
(Both chuckling)
So how'd you become a lord?
Oh. That's a long story.
Better not, then. I'm a bit busy.
Many years ago I helped king
Stannis out of a difficult situation.
He rewarded me with a lordship.
And this.
You see?
Highborns.
I didn't want to be a lord.
I nearly didn't accept.
Why did you?
I did it for my son.
I didn't want him to
step over a river of shit
every time he stepped
through his front door.
I wanted him to have a better life.
Does he?
He's dead.
How'd he die?
Following me.
When did you come to this strange country?
When I was 13.
You were only a child.
I stopped being a child when I was nine.
My mother made sure of that.
You've been a good
influence on our mutual friend, you know.
He used to drink from sundown to
sunup, visit three brothels a night,
gamble away his father's money.
Now it's just the drinking.
And now I'm his wife's servant.
I brush her hair and clip her
nails and empty her chamber pot.
She is a sweet young thing.
None of this is her fault.
I love that girl. I would kill for her.
Do you think that makes it easier for me?
No, I expect not.
She's young
and she's beautiful and highborn.
We break bread with them,
but that doesn't make us family.
We've learned their language, but
we'll never be their countrymen.
If you let yourself believe
that a foreign girl with no name
could spend her life with
the son of tywin Lannister...
I have a name.
You have one name.
As do I. Here, only the
family name matters.
What do you want from me, lord varys?
Diamonds.
I'd tell you to beware
carrying so much wealth,
but you know how to protect yourself.
Get on one of those
ships. Sail to pentos or lys or myr.
You can buy a house
with these diamonds, a very large house.
Hire servants.
Start a new life, a
good life, far from here.
The mysterious foreign
beauty. You'll have suitors lining up.
Why do you want me to leave?
Tyrion Lannister is one
of the few people alive
who could make this country a better place.
He has the mind, the will,
and the right last name.
And you,
you are a complication.
I know you love him.
And I know it's
true love, not bought by gold and silver.
I'm not asking you to leave him for money.
I'm asking you to leave
because your presence
in the capital endangers him.
This will never be your home, my lady.
Find a true home somewhere far from here,
while there's still time.
Lord varys.
If he wants me to leave,
he can tell me himself.
Keep up.
I don't think I can, my lord.
It's not easy being drunk all the time.
(Door opening)
Everyone would do it, if it were easy.
(Footsteps approaching)
Leave.
(Door opening)
So, enjoying married life?
(Door closes)
An unhappy wife
is a wine merchant's best friend.
She doesn't deserve this.
Deserve?
Be careful with that.
Start trying to work out who deserves what,
and before long you'll spend your days
weeping for every person in the world.
There's nothing worse
than a late-blooming philosopher.
(Chuckles)
Will you be facing your
marriage to ser loras
with the same philosophical spirit?
I won't be marrying ser loras.
I seem to remember saying something
similar about my own marriage.
You're not me.
You want to make
things better for sansa? Give her a child.
So you can tell father it was you
who finally talked me into it?
So she can have some happiness in her life.
You have children.
How happy would you say you are?
Not very.
But if it weren't for my children,
I'd have thrown myself
from the highest window in the red keep.
They're the reason I'm alive.
Even Joffrey?
Even Joffrey.
He was all I had once.
Before myrcella was born.
I used to spend hours looking at him.
His wisps of hair.
His tiny little hands and feet.
He was such a jolly little fellow.
You always hear
the terrible ones were terrible babies.
"We should have known.
Even then we should have known."
It's nonsense.
Whenever he was with me, he was happy.
And no one can take
that away from me, not even Joffrey,
how it feels to have someone.
Someone of your own.
How long does it go on?
Until we've dealt with all our enemies.
Every time we
deal with an enemy, we create two more.
Then I suppose
it will go on for quite a long time.
- (Man imitates whimpering)
- (Men laughing)
I'm telling you, that's what she did.
(Imitates whimpering)
(Men laughing)
Man 1: Sounded like a cow in heat.
Man 2: Aye, not for long.
Man 3: That's right.
Black walder shut her up right quick.
None of the starks
had much to say about the end of that meal.
I'll tell you what, though.
The hardest thing was getting
that wolf's head to stay on the body.
Man 2: You sewed it on?
I did.
I bet there were 1,000 men
claiming they were the one.
It was me.
And Malcolm and talbott.
(All laughing)
Well, the thing was so heavy,
it fell off the first time.
Took the skin right with it.
What we ended up
having to do was hook the needle
right under the collarbone,
give it a nice firm mooring and...
What do you want?
Mind if I keep warm?
Fuck off.
But I'm hungry.
Does "fuck off' mean
something different where you're from?
I've got money.
What kind of coin is that?
It's worth a lot.
Sorry.
Little shit.
(Groaning)
Man: Fooi!
(Grunting)
Where did you get the knife?
From you.
Is that the first man you've killed?
The first man.
Next time you're going
to do something like that, tell me first.
(Whispers) Valar morghulis.
(Grunts)
(Bow stretching)
(Horse neighing)
Ygritte, you know I didn't have a choice.
You always knew who I was, what I am.
(Grunts)
I have to go home now.
I know you won't hurt me.
You know nothing, Jon snow.
(Chuckles)
I do know some things.
I know I love you.
(Whimpers)
I know you love me.
But I have to go home now.
(Exhales)
(Groans)
(Grunts)
(Groaning)
(Groans)
(Sobs)
I know how this must look.
What I meant was...
I swear to you, my lord...
Aemon: I'm not a lord, my dear.
Not for many, many years.
Every man who joins the night's
watch renounces all former titles.
Among other things.
What is your name?
Gilly.
For the gillyflower. Lovely.
Yes, my...
Maester.
Master.
And the child?
She hasn't chosen a name yet.
His name is Sam.
Aemon: Tarly,
do you remember the oath you swore
when you joined this order?
He's not my child, maesteraemon.
She's one of craster's wives.
(Baby crying)
I remember every word of the oath.
"Night gathers and my watch begins.
"I am the shield that
guards the realms of men.
"The realms of men."
That means her as well as us.
We didn't build 500 miles
of ice walls 700 feet high to keep out men.
The night is gathering,
maesteraemon. I've seen it.
It's coming for all of us.
Gilly, you and your son
will be our guests for the time being.
We certainly
cannot send you back beyond the wall.
Thank you...
Maester.
I can cook and clean and I can...
Good.
Samwell, fetch a quill and inkwell.
I hope your penmanship
is better than your swordplay.
Miles better.
We had 44 ravens at last count.
Make sure they're all fed.
Every one of them flies tonight.
"To his grace
"king Stannis Baratheon.
"Invaded... invited
"to the name day celebration
"for rylene florent
"on the first nigit..."
Night.
"First night of the full moon."
Why is there a "g" in night?
I don't know. There just is.
Well, your father's
not going to go to that.
My books are better
than these boring scrolls.
You could read about balerion the dread.
They say you can still see his skull
in the dungeons beneath the red keep.
I'd like to see that someday.
I've been trying to stay out of
those dungeons my whole life.
"His fangs were as long as bastard swords."
Aye, old balerion's definitely better
than anything your cousin
rylene's got on offer.
But now that I'm your father's hand
again, I have to keep him informed.
The king does not have time
for this drudgery.
"To all the lords
and knobble men of Westeros..."
Noblemen.
"Noblemen of Westeros,
"the night's watch
"implores..."
What is it?
(Bells tolling)
Why are they ringing the bells?
Are we being attacked?
Stay here. Bar the door.
(Door opening)
The usurper robb stark
is dead. Betrayed by his bannerman.
And you take credit
because you dropped a leech into the fire?
I take no credit.
I have faith, and my
faith has been rewarded.
Your grace, the world has got so far bent.
I've seen things crawl out of
nightmares, but my eyes were open.
I don't know if robb stark died
because of the red woman's sorcery
or because at war men die all the time,
but I do know that uniting
the seven kingdoms
with blood magic is wrong. It is evil.
And you are not an evil man.
Do you know who had
this table carved and painted, ser davos?
Aegon Targaryen.
And do you know
how aegon Targaryen conquered Westeros?
On the back of his dragon,
balerion the dread.
He had a smaller fleet
than the kings he faced
and a smaller army,
but he had three dragons.
Dragons are magic, ser davos.
My enemies have made my kingdom bleed.
I will not forget that.
I will not forgive that.
I will punish them
with any arms at my disposal.
You do not need to burn the boy.
If what you say is true,
a drop of his blood killed robb stark...
And our king is
still no closer to the iron throne.
A great gift requires a great sacrifice.
His name is gendry. He's a good lad.
A poor lad from flea bottom, who
happens to be your nephew.
What is the life
of one bastard boy against a kingdom?
Everything.
The boy must die.
- What are you doing?
- You're leaving.
Is this some kind of trick?
Yes, but not on you.
Aim for that star. Don't stop.
There's bread and water. Go slow with it.
If you finish it off,
no matter how thirsty you get,
don't drink seawater.
I know not to drink seawater.
Row for a full day and night
and you'll reach rook's rest.
You'll want to stop there.
Don't. She'll find you.
Where should I go?
You must keep the coast on your left side
until you reach king's landing.
The gold cloaks are looking for me.
They were looking for me for 20 years.
- Do they know your face?
- No.
I'd worry more about the red woman.
The other way.
You ever been in a boat before?
You know how to swim?
Don't fall out. Go on.
Why are you doing this?
Because it's right.
And because I'm a slow learner.
When you get to flea bottom,
have a bowl of brown for me.
Guard: Horse approaching!
Halt! Halt!
(Horse neighing)
(Men grunting)
Jon! Jon!
Jon, it's us.
I don't think he can see us.
Pyp?
Sam?
Hush, now. You're home.
Carry him inside. Gently.
(Vendor shouting)
(Chickens clucking)
(Indistinct chattering)
Out of the way.
Step aside, country
boy. People working here.
Cersei.
(Gasps)
You don't deny it?
No. I let him go.
Your mercy saved the boy's life.
You feel good about that?
Aye, I do.
Melisandre: You saved one innocent.
How many tens of thousands
have you doomed?
There has got to be another way.
(Shouting) What other way?
Tell us about this other way.
Davos: I don't know, your grace.
I can't see the future in the fire.
Very well, ser davos seaworth.
I, Stannis of the house Baratheon,
first of my name, rightful king
of the andals and the first men,
sentence you to die.
Davos: I understand.
But since you haven't
yet unnamed me hand of the king,
it is my duty to advise you against it.
You're gonna need me.
Take him away.
Why am I gonna need you?
My king.
Davos: It's from maesteraemon of the
night's watch. Their lord commander is dead.
Took a ranging party north
and never made it back.
One lad did, though.
What he saw beyond the wall,
it's coming for all of us.
When did you learn to read?
Matthos taught me before he died,
so I could be of better service to you.
This war of five kings means nothing.
The true war lies to the north, my king.
Death marches on the wall.
Only you can stop him.
You can't stop him alone.
You need someone to
rebuild your army for you,
someone to convince
this lord and that lord to fight for you,
to bring sellswords
and pirates to your side.
I've made my decision.
He's right. You need him.
He has a part to play in the war to come.
(Scoffs)
(Laughing)
You see, ser davos?
You've been saved
by that fire god you like to mock.
You're in his army now.
They will come, your grace.
When they're ready.
Perhaps they didn't want to be conquered.
You didn't conquer
them. You liberated them.
People learn to love their chains.
(Dragons screech)
(In valyrian)
This is Daenerys Targaryen,
the stormborn, the unburnt,
the queen of the seven kingdoms
of Westeros,
the mother of dragons.
It is to her you owe your freedom.
(In valyrian)
You do not owe me your freedom.
I cannot give it to you.
Your freedom is not mine to give.
It belongs to you and you alone.
If you want it back,
you must take it for yourselves.
Each and every one of you.
- Mhysa!
- All: Mhysa!
All: (Chanting) Mhysa! Mhysa!
Mhysa! Mhysa! Mhysa!
What does it mean?
It is old ghiscari, khaleesi.
It means "mother."
(All continue chanting)
(Dragons screeching)
It's all right. These people won't hurt me.
All: (Chanting) Mhysa! Mhysa!
- Mhysa! Mhysa!
(Dragon screeches)
(Chanting continues)
(In valyrian)
Fly
(screeching)
(Chanting continues)
Let me pass.
- Mhysa.
(Chanting continues)
All: Mhysa! Mhysa! Mhysa! Mhysa!
(Dragons screeching)