Arya: Joffrey
Cercei
Tywin Lannister…
The red Woman.
Arya: I can’t Sleep until I say the names.
Sandor: The names of every person in westeros?
Only the ones I’m going to kill.
Robb Stark is dead.
Sansa: I lie awake all night thinking about how they died.
Jon Snow: He was betrayed by his own men.
Jon Snow: all we can give him now is justice.
Tyrion: if you want justice…
You’ve come to the wrong place.
(battle cries)
Stannis: I will not be the page in someone else’s history book.
Littlefinger: what we do to those who hurt the ones we love?
Cersei: The day will come when you joy will turn to ashes in your mouth…
And you will know the debt is paid.
The lannisters aren’t the only ones who pay their depts.
Daenerys: I will do what queens do.
I will rule.
>
Abolfazl & Mohammad