Burqa Khamoush
Clitus
Are you there
My angel
This is for you
What did the doctor say?
He said his jump was too much
I have a lot of power
Clitus I'm afraid
everything is going to be alright
They want to take my expression
They are sending me somewhere
That keep people like me
They can not do that
They can't take you from me
You are the only light
I have always loved you
Babe
leave me
نههه
Do not have the last word?
Welcome to your new home Francis
Will Clytus Cassidy be sentenced to death? Police are looking for more bodies
Did your old boyfriend finally get what he deserved?
And the world would be a safer place without it
Presented by Persian Geekpedia team
Presented by Persian Geekpedia @persiangeekpedia team
Presentation from Persian Geek Pedia team @persiangeekpedia youtube: Persian Geek Pedia
Presentation of the Geek Porn Wikipedia @Persiangeekpedia telegram: Persiangeekpedia
Detective Mulligan with all due respect to you
I do not want to have anything to do with Clytus Cassidy
Well, it got very bad
Because he just wants to see you
I think you had a chance with Cassidy and ruined it
Right ... So, well
What do you want from me?
We want someone to know where the body is buried
So you have to do the right thing to change something
Nah
Get your little hands away from me
We have to get him out
Protect a city
What was he doing?
Leave me alone
Someone who can fly
It should not crawl on the ground
You eat leftovers
You better be quiet
I told you many times
Hide yourself while I work
I'm quite serious
The important thing is to respect
Respect? Yeah
Ok ok
Someone is going to give you some information, right?
it's true
Not wrong
what do you mean?
Because you ruin everything
Oh, I understand you are talking about it again
I miss him
I will do it
I do not like you
Let me eat it
You
Merit
You do not have good things
hmmm
Welcome back Eddie Brock
I was thinking about you
What do you want, Clitus?
I mean, why am I here?
Can you do a favor to a person who is buried alive?
A message to all
Give me a fan
And in it
I will give you my life
What?
Story
The current narratives do not seem to be very useful
A scary and exclusive story like this
It takes you back to the top
continue
People love
Serial killer
All my secrets are yours
Eddie
A sign of killing
But why me?
I like you
OK. Accept
What is your message?
The church that is far away
Is the only thing i see
Broken Angel
My other half
Print this in your column
This?
Who is going to read this?
A mess
Print it
And whatever for me
It will be for you
Wow how lucky I am
Goodbye Eddie
thank you
I thank you
What a bitch
Look at Eddie
look
what are you doing?
I will do your job properly
Eddie
Don't forget me Eddie
what did you get?
I got a headache and
And I probably have tuberculosis too
Say it a little louder
You read me a poem, man
Is this a joke for you Eddie?
Because I do not laugh
Yes, you can laugh
Carefree man
These things take a while, right?
As soon as you find something - sure -
Do this sooner than the rest
Don't be embarrassed
OK
Do you understand?
Trust me
The only thing I do slowly today is buy chocolate ice cream
It does not freeze
come here
look
I am looking
Take them
OK
Okay
What do you think?
I think we are Pablo Picasso
Nah
OK
Come see here
So tell me what do you see?
Umm a blood
ignore it
Oh I know what this one is
A tree
Take Eddie and sit down
Now
be careful
We hit you on the spot
لامصب
It can be said that your friendship with Clytus caused Cassidy
Solve this mystery that has not been solved for decades?
You are the only one you talked to from the outside
He seems to like you
Oh yeah he's a serial killer
I do not know how he might love someone
Brock was released with the help of the FBI, but police were unable to do so
Based on public sources
The mayor of California commented on
The harshest execution changed the sentence for Cassidy
Brock by this revitalizing move
Once again he returned to the top
The end of a tragic story
The acquitted suspects and their families were relieved
Thanks for the courage
Thank you Eddie Brock
And I didn't
U know
We could be like this Eddie
Let's go out and solve the cases
Let's fight with a bad person
Maybe I should eat them
Let's have a good time
But our day ended well
نه
You said I could eat bada
This issue again?
I must be free
Let the wind pass through my hair
And I can feel the sand on my toes
You have no hair
You do not listen to me
Oh, I'm listening
I can no longer live like this
I'm starving
Well eat them
I can not
Sonny and Evil are my best friends
Are you serious?
... This is ridiculous
It was a bad move
It was a really bad move
And this is a $ 2,000 TV
You have to control yourself
That's why we have this billboard (to vent your anger on this)
I can't live with chicken and chocolate
I need a brain
Chickens also have brains
I totally disagree with you
look
Look at that poor idiot
Their brains are small
It is not their fault
You live for Fenilava Lafnilafva
Technical lafawalalai
Yes, I said the same thing - I told you a thousand times -
Because it is found only in the brain and chocolate
Because it is found only in the brain and in chocolate - and in chocolate -
Yes its true
Well, look at this as long as you live in my body
You live by my rules
I live in your body because - why -
Unfortunately, I have no other choice
How is this, Han?
The FBI is still investigating the issues we were involved in
So if another head disappears
They take us to Area 51
They kill our couple
... so one must
Take responsibility
... assume responsibility
It's stupid
Food
Can you be carefree for a minute?
Please do not continue
Food
Diet
God damn you
Good evening Eddie - Hello Ms. Chen -
Not a contemporary fever
Hello, I am at your service
Chocolate has not yet arrived
Oh, no, no
We have an appointment
So now what?
Can't you protect me anymore?
I do not think you can do that
I kept my mouth shut and fed that little secret
Wow, look at Ms. Chen Pir, what has been extorted from her, huh?
I'm not old at all, I'm 39 years old
And I'm very hungry, too
Let me see
I want to eat Ms. Chen
No, no, you can not eat Ms. Chen
What?
I think I should use an alternative map
What is an alternative plan?
Aaaaaaah, not this again
I need a human brain
I need it to survive
Nope
Let's go get some chickens, man, let's go
This is a few games
See how much we can do awful
We are depriving our talent
Oh, a bad person
Sliding bars
Windom, Walsh Conn
Let go, let go
I'm going to hit you on the head now
No, you do not
I play bowling with him
You do not
I'll take him to ... What was his name when we loved him, Eddie?
His name was Lucky Strike.
His name was Lucky Strike
"I want to take her to" Lucky Strike
I get 300 points in each game
No, you do not
The rest of the body stays here
Make the wrong soil and blood
Oh my God
No, let it land
No, no, no, no
OK
The woman did not need our help
He did not want to help us, Eddie
These are different
جانمی جان
On the back of the line, Eddie
Hey, Anne
Hey, Ed-Eddie Hello
Hi
Talk to him kindly - you breathe -
Bad when I did not call?
... No, not at all, I just had
I was just going out for a while (another meaning: I just got hung up)
Oh well, oh me
Sorry I did not answer the calls ... I think
I wanted one space, then all ... those adventures
... that space covers people's heads, well
Oh, good old days
Anyway, I have some news and I wanted to see if we could see each other?
اررررههه - yeah, surely -
It will be very good, great
Okay, how about tomorrow night?
tomorrow night? Well, very good
8 oclock?
(Restaurant name)
Ok great
I'm so excited - yes I am too, goodbye -
Very good
Confused with the doctor
It was the voice of a woman I was just hitting
stop
Don't you want to be the most handsome?
You always get rid of my head
Wow
Hey
What a waste
So ... how are you?
How about Jenap (says the dog)? - Good, good -
Kunshu still learned this from you
How is your neighbor?
Well, you know how much I love "Underdogs" - yeah -
Yes, you have been interested in this for a long time
Nicely said
... Well, then
Okay
Okay??
Eddie, I thought I'd better tell you personally
نه
Wow, wow wow ... wow wow
It's a lot bigger than what I got for you
O miserable humiliation
Didn't Dan buy it? The same Dr. Dan
Yes, Dan bought it
Oh damn it
are you alright?
Yeah Al that sounds pretty crap to me, Looks like BT aint for me either.
You can just say congratulations and I'm happy for you
You know, like two people who care so much about each other that they lie to each other
That one does not feel like garbage
Maybe we can do that model
You know ... you know I'm happy for you
Um ... congratulations to you - no -
thank you
We were going to marry him, Eddie
I personally pray
Five lambs under the trailer
Everything should be sausage
What?
What was that?
What? Nothing
If I ask you a question, can you tell the truth?
Do you mean, for example, why am I not so happy with you?
Because of your marriage? ... Because you just told me to lie, well this one
I am confused
Whats the name?
He is dead
Saw the spirits of Ummah
... Yes, um
Ok - ok -
...Okay
... this
You do not change, do you?
What are you talking about? This was shocking news
... I mean, I love you
Too much to digest
No, the fact is that you do not love anyone
You can not ... life is not what you think
Well then
Do not marry Dan
Dan gives me a sense of security
And you made me feel like I was riding an air train
Sometimes I thought there was no way to get off
Oops, Oops
I don't
Take care of him?
Let it ruin everything
I'm doing something to make you cry now, Eddie
He falls in love with her
cry
It is difficult to digest
Congratulations Anne
it was a good news
Go slower, buddy
Why?
You do not believe in consequences
I will not be harmed, you will repair it
Hangover after drunkenness has no effect
I can't hurt myself even if I want to
Eddie, I'm sorry
That I did not consider your heart
Emotional pain is much harder
And it lasts longer
Just have to
Be an adult and accept it
It's easy for you to say
Why?
Because I'm a real boy
And you are just a pendant
I accept this because we are not feeling well now
Do not worry, my friend, I have your air
Dirty omelet always keeps me fresh in the morning
Sausages and cereals (from now on he snoozes and sings no)
Be a good friend
This is for you
A letter from your aunt?
Wow, listen to this
My dearest friend
I wrote you a letter
To witness
My death
the final
My moments on this
the wheel
Dirt Battalion
Which I call it
the earth
You are responsible
You are the end of Clitus Cassidy
You just kept the door open for me
To go out
They move my heart
Just like he was standing at birth
What if Clitus Cassidy was not revived?
She never threw her grandmother down the stairs
Goodbye Grandma
The misery of the old dog
He never threw the hair dryer in his mother's bathtub
Yeah Al that sounds pretty crap to me, Looks like BT aint for me either
He was never beaten to death by his father
... and could not be sent to
"Synthes"
A home for children that no one wants
That hellish circus
With a bright light
Oh Eddie
All of us in this world
We were born with blood and pain
Each hero has a main and beginning story
Your friend, Clytus Cassidy
Kiss, armpit Kiss, armpit
Smiley face
What is a drop?
You know, I-I have to be there
Oh no, think about it
Oh, oh, well, I threw it there
In fact, he threw himself into it
When he decided to be a chain psychologist
Tada
You know, it would be great if you could support me
Ketchup?
Here is a self-service for himself
Who cares if I eat a few of these idiots?
We can not be sure who is not guilty, comrade
Anna is a prisoner
Yeah Al that sounds pretty crap to me, Looks like BT aint for me either
Or unjustly here they are not all just killers
are you alright?
Yeah man I'm just practicing
I'm a hunter, Eddie
I'm not used to eating salads
Yeah Al that sounds pretty crap to me, Looks like BT aint for me either
Very good
Do not use - Do not use -
Excuse me, what?
ahh wow
I have no explanation for it, am
Oh, I'm signing here
Take two steps away from the bars
Do not make any calls
I realized
Here is a meeting
This is my meeting (semantic similarity with my appointment and the word appointment itself) not Wei Ting (our appointment)
Everything Yu Ting Ah (Your Appointment) (Issues About You)
Ooooh Rosette Goodbye Eddie Brock
Wow this thing
End of tour
Magical misery
I'm worried about your mood (your conscience)
How do you want to go about your life with a man?
I was hoping you could
Give me some advice
You're a funny person, aren't you?
You do not need it. My memory holds everything
impolite
Outcomes
Every decision you have made so far
Who to leave behind
How to leave them behind
A canopy bed (beds that have a roof and columns and are in palaces in the movie)
خالی
Wait
A savior in the dark who never comes
That's because of you
It makes you feel emotional
You
And I
Like us
No
No, we are not
We are twisted from the inside
Bad morals
Eddie is like home and family to me
And that's really all I want in this world
Family
Well, killing your mother and grandmother is definitely an interesting way to show it
There is something you want to say ... before
Did this happen?
Yeah
I have dreams
To do for you
Oh how kind
from
I wish you
I have a broken heart
He said you were late
I wish you to spend your day alone
As always
Hey be careful buddy
Where do you want to go with these words?
You
For anyone who has ever loved you like a cancer, Eddie
You deceived your fiancé who trusted you
No wonder Daddy couldn't look at you like before
After his wife killed your mother
You were born only
O bastard
No no no no no
Do you dare talk about Baba again?
Have you heard of any contact?
Hey go back
Eddie?
The card is over here
I had tasted blood before, my friend
But it was not the taste of blood
Eddie Brock
... as a big secret
Shut up Kasidi
It was a big mistake
light it up
Hey, aren't you Eddie Brock?
No, I'm not anymore
Eddie - One more word I do not want to hear from you, idiot -
Eddie Joon - I do not want to hear -
Eddie, I'm sorry
It was the last time he could be interviewed
There is no more talk of his victim because they died
And there is no trace of their bodies
We lost them forever - completely
I did not mean
You did not mean?
I said I'm sorry
You had no intention, but you did it
I mean, Yahoo, you decided that
I do not know what to call it, you know
That's what you did
You did not even think we could be arrested, we could be killed
You don't think about these things at all, do you?
You only think of the chicken and you only think of yourself and whatever you want
Let me remind you of something, Eddie
You were a loser before I came
You were nothing. I did something to make you special
Oh, you did something to make me special
Okay, let me tell you something, okay?
Before you came, I had a life. I didn't have chicken, okay?
But I had a dream
Yes, I had a dream and I had a fiancé
And I had a successful TV show
But you destroyed them all
Yeah, but, you know what, I rebuilt my life
And now I just want to live. Good Night
And how did you build this new life?
Sorry?
Well, who found the clue on the wall?
So you can be a brilliant little hero?
Hmmm, when did you find the clue? Who?
!Wow
Yeah
no no no. My problem is not to be a hero, man
My problem is living in peace
You know what I mean?
No, you do not understand, you do not understand what I am talking about
Well, the problem is, I want to live without you
I do not want to hear about eating bad all the time
I do not like to hear about you
I do not like you to destroy the house of my life
Do you know how lucky I was to be chosen?
Did you choose me?
Comrade, when your friends fly off the planet Ming Mang
I was the only one who let you go
You are an outcast, a fool
You want to take care of me
But you can not take care of anything
You are useless
Just do something to wash the toilet
Sorry
I do not know what happened to Yahoo
Please let me fix it
How bad
It will be like the first day
O bastard
Get out, get out, pack up
go out
This is my house
Up there, be quiet
go out
Sunny
You do not dare
I have, how I have
No, no, no
Yeah
No
I am calling the police now
I'm so sorry
Show yourself
You can not win
Take a look at me and take a look at your size, little one
How dare you
I guess this is a goodbye
Oh, yes, you finally said the right thing
What a mess
What is this wedge?
اررره
No, no no, no, no
No
Yeah
نه
O yeah
No
No, no, no, no, I wish I had never seen you
Sayonara (Goodbye)
Clytus Cassidy, you were tried and sentenced to death by the state of California
May your death comfort the families of the victims
And may you find peace from now on
Chaos is coming soon
These are your last words
Enjoy the show
Chairman
One thing can
Break this world
Do not move
Please
I have a family
What is the word of the hereafter, boss?
Do not do this, please
I was released, I am happy, Grandma
God willing, everyone is free
I was released, our eyes were wet
God willing, the outside world is better
You two fell victim to this incident
Do not look at me like that carefree, you were never supposed to answer, right?
Yes
breaking news
The serial killer of Clytus Cassidy is now on the run ... as the government seeks
Oh, damn it
He escaped from St. Quentin Prison
Hey - aren't you dead? -
No
can I come in? - Yes sure -
Um ... I just saw him in the news
Give one to ten these eleven degrees
According to St. Quentin, the situation is very good
TV is beautiful
How ... how did he escape?
Ah ... he ran away, that's the main question
And again you were on a special date
So what did he tell you?
Avalanche? Nothing
He did not say anything at all
Didn't he say anything about the escape plan?
Or did he not tell you anything about a particular escape dress?
But how is it possible that you are at the center of such a story whenever it seems
And strangely enough, you know nothing about it
Maybe I'm lucky
Oh well
... You said that I am
The report from St. Quentin is the same as Cucumber
What did you mean by that?
I was asking the same question, do you know what I got?
The information is confidential, but you should not know what to say
never mind
I thought maybe he would come looking for the man who ... almost sent him to that world but
I guess he doesn't
If I were you, I would not be sunny
I know the way out myself
Think, think, think
What was Venom doing in this situation?
Before you found me, he would find you and bring your face down
all right
Who to leave behind and how to leave them behind
A canopy bed
خالی
Left to rot
Does he mean marriage? - Wait -
A savior in the dark who never comes
I do not understand
Church - This Hell Cycle -
Silence
because of you
You and I are like -
Bright light - we have a complex nature -
Bad morals - Vaisa, Vaisa -
You are like home and family to me
St. Estos
Daddy brought another one
See this strange
It's totally different
Wow secret clothes
Hey ... the card is correct
The most beautiful dress I have ever seen. Oh my God
Japan?
No, I made it myself
Hey
Ooof
Hi beautiful
Sorry, no you are not my type (I do not like people like you)
I was released from Eddie's confinement (meaning sexual orientation)
Hello dear
I have to cut a red one
Let's start the celebration
Oops
Hey hey hey vaisa hey vaisa
You are real - yes I am -
And when I kill that thing that made me, we become indestructible
I know where we can find it, but first
I want you to help me find what I lost
accept it
solve it
thank you
Oh damn
That wonderful dress
Thank you one
Eddie was wrong
Everyone was embarrassed because he was embarrassed
But see me now
You are in love
And I'm free
Stop this cruel behavior against space, which is a mistake
We should all be able to live together
On this piece of rock (Earth)
Be free to be who we are
L love you
I love you too
A word ending word
Is it over? It was very impressive
I wish you saw me tonight
Eddie
Oh damn
I'm Mulligan
... I'm Eddie Brock
Look, it might be weird, but I think I found something
Well tell me what
The last time I talked to Cassidy, she was talking about a canopy bed
And also marriage and a series of other things but
I'm at St. Stos right now and ... oh this
I found a tree that
I'm looking at it and the method of something that is written has been dug out
CK
Loves FB
I think anyone who has this FB knows where Cassidy is going
... and I oh
... if you can
I don't know, read a series of files to see if you understand who this FBI is or not
FB means Francis Bryson
Wow how fast
Impossible Eddie
He's dead ... oh I shot him
Can I help you sir?
See if there is anything on the internet?
are you alive
From here, I will take out the skin of your face and go with it as a guest
It never leaves here, Sickfried
No one goes out
All right, Francis
Your sweetheart seems to have left St. Quentin
Everything is in the news
Oh, don't get excited
He will not find you
گا ** دمت
how interesting
But you are not my type
I wonder where it could be
I have the same cup
Tada
Hey Baby
... from
I do not want to be afraid, right?
... I like that with
Get to know the carnage (carnage = killing)
Very attractive
Model year 66
The one I always wanted
Yeah, I remember
Let's see what you do with it
ارررههه عزیزم
Stop it, kill it like this
If he does this one more time, I will eat his face
Sensitive to sound
Stop the car
Stand up
Who said love and affection are gone
Hey, don't hit here
Help me
Food
Get out, get out
... Chocolate
I do
I had a problem supporting them
Where is Eddie then?
غذااا
Monsters, monsters are everywhere
They are everywhere
هیولاهااا
Call EPB (Broad Crime Organization)
And relevant authorities
Close here
And bring me Brock
I have no benefit for anyone here, you are just wasting your time
Oh you know what I'm all thinking?
I'm all thinking about what else there is to Clytus Cassidy that Eddie does not say
Why was Eddie the person Clytus Cassidy wanted to see before his execution, huh?
Bad things are happening around you
Last year, several bodies were found near your home
The story you made at the Crab Restaurant (Venom 1 went to the aquarium and bit the crab)
And you survived the missile explosion (the end of Venom 1)
And now finding a mountain of corpses and a dead psychiatrist in the tail of the device
I did not know about it until today
And people are talking about seeing a monster
Monster..Um what exactly do you mean by monster?
Another monster, Eddie ... wherever Clytus goes, that monster goes with him
Oh my God
Talk to Eddie
Talk
How does that work Eddie?
What is the secret? How does it make people delusional?
I can no longer answer your questions before making a call
I'll make you a phone
Do you know what the problem of secrets is?
They are finally revealed
That's why they are so hard to keep
Did Eddie ask you to do this?
Did no one else help him? We arrive late to the party
You are in trouble
Yes, his work is always in trouble
Is it going to be space again?
It's not clear
I want to talk to him alone
You came and Nesazia because you know you try to have a party
Is this to teach you at university?
Hey n ... hey n thank you so much for coming
Dude is very Teflon and non-stick
How much should I worry about you now?
I .. I ruined
Okay, how bad?
It could not be worse and it is all my fault
Whatever you do, you have to tell the police the truth
No, no, I can not tell them
They are looking for a serial killer who has a space inside
And it kills everyone
What?
Talk to me about what happened
No ... oh he ... he's not here
"Like, 'I'm lying, he's not here,' or 'He's not really here?'
Not really here
Sintostos on fire to all units
گاومون زایید
I do not know, I do not know - what do you think? -
All I know is that he can't do much without eating
That's why he should eat chicken and chocolate
This is how the whole world is summed up in this
We have to find it
You mean, like, saltines and their ilk, eh?
Yes, please find it
Then I'm on my way
I will try - thank you -
Ms. Chen - you? -
منم
What do you want?
Very good-natured
Well, listen - you broke Eddie's heart -
The truth is, I do not have time to sit down and tell you the story. Do you know where Venom is?
Do you want to break his heart too?
I do not want to get into the discussion of who did what to whom
Eddie said maybe it's because of the chocolate here, I just want to talk to the space
We were not supposed to do this now, but
... Mayor in progress
Can you please raise his voice?
Cassidy and Bryson are probably extremely dangerous and fully armed
And the search for them continues tonight
Okay?
Clitus has a symbiote
Oh my God, is there anything else you lied to me about?
cute
Sorry?
Eddie needs Venom
She called me Naz Nazi
He said he did not need her to live better without him
... Look, I do not understand why it matters to you
Oh, let me see for a moment
Come out now
Did you see him? Did you see him seriously? - Yes baby I saw it -
Eddie fights that lonely figure
Don't be a big kid, go and help your friend
He said I should just go and repair the toilet
Clytus goes to him and he will not live without you
Of course, he will not live, because I am the hero
Yes, you are a great sexy hero
You are the coolest, the most attractive and the bravest
Yes, I am
You know I'm still standing here
Nobody loves you
We love when you are struggling
Let's go see that bitch
I promised we would be released from here
And we go to the church on the hill
A marriage
Three guests
One for each of us
The policeman who took my eyes off me
Eddie Brock
And I didn't
A bloody wedding
Didn't find it?
What happened?
Hey Dan, very well, let's go
I do not talk to him
Well he does not want to come out
Wow ... let me see what that means?
We have to go right now because Cleitus wants to destroy the whole city
We do not make any mistake to apologize
You just want an apology
Look, I know the situation is complicated - do you apologize? Right now, do you apologize? -
I want to beg
Ok i'm growing up
I am always the greatest
But go on - what does it say? What is he saying? -
He says I'm listening
Well, listen to this
I am sorry
No, I did not like it that way
I'm sorry - no -
I- I'm sorry
Very strange
I'm sorry - I do not know why you shout at me -
...Because
Well, I was a loser before I met you
Absolutely right - ... and I -
And now, I am a person
Hey, you made me special
So right
Make it a little more beautiful
... make it more beautiful? Ok i am
I'm really sorry for what I said
Hmmm - and also for what I did not say -
Oh my gosh - and for what I did and did not do ... even for what I did not do -
You know he's thinking - oh ... carefree -
OK
Oh no - kiss her -
Do you want to kiss me? - No -
Oh God, I will never do that again
Of course, maybe never, though
If everything goes well, we can order potatoes
..Well Eddie..den..everything..closed the flanges..example
And if for any reason
Fire and sound
Fire and sound? The name of a music band?
No it kills them - yeah -
Okay, man, look, I'm careful
Ashamed
Dan, I'm really sorry
We need a series of serious counseling sessions
I'm going to Brock's house
damn it
Put your hands on your head
Which one do you say?
We found you
The partner is very happy
Yohoo
براک جونم
Wow ring
When were you supposed to go?
A shining prey
For small fish
This is from this friend
hello
I just tied your boyfriend together
It's nothing
If you answer the question "Where is Eddie Brock?"
Well, I'm certainly not going to tell you this
It's a pity to hurt you
Tell Brock
Clitus has something to exchange
Its head in exchange for Eddie's head
It kills your partner
The same people are trying
شخوش
They can not find it
They are looking for us too, buddy
Where are you carefree?
Hey Dan, what happened?
Getting Eddie - Huh? -
They get it
Calm down
They took her to a wedding
Where to take it? - To a wedding -
You have to hurry - we set off -
Get ready we are going to the wedding
Oh the sweat of the gold leaf?
Asan Safa
That church in the distance
Is the only thing i see
Broken Angel
My other half
Dear heart
... hiss ... first
... Actually at the ceremony
... دهنتو
close
Father
Honey, I got what you want
You want more than anything
That policeman? - Pleated itself -
Go on, father
Dear heart
If anyone has a problem with this connection
Say it now or be silent forever
Where is that?
Inhashi
Death to you father
I will not tell your father
You father
Oh damn
Oh ... where did you go? What are you doing?
Worse than I thought
She is a redhead
A red one?
We have to go right now
Annie manages to get along with us that we did not get along with at all
Well, let's go - now? -
We are leaving with the wish of happiness for our dear couple
Eddie ... Yoho
Will I be ahead now?
Look, you have to come out right now
Because I feel very, very vulnerable
Brock is like you?
It does not stay like this for a long time
Eddie, come here again
You have to come out right now
I let you eat everyone, you can eat everyone
Of course, except for the father who is wearing a robe
say it
I promise
thank you
عزیززززممم
See your mouth
Nothing has happened yet. Do you have a problem in your marriage?
Time to die
This is called spirit
I meant we were going to die
I killed you - oh you can not kill a ghost -
Pull it but keep your mouth shut
Our wife knows what she is doing
Just take your voice
Who do you think you are talking to?
Get ahead
My police
Oh, that guy in the robe
Oh God, no oh
Let's gain power
نه
Help Help Help ... Clytus Cassidy
... what they say
About eye to eye?
Fire and sound
Of course, except for the sound part
Babe
Clitus
Let me see how many Brock bat dead
Do you know how I spent my endless days?
I spent it thinking about how you defined one side of the story for them
You did not write the part where Klitos was harassed by Mommy, Daddy and Johnny
You did not tell the world how scared that little boy was
Something that did not matter to anyone
And no one came to save him
... Never ask yourself
To write this story
Oh good day back
I'm not crazy
But I am a vindictive person
You're going to see him die
that...that
Do something
Eddie, unfortunately we can not defeat them
Baby, this is too much
You have to stop it
what are you doing?
I will dismantle it forever
No, you are hurting him
Another foot
I can not
See see
They do not unite like symbiotes
Shut up - Shut up -
Take your hands off my wife
They do not combine
We became
That's right we became
We are together
We must protect it
Let the slaughter take place (let Carnegie take over everything)
Got you, okay?
Father, one of us must die
Oh, we need fire
Maybe the sound
It did not taste good at all
I'm a killer
Whether with monsters or without monsters Eddie
Do you know what I really wanted?
How do I know?
I told you before but you did not listen
But now I'm listening
I wanted to be friends with you
I'm sorry, Clitus
The grave of the father of this cove
You's inside, take Eddie out of here
Follow your partner
I know
This is it
Take care
Yes, you are also a hero
Day
Take care too
thank you
I like you
Although I told her we needed her
I really think it was more than a simple help
The monsters are Carnegie son's taxinee (because he was injured by a piece of carnage, so it happened
Summary of the whole story of Don Quixote and his colleague
It showed two completely different people with different tastes
They were doing a strange job
Sometimes they didn't get along very well, but in the end
Working together to show the best of each other
Eddie
The time has come
I have to go alone
They want me
Yeah
Well, my dearest friend
Reality is the enemy of reality
What do you mean by that?
that's mean
That is us
Are
... van - Ferrari -
Um ... yeah.yes
On the run
That's it
Thank you, sir, for bringing me here
You could not, comrade
Isn't it beautiful?
Sorry we can not talk about
Let the wind blow in your hair
Osho says
When you love someone
You accept what it is - Osho? -
With all its flaws
Defects
No one is perfect
Go back one step ... did you just say that you love me?
اممم - گفتی -
Where are we going?
I do not know, I do not know
Wherever you read less carefully, I think
Who really did not mean that?
Why was it
We need a cape and a mask
No, we can't do that, that's fine
Presented by Persian Geekpedia team
Presented by Persian Geekpedia @persiangeekpedia team
Presentation from Persian Geek Pedia team @persiangeekpedia youtube: Persian Geek Pedia
Presentation of the Geek Porn Wikipedia @Persiangeekpedia telegram: Persiangeekpedia