What have you done?
All done.
Not so bad, was it?
See?
There's nothing to be afraid of.
Is there, Nancy?
Why don't you take a seat?
No!
Nancy, just stay with me.
Stay with me, okay?
Whatever you guys are doing, hurry up!
Steve says you need to hurry!
- Yeah? No shit!
- We're trying. We can't find anything.
- What is all this shit?
- What are you even looking for?
Madonna, Blondie, Bowie, Beatles?
Music! We need music!
This is music!
Son of a…
God!
Nancy.
What are you doing?
It's not time for you to leave.
Now that you've seen where I've been…
…I would like very much to show you
where I am going.
Take a seat, Nancy.
I…
Want you to tell
Eleven.
I want you to tell her
everything you see.
No!
- Tell her…
- No!
…everything.
No!
Hey, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
It's okay. It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay. I'm here.
I'm right here.
What's going on there?
Get the power back on!
Tell him that the prisoners
are contained...
and that you're working on the power.
Tell him!
And that door there, where does it lead?
To... to cell block two...
No cell blocks!
I need a safe way out of here.
Guess you got
my message, huh?
Oh, no, I just have always wanted
to visit the Soviet Union.
With Murray.
You two getting along?
He's the Star sky to my Hutch.
I thought you were dead.
Thought I lost you.
I did lose you.
For eight months.
We had a funeral.
Anybody show?
Are you kidding?
You're the hero of Hawkins.
It's true.
Yeah, I always felt
I'd be easier to like when I was dead.
How about El?
She's good.
She misses her dad.
We all do.
Uh, I hate to interrupt,
but apparently, they can climb too.
Lower your weapons.
Lower your weapons!
Don't shoot!
Stop!
The hell is that?
Please tell me they don't have
another one of those things.
You can't go in there!
It's dangerous!
Oh my God.
The hell are they doing?
Hey.
Found something.
- Think this'll lead us outta here?
- I give it a hundred to one odds.
And one, two, three.
Again.
One, two, three.
Pulse is dropping.
One-fifty now. BP's 160…
How do you feel?
Can you hear us?
Eleven. Can you hear us?
No, leave her.
Hi, Jane.
Holy shit, dude. Check it out.
I didn't know they expanded into Nevada.
Watch out, Domino's.
Your dominoes are gonna fall.
How far is Nina from Vegas?
From Vegas?
Um, as long as
Suzie's coordinates are right,
about another 90 miles. Why?
Well, once we save her, El,
we should stop on the way back.
El could make us, like, super rich,
and we'd never have to work.
We could just play D&D and Nintendo
for the rest of our lives.
Yeah. Totally.
We're gonna make it, Mike.
She's gonna be okay.
Yeah, I know. I… I know she is.
But… But what if
after all this is over, she…
Sh… she doesn't need me anymore?
No, o… of course she'll still need you.
She'll always need you, Mike.
I keep telling myself that, but I…
I don't believe it.
I mean, she's special.
She was born special.
Maybe I was one of the first people
to realize that.
But the truth is,
when I stumbled on her in the woods,
she just needed someone.
It's not fate. It's… It's not destiny.
It's just simple dumb luck.
And one day she's gonna realize
I'm just some random nerd
that got lucky
that Superman landed on his doorstep.
I mean, at least Lois Lane
is an ace reporter
for the Daily Planet, right? But…
- Sorry.
- No.
No, I… it's so stupid,
given everything that's going on.
It's just… I… I don't know, I just…
Uh…
You're scared of losing her.
Can I show you something?
This is amazing.
Did you paint this?
Yeah. Yeah. I mean…
I mean… I mean, El asked me to.
She commissioned it, basically.
I mean, she told me what to draw.
Anyway, my point is,
see how you're leading us here?
You're guiding the whole party,
inspiring us.
That… That's what you do.
And see your coat of arms here?
It's a heart.
And I know it's sort of on the nose,
but that's what
holds this party together. Heart.
Because, I mean,
without heart, we'd all fall apart.
Even El. Especially El.
These past few months,
she's been so lost without you.
It's just, she's so different
from other people, and…
…when you're…
when you're different,
sometimes…
…you feel like a mistake.
But you make her feel like
she's not a mistake at all.
Like she's better for being different.
And that gives her
the courage to fight on.
If she was mean to you
or she seemed like
she was pushing you away,
it's because she's scared of losing you,
like you're scared of losing her.
And if she was going to lose you,
I… I think she'd rather just
get it over with quick.
Like ripping off a Band-Aid.
So, yeah, El needs you, Mike.
And she always will.
Yeah?
Yeah.
After the attack,
you fell into a coma.
Like One, you had pushed yourself
beyond your limit.
And it very nearly destroyed you.
But that is where your similarities ended.
What you displayed that day
was beyond anything I'd ever imagined.
A potential I'd only dreamed of.
But when you awoke,
something had been lost.
Your memories,
along with whatever else
you'd found within yourself that day.
But I knew then, just as I knew today,
that your powers had not been lost.
They just needed a spark.
But that day,
you awakened something else.
A doorway to another world.
I always thought that Henry was out there,
hiding in the darkness.
I didn't know for sure,
not beyond a feeling.
Until now.
He's claimed three victims so far,
and when I saw the eyes,
I knew… I knew that was him.
He was sending us a message,
letting us know he's back.
That's when I came to see you.
My friends.
Well, we… we haven't risked contact,
but, as far as we know,
they're… they're all safe.
But I'm not gonna lie to you, Eleven.
Your friends are in terrible danger.
With each victim he takes,
Henry is…
Chiseling away at the barrier that exists
between our two worlds.
"Chiseling"?
Imagine, if you will,
the barrier between our worlds is a…
Concrete dam.
Henry is putting cracks in this dam.
Cracks in dams
create pressure.
Left unchecked,
the pressure will build.
And build.
And eventually,
it will reach a breaking point.
And the dam will burst.
And when that happens,
Hawkins will fall.
Well, that went very well, I thought.
You eased her into it, nice and gentle,
just like we talked about.
Not ominous at all.
He showed me
things that haven't happened yet.
The most awful things.
I saw
a dark cloud
spreading over Hawkins.
Downtown on fire.
Dead soldiers.
And this…
Giant creature
with… a gaping mouth.
And this creature wasn't alone.
There were so many monsters.
An army.
And they were coming into Hawkins.
Into our neighborhoods.
Our homes.
And then…
He showed me my mom.
And Holly.
Mike.
And they…
They were all…
Okay, but… he's just trying
to scare you, Nance.
Right? I mean…
I mean, it's not real.
Not yet.
But there… there was something else.
He showed me gates.
Four gates.
Spreading across Hawkins.
And these gates, they looked like
the one outside of Eddie's trailer,
but… they didn't stop growing.
And this wasn't the Upside Down Hawkins.
This was our Hawkins.
Our home.
Four chimes.
Vecna's clock.
It always chimes four times.
Four exactly.
I heard them too.
He's been telling us his plan
this whole time.
Four kills.
Four gates.
End of the world.
If that's true…
He's only one kill away.
Oh Jesus Christ. Jesus Christ.
Try 'em again. Try 'em again.
- Anything?
- No.
Rang a few times,
then went to busy signal.
Maybe you punched it wrong.
Try again.
- I didn't punch it in wrong.
- Well, I don't know.
I think she knows
how to use a phone.
I'm just saying,
she could've typed it in wrong.
- Same shit.
- How is that possible?
Joyce has this telemarketer job.
Always on the phone.
Mike won't stop whining about it.
Yeah, but this phone's been busy
for, what, three days now?
That's not Joyce.
No way. Something's wrong.
She's right.
It can't be just coincidence. It can't be.
Whatever's happening in Lenora
is connected to all of this.
I'm sure of it.
But Vecna can't hurt them.
Not if he's dead.
We have to go back in there.
Back to the Upside Down.
- Whoa, no, no, no. What?
- Nope.
- Let's think this through.
- What is there to think through?
- We barely made it out of there.
- Yeah, because we weren't prepared.
But this time, we will be.
We'll get weapons and protection.
We'll go through the gate,
we'll find his lair, and we'll kill him.
Or he'll kill us.
The only reason you survived
is because he wanted you to.
- He's not scared of us.
- And for good reason.
We were wrong about Vecna. Henry. One.
Sorry, what are we calling him now?
- One.
- Vecna.
- Henry.
- Right.
We've learned something new
about Vecna/Henry/One.
He's a number like Eleven,
only a sick, evil, male, child-murdering
version of her with really bad skin.
But my… my point is, he's super powerful.
Could turn us inside out with a snap
of his fingers. It's not a fair fight.
Then why fight fair?
You're right. He's like Eleven.
But that gives us an upper hand.
We know Eleven's strengths.
And weaknesses.
Weaknesses?
When El remote-travels,
she goes into
this sort of trance-like state.
I bet the same is true of Vecna.
That would explain
what he was doing in that attic.
Exactly. When he attacks his next victim,
I'll bet you he's back in that attic,
physical body defenseless.
Defenseless? What about the army of bats?
True. We'll have to find a way past them.
Distract them somehow.
- And, uh, how do we do that, exactly?
- No idea.
But once they're gone,
he doesn't stand a chance.
It'll be like slaying sleeping Dracula
in his coffin.
That all sounds good in theory,
but there is no pattern
to Vecna's killings.
Not one that I can decipher.
We don't know
when he's going to attack next.
- Don't even know who he's going to attack.
- Yeah, we do.
I can still feel him.
I'm still marked.
Cursed.
I ditch Kate Bush,
I draw his focus back to me.
Max.
You can't.
He'll kill you.
I survived before.
I can survive again.
I just need to keep him busy long enough
so that you guys can get into that attic.
Then you can chop his head off.
Stab him in the heart. Blow him up
with some explosive Dustin cooks up.
I honestly don't care
how you put this asshole in his grave.
Just…
…whatever it is…
Whatever you do…
Try not to miss.
Bam.
Durak.
Son of a bitch!
Sayonara!
Oh God! Oh God!
Son of a bitch!
- You okay? All right?
- Yeah.
- You okay?
- Okay? I'm great! Whoo!
Oh, nothing like a little prison escape
to get your day started, am I right?
We're not out of the woods yet.
My people do not take kindly to escapes.
They'll be hunting us.
Yeah, well, we aren't exactly
planning on sticking around.
- Where's the plane you came in on?
- That plane? Um, that crashed.
- Crashed?
- His fault.
A word of warning.
That man is more slippery
than an eel dipped in baby oil.
I wouldn't trust a word out of his mouth.
My tongue. My tongue!
I… I can't feel my tongue.
We need to get out of here,
back to the States.
Can you get us to another plane?
Now?
You're asking for Yuri's help
after dragging him through miles
of shit tunnel?
I could have told you
we are going wrong way hours ago.
You Neanderthal...
Watch your mouth, or I am gonna take this,
I'm gonna rub it along
the bottom of my shoe,
and I'm gonna jam it down your throat.
Well, go ahead!
But then you'll never
make it out of my country alive.
So you can get us out.
For a glass of water and hot steam bath
and five-inch stack of American dollars,
Yuri will fly you to moon.
You make another demand,
you double-crossing mudak,
I'll decorate the roof of this Van
with your brains.
Why so angry, comrade?
Rough couple of days for you, I'm sure.
But now you are free.
Everything works out.
Happy ending for everybody.
No?
For you, that will very much
depend on how you answer. Comrade.
Will you take us to America?
Yes?
Or no?
Check this out. The War Zone.
I've been there once.
It's huge.
They got everything you need for, uh…
Well, killing things, basically.
You think fake Rambo has
enough guns there?
Is that a grenade?
I mean, how is any of this legal?
Well, lucky for us it is, so…
This… This place is just far enough
outside of Hawkins.
As long as we steer clear of main roads,
we ought a be able to avoid cops
and, uh, angry Hicks.
If we're trying to avoid angry Hicks,
maybe we shouldn't go
to some store called the War Zone.
Normally, I'd agree,
but we need the weapons.
- So I think it's worth the risk.
- Me too.
But is it worth the time?
It'll take all day to bike there and back.
- Who said anything about bikes?
- You got some car we don't know about?
It's not exactly a car, Steve.
And it's not exactly mine,
but, uh… it'll do.
Hey, Red, uh, you got a ski mask
or a bandanna, something like that?
That was suffocating.
Go! Come on.
Where'd you learn how to do this?
Well, when the other dads were teaching
their kids how to fish or play ball,
my old man was teaching me
how to hot-wire.
Now, I swore to myself
I wouldn't wind up like he did,
but now I'm wanted for murder,
and soon, Grand Theft Auto.
So, uh, I'm really living up to
that Munson name.
Eddie, I'm not sure
I love the idea of you driving.
Oh, I'm just starting this sucker.
Harrington's got her.
Don't ya, big boy?
What the hell?
Hey! Open this door!
- Hey!
- They locked the door!
Shit! Go.
It's just a car.
Everybody, hang on to something!
Oh my God! Let's go! Let's go!
Drive, Steve! Drive!
Go, go, go!
♪ Hitch a ride to the end of the highway ♪
♪ Where the neons… ♪
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
Shit, they look pissed.
It's not every day you lose
your house and car in one fell swoop.
♪ …around the bend ♪
Hold on! Hold on!
♪ You can ponder perpetual motion… ♪
Them!
Stop 'em! God bless it!
Okay.
♪ …a good conversation ♪
♪ There's an ear for what you say ♪
♪ Come on the rising wind ♪
♪ We're going up around the bend ♪
My friends. I saw them.
You told me they were safe.
- They are not safe.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, okay.
Uh, just give us a second, please.
Please.
Okay, okay, first… first things first.
We're not gonna let anything happen
to your friends, okay, kiddo?
I will personally make sure of that.
Did… Did you see where they were?
They were at… They were at Max's house.
They're planning to kill him.
To kill Henry.
Okay. Okay.
This… Does this Max have a last name?
Max… Max Mayfield.
Okay. So here's what's gonna happen.
I have people in Hawkins,
and I'm gonna send some to Max Mayfield.
- And they will stop him...
- Her.
Stop her. And the rest of them
from whatever foolish,
although well-intentioned, mission
that they're attempting, alright?
No. No, do not send your men.
Send me.
Your friends are not prepared
for this fight, Eleven.
And neither are you.
You must understand,
when One kills, he doesn't simply kill.
He consumes.
He takes everything from his victims.
Everything they are
and everything they ever will be.
Their memories, their abilities.
And we do not know
where he's been these lost years.
But if he has survived this long,
we can only assume
that he has grown in strength.
To underestimate him,
to act rashly,
would be very dangerous.
I don't want to upset you, Eleven.
What you've accomplished
is nothing short of a miracle.
You came to me broken.
And you've learned to walk again.
But if you want to stop One,
you will need to do more than walk.
You will need to do more than run.
You will need to fly.
And you're not ready.
My friends need me.
I've stopped him once. I will again.
I'm sorry. You can't.
It's impossible.
Nothing's impossible.
I can call Stinson. She's got connections
at Nellis. That's two hours away.
And if we hustle, I'll bet we can be
in Hawkins before nightfall.
That would be a grave mistake.
Waiting would be an even greater mistake.
What if One makes his move
before we've had a chance
to throw a punch?
Then what is the point of all this?
That's a risk we're going to have to take.
We pushed her before
and look what happened.
She lifted a 10,000-pound tank
into the goddamn air.
You don't understand what he's capable of!
Maybe you're right.
Or maybe you are overestimating him.
Either way, doesn't matter
because this is not our choice.
We agreed this was not gonna be a prison.
We'll show her what this is,
what we can offer,
and then it is her choice
whether she wants to stay or go.
Right, Doc?
You may not agree with it,
but here she is, standing before us,
making a choice.
You're sure you wanna do this?
Okay. Pack your things, say your goodbyes.
- How's it handle?
- Not half bad.
Considering that this is a…
House.
♪ Yesterday mornin'
They let me know you were gone… ♪
Yeah, it's…
It's silly, but I… I've actually…
I always had this dream that I'd have
this really… really big family.
I'm talking, like, uh,
a full brood of Harringtons.
Like, five, six kids.
- Six?
- Yeah. Six little nuggets.
Three girls, three boys.
And… and every summer,
I figured all of us Harringtons,
we would pack into something like this
and… just see the country.
You know, the Rockies, Grand Canyon,
maybe Yellowstone.
End up in some beach side town
in California.
Spend a week parked in the sand.
Learn how to surf or something.
That sounds nice.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Well, uh, except for the six-kid part.
That sounds like a total nightmare.
If only I had some practice.
All right. Fair.
That's fair.
♪ Oh, I've seen fire and I've seen rain ♪
♪ I've seen sunny days
That I thought would never end ♪
♪ I've seen lonely times
When I could not find a friend ♪
Hey.
♪ But I always thought
That I'd see you again… ♪
So I've been thinking,
two of the three of Vecna's victims
were seeing Ms. Kelley, right?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
So I figure there's a good chance
Vecna cursed another one of her students.
We go back to her office.
We read all of her files.
Look for mentions of headaches,
nosebleeds, nightmares.
- We identify his most likely next victim.
- Lucas.
- We stake out his house...
- Lucas, stop.
We don't have time for any of that, okay?
And even if we did,
even if your plan did work,
we'd be putting a total stranger at risk.
A stranger who has no idea
what they're up against.
I do.
He uses my memories against me.
But… only my darkest memories.
- Same with Chrissy and Fred, right?
- Right.
It's like he only sees the darkness in us.
So, I'll just run
in the opposite direction.
Run to the light.
And maybe he won't be able
to find me there.
Now, how exactly
do you plan on doing this?
I'm not sure.
But it's my mind.
Not his, right?
So I should be able to control where I am.
I just need to… push him away.
Find a happy memory and hide there.
Hide in the light.
You got a memory in mind?
Yeah.
It was a time when I was
the happiest.
Was I there?
That's presumptuous of you.
But yeah.
You might've been there.
Okay, but the second you start to lift,
I'm calling in Kate Bush.
- All right?
- Okay.
- Deal.
Heh, come on. This way.
If I get a whiff
of any funny business, smuggler...
I will not hesitate to kill you.
In fact... I am just looking for a reason.
Understand?
Are you a parrot, cop?
You keep repeating the same thing.
You were trapped in a cell
with this dull man
and you didn't take opportunity
to smother him.
Beautiful, yes?
Please tell me this is another poor joke.
You said you had a plane.
- A plane!
- No, no, no.
I… I told you I could fly you home.
And Katinka can fly you home, little bird.
She was named Katinka
after my first lover.
Katinka also had
very beautiful, very round buttocks.
Uh, mu… much like this.
This cannot fly us to America.
Why not?
As long as winds are not too strong
and your military friends
do not shoot us out of sky,
we can make it to the coast.
There, while we refuel,
we skin dip in ice-cold water
and wash off this muck.
Then we fly her rest of the way.
Happy ending.
Okay, what is the furthest
Katinka has ever flown?
For me, she is still a virgin.
Uh, not real Katinka. Goodness, no.
That Katinka, no.
But this Katinka, pretty much unspoiled.
But I'm sure she will soar
when given a chance.
She just need little tune-up.
- I did warn you, Jim.
- Okay.
Should I shoot him now? Or later?
What about Owens?
He… He's gotta have contacts or spies here
that could help us.
Can we do that?
Can we make a call to the States?
Yes, hello, miss.
I'd like to place a call to
the United States. A very sick relative.
Correct. Yes... The number is...
- The number?
- It's 775…
…305…
…3450.
Da, spasibo.
- What are you doing?
- How exactly do you think this works?
They will make the call for us,
and then they will call us back.
How long's that gonna take?
Five minutes. Five hours.
Five days. Who knows?
And when we do get the call,
assume the KGB will be on the other line,
listening to everything you say.
So,
I suggest talking in code.
Say the wrong thing
and they will be on us like flies on shit.
Welcome to the Soviet Union.
♪ Couldn't stop moving
When it first took hold… ♪
So much for avoiding angry Hicks.
Let's be… fast.
- Yep.
- Definitely.
♪ Don't ya know
I'm never gonna lose that funky sound?… ♪
- How many of these do you think we need?
- Five or six.
What are you gonna do? Stand and gawk?
Shut up.
Ah!
Jesus, you scared me.
Whoa. You gonna mace me with that?
If it keeps you in line, yeah.
See? Not so scary.
Robin. Robin!
Who's that?
Someone from band.
How much is this?
$120.99, but I'll throw in
20 rounds of buckshot for ya.
Hey, can I see
this real pretty .357, please?
Sure thing.
- Here you go, son.
- Thank you.
Nancy Wheeler.
Wouldn't expect to find you here.
Yeah, well, it's just… scary times.
I'm… sorry about Chrissy.
Want my advice?
Shotguns are not good for much of anything
past killing small birds.
I mean, they got power, sure,
but not much range.
And that's just gonna force you
into close-range combat,
then someone can
just grab that barrel like this…
…and redirect it.
Well, you look nervous.
Like I said,
scary times.
Now, your brother, he, uh…
Is he here with you, by chance?
Mike?
Mike.
No.
I only ask because he's…
He's in Hellfire, isn't he?
- I don't know what you're talking about.
- What about his friends?
They here with you?
Would you let go?
Let go.
What the hell is taking so long?
- What happened?
- Gotta go.
- Your old friends are here.
- Shit!
- Let's go! Let's go!
- I'm going! I'm going! Sit down!
Should be up on our right.
There's nothing out here.
Mmm. We there already?
- Already? It's been nine hours.
- It's gotta be around here somewhere.
What are we looking for, my dudes?
- Some sort of facility.
- A fence. A building.
Any signs of life would be nice.
Since when did we decide Nina
was a building and not a small woman?
Sounds like a small woman to me.
It's not a small woman.
Small woman out in this desert
would be hard to see.
- How is he still high?
- Sure you got your measurements right?
Yes, they're right.
- You're 100%, right?
- Yes.
Maybe latitude and longitude are wrong.
- Are you really questioning Suzie?
- She's a genius, Jonathan.
- Even geniuses make mistakes.
- Well, she didn't.
If that small woman is small enough,
she could fit behind a small tree.
Stop! Just…
- Ouch.
- What are you doing?
I am stopping us before we get more lost.
- Give me the coordinates.
- Um, okay.
Longitude is 116 degrees,
five minutes, and 17...
Slow down. Slow down.
Nina!
Nina.
Nina?
Nina!
Holy macaroni.
All right. You just go straight down.
Like, straight… straight…
Right on the money, as I said.
- It just doesn't make sense.
- Yo, dudes!
My dudes!
Jesus Christ.
Come check this shit out!
What is it?
Gotta see it to believe it, my dudes!
Come on! Hurry!
Let's go! Let's go! Let's go! Pronto!
Okay.
So no small woman named Nina.
But you said any signs of life,
am I right?
Right.
Well,
these are no regular
tire tracks, brochachos.
I mean, look at the tread
on these monsters.
They're fatties.
And you know what that means.
Military.
We gotta go.
Well, I wouldn't do it
if I didn't think she was ready.
But either way,
I don't think we have any other choice.
- Do you?
- No, I don't.
Yeah.
- It might take me some time though.
- Just… As fast as you can.
It's gonna take us two hours
to get to Nellis as it is.
And, Ellen, one more favor.
Can you send somebody over
to a Max Mayfield's house?
There are some kids there
that just need looking after, okay?
Ellen? Hello?
Sam? Hello?
Why the long face, Doc?
We just wanna talk.
No! Wait!
No! No!
What…
You can't leave, Eleven.
Where is Dr. Owens?
Dr. Owens had a change of heart.
I know you wish to go to him,
and there's nothing I can do to stop you
from forcing open that door.
But if my men hear you coming,
they will kill him.
And alone, you will never find your way
out of this desert to your friends.
Here's what we're going to do.
You and I are going to complete
our work together.
And when I decide that you are ready,
we will return to Hawkins, together.
Papa and daughter.
Why are you doing this?
Because there's no other choice.
There is a choice.
Only one that is right.
And you make the right choices?
I try.
Did you make the right choice with Mama?
Four-fifty.
Your mother was sick, Eleven.
She was a danger to herself and to others.
She brought a gun into the hospital.
She killed a man.
Hospital?
No.
A prison.
Everything I have done
was for your own good.
For your own protection.
And Henry?
You kept Henry in that lab.
With the children.
Was that for our good?
Was that a right choice?
I had no idea what Henry would do.
I cared for you.
I loved you. I loved all of you.
Even Henry?
Yes.
I was trying to help Henry,
to understand him. Yes.
Yes, I cared for him.
Even after what… what he did?
Yes.
Because I knew I had failed him.
So this morning,
you said you believed
he was always alive in the darkness.
Is that why I was searching the darkness?
Was I looking for him? For Henry?
No. No.
We were focused on the Soviets.
You knew that.
"Papa does not tell the truth."
Henry said that.
And now you trust Henry?
Henry, who's manipulated you
like some puppet?
You are the one
who released him from his prison.
You.
And now you are angry with yourself
and you're taking your anger out on me
and you're risking everything.
No.
No, you.
You have risked everything!
You have lied!
You made me look for him!
The gate.
The Mind Flayer.
So many dead.
And all because of you.
Because you could not stop.
You could not let him go.
I came here
to try and understand who I was.
To see if I…
If I was the monster.
Papa!
And now I know the truth.
It is not me.
It is you.
You
are the monster.
I am going to open that door,
and I am going to leave
with Dr. Owens.
If you try to stop me, I will kill you.
You'll soon see the truth, Eleven.
Ah!
Is this legal?
Actually, I think it's a felony.
Right.
But it guarantees one thing.
I won't miss.
- How's she feeling?
- Light. But durable.
Deadly.
But reliable.
Hear me now.
There will be no more retreating…
…from Eddie the Banished.
Hey, you're really ready for bat-tle.
You get it?
"Bat-tle."
B-A-T.
No?
I thought I had a good one.
What are you doing?
You son of a bitch!
No wedgies! No wedgies!
Never change,
Dustin Henderson.
Promise me?
I wasn't planning on it.
Good.
- Good.
Hey, Sinclairs.
How are those, uh… those Spears coming on?
Flip that damn thumb around.
What?
It's too loose, Lucas.
This isn't a basketball game
where they blow the whistle
when your shoes fall off.
Okay, okay, for the record,
my shoes never fell off.
Okay, for the record,
it's kinda hard for your shoes to fall off
when you're riding the bench.
Yet, for some reason,
you show up to every game.
Mmm, except the one that mattered.
Plus, Mom and Dad forced me.
Bull. Mom and Dad
can't force you to do shit.
Well, even though
you're a bench-riding loser,
you're still my brother.
Just the facts.
- It just doesn't make sense.
- What doesn't make sense?
That was Dan Shelter.
He graduated, like, two years ago.
- So?
- So he's in college.
Which means he was visiting
on spring break.
Fast Times was returned,
like, I don't know, a week ago?
Right? Unless she's got
some horn dog brother we don't know about.
Which is possible.
Or she's just really into Judge Reinhold?
- Steve.
- Nah.
- What?
- I don't care.
I don't understand why you do either
with everything that's going on.
Honestly, this feels like a perfect time
for that little pull of the rug because…
In the face of the world ending,
the stakes of my love life
feel spectacularly low.
Yeah. I mean, I get you there,
but… I still have hope.
- Not everything has a happy ending.
- Yeah, yeah, believe me, I know.
I'm not talking about failed romance.
I just…
I have this terrible,
gnawing feeling that…
It might not work out for us this time.
You think we shouldn't be doing this?
I think we're mad fools,
the lot of us, but…
…but if we don't stop him,
who will?
We have to try, right?
Yeah.
To killing Vecna.
Slash Henry.
Slash One.
It's only a precaution, Eleven.
I never intend to activate it.
I very much hope
our fighting has come to an end.
Shh.
I know.
You're angry with me.
But it was the only way.
The best way.
- What's going on?
- It's Sullivan.
They found us.
Go, go, go!
Three! Two! One!
- Go to the back!
- Get moving!
- Move out!
- Go!
- Get 'em out of here!
- No more time!
Evacuate now!
Move!
Steady! Fire!
Eleven, we have to go.
- What is happening?
- They've come to kill you.
Evacuate immediately.
Please proceed…
- Clear.
- Clear!
Quarter and search by twos.
Hicks, take the upper level.
Yes, sir.
Sir?
We found something you're gonna wanna see.
Well, well.
And what happened here?
Hmm?
Are Mommy and Daddy fighting?
Okay.
Let's try this again, shall we?
Where's the girl?
Where do you think you're going, Doc?
- Why don't you give 'em some lead?
- I got it.
Down he goes.
Victor-Two-Sierra,
this is Charlie-Lima-Golf.
Do you copy, over?
Victor-Two-Sierra, I copy, over.
We've got the target in our sights.
Requesting permission
to take the shot, over.
Jack, you don't have to do this.
It's over, Sam.
Wait! Wait! Wait! I can put her in a coma.
A medically induced coma.
We have the drugs.
We can do it right here.
And we'll see
if… if these murders keep happening.
If you're right, the killing ends,
and you can pull the plug on her.
In fact, I'll do it myself.
But if you're wrong about this,
God, are we gonna need her.
Jack.
Don't do this.
I'm begging you.
Take it.
You son of a bitch!
No! You son of a bitch!
Green light. Light her up.
Civvies. Five o'clock.
The hell?
- There she is! There she is!
- Where?
- On the ground!
- What are those dudes doing on the ground?
- Is that blood, man?
- Shit.
Victor-Two-Sierra,
we've got a civvy headed our way.
Ignore it. Just take out the girl.
Copy that.
Ignore the civvy. Take the shot.
Found ya.
- Hell are you doing? Hold her steady!
- I don't know, man. Something's wrong!
Jesus Christ.
Holy shit!
Shit!
I'm losing her!
- Shit!
- Shit! I can't! I can't hold it!
Shit! Shit! Shit!
Eleven!
Eleven.
Oh, Mike.
It's really you?
It's me.
- I'm here.
- Okay.
Everyone's here.
Shit. Shit. Shit.
Oh shit.
Oh shit. Oh shit. Oh shit. Shit!
Eleven.
You… Are you okay?
- I'm okay.
- Okay.
Hey, guys. We gotta go.
We gotta get you outta here.
Papa.
Eleven.
I want you to know
I'm proud of you.
So very proud.
You
are my family.
My child.
I've only ever
wanted to help you.
To protect you.
Everything I did,
I did for you.
I need you to understand.
Please tell me you understand.
Please.
Goodbye, Papa.
- We need to get to Hawkins.
- I know. And we will.
But we need to get you somewhere safe.
Gonna be people behind us.
No, Mike,
we need to get to Hawkins tonight.
We'll never make it.
That's over 2,000 miles.
We need to find a way.
If we don't, they are going to die.
Who's gonna die?
El, who's gonna die?
"Separate Ways"
by Journey playing...
♪ Here we stand ♪
♪ Worlds apart, hearts broken in two ♪
♪ Two ♪
♪ Sleepless nights ♪
♪ Losing ground ♪
♪ I'm reachin' for you ♪
♪ You ♪
♪ Someday, love will find you ♪
♪ True love won't desert you ♪
♪ You know I still love you ♪
♪ Though we touched
And went our separate ways ♪
Music builds to dramatic climax...