It's perfect.
- Somewhere like…
- Yeah.
I can totally see it.
You in Indiana.
- Indiana?
- Yeah.
Well, you have a certain stoic...
More Clint Eastwood than...
Good news, my friends.
Katinka feeling better.
Shall we give her another try?
Why not?
Asshole.
This guy.
Yuri!
That's enough.
That's enough! Hey!
The hell you think you're doing?
Get your hands off me, potato head.
You're trying to break her, aren't ya?
Get us captured again
so you can get your reward? That it?
What do you two lizard brains know?
You're engineers now?
I know that sound is not good.
On contrary, those noises you hear,
that…
…it's very good sign.
- Good sign, huh?
- Yeah.
My women make noise when I please them.
You don't know what that is like.
I understand.
But for those like me
who knows what and where to touch,
much noise.
Yeah.
These are the smallest I could find.
That's it for shirts.
Oh. Well…
Cute.
Yuri has good taste. What can I say?
Um…
- Oh, sorry.
- Sorry.
- I'll go over here.
- Okay.
What did they do to you?
Oh my God.
No, it's not that bad. It's…
You know, I needed to lose weight anyway.
It's given me time to think, you know?
About who I've been and…
And what I've done.
I never should've sent you that message.
You didn't know what was gonna happen.
I knew it'd be dangerous.
So did I.
I made this choice.
And I would choose it again,
even knowing everything that I know.
I would.
Plus, you know,
we do have that date to get to.
Remember?
"Remember"?
I've been dreaming about it.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah.
I have it all planned out.
Pray tell.
I'm getting two orders
of bread sticks. Two.
Those things knock your socks off.
Enzo puts some spice on 'em.
I don't know what it is, but it's good.
And you dip it in olive oil?
Forget about it.
And, uh, I'm wavering on the main course
between the veal and the lasagne.
But I think I gotta go
with lasagne, right?
So, you… you've been dreaming
about bread sticks and lasagne?
I've been on a diet of watery soup,
moldy bread, and maggots,
so, yeah, I've been dreaming
about bread sticks and lasagne.
I mean, sue me.
Should I have been dreaming
about something else?
You tell me.
Well,
there's wine.
Oh, well, wine's good.
I was thinking about a nice "Cheeanti."
- Chianti.
- Chianti, right.
- Then there's dessert.
- You gotta have dessert.
Gotta have dessert.
And after that?
I don't know.
Use your imagination.
Who needs imagination?
- Damn it!
- Remember, they're listening!
Okay.
I wanna run through it one more time.
- Phase one.
- We meet Erica at the playground.
She'll signal Max and Lucas
when we're ready.
- Phase two.
- Max baits Vecna.
He'll go after her,
which'll put him in his trance.
- Phase three?
- Me and Eddie draw the bats away.
Four.
We head into Vecna's
newly bat-free lair, and…
…flambé.
Nobody moves on to the next phase
until we've all copied.
Nobody deviates from the plan,
no matter what.
Got it?
Got it.
- Be careful.
- Thanks, buddy.
Here goes nothing.
What does he want us to do, applaud?
All right.
Let's go.
Gotcha.
Hey, guys, listen.
If things here start to go south,
I mean, at all,
you abort.
Okay? Draw the attention of the bats.
Keep 'em busy for a minute or two.
We'll take care of Vecna.
Don't try to be cute
or be a hero or something.
- Okay? You guys are just...
- Decoys.
Don't worry. You can be the hero, Steve.
Absolutely. I mean,
look at us.
We are not heroes.
Hey, Steve?
Make him pay.
No, no.
Like I said, I… I've tried everyone.
Yeah, TWA, Pan Am, Eastern.
No, it doesn't have to be a one-way.
I'll take one seat, if you have it.
I mean, please,
there has to be something that you can do.
One of our family members
is really, really sick,
and I don't know
if she's gonna make it through the night.
Is there any way that you could just…
No. No. No.
Like I said before,
I… I've tried them already.
Okay, well, is there any way
that I could speak to a manager?
There… There's no one there?
No, that's the problem. I can't call back.
Breathe. Sunflower.
Rainbow. Three to the right. Four to the…
Three.
Rainbow.
Get away!
- Damn it.
- What'd they say?
Earliest is tomorrow.
- No. That's way too late.
- Shit.
- I know.
- Hey, dudes?
Ask 'em if we can ride
in the baggage compartment.
The baggage compartment?
We'd suffocate.
Dogs ride in there all the time, man.
They don't suffocate.
- Jesus Christ.
- Holy shit.
I have a way.
A way to protect Max.
From here.
This is Max.
When One attacks, he'll be in her mind.
But I can do that too.
I went into Mama's mind, into Billy's.
I can go into Max's.
She can carry me to Vecna.
I can piggyback.
I can protect her.
From One.
Fight him from here.
Mind fight. Righteous.
Wait, so you actually think this can work?
A bathtub would help.
Yeah. Gotta be clean to enter the mind.
What? No, no.
It's a sensory deprivation tank.
It helps her calm down
and focus on her powers.
Wait, we… we just passed a motel.
Yeah, but they won't have enough salt.
Well, how much salt
are we talking here, my dudes?
Well, depends on
the size of the tub, but a lot.
Does 600 pounds suffice?
You know a place
that has 600 pounds of salt?
Let's see…
Yep.
Mm-hmm.
Yep. It'll work.
What will work?
I know a magical place
that has all you need,
my brave, little super powered friend.
That mind fight is on.
Come on.
¡Vámonos! Let's go! Pronto!
Hey!
- I think we got something.
- Send Ryan.
I don't wanna waste any more time
with bullshit leads.
I don't think you'll wanna
send Ryan on this one.
You know the murder house on More head?
Yeah.
What about it?
Okay, and, uh, who exactly
was this mystery woman?
Not sure.
I mean, she wasn't exactly Miss Talkative.
You know? I spent five minutes
trying to convince her I was real.
I'm supposed to be dead, remember?
Anyway, I finally get around
to half-convincing her,
she starts to open up a little,
then says that she's…
A friend of the doc's.
Great, so am I.
Now put me on the phone with him.
I'm afraid the doc is indisposed.
"Indisposed"?
It gets worse.
She said the doc's with the girl.
And the girl went off to fight
some evil in Hawkins.
Then they all went off-grid.
The doc, the girl, everybody.
"The girl," meaning… El.
Yeah, it has to be.
This is your daughter, American?
Mm-hmm.
And they're not alone.
Joyce's kids are with 'em.
Okay, I… I see the mood here is bleak.
And understandably so.
But I do think we need to consider
the very real possibility
that this mystery woman is, in fact, KGB.
- And she's...
- No.
She's telling the truth.
When we were in the lab,
those particles we saw,
they were alive.
And if they're alive,
that means a gate's open in Hawkins.
"Gate"? What does this mean?
It means we have to go home right now.
What is taking so long?
I thought you said he was close.
Yeah, close to sabotaging us, you mean.
We think he's playing us again.
So put a goddamn gun to his head.
And then what?
He just spits out more lies.
It's moot anyway.
If your kids are truly
in some kind of imminent danger,
even if we were to leave this very moment,
we wouldn't make it in time.
The earliest we'd get there
is late tomorrow.
No, we… we don't have to make it back.
Not tonight.
Whatever this evil is,
we know it's connected to the hive mind.
And now we know
part of that hive mind is in Russia.
So we don't need
to get back to Hawkins to fight it.
All we need is to destroy those particles.
And if we're lucky,
it'll hurt it enough
to give the kids the upper hand.
Wait, time out.
We're talking about the particles
inside the prison?
The prison that
we just narrowly escaped from?
We broke out.
We can break back in.
Jim!
The entire Soviet army is looking for us.
Sure. And we'll be exactly
where they least expect.
All right. There is a fine line
between courage and stupidity,
and this falls very far
on the side of stupid.
This is Dirty Dozen stuff.
Except there are, uh, four of us.
Three, actually.
Breaking back in's gonna be easier
than breaking out.
Which is why we need an airlift.
This is where you come in.
I don't care what it takes.
You get Yuri in line,
and you get that bird in the air.
On it.
Yu… Yuri mentioned something
about a flamethrower, right?
Oh, yeah.
This'll do.
This'll do just fine.
You gotta be shitting me.
Trust me on this one, my dudes.
Surf's up, my dude.
Uh, whoa.
Nice shirt, my dude.
Thanks, my dude.
Uh, listen, I would love to feed
a fellow Surfer Boy,
but kitchen closed, like,
five minutes ago,
so no more pies tonight, man.
That's all right, my dude.
We're not here for your tasty pies.
You see this weird girl behind me?
She needs a tub with a bunch of salt
so we can enhance her psychic power
so she can save the world
from this super bad dude.
But to make this salty tub,
we require your kitchen.
Ah.
Well, it's just, uh…
I'm supposed to meet Chaz at Taco Bell
in, like, ten. So…
My dude.
We're not asking you to help for free.
You ever partake in…
Purple Palm Tree Delight?
It'll make all your troubles float away.
Like the seed pods of a dandelion
in the wind.
First-ever mind fight
held in a pizza dough freezer.
Pretty rad, right?
Not bad.
Not bad at all.
Now for the fun part.
Jesus Chr…
It's like… she was destined
for an alternate dimension.
What do you say, Henderson?
Are you ready for the most metal concert
in the history of the world?
That a rhetorical question?
Let's do it.
Uh…
I don't mean to freak anyone out,
but I swear we've seen this tree before.
- That's impossible.
- That would suck, right?
If Vecna destroyed the world
because… 'cause we got lost in the woods?
We're not lost, Robin.
Robin, hey.
Watch out for the vines! Hive mind.
- Remember?
- Thank you!
Uh, Don't worry about her.
She's just stressed.
You know, scared.
Yeah. Yeah. I… I know.
It's just…
She's a super klutz?
She did tell me that it took her
longer to walk than most babies, so…
I really shouldn't laugh.
When I was a baby,
I actually crawled backwards.
Crawled backwards?
You know, I'd push
with my hands like this. Beep. Beep.
Always in reverse, you know?
Come on, it makes sense.
You push to move, right?
No, no, it doesn't make sense.
Well, it did
to my tiny little Harrington brain.
That is, until I reversed
my baby butt down a flight of stairs
and thumped my head really good.
Yeah.
Wow. That explains
so much.
Yeah.
I think it kinda does.
I think, like, right out of the gate,
like, I'm super confident.
But I'm also, like, an idiot.
Which is just…
I mean, it's a brutal combination.
But, I mean, the good news is,
I get a big enough thump on my head,
I can change, you know?
I can learn.
I can
crawl forward.
Listen, I guess what I'm trying to say
in a really stupid, roundabout way is, um…
…is thank you.
Thank me?
- Yeah.
- For…?
For giving my head
the biggest thump of its life
two years ago.
I needed it.
It's changed my life.
And now I'm crawling forward.
Slowly.
I just wonder sometimes…
You know, if… some other girl had given me
a proper thump before we'd met,
would things have been different?
Like, if we were meeting together
for the first time right now, part of me…
I dunno, part of me
thinks we would've made it.
Steve…
Remember the dream I told you about?
About the Winnebago?
Seeing the country
with my six lil' nuggets?
It's all true.
Every last word.
But I left one part out.
It's the most important part.
You're there.
You've always been there.
Hey, guys!
You guys! Awesome news!
Looks like we weren't
going the wrong way after all.
Come on.
- Let's go!
- Okay.
Ro… Slow down! Ro… Robin!
Erica.
Where are the guards?
Maybe this'll be easier than we thought.
I don't know, Jim.
I got a bad feeling about this.
I have a question.
What if I don't want to answer?
Have you always been a coward?
Yuri Ismaylov
is many things, you traitor.
But he is…
No coward.
If that is so,
why do you continue to stall?
What do I owe these Americans?
Nothing!
This isn't just about America, smuggler.
They have warned us
of a great evil in the world.
An evil that does not rest,
that does not respect borders.
After it has consumed
everything in their land,
it will come for us.
For our families.
For our Motherland.
You saw it with your own eyes.
You know it to be true.
And yet you continue to play tricks!
I was told the Peanut Butter Smuggler
was once a great man.
Before he lost his way to drink and cards.
That he led his men to victory
over the Chinese in Damansky.
Is it true?
It is true.
That hero, where is he now?
Because I do not see him.
Come on. Come on.
Okay, the lovebirds have copied.
Max is moving into phase two:
distracting Vecna.
So far, so smooth.
Yeah, we're not even at the hard part yet.
Take the bait, you son of a bitch.
Take the bait.
Hey!
Asshole!
I'm here.
No more music.
No more games.
Do you hear me?
What are you waiting for, huh?
Come on! Do you want me or not?
Okay, almost done.
Okay, so, hopefully this blocks out
any peripheral light, right?
And it's totally dark,
which means it works.
But I have one more important question:
do I look cool?
Feel like I look really cool.
Are you giggling?
You're giggling because I look awesome.
I can't see it, but I know you're smiling
because I look so good. Right?
- Mike.
- Yeah?
I…
Missed you.
Yeah.
Yeah, I missed you too.
You know,
the last few days, I… I've had to think
about the last talk we had.
You know, before the cops and…
The whole world went to shit?
I… I guess
I just…
I dunno.
I guess I just wanted to say that...
Surf's up, Romeo.
Oh, uh, too much flavor awesomeness
can't overpower your battery, can it?
- Dude, this is pineapple.
- Try before you deny.
- Good.
- Hmm?
- It's good? What do you mean?
- Really good.
What? That's insane.
Blasphemous. Putting fruit on pizza?
- Did you try? Try before you deny.
- No. I...
- Try before you deny!
- Stop! Enough! I'm not a dog!
- No, not a baby! Thank you!
- Try some.
- Try before you deny!
- No!
No! Stop it!
Okay! Okay!
No, you're right. It's good.
Do you remember that time you told me
you had a Lego stuck up your nose?
- What?
- Yeah.
Like, it was like a…
It was like a construction guy.
You'd call him Larry.
Come on! You don't remember?
He had the high viz jacket
and removable hat?
Yeah.
Vaguely.
Well, I remember it like it was yesterday.
Man, I was… I was freaked.
'Cause… 'Cause this Larry…
I mean, Larry was way, way up there.
I don't even know
how you got him that far up.
I had to do surgery.
I… I had to get tweezers to pull him out.
- Bull.
- No.
No, no, I swear on my life.
I don't know, I just…
I feel like you used to
come to me more for help.
Or to just… talk, you know?
'Cause, like, you don't do that anymore.
Not like before.
A lot of that is probably my fault.
This last year…
…I know I've been distant.
Or stoned.
Yeah.
But that has nothing to do with you.
And that's me dealing with my own shit.
Hiding from my own problems.
The truth is,
I miss talking to you.
I, like, really miss it.
And I think,
right now,
we need to talk more than ever.
Because things are getting
just complicated.
A lot more complicated
than Legos up the nose, you know?
I just…
I don't want you to forget that I'm here.
And I'll always be here.
No matter what.
Because you're my brother.
And I love you.
And there is nothing in this world, okay,
absolutely nothing,
that will ever change that.
You got that?
Yeah.
And I'm always
here for you too.
I know.
I know you are.
Come here.
It's gonna be okay.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
I think it's ready.
All right.
It's time.
Wild.
I found them.
They're carrying a light.
A blue light.
What are you waiting for, asshole?
Hmm? I'm right here.
I'm right here!
Okay, El, what's going on?
It's not working.
What? What's not working?
Max's plan.
I know you can hear me.
I know you can read my thoughts.
Even the worst ones.
Maybe mostly the worst ones.
I thought about what you said.
About how I wanted my brother to die.
I thought you were
just trying to upset me.
To anger me.
But you weren't, were you?
You were just telling the truth.
Billy, he made my life living hell.
Every chance he got.
So, sometimes…
When I would lie in bed at night, I would…
I would pray…
…I would pray
that something would happen to him.
Something awful.
I knew that he drove too fast,
so I would imagine him
crashing.
Dying in that stupid car.
I just…
I wanted him out of my life.
Forever.
I wanted him to disappear.
The day that he died…
I think that's why I just stood there.
Watched.
Not because I was scared or… weak.
But because…
I didn't know if he deserved to be saved.
And I've tried to forgive myself.
I've tried, but…
I can't.
So now…
Now, when I lie in bed at night…
I pray that something will happen to me.
That something terrible will happen to me.
So that's why I'm here.
Because…
I just want you to take me away.
And I want you…
To make me disappear.
Is that all true?
You wanted Billy to die.
Why are you talking?
You ever have thoughts like that about me?
What?
No, Lucas, never.
Normal people don't fantasize
about killing other people, Max.
You realize that, right?
Lucas, please.
I thought you were getting better.
But you're not, are you?
You are sick.
Lucas, you don't mean that.
Maybe it is good he takes you.
Maybe it's for the best.
In fact…
…I'm glad it's going to be you.
You will be the chosen one.
The fourth. The final sacrifice.
It's going to be you
that breaks the world.
Max? Can you hear me?
Max!
He has her.
Max.
- Where are you going? Don't be scared.
- Stay away from me.
Max, I thought you said you were ready.
Ready to disappear!
I said, stay away!
Max. It's okay.
I'm coming.
I'm coming. Just hold on a little longer.
I dunno if you can hear this.
I'm sorry.
I'm so, so sorry, Billy.
- Max, sweetie.
- Mom?
It's gonna be okay, baby.
Ready?
Hi.
- Trick or treat!
- Should've seen the look on your faces.
Maxine.
What's happening now?
I think
I am in a memory.
A Max memory.
Do you see her? Do you see Max?
No.
But she's here.
She has to be here.
Okay, she's in. Initiate phase three.
She's in. Move on to phase three.
Copy that. Initiating phase three.
Let's hope they hear this.
Chrissy, this is for you.
Okay, it's working.
Let's go.
Where are you going, Maxine?
- You see her?
- Yeah.
I see her.
Max!
Let me out of here!
Max! Open the door!
Open the door!
Get off!
Eddie!
We gotta lock down in T-minus 30 seconds!
T-minus 20!
Max! Let me out!
Max! Max!
T-minus ten!
Max!
Five!
One!
Holy shit.
- Move! Move! Move!
- Let's go!
- Eddie, come on!
- Hurry!
- Go, go!
- Shit! Shit!
Hurry! Eddie, shut it!
Hurry! Come on!
Dude!
- Most metal ever!
- Oh my... Oh my God.
Oh dear God.
What happened here?
The monster got in.
The guards, they tried to stop it.
The gunfire shattered the tanks.
The others came alive.
The particles.
Ask him about the particles.
He says
they call it "the shadow."
The shadow
went into them.
Into who?
I think
this answers your question, Jim.
The shadow is in them.
Oh shit.
That's not good.
Shit.
It's okay.
You got this.
Shouldn't you be playing with dolls
or something?
Shouldn't you bag your face?
Max.
Max!
I found her.
But she's young.
She can't see me.
Can't hear me.
Do you see anything weird
in this memory?
Any sign of Vecna or… or the Mind Flayer?
No, everything
is normal.
There is something
that doesn't fit.
I think it is
another memory.
A memory within a memory?
Oh shit.
What the hell is taking so long?
- Let me go, you meat head!
- Shut your mouth or I'll break your arms.
Hear me, you little shit?
Shit.
Jason?
You can't be here right now, man.
- The hell have you done?
- Jason.
You need to leave.
Is this what you did to Chrissy?
- Just listen, Jason.
- Hey.
- You need to go, man.
- Hi. Can… Can you hear me?
Jason, don't touch her.
- I'm not messing around.
- Hey.
- Please, just...
- Hear me?
Hey, back up! Back up!
Not another step.
Wa… Wait. We… We don't have to do this.
- We don't have to do this.
- I hope you're right.
- Wait.
- Is there anyone else in the house?
No. No.
Turn around.
- What?
- Turn around!
Okay, okay. Relax, relax.
- And put down your flashlight.
- It's okay. Okay.
And empty your pockets.
- Empty your pockets!
- Okay. Okay. Okay.
Okay.
Now, this is what's gonna happen.
I'm gonna back away
to the top of the stairs there.
Then I'll watch as you wake her up
from whatever the hell this is.
I can't.
Jason.
If I wake her too soon,
we all die.
No.
You don't wake her up right now,
you die, Sinclair.
Just you.
- You shut off this fence, right?
- Yeah.
Good. So you can turn it back on again.
Jim, you wanna clue us in
on what you're thinking here,
or are we supposed to read your mind?
This pit was designed to trap monsters.
We get 'em in here, we lock it up,
we rain fire from above,
and we hope to hell
that gives El and the kids an upper hand.
Okay.
I'm with ya.
Except the whole, uh…
… "getting them all in here" part.
It's a hive mind.
You draw one,
you draw 'em all.
- You're the grill master.
- Okay.
And you, you're the jailer.
You get that fence turned on.
And once they're all in here,
lock that door behind 'em.
What about you?
I'm the bait.
That one there.
See him? In the laundry room?
It's not far from here.
He's all alone.
He's our target.
- No!
- Let's go!
Hey.
I'm gonna die someday.
But not today.
I still got a date to make, remember?
I don't know, Hop.
This time,
it's gonna be different.
It better be.
I am not having another funeral.
Hey, dip shits!
- Give up that easy, huh?
- Shh!
Is that really necessary?
They're on the roof.
Shit. Shit. Shit.
They can't get in through there, can they?
Die! Die!
Die! Die! Die!
Ugh.
Easy.
Steve!
Nancy!
Eddie!
I need you!
Get out of the way! Get out of the way!
Holy shit. Holy shit.
- Nice.
- Thanks.
Are there other vents?
Oh, shit.
- Shit!
- Shit, shit, shit, shit.
Shit!
That's not gonna hold!
Let's go! Let's go!
Come on! Quickly!
Ah!
Eddie, come on!
Eddie, come on! Let's go!
Eddie, you're so close! Eddie! Let's go!
Eddie.
Eddie!
What are you doing? Eddie, no!
Eddie, stop! Eddie, stop!
Stop! Stop!
Eddie, what are you doing?
- I'm buying more time.
- No!
Eddie, please!
You can't hide from me, Max.
You think I don't see what you're doing?
Is Mike a good kisser?
You think I don't see
everything?
- Please.
- You thought you could trick me?
You thought your friends
could stop me?
I see them.
I see your friends.
Just as clearly
- as I…
- Stop!
…see you.
I can feel them.
I can feel them
dying.
It's time, Max.
It's time.
We call him Vecna.
He lives in another dimension.
That's why you can't see him.
And Eddie Munson
and his… his Hellfire acolytes,
what, you all summoned this Vecna?
No, no, you're not listening. Just listen.
There… There's no cult.
There never was.
- You expect me to believe that?
- It's the truth.
- Then why was Chrissy at Eddie's trailer?
- She was buying drugs.
Liar!
Okay.
Chrissy…
She was seeing things.
Terrible things.
Things Vecna forced her to see.
- She was scared.
- No.
She just needed help.
That's how I know you're lying.
If Chrissy was scared,
if… if Chrissy wanted help,
she would've come to me!
Not Eddie!
Not that freak! Never!
You're wrong about Eddie.
No.
But I was wrong about you.
I never should've let you in the door.
And I never should have knocked.
I thought I wanted to be like you.
Popular.
Normal.
But it turns out,
normal's just a raging psychopath.
You have five seconds to wake her up.
Four.
Three.
Hey! Hey!
Crit hit!
No! No!
You are brave, Maxine.
Much braver than your brother.
But in the end…
You are weak
and fragile,
just like him.
Like all the rest of them.
And you
will
break.
You.
Hi.
Come get me, you sons of bitches!
Screw it.
I didn't know what to do, so I… I…
I ran away.
I just ran, and I left her there.
I mean, look at us.
We are not heroes.
Shit!
Max, are you okay?
Huh?
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Are you…
Are you real?
Di… Did I make you?
I'm real.
How?
I piggybacked from a pizza dough freezer.
What?
Uh...
Stay back.
If you touch her again,
I will kill you again.
Is that what you did?
Hmm?
Did you kill me?
I am so glad
you are here, Eleven.
This…
Is going to be
beautiful.
So beautiful.
And it's all thanks to you.
She's fighting him.
Eddie!
Come on!
Before
I kill you…
…I want you to watch.
Papa is dead.
I know what he did to you.
You were different.
Like me.
And he hurt you.
He made you…
Into this.
He is the monster, Henry.
Not you.
You're right.
You
and I,
we are different.
And Papa did hurt me.
But he was no monster.
He was just a man.
An ordinary, mediocre man.
That is why he sought greatness in others.
In you.
And me.
Hmm.
But in the end…
He could not control us.
He could not shape us.
He could not change us.
Do you not see, Eleven?
He did not make me into this.
You did.
At first,
I believed you had sent me to my death.
To purgatory.
But I was wrong.
I was somewhere new.
I became an explorer.
An explorer of a realm
unspoiled by mankind.
I saw so many things.
And one day,
I found the most
extraordinary thing of all.
Something
that would change everything.
I saw a means to realize my potential.
To transcend my human form.
To become the predator
I was always born to be.
It was…
It was you.
Always you.
All I needed was someone to open the door.
And you did that for me.
Without even realizing it.
Didn't you?
And when you did realize,
you chose to resist.
So I sought a means to open my own doors.
I sought…
Your power.
All this time, we've been building it.
For you.
So, don't you see?
Once again,
you have freed me.
No.
You don't have to do this.
You can still stop this.
It is over, Eleven.
Your friends
have lost.
No!
Eddie!
There is nothing…
Nothing you can do
to stop this now.
Hawkins will burn and fall.
And the rest of this senseless,
broken world.
And I will be there.
Lucas!
I will be there
to pick up the pieces when it does.
Lucas!
And remake it into something… beautiful.
There was a time
when I had hoped to have you by my side.
But now I just want you to watch.
Don't be afraid.
Try and stay very still.
No.
It will all be over soon.
Max!
El! El, can you hear me?
El, come on. Wake up! Wake up, El!
- Wake up! El!
- She can't breathe.
El, get outta there!
God, El! Wake up! Wake up!
Help me! Help me!
On the table. Get her on the table.
El, can you hear me?
El! El!
Can you hear me?
El!
Mike.
Don't stop. Okay?
You're the heart.
Okay? Remember that.
El?
I don't know if you can hear this,
but… but if you can,
I want you to know I'm here, okay?
I'm right here.
And…
I love you.
El, do you hear me?
I'm sorry I don't say it more.
I… It's not because I'm scared of you.
I'm not.
I've never felt that way.
Never.
But I am scared that one day
you'll realize you don't need me anymore.
And I thought if I said how I felt,
it would somehow make that day
hurt more.
But the truth is, El,
I don't know how to live without you.
I feel like my life started
that day we found you in the woods.
You were wearing
that yellow Benny's Burgers T-shirt.
And it was so big,
it almost swallowed you whole.
And I knew right then and there,
in that moment, that I loved you.
And I've loved you every day since.
I love you on your good days.
I love you on your bad days.
I love you with your powers,
without your powers.
I love you for exactly who you are.
You're my superhero.
And…
I can't lose you.
Okay? Do you hear me? I can't lose you.
You can do anything.
You can fly. You can move mountains.
I believe that.
I really do.
But right now,
you just have to fight.
Okay?
El.
Do you hear me?
You need to fight!
You have to fight.
Fight!
That's it, El.
Fight, El.
Fight.
Fight!
Eddie!
Max!
Fight!
Joyce!
Hop!
Hey, assholes!
Yeah!
I don't believe in a higher power
or divine intervention.
But that was a miracle.
Then we better not waste it.
Phase four.
Flambé.
You and your friends
believe you have won.
Don't you?
But this
is only the beginning.
The beginning of the end.
You have already lost.
No.
You have.
Max! Max! Max!
Son of a bitch!
Whoo!
Yeah!
Katinka!
Eddie!
Oh God!
Oh God, Eddie.
Bad, huh?
No. You're gonna be fine.
- Just gotta get you to a hospital, okay?
- Okay.
- All right. All right.
- I think…
Come on.
I think I just…
I think I just need a second, okay?
Okay.
I didn't run away this time, right?
No. No. No. No.
You didn't run.
You're gonna have to look after
those little sheep for me, okay?
No, you're gonna do that yourself.
Nah, man.
Say, "I'm gonna look after them."
Say it.
I'm…
I'm gonna look after…
Good.
'Cause I'm actually gonna graduate.
I think it's my year, Henderson.
I think it's finally my year.
I love you, man.
I love you too.
Eddie…
Eddie?
Eddie!
Come on.
Lucas!
We need a doctor!
Call an ambulance!
Hurry! Call an ambulance!
- Lucas…
- Yes, yes I'm here. I'm here.
I… I can't feel or… …see anything.
I know. I know. It's okay.
We're gonna get you help, okay?
Just… Just hold on.
Lucas, I'm scared.
I'm so scared. I'm so scared.
I know. I know. I know.
I don't wanna die. I'm not ready.
You're not gonna die. Hang on.
I don't wanna go! I'm not ready.
You're not gonna die!
Just… Just hang on!
Max. Max! Max!
No, no, no, Max. Stay with me.
- No.
- Stay with me! Don't go, Max.
Max, stay with me.
Just look at me, Max. Max, look.
No. Stay with me, Max.
Hang on. Just hang on.
Erica, help!
Max?
Max? Max? Max?
Max, stay with me.
No! No!
Max! Max! Please, stay with me!
No!
Max!
Four chimes.
Max.
Holly! Holly!
Come on.
Come on. I know you're in there.
I know you're in there. Wake up.
Wake up.
No.
You're not going.
Hi.
Hi…?
Max wanted to have a sleepover.
Which one?
This is Wonder Woman.
AKA Princess Diana.
Not Hopper.
Not Mike.
You.
Holy shit. This is insane.
Is this really gonna work?
See? What'd I tell you?
There's more to life than stupid boys.
Against the rules?
We make our own rules.
It's been less than 48 hours
since a 7.4 magnitude earthquake
rocked the quaint town of Hawkins,
80 miles outside of Indianapolis,
in an event that seismologists are calling
"a natural disaster
of near-unprecedented scale."
The death toll now stands at 22.
But with hundreds more
filling Roane County hospitals
and many more still missing,
officials expect those numbers to rise.
Go! This way! This way! Let's go!
This is only the latest tragedy
to befall this once-safe town.
Most recently, a string
of high school students were killed
in a series of ritualistic murders,
which have been linked
to a local satanic cult
known as "Hellfire."
Eddie Munson, the leader of this cult
and prime suspect in the murders,
has been missing since the earthquake
and is presumed dead.
But this offers little comfort
to the people of Hawkins,
who are scared, angry,
and searching for answers.
Why their town? What have they done
to deserve so much suffering?
A growing chorus believes
the two recent tragedies are linked,
claiming the Munson murders
opened a doorway between worlds.
A doorway, they say, into hell itself.
Are you hearing this?
They're now calling it
a doorway into hell.
Great. More hysteria. Just what we need.
Well, it's the news.
Now indistinguishable from the tabloids.
Hey, Nance!
I found some more of your old stuff
in the attic.
Mr. Rabbit.
It's okay if you wanna save him, you know?
No, he'll be more loved in a new home.
- Someone order a pizza?
- Pizza?
Mom!
Hey!
You are never going on vacation again,
you hear me?
In fact, you can forget about college.
You are staying right here.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm okay.
But, Jonathan...
This isn't an earthquake.
I know.
I know a lot more than you think.
How?
- We've been trying to call you...
- I know.
I know. I'm sorry.
We just couldn't risk contact.
"We couldn't risk contact"?
Hey, hey, I'll tell you everything, okay?
- Okay.
- I promise.
But, for now,
I'm just glad you're safe.
Where's Lucas?
He's at the hospital.
Was he hurt?
No. No, he's…
Oh God.
You don't know.
"He opened his eyes,
and further words died in his throat."
"He forgot about the need to sick up
that horrible parody of wine."
"He forgot about his mother,
and Uncle Morgan, and his father,
and almost everything else."
"Speedy was gone."
"The graceful arcs of the roller coaster
against the sky were gone."
"He could feel the hair stirring
on the nape of his neck,
could feel a goofed-up grin
pulling at the corners of his mouth."
"Speedy! I'm here, my God!"
"I'm here in the territories!"
Oh my God.
- We've been calling you guys like crazy.
- I know.
We came as soon as we heard.
I'm sorry.
Do they know…
When she will wake?
No.
They say she might not.
Her heart stopped.
For over a minute.
She died.
I… I mean, clinically, but…
Then she came back.
The doctors don't know how.
They say it's a miracle.
I'm here, Max.
- Hi.
Uh, so these are blankets and sheets.
And some… some clothes
and… and some kids' toys.
Wow. It's already so organized.
We appreciate that.
- Do you want a tax receipt for it?
- Um…
No. I don't think that we need one.
Thank you, though.
But is there anything else
that we can do to help?
Okay, then we sort by age.
We've got infants, girls,
boys, men, women…
Oh, if anything is in too bad shape,
we really don't want that.
I found another jar of peanut butter,
and it's crunchy…
Robin.
Hi.
- What are you doing here?
- I am…
I… I am making PB&Js.
Right, yeah. No. Duh. Of course.
Uh, I… I am also making PB&Js,
as it so happens.
Cool.
Hey, uh, I… I'm sorry
if that came out weird.
I didn't mean it like,
"What are you doing here?"
I just meant, "What are you doing here?"
Like, "Nice surprise. Great to see you."
Uh…
- I didn't take it as anything negative.
- Okay, good. Good.
No, I… I'm sorry.
My brain's been a little frazzled lately.
- 'Cause...
- Of everything?
Yeah.
Yeah, and Dan.
Um, he's my boyfriend.
Well, was my boyfriend.
He was visiting, took one look at this,
and it's not what he was envisioning
for spring break.
He was like, "I'm outta here.
Back to Purdue. Good luck."
Which, ultimately, it's bordering on
a good thing, 'cause he was grating on me.
He is the type who trashes Fast Times
'cause it has no plot.
I should've just ended things
right there and then.
Sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I am rambling about my dumb boyfriend
when there are people out there suffering.
Who need… food.
And I have just made a peanut butter
on peanut butter monstrosity.
Um…
I don't know what's wrong with me.
Um, it's like sometimes my mouth
is moving faster than my brain,
and it's like this runaway train,
and I cannot seem to get it to stop,
no matter how hard I try.
You know what I mean?
Uh, yeah, I think I know what you mean.
It's a gift.
- Oh, for me?
- You're welcome. Mm-hmm.
- You really shouldn't have.
- Oh, but I did.
- I just don't even deserve it.
- But I did.
- I mean, thank you.
- Early birthday.
Thank you so much. Oh, oh, wow.
H2O?
Vital for all forms of life.
Mr. Munson?
I'm Dustin Henderson.
Can we talk?
I can't imagine
we got anything to talk about.
My nephew is innocent.
He's still missing.
I'll put up as many posters as I need
until he's found.
Good day to you.
I was with him.
I was with him when the earthquake hit.
And… where is Eddie now?
I'm…
I'm so sorry.
I wish everyone had gotten to know him.
Really know him.
Because they would've loved him,
Mr. Munson.
They would've loved him.
Even in the end…
He never stopped being Eddie.
Despite everything.
I never even saw him get mad.
He could've run.
He could've saved himself.
But he fought.
He fought and died to protect this town.
This town that… hated him.
He isn't just innocent…
Mr. Munson, he's…
He's a hero.
Oh Jesus.
Holy shit.
This place is a total disaster.
Yeah.
Well, that's a bit of a problem.
I get we gotta hide Supergirl,
but this isn't exactly
the Fortress of Solitude, man.
It's more like a fortress of grodiness.
Come on, guys, seriously.
I've seen Mike's room
look worse than this.
Ah, brutal, dude.
Ah! See?
Water still works.
And, voilà. Cleaning supplies.
All right. That's good.
Hold it right there.
What's he doing?
Looks like
he's gathering mushrooms.
He's a little on the eccentric side.
Welcome to the club, right?
Yeah, welcome to the club.
Hey, Nancy?
Yeah?
I'm sorry I wasn't here.
Oh. I mean…
To be honest, I'm kinda glad you weren't.
I just mean, I'm glad you were with Mike.
And Will.
And I'm… I'm glad you were here too.
Otherwise, who'd have been in charge?
Steve?
He's actually grown up quite a bit,
you know?
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm sure.
Hey.
Yeah?
Are we okay?
Yeah.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, totally.
Yeah, it's… it's just…
You know, it's hard.
I feel like
life keeps throwing things
in the way of our big plans.
Yeah, sure seems like that.
You think it's too late to throw
"saving the world" on your college resume?
Your… Your application letter…
Not that it matters at all anymore, but…
Did it ever come?
No. No, uh…
Not yet.
Did she… talk to you at all?
Not much.
I mean, a little bit.
Dr. Brenner.
He says that she wasn't ready.
And now she's starting to think
he was right.
That's crap.
If it wasn't for her,
if she hadn't left the lab,
- Max wouldn't be alive right now.
- I know.
It's just, she's, um…
She's never lost before.
Not like this.
- She'll have another chance.
- Let's hope not.
Let's hope One is dead and rotting.
He's not.
Now that I'm here, in Hawkins,
I can feel him.
And he's hurt.
He's hurting.
But he's still alive.
It's strange, knowing now who it was
this whole time, but…
I can still remember what he thinks,
and how he thinks.
And he's not going to stop.
Ever.
Not until he's taken everything.
And everyone.
We have to kill him.
And we will.
We will.
Government.
Max?
Max!
Hey, kid.
Hi.
I kept it open.
- I kept the door open three inches.
- I know.
I never stopped believing.
Oh, I know. It's okay.
It's okay.
It's okay. I'm here.
I'm here.
You look…
Not fat?
And your hair.
My hair?
Look at your hair.
Yeah.
I kinda stole your look, kid.
Well, what do you think?
- Bitchin'.
- Hmm.
You aren't the only one
that didn't stop believing.
Oh!
I'm happy
you went to your…
Conference.
That was quite the experience.
Oh.
Hey.
You've grown.
Yeah.
You shrunk.
Mom, it's snowing!