I've seen you grow up.
Become a man.
The whole cycle of your life.
Time chose you.
God chose you.
Don't forget
that we are your home now, too.
No harm will come to you.
We're watching over you.
Time is always with you.
Wherever you go.
You carry it in you.
And it carries you.
It sees and hears everything
that you do and say.
Claudia! Haven't you left yet?
I... I forgot the milk money.
-But it's okay.
-Wait.
Get yourself some fruit drops.
Thanks.
Do you think she noticed?
Don't worry.
Every family has its secrets.
Are you going somewhere?
Nowhere special.
Just some errands.
You're beautiful.
JUNE 23, 1954
FOUR DAYS UNTIL THE APOCALYPSE
Helge.
And if we know that He listens
to what we ask for,
we can be sure
that we have what we've asked of Him.
Nothing is lost from His sight.
He returns all things.
POLICE
Seven months on and we still have no idea
who this monster is.
Why is he refusing to reveal his identity?
Why is no one looking for him?
It makes you wonder
how some people live.
Almost like ghosts.
Egon...
Can I ask you something?
Your wife and you,
are things still...
Do you still have...
A lot?
No. At all.
Look at that.
I didn't think
they still made people like you.
Boy, Egon...
You've got to let off some steam.
Marriage isn't...
the way it's sold to us.
As soon as they have children
they become different people.
It's like they're married to the brats.
It's how nature wanted it.
But out there...
there are still loads
of tender buds to pluck.
They found him!
Found who?
The Doppler boy.
Helge Doppler?
-His body?
-No.
The boy is alive.
He just walked in the door
as if nothing had happened.
Do you like your mother?
Mine is peculiar sometimes.
She always acts like I don't get anything.
When I have kids I'll be different.
How come you never talk about
how it was where you're from?
Before you came to Winden?
My mother was often sad.
I was in an orphanage for ages.
She doesn't like to talk about it,
so I don't, either.
Don't you have any family
besides your mother?
My mother has a brother.
But I think they hate each other.
Do you think she's happy here?
Will you show it to me now?
Where are those damn ghosts?
-Have you seen my book?
-What book?
The Ghosts!
You don't have to gawp at me like that.
I know I'm late.
-Did you put that there?
-No, I...
I thought maybe...
Maybe you'd like to skip school
and we'll do something nice.
I don't know. I just thought we haven't
done anything together in so long.
I have a German exam today,
and I wanted to go to the lake later.
Maybe another time.
Regina, wait.
I like how you wear your hair now.
It makes you look so... grown up.
Thanks.
I don't have any time. I have to go.
Time...
A JOURNEY THROUGH TIME
FOR CLAUDIA FROM HELGE
Hello, Mrs. Doppler.
I've already told
your colleagues everything.
I'd like to ask Helge a few questions.
He still hasn't said a single word.
Something is odd about the boy.
It won't take long.
Helge.
Remember me?
I'm Claudia's father.
Won't you tell me
where you were all this time?
And with whom?
Who did that to you?
The inspector asked you something.
Say something, for goodness sake!
I just wanted to see how you're doing.
It may sound peculiar, but I...
The book from last year.
-Why did you give it to me?
-I...
thought...
you may be the only one
who understands me.
Time is always with you
wherever you go.
You carry it in you.
And it carries you.
It sees and hears everything you do
and say.
What's that supposed to mean?
He said...
it's a battle between good and evil,
between light and dark.
That the travelers can undo
everything that happens.
If we succeed, none of it will happen.
Who said that?
Noah.
Who is Noah?
You mustn't trust him. Never! Do you hear?
Never!
Helge!
I'm sorry.
I didn't want all this.
Did anybody see you?
They sent Helge back today.
Noah is back, too.
I'm not scared of him anymore.
You carry the same blood.
You can't choose your family.
Renouncing your blood
means freeing yourself.
You said so yourself.
Still, our family shapes us
our entire lives.
Sic Mundus...
They're preparing the next cycle.
In four days.
Your brother is a blind fool.
All the suffering he causes people.
But it will have an end.
You must give me this.
Not now. There is still time.
Today?
I wanted to thank you.
For everything.
My mother loves you, do you know that?
She will make you very happy
if you let her.
Are you HG Tannhaus?
Heterochromia.
One blue eye,
one brown.
Did you write this book?
I wondered when the day would come.
When we'd meet again.
I don't even know you.
But I know you.
A never-ending cycle.
Peculiar.
And he didn't talk?
What do you make of it?
He just turns up out of nowhere.
Maybe they are unrelated after all.
The madman who killed the children
and the Doppler boy.
How could he have done it?
He's been doing time for six months.
Maybe he wasn't alone.
You mean he has an accomplice?
Visit the madman again.
Maybe he'll talk now.
An accomplice. Yes.
CLOSED PSYCHIATRIC WARD 3
I want to know what it all means.
These lyrics.
You said those words to me in 1953.
But this was only released last year.
You said...
you had a son yourself.
Why did you murder the children?
I didn't murder the children.
I wanted to save them.
You said I was going to die.
How did you know I have cancer?
The White Devil?
Do you know who that is?
You're more deranged than I am.
Why did you never tell us
what your name is?
Who you are?
Ulrich.
Ulrich Nielsen.
And I come from the future.
I am what one calls a fraud.
Have you ever heard
of the bootstrap paradox?
No.
In a bootstrap paradox,
an object
or information
from the future is sent back to the past.
That creates a never-ending cycle
in which the object
no longer has any real origin.
It exists
without ever having been created.
Put simply,
this book has traveled back in time.
It found me
before I even wrote it.
It's all a question of origin.
Where is the beginning?
When is the beginning?
Is there a beginning at all?
The world is full of such paradoxes.
Only most of the time,
we choose to look away.
Good luck, but he doesn't talk.
To anyone.
I don't think
you'll get anything out of him.
Hello.
My name is Tiedemann.
Egon Tiedemann. Do you remember me?
I arrested you last year.
There are a few things
I'd like to ask you.
The Doppler boy is back home.
I want to know where Helge was.
Do you have an accomplice?
If you talk to me it...
might influence your situation here.
It's his medication.
We have to sedate him.
Has he said what his name is yet?
Not to my knowledge.
My name is Ulrich Nielsen.
MADS NIELSEN (12) MISSING
MADS NIELSEN CASE:
POLICE IN DARK
WINDEN BOY VANISHES WITHOUT A TRACE
REFERENCE FILE
INTERVIEW TRANSCRIPT
Name unknown.
Age nine to 11.
Claims his father's name
is Ulrich Nielsen.
Don't you want to tell me at last
why you're really here?
You want to know how it works.
How did you know that?
She told me
that you would turn up here one day
and that I should explain the device
to you.
That is,
you, yourself.
Your future self.
The paradox is that a short time ago
I wouldn't have been to explain it to you.
But last year
someone else explained it to me.
Another...
time traveler.
I think she knew it.
She knew everything that would happen,
right up to the present moment.
She knew that you would show up here
for me to tell you,
and therefore her,
how the device works.
I find him creepy.
As if he were empty inside now,
merely a husk.
He was never the brightest child,
but you could now believe he's mindless.
He scares me.
And without Bernd at home, I don't know
how to deal with the situation.
Perhaps the devil himself
has possessed him.
Please look at him and tell me
everything is all right with him.
And he hasn't said a word?
Helge, come downstairs.
Someone wants to talk to you.
Time is always with you.
Wherever you go.
You carry it in you.
And it carries you.
It sees and hears everything
that you do and say.
Your mother is worried about you.
Shall we show her she has no reason to be?
I'd like you to read this for me.
Will you do that?
"You are my protection,
my shield.
I hope for your word."
He speaks!
Give him a little time.
I'm sure he's just choosing his words
with great care.
You can keep it.
Won't you stay a while?
He has returned.
To your bosom.
He is a miracle.
Don't forget that.
So just what are you doing here?
I'm merely trying
to fill in some gaps in a few old files.
Just to order things.
I'd like to talk to the boy.
Michael's asleep.
During the day?
He wasn't feeling well.
Has he ever said anything to you
about his parents?
Michael wants to put that all behind him.
He has a new life now.
Has he ever mentioned their names to you?
First names? Nicknames?
The name Ulrich?
He hasn't mentioned that to you, either?
Has he ever...
talked about a "White Devil"?
No.
I don't understand
what the point of all these questions is.
Perhaps I can talk to him tomorrow?
-Yes.
-Fine.
If anything else comes to mind,
just give me a call.
All right.
SLEEPING PILLS
I, um...
I've been sleeping badly again.
Nightmares.
One more thing.
Do you maybe have a photo of the boy?
Just for the files.
Just for the files, right?
What do you want here?
Did Claudia send you?
If you think Adam will let you back in,
you're wrong.
You picked your side.
There's no salvation for you.
I know where the final pages are.
I also know
how long Adam's been looking for them.
Don't you think he'd do anything
to get them?
I don't believe a word you say.
She would never have told you
where they are.
Claudia has them on her.
In return, I want you to tell Adam
I want to come back.
Before the new cycle begins.
You're sacrificing her?
You can't hate your own sister
the way you hate her.
Consider it a peace offering.
Yes?
There's someone here to see you.
All right.
You can go in.
Can I help you?
One brown eye, one blue eye.
That's rare.
Like my daughter.
You're too good a person.
But you always have been.
The world doesn't deserve you.
Excuse me, but...
do we know each other?
I'm here
because I have to tell you something.
I'm sorry.
What are you sorry about?
Everything.
You don't deserve any of this.
But sometimes
the good ones get hit hardest.
I don't understand.
You will one day.
And then I want you to know
that I'm sorry that things turned out
the way they turned out.
Either you tell me this instant
what this is all about
or I'll ask you to leave immediately.
I am sorry, I really am.
Ms. Tiedemann,
I've been trying to reach you all day.
The people from the press waited
for over an hour.
And...
And?
I postponed the meeting
till 10:30 tomorrow.
You meet the union reps after that.
Cancel all appointments.
And one more thing, your father...
He's here.
I didn't know where to put him.
What are you doing here?
Why didn't you call first?
I wanted to talk to you.
-It won't take long.
-This is really a bad time.
You can just show up here.
Why don't you make an appointment
with my secretary that suits us both?
-Next week, for example.
-I have cancer.
Prostate.
I didn't want to upset you.
But now the cancer has spread.
And I thought
it's best if you know that.
I...
I don't know what to say.
It's okay.
I just wanted you to know.
I'll be on my way then.
I'm sure you have loads to do here.
Dad.
-You're back!
-Hello, my precocious princess.
Where's Mom?
You look sad.
Can you keep a secret?
I think I saw a witch today.
-There are no witches.
-There are!
This one was very real.
How did she look?
Long white hair.
Like in books.
And what did she say?
That she was sorry.
That doesn't sound like a witch.
How would you know?
You've never seen one.
Are those for Mom?
Yes.
You're too good a person, Dad.
The world doesn't deserve you.
Everything okay?
Yes.
It's just déjà vu.
I used to think the worst thing
that could happen to a person in life
is to lose your own child.
But we can't do anything about that.
No matter how hard we try
to hold on to them,
they still leave, sooner or later.
Parents...
Children...
They only share a common path
for a part of their lives.
In the end...
they are miles away from one another.
Last winter
a boy came to Winden.
A stranger.
He said something peculiar to me
at the time.
It makes no sense, but...
Maybe my cancer
is already driving me crazy.
Do you know this boy?
He's here?
Where is he?
You knew he was here?
You knew the whole time?
Where is he? Where is he?
Let go of me!
Where is Mikkel?
I'm closed for the day.
It's you!
I...
It's not ready yet.
It'll take another 33 years
before it's ready.
This thing... The blueprint...
I don't really understand what it is.
I've seen this before.
All our lives
we wonder what our journey will be.
This is yours.
-Keep it. I don't need it anymore.
-Why are you giving it to me?
I'll be dead soon.
I don't understand.
You will.
One day.
And then we'll meet again.
Before you die.
No. After that.
How...
How can that be possible?
Time is just an illusion.
Then you'll have to explain
the device to me.
But I don't know what it's for.
Why don't you tell me what it's for?
Because you told me
someone else explained it to you.
Things take their course,
as they always have.
No, I didn't tell you anything.
No one explained anything to me.
Not now, but in the future.
All this will come to an end soon.
But until then everything must remain
as it always has been.
Wait. Please.
You thought you could trust her.
She betrayed you.
She didn't even bat an eyelid.
You took everything from me.
You're going to die!
And everything you stand for
will die with you.
I know that I am going to die.
But am I going to lose this match?
Or is this here, our meeting,
you and your gun,
only part of a game
you still don't know how to play.
You think you can manipulate me
with your words.
I'm no longer one of your pawns.
But you're still one of Adam's.
The paradise he's promising you
is nothing but a lie.
He's selling you the illusion of freedom.
Ask yourself if you are really free.
If you were really free,
you'd have a choice.
Do you have a choice?
UNIDENTIFIED WOMAN'S BODY
FOUND IN WOODS
That can't be.
Charlotte?
That's not...
No, this isn't right.
This isn't true.
No matter how much we want to fight it,
we are connected through our blood.
We can be alienated from our families
and not understand their actions.
Still, in the end,
we would do anything for them.
A common thread
that connects all of our lives
with each other.
Did she have the pages on her?
She got what she deserved.
In the end, we all get what we deserve.
Subtitle translation by Nathan Fritz