AND IF YOU GAZE LONG INTO AN ABYSS,
THE ABYSS ALSO GAZES INTO YOU.
JUNE 21, 1921
The beginning
and the end.
A strange idea
that both should be the same.
Sic mundus creatus est.
Thus the world was created.
Sic
mundus
creatus est!
You no longer believe the prophecy?
I believe in the irony of fate.
Adam says that all things must happen
as they've always happened.
We have to bear the cross,
no matter how heavy it seems.
In six days paradise begins
and hell on earth will end.
Sometimes I wonder
if paradise and hell
are not one and the same thing.
Adam was right.
You've lost faith.
Is that why he sent you?
I've waited a long time for this moment.
It's interesting that it's you.
I hope that the day comes
when you don't believe
everything Adam tells you.
Ask him...
why he took you in.
And why he called you Noah.
JUNE 27, 2020
BEGINNING OF THE LAST CYCLE
A NETFLIX ORIGINAL SERIES
I think we're a perfect match.
Never believe anything else.
DO NOT OPEN BEFORE NOVEMBER 4,
10:13 P.M.
JUNE 2020
My name is Claudia Tiedemann.
I am one of the few survivors
of the apocalypse of June 27, 2020.
Almost three months
have passed since the catastrophe.
It's still unclear
what exactly led to the events in Winden.
But the God Particle...
If we can stabilize it,
maybe it is a way back.
Back to the past.
Maybe we can save them.
All of them.
JUNE 21, 2020
SIX DAYS UNTIL THE APOCALYPSE
Wake up, late risers!
It's the first week of summer vacation
and it is perfect beach weather.
WHERE IS MIKKEL?
Local news.
Over six months after the mysterious
disappearance of four teenagers,
a senior citizen and a local
police officer from the town of Winden,
there are no clues as to their whereabouts
or the circumstances.
A federal police task force
will now assist with the investigation.
How do you feel today?
Still having joint trouble?
Nausea?
To be honest, your lab results worry me.
We should treat you in the hospital again.
No.
Absolutely not.
-I want to stay here.
-Fine.
We'll wait for the next MRI results.
We may have to switch
from hormone treatment back to chemo.
MARTHA: COME TO THE BRIDGE.
He that has eyes to see...
and ears to hear...
may convince himself that no mortal...
can keep a secret.
If his lips are silent,
he chatters with his fingertips.
Betrayal oozes out of him at every pore.
That was Freud.
I'm Clausen,
head of the Winden task force.
Today I take charge of last year's
unsolved missing persons cases.
The task force's aim
is to reopen these cases entirely,
to review all evidence and clues
until we have unearthed the secrets
that lie hidden below the surface.
Recently, some of you should have received
summons for renewed interrogation.
-Yes?
-You said "we." Who do you mean by that?
Myself and Ms. Doppler,
who is still assigned to these cases.
That's no task force!
Six people have been missing for months.
And that's what they send us?
One person?
And the woman who found nothing?
Ten people
who look at an elephant
from ten different angles
will give ten different statements...
about its shape and appearance.
A single person
who sees that same elephant
from those ten different perspectives...
will be able
to piece together those observations
and to draw the only possible conclusion.
My son is missing.
The next time I need to find an elephant,
I'll let you know!
Right!
Does your mom talk at home?
About the investigation, I mean.
Not to us.
We sit around and wait.
And nothing happens.
We know as little as we did
eight months ago.
Sometimes I think it'd be better
if they were dead.
Don't say that.
I have to go.
Where to?
To pick up Elisabeth at a friend's.
I'll call you later, okay?
I've been trying to reach you for days.
A lot was going on.
I wanted to talk to you.
-I've wanted to for a long time.
-Save your breath.
It's probably better that way.
So...
that's it then.
Because of him?
-Because of Jonas?
-What?
What's that got to do with it?
We hardly ever see each other.
I don't know...
You've changed.
I...
I feel like you're hiding something.
-I don't know what's up with you.
-What's up with me?
What the fuck? My mom is dying!
And...
-there's stuff I can't tell you.
-Why not?
I just can't.
Okay?
If you knew the crap I'm going through...
The crap you're going through?
In case you forgot,
my father and brother have disappeared.
My mom is crazy
and couldn't care less about me.
And you want to tell me about your crap?
It's better this way.
FROM UNKNOWN SENDER:
THIS EVENING.
Energy creates community.
Nuclear power was, is,
and will remain the only alternative.
Nothing is cheaper,
safer, more reliable.
But the outside world insists on progress.
In six days our plant
will be decommissioned for good.
This is a dramatic event for all of us.
I would like to thank you
for your loyalty.
Without you the Winden nuclear power plant
as we know it
could never have existed.
Let us, during these last six days,
fill it with life
in the spirit of the community.
Everything has been prepared for transport
as planned.
And the demolition plans?
Everything at ground level will be left
and become part of the greenfield.
The radiation of the barrels
will be traced to the pool's previous use.
PASSPORT
Hello?
Who are you?
What do you want?
Why do you have a key?
It's my key.
What do you mean, it's yours?
I know it sounds like it makes no sense.
But hear me out.
Do you remember the yellow bike?
The bike you and dad gave me
on my eighth birthday.
I rode it into a ditch the very first day.
I gashed my arm open. Here.
Get out.
Here.
Dad was making pancakes here.
He dropped the pan
and spilled the hot oil here.
I vanished from your life six months ago.
You found me over 33 years ago.
I knew it was you right away.
It was raining, remember?
Grandpa and you wanted
to take me along in the car.
You said it was still acid rain
because of Chernobyl.
I was wearing my yellow coat.
Mom.
It's me.
Jonas?
But that's impossible.
There is no coincidence.
Every path is predetermined.
Everything happens when it must.
At the right time.
In the right place.
As if the world was a carpet
made up of an endless network
of endless threads.
Each in its place.
CAVE ENTRANCE
But very few of us know
where the journey takes them.
You've taken your first step.
Adam will be proud of you.
I felt the same way.
It will pass.
Adam.
Why did he take us in?
Things are still hidden from you.
But they will come to light.
Bit by bit.
When the time is right.
How do we know what's right
and what's wrong?
What is good and what is evil?
By heeding our inner voice.
By not following anyone else
but ourselves.
Our true nature reveals itself not only
in our deeds but also in their purpose.
I am you.
I am your voice.
Never forget that.
Everything is connected.
You.
Me.
The past.
And the future.
No, no!
Stop!
Who are you?
You are hiding it!
There, behind the wall! We saw it!
We followed the signal.
Till the dead zone.
You're hiding God!
You mustn't hide God.
He's not yours alone!
No!
No one can enter the dead zone.
Any attempt will be punished by death.
Those are the rules.
We are the future.
Sic mundus creatus est.
Where were you?
There's nothing out there.
The passage is our only hope.
The faithless are dead.
The prophecy will come true,
the passage will open
and we will be led into paradise.
The faithless are dead?
Everyone is dead, my family, my friends.
Everyone dies in six days, in my time!
I don't need your damn paradise.
I just want to go home.
What did they want behind the wall?
Why did Mom keep it all?
Great-Grandpa died ages ago.
I think because it's the only thing
that reminds her of her family.
Some things are hard to let go of.
It's a shame
I never met Grandpa and Grandma.
Does Mom remember them?
Your mother was still little
when they died.
Come on.
Were you born here?
My grandfather was.
I grew up with him.
Is your grandfather still alive?
No.
Have you thought it could have been him?
-Who? My grandfather?
-No.
Your colleague, Ulrich.
No.
Why?
He called you shortly before he vanished.
The call lasted exactly 12 seconds.
Probably a voicemail message.
What did he want?
Nothing.
He misdialed.
Do you still have the message?
No.
Of course not.
These are the parents' statements.
Thanks, Wöller.
You're welcome.
I had an office set up for you.
Just down the hall.
Disappointments are the result
of false expectations.
"Have hope," my mom always said,
"and no expectations,
then you might get a miracle
and not a disappointment."
Maybe you expected someone different
and got me.
Coincidence?
I don't believe in coincidence.
I think things come together
because they belong together.
Shall we?
Mom?
INVESTIGATION FILE
STEEL DOOR?
It's remarkable people don't crack,
given the futility of their own existence.
An endless cycle of life and death.
Where is the origin of all this suffering?
Did you tell Bartosz?
And he didn't get at all suspicious?
He has always been naive by nature.
The apocalypse has to happen.
Are you having doubts?
What do you do with an old forest
so new trees can grow?
You burn it down.
There isn't much time left.
The missing pages...
you must find them.
Adam?
They're waiting for you.
Six more days.
I'm on my break.
Oh, well... Blow job 40 euros, anal 85.
Kinky stuff costs extra.
But I need to eat first.
Get undressed.
You could say I exist infinitely.
I'm here now.
And I'm in every second
between my birth and my death.
I'm always Jonas.
I'm the same.
And yet not the same.
Like you're not the same person
who came through that door an hour ago.
But where is Jonas?
Where is my Jonas?
He's in the future.
In the future?
Yes.
But he can't come back.
I tried to destroy the passage,
but I only closed it.
That's why he's still there.
Why are you here?
To put an end to it all.
Once and for all.
That's the man!
Which man?
The man with the watch. That's Noah!
Noah?
POLICE
Watch out for the tiniest deviations
in their statements.
Every detail is important.
PETER: I'VE FOUND NOAH.
COME TO THE BUNKER.
Something wrong?
I have to go.
I don't have a driver's license.
I assume it's okay
if I ride with you tomorrow?
Yes.
Mom didn't lock it.
What's that?
Dad's stuff.
Police documents and maps of the cave.
That's why Mom goes in there every day.
I think she's looking for this.
A door. In the caves?
It goes to the nuclear power plant.
They all know something
we're not supposed to know.
Mom, Bartosz.
The police.
Each with their own shitty secret.
Are you ready?
Thanks for the coffee.
I'm glad to get rid of that thing.
Call Mom again. Okay?
Bye.
That's Noah.
Elisabeth found it, at the store.
It was in a book.
She said that's the man
who gave her the watch.
"January 8, 1921.
Sic mundus creatus est."
Charlotte, who are these people?
Why did your grandfather have this?
I don't know.
CALL REJECTED
Subtitle translation by Nathan Fritz