I was, uh,
I was about nine or ten.
My old man made me...
fight this older kid
in the neighborhood.
He said I was a pussy.
And if I didn't want
to be a pussy my whole life,
I needed to
kick this kid's ass.
So...
I beat the kid up.
Beat him to a pulp.
He told me I might not
be a pussy, after all.
Got some product coming in
from New York
the next few days.
Need a nice white face
to pick it up and deliver it
-when the time comes.
-What kind of product?
Okay.
Look, I need to know
what the fuck
we're bringing up.
No, you ain't fixing
to ask me specifics
about my product,
are you, ese?
Didn't mean to offend you.
No, no, don't tell me
what you meant.
I fucking heard your ass.
Okay. Okay.
I'm sorry.
Now, don't come
in here acting like
you've got some fucking
weight behind your ass.
You know the fucking drill.
You either take
the fucking job or you're not.
How's that number?
Looks about right.
One of these days
the FBI...
The fuck did you
get that relic?
I inherited him
from my old man.
A fucking throwback,
right there.
Does it talk?
This dude was the real
deal back in the day, man.
Was ain't is, homes.
Homie past his sell-by date.
Somebody tell this fuckpig
that if he don't stop
staring at me,
I'm gonna have
to break his shoulders.
In the present tense.
Oh, whoa, whoa.
Take it easy, man.
That motherfucker
still got some game, huh.
I like him.
So we got a deal or what?
Deal.
Dude, you really need to
not be saying shit like that.
Do you know
who those guys are?
Somebody
had to say something.
Never seen anyone
backpedal so fast.
Hey!
Who's the fucking boss here?
You want
to be a boss one day,
you got to start
acting like one.
You really need that
to find your way home?
No, but my nav system
has real-time
traffic pattern algorithms.
Oh, you can't smoke in here.
Algorithms... Algorithms...
That blow's gonna kill you,
you know that?
You think I'm a tool,
don't ya?
No, kid.
I don't think you're a tool.
You're just green is all.
There he is.
So, the kid bargained
a good price?
Uh, he got an okay price.
So, he shit the bed?
I would have been
scared too at his age, boss.
You know, when he managed
to get his degree from BC,
I wanted him
to go to law school.
He had other ideas.
He wants to be a tough guy,
like you.
You know, he set this
whole deal up himself.
He's trying to prove to
everybody he's a shot-caller.
What do you think?
That ain't
none of my business.
I'm not sure he's ever
gonna be ready, you know?
He's just not cut out for it,
like you and me.
He just needs some time,
Mister...
You forget
my fucking name again?
You forget my fucking name?
I...
I've been having
some trouble sleeping,
I get these headaches.
All right.
Just make sure the kid
doesn't fuck this one up.
Hey, there he is.
Like clockwork.
You late with your rent again?
You got anything or not?
I've got a hot kid that
could use some sparring.
I don't fucking need that.
You okay?
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, yeah. I'm fine.
What'd you think
of the mick?
Yeah, he... He can punch,
he's got some juice.
Bit mouthy.
Ain't you
forgetting something?
Oh.
Hey.
Tilda says only single shots
and to cut you off
at three drinks.
I don't see Tilda.
Do you?
You can't touch
a lady like that!
Crazy bitch!
Who you fucking
calling a crazy bitch?
You can't talk to
a motherfucking lady
like that!
-What did I tell you...
-I don't give a fuck...
-You'll put me in a bad mood.
-Fuck you. I will kill you!
-I will fuck you up, bitch!
-You're gonna fuck me?
Yeah, bitch-ass.
Are you out of your mind?
-No.
-Fuck, you bit me!
Hey!
You know what happens
-when I get in a bad mood.
-Or what?
You want me to put
my fucking hands on you?
Fuck you.
Come on, pal.
Take it outside.
What'd you say to me?
I said take it outside.
Get the fuck out of here.
Go back to your drink...
Hey, you killed him!
He ain't dead.
He's just stupid.
Hey!
Hey, asshole!
Look, lady,
I don't want no trouble.
You knock out my boyfriend
and you don't want no trouble?
He had it coming.
Okay.
Maybe he had it coming.
Who's gonna walk me home?
Easy, babe, easy!
Easy...
No need to be so rough.
We'll get there soon enough.
Promise.
Ah. Easy!
Easy.
How do you get
any sleep living here?
I like the noise.
I mean, that drunk guy,
he screams, like, every night,
so it's like music to me.
I hate silence.
I gathered that
back at the bar.
Like, this silence
reminds me of home.
Hmm. Where's that?
Hmm...
Wellesley.
Wellesley? Really?
The good part.
Big house on Cliff Road.
And I was a good girl, too.
Yeah?
What the hell
happened to you?
Oof...
God save the soul!
Yo, Larry, shut
the fuck up! I've got company.
Congratulations,
have a nice evening!
See, you couldn't do that
in Wellesley.
I guess not.
Hmm...
Get out.
What?
Lupe?
Yeah?
That's my name.
You're kidding me.
Well, I mean,
it's not my real name,
it's my nickname.
Actually,
it's not even my nickname.
When I was at school,
they used to called me loopy
'cause I was so fucking crazy.
So it was kind of close, right?
That's trippy, don't you think?
Yeah, must be fate.
So who is she?
Oh, some whore.
That's not nice.
Listen,
she charged me ten bucks,
so I don't know what else
you would call her.
I thought I was in love.
Got her name
tattooed on my hand,
went back to show her...
She was shagging
two of my friends.
That was the end of that.
That's fucking romantic,
is what that is.
Yeah, boss?
I need for you
to go over to Dr. Gruber's,
pick something up for me.
Uh-huh.
You remember
the address, right?
Of course, I do.
Those are the bombers. 30 mills.
They're all sealed.
That's what
you said last time.
Hey, man, they were sealed.
Any tampering happened,
that was on the other end.
You sell this shit, you've got
to put your name on it, doc.
-Any blanks in this batch...
-Okay, okay, I get it.
I'll let 'em go for 15.
Okay, man.
Twelve.
I don't have time
for this shit, doc.
Fine. Ten.
Let me ask you something.
I've been having
some memory issues lately.
Like what?
Ah, forgetting names
and directions.
Shit like that.
How bad is it?
I forgot where I lived for
a few minutes this morning.
It's not the first time.
It's not good.
It's not good at all.
You should
get that checked out.
Good afternoon.
Hey.
Okay.
Have you heard of CTE?
Stands for Chronic
Traumatic Encephalopathy.
Lots of football players
and boxers develop it.
Too many blows to the head.
Punch drunk.
That's what
they used to call it.
Have you sustained
multiple concussions
over the course of your life?
You could say that.
Starting at what age?
I don't know.
First one was probably
around six or seven.
Maybe younger.
So, this took place at home?
Just tell me what I got
and what I need to take
to get better.
There is no treatment.
No drugs.
And it's
a fairly advanced case.
Do you...
have anyone?
Wife?
Kids?
No, I don't know.
I've got a couple of kids. Why?
In the next couple of years,
you can expect
a fairly sharp decline.
Eventually, you won't be
able to care for yourself.
Bullshit.
I know it's hard...
Listen, you don't know me.
Just tell me
how long I have.
Until you're incapacitated?
I can't predict that.
Just tell me,
how long do I have?
I don't know.
A couple of years
at the most.
Could be sooner.
-Hello?
-Hello, Daisy.
Dad?
Is something wrong?
No.
Did someone
die or something?
I just wanted to say hello.
Are you drunk?
No!
What the hell
do you want then?
Can I come by and see you?
Uh, fuck no.
Okay.
I didn't mean to bother you.
No,
I don't want to see you.
We have nothing to talk about.
I've got an okay thing
going on right now.
And I don't need you
or anyone else
fucking it up for me.
Mmm-hmm...
Okay.
Have you heard from...
My... my son?
Your son?
You mean Colin?
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Colin.
You have his number?
I want to go see him.
Colin's dead.
What?
When?
Almost two years ago.
But...
What...
Why didn't anybody tell me?
Why would they, Dad?
You didn't even remember
his fucking name.
Where... where is he buried?
Colin, Colin...
Colin...
Fucking idiot.
You should take better
fucking care of this place!
I thought I told you
not to come.
Just wanted to see you.
Okay. Well, you saw me.
You can fuck off now, Dad.
Excuse me.
This is
un-fucking believable.
And to invite you
and your family to dinner.
And why on earth
would I want to do that?
Hi, sweetie.
I'm your grandfather.
Get your butt
back inside.
Why are you... Why are you
selling the house?
You really think
I can afford to buy a house?
I rent it.
The owner died
and his kids are selling it
out from under us.
Are you working?
I'm dancing.
Stripping?
No,
I joined the fucking Bolshoi.
Hey, hey, hey.
-Hey, Mom!
-Hi.
Um...
This is your grandfather.
Hey.
So, you're the boxer?
Was.
You... you play for Dorchester?
Newton.
Newton?
They have a football team?
He punched out
the Dorchester coach's son,
and they kicked him
off the team.
It's not funny.
I don't even want him
playing football.
You've got to go clean up.
I could smell you
coming from a mile away.
-Smell this!
-Goodbye.
What, did you find Jesus
or something?
I just want to explain...
You...
you don't understand...
No, that's just it.
I do understand.
You were a fucking asshole
to us.
Just like my babies' daddies
are assholes.
Just like your dad
was an asshole.
And his dad, and on and on.
Back to the asshole caveman
that spawned you all.
It's a fucking family curse.
The curse
of the asshole father.
The dinner,
just think about it, yeah?
Okay.
I thought about it.
Fuck off.
Dad?
Yeah.
I thought you were dead.
Nah.
It don't work that way.
Are you still mad?
Nah.
I ain't mad no more, kid.
We gonna fish?
Nah.
Where are we going?
You'll see.
I don't see any land.
Enjoy the ride.
There'll be land soon enough.
Promise?
I promise.
What is that sound?
It's a guitar.
It's in the engine.
Yo!
Yo, you lost?
Come on.
Yeah, you're the boy
our parents warned us about.
-Look at you now.
-Mmm-hmm.
So what do you do?
What's you, a gangster?
Huh? You a gangster?
Were you born
without a filter,
or is that something
you have to work at?
Ugh. Whatever.
Nah, it's all just
a bunch of boo-boo.
"Boo-boo"?
Well, you know...
You know,
boo-boo just means like...
Some weak ass bullshit.
Life ain't weak.
Life's a shitstorm.
But it sure as hell
ain't a bunch of boo-boo.
Wow.
So deep!
I feel like I need to run.
Let's race!
-Come on, let's race!
-No.
Oh, oh, oh.
Okay, soccer knee, soccer knee.
How about backwards race?
-That's even worse.
-What?
-It's worse.
-Come on! Come on!
Stop it, there's people looking.
There's people looking.
Oh, they gonna look,
all right. Come on!
You gonna buy me a Guinness?
I'll make 'em stop looking
if you buy me a Guinness.
Come on, you gangster, boo-boo!
Hey,
where's the screaming drunk?
It's too early for him.
He's a closing act.
What are these bumps
in your tattoos?
Scars.
Cigarette burns.
Life gives you lemons,
you make flowers.
Who did this to you?
Some asshole.
I don't want to talk about it.
I see you got your own scars.
Yeah, well, who doesn't?
How'd you get those?
Some asshole.
Where you going?
Have to go to New York.
You not gonna
kiss me goodbye?
No.
I don't have time for that.
Hmm...
Quite the sweet talker you are.
Hey.
Hey, you deaf?
What?
I asked, how much longer
to stay on I-90?
Why aren't you
using your "gorithm"?
Yeah, very funny, smart-ass.
You said you've been to New York
like a million times.
So, what's the best way
to get there?
Did you forget?
No.
Go ahead. Use your toy.
Yeah, I think you forgot
how to get there.
Bullshit.
They said
the northeast corner.
Where should I park?
Make a loop.
What are you looking for?
Anything that doesn't fit.
Keep driving.
Slower. Slower...
Is that us?
Yeah.
-I'll see you back in Boston.
-Hey, no, no, no.
I'm coming with you.
No, it's not happening.
Jeez,
what is wrong with you?
Pop says he wants me
to learn the business
from the bottom up.
Remember?
I got news for you.
This business is all done
on the bottom.
I want to know
what's back there.
No, you don't.
On jobs like this,
you got to learn not to look.
Just do your business.
And look the other way.
Cops.
Fuck.
Just be cool.
Aw, shit!
Fuck, fuck, fuck.
Do me a favor
and get on the floor.
What?
-Get on the floor.
-Why?
When this guy passes us,
he's gonna
take a good, long look.
And I don't need him
seeing you shit your pants.
I'm... I'm cool.
-I'm cool.
-You're not.
Do me a favor, get down.
-Fuck!
-Get on the fucking...
No, I'm not getting
on the fucking floor.
Hey, stop.
Get down, now, get down!
Let me up!
Get down and stay there,
stay down.
Stay there.
This is fucking bullshit, man.
I'm telling Pops
what you just did to me.
You mean saving your ass?
I'm getting sick
of the lack of respect
that you've been showing me.
They don't just hand
that shit out, son.
You've got to earn it.
And I know you're talking shit
to my old man about me.
Trying to hold me back.
That rocket fuel's
making you paranoid.
If it ain't the dinosaur.
Hey, fuckpig,
where do you want this?
Take it around back,
Jurassic Park.
What are you smirking at?
What are you doing?
Don't get out.
Those guys don't want us
seeing what's back there.
You afraid of that guy?
Just stay put.
Get her! Let's go!
Holy shit.
I'm going to break your legs!
Stop!
Help. Please, help me.
No! I want to go!
Get down!
Come down!
No!
Get the shit back off!
I want to go!
Shut the fuck up!
Help!
-Shut the fuck up!
-Help!
Shut up!
No! No!
All right, here we go,
number four!
Here we go. You got this!
Come on, Dre!
Knock him on his ass!
Come on, Dre.
Get up off the ground.
Come on, focus!
Come on. You've got this.
All right. All right.
-Here we go! Here we go!
-Hit it, hit it!
Don't like him
playing football, huh?
Do you mind?
Free country.
Jesus, he's playing terrible.
Come on!
Hit somebody!
Please tell me
that's not a beer in there.
Here we go! Here we go!
Yeah, Dre!
That's my boy!
Yes! Yes!
-Touchdown!
All right, let's do it again!
Okay, excuse me, where's
my little Patriots player?
Give me a hug. Oh, my God.
You are so good.
I am so proud of you.
-Thank you, Mom.
-Yeah, all right.
We've got to go pick up Katie.
You looked good out there.
Ah. I did okay.
Here's something for you.
That's my old reel.
It's a Pflueger.
It ain't for the heavy-duty
deep-sea stuff, but...
it'll be good for what you need.
-But... I don't fish.
-It doesn't matter.
What do you say?
Well, thank you.
All right,
we've got to go get Katie.
But you said I could stay
and watch the next game
with my friends.
I did? Fine.
Just be home by dinner.
-Okay, bye, Mom.
-Okay. Bye, I love you.
Didn't the court say you
couldn't hang out in parks?
Take it easy.
Yo, Dre!
There you are.
-I want to go with my friends.
-You're riding home with me.
-Wait...
-I promised your mom.
Come on.
I have a question for you.
Why did you punch
that coach's son out?
He cheap-shotted me.
Sometimes
you've just got to walk away.
Mom says you were in prison.
What for?
Not walking away.
I've done so much
stupid shit in my life,
I can't even tell you.
Are you still doing
stupid shit?
Mom said you probably were.
What else
did your mom tell you?
That you...
That you ran out
on your family.
Is it true?
What was boxing like?
What are you doing here?
It ain't the end of the month.
This is my grandson.
I want him
to take a look around.
You want to be a boxer
like your grandfather?
Mmm...
I don't really know.
Hey.
This guy, back in the day,
if he punched you,
your fucking
ancestors would feel it.
You think I'm joking?
Make yourself at home, kid.
Hey. Watch these two.
Which one's better?
They both look good to me.
Watch their footwork.
Just their footwork.
The guy on the right
has more power.
But watch the girl.
She's coming at him
from five different angles.
Moving, sticking,
getting out of there.
See what I mean?
Calm, controlled,
moving fast.
Okay, now start punching.
Two lefts. Left!
Right.
Don't stay still.
I'm gonna hit you
if you stay still.
Left, right.
Left, right. That's it.
Don't stay still.
Don't stay still, that's it.
Back over this way.
Keep moving.
Good job.
There you go.
You're a natural, kid.
Hey.
Don't tell your mom
I took you to the gym.
You afraid of her?
Damn right, I am.
Me, too.
The water's really cold.
On top, it is.
But not down deep.
Did you go to the bottom?
Sure I did.
Is that where guys
like us belong?
Yeah.
Help me, help me!
Just don't think about it.
Hey!
Do like I taught you.
Look the other way
and enjoy the music.
He used to take me
fishing every Sunday.
Every single Sunday.
Just me and him.
I wasn't allowed to set foot
in that boat
if he wasn't with me.
He gets arrested
this one Saturday night.
And we can't raise the money
to bail him out until Monday.
So, I figured
I would take the boat out,
and he'd never
find out about it.
He found out.
He never took me
fishing again.
It was the one thing
we loved doing together.
And he took it away
to punish me.
Waiting for the presents.
Things are happening.
Jurassic Park!
What are you doing here
on a Sunday?
You got some girls here,
right?
I thought maybe
I'd take a look.
You're a dirty old dinosaur,
homie! Mmm...
We got Viagra too,
if you need it.
Come on, OG.
Hey.
I've got to
give you props, viejo.
You delivered us a good crop
right there.
All right, now!
Lovely ladies.
Smile for me.
Hey, come here. Smile.
Smile.
Ooh!
Trouble, ah, come.
She's my favorite.
Whole lotta trouble right here,
if you like that kind of stuff.
Smile.
Put on a smile, beautiful.
Come now, off you go!
Smile.
No, no, no.
I don't...
I don't know why I'm here.
Do... Do you have family
in the US?
Familia?
You want me to call?
They already know.
They know?
Diego wants money...
How much?
Twenty-thousand.
20,000, and they let you go?
I will be free.
Fuck.
I can't help you.
I'm sorry.
Yeah?
Okay. The Priest
can meet you after mass.
Got it.
Get the whole nut,
right? No excuses.
Hey, Father.
What's the rush?
Fucking idiot.
I...
I don't know
what I was thinking.
It's all there. 20,000.
Don't want to know
where you got this.
This'll buy you another month.
Hey, Father, do you still
take confession?
I don't have
that kind of time.
I'll see you next month.
Shit!
I shot a fucking priest.
So, where's our guy?
He must
still be in there.
Who the fuck are you?
Do I know you?
Who hired you?
Fuck you.
You're gonna kill me
either way.
Let me tell you
what's gonna happen.
You'll be dead in a few minutes.
And I'm gonna find out
where you live.
I'm guessing,
I'm gonna find someone there.
Maybe your girl.
He's a big motherfucker.
Big spider tat on his neck.
He said
you'd be hard to kill.
You don't think
these guys were there
to take out the 20 grand,
do you?
That's not
what the guy told me.
You owe anybody any money?
Nothing worth
that kind of attention.
Revenge?
Now that's a long list.
So, who the fuck
are these guys?
Eh, just some
fucking amateurs.
You know, I'm starting to
worry about you a little bit.
You worried now?
Nice work.
Hey!
Hey, what up, bud?
You shouldn't be here.
Oh, yeah, why not?
Just go home.
So why don't you
park by your house?
I like my privacy.
I come all the way
out here to see you,
and this is
the greeting I get?
How do you even know
where I live?
I went through
your wallet the other day.
I know, that sounded a little
crazy out loud, right?
Come on!
Cute place.
It's a shitty rental.
There's...
there's nothing to do here.
We can watch TV?
It doesn't work.
How 'bout some music?
I don't have music.
Everybody's got music.
I don't.
Those aren't mine.
Okay, they're mine.
Did you notice
that I had memory problems?
Yeah.
But I just thought
you were an alcoholic.
I am.
I'm a real prize.
It's sure quiet here.
You know my son
I told you about?
The one who died?
Yeah.
He overdosed on heroin.
I'm sorry.
He was gay.
Did that bother you?
I don't know.
I guess so, yeah.
Maybe if
I'd been around more
when he was growing up,
things would've been different.
So what, you think
you're so fucking macho,
it's just gonna
rub off on him?
Shit don't work like that.
We aren't gonna end well,
you and me.
You know that, right?
Yeah, we're like
that scene in the movies
where the gasoline...
moves slowly...
towards the flame.
Sooner or later...
But not tonight.
Hey.
It's me.
Yeah, I know.
What are you doing?
Listening to that guy
playing the guitar.
What guitar?
He... he was just playing.
Didn't you hear him?
No.
You're hearing things.
I'm taking my daughter
and her kids
out to dinner on Friday night.
I want you to come with me.
You sure about that?
Yeah. I'm sure.
You look nice.
I need a drink.
"Why, thank you.
You look lovely too."
Hey! Can I get a drink?
Sure.
-Uh, double bourbon, rocks.
-What kind?
The cheap kind.
And for the lady?
Uh, just a glass of water,
please.
Calm down, Sally,
they'll be here.
It's all good. Come on.
They aren't coming.
Maybe... maybe I gave her
the wrong address.
Shit, I must've given them
Sorry, but I simply
cannot hold this table
any longer.
Fuck off!
Excuse me?
I said, fuck off!
Who says, "simply cannot"?
No one talks like that.
Would you
speak to our manager?
No, no, no, no. That's...
That's not necessary.
-Yeah.
-No!
-Okay.
-No, no!
Hey, hey, okay.
What the fuck
are you looking at? Huh?
High-end motherfuckers!
-Okay.
-We were supposed to...
Hey, hey, hey!
-Let's just go...
-Where's the person
we were supposed to meet?
Daisy.
-Daisy?
-Yeah.
What about Colin?
Colin couldn't make it.
Daisy?
Yeah, your daughter.
My daughter's not coming,
is she?
No, I don't think
she's going to be able...
I gave her the wrong address...
What... What...
My... my... my...
My daughter's not coming,
is she?
No, she's not coming.
What... what's her name?
Your daughter's name
is Daisy, baby.
What the hell's
happening here?
Why didn't you tell me
you were sick?
You told her?
Yeah.
I called her last night.
I mean, I thought, you know,
you were really upset.
You fucking told her?
-Hey!
-Yeah, she should know.
Get out of my house.
Dad, stop.
She didn't mean anything.
Get out,
or I'll throw you out.
Crazy fucking bitch!
Cut it out!
So, you want to hit me?
You want to hit me?
Okay.
Okay, fucking hit me.
Hit me, you fucking pussy.
I know you want to.
Dre,
get back in the car.
Dre! Please! Go,
get in the car right now.
Go!
I didn't want you to know.
Okay.
Well,
she didn't deserve that.
Fuck.
Why... why didn't you come
to dinner last night?
Says the guy who walked away
and never came back.
You suck.
I've got to go pack,
'cause now we've got to be
out in two days.
Where... where will you go?
I'll figure it out.
Is there...
is there anything I can do?
I can take care of myself.
Are you gonna get treatment?
I don't know.
Well, you got a doctor?
I did.
That bitch can't help me.
Christ.
Hey.
Do you need my help
to find a new doctor?
Why...
Why would you do that?
Well, if you need my help,
let me know.
Life's a shitstorm, isn't it?
What's her name?
What's her fucking name?
Fuck.
Yeah.
Maybe my son...
He's dead...
Yeah, he was a big dude...
Dude, dude...
Ta-ta, tattoo, tattoo...
Big dude, tattoo...
on his neck.
I can't remember it.
You fuckin' idiot!
Fuckin' idiot.
Fuck you! Big dude.
Fuck you. Tattoo!
Tattoo! Fuck you! Fuck you!
Fuck you!
Fuck you, you, you!
Here comes the packing train!
Choo-choo!
Thank you. Keep it coming.
Chugga-chugga, chugga-chugga...
Train is leaving the station.
Chugga-chugga, chugga-chugga,
chugga-chugga...
What?
Um... I need to talk to Dre.
All right.
Hey.
Can we talk?
Dre, I...
It's hard.
Life, life... Life is hard.
I, uh...
I...
What you saw yesterday...
my anger.
What I'm saying is,
don't be like that.
Don't be like me.
Fucking idiot.
$40,000.
It's...
It's for a downpayment
on a house...
For my daughter, Daisy.
Mr. Connor, I know
that's a lot of money, but...
I'm willing to pay whatever
interest you decide on.
Mr. Connor...
So...
I know 40,000
is a lot of money, but...
I've been working for you
for 30 years.
30 long years. And...
Mr. Connor?
Have a seat.
-Who's...
-He works for me.
So...
I saw doctor Gruber yesterday.
He came by for his Oxy money.
Okay.
He said something about
you maybe having some sort
of brain disease or something.
He said I might.
I mean, I can't even put
into words how sorry I am...
Get to the point.
I have to let you go.
Let me go?
Boss! It's...
it's me! I'm fine.
Please.
What about the other day?
The... the shooters?
I got all your money.
What's your phone number?
617...
What's your address?
"Gee, SpongeBob,
I don't know..."
-Kyle!
-No, fuck this guy!
Sorry.
I can't have somebody
in your condition
working for me.
It's just too risky.
So, that's it?
After 30 years?
I'm afraid so.
This...
this doesn't make sense, boss.
Come on, man.
Let's not prolong this.
The door's over there.
Or do you need directions?
First day on the job?
Yeah.
You...
you hired those guys
to kill me.
Did you know about this?
Look.
You just walk away, all right?
There'll be no repercussions.
I like repercussions.
Open your safe.
There's no winning
here for you.
Open your fucking safe!
You're fucking crazy.
Hey!
-No!
-Hey!
Don't kill him!
Don't kill him, all right?
I'm opening the safe.
Back up.
Fill the bag up...
and the guns.
I came in here
to ask you for a favor.
And you get rid of me
like I'm dogshit on the bottom
of your fucking shoe.
Come on, man.
Isn't the money enough?
Can't you...
can't you just walk away?
Yeah.
Can you make me a promise?
The kid stays alive.
Sit down.
All right.
What's the fucking emergency
I had to rush down here
in the middle
of the night for?
Like you have anything
better to do.
I was playing poker.
I've seen you play cards.
I did you a favor.
Jesus.
You going on a shooting spree?
Maybe.
This is for you.
You've got my attention.
Can you get a cashier's cheque
for 70 grand?
Sure.
I want you to put
a downpayment on this house.
Take the check
to my daughter,
and help her with
the paperwork and tax stuff.
She's a bitch on wheels.
So, watch yourself.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
I'm good.
Should I ask you
where you got the dough?
It was nice knowing you.
Come on, come on,
pick up.
Fuck.
You home?
Holy shit.
Hey, buddy.
What did you...
What...
Why the hell would you
do this to yourself?
Boo boo...
Come on.
-Shit.
-Come on.
Shit.
Let's get you up.
After three.
Oh, shit.
Lay down with me.
No.
Ow.
How do you feel?
I'm sorry I screwed up.
When I said things
weren't going to end well,
I knew it would be me
that would fuck things up.
Mmm.
You need help.
You're helping me.
I'm serious.
You are helping me.
If it ain't my old friend,
Jurassic Park.
I want to talk some business.
What's your business?
I want to buy
one of your girls.
You fall in love, viejo?
You going to pimp her out?
You and me,
we're pieces of shit.
You're a funny guy.
We live off pain and weakness.
We're bullies.
And you think buying a puta
gonna change all that?
Thirty thousand.
Not bad.
Which one do you want?
The little one
with the curly hair.
And the blonde bangs.
She ain't for sale.
Hey.
I'm offering you
10,000 above asking price.
She ain't for sale.
Why not?
One of the puteros
got a little carried away
with her tonight.
What was her name?
Araceli.
What are you gonna do
with her?
I don't know, man.
You can't change the world,
viejo.
World don't
want to be changed.
I really don't want to
hurt anyone else,
not even you.
So, just do what I say, okay?
Come on.
Come out! Come on, let's go!
Girls! Come out...
Wait downstairs.
Come on.
Tell your boy
at the front door to go home.
-Do it!
-Armando,
you can knock off now.
You sure?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I got it covered.
All right.
Get the girls out of here.
Girls, get out here!
Go wait in the bathroom.
Come on, in the bathroom!
Johns stay inside.
Out of the rooms!
No rush.
Hey, you! Inside! Inside!
Which way do you want me to go?
The kitchen!
Come on, girls.
You, sit down.
You, go!
Dinero, inside.
Bring... bring in here.
Come on.
Attagirl.
You're free.
Go! Go!
Pay them.
Easy, easy...
He has a gun!
No!
Yeah, that's Sureno style
right there, bitch.
You're bleeding out good,
viejo.
I can finish it off.
You want me
to make it quick?
After you, fuckpig.
Just go. Go.
Don't wake up your mom.
You hear me?
Don't come any closer.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Listen to me, Dre.
You're gonna hear
some bad stuff about me
in the next few days.
Maybe the only way for me
to do something right...
is by doing something bad.
I... I don't get it.
It might not make any sense
to you now, but...
I tried.
Go back inside.
I... I'll be fine. Go on.
Go on. Go on.
Hello?
Anybody here?