Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
I was--
I was about nine or ten.
My old man made me
fight this older kid
in the neighborhood.
He said I was a pussy.
And if I didn't want to be
a pussy my whole life,
I needed to
kick this kid's ass.
So...
I beat the kid up.
Beat him to a pulp.
He told me I might
not be a pussy, after all.
I've got some product coming in
from New York the next few days.
Need a nice white face
to pick it up and deliver it when the time comes.
What kind of product?
Okay.
Look, I need to know
what the fuck we're bringing up.
No, you ain't fixing to ask me
specifics about my product, are you?
Didn't mean to offend you.
No, no.
Don't tell me what you meant. I fucking heard your ass.
Okay. Okay.
I'm sorry.
Hey,
don't come here acting
like you've got some
fucking weight behind your ass.
You know the fucking drill.
You gonna take the fucking job
or you're not.
How's that number?
Looks about right.
The fuck did you get that relic?
I inherited him from my old man.
A fucking throwback,
right there.
Does it talk?
This dude was the real deal back in the day, man.
Was, ain't is, homes.
Homie past his sell-by date.
Somebody tell this fuckpig
that if he don't stop
staring at me
I'm gonna have to break
his shoulders.
In the present tense.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Take it easy, man.
That motherfucker
still got some game, huh?
I like him.
So we got a deal or what?
Deal.
Dude, you really need
to not be saying shit like that.
You know who those guys are?
Somebody had to say something.
Never seen anyone
backpedal so fast.
Hey!
Who's the fucking boss here?
You want to be a boss one day,
you got to start
acting like one.
You really need that
to find your way home?
No, but my nav system
has real-time
traffic pattern algorithms.
Y-you can't smoke in here.
Algorithms...
That blow's gonna kill you,
you know that?
You think I'm a tool, don't you?
No, kid.
I don't think you're a tool.
You're just green is all.
There he is.
So, the kid bargained
a good price?
Ah, he got an okay price.
So, he shit the bed?
I would have been scared too
at his age, boss.
You know, when he managed to get
his degree from BC,
I wanted him
to go to law school.
He had other ideas.
He wants to be a tough guy,
like you.
You know, he set
this whole deal up himself.
He's trying to prove
to everybody he's a shot caller.
- What do you think?
- That ain't none of my business.
I'm not sure he's ever
gonna be ready, you know.
He's just not cut out for it,
like you and me.
He just needs some time,
Mister...
You forget
my fucking name again?
You forget my fucking name?
I've-- I've been having
trouble sleeping.
I get these headaches.
All right.
Just make sure the kid
doesn't fuck this one up.
Hey, there he is.
Like clockwork.
What, are you
late with the rent again?
You got anything or not?
I've got a hot kid
that could use some sparring.
I don't fucking need that.
You okay?
Yeah. Yeah. I'm fine.
What'd you think of the mick?
Uh, he-- he can punch,
he's got some juice.
Bit mouthy.
Ain't you forgetting something?
Oh.
Hey.
Tilda says only single shots
and to cut you off
at three drinks.
I don't see Tilda.
Do you?
You can't touch
a lady like that! - Crazy bitch!
Who the fuck you calling a crazy bitch?
You can't touch a motherfuckin'
lady like that!
- What did I tell--
- I don't give a fuck.
You're gonna put me
in a bad mood.
Fuck you! I will kill you!
I will fuck you up, bitch!
- You're gonna fuck me?
- Yeah, bitch ass!
- You out of your mind?
- No.
- Fuck, you bit me!
- Hey!
You know what happens
when I get in a bad mood.
- Hey!
- Or what?
You want me to put my fucking
hands on you? - Hey!
Come on, pal.
Take it outside.
What'd you say to me?
I said take it outside.
Get the fuck out of here.
Go back to your drink.
Hey, you killed him!
He ain't dead.
He's just stupid.
Hey! Hey, asshole!
Look lady,
I don't want no trouble.
You knocked out my boyfriend
and you don't want no trouble?
He had it coming.
Okay, maybe he had it coming.
But who's gonna walk me home?
Easy, babe, easy! Easy.
No need to be so rough.
We'll get there soon enough.
Promise.
Ah, easy!
Ea-sy.
Easy.
How you get
any sleep living here?
I like the noise.
I mean, that drunk guy,
he screams, like, every night,
so it's like music to me.
I hate silence.
I gathered that back at the bar.
Silence reminds me of home.
Where's that?
Wellesley.
Wellesley? Really?
Yeah, the good part,
big house on Cliff Road.
And I was a good girl, too.
Yeah?
What the hell happened to you?
Ugh...
Yo, Larry, shut the fuck up! I've got company.
Congratulations,
have a nice evening!
Woah!
See, you couldn't do that
in Wellesley.
I guess not.
- Get out.
- What?
- Lupe?
- Yeah.
That's my name.
You're kidding me.
It's not my real name,
it's my nickname.
Actually,
it's not even my nickname.
When I was at school,
they called me Loopy 'cause I was so fucking crazy.
It was kind of close, right?
That's trippy, don't you think?
Yeah, must be fate.
So who is she?
Oh, some whore.
That's not nice.
Listen,
she charged me ten bucks,
so I don't know
what else you would call her.
I thought I was in love.
Got her name
tattooed on my hand, went back to show her...
she was shagging
two of my friends.
That was the end of that.
That's fucking romantic,
is what that is.
Yeah, boss?
I need you
to go to Dr. Gruber's,
pick something up for me.
- Uh-huh.
- You remember the address, right?
Of course, I do.
Those
are the bombers. 30 mills.
They're all sealed.
That's what you said last time.
Hey, man, they were sealed.
Any tampering happened,
that was on the other end.
You sell this shit,
you've got to put your name on it, doc.
Any blanks in this batch--
Okay, okay, I get it.
I'll let 'em go for 15.
Okay, man. 12.
I don't have time
for this shit, doc.
Fine. Ten.
Let me ask you something.
I, uh, I've been having
some memory issues lately.
Like what?
Forgetting names and directions.
Shit like that.
How bad is it?
I forgot where I lived
for a few minutes this morning.
It's not the first time.
It's not good.
It's not good at all.
You should get that checked out.
Good afternoon.
Hey.
Okay.
Have you heard of CTE?
Stands for Chronic
Traumatic Encephalopathy.
Lots of football players
and boxers develop it.
- Too many blows to the head.
- Punch drunk.
That's what
they used to call it.
Have you sustained multiple
concussions over the course of your life?
You could say that.
Starting at what age?
I don't know.
First one was probably
around six or seven.
Maybe younger.
So, this took place at home?
Just tell me what I got
and what I need to take
to get better.
There is no treatment.
No drugs.
And it's a fairly advanced case.
Do you have anyone?
Wife?
Kids?
No. I-- I don't know.
I've-- I've got
a couple of kids.
Why?
In the next couple of years,
you can expect
a fairly sharp decline.
Eventually, you won't be able
to care for yourself.
Bullshit.
- I know it's hard.
- Listen, you don't know me.
Just tell me how long I have.
Until you're incapacitated?
I-- I can't predict that.
Just tell me,
how long do I have?
I don't know.
A couple of years at the most.
Could be sooner.
- Hello?
- Hello, Daisy.
Dad?
Is something wrong?
- No.
- Did someone die or something?
I-- I just wanted to say hello.
Are you drunk?
No!
What the hell do you want then?
Can I come by and see you?
Uh, fuck no.
Okay. Okay.
I-- I didn't mean to bother you.
No,
I don't want to see you.
We have nothing to talk about.
I've got an okay thing
going on right now.
And I don't need you
or anyone else
fucking it up for me.
Uh-huh.
Okay.
Have you heard from...
um, my-- my son?
Your son? You mean Colin?
Yeah. Yeah, yeah. Colin.
You-- you have his number?
I-- I want to go see him.
Colin's dead.
What?
When?
Almost two years ago.
But--
What--
Why-- why didn't
anybody tell me?
Why would they, Dad?
You didn't even remember
his fucking name.
Where-- where is he buried?
Colin, Colin.
Colin.
Fucking idiot.
You should take better
fucking care of this place!
I thought
I told you not to come.
Just wanted to see you.
Okay. Well, you saw me.
You can fuck off now, Dad.
Excuse me.
This is un-fucking-believable.
And to invite you
and your family to dinner.
And why on earth
would I want to do that?
Hi, sweetie.
I'm your grandfather.
Get your butt
back inside.
Why are you--
why are you selling the house?
You really think
I can afford to buy a house?
I rent it.
The owner died
and his kids are
selling it out from under us.
Are you working?
- I'm dancing.
- Stripping?
No, I joined
the fucking Bolshoi.
Hey, hey, hey. Hey, Mom!
Hi.
Um, this is your grandfather.
Hey.
So, you're the boxer?
Was.
You-- you play for Dorchester?
- Newton.
- Newton?
They have a football team?
He punched out
the Dorchester coach's son,
and they kicked him
off the team.
It's not funny.
I don't even want him
playing football.
You've got to go clean up.
I could smell you coming
from a mile away.
- Smell this!
- Goodbye.
What, did you find Jesus
or something?
I just want to explain.
Uh, you-- you don't understand.
No, that's just it.
I do understand.
You were
a fucking asshole to us.
Just like my babies'
daddies are assholes.
Just like your dad
was an asshole.
And his dad, and on and on.
Back to the asshole caveman
that spawned you all.
It's a fucking family curse.
The curse of the asshole father.
The dinner,
just think about it, yeah?
Okay. I thought about it.
Fuck off.
Dad?
Yeah.
- I thought you were dead.
- Nah.
It don't work that way.
Are you still mad?
Nah, I ain't mad no more, kid.
We gonna fish?
Nah.
Where are we going?
You'll see.
I don't see any land.
Enjoy the ride.
There'll be land soon enough.
- Promise?
- I promise.
What is that sound?
It's a guitar.
It's in the engine.
Yo!
Yo, you lost?
Come on!
Yeah, you're the boy
our parents warned us about.
- And look at you now.
- Mm-hm.
What do you do?
What, you a gangster?
Huh, you a gangster?
Were you born without a filter,
or is that something
you have to work at?
Ah, whatever.
No, I-- It's all
just a bunch of boo-boo.
- Boo-boo?
- Well, you know.
You know, like,
boo-boo just means, like...
some weak ass bullshit.
Life ain't weak.
Life's a shitstorm.
But it sure as hell
ain't a bunch of boo-boo.
Wow.
So deep!
I feel like I need to run.
Let's race!
- Come on, let's race!
- No.
Oh, whoa, whoa, okay.
Soccer knee, soccer knee.
- How about backwards race?
- That's even worse.
- What?
- It's worse.
- Come on!
- Stop it, there's people looking.
Oh, they gonna look, all right.
Come on!
What, you gonna buy me
a Guinness?
I'll make 'em stop looking
if you buy me a Guinness.
Come on, you gangster, boo-boo!
Hey,
where's the screaming drunk?
It's too early for him.
He's the closing act.
What are these bumps
in your tattoos?
Scars.
Cigarette burns.
When life gives you lemons,
you make flowers.
Who did this to you?
Some asshole.
I don't want to talk about it.
Hmm.
I see you got your own scars.
Yeah, well, who doesn't?
How'd you get those?
Uh, some asshole.
Where you going?
Have to go to New York.
You not gonna
kiss me goodbye? - No.
I don't have time for that.
Hm.
Quite the sweet talker you are.
Hey.
Hey! You deaf?
What?
I asked, how much longer
I stay on I-90?
Why aren't you using
your "gorithm"?
Yeah, very funny, smart-ass.
You said you've been to New York
like a million times, so...
What's the best way
to get there?
Did you-- did you forget?
No.
Go ahead. Use your toy.
Yeah, I think you forgot
how to get there.
Bullshit.
It's at northeast corner.
- Where should I park?
- Make a loop.
What are you looking for?
Anything that doesn't fit.
Keep driving.
Slower. Slower.
Is that us?
Yeah.
- I'll see you back in Boston.
- Hey, no, no, no.
I'm coming with you.
- No, it's not happening.
- Jeez, what is wrong with you?
Pop said he wants me to learn
the business from the bottom up.
Remember?
I got news for you.
This business is all done
on the bottom.
I want to know
what's back there.
No, you don't.
On jobs like this,
you got to learn not to look.
Just do your business.
And look the other way.
Cops.
Fuck.
- Just be cool.
- Oh, shit!
Fuck, fuck, fuck.
Do me a favor
and get on the floor.
- What?
- Get on the floor.
Why?
When this guy passes us,
he's gonna take
a good long look.
And I don't need him
seeing you shit your pants.
No, I'm-- I'm--
I'm cool, I'm cool.
You're not.
Do me a favor, get down.
- Fuck, fuck, fuck!
- Get on the fucking--
No, I'm not getting
on the fucking floor.
Hey, stop.
- Get down, get down!
- Let me up!
Get down and stay there,
stay down. - Ow!
Stay down!
This is fucking bullshit, man.
I'm telling Pop
what you just did to me.
You mean, saving your ass?
I'm getting sick
of the lack of respect
that you've been showing me.
They don't just hand
that shit out, son.
You've got to earn it.
And I know you're talking shit
to my old man about me.
Trying to hold me back.
That rocket fuel's
making you paranoid.
If it ain't the dinosaur!
Hey, fuckpig,
where do you want this?
Just take it
around back, Jurassic Park.
What are you smirking at?
What are you doing?
Don't get out.
Those guys don't want us seeing
what's back there.
You afraid of that guy?
Just stay put.
Get her! Let's go!
Holy shit...
No, no, get away!
No!
- No!
- Get that shit back off there.
Shut her the fuck up!
Shut her up!
All right, here we go,
Number Four!
Here we go. You got this!
Come on, Dre!
Knock him on his ass!
Come on, Dre.
Get up off the ground.
Come on, focus!
Come on, you've got this.
All right, all right.
Here we go, here we go!
Hit it, hit it!
Don't like him
playing football, huh?
Do you mind?
Free country.
Jesus, he's playing terrible.
Come on!
Hit somebody!
Please tell me
that's not a beer in there.
Here we go! Yeah, Dre!
That's my boy!
Touchdown! Touchdown!
All right, let's do it again!
Okay, excuse me, where's
my little Patriots player?
Give me a hug. Oh, my God.
You are so good!
I am so proud of you.
- Thank you, Mom.
- Yeah, all right.
We've got to go pick up Katie.
You looked good out there.
Ah, I did okay.
Oh, here's something for you.
That's my old reel.
It's a Pflueger.
It ain't for the heavy-duty
deep-sea stuff, but...
it'll be good for what you need.
- But I don't fish.
- It doesn't matter.
What do you say?
Well, thank you.
All right,
we've got to go get Katie.
But you said I could stay
and watch the next game with my friends.
I did? Fine.
Just be home by dinner.
- Okay, bye, Mom.
- Okay.
Bye, I love you.
Didn't the court say
you couldn't hang out in parks?
Take it easy.
Yo, Dre! There you are.
- I want to go with my friends.
- You're riding home with me.
- Wait.
- I promised your mom.
Come on.
I have a question for you.
Why did you punch
that coach's son out?
He cheap-shotted me.
Sometimes,
you've just got to walk away.
Mom says you were in prison.
What for?
Not walking away.
I've done so much
stupid shit in my life,
I can't even tell you.
Are you still doing stupid shit?
Mom said you probably were.
What else did your mom tell you?
That you--
That you ran out on your family.
Is it true?
What was boxing like?
What are you doing here?
It ain't the end of the month!
This is my grandson.
I want him
to take a look around.
You want to be a boxer
like your grandfather?
Eh, I don't really know.
Hey, this guy, back in the day,
if he punched you, your fucking
ancestors would feel it.
You think I'm joking?
Make yourself at home, kid.
Hey. Watch these two.
Which one's better?
They both look good to me.
Watch their footwork.
Just their footwork.
The guy on the right
has more power.
But watch the girl.
She's coming at him
from five different angles.
Moving, sticking,
getting out of there.
See what I mean?
Calm, controlled, moving fast.
Okay, now start punching.
Two lefts. Left!
Right. Don't stay still.
I'm gonna hit you
if you stay still.
Left, right. Left, right.
That's it. Don't stay still.
Don't stay still, that's it.
Back over this way.
Keep moving.
Good job!
There you go!
You're a natural, kid.
Hey!
Don't tell your mom
I took you to the gym.
You afraid of her?
Damn right, I am.
Me, too.
The water's really cold.
On top it is.
But not down deep.
Did you go to the bottom?
Sure, I did.
Is that where guys
like us belong?
Yeah.
No!
Just don't think about it.
Hey!
Do like I taught you.
Look the other way...
and enjoy the music.
He used to take me
fishing every Sunday.
Every single Sunday.
Just me and him.
I wasn't allowed
to set foot in that boat
if he wasn't with me.
He gets arrested
this one Saturday night.
And we can't raise the money
to bail him out until Monday.
So, I figured I would
take the boat out, and...
he'd never find out about it.
Oh, but he found out.
He never took me fishing again.
It was the one thing
we loved doing together.
And he took it away
to punish me.
Jurassic Park!
What are you doing here
on a Sunday?
You got some girls here, right?
I thought maybe I'd take a look.
You're a dirty
old dinosaur, homie!
We got Viagra too,
if you need it.
Come on, OG.
Hey!
I've got to give you
props, viejo.
You delivered us a good crop,
right here.
All right, now!
Lovely ladies. Smile for me!
Hmm?
Hey, come here.
Come on. Smile.
Ooh!
Trouble, ah, come.
She's my favorite.
Whole lotta trouble right here,
if you like that kind of stuff...
Smile.
That's good.
No, no, no.
I don't--
I don't know why I'm here.
Do-- do-- do you have
family in the US?
Familia?
You want me to call?
They know?
How much?
20-- 20,000,
and they let you go?
I will be free.
Fuck...
I can't help you.
- Yeah?
- Okay.
The Priest
can meet you after mass.
Got it.
Get the whole nut,
right? No excuses.
Hey, father!
What's the rush?
Fucking idiot.
Huh.
I...
I don't know
what I was thinking. Uh...
It's all there. 20,000.
Don't want to know where
you got this.
This'll buy you another month.
Hey, father.
Do you still take confession?
I don't have that kind of time.
I'll see you next month.
Shit!
I shot a fucking priest.
So, where's our guy?
He must still be in there.
Oh!
Oh! Fuck!
Who the fuck are you?
Do I know you?
Who hired you?
Fuck you.
You're gonna kill me either way.
Let me tell you
what's gonna happen.
You'll be dead in a few minutes.
And I'm gonna find out
where you live.
I'm guessing
I'm gonna find someone there.
Maybe your girl.
He's a big motherfucker.
Big spider tat on his neck.
He said you'd be hard to kill.
You don't think these guys
were there to get the 20 grand, do you?
It's not what the guy told me.
You owe anybody any money?
Nothing worth
that kind of attention.
Revenge?
Now, that's a long list.
So, who the fuck are these guys?
Ah, it's just some
fucking amateurs.
You know, I'm starting
to worry about you a little bit.
You worried now?
Nice work.
Hey!
- Hey, what up, bud?
- You shouldn't be here.
- Oh, yeah, why not?
- Just go home.
So why don't you park
by your house?
I like my privacy.
I come all the way
out here to see you, and this is the greeting I get?
How do you even know
where I live?
I went through your wallet
the other day.
I know, that sounded
a little crazy out loud, right?
Come on!
Cute place!
It's a shitty rental.
There's-- there's nothing
to do here.
Well, we can watch TV.
It doesn't work.
How about some music?
I don't have music.
- Everybody's got music.
- I don't.
Those aren't mine.
Okay, they're mine.
Did you notice
that I have memory problems?
Yeah.
But I just thought
you were an alcoholic.
I am.
I'm a real prize.
It's sure quiet here.
You know my son
I told you about?
- The one who died?
- Yeah.
He overdosed on heroin.
I'm sorry.
He was gay.
Did that bother you?
I don't know.
I guess so, yeah.
Maybe if I'd been around more
when he was growing up...
things would've been different.
So what, you think
you're so fucking macho,
it's just gonna rub off on him?
Shit don't work like that.
We aren't gonna end well,
you and me.
You know that, right?
Yeah, we're like that scene
in the movies
where the gasoline...
moves slowly...
towards the flame.
Yeah, sooner or later...
But not tonight.
Hey!
It's me.
Yeah, I know.
What are you doing?
Listening to that guy
playing the guitar.
What guitar?
He-- he was just playing.
Didn't you hear him?
No.
You're hearing things.
I'm taking my daughter
and her kids out to dinner on Friday night.
I want you to come with me.
You sure about that?
Yeah. I'm sure.
Oh!
You look nice.
I need a drink.
"Oh, why, thank you.
You look lovely, too."
Hey! Can I get a drink?
Sure.
Uh, double bourbon, rocks.
- What kind?
- The cheap kind.
And for the lady?
Uh, just
a glass of water, please.
Calm down,
Sally, they'll be here!
It's all good. Come on.
They aren't coming.
Maybe-- maybe I-- maybe
I gave her the wrong address.
Shit, I must've given them
the wrong address.
I'm sorry, but I simply
cannot hold this table any longer.
Fuck off!
- Excuse me?
- I said, fuck off!
And who says "simply cannot?"
No one talks like that.
Would you speak to our manager?
No, no, no!
That's not necessary.
- Yeah--
- No!
- Okay.
- No, no!
Hey, hey, okay--
What the fuck
are you looking at?
Huh? High-end motherfuckers!
Hey. Okay.
We were supposed to--
Hey, hey, hey!
Let's just go home.
Where's the person
we were supposed to meet?
Daisy.
- Daisy?
- Yeah...
What a-- what about Colin?
Colin couldn't make it.
Daisy?
Yeah, your daughter.
My daughter's not coming,
is she?
No, I don't think
she's going to be able to--
I gave her the wrong address.
- What-- what-- my--
- Hm?
My-- my daughter's not coming,
is she?
No, she's not coming.
What-- what's her name?
Your daughter's name
is Daisy, baby.
W-- what--
What the hell's happening here?
Why didn't you tell me
you were sick?
You told her?
Yeah. I called her last night.
I mean, I thought,
you know, you were--
- You fucking told her?
- Hey!
Yeah, she should know.
Get out of my house!
Dad, stop.
She didn't mean anything.
Get out, or I'll throw you out.
Crazy fucking bitch!
Cut it out!
So, you want to hit me?
You want to hit me? Okay.
Okay, fucking hit me.
Hit me, you fucking pussy. I know you want to.
Dre, get back in the car.
Dre! Please!
Go get in the car right now.
Go!
I didn't want you to know.
Yeah, okay, well,
she didn't deserve that.
Fuck.
Yeah.
Why-- why didn't you come
to dinner last night?
Says the guy who walked away,
and never came back.
Fuck.
I've got to go pack, 'cause now
we've got to be out in two days.
Where-- where will you go?
I'll figure it out.
Is there--
is there anything I can do?
I can, uh, take care of myself.
Are you gonna get treatment?
I don't know.
Well, you got a doctor?
I did. That bitch can't help me.
Christ.
Hey.
You need my help
to find a new doctor?
Why-- why would you do that?
Well, if you need my help,
let me know.
Life's a shitstorm, isn't it?
Uh, what's her name?
What's her fucking name?
Fuck.
Yeah.
Maybe-- maybe my son.
He's dead.
Yeah, he was a big dude.
Dude, dude...
He had-- had...
Ta-- ta-- tattoo, tattoo.
Big-- big dude, tattoo...
Big dude, tattoo--
tattoo on-- on his neck.
I can't remember.
You fuckin' idiot!
You fuckin' idiot, fuck you!
Big dude. Fuck you. Tattoo!
Tattoo! Fuck you! Fuck you!
Fuck you!
Fuck you, you, you!
Here comes the packing train!
Choo-choo!
Thank you. Keep it coming.
Train is leaving the station.
What?
Um, I need to talk to Dre.
All right.
Hey.
Can we talk?
Dre, I...
It's hard.
Life-- life-- life is hard.
Mm-hmm.
I, uh...
What you saw yesterday...
my anger...
What I'm saying
is don't be like that.
Don't be like me.
Fucking idiot.
40,000 dollars.
It's, uh, it's for
a down payment on a house...
For my daughter, Daisy.
Mr. Connor, I know
that's a lot of money...
I'm willing to pay
whatever interest you decide on.
Mr. Connor...
So, Mr. Connor...
I-- I know 40-- 40,000
is a lot of money, but...
I've been working for you
for 30 years.
30 long years. And...
Mr. Connor?
Have a seat.
- Who's, uh...
- He works for me.
So, uh--
I saw Dr. Gruber yesterday.
He came by for his Oxy money.
Okay.
He said something about
you maybe having some sort of
brain disease or something.
He said I might.
I mean, I-- I can't even put
into words how sorry I am--
Get to the point.
I have to let you go.
Let me go?
Boss!
It's-- it's me! I'm fine.
Please.
What about the other day?
The-- the-- the shooters?
I got all your money.
What's your phone number?
617...
What's your address?
"Gee, SpongeBob,
I don't know--"
- Kyle!
- No, fuck this guy!
I'm sorry.
I can't have somebody in
your condition working for me.
It's just too risky.
So, that's it?
After 30 years?
Afraid so.
This--
this doesn't make sense, boss.
Come on, man.
Let's not prolong this.
The door's over there.
Or do you need directions?
- First day on the job?
- Yeah.
You...
you hired those guys to kill me.
Did you know about this?
Look...
you just walk away, all right?
There'll be no repercussions.
I like repercussions.
Open your safe.
There's no winning here for you.
Open your fucking safe!
You're fucking crazy. Hey!
- No!
- Hey!
Don't kill him! Don't kill him!
Don't kill him, all right?
I'm opening the safe.
Back up!
Fill the bag up.
And the guns.
I came in here
to ask you for a favor.
And you get rid of me
like I'm dogshit
on the bottom
of your fucking shoe.
Come on, man.
I mean, isn't the money enough?
Can't you--
Can't you just walk away?
Yeah...
Can you make me a promise?
The kid stays alive.
Sit down.
All right.
What's the fucking emergency
I had to rush down here in the middle of the night for?
Like you have
anything better to do.
I was playing poker.
I've seen you play cards.
I did you a favor.
Jesus.
You going on a shooting spree?
Maybe.
This is for you.
You've got my attention.
Can you get a cashier's check
for 70 grand?
Sure.
I want you to put
a down payment on this house.
Take the check to my daughter,
and help her with the paperwork
and tax stuff.
She's a bitch on wheels,
so watch yourself.
Are you okay?
Yeah. I'm good.
Should I ask you
where you got the dough?
It was nice knowing you.
Come on, come on, pick up.
Fuck.
You home?
Holy shit.
Hey, buddy.
How did you-- What--
Why the hell
would you do this to yourself?
Boo-boo.
- Come on.
- Oh! Shit.
- Oh, shit.
Let's get you up.
It's after three.
Oh, shit.
- Lay down with me.
- No.
Ow.
How do you feel?
I'm sorry I screwed up.
When I said things
weren't going to end well,
I knew it would be me
that would fuck things up.
Mm.
You need help.
You're helping me.
I'm serious.
You are helping me.
If it ain't my old friend,
Jurassic Park.
I want to talk some business.
What's your business?
I want to buy one of your girls.
You fall in love, viejo?
You gonna pimp her out?
You and me,
we're pieces of shit.
Ah, sure, you're a funny guy.
We live off pain and weakness.
We're bullies.
And you think buying a puta
gonna change all that?
30,000.
Not bad.
Which one do you want?
The little one
with the curly hair.
And the blonde bangs.
She ain't for sale.
Hey.
I'm offering you
10,000 above asking price.
- She ain't for sale.
- Why not?
One of the puteros got a little carried away with her tonight.
What was her name?
Araceli.
What are you gonna do with her?
I don't know, man.
You can't change
the world, viejo.
World don't want to be changed.
I really don't want to hurt
anyone else, not even you.
So, just do what I say, okay?
Come on.
Come on, tell your boy
at the front door to go home.
- Do it!
- Armando.
- You can knock off now.
- You sure?
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
I got it covered.
All right.
Get the girls out of here.
Johns stay inside!
Johns stay inside.
Hey, you, inside! Inside!
Which way do you want me to go?
Cocina.
Girls, cocina, cocina.
You, sit down.
You, go!
Dinero, inside.
Bring. Bring in here.
Come on, here you go.
Go, go!
Pay them!
Easy, easy.
Yeah, that's sureo style
right there, bitch.
You're bleeding out good, viejo.
I can finish it off.
You want me to make it quick?
After you, fuckpig.
Just go. Go!
Don't wake up your mom.
You hear me?
Don't come any closer.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Listen to me, Dre.
You're gonna hear some bad stuff
about me in the next few days.
Maybe the only way
for me to do something right
is by doing something bad.
I-- I don't get it.
It might not make
any sense to you now, but--
I tried.
Go back inside.
I-- I'll be fine. Go on.
Go on, go on.
Hello?
Anybody here?