[father] No!
[mother] You gotta get out now!
I can't do this anymore.
I will not let her see you like this.
-You need help!
-[father] I didn't mean it. I'm sorry.
-[mother] You're always sorry!
-[father] Come on.
[mother] How am I supposed
to believe you?
[father] Come on. You've been trying
to get rid of me since day one.
[mother] You know how many times
you promised you would stop?
-This is not my fault.
-Not your fault?
Look at you, you're drunk in the middle
of the day. Of course they fired you!
-Can we please talk about this?
-You don't give a shit about us.
-Please, don't do this.
-No, you have to go.
Get out and don't
come back until you're sober.
-[door closes]
-Daddy?
Daddy!
Daddy, don't go!
No, no, no, no, Dad, please!
No, don't! Oh-- please, come back, please!
Come back. Please, Dad.
-Please, Daddy, don't go!
-[mother] Tessa.
Daddy, please don't go!
Daddy! No!
I can't tell you how good it is
to see you again, Tessie.
There's-- there's towels in the bathroom
if you wanna take a shower.
-I'll make us some food.
-Thanks.
This is good.
-You are quite the cook, Tessie.
-Thanks.
Just like your mom.
Tried to call, you know.
Sent you gifts, every birthday, Christmas.
She didn't tell you, did she?
No.
Yeah.
So, the prodigal father has returned.
What for? What do you want?
You can stay, if-- if you want to.
We have room,
and I don't want you out on the street.
-Are you still drinking?
-Can you excuse us for a second?
I know that
this isn't the most convenient,
but you of all people should
appreciate me giving him a second chance.
Me of all people would know
that he's probably out there right now
shoving all of our shit into his pockets.
[scoffs] He's gonna hurt you.
You don't know him.
[man] Neither do you.
It's been, what,
ten years since you last saw him?
Nine.
Look, I'm just trying to protect you.
I don't need you to protect me.
[exhales]
[door closes]
Listen, I know exactly why you're here,
so you may as well
just take this and be on your way.
I don't want your money, kid.
All I want
is a relationship with my daughter.
-If you hurt her--
-Hey, whoa, easy.
I know you have no reason
in the world to trust me,
but how about you give me a shot, huh?
Well, have you found
a place in Seattle yet?
Nope. [exhales]
-No?
-No.
I'm gonna miss you, dude.
I'm gonna have to start watching
the Kardashians to get my fill of drama
in your absence.
Landon, I'm only going to Seattle.
-You're just a FaceTime away.
-Unh-unh.
You can always visit.
Between work and school,
you are gonna be swamped!
You're not gonna have
any time for anything, like,
friends, family,
especially not people like--
[clicks tongue]
People like who?
Me?
Is there something you wanna tell me,
or should I ask Landon?
'Cause he seems to know
a hell of a lot more than I do.
Not today, Satan.
I am gonna see you
both this weekend at the lake house.
-Don't bet on it.
-[Landon] Okay.
We'll be there.
[Landon exhales]
-What?
-What do you mean, what?
-When was this supposed to happen?
-A week.
What? A week?
You're going away in a week,
you haven't bothered to even tell me.
Well, when was I supposed to tell you?
Because you left.
Yeah, I'm here.
I came back, and I came back for you.
I couldn't get a hold of you
for nine days.
I didn't know if I'd ever see you again.
So what, is that it then?
I mean…
yeah, this-- this job's
a huge opportunity for me and…
And I'm hoping-- I was hoping
that you would come with me.
I was hoping
that we could move
to London after graduation.
And how was I supposed to know that?
Well, I was gonna tell you.
But I mean, it-- it doesn't really
matter anymore, does it?
You've made up your mind.
You've got a plan.
You've envisioned your life
in a way that doesn't have me in it.
You are in it if you wanna be.
Look, I get that you're angry,
and we do need to talk about this,
except I have to get to class, so…
We will continue this discussion.
Ooh, that's-- that's really big of you,
to find time in your busy schedule.
Thank you.
[TV playing]
Hey. [sighs]
[exhales]
[cell phone vibrating]
[beeps]
[man] Hi, Mom. How's London?
Good. I just wanted to check you're okay.
I heard that Tessa took a job
with Vance in Seattle.
-Where did you hear that?
-Christian and I were talking earlier.
That's kind of weird.
He and I have known each other
since long before you were born.
Look, I just prefer
not everyone knows my business.
Mom, I'm gonna call you back.
[beeps]
[exhales]
Do you need a ride somewhere?
Uh, yeah, yeah, sure.
-Thanks.
-Mm-hmm.
Hey, you wanna come inside?
Fuck it, why not?
[bartender] Enjoy.
-What are we drinking about?
-Didn't know we needed a reason.
Cheers to that.
[man] Aww, look at her in this one.
Mmm. [gasps]
-She looks really happy.
-[man sniffles]
I've really been trying.
Now more than ever.
-Yeah.
-Well, clearly not right now, but… [sighs]
…I am trying.
You know, you-- you really remind me of me
when I was your age.
-Fuck that.
-[customer] Mm!
-[father] Yeah.
-[customer] Seriously?
Hey, hey, buddy,
private conversation if you don't mind.
Hey! Just trying to get some ideas.
-[man] Whoa.
-[customer laughs]
That's my daughter,
you fucking piece of shit.
[grunting]
♪ I live a life of poison ♪
[vibrates]
Hey.
I'm sorry. Who is this?
-What are you doing here?
-Uh…
-Bonding. You know, Hardin here--
-Hey, Tess!
-What the hell did you do?
-I didn't do--
[Tessa] The bartender called me.
Oh, come on.
It wasn't a big deal. Look, he's fine.
You're drunk.
I had a drink. I just-- I was--
-I was backing up your dad, okay?
-Really?
-He started it, actually, so…
-[Tessa] Wow!
Somebody called the cops.
-You probably called the cops, you snitch.
-Great. Okay, let's go.
[father] Don't be mad at him.
He loves you.
[Hardin] Let's go.
[father] Oh-ho!
Yeah, you see that?
-Solid guy, right there.
-[Tessa] Hmm.
[father]
Why would anyone wanna leave you?
[Hardin] I don't know.
Yeah, this is just-- it's so enjoyable.
Why wouldn't I stay?
[laughs]
I think we're in trouble.
-Hey, hey, take it easy.
-[Hardin sighs]
[father moans]
[mutters]
[sighs]
[snores]
You know, I'm not sure
that I like this new friendship.
[Hardin] I was just trying to be nice.
I offered him a ride,
and the bar was actually his idea.
He's an alcoholic, and so are you.
Two alcoholics walk into a bar.
[laughs]
I'm glad that you think this is funny.
I was showing him some pictures
of you on my phone.
This asshole leans over and starts
saying what he'd like to do to you.
I'm-- so?
So I told him I've already done that.
["Maraschino Love" by EZI playing]
[gasps, sighs]
-Hardin.
-What?
I'm apologizing.
♪ Around four in the morning
It was dark, I was lonely ♪
♪ And you swore to God that you knew me ♪
♪ And I lied, said "yes"
So you'd hold me ♪
♪ From the back of the hallway ♪
♪ Pulled you into the doorway… ♪
-[Hardin kisses]
-[mutters]
[sighs]
♪ We were both fucked up in the story… ♪
-I'm sorry.
-[exhales]
-I'm so sorry.
-[mutters]
♪ Like candy on my tongue ♪
♪ Once I got a taste, I couldn't stop… ♪
-Please forgive me.
-[sighs] I-- that's--
-[exhales] That's not fair.
-Please forgive me.
What if--
-Shh! He's asleep.
-[sighs]
[slurps]
♪ Was like, Oh, my God
My new favorite drug ♪
♪ You go down like liquid velvet
Maraschino love ♪
♪ I was lost in the moment… ♪
-[sighs]
-[wrapper crinkling]
[Tessa sighs]
♪ Going round and round in an orbit… ♪
[both panting]
♪ Your lips a sugar rush… ♪
[Tessa grunts]
-[Hardin] Tessa,I feel so happy.
-[grunting]
[sighs]
-[Hardin] You feeling this?
-[both panting]
♪ I'll sip you out the bottle
You're so sweet like cherry pop ♪
[panting, grunting]
[vocalizing]
[whistling]
So, um…
I heard you guys are moving.
Yeah, yeah,
I actually need to start packing.
-I'll just finish up and get out of here.
-No, no, no, no, I didn't mean it like--
[chuckles] No, no, you don't
need me around here. I'll just, uh…
-I got a few errands to run anyway, so--
-Dad.
[clicks tongue]
That feels really weird to say.
[knock on door]
Well, that'll be my ride. [sighs]
You're leaving now?
Yeah.
Come here.
Thank you so much for letting me stay.
No, stay, stay, he's coming.
Uh, hey, don't…
Don't disappear on me again.
[father] Hardin.
-Right.
-[Hardin exhales]
So you're shipping me out next?
[sighs]
You okay?
You know,
it's not like I want to leave you.
You don't have to.
Oh.
Vance's offer, it's literally,
it's a dream come true.
I've wanted to live in Seattle
since I was a kid,
and the only thing that would make
it better is if you came with me.
I don't--
I don't know why you want me there.
You know, I don't really fit
into that flashy lifestyle,
and it's never been
the kind of thing you've been after.
-I want to make a life together.
-So do I. So stay here and we can.
-You're not listening to me!
-I am listening!
-I've wanted this job since I was--
-I know. I know. I know.
You have a great job in Seattle.
That is great. I'm happy for you.
But I don't. I don't have anything there.
-You'd have me.
-Okay, that's not enough.
[sighs] You know I didn't mean it.
[inhales, exhales]
Well, if I'm… [sniffles]
if I'm not enough,
that's-- that's-- that's your problem,
but you're not gonna stop me.
[scoffs]
[sighs]
[woman] Vance Publishing, please hold.
No, I can't. I'm swamped.
Well, you're gonna have to speak
to my assistant. No, the new one.
Um, well, I'll try and squeeze you in
for 30 minutes this afternoon, all right?
-Tessa! Hey, come in!
-Okay.
I can come back.
-No, no, come in. I'm just heading out.
-Yeah.
-Um, you have a safe trip.
-Okay.
See you.
Are you sure that you're okay
driving up by yourself?
-Uh, she's not going by herself.
-I'm taking Smith with me.
Besides, I prefer
to get us settled up there
while Christian finishes things here.
Have you decided what part of town
you'll be staying in?
No, I'm still deciding between two places.
It's a little scary trying
to pick somewhere off the internet.
No. Tessa, just stay with us.
-You know, until you get situated.
-No, no, I couldn't ask--
You didn't. Come on.
It'll be fun. Christian will be thrilled.
He's been dying to spend
more time with Hardin. [exhales]
[hesitates] Uh, well,
he's actually not coming with me.
Oh.
Well, when he comes to visit, then.
You know, between us,
Christian was pretty disappointed
Hardin turned him down on his job offer.
What-- what job was that?
Basically anything he wanted.
Hey.
Hey, hey, hey. Don't walk away from me.
Hey, don't follow me.
Tess, I'm sorry. I didn't mean it.
Really, I-- I shouldn't have said it.
Can you stop saying things
you don't mean?
I can't tell what's true and what's not.
Can you maybe stop making decisions
without talking things through first?
Okay.
Kimberly invited me to stay
with them in Seattle if that's not…
-Did she?
-…weird.
No, no, no.
It's not weird. It's good. It's great.
Vance is always gone on business trips,
so I think it'll be a win-win.
Yeah.
How do you think they make that work,
the long distance?
I don't know. They communicate?
[laughs] Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
What was that?
What?
You know, the thing underneath
the thing that you just said.
Why-- why didn't you tell me
that Vance offered you a job in Seattle?
'Cause I wasn't gonna take it.
Yeah, but why didn't you tell me
that-- that you weren't gonna take it?
Because here I am begging you
to come with me
just to find out that
you had something there.
He kept harping on me. It wasn't
something I wanted to deal with.
And remember, at the time,
I had no idea you were going.
We do need to stop
keeping secrets from each other.
Yeah, agreed.
[kisses]
We'll have fun this weekend, okay?
Okay.
You look like Popeye. [laughs]
A very sexy Popeye, come on.
[Tessa] Get up, we're gonna be late.
We could have just met you there,
couldn't we?
-[laughing]
-Why did we all have to come together?
It's a long drive,
and this way we get to have
some very much needed family time.
Yeah.
Much needed. Great.
You're lucky I love you.
Okay. I spy
with my little eye something black.
Black. Easy, Hardin's soul.
-[laughs] Oh, yeah. 'Cause you just--
-Hey!
-[man] Come on, boys.
-That's why!
-Boys…
-That's why your soul is black!
Hey, don't-- don't touch me!
["Can't Stop" by Coucheron playing]
♪ But now I can't stop dreaming
About your love ♪
♪ But it's all right
Yeah, it's all right… ♪
-[chattering]
-[laughing]
[chattering, laughing]
-[chattering]
-[laughing]
♪ Just to recommend to you ♪
♪ Put my radio on a pedestal… ♪
Are you still going to New York?
Yeah, I mean, I've got everything
set up at NYU, so I'm just gonna…
[inhales] I guess, go with the flow.
You know?
Hmm. I need to get better at that.
What, are you having, uh,
are you having second thoughts?
[Tessa] And third
and fourth and fifth and…
I don't know. I'm just worried
that I made the wrong decision.
[Landon] Tess.
It's-- it's just, apparently,
Hardin wanted me to go to England
with him after graduation.
And I don't know, maybe I should.
Tess, you've been--
you've been gushing about Seattle
since the day I first met you.
Why stray from your path?
Go with the flow?
[Landon] No, no.
Cop out. That's not you. That's me.
You have to do you.
Yeah, and what about him?
What about him? He--
Mr. Grumpy, he's…
If he loves you, he could…
follow you. Just saying.
[sighs] Ooh, wow.
Mm-hmm, some hard truths. Tough love.
-I'm gonna need more wine.
-Good luck.
See? Did you see--
I don't wanna lose this.
I don't either.
"But if adventures will not befall
a young lady in her own village,
she must seek them abroad."
[chuckles] "But there is nothing like
staying at home, for real comfort."
"You pierce my soul.
I'm half agony, half hope."
"We are all fools in love."
I thought you were Darcy, and you've
just been Jane Austen the whole time.
[laughs]
So are you ever gonna show me
what you're writing in there?
I-- maybe.
Someday.
[man] Reservation for Scotts?
[hostess] Yes, Mr. Scott, right this way.
[chattering]
[Mr. Scott] Thank you.
Hardin.
-[laughs] Hey, Lilly! How are you?
-[gasps]
[Hardin] How are you?
-No fucking way, it's been forever!
-A long time, huh?
-This is Tessa. Tessa, Lillian.
-Hi.
Nice dress.
I'll be over in a sec.
[chattering]
-I might get something different, but--
-[Mr. Scott] Really?
-Crab cakes?
-[laughs]
-Good evening, folks.
-[Mr. Scott] Yes.
Every time.
I'm Robert.
I'll be taking care of you tonight.
Uh, can I get you started
with a round of drinks?
Yeah, I think, uh, we'll do
a bottle of cab for the table.
-And some water for us.
-Uh, and I think we're ready to order.
-Great. What'll it be?
-You're gonna get the cr…
-Crab cakes.
-Yes, and I'm gonna get the…
-…fish and chips. Yeah, always. Um…
-Fish and chips.
[Mr. Scott] And also, uh,
we would like to get a sablefish
for after the meal to take home.
It's a good choice.
And for you?
Um, is there anything
that you'd recommend?
The cedar plank salmon is our specialty.
Okay.
I'm more into, like, pasta.
Carbs. Yeah, love carbs.
Um, we have a squid ink spaghetti.
Um, it was lovely
to see you and to meet you guys,
but I'll, uh, I'll have to go, so…
Too fancy. How about
we whip you up something special?
Yeah. Okay. Thank you.
Can I get you anything,
or do you need a minute?
Yeah, you can come back.
"Robert."
-Thank you, man.
-[Mr. Scott] Thank you, Robert.
-Thank you.
-[Landon clears throat]
["Heaven" by FINNEAS playing]
[Hardin] Alone at last.
[shudders]
[sighs] That's good.
[clears throat]
Come on! Before they get home, ideally.
[Tessa gasps]
Ow, ow. [laughs]
Oh!
I really hope they're having
more than one cocktail.
You do kind of like it, though.
The thrill of being caught.
-[clicks]
-[bubbling]
Oh, that's nice.
♪ So what if one night is never enough? ♪
♪ Drive me in… insane ♪
♪ Don't stop ♪
♪ Tell me, tell me, tell me, don't stop ♪
♪ Heaven isn't as wonderful ♪
♪ Heaven isn't as beautiful… ♪
Trust me.
♪ As you ♪
♪ Isn't as wonderful ♪
♪ Heaven isn't as beautiful ♪
♪ As you ♪
♪ We got big plans in bed again ♪
♪ 'Cause you're no saint ♪
♪ Slipping my hand under your dress ♪
♪ I'm glad you came ♪
♪ Don't stop ♪
♪ Tell me, tell me, tell me, don't stop ♪
♪ Heaven isn't as wonderful ♪
♪ Heaven isn't as beautiful… ♪
[gasps]
[panting]
♪ Isn't as wonderful ♪
♪ Heaven isn't as beautiful… ♪
-Oh, Tess.
-[both panting]
[Hardin] Mm.
♪ So what
If I'm such a sucker for pleasure? ♪
♪ So what if one night is never enough… ♪
[panting continues]
♪ Drive me insane ♪
[both continue panting]
-[Tessa grunts]
-[moaning]
♪ Heaven isn't as beautiful… ♪
♪ As you ♪
[Hardin sighs]
[sighs]
[Tessa] I really wish
you were coming to Seattle.
-Can I ask you a question?
-Mm.
Does your moving to Seattle
have anything to do with Trevor?
No, no. I mean…
we barely even talk anymore.
Did you ever have feelings for him?
-That's two questions.
-Tess, be honest.
Uh, there was a moment when--
Hey!
Seriously?
That's not fair.
Hardin!
-[clicks]
-[Hardin's voice] Leave a message.
[sniffles]
Hey, where are you?
Can you give me a call back?
[cell phone chimes]
Robert.
Right, um, Tessa.
So what are you doing out here?
[sighs] I had a fight with my--
It's complicated.
Oh. A few of us are doing
after hours if you wanna join.
Um, yeah.
-[Robert] Yeah?
-Yeah.
[Robert] Okay.
[chuckles] Probably
should have worn a coat.
[Tessa] So you live here, right?
[Robert] Born and raised.
-I actually just got into med school.
-[Tessa] Oh, wow!
So just working here, saving up till then.
Wow, congratulations.
-Thanks.
-Where-- where are you going?
U-Dub was my dream, but Mount Sinai gave
me a scholarship I couldn't pass up, so--
Mount Sinai's in?
-NYC.
-Okay.
-New York City, if you've heard of it.
-[laughs]
The Big Apple. You know, Nora, actually,
Nora and I went to undergrad
together, and then she moved out there.
-So I'll know someone.
-[Nora] Hmm.
Talking shit? Yeah?
Now, look.
She's already got the New York attitude.
-Tess! Hey!
-[Tessa] Hey!
Hey. Okay,
so this is Robert, and this is Nora.
Yes, there will be a test afterwards.
[Tessa] And they both live in New York.
-[Landon] Thank you. New York!
-[Robert] Pleasure.
Hey! What? Oh, my God! [laughs]
[Nora] How are you? It's been a while!
-You-- you remember Robert, right?
-[Hardin] Yeah.
I remember Robert.
I'll do an old fashioned, actually.
[exhales] I'm off, actually.
You're still wearing
your name tag and your uniform, so…
So, I heard that you're moving to Seattle.
Yeah, um,
I'm actually transferring for work.
Oh, I'm jealous. I'd much rather
be in Seattle than New York.
Well, I keep telling Hardin
he should give it a shot.
-It's not for me.
-No, it's not for him.
-[scoffs] It's the best. It is, yeah!
-[Robert] It's the best.
My girlfriend and I, we've lived
in Capitol Hill for a few years now.
Oh, your girlfriend?
[Lillian] Yeah, my girlfriend Riley.
We should probably leave now.
I don't really wanna go just yet.
I'm-- I'm gonna head home.
Let me walk you out. [clears throat]
[chattering]
-I'm really sorry about all of…
-You don't have to apologize.
Sorry.
-Sorry. It's…
-[both laugh]
I don't-- I don't know why I do that.
I could guess, but I won't.
Um, it was nice meeting you.
[scoffs] You too.
And thanks for…
Hmm.
I'm not expecting anything, but if
someday, you find yourself in the city…
Give me a call.
Or don't.
Hmm? It's up to you.
[Tessa] Hey.
Hey.
Good morning.
-What-- what's that face?
-How was, uh, how was last night?
Oh, it was good.
It was-- it was-- it was fine.
Nora's nice. She's, uh, she's…
kind of a big deal
on the, uh, restaurant scene.
She's gonna show me around
when I get to New York.
-Hmm. That's really-- really convenient.
-I don't know. [laughs]
How was-- how was the hot tub?
[hesitates]
[Landon laughs]
[Tessa] Guess what Landon found.
I thought that we were gonna
be more open with each other.
So did I.
I didn't ask for his number.
He just gave it to me.
No, I just found
another guy's number in your things, Tess.
You made it look like
you were with Lillian last night.
-Lillian's my friend.
-So is he.
You guys just met.
How could you be friends?
This is what you do. You sabotage
every good moment that we have.
No, no, no, if I wanted to try
and sabotage a good moment,
I would have brought up your moment
with Trevor. But for now--
Why can't you just let things be,
like, let us be happy for once?
Tess, you must admit,
if I were moving away
with an admitted love interest,
you would have some feelings about that,
wouldn't you?
We're friends! From work.
You don't get to choose
who I have as friends!
They don't wanna be
your fucking friends, okay?
-Then why can't you just trust me?
-I do. I do trust you.
-It's them I don't trust.
-No, you don't.
You don't trust me. You don't trust
anyone. You just control them.
Is this-- is this really about them,
or is this about me moving?
[scoffs] The irony is I got you
the damn job in the first place.
I mean, I might have had
something to do with it.
Tess, how many freshmen do you know
with jobs at top publishing firms,
their transfers taken care of,
places to live? How many?
-Wow.
-[zips bag]
Yeah, this honesty thing's
really paying off for us. So I won't…
I won't give up Seattle for you,
so you just turn on me?
There is a big difference between
not being able to live without someone
and loving them.
[Mrs. Scott]
I'm really excited for your new adventure!
Yeah!
He is scared of losing you.
He loves you,
and he knows that you're the best
thing that's ever happened to him.
-Well--
-No, Tessa, it's true.
-You've changed his life. He knows it.
-[exhales]
We all know it. [chuckles]
You stay in touch. Okay.
Bye.
-["Unfolding" by Luca Fogale playing]
-♪ Let me out… ♪
She's gonna thrive up there, man.
What, and that's a bad thing?
This is a big step for her in her career.
You should be happy for her.
I am.
I am happy.
[scoffs]
You could come with her.
I've got loads of work for you.
-I don't wanna do that.
-You'd get great benefits.
-We could spend time together.
-I don't want your handouts.
I'm sorry. I--
They're the reason I'm here in the first
place, and I don't want any more help.
Tessa didn't get a favor. She's excellent.
She earned this position.
She does deserve it.
I'm sure she'll do smashingly.
♪ Lost to win ♪
♪ Everything believed in… ♪
Tessa.
Tess.
Tess?
♪ In time, untrace ♪
♪ Every part of this still holding ♪
♪ You are not breaking ♪
♪ You're not broken ♪
♪ You are unfolding ♪
♪ You are, you are, you are ♪
♪ You're not breaking ♪
♪ You're not broken ♪
♪ You are unfolding ♪
♪ You are, you are, you are ♪
♪ You're not breaking ♪
♪ You are not broken ♪
-♪ You are unfolding ♪
-♪ You are, you are, you are ♪
♪ You… ♪
-♪ Are ♪
-♪ You are, you are, you are ♪
♪ You are, you are ♪
[vocalizes]
[Tessa] Pain.
Lately, I've become
very well acquainted with it.
The slow and steady, aching pain.
The type that comes when you've
been hurt repeatedly by the same person.
You finally breathe,
thinking that
yesterday's problem will stay in the past.
-[scoffs, sighs]
-[Tessa] In fact, it's today's problem.
Tomorrow's problem
and the problem of every day after that.
Only in those rare moments
when he pulls me to his chest
and makes promises
he never seems able to keep
does the pain disappear.
[doorbell rings]
Shit, she looks upset.
[Kimberly and Tessa] Hey!
-Let me take that for you up them stairs!
-[Tessa] Oh, thanks!
-Welcome home.
-Thanks.
Well, you look…
[sighs] terrible.
Come here.
["Betsy" by Billie Marten playing]
♪ Heard you got the job ♪
♪ Hope it serves you well… ♪
Oh, uh, excuse me, do you guys
know where Bagley Hall is?
♪ Coffee ticket town ♪
♪ Your steady behavior
It's all in your nature ♪
♪ I call you my neighbor at number nine ♪
♪ It's all right now ♪
♪ Now, all right, now ♪
♪ Take a generational bow ♪
♪ Are you calling out… ♪
[grunts, sighs]
♪ …bang! Baby, you're dead ♪
♪ Politics will mess with your head… ♪
[cell phone chimes]
♪ You leader of evil ♪
♪ You messed up the church
Put a gun to the steeple… ♪
[ringing]
[Hardin] Hello.
Hey!
Hey, what's going on?
[woman] Hardin, come back here!
[exhales]
[cell phone vibrating]
Wait, wait, don't hang up.
That was Iskra, my trainer,
I'm at the gym.
-I'm kicking his ass, Tess!
-And he's not kicking my ass.
I didn't mean to hang up.
I think you did, Tess,
and I know exactly why,
'cause I would've
thought the same thing.
I mean, yeah, I'm a little relieved.
It's nice showing Landon the ropes.
[laughs]
-[Iskra] Don't take all day!
-[Hardin] Okay, one minute.
You okay, though?
Yeah, yeah, I'm fine.
How was the drive down?
Was it not too long?
It was good, but when you get
in the city, the traffic's terrible.
It takes, like, 20 minutes to go a mile.
[chuckles]
And Vance and Kimberly's?
Yeah, yeah, it's great.
The, um, the place is amazing.
It's, like, it's huge. It's like a palace.
Nice.
I'm really glad, Tess.
[exhales]
-I'm sorry I hurt you.
-You don't--
No, I…
I just want you to be happy.
You deserve to be happy.
It's cool that you're boxing.
I know, right? I really fucking like it.
It's also nice to be able to punch people
and not have anyone call the police.
[laughs]
I think that that's a step forward.
Right?
[exhales] Trying a new approach.
Hardin, this is not leisure hour, come on!
All right, Tess, I really have to go now.
I'm so glad you called.
Yeah, yeah. Me too.
All right, we'll talk soon.
-Bye, Tess.
-Bye.
[sighs]
[Iskra] Yes.
Oh, look at that face, you pretty boy.
You scared to fight Landon?
-You heard-- oh, shit!
-Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
[woman] Vance Publishing, please hold.
[camera shutter clicks]
Selfies, huh?
No, I was…
I-- I was just
showing Hardin my new office.
Mm-hmm.
Seattle looks good on you.
So, how's it going?
Fine. Yeah, I mean…
work, school,
it's a lot, but it's fine.
Give it time, you'll settle in.
You'll find a place. It's exciting.
[Tessa] Are you sure
that you don't want a glass?
I think she might be onto us, darling.
Well…
we have some news.
We just found out we're having a baby!
Are you kidding?
I'm so happy for you guys.
I'm gonna tell Hardin, though,
if that's all right with you.
Yeah, yeah, of course.
Ken mentioned that he managed
to get his GPA up to a 4.0.
Must be looking forward to graduating.
Yeah, that's great.
Um, I-- I didn't even know that.
It's because of you.
I mean, I didn't write his papers…
-[Vance] No.
-…for him. [laughs]
[chuckles] Maybe not.
I'm sure he did that.
But he has got a gift, that boy,
but he's stubborn as hell.
You're one to talk.
-Touché.
-[laughs]
Well, I should get some sleep. [exhales]
But I will see you guys tomorrow.
Yeah! Of course.
And you should take this.
It's too nice of a bottle to go to waste.
-Yes, please!
-Don't worry about me, I won't have any.
-[laughing]
-You-- you don't need any more!
-Good night, darling.
-Night!
You have to suffer like me.
[cell phone vibrates]
There you are.
-Just got back from the gym.
-[Tessa inhales] You did?
Wow, you--
you must be getting pretty good.
[chuckles]
Are you drunk?
I was hanging out with Vance and Kimberly,
and she gave me the rest of the bottle.
Oh, yeah? So how much wine have you had?
I'm on my… third?
You were actually quite the… topic.
You didn't answer my call earlier.
No, I know,
I've been at work since, like, eight.
Except for taking office selfies.
Which you didn't respond to.
Tessa.
[British accent] Hardin Allen Scott!
[laughs]
Why are you laughing?
It's just all so ridiculous.
I think you need to put that wine down.
Make me.
Well, I would, if I was there.
What else would you make me do?
Theresa Lynn Young!
Are you trying to have phone sex with me?
Tell me what you would do
if you were here.
Are you lying in your bed?
Mm-hmm.
Close your eyes.
-Are they closed?
-Mm-hmm.
Are you sure?
[exhales]
[softly panting]
Fuck, I wish I was there
watching you right now.
You like that, don't you?
Watching me?
Fuck yeah, I do.
How'd you sleep?
[Tessa] Good.
Not as good as I do with you.
I know the feeling.
[Tessa] Come here.
I miss you.
I miss you too.
Don't say "too." It sounds like
you're just agreeing with me.
I love you.
[moaning]
Tessa?
Tess!
No, no, no, Tessa! Tessa! [gasps]
-[Tessa panting]
-Tessa! Tessa!
Tess! No! No! No! [pounds door]
I love you.
[Tessa panting] I love you too.
[Hardin] Fuck! No, no, no!
[shouts]
[panting]
[sighs]
[doorbell rings]
-[Hardin laughs]
-Hi! Hi.
Hi.
What-- what are you doing here?
I mean, I came to see you.
I can leave.
No. [exhales]
-[Hardin] Let me get my bags.
-Mnh-mnh.
[both chuckle]
[Hardin] Give us a hand.
-[Tessa groans]
-[chuckles]
[boy] What's the fastest train
you ever been on?
-There's this train in Japan--
-Oh, hey!
-Hey, hey!
-[boy] Hardin!
-Smith. What's up? How you doing?
-Fine.
He asked if he could stay, and I thought
you might be all right with that.
[chuckles] It's a lovely place.
Where should I, uh, drop my stuff?
-Uh, let me show you.
-Cool.
-I'll call you guys when dinner's ready!
-[Hardin] Sounds good!
[Tessa] It's this way.
It's nice to see a smile back on her face.
It is.
[laughs]
So, um…
I found this.
And I'm really sorry, but once
I picked it up, I couldn't put it down.
[exhales]
You're a brilliant writer, Tess.
And I came
across that page about pain and…
I just wanted to apologize.
The way I made you feel is inexcusable.
So, I'm sorry.
I didn't-- I didn't mean
for you to read any of this.
-It's pretty raw. [exhales]
-I'm sure you didn't.
I needed to hear it.
In your words, and…
I fucking hate myself for making you
feel that way, but I'm sorry.
Thank you.
[Kimberly] Hey, steaks are on!
Be right there!
Oh.
Will we?
[Tessa panting] I love you too.
We shouldn't keep them waiting.
[chuckles] What?
I-- I mean, I'm sure that they're fine--
Come on, I'm hungry.
He really wants me to go.
He keeps talking about me wearing
the hat and the gown and everything.
What's so bad about that?
It just looks ridiculous.
Can you imagine me
in the hat and gown and everything?
I don't even wanna go to the ceremony.
I can't imagine it,
but I really wanna see it.
[laughs] Yeah.
You gotta celebrate
your accomplishments.
You don't wanna look back in regret
at having not had those experiences.
Trust me, I know firsthand.
-I'll give it some thought.
-I think you should.
-Hey, buddy.
-[Smith] Hi.
-This needs turning. Do you wanna do it?
-[Smith] Why not?
Okay, there you go, grab that.
-This is really nice.
-Yeah.
You know,
all of us together under one roof.
[chattering]
-[Kimberly] Here we all are.
-[Tessa] Yeah.
Well, tonight anyway.
[Kimberly] Oh, come on.
You two will work it out.
-Sometimes distance is a good thing.
-[groans]
You think so?
Honestly, I have no idea. [laughs]
Look, relationships…
…are complicated.
[Tessa spits]
[exhales]
[panting]
[shouting]
Hey.
[panting]
-[exhales]
-Did I do something?
You barely said a word to me
the whole night.
I had this horrible dream
of you and Robert.
And I can't get it out of my fucking head.
But I'm here with you.
[Hardin] That's exactly it.
I can't help but think that
you should be with someone else.
Your life would be so much easier.
There's all this bad shit that
I've been trying to suppress for so long,
it's-- it's just all coming up.
And there's nothing I can do.
The added thought
of losing you is just… [laughs]
It's pretty fucking dark in here, Tess.
Why didn't you just tell me?
That's the whole point
of being open with each other.
It's a burden for me,
and I don't wanna burden you.
[Tessa] I don't want
to be with anyone else.
-I wanna be with you.
-[sighs]
Hey.
["Free Animal" by Foreign Air playing]
[moaning]
Fuck me till you forget about that dream.
♪ My heart beats in patters
With a broken sound ♪
♪ You're the only one
That can calm me down… ♪
[Hardin] Fuck yeah.
♪ All of this time
I should've figured it out ♪
♪ I'm a free animal, free animal… ♪
[moaning continues]
♪ Free animal, free animal ♪
♪ My heart beats in patters
With a broken sound ♪
♪ Free animal, free animal ♪
♪ You're the only one
That can calm me down ♪
[panting and moaning continue]
♪ Get what you came for
What you stayed for ♪
♪ I only know how to… ♪
[Hardin] Oh, fuck.
Look in the mirror.
[panting]
Yes, baby.
-You close?
-Yeah.
♪ Flesh and bones won't lie ♪
-♪ They won't lie ♪
-♪ Free animal, free animal ♪
♪ My heart beats in patters
With a broken sound ♪
[panting]
[clears throat]
We didn't use protection last night.
[sighs] Yeah, I know.
I have to go to the drug store today.
I should get on the pill anyway.
[both laugh]
Yeah.
Yeah, you with no condom
on a regular basis,
that's gonna work for me.
[chattering]
-Hey-hey!
-[Tessa] Hey!
You look in better spirits this morning.
[laughs] Yeah, think I just needed
a good night's sleep.
[cell phone vibrating]
-Oh, it's Mom. One sec, guys.
-[beeps]
-Hi, Mom.
-Hi, my love, how are you doing?
Good. Thanks. How are you?
That must be about the wedding.
The-- whose wedding?
Trish is-- oh, my God.
Yeah, yeah.
-Oh, that's amazing. She deserves it.
-[chuckles]
[Vance] Yeah.
And Mike is a good guy,
so he'll look after her.
-I need to go.
-[Kimberly] Oh.
-Okay.
-Come on, bud.
Smith! Hey, hey, hey, back here!
Hey!
-Bye!
-[Smith] Bye!
[Kimberly] Bye.
I will. I will. I will.
All right, all right, goodbye.
[beeps]
[laughs] What?
What?
So?
So, what do you wanna do today?
[chattering]
Got everything?
[Hardin] Yep.
There's nothing--
there's nothing you've forgotten?
No, I think I'm good.
What happened to we're not keeping
secrets from each other?
What are you on about?
You're not-- you're not gonna tell me
about your mom's wedding?
[chuckles] Tess.
The only reason I haven't told you
is 'cause I don't wanna go.
Okay, why-- why don't you wanna go?
I mean, I thought you wanted
to show me your hometown.
I wanna show you London.
I do not wanna show you my hometown.
If you don't wanna bring me, I think
that that's fine, but it's her big day.
I really think you need to be there.
If I was going, I would bring you, but--
Do you know what,
I'll think about it, okay?
Okay.
Hey, this was a good weekend.
How good?
-[Hardin] This good.
-[chuckles]
-Better.
Can you come back on Wednesday?
Vance is having an event.
I'll try.
Okay.
[man coughs]
[coughs]
[continues coughing]
Richard, I nearly
smashed your fucking head in!
[exhales]
The fuck are you thinking,
breaking in here?
[Richard] You weren't here and, uh…
Tess told me where you keep the key.
[clears throat]
You look like shit.
Yeah, well, uh, I owe a guy.
How much are you in for?
Five hundred.
[exhales]
[exhales, groans]
You can take this.
Here.
-[clears throat]
-[Hardin] My dad gave me that.
I never wear it.
And it's worth a lot more than
what you need, so…
Thanks. I…
-[Hardin] Yeah.
-[gags]
I'm gonna get better for her. [panting]
I'll get better.
[exhales] I promise.
This should protect you
from pregnancy for the next three months.
My concern is you may not need it.
It's your cervix.
You may not be able to get pregnant.
We need to do more tests before we know.
[Ken] Hmm.
As much as I'd like to help,
by the time you apply for the transfer,
you register and start classes,
I don't think
it's gonna be worth the hassle,
and I don't think you're gonna get
the classes you need to graduate.
I know. I figured you were gonna say this.
I thought I'd give it a try.
It's only two months.
And, you know, it's been one
of my biggest dreams to see you graduate.
[scoffs] I guess
it hasn't always been a given, has it?
No, no, it hasn't.
It has been a gift having you here.
And…
and I'm grateful that you were willing
to give me a chance to see me sober.
Yeah.
When was that?
Oh.
That was freshman year.
Your mom, Vance and I.
I've never seen it before.
-You know she's getting married?
-To Mike?
-To Mike.
-Oh.
Good for her.
He always seemed like a nice guy.
I've always thought he's a bit
of a wanker, but if she's happy.
-Two months! It's just gonna go like…
-[snaps fingers]
["Disco Body Parts" by Yung Bae playing]
-[chattering]
-[laughing]
♪ Skin covering bones ♪
♪ Fear finally fading ♪
♪ Love you, la-la-la-la-la ♪
♪ Ooh, everything's glowing ♪
♪ Faces guiding me home… ♪
[laughing]
-Hey!
-[Hardin] Hello.
-Don't you two look gorgeous.
-Obviously! [laughs]
Relax, its soda water.
Did you tell him? Did…
-Vance told me.
-Oh.
Well, enjoy.
I have to go play hostess. Okay.
They were ecstatic
when I told them you were coming.
What, just them?
Well, I was happy.
Um…
I do have some bad news.
Oh, uh, what?
It's not looking like I'm gonna be
able to get here for another two months.
What-- what do you mean, like visit?
-Wait, what?
-[laughs]
[Tessa] What? What do you mean?
I mean, like, for good.
Like…
Uh, wait.
What, do you mean, like, move here?
-It's two months, though, I wonder if--
-Are you serious?
Should I just call the whole thing off?
Maybe I should just cancel.
-I love you so much.
-I love you.
Hate to break it up, but I wanna dance!
Come on!
["Love Me Land" by Zara Larsson playing]
-There's my boy. How are you?
-Hey.
Never better.
I better go work.
Go ahead.
[vocalizing]
♪ Touch me in the way that you do
No matter who's in the room ♪
♪ I see you sweatin' when you feel it
Going full out, baby ♪
♪ Touch me in the way that you do
No matter who's in the room ♪
♪ I see you sweatin' ♪
♪ Never thought I would love again
Never thought ♪
♪ Here I am in love me land ♪
[vocalizes]
♪ Never thought I would love again
Here I am ♪
♪ Here I am in love me land ♪ [vocalizes]
♪ Lost in your vocabulary ♪
♪ Got our own vernaculary ♪
♪ Take me home, don't call me Mary ♪
[vocalizing]
♪ Touch me in the way that you do
No matter who's in the room ♪
♪ I see you sweatin' when you feel it
Going full out, baby ♪
♪ Touch me in the way that you do
No matter who's in the room ♪
♪ I see you sweatin' ♪
♪ Never thought I would love again ♪
♪ Here I am in love me land ♪ [vocalizes]
Let's go.
-Right now. Yeah?
-Mm. Mm.
-[both laughing]
-[Tessa exhales]
-[Hardin laughs]
-[sighs]
-You're moving here.
-[laughs]
-Yeah.
-[Tessa panting]
[grunting]
-Your elbows are up again.
-[Vance] Oh, man.
[panting] All right, then.
You looking forward to visiting home?
I know I am.
Oh, I see.
Celebrating your mom's
happiness doesn't sound appealing?
-[chuckles] It's not that.
-So, what's going on?
I really wanna bring Tessa, but I don't
wanna bring her around my old life.
It's just a sad house and a sad place.
[sighs]
Has she ever made you
feel badly about your past?
No.
The only way you can find out
if you trust her is to trust her.
And it would mean the world to Trish
having you both there.
[panting] Look, seriously, mate.
Your wedding is a moment that's…
…bigger than anything else
that you can possibly imagine.
-[scoffs]
-It kind of changes you.
Mm-hmm.
And that's why they all fail, right?
Not all of them.
Not if you find the right one.
You know…
I believe that you
have two real great loves.
So in your case,
that would be Tessa and you.
[both laugh]
You gonna show me what you got?
-Come on then!
-[shouts]
[Hardin grunts, laughs]
I got us tickets to England.
[both] Mm!
[kisses]
Hey, don't worry, Mom, I'll get it.
No, no! I've got it!
-Hi!
-Oh, it's so good to see you both.
-[Hardin] Tess, is there a body in here?
-I didn't know how much I'd need.
-[Trish] Here you go.
-Thank you.
[Trish] How was the flight?
Sorry it's not more comfortable. I, uh…
I didn't expect the house to sell
on the first day.
[Tessa] No, it's great.
I left your bed up, Hardin.
I wasn't expecting to sleep on the floor.
-[Tessa] It's perfect. Thank you.
-[laughs]
Well, you guys must be exhausted,
so, uh, I'll leave you to it.
-I'm staying, uh, next door at Mike's.
-[cell phone vibrates]
[Hardin] Okay.
-[beeps]
-Give me a second. I'm stepping outside.
We're really happy for you.
Thank you. I'm glad you came.
Actually, I've gotta go
to the bridal store in the morning.
I was wondering,
do you wanna come with me?
-Yeah, I'd-- I'd love to. That's…
-Great. Great.
-Call me if you need me.
-[Tessa] Okay.
[both] Bye.
And don't take any of my stuff
or go in my room
and definitely
don't have any friends over.
[Richard] Yeah, yeah. Yeah,
hey, thanks for letting me stay here.
Yeah, well, don't thank me,
'cause it's not permanent.
-[scoffs] Yeah, yeah, I know.
-[Hardin] Call me if there's a problem.
Sure thing, Hardin. Bye.
[beeps]
Who was-- who was that?
That was a random homeless man
who I've been letting sleep on my couch.
All the hipsters
are doing it these days, so…
-Thank you.
-Of course.
-[scoffs] There's nothing to eat.
-What are you looking for?
I don't know. Something edible
that I don't have to cook, preferably.
Look, why don't you take the keys
and go to Sainsbury's?
It'll give you something to do
when we're gone.
Hi! You ready?
[Tessa] Yep.
-[sighs]
-Are you sure you're not jet-lagged?
-I feel fine.
-You don't have to go, you know.
Hardin.
Come on, Tessa. Let's do this.
["It Takes Two" by Fiji Blue playing]
[door closes]
♪ What if I wake up happy? ♪
♪ And what if I wake up sad? ♪
♪ Sorry if I said something
Something that made you mad ♪
♪ Wishing that I could call you
Sorry my service bad ♪
♪ My bad ♪
♪ When I wake up, you're not next to me
Guess I'm missing all your energy… ♪
[shouting]
I really shouldn't.
I'm sorry, guys. Have one for me.
-[jeering]
-[man] Man! Oh, man!
♪ …is you ♪
♪ It takes two ♪
♪ 'Cause all I want is you, is you ♪
♪ It takes two… ♪
You really look amazing.
It's beginning to feel real. [chuckles]
[sighs]
What's her dress like?
Mmm. I can't tell you.
-You're seriously not gonna tell me?
-I can't-- I can't tell you.
You're gonna have to wait and see.
-[sighs] Don't care that much anyway.
-[laughs]
-Please tell me.
-[both laugh]
I'm not gonna tell you.
I'm so glad you came.
You're my better place, Tess.
[exhales]
[clattering]
[man and woman grunting, moaning]
[grunting, moaning]
What the fuck?
-Oh!
-[clears throat]
Vance? Fucking hell!
[Trish] Look, uh, it's not what you think.
Are fucking kidding me?
Well, it clearly fucking is.
You're getting married tomorrow.
What the fuck is wrong with you?
And the love of your life, Kimberly,
is carrying your fucking child
while you're here.
-Enough, Hardin.
-[Hardin] What the fuck is wrong with you?
[panting]
-Vance.
-[Vance] Yeah.
-He's been fucking my mom.
-Please, Hardin, just stop it!
Don't fucking yell at me!
You don't get tell me what to do.
You were getting fucked
on the counter like a slag.
-Don't you talk to your mom like that!
-Oh, fuck off!
Who the fuck are you
to tell me what to do, huh?
-You really wanna know?
-No, Christian, don't--
-[Hardin] Come here!
-Enough!
-Stop, stop!
-[Vance] Stop it!
[grunts]
-[Trish] Please, Hardin!
-[grunting]
-Hardin, that's enough! That's enough!
-[Hardin screams]
-[sobbing] Enough! That's enough.
-[Vance groans]
[Hardin] You're getting married tomorrow!
Did you forget?
-[Vance exhales]
-[Trish sniffles]
Who the fuck does that?
What you gonna tell Mike?
Hardin. Christian and I…
-He's--
-What?
[sobs] It's not that simple.
[continues sobbing]
[mutters, exhales]
-[Tessa] Okay, let's go. Let's go.
-[sighs] Tessa, don't.
[gasps]
[Trish exhales]
[Vance panting] You all right?
[crying]
[mutters]
-It's okay.
-[continues muttering]
It's okay.
[sobbing] It's not okay.
It's not okay.
[indistinct]
-Please don't ever let me go.
-I won't. I'll never let you go.
[Hardin continues sobbing]
…and even though you're a superhero
in my eyes, you are still human.
Mike Richards…
do you take Trish Powell,
for better or worse?
I do.
I really do.
[minister] I'm happy to pronounce you
husband and wife.
-Hardin--
-I have nothing to say to you.
-Come on--
-Get the fuck off me.
Do you wanna go again, old man?
If that's what it takes, yeah.
There's a bar in the hotel.
A fucking bar?
It's just down the street.
I'll wait there for you.
I can come if you want me to.
-But either way, I think you should go.
-[shudders]
She looks like she doesn't need telling.
Yeah, she definitely knows.
I'm gonna go sit with her, but if
anything goes wrong, just come find me.
[sighs]
-Surprised to see you here.
-[chuckles] Yeah.
I'm afraid I won't be able
to stay as angry as I am.
Trust me, I am.
[clicks tongue] But what do I do?
I love him.
And I love the life we're building,
and I love Smith.
You wanted to talk. Let's talk.
I know you feel betrayed.
-[scoffs]
-I wanna explain myself.
But I honestly don't know where to begin.
-I guess that makes us done, then.
-Look, lis-- listen.
You are so important to me and your mom.
Are you serious?
Now you two wanna play some
sort of united front? Fuck off with that.
You wouldn't be so angry
if you didn't care.
You know,
I wish I could say I'm surprised.
But I'm not.
They have a history together. [exhales]
One that I'm not sure I can compete with.
I was gonna tell you ages ago,
but your mom didn't want…
[exhales]
Tell me what.
["Never Say Never" by the Fray playing]
[Vance sighs]
[gasps]
♪ Some things we don't talk about… ♪
Hardin is Christian's son.
Fuck!
-Oh, fuck. Fuck off!
-I'm so sorry.
♪ While we don't know when ♪
♪ But time and time and time again ♪
♪ Younger now than we were before… ♪
[Tessa sighs]
I'm sorry.
I have to go.
♪ Don't let me go, don't let me… ♪
[bell rings]
♪ Don't let me go ♪
♪ We're falling apart ♪
♪ And coming together again and again ♪
♪ We're growing apart
But we pull it together ♪
♪ Pull it together ♪
♪ Together again ♪
[vocalizing]
♪ Oh! ♪
♪ Don't let me go, don't let me go ♪
♪ Don't let me go ♪
["After Our Dawn"
by Taylor Conrod playing]
♪ I'm tethered to your cannonball heart ♪
♪ Your wind, your rain
And all your flaws ♪
♪ I'm tethered to your moon and her tide ♪
♪ The push, the pull
And all of your lies ♪
♪ Dark and light, I'll save your life ♪
♪ Just stay the night
And we'll be all right ♪
♪ As distant as the stars ♪
♪ Together through our chains
Of broken hearts ♪
♪ And you're holding on to me ♪
♪ Like a comet falling from the sky ♪
♪ Till after our dawn ♪
♪ I'm falling right back to the start ♪
♪ The spark of your touch
When I'm in your arms ♪
♪ There's something
In the way that you smile ♪
♪ The warmth in your eyes
Like a blanket of fire ♪
♪ Dark and light, I'll savе your life ♪
♪ So stay the night
We'll be all right ♪
♪ As distant as the stars ♪
♪ Together through our chains
Of broken hearts ♪
♪ And you're holding on to me ♪
♪ Like a comet falling through the sky ♪
♪ Till after our dawn ♪
♪ Till after our dawn ♪
♪ Till our dawn, till our dawn ♪
♪ Till our dawn ♪
♪ Breathe, we're falling deep ♪