ZOMBIE APOCALYPSE IN KOREA
Hello.
This is Orangibberish,
who gets to the truth behind rumors.
Today, I'll be uncovering the truth
behind the Hyosan zombie rumor.
I'm on my way to see
if it really turned into Zombieland
as they say online and on social media.
-FINALLY
-HE'S REALLY GOING
Damn. It's insane here already.
Look.
-WHAT'S WITH THE TRAFFIC?
-WHY ARE YOU GOING TO HYOSAN, SON?
Do you see this?
It's bumper to bumper
with cars trying to get into Hyosan.
There are so many cars.
Hold on.
I'll have to get out and hike my way in.
I came up the mountain
to avoid the roadblock.
See that down there?
That there is Hyosan.
Okay. Let me show you the equipment
that I've brought.
First. A helmet.
A hockey mask. Knee and elbow pads.
These are shin guards.
This is emergency food.
First aid kit. And water.
And most important of all, an axe.
If something grabs me,
I'll chop their necks, and…
I'm all set.
Please subscribe and like, okay?
-MY MOM TOLD ME TO STAY HOME
-LOOK AT YOU ALL GEARED UP
Hold on.
-RUN FASTER!
-IS THAT REALLY A ZOMBIE?
I'm fucked.
Damn it. These crazy assholes.
-RUN, BROTHER!
-DAMN
-IT SHOULD BE OVER SOON
-THIS FOOTAGE WILL HELP US
-LOOK AT THAT ACTING
-THIS IS FUN
Are they gone? You saw that, right?
-TAKE OUT YOUR AXE!
-WATCH OUT BEHIND YOU
Fuck. These bastards are so fast.
-SHOW US THE STREET
-COME BACK
-I DON'T THINK I CAN SLEEP TONIGHT
-GOODBYE
You saw that, right? Fuck.
Tell me you saw it, assholes.
-SO DAMN SCARY
-JUST RUN AWAY
-IT'S SCARY
-WHERE ARE THE REAL ZOMBIES?
-ZOMBIELAND! AWESOME!
-IS THAT A REAL ZOMBIE?
-YOU SHOULD'VE TAKEN A GUN
-ZOMBIE!
Are you okay?
Your hand.
You're not okay.
Gyeong-su?
Gyeong-su. It's you, isn't it?
It's me.
Cheong-san's mom.
Gyeong-su. Where's Cheong-san?
I'm sorry to say this…
but be strong.
Don't comfort me.
You're not good at it.
No, I am.
Still, don't.
I didn't know…
I-sak was such a precious friend.
Thinking that she's gone
made me feel
like I had lost my whole world.
Gyeong-su…
must be out there somewhere.
Yes.
Gyeong-su!
Gyeong-su. I'm Cheong-san's mom.
Gyeong-su.
Cheong-san…
I wonder if things are okay outside.
Your dad's a firefighter,
so I'm sure he's fine.
My mom and dad
should be at the restaurant.
That's the most important thing
for my mom.
She might be serving chicken
to zombies right now.
I wish I could have her chicken right now.
-You said it was salty.
-But it still tasted good.
Let's have some
once this is all over
and we get out of here.
I didn't hear anything.
I couldn't hear anything.
-Like what?
-After Na-yeon went out…
and Ms. Park went out after her.
Ms. Park!
I didn't hear anything after that.
You mean, screaming?
Yes.
Maybe they didn't die, then.
They wouldn't have been quiet
if zombies were biting them.
They must be alive.
Why won't you respond?
No one's responding.
I'm always talking to myself.
-I think you're right.
-Forget it.
I didn't hear anything either.
Me neither.
I was scared because I didn't know
how I'd feel if I heard them screaming,
but I didn't hear anything.
Come to think of it, neither did I.
Then I'm right. They're alive, right?
Should she be?
What do you mean?
She's a murderer.
She killed Gyeong-su
and walked out on her own.
Is it right for her to be alive?
Aren't you all being pretentious?
What about Ms. Park?
Should she have died too?
Is that our fault?
Regardless, it happened because of us.
What?
What did we do?
Na-yeon killed someone
and played the victim
and left on her own.
Because we didn't listen to her?
If no one's on your side,
is it okay to kill?
Ms. Park talked
as if we were in the wrong.
We didn't tell Na-yeon to go out there.
We didn't tell Ms. Park
to go out there either.
Why should we feel bad?
Fuck. What the hell did we do wrong?
Hey.
I'm not sure if I should say this--
Then don't say it.
Doesn't anyone else
need to go to the bathroom?
Is it just me?
Me too.
We have to go, too,
but we can't go out.
See?
I told you no one would come.
No one cares about this school.
If they did,
they would've saved us sooner.
Would've saved us from being bullied.
I wish the school would burn down.
So that nothing remains.
They'll come and save us.
They have to.
Otherwise…
I don't know.
I hope a fire really does break out…
and kills everyone.
Right?
You want to die too, right?
No.
I know you actually want to live.
I know that you're…
dying to live.
Why are you blaming me?
Su-hyeok is the one who brought it up.
It's not a crime to need to poop.
It's not a crime, but…
But what? Don't you need to go?
Yes, I do.
-But I don't need to poop.
-Cheong-san, what about you?
I don't need to poop either.
Don't you need to go?
Why are you asking me?
Why are you snapping at me?
What are we supposed to do?
We can't go out anyway.
I have a good idea.
First,
boys and girls will take turns.
Where?
Here.
He's lost his mind.
-Cut it out.
-Why?
Girls can wait in there,
and the guys can pee out the window.
What about poop?
Poop. Well,
you can pull down your pants
and hang out the window.
Like this.
See? Outside.
Like you're taking a dump
at the edge of a cliff.
What reaction is he hoping for?
Stop being ridiculous.
But someone has to hold you or you'd fall.
How will you wipe?
-We can wipe each other.
-What is he saying?
What a nutjob.
Let's just hold it in.
If the rescuers come--
It'll take a while for them to come.
It may be the same outside of the school.
I don't know how long we'll be here,
but my dad said
you have to separate the bathroom from
where you sleep if you're ever isolated.
Where can we make a bathroom and how?
Over there.
Yes, sir.
They're sending a chopper.
We have to get to the roof
by 11:00 a.m. tomorrow.
Wait.
Go up to the roof?
When the infected are everywhere?
Also,
tomorrow at 11:00 a.m.?
Not 11:00 p.m. tonight?
Yes, tomorrow.
We'll have to spend the night here.
How can she sleep here? Radio in again.
We'll have to stay here tonight,
so we'll create a temporary bathroom.
-U-sin.
-Yes, sir.
Prez and you guys,
look for something to cover the window.
Okay.
Cheong-san and Joon-yeong,
make something that can absorb urine
and feces to use as a toilet.
Cheong-san.
The rest of you…
A screen?
-A screen?
-To block the view.
MUSIC 3
Come with me.
The bathroom is over there.
Put this in here.
Why don't we put this
on top of the basket?
Oh, okay.
Okay. We'll use this as a toilet
as it will absorb urine and feces.
Put this there too.
Dae-su's butt is big, so let's…
Why don't we tape CDs up there?
-Tape.
-Is there more tape?
Have they made the toilet yet?
What's taking them so long?
That's good.
This should be good enough.
How can we poop on this?
Use the cover for poop
and remove it to pee.
Get out.
-Oh.
-Out.
How do we use that?
-Get out.
-Don't push me!
Get out!
At least there are cops
and soldiers out there.
But in the movies,
cops and soldiers are helpless too.
Still, they always save people in the end.
-Take the toilet paper.
-I need to pee.
Damn it.
Just stay inside.
Does it smell?
-Shit.
-What?
Stop overreacting. It doesn't smell.
Sit somewhere else.
There's nobody out there.
There are no lights on
in the stores and apartments.
They all either fled or died.
What are you saying?
I'm saying no one will come to save us.
Don't be so pessimistic.
Don't you know my mom?
She would've torn the school apart
looking for me, but she isn't here yet.
What do you want to do?
I'm just pointing out the facts.
We all know no one's coming.
Let's discuss what we're going to do.
We have to wait to be rescued.
We shouldn't leave safety
and go somewhere dangerous.
What if no one ever comes?
We haven't waited that long yet.
Then how much longer?
Do you want to wait until we die?
No.
I'm saying let's wait
for as long as we can.
We can't go out right now anyway.
It's probably because it's nighttime.
I'm sure somebody will come
in the morning.
There are a lot of choppers flying around.
Let's wait until morning.
What are you saying?
You'll leave first for a personal matter?
How could a firefighter say that
during a disaster?
I'll accept any punishment later.
I'll resign if that's what they want.
Listen.
You'll leave all these people
and go by yourself?
You'll abandon your sick colleague
and leave a new kid in charge?
Kid? He is not a kid.
He's a firefighter.
Fine. That was a slip of the tongue.
My apologies if I offended you.
But this isn't just about you.
My daughter is at school,
but I can't reach her.
I know she's waiting for me.
I need to go. I'm sorry.
Wait.
I want to tell you something.
His home is right over there.
If he says he needs to go save his mother,
should I let him?
She lives over there.
She has a husband and children.
Would it be right
to let her go if she wants?
Knowing they'll all die if they go out?
I have to go, even if I die.
That's why I'm saying this.
You're a firefighter.
And I'm a politician.
Do you know
when it's the hardest for people like us?
Right now.
Because we have to save the most people,
not the people most precious to us.
Fuck, that's perfect.
I'll get away on that bike.
Fuck!
Damn it. Wash your hands.
Do you know where the juniors are?
I don't know.
They're all zombies. It's not like
they'd stay with their classmates.
Stop that. You're driving me crazy.
It's dark out now, right?
Let's go.
Let's just leave tomorrow.
It's too dark to see anything.
We won't see the zombies coming.
You said we should go at night
so the zombies don't see us.
People can change their minds.
Shut it and stand up.
No, I'm not going.
Damn it.
Forget it, then.
Hey. Grab your bow and follow me.
Shut up. Don't do anything.
That bitch.
Spoken like an athlete.
-What?
-Doing nothing is your specialty.
You do nothing but shoot arrows,
and you go to college and make money.
You have an easy life,
so you sit on your fucking ass and wait.
Who says shooting arrows
gets you into college?
Doesn't it?
Stop making it obvious
you're stupid and stay down.
You know nothing.
You bitch.
Hey.
What did you say?
How did you know I was stupid?
Tell me. Is it on Facebook?
Stop it. Let it go.
Why the hell should she let it go?
Ha-ri, don't hold back.
You bitch.
You little--
Let go of me!
-Come at me.
-Stop it.
-Come at me, bitch.
-That's enough.
-Come at me! Let go!
-Stop it.
-Stop it!
-You bitch!
-Let go!
-Do you want to die?
Cut it out!
-Hey.
-You said not to hold back!
Are you touching my boobs?
-Get lost.
-Move.
Get out of the way!
-Stop it!
-Who do you think--
People.
-ANYONE ALIVE?
-ANYBODY THERE?
This is pure hell.
The cops won't pick up.
-IT'S SCARY
-LOOK AT THE VIEWS
And there are no first responders.
Damn it!
-LOOK AT HIS FACE LOL
-YOU REALLY WENT?
I'm going to hide and wait to be rescued.
Please subscribe
and like my channel, orangekay?
Fuck. Don't you think I deserve a like?
-IS THIS REAL?
-I RESPECT YOU, BROTHER
Okay. I'm going to go now.
-IS IT A VIRUS?
-WHERE'S YOUR BADASS AXE?
What the hell?
What asshole threw away garbage here?
-MY CONDOLENCES
-GARBAGE ASSHOLE LOL
-LET'S NOT GO THERE
-SURE THERE'S NO ZOMBIES?
Look, everyone.
-I CAN'T TURN THIS OFF
-DON'T GO FURTHER
It's clean.
I think it's safe.
-MY HEART'S RACING
-I HATE ZOMBIES
I'll go in now.
-IT'LL BE FULL OF ZOMBIES
-IS THIS REALLY SCARY?
-YOU'RE WORKING HARD
-SHOULD'VE BROUGHT A GUN
-WHY'D YOU GO TO HELL?
-STRAIGHT TO HELL
-YOU SHOULD HIDE
-STOP GOING
-BE CAREFUL
-WHAT IF THEY'RE IN THERE?
-IT'S EMPTY, SPEND THE NIGHT
-DON'T MAKE A SOUND!
It looks like there's no one here.
-I'M SCARED…
-SAFETY FIRST!
-IT'S TOO DARK…
-IT'S NOT TOO LATE TO RUN…
Hold on.
What is that?
-THANKS FOR EVERYTHING
-BYE BYE
-I HEAR SOMETHING
-WHAT IS IT?
-ALL THIS JUST FOR LIKES
-WE'RE WATCHING SOMETHING DIE
Damn it.
-YOU'RE INSANE
-CUTE ZOMBIES LOL
-RUN! RUN!
-I WANT TO GO THERE TOO
This is bad.
-SO SCARY
-IT'S ALL FAKE ANYWAY LOL
-IS THAT REAL?
-KEEP STREAMING!
Do you see that? Damn it. Where do I go?
-IS THIS FOR REAL?
-DAMN
Damn it.
Seriously?
Do you know
what's going on out there?
The strong are ripping apart the weak.
It happens all the time.
Are you crazy?
The world is crazy.
Why did you do this?
I tried to tell everyone,
but no one listened.
My son was bullied for a very long time.
I only found out
after he tried to kill himself.
I found out too late,
but I thought I could fix it.
SCHOOL VIOLENCE RESOLUTION COMMITTEE
We were just…
Well, we…
We were only fooling around.
Come on, guys.
We were just messing around.
That's what we do when we hang out, right?
Is that right?
Eun-ji?
Yes.
I'm sure you know this
since you work at the school,
but it's difficult to prove
what happened among kids,
and it's difficult to punish them.
They won't go to prison.
The kids were just fooling around.
How could you go to the police?
The school punished them. That's enough.
Is writing apologies
considered "punishment"?
They're students.
They apologized and promised
not to do it again. Isn't that enough?
We have evaluations coming up.
Why make an issue of it
and blow it out of proportion?
You're right.
You were kicked out
of a pharmaceutical company
and were a contract teacher.
But our principal took you in
as a permanent teacher.
You should think of the school too.
That's how they always were.
We transferred him immediately.
But they kept finding him
and harassing him.
It was fun for them.
Like playing with a toy.
Smile for the camera. Smile.
Look at him.
Dad.
Just fight back instead.
Fight as if your life depended on it!
I'm sorry, Dad.
I just want to die.
I think that would be easier.
That's when I realized it.
We live in a system of violence.
A nobody like me…
can't change the system.
That's why I decided to change my son.
I just hoped he wouldn't die.
I didn't want him
to try and commit suicide again.
Please stop!
You…
created a monster.
That's how desperate I was to save him.
Rather than die as a human,
I wanted him to survive as a monster.
Don't you realize
that monster is killing everyone?
Who cares if they all die?
They're all accomplices.
You crazy bastard.
Who made the world like this?
I warned you countless times
that ignoring minor violence
would result in violence
taking over the world.
But no one listened.
"It happens."
"Kids fight. They were bullied
because they deserved it."
Those who thought that and shunned them
made this world what it is!
No. You're the one who made this hellhole.
As a cop, I'm partly responsible.
Those who are out there dying
without knowing why?
Sure. They may be partly responsible.
But there are things
you must pay with death
and things we must amend
while still alive.
What you wanted was
for the world to change.
Not for everyone to die like this, right?
Day 39 of infection.
I've tested several sedatives.
The most effective…
Where's the cure?
There must be a form of treatment.
There isn't.
Let's go. We've been ordered to evacuate.
What are you looking at, asshole? Get in.
Shove them in.
Yes, sir. Come on.
Move quickly. Go.
Hey. What's wrong?
Help…
What the hell?
This is the closest they are
to following their raw instincts.
This is just one side of human nature.
Perhaps it's best
to accept them for what they are
and give up on trying to cure them.
Mr. Lee!
My laptop is in the school science lab.
Let's go.
The solution is in there.
That's the only way.
Fine, so let's get the laptop! Damn it.
Lee Byeong-chan!
Go! Get out of here!
Hurry!
Fuck. That was close.
What the hell?
Wait!
Help me.
I'm stuck.
Come on.
The standards of being human
emasculate human nature.
How are we different from a seeing eye dog
whose instincts to run
and bark are stripped?
Must all dogs abandon their instincts
and become seeing eye dogs?
Must everyone abandon their instincts
to become truly human?
-Hey.
-Yes, sir.
We're going to
the Disaster and Safety Management.
We have to tell them to get the laptop
from the Hyosan High science lab.
The solution to this disaster is in there.
Understand?
Hyosan High. Science lab. Laptop.
Why are you telling me?
If I die, you have to stay alive
and tell them, you idiot.
Me?
You dumbass.
Let's go.
Where are you going?
The Disaster and Safety Management.
I told you two seconds ago.
Get with the program.
-Where?
-Disaster and Safety Management.
-And tell them what?
-Hyosan High, science lab, laptop.
-That's right.
-Okay.
-Are you ready?
-No.
Let's go.
Follow me.
It's cold.
No one came.
This is driving me crazy.
No cops and no cigarettes.
Nothing.
Really? Nobody came?
Let me down.
-My back.
-Damn.
Hey. What do you want to do?
We need to leave.
No one's coming to save us.
All the zombies will see us right now.
Let's go at night.
Okay. You can stay right here.
Let's go out back
and leave through the back gate.
That's the fastest route.
-I'm going to the second floor first.
-Why?
My brother's a junior.
I need to check if he's there.
Hey. Would a zombie sit
and wait at his desk in his classroom?
Did you see him turn?
He may have.
There's no guarantee that he didn't.
You little…
Why are you guys arguing?
Just fight some more.
Sorry.
Come with me if you want.
She's so cool. Damn it.
So annoying.
Wait for me.
They'll come for us eventually.
How long do we wait?
Until they come.
We don't even know if they're coming.
So? You want to go out there?
But even if they come, they can't find us
if they don't know we're here.
-We can put up a signal for help.
-How?
My dad taught me a signal
that's used internationally.
What is it?
It's Cheong-san. See you later.
Eat another bite.
Hey!
It was red and blue arranged together
to create some sort of a pattern.
Should we just write "SOS"
on the curtains?
Yes, let's do that.
We can't last long anyway.
Three minutes of no oxygen,
three days of no water,
three weeks of no food.
What's that?
How long a person can survive.
It's only been a day.
We have to try the best we can.
We'll show signs of dehydration
after today.
-We won't be able to move by tomorrow.
-What are you getting at?
Are you saying we should go?
Or are you saying we'll die anyway,
so we shouldn't bother doing anything?
I don't know.
Then don't say anything.
I think Prez means
we should think about all of our options.
Right?
-No.
-No?
I mean, we know nothing.
We need to know more
to think and make plans--
What do you mean?
What she means--
You don't know what she's saying either.
Right.
Are you saying we need to grasp
the situation before taking action?
Yes, something like that.
I agree.
We need to know more to decide
whether to wait, run, or go out.
How can we do that right now?
We can go online if we have a phone.
But we don't have one.
In the teachers' office.
Why are you telling me that now?
Sorry.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
What can I do about it now?
What time is it?
It's 9:00 a.m.
Hyosan High. Mo Eun-ji.
Nude. Kim Cheol-su.
SCHEDULE SETTINGS
Schedule post…
PROCESSING
…for 9:00 a.m. tomorrow.
Bring the money by 9:00 a.m.
If you don't,
it'll be uploaded automatically.
I just had to give him the money.
But I couldn't because of the zombies.
I was going to ask the rescuers
to find his phone if they came, but…
It's past 9:00 a.m., right?
How would I know? I don't have my phone.
No.
It can't be 9:00 a.m. yet.
If that gets posted online, I'll…
What's wrong? Where are you going?
-Let go. I should've died yesterday.
-Don't say that.
Please stop it!
Whether or not you die,
the video will be posted.
What will it change?
You're right.
Even if I die, everyone will see my body.
Everyone will watch,
and my mom…
It'll be okay.
We did nothing wrong.
We were victims.
I'm going.
Where?
-To get his phone.
-Are you insane?
Will you come with me?
-You filmed me.
-But…
I had no choice. They made me do it.
It's the same as committing murder
because you had no choice.
Still,
we'll die if we go.
That's so you.
You don't have
the courage to live or to die.
You're a fucking coward, asshole.
Cheong-san.
Stop being so stubborn.
The teachers' office is two rooms across
and one floor down.
Don't go.
I'll come back
if I can't make it all the way.
-Don't worry.
-I'm not worried about you.
I'm angry.
Sure. Why would you worry about me?
Damn it.
Su-hyeok.
I'll be back.
Careful, Cheong-san.
Bare-su is a man of loyalty.
-You too?
-I'm going too.
-Stop it. Come down.
-Why?
You can't go out there
with that body, fatso.
What's wrong with my body?
What do you think?
Why do you keep following me?
Who else do you have?
Stay close.
Careful.
Can we go in?
Come back.
What are you going to do?
Let's hang by our hands and go.
No, I mean…
I heard that On-jo told you she likes you.
-Are you going to go out with her?
-Is that important right now?
I'm not asking because it's important.
I'm just curious.
Why?
-Should I go out with her?
-Hey.
Why are you asking me?
Do as you wish.
What do you think?
Go.
You go.
Be careful.
Why are you doing this to me?
What is it?
What is that?
I don't know. Let's go see.
I'll destroy them all.
All of them.
What the hell?
GWI-NAM
UPLOAD
That bastard.
I'll kill you!
Give it to me, fucker! I'll kill you!
Cheong-san.
Damn it.
Go first. I'll catch up.
Hey.
Wake up.
You're Yoon Gwi-nam, right?
What? Why?
How is it outside? The same?
I don't know.
You know how to drive, right?
-No.
-Yeah, right.
You guys drove your dad's car
and crashed it last year.
Do you know what a headache
that was for me?
But why do you ask?
My car is in the parking lot.
The plate number is 7340.
Bring it here.
Me?
Go through the window
of the night duty room to the lot.
I don't want to.
You punk. Listen to your principal!
I said I don't want to.
-Give me that.
-Let go. You punk.
Fuck! I said to let go.
Damn it.
Fine. Just go.
Come with me.
Why should I? Go.
Come with me to the car.
I wanted a shield anyway.
What's wrong with you? Stay away.
God.
Look, Mr. Principal.
If this were a game,
I'd be… taking down the final boss,
sir.
Is that okay?
Yes.
Okay. We'll go to the rooftop now.
Please work together as we practiced.
Hurry!
-How much longer?
-A little more.
Hold on!
-I'll do it. Block them with the desk.
-Yes, sir!
-Come with me.
-Okay!
Okay, come one by one.
Ma'am, go first.
-You go first.
-You first!
-Anybody! Come!
-Go! Hurry!
Go! Hurry! Go!
Okay. Run here together on my signal.
Three! Two! One!
Now!
Get back!
Charge!
Hurry!
-Back up!
-Yes, sir!
I've got it!
What now?
Hello…
Close the door!
Captain, downstairs!
Captain, here too!
Upstairs…
Go up first.
We can't.
The door to the rooftop is locked.
What?
The door is locked!
-U-sin, do you have the tools?
-Yes, I do.
-Go upstairs.
-What about the door?
Hurry!
Go up now!
Hurry.
-Get out of the way.
-Step aside.
Help him!
A little more!
-Okay. One more time.
-Okay. One, two, three.
-Hurry, ma'am.
-After you, ma'am.
All right, let's go.
Damn it.
Hurry up!
What happened?
Careful. Hold on.
You all did great.
Is anyone hurt?
-Sir.
-What are you doing? Grab this psycho!
Hey, Gwi-nam.
Cheong-san.
Come here and tie his arms.
He won't stay still.
Hey. What are you doing?
Come and tie him up.
You're finished.
You're expelled! Untie me!
Gwi-nam!
Don't do that.
Don't do what? This principal bastard
tried to kill me.
He told me to go out and get his car.
Is that okay?
-Hey.
-That's it. Good job.
I'm filming everything.
Let him go
or I'll send this to the police.
I'm going to kill you.
Please stop acting like human trash.
No one respects you
just because you act tough.
I'm the head boss of this school now.
Don't you get it?
My ass, you are.
You're just a loser scumbag
who'll spend his entire life
serving bullies.
Say that again.
You fucking…
Am I still a loser?
Am I?
Everyone who doesn't listen to me dies.
Give me the phone.
-You just killed--
-Give me the phone!
Damn it!
ALL CHARACTERS, ORGANIZATIONS,
INSTITUTIONS, LOCATIONS,
AND EVENTS IN THIS SHOW ARE FICTIONAL.
Subtitle translation by: Jeong Lee