Stay away from us.
Stay away!
Shit. We won't go to heaven now.
We're alive, so this is heaven.
JUNG YONG-HYEON
In some countries, they are sadder
when adults die than when children die.
And in others,
they are sadder when children die.
Which do you think our country is?
What do you mean?
When kids die, you lose hope.
When adults die, you lose their wisdom.
Hope and wisdom.
Which do we value more?
What?
They've been flying around
since yesterday.
If they wanted to save us,
they would have.
But even if they do come,
we won't be the first to be rescued.
We're not that important.
We're just students. Nothing more.
This is Chopper One.
Seven survivors confirmed
at Hyosan City Council.
RESCUE HEADQUARTERS
We have everyone.
We're heading to the quarantine camp now.
Around 11:00 a.m.,
the government announced
they've declared martial law
in order to control
the Hyosan Disturbance.
Since yesterday afternoon,
a strange infection began to spread,
leading to an evacuation order
and a lockdown of the city.
It's the first time in 41 years
that martial law has been declared,
since the Democratization Movement
on May 18, 1980.
I repeat. They have declared martial law
in order to control
the Hyosan Disturbance.
The sense of crisis
caused by the Hyosan acute epidemic
has caused the stock market to crash.
A sidecar that was activated
for both the KOSPI and KOSDAQ
due to the crash caused by Covid-19…
We don't want refugees from Hyosan!
-We don't want them!
People from Hyosan, return home right now!
We are the Lord's people
who have received salvation.
People will die as people,
and demons will die as demons
in these end times.
-Amen!
Stay away!
-Everyone will die!
What's this?
-Wait.
-Everyone here will die!
-Why won't you let us in?
-Damn it.
-We refuse them!
Don't come here! Why are you coming here?
-Please help us!
-Go back!
Go back!
REMOVE THE GOVERNMENT!
Our Lord Jesus Christ
will not ask whether you are his son
or the son of the Devil.
He will not.
EVERYONE WILL DIE!
Those who do not act righteously
and those who do not love
their brothers and sisters…
REMOVE THE GOVERNMENT!
…are not people of God.
-Amen!
We'll break a million views in no time.
With a false rumor that
the Hyosan epidemic has spread to Seoul,
the number of people leaving Korea
through Incheon Airport
rose to 228,000 in a day.
Hello. I apologize
to the people and to the viewers
who were scared
because of our zombie performance
on the subway.
I am on my knees begging for forgiveness
for unintentionally causing
a misunderstanding about the crisis…
Is that what you expected? Really?
SUBWAY ZOMBIE PERFORMANCE
APOLOGY VIDEO
We must expand martial law
to control the media.
There are rumors
that radiation from nuclear bombs
in the US military base
created the zombies.
That the heads of the top 30 corporations
fled the country.
Most of the media are spreading fake news
circulating on social media
without verifying it,
exacerbating the chaos.
The government
should not control the media.
The people control the media.
Our citizens have enough power to do that.
We will not expand martial law.
Let's focus on preventing the spread
and rescuing the uninfected.
That should be our focus.
-Su-hyeok.
-Hey, Bare-su.
Are you okay?
-Where's the phone?
-Where's Cheong-san?
Su-hyeok.
Where's Cheong-san?
We got separated in the teachers' office.
He'll be fine.
You got separated? Fuck.
I'm sorry… for coming back alone.
Come here.
Were you bit? You were bit, right?
No, I--
Stop it.
Give me the phone.
You killed a person, you murderer.
You made me kill him.
-You said to prove I wasn't a loser.
-You crazy bastard.
Let go!
Do you want to live?
Do you?
Beg for your life.
Screw you.
Fuck!
Help me, fuck!
Cheong-san!
Fuck!
Please!
Cheong-san!
I'll kill you.
I will kill you.
I'll…
I'll kill you.
Shit.
There's not a single normal one.
They're all zombies.
Hey! In front of you!
Fuck. Shoot it already!
We're going to die
before we find your brother.
Let's go, Ha-ri.
Seriously--
Damn it.
I told you we should have stayed put.
It's crazy to think
we can find her brother.
And just as crazy to have followed her.
-I told you--
-Ha-ri!
-What?
-There's a computer.
Turn it on.
Post on Instagram or Facebook for help.
Shit.
Martial Law Command has acted swiftly
and thoroughly sealed off Hyosan
to prevent the situation
from spreading to other areas.
If you live outside
of the area under martial law,
please go on with your lives.
Martial Law Command is doing its best
to confirm and quarantine those infected
and to rescue and protect
those who are not infected.
EMERGENCY CALL
Every operation is being performed
in strict compliance with the laws
and principles in place.
EMERGENCY CALL
CONNECTING
Fake news about the Hyosan epidemic
is spreading uncontrollably.
Martial Law Command will block
all unconfirmed rumors,
and at the same time,
in the interest of improving
the efficiency of operations,
from this moment on,
all communication from Hyosan,
including all cell phone services,
landline services, and Internet services
in Hyosan will be terminated
from this moment on.
-The cable's connected. Why won't it work?
-I keep refreshing, but…
-Try the phone.
-Okay.
Fuck. Assholes.
They cut off our phones and Internet.
We at Martial Law Command
are doing our best
to suppress the spread.
Moreover, we are focusing
all of our resources
on rescuing the people who are trapped.
If you live in Hyosan
and are watching this now,
please have hope and wait to be rescued.
NO SIGNAL
OCTOBER 21, THURSDAY
WATER FLOW DETECTOR
What do we do?
On-jo and Cheong-san are really close.
They're going out.
On-jo says they're not.
I'm telling you they are.
They're always together.
Really?
NAM ON-JO
Poor On-jo.
I'm sure Cheong-san is fine.
You know how fast he is.
He never listens to me.
He's never done as I said
ever since we were kids.
I told him not to go, but he insisted.
I'm sorry.
I should've brought him back.
Where do you think…
he is?
I'm sure he's hiding somewhere safe.
Joon-yeong. Didn't you say
your science club made drones?
You want to look for Cheong-san
using a drone?
-Can't we?
-We can, but it's in the science lab.
We can go get it.
How can we get there?
It's full of zombies out there.
That.
You want me to climb up using that?
The science lab
is filled with zombies too.
There weren't any
in the supply room. Right?
That's true, but…
We have to find Cheong-san.
Right now, we only have
each other.
Yes. It would be good if we had a drone.
We can find Cheong-san
and see how things are outside.
We may even be able
to send a message asking for help.
That's all good, but
who will go?
I'll go.
I've had fire department training,
and I've climbed ropes before.
No, I'll go.
You went to the teachers' office already.
You can't keep putting yourself in danger.
The drone wasn't completed,
so we need a few more parts.
Do you know what to get?
I have to go anyway.
I'll go with On-jo.
No.
I'll really go this time.
You can't go.
Not with that body.
The rope will snap.
It was fine when I came down.
But it'll snap if I climb up, right?
-Right.
-It'll snap.
Right. Good boy.
Joon-yeong, let's go together.
It's too dangerous.
I'll go.
Thanks.
But I don't want you
to be in danger either.
I'm going.
Be careful, On-jo.
Come back safely.
I'll be watching from here.
Do you think
everything's all right out there?
I'm sure it is.
As you said,
the soldiers and the police are there.
I want to go to my dad's factory
and my mom's sundae restaurant.
Whatever.
You hate the smell of leather and sundae.
I just do.
I suddenly want my mom's sundae soup.
Did you finally grow up?
You should've been like that sooner.
It's too late.
Hey, look.
I bet there's a key in there, right?
I don't think so.
Wouldn't it be better to hide
somewhere safe and wait to be rescued?
Hey.
He said the solution is in his laptop.
We need to hurry and notify
Disaster and Safety Management.
The people with important information
need to survive.
So doesn't our survival come first?
Why do you keep acting
like a leader of society?
Did you go to Seoul University
or something?
-Yes.
-What? Why?
You really went there?
No, I haven't graduated yet.
I have to go back.
I see. Grad school?
-No. I'm a sophomore.
-What?
Did you retake your exams?
Four times? Five?
I see. Six times.
I went straight after high school.
My goodness. You must've studied hard.
Your face says it all.
Hey. You're smart,
so I'll only say this once.
Be quiet and follow me.
Wait.
Damn it!
Shut the door!
Damn it.
Why won't it start?
Hurry!
Please help me!
-This way!
-Stay away!
Get him off me!
-Come here!
-Yes, sir.
Hurry!
GOOD LUCK WITH YOUR NEW BUSINESS
Shit! Oh my God!
It's a zombie, sir.
There's a zombie inside.
-There's one inside?
-Yes.
Damn it.
CHEONGSAN CHICKEN
It's okay. Come in.
Damn it.
Really?
It's okay. She's tied up.
A student should be in school.
Why is she in a chicken place…
Why is she tied--
Oh my God!
What? What is it this time?
Look. Over there.
What? What is that?
Shit.
Is it okay?
Is the baby a zombie?
No. It's alive.
Check the fridge
for some milk or something.
Why? Are you thirsty?
For the baby.
We need to feed the baby.
It looks exhausted.
What if there's no milk?
Just check the fridge first.
We can think about what to do
if there isn't any.
Oh. You're right.
-If there's no milk, what should I bring?
-Just check first.
Before I beat you up.
What do we do now?
What else? We have to go to headquarters.
What about the baby?
It's hard enough with just us.
Are you going to take it?
Careful.
-The drone and the bag are there.
-Okay.
Hang on. Where was it?
Where is the battery?
Have you thought about that?
About what?
What if everyone turned
and we're the only humans left?
No way.
What if that were true?
Come on.
That means we're the minority.
Minorities always go extinct.
I'm sure we're not.
But what if we are?
Can you endure this?
I don't know.
But I don't want to become a zombie.
They don't recognize anyone.
Then…
I won't recognize you either.
I have a favor if I do get bit.
No.
Don't get bit.
-If by chance--
-No.
Don't get bit. You can't.
Don't even think about it.
THIS DOOR DOES NOT OPEN FROM THE INSIDE
Damn it.
-Eat up, I-sak.
-Thank you.
On-jo. Which do you like better?
-They both taste good.
-They do?
Is this better
or is this better?
Why?
Fuck this.
MUSIC ROOM
INSTRUMENT STORAGE
Be careful, On-jo.
Take your time.
Hurry up. Hurry.
HELP, WE'RE IN THE BROADCASTING ROOM
IN HYOSAN HIGH SCHOOL
Does it work?
Is it working?
I think it will.
You scared me! That's mad fast.
I'll take it outside
after I find Cheong-san.
If I find rescuers outside,
I'll land it in front of them.
Wait.
They say when people confirm
their situation is hopeless,
they truly fall into despair.
That's a cool saying.
But what does that mean?
Even if the entire world
has turned into zombies,
let's not despair.
I see. So that's what it means?
Prez.
It's best to have a plan
and act accordingly,
but we're not top students
or as smart as you.
Being logical
isn't necessarily being human.
We should be logical in crisis situations.
Right now,
we need hope more than logic.
Hey. I think
flying that is
what we need most right now.
-Try it.
-Here I go.
Okay.
Oh no.
Everyone's turned.
I wouldn't have studied
if I knew this was going to happen.
I can't take the CSAT anyway.
Fuck. I'm never studying again.
Can you please be serious
in serious situations?
I'm very serious right now.
What will you do?
Will you keep looking for your brother?
The archery training center
has an emergency phone.
It connects to 911 automatically.
-Really?
-Yes.
We got it installed
in case there were accidents.
What if it doesn't connect?
The phone and Internet are dead.
It doesn't matter.
That's where all the arrows are anyway.
I have less than 20 left. We need more
if we want to leave the school.
-I think--
-Okay, let's go.
Let's go to your training center
and get your arrows.
Then let's go home or to a supermarket.
You know, in zombie movies,
the ones that go to supermarkets
always live the best.
They have cigarettes too.
I think--
The dumpsters are below these windows.
I think we should jump down
rather than use the stairs.
Okay. Let's jump.
Falling from the third floor won't hurt
as much as failing to get into college.
Let me get a word in!
Min-jae. Go down first
and shoot any that come running.
Okay.
Then you two go down and help him.
I'll cover you in the hallway and go last.
-What did you want to say?
-Let's just stay here.
The adults will come to rescue us.
You can stay if you want.
But I don't trust adults.
Damn. That bitch is so my type.
I'm too scared to be alone.
Hurry up.
Look out! Behind you!
Move.
Damn.
Why is this so high? Fuck!
Jump already.
Damn. Okay, I'm going.
Whoa. Fuck!
There's no one in the infirmary.
Joon-yeong, go somewhere else.
Wait. Hold on.
Isn't that an arrow?
-Where?
-This.
You're right. It is an arrow.
Why?
My sister.
She had a competition today.
Where the hell is Cheong-san?
It's Cheong-san!
-What room is that?
-Cheong-san!
He can't hear you.
Be quiet.
-Hey, Cheong-san!
-I said he can't hear you.
On-jo, it's all right now.
Cheong-san's alive!
He's alive!
What's he doing? Where's he going?
Look this way! Over here!
Where are you going, moron?
He can't hear you!
Be quiet, will you? You're so damn loud.
You could get us killed.
My bad.
Didn't you say the battery was low?
Yes. I couldn't fully charge it,
so there isn't much juice left.
Since we confirmed where Cheong-san is,
let's look elsewhere.
We wanted to check outside
and ask for help too.
On-jo, is that okay?
Yes, since we saw that he's alive.
Here we go.
Damn.
Fuck. It's Zombieland out there.
I think we should look
outside of the school.
Let's go outside.
Okay.
Wait.
What is it?
What's wrong, Ji-min?
Wait.
I can't…
What is it?
This…
this is my dad's car.
Which one?
The white one? The black one?
This truck.
It's my dad's.
Don't worry.
I'm sure there are lots of cars like that.
Let me check.
Ji-min.
11:47 AM
ABANDONED PRISON IN THE SUBURB OF HYOSAN
This announcement is for the citizens
of Hyosan who are in quarantine.
Please abide by the quarantine rules
and keep order…
-Don't you see us in line?
-…under the control of the military.
What about us?
Please cooperate with the tests
to determine if you are infected…
Who are they to get special treatment?
…and follow the rules
of living in this facility.
I repeat.
Please abide by the quarantine rules
and keep order
under the control of the military.
Please cooperate with the tests
to determine if you are infected
and follow the rules
of living in this facility.
EXAMINATION ROOM
Thank you for your service.
Where's the control room?
As per martial law,
you will be quarantined
until you are examined.
Why must she quarantine?
She just returned from a battlefield.
It's okay. That's enough.
Where is the control room?
You will be examined first.
I'm not refusing to be examined.
Please follow the rules.
I'm Capt. Nam So-ju
of Rescue Team One at Hyosan Fire Station.
I was responsible for their rescue--
Hey!
Does it sound like I'm asking?
-Take them to the examination room.
-Yes, sir.
What is this place?
This isn't an examination room.
There are too many awaiting examination,
so you must wait.
Then you should've explained
the situation and asked her to wait
and then escorted her.
What is wrong with you?
Others are sitting on mats
on a concrete floor.
We're offering the best we can
since you are an assembly member.
The wait time
for an examination is 12 to 72 hours.
Wait.
My daughter is at her school.
It may be too late if we delay any longer.
Please rescue them.
We're doing the best we can.
Wait here.
Fuck.
Did I die?
Am I fucking dead?
Hey.
Aren't you going to eat me,
you zombie bastards?
I gave them serotonin injections
for a week, but it had no effect.
The Jonas Virus evolves
as soon as it detects antibodies
so the antibodies lose their target.
The only explanation is
that the virus learns and evolves.
If this virus
manages to learn the human mind…
a new breed of human may be born.
Cheong-san, you son of a bitch.
I'll kill you.
What the hell?
This means…
ONE HEART
…I'm in heaven.
Hey, Cheong-san!
ALL CHARACTERS, ORGANIZATIONS,
LOCATIONS, INSTITUTIONS,
AND EVENTS IN THIS SHOW ARE FICTIONAL.
Subtitle translation by: Jeong Lee