Mom.
Cheong-san!
Damn it.
What the hell?
Fuck!
There's another zombie here!
Dae-su!
Stop it.
Stop it!
What are you doing?
-Cheong-san!
-What the hell?
You son of a bitch!
Stop it!
Let go!
Get the fuck off of me!
Mom!
Mom…
-Hurry.
-Let's go.
Run!
Come on.
Hurry up!
Let's go.
Let's go, Cheong-san.
Pull yourself together!
Dae-su, the others!
What?
Why aren't they coming?
What now?
Did you see them coming?
Please, Cheong-san.
-Come with us.
-Let's go.
Mom!
-Mom…
-They're here. Hurry up!
-Wu-jin!
-Get up.
Come on. We have to go.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
Shut up. You're so heavy.
Thank you, Mi-jin. Thank you so much.
-Then will you go out with me?
-No.
Screw you.
Hold on.
Why? What is it?
Hear that?
Shit. Fucking zombies.
Let's run.
Let's go.
To the mountain.
Ji-min. Help me.
Hyo-ryeong!
Get up!
Get up.
Ha-ri.
-Wu-jin. Go.
-What are you doing here?
Go.
Go!
-Hey!
-Hyo-ryeong. You go first.
-Come on! Let's go!
-Let's go.
Nam-ra, what's wrong?
Damn it.
Run away.
What the fuck?
Run!
-Run!
-Run! Go!
-Come on!
-Just go!
Just fucking go! You're going to die!
I don't fucking care!
-Over here!
-This way! Hurry!
Come on!
Are you crazy, Mi-jin? Let go!
Shut up!
-No! Joon-seong!
-Ha-ri!
What are you doing?
No! Let go, you assholes!
Fuck off, assholes!
Go! Hurry!
No! Joon-seong!
-Let go!
-Close the door!
Fuck! Let go of me!
Shit.
Damn it.
Hey, Cheong-san…
I'm so sorry.
I didn't know it was your mom.
I'm sorry.
Stop!
Stay away!
Mom…
A virus must have a consistent pattern
for a vaccine to be made.
But the Jonas Virus
transforms and evolves on its own.
It is an ever-changing monster.
A treatment or a vaccine are impossible.
There is only one solution.
Death.
Completely burning and killing the host
so that not a single cell remains.
The moment we are consumed by arrogance
and think we can defeat the virus,
mankind will become extinct.
The amount of data was massive,
so we couldn't analyze it all,
but a significant portion
of it is credible.
How can you prove that?
The KDCA is creating a virus
using the exact method he described.
If they can create the same virus,
they'll conclude it is credible.
My goodness.
I thought only crazy soldiers
were frightening.
It's scarier when a scientist goes crazy.
Did you hear
they're expanding martial law?
What do you mean?
Why? We're handling it well.
I have a friend in the NIS analysis team,
and he said they're discussing
pulling back the blockade to Yangdong
and expanding martial law.
What about Hyosan?
They understand there may be sacrifices.
We may have ceased our rescue operation,
but we never know
when we may rescue survivors again.
Strengthen the blockade
on the outskirts of Hyosan.
The moment the blockade is penetrated…
someone must step forward
and abandon Hyosan.
Take this.
LETTER OF RESIGNATION
I thought you came in person to save me,
but you came to abandon me.
My source in the NIS tells me
something will happen soon in Hyosan.
In your district.
If something bad really does happen,
I'll say you even resigned from your post
in order to prevent it.
You should be able
to avoid responsibility.
Responsibility for what?
Anything.
Trust me and sign it.
I'll protect your political career
until the end.
Do you need time to think it over?
They're not saving Hyosan, are they?
They're abandoning it?
Take your time and think about it.
Sign it within the day
and give it to the person in charge here.
Sir.
-Sir…
-Let's go.
Ma'am! We're getting out now, right?
Since the party leader came,
it'll all be resolved, right?
He says he'll save us, right?
Ma'am?
I thought about it all night.
What do I do?
How do I go on living?
Let's talk a little later.
Tomorrow or the day after.
Or next week.
After we get out of here, eat,
and get ourselves clean.
Let's talk then.
Okay?
We still have a lot to talk about.
So let's do that.
Whatever happens…
don't give up.
Okay?
Okay.
Never.
You too.
Okay.
Me too.
What is it?
Do you see something?
The smell got stronger.
I don't smell anything.
I think they're all coming this way.
The smell is really strong.
We're trapped in here.
There's no way to leave.
Don't say that.
But it's true.
There is no way.
Whatever.
Let them kill us if they want.
Ha-ri.
You didn't get eliminated
in the preliminaries, did you?
No.
I made it.
You had a tournament.
Why did you come to the school?
-Are you her brother?
-Yes. So?
She got a perfect score.
She made it onto the national team.
I saw her.
Really?
Yes, really.
Then you're really on the national team?
Do Mom and Dad know?
How could they? Look at what's going on.
She jumped out of the team bus
and ran here to find you.
Hey, kid.
You better be good to her.
Be good to me too.
Who is she anyway?
Why does she keep speaking for you?
She's my friend.
We're freaking besties.
Jeez, you scared me.
What's your deal?
I…
What?
I like you.
What? Crazy bastard.
Hey.
What's wrong with you?
I saw you shooting arrows.
I saw you train every morning.
I went to every tournament
and cheered for you.
I'm the one who yelled,
"Bronzed beauty Jang Ha-ri."
I've sincerely liked you for years.
Now…
I want to be a man, not just a fan.
I'm going to die anyway.
So I want to say what I want first.
This is awesome.
You're Dae-su, right?
The one who calls my brother
"Brother-In-Law."
Yes.
So you knew.
Brother-In-Law, did you tell her?
I might have.
Does confessing feel cathartic?
Yes.
-Then you're okay with dying, right?
-Yes.
What? Now?
You asshole.
I'm pissed off and needed to vent.
-Wu-jin, stop her.
-Ha-ri.
-You're dead.
-Stop her.
-Come here.
-I'm sorry. I was wrong.
-No. I'm glad you told me.
-Hey. That's not it.
Yes, it is. Get over here.
Why don't you understand?
I really like you.
-Get over here, asshole.
-Wu-jin. Help.
-Sorry.
-Stop her, Wu-jin.
Get over here. You punk.
-Beat him up, Ha-ri.
-Come here.
-He needs a good beating.
-Look at him dodging.
Look at him.
What's that?
That's not it!
Hey.
Come here. You're going to keep dodging?
-Hey, stop it. Stop her.
-I don't want to come between you two.
-Come here.
-Only if you promise not to hit me.
Where did those fuckers go?
What are you doing?
Don't you think
we can get out using these?
We can tie the carts together
in a circle and go inside to escape.
We need string or something
to tie them together in a circle.
I think it's this one.
Cut as many as possible.
Hey. It won't work like this.
We should flip it completely
and hide underneath.
No. We should stand it up.
You think the zombies can't climb this?
This is enough.
Don't be stupid.
Untie them all. Let's redo them.
It's too short if we close the lids.
What? You want to crawl?
Must she pull rank right now?
Hey.
What did you just say?
If you don't like it, make your own.
Hey.
Hey. What's wrong with you?
Stop that.
-Ha-ri. Stop her.
-Say that again.
So what if you're older.
Stay out of our way.
Hey.
Fuck you.
"Fuck you"? Get out of my way.
Cut it out.
You too, Joon-yeong.
Who the hell is she to tell us to redo it?
"Who the hell is she"? You rude prick.
-You're coming with us, right?
-You're the ones coming with us.
We're not leaving the seniors, right?
Of course not.
We're going to go together anyway.
Why are you fighting already?
So do as I say unless you want to die.
We want to make it high
so that we don't die.
Enough already.
How many died on our way here?
We can't lose anyone else.
We shouldn't fight among ourselves.
I'm not fighting to die.
It's because I want to live.
Then do as I say, asshole.
Then let's go separately.
Make it yourself.
-That fucker. Get back here.
-Joon-yeong.
Get back here!
Let go of me, fuck!
Am I doing this because I want to die?
Let's vote on it.
And who are you?
The classroom president.
One. We split up.
Two. We go together.
-We'll go together. Next.
-Is it smart to vote?
On life and death matters
and just follow the majority?
What if we collectively decide
to do the wrong thing?
There's something called
collective intelligence.
There are too many
unintelligent people here.
-What are you looking at?
-It doesn't work like that.
Then what?
Should we vote about voting?
Hey, how did you kids survive until now?
Sorry, but will you butt out?
We're doing this
because you started the fight.
Give me an arrow so I can stab him.
We'll proceed to the next item.
One. Make the outside high.
Five votes.
Two.
Fold the lids and make a box.
Four votes.
What the hell?
You said it's better to stand them up.
I changed my mind.
Option one received the majority vote.
We'll make the walls high.
Hey. What about you?
It's a tie if you're for two.
I'm for option one.
Fuck.
-Hey. Let's make it.
-Okay.
Hey, don't resent me later.
The zombies really will climb over.
I'll lead the way and take responsibility.
You can stand back.
That prick.
Hey. Why are kids these days so damn rude?
No one compares to you.
Must you humiliate me
in front of underclassmen?
This is the virus that was created
using Lee Byeong-chan's method.
This is a sample from an infected person.
The two viruses are a 98% match.
Are you saying everything he said
in the videos is true?
Yes. When someone gets infected,
their heart stops.
Only the virus survives. It stimulates
the brain stem and moves the body.
They're like moving corpses.
There's no way
to bring a dead person back to life.
Are you saying he's dead?
Staff Sgt. Lee Jae-jun is dead
from a medical perspective.
But for that girl,
it's difficult to explain.
She was found alive.
There's never been a virus with this fast
of a rate of infection before.
Getting rid of the host is
the only solution.
Don't make it sound so simple!
You people must find a solution.
Commander.
They broke through the barricade.
It's spreading into Yangdong.
How bad is the spread?
They're taking Route 643
into downtown Yangdong.
We sent army reservists
from the area to the barricades.
Send all the reservists
to create a lockdown zone in Yangdong
and evacuate the city.
-Call in all the officials.
-Yes, sir.
You said you had a friend
in the NIS, right?
Yes, sir.
Ask him to meet officially.
You have to tie the knots tighter.
Here too?
-I hope we aren't doing anything stupid.
-My hands hurt.
Just do it.
-Hey, that looks good. Hand it to me.
-We're dead either way.
-Hey, come here.
-Me?
Ha-ri almost killed me.
-Hey.
-Hey, Dae-su.
A candy bar.
Let me see.
Can we eat it?
It's past the expiration date.
Can't we just eat it?
Of course we can.
You have to take tiny bites.
-Me first?
-We all need to have a bite. Okay?
Damn it. I said to take a small bite.
I only ate this much.
Fuck. Selfish prick.
I already ate.
I already ate too. Here.
-Hey.
-What?
Joon-yeong didn't eat.
How could you eat it all?
I…
I thought I was last. I'm really sorry.
Damn it.
Let's just put on our protective pads.
-That asshole.
-Joon-yeong, you wear the best one.
Take off your shoes. I'll do yours first.
Let's do this first.
Hold on tight.
Cheong-san.
What?
Don't you hate me?
-No.
-Why not?
I don't know.
I've never hated you.
That amazes me too.
Is everyone ready?
I'm opening the door.
Hold on.
It'll work out, right?
It will.
-Don't do anything stupid. Stick with me.
-You stick next to me.
Don't do anything stupid.
Then neither of us can move.
I'm scared.
I'll lead. You take the tail.
I'll open it.
Fuck.
I hope you're right.
I've seen countless zombies.
They don't have
the intelligence to climb over.
-Push!
-In front of you!
Go forward!
More!
Turn!
Get in!
-Hurry!
-Close it!
Did you tie it?
Done! Push!
Push!
Fuck!
They're climbing over!
It won't fucking budge!
Push harder!
We can do this!
Push harder! Harder!
It won't move!
Fuck!
Be careful!
Let go!
What are you doing? Push!
Push!
-Su-hyeok! Above you!
-Damn it.
-No!
-Fuck!
Hey! Are you okay?
Damn it! Hey!
Shit. I shouldn't have said
I'd take responsibility.
-Where are you going?
-Hey, wait!
-Joon-yeong!
-Hey! Stop!
-What the hell?
-Hey!
-Joon-yeong!
Get off, fuckers!
Get off, you bastards!
Push!
Hurry! Push!
Let's go! Let's go home!
Fuck…
Let's go home!
A little more!
Just a little more!
-Joon-yeong…
-A little more.
No!
No! Wait! Fuck!
Push!
Push! Push harder!
-Push!
Fuck!
HYOSAN
Each of those red dots
is the location of a random cell phone
owned by a Hyosan resident.
At first, they moved erratically,
so there was nothing to analyze.
But they slowly began to display
a collective movement.
If you look at them as a whole,
they're slowly traveling outward.
There is no one left
to attack in the city,
so they are increasing their radius.
It's probably similar
to animals leaving the mountains
and coming into civilization
when they run out of food.
Let's cut to the chase.
You predicted future movements too, right?
That's why you proposed to the NSC
that we abandon Yangdong as well
and expand martial law.
It isn't precise,
but take a look.
A week from now, it'll reach Seongnam,
Hanam, Gwacheon, Anyang,
and Gwangmyeong.
And the day after that, it'll reach Seoul.
Isn't that stretching it?
That's one person.
It was a simulation of what would happen
if just one infected person
got out of Hyosan.
That's what will happen.
Her heart rate is reaching 250.
Abnormal heartbeat detected!
I'M HUNGRY
Tell the tactical team
to come up with a strategy to bomb Hyosan.
Bomb the city?
Do you plan to blow up Hyosan?
We'll lose Korea trying to save Hyosan.
Act like a soldier.
We can't.
The infected are one thing,
but what about the civilians
we haven't rescued?
Don't calculate how many we'll kill.
Think only about how many we'll save.
WARNING: NO TRESPASSING
PRIVATE PROPERTY OWNED BY THE SCHOOL
Just a little bit more!
Untie it!
It's untied! Push!
-Push!
A little more this way!
Fuck!
-It won't open!
-Shit.
What do you mean?
-The door won't open!
-Move back!
Ha-ri, move!
Get lost, assholes! Get lost!
Hurry up!
It won't open.
It must be locked from the outside.
Damn it.
Dad.
ALL CHARACTERS, ORGANIZATIONS,
LOCATIONS, INSTITUTIONS,
AND EVENTS IN THIS SHOW ARE FICTIONAL.
Subtitle translation by: Jeong Lee