Hans Jonas discussed
the responsibilities
of life-related technologies.
I thus named the Jonas Virus
after this philosopher.
It's also my responsibility
to create an antidote.
I refuse to fail.
I'M SO SEXY
Hey, hey, hey! Help me!
Shit.
Let's go.
Ji-min!
- Stop her! Hey!
- What are you doing?
- Let go.
- What's with you?
I said let go of me!
Please come down.
- I want to die! Leave me alone!
- Don't be like this.
I don't wanna live!
- Ji-min. Come on.
- I want to die!
Please leave me alone! Please!
Let go of me!
Please let me go!
My mom and dad died.
What am I supposed to do alone?
Why would you die, you idiot?
What's the use in living?
Still, you should live, anyway.
I have nobody.
I don't have a mom or a dad.
I have nowhere to go
and no one waiting for me.
No one to scold me or praise me.
Do you know what that's like?
No, I don't.
Then don't act like you know everything.
Don't tell me what to do.
You don't know what it's like being me.
- No.
- Exactly.
So just leave me alone.
Every exam, I'm always last.
Well, not completely last.
Whenever I get my report card, my dad says
that my grades won't get me
into Seoul University,
so I shouldn't even bother having hope.
He says to make sure
I don't get hurt or sick.
To just stay healthy.
No offense.
I don't care about your dad.
I didn't believe him.
I'm sure he'd love it if I got into Seoul.
He was only saying that.
But...
He would also say to me...
if anything ever happens,
he would be the first one there for me.
But he's not.
He's not.
Who knows?
Maybe he can't come.
What if my...
my dad died?
At least you can have hope.
My hope is dead.
Is there hope?
Is it stupid of me to wait for him?
Or should I run away? Give up?
I don't know anything.
Both I-sak and Gyeong-su are killed.
I don't want any of my friends to die.
Why are you crying?
Don't die, Ji-min.
I don't want my friends to keep dying.
No one.
I gotta go.
I feel like I'm going crazy in here.
Okay, then.
So let's leave.
I really hate it here.
But how do we get out?
We have nowhere to go, anyway.
Ji-min. The mic went off in there.
Ugh, stay!
Can't you people smell? It stinks.
Breathe through your mouth.
What is it?
I think I have a plan to escape.
This is where we are.
This is where Cheong-san is.
If we turn our music only on this speaker,
the zombies will go left.
Then we'll take the stairs on the right,
get Cheong-san, and go to the roof
using the center stairs.
But why the roof?
Choppers keep flying around.
If we light a roof fire,
they might come save us.
Speakers. Will the zombies really go
towards the sound?
I think she's right.
They're drawn to sound.
That's right. They come running
whenever they hear us.
Can we turn on only the speakers we need?
Yes. The ones in the cafeteria,
yard, and library, too.
And draw them there.
Nam-ra, you were
in the broadcasting club, right?
Uh, yeah, my mom made me.
That's all good, and all.
Where do we get music?
There's no internet,
so we can't stream it.
Right there.
That thing?
This is ancient.
Will it even work?
That's good.
Anyone?
I've never done it before.
Somebody do it. Dae-su?
Here goes nothing.
Uh, mic test. One, two. One, two.
Cheong-san, are you there?
- We...
- What are you doing?
H... Hey.
Cheong-san, do you hear us?
It's Su-hyeok.
We'll come to you, so stay put.
Got it?
Don't come, moron. You're gonna get bit.
I know what you'll say,
but we can't hear you here.
What the hell are you doing, Bare-su?
So don't go anywhere.
Wait for us.
You really can't go anywhere, okay?
We'll come now.
All good.
Anyway, let's go.
The smell of shit makes me wanna hurl.
Dude, it's your shit.
- It's not just mine.
- Yes, it is.
- Really?
- Yes.
This can't end well.
Cheong-san.
Please stay still.
I know you never listen to me,
but please do it this time.
What's wrong?
- Why isn't it working?
- Beats me.
Time for meditation.
Once again,
another fun day at school.
Everyone, close your eyes...
...and calm your hearts.
Okay.
Broadcasting room.
Nam-ra, turn off the right
and middle speakers.
BUILDING CENTER, RIGHT, LEFT
Sound's distant.
Uh-huh. I hear it on the left.
- The speakers are working.
- Really?
It worked.
ONE HEART
Dae-su.
We're good.
- Hold on.
- Why? What?
There's one more.
Huh?
I'm going now.
You must keep moving forward...
Let's go.
Come on.
Check the left.
Shit, shit, shit, shit.
Close it. Close it.
Close it.
I could've totally died.
You said it was fine, you idiot.
- What? Where?
- There's one right outside.
Look right.
What do we do?
You think there's
something wrong with him?
Not any more than you.
- Rude as hell.
- Sorry.
Everyone else followed the sound,
but he's still there by himself.
Maybe he's deaf.
How the fuck could he hear
when the fucker's dead, huh?
What about the other zombies?
They all respond to sound.
Shit. Beats me.
Damn it.
How do we get out?
Hold on.
Let's wait a little bit.
I'll look.
Let's wait.
We can't be waiting.
Take the others and walk past him
as carefully as possible.
I'll do what I can from here.
All right.
Let's go.
...will never perish
even when all else withers and dies.
Hold on tight.
And don't let go.
BROADCASTING ROOM
Go!
Lee Cheong-san.
ROOFTOP
You moron.
Total loser, huh?
Thank you.
Of course. I saved your ass.
- I'm looking for Cheong-san?
- Cheong-san?
For what?
Death.
What do you mean?
I'm killing him.
You're badly hurt.
Are you okay?
I'm great.
I'm so fucking great.
So Cheong-san?
That's not funny.
You were always like that.
Isn't that right?
"Do this."
"Don't do that."
Always ordering me around.
It's okay, though.
You fought better than I did.
But you can't do that anymore.
You're nothing special.
You're scared?
That's okay.
Hey.
Aren't you scared?
Crazy asshole.
Weak asshole.
You little shithead.
Leave her alone!
Let's go.
Hurry up.
Here comes one. Run!
Shit, what's the code?
- Three-two-one-zero!
- Three-two-two-zero?
Three-two-one-zero!
Shit. Three, two...
What is it again?
Three-two-one-zero!
Three, two...
It worked! It's open!
Hey! Hurry!
Hurry! Joon-seong!
Help me!
Come on!
What are you waiting for? Hurry!
Hurry!
Get in here!
I'm tired as shit.
- Shit.
- You're crying?
You're crying?
Embarrassing.
Oh, god!
What happened to you, huh?
How do I fix it?
Let me see.
Wait. You're stabbed?
Why are you getting stabbed and shit?
Get the first aid kit.
I said get the first aid kit!
Where is the kit?
Oh, shit.
Where were you?
Cheong-san.
Where's On-jo?
On-jo!
Are you okay? Are you hurt?
Hurt as hell.
How did you guys know I was here?
Aah!
I told you not to go.
Why don't you ever listen to me?
Hey, save the lovers' quarrel for later.
- Huh?
- Let's go.
- Where?
- We have to get to the roof
- before the meditation music ends.
- Let's go. Hurry.
Wait.
Where's Su-hyeok? Su-hyeok isn't here.
- Where are you going?
- Hey! Hey! Hey!
Are you crazy? Don't go by yourself.
- Go in! Go inside!
- They're coming.
Hurry!
The curtains. Come on.
There's a zombie there.
It's caught under a piano,
so it can't go anywhere.
We can't...
go to the roof?
We're trapped again, aren't we?
There are zombies out there, so...
Let's just think a little.
This is so annoying.
Hey.
Hey, Nam-ra.
What happened to your arm?
That's a bite mark, isn't it?
I can't eat pork. Is there anything else?
Take it and go!
- Hold on.
- Go on. Get out of here.
I can't eat pork!
- Come on, we're all waiting.
- That's enough!
I'm good.
Are the cell phones working in here?
No. There won't be service here.
So you're telling me...
a politician can't talk
a way out of here?
It's true.
I've never been treated this way before.
There's nothing politicians
can't do in our country, right?
Don't be sarcastic.
I've never done anything illegal.
Never did anything improper my whole life.
Then can't you do it just this one time?
I really need to leave.
Wait a little.
I'll get you a helicopter
after we're tested,
and send you to your daughter's school.
The test isn't the problem.
Even if we test negative,
we'll still have to quarantine here.
It was nine days for MERS,
two weeks for Covid-19,
and even three weeks for Ebola.
And then what?
Are you saying we have to stay here
even after we get tested?
It depends what they consider
the incubation period is.
Please eat as much as possible,
and leave your empty food containers
by the door.
Hold on.
Special Mission?
I was a Master Sergeant when I left.
Are you our senior officer?
He was also Special Mission Unit.
Nice to meet you.
Sorry. I'd buy you a drink
if we had met outside.
It's fine.
Tell me, how long are they considering
for quarantine?
We don't know, sir.
Sure you do.
It's true.
They don't know what this virus is,
so they don't know the incubation period.
From what I hear, they're thinking
a minimum of, I don't know, four weeks.
What? That means we have
to be here for at least a month!
Wait until you get tested.
Wait a minute.
- Yes, sir.
- Well...
I'm sorry,
but I have to get out of here
much sooner than that.
Sir.
Even judges and prosecutors
are standing by and waiting.
Connections don't work here.
I know. And I'm very sorry.
- I sincerely apologize.
- For what?
What good do you think that's gonna do?
Why are you doing this?
Ma'am, I'm really sorry.
I have to get to the school.
I already said I'd follow protocol
and help you.
Those protocols kept me
from saving too many lives.
I'm leaving.
Please help them out,
so they are not punished,
not too severely at least.
You create this mess,
but you want me to clean it up?
I know you're a mother as well.
I'm a father.
Hey.
Why did you do that?
What? He... He tried to get up.
So what now?
Don't even think about coming with me.
You want me to stay here
after what I've done?
We can't go that way.
There are no kids
in school uniforms.
No one got out.
No one saved them.
No.
That's not it.
Move. Step back, Su-hyeok.
That's not it, asshole.
Tell him.
You weren't bitten by a zombie.
Say something.
Gwi-nam.
He bit her. It wasn't zombies.
Who?
Gwi-nam. The bully.
- Yoon Gwi-nam?
- Yeah.
Nam-ra. Did Gwi-nam really bite you?
Say it clearly.
It's true.
Gwi-nam was bitten by zombies.
Bullshit.
I saw him get bit.
If you get bitten by zombies,
you turn into one.
- So if Gwi-nam bit her...
- He's not one of them.
Gwi-nam wasn't a zombie.
He wasn't.
He literally talked to me.
You saw him. He wasn't a zombie at all.
Are you sure he was bitten by a zombie?
Yeah.
So I'll turn into a zombie.
You won't.
I...
Never mind. So be it.
Su-hyeok, thank you.
Hold on, prez.
I wonder why you never called me
by my name.
You won't.
She won't turn into one.
Don't you trust me?
I saw when Gwi-nam got bitten.
- It happened after fighting with me.
- I fought him, too. Believe me.
I know.
You see?
If she turns, I'll throw her
out the window, so she can't attack you.
So back off.
- Su-hyeok.
- Back off, asshole.
You shouldn't do this.
I owe it to you.
Don't come closer.
I'm warning you.
Screw you.
I warned you first.
Get lost.
Gyeong-su was enough.
I won't lose any more friends.
Get out of my way.
I said to stop it...
Get out of my way!
Stop it, both of you!
If I feel strange in any way...
I'll just end it quickly.
Sorry, but...
No need to be sorry.
I'm actually not sorry, not at all.
Sorry.
Su-hyeok.
Kill me if I turn.
Hey! Hey!
That's enough.
She should've turned by now.
Not yet.
She was bitten by Gwi-nam,
so she should be fine.
He was bitten by zombies.
Su-hyeok says he wasn't.
I saw it with my own eyes.
Su-hyeok has no reason to lie.
And you're telling me that I do?
Su-hyeok was saying...
I know you like him, but...
This is a little more important,
don't you think?
Why would you bring that up?
Because you always take his side.
I don't do that.
Yes, you do.
Does it hurt a lot?
I said we shouldn't come out!
I said we would all die!
We stopped the bleeding
and sterilized the wound.
So you'll be fine
once you get to a hospital.
How can I go to a hospital right now?
What a joke.
Stop complaining. You'll be fine.
It's all your fault.
It's your fault.
Just stop crying. Fuck!
Hey. Anything?
Of course, it's broken.
I said it wouldn't work, didn't I?
How annoying can you be? You won't die!
Su-hyeok.
I feel weird. I'm hungry.
Why do you smell so good?
Nam-ra.
Su-hyeok!
Get out of the way!
- Stop it.
- Get back now!
I said to stop it!
Stupid asshole!
Hey. Hey, hey, hey. Cut it out.
Stop it already!
- Let go! Let go of me!
- They're going to come in!
Don't do it!
Get out of my way! Let go of me!
Stop it. Are you blind? Look at Nam-ra.
She would have blood
on her mouth if she bit him.
Does she?
And he's not bleeding, right?
It's true. There's no wound.
But if Gwi-nam bit her...
She's still fine,
which means you'll be fine.
Come on, put that down.
Stop being stubborn.
Let go.
I got it. Let go. Fuck.
Why won't you drop that?
That's my business.
Are you okay?
- Why do you care?
- What?
It's weird.
You've always hated me.
Sometimes, I still do.
What's wrong is wrong, though.
She seems fine. Let's...
She would've definitely turned by now.
No.
I'm not okay. I wanted to bite Su-hyeok.
That's not true.
Stop that.
I really did.
I wanted to bite him.
Wait, what do you mean by that?
I mean...
I wanted to bite him.
I shouldn't stay with you any longer.
If I hadn't come to my senses,
I would've bitten him.
Hey, come on, stop that.
What's wrong with you?
I'll go.
Please wait.
You saw Gwi-nam get bitten by zombies?
I told you a hundred times, yes.
And you saw Gwi-nam turn?
No, I didn't.
I was busy running away.
Su-hyeok, you definitely fought Gwi-nam?
Yes, I did.
There's no reason for either to lie.
Maybe Gwi-nam was bitten,
but was not affected.
In the movies, there are always people
who are immune, remember?
Still, she tried to bite him.
She could have bitten him for real.
Regardless, she isn't normal.
So I'm not going with her.
Ji-min, stop.
What? Are you saying that I'm wrong?
Maybe.
I really don't know what we should do.
We can't pretend she's fine.
Enough.
Please don't fight.
Leaving will solve everything.
Don't go. Where would you go?
Stop it.
Please.
I don't want anyone dying.
Hyeon-ju and I-sak...
They're hands were very cold
before they turned.
Nam-ra's hands are warm.
She isn't a zombie.
So cut it out,
and let's talk how to get to the roof.
- No.
- Ji-min!
No way!
She may be fine now,
but who knows what's gonna happen
when she turns?
Guys, say something. This is wrong.
She said herself
that she wanted to bite him.
She has zombie blood in her veins.
Zombies killed my mom and dad.
My mom.
Hey.
Give me your hand.
- What are you doing?
- Tying a knot.
Stop it. Stop.
Hold still.
Happy? This way,
she can't get to you if she turns.
I'll get bitten instead.
What are you going to do?
I have to go.
Be back in a minute.
It's probably not gonna start, you know?
Why are you so damn pessimistic, huh?
The earlier one was in an accident.
That's obviously fine.
How are we gonna fit two people
on that thing?
Try three.
You wanna take the baby with you?
If we leave the baby here,
it won't survive.
Here.
Sit in the back and kill anyone
who gets too close. Okay?
Oh, I can't go. There's no way.
You coward.
You wanna be reported for desertion?
Fine, go ahead.
Given the situation I'm currently in,
the court will agree
these were extenuating circumstances.
- Court?
- Yeah.
- Circumstances?
You're smart.
Yes, I am. I go to Seoul University.
Okay, then, I'll break
all the windows on my way out,
so that they can get in.
Oh! All right!
All right! I'll go. I'll go.
Seriously?
A person should use his head.
We need to stay alive
to tell anyone about the laptop.
CHEONG-SAN CHICKEN
What's going on?
Hey. Hey.
Come here!
You said we were going,
so we should've just gone.
Are you going to save
everyone in the world?
- Are you the spirit of God?
- Police officer.
Damn it.
- Take the baby.
- Okay.
The baby.
Are you okay?
Are you hurt anywhere?
Mommy.
- Mommy is over there.
- Where?
Where's Mama?
Is...
Is that your mom?
The one in red?
Sir. I don't know how to hold babies.
This baby keeps smiling.
- What do I do? What do I do?
- Wait a minute.
Stay still for one minute.
What is wrong with this world?
It will be okay.
If Nam-ra's immune,
does that mean she's okay
even if she gets bitten?
- Probably.
- Oh, shit.
That's not fair.
She still has zombie blood in her veins.
She isn't completely a zombie.
A half-bie?
What's half-bie?
Short for half zombie?
Really?
It's like half and half.
Like half spicy, half fried... Oh!
- I want chicken.
- That's enough, Dae-su.
We haven't had water for two days.
Is it true we'll die
if we don't have water for three days?
I don't know.
Please don't talk to me. I'm too hungry.
Dae-su, don't you want that soda
we had on our way to school?
Oh!
- Don't you want it so bad?
- Yes.
I want Hot Six with Pocari.
I'll see your soda,
Hot Six, and Pocari,
and raise you an iced vanilla latte.
How could you think about food
with a zombie here?
Stop it. Nam-ra isn't a zombie.
Half-bie.
Close enough.
Let's not do this to ourselves.
We're all we've got now.
She's right.
Nam-ra is better than Na-yeon.
Don't even say her name.
She's subhuman.
Gyeong-su died, because of her,
and Miss Park...
That's true.
If it weren't for Na-yeon,
they'd be here with us right now.
Wait a sec.
The PTA asked the parents
to send some stuff before the competition,
and asked my mom to send some chicken.
Chicken?
We would've seen it
if it were here.
I don't see anything.
Hold on.
Shit. Maybe it's in there.
Hey, hey.
- What?
- We don't know what's in there.
We need to eat and survive first.
- Damn it. It's locked.
- It's locked, goddamn it.
Let's open it.
Find something
to pick the lock with.
Look for something. Hurry.
What do you think?
- That wall is our only way out, right?
- Yes. That's our best option.
Security is insane.
We're completely trapped.
- Let's go over it.
- Are you sure?
- We'll be seen for sure.
- That's the only way.
RESTRICTED AREA
AUTHORIZED PERSONNEL ONLY
The line.
Drop me a line.
- U-sin.
- Yes?
Just...
Stay alive.
Are you insane? Take me with you, please.
Captain! Captain!
Captain!
Freeze.
Freeze!
What are you doing?
Stop right there.
What the hell?
I said to freeze.
I'm on patrol, moron.
Which unit are you with?
- Sorry.
- Pardon?
Nothing?
Should we knock it down?
Damn it.
PTA DONATIONS
Hey. Take it easy.
Hey. Keep it down! You gotta be quiet.
Hey.
Hey, stop doing that.
It won't work.
What a waste of energy.
And please, no music.
My mom and dad...
They came to the school to save me.
The police...
and firefighters never came.
If anybody is watching this after,
punish them.
All involved.
They abandoned us.
All of them.
I'll make you pay.
Hi, Mom.
Hi, Dad.
I'll stay alive and get revenge.
I'll kill all the zombies...
and anyone else.
Mom.
And Dad.
Hello.
I'm here with some of my classmates
and they're really good to me.
Let me just show you. This is them.
Uh...
Um...
Mom, Dad...
I miss you.
I miss you both.
And, um...
I'm so sorry.
Um, give it to me.
Hey, Mom.
I want a raise in allowance.
- Is it ready to go?
- Yes.
Music and lyrics
by intergalactic superstar Yang Dae-su.
Beat.
♪ Chicken tastes better fried ♪
♪ In olive oil ♪
♪ Pork tastes better than soy meat ♪
♪ Strawberry cake tastes better
Than plain strawberries ♪
♪ What makes me laugh, laugh, laugh ♪
♪ Is trans fat ♪
Cheong-san?
Mom.
It's me.
Dad, you're okay too, right?
I'm...
I'm good.
Hi, Dad.
I miss you.
You're not here,
but I waited for you all night,
and we're holding on together.
You always say being healthy
is better than getting good grades.
You said you'd be the first to come
if anything ever happened.
And you're okay, right?
You have to be okay, Dad.
You don't have to come save me, but...
But still, I wish you'd come.
I really thought you would be here by now.
But I'm okay.
Usually, I save this for my allowance.
But I'll say it for free here.
Dad, I...
I love you.
I really love you.
ALL CHARACTERS, LOCATIONS,
ORGANIZATIONS,
AND EVENTS IN THIS SHOW ARE FICTIONAL.