-Mom.
-Cheong-san, no.
What the hell?
Damn it!
There's another zombie here!
Dae-su!
Stop it.
Dae-su! Get up!
I said stop that!
-Stop that!
-Hey!
Cheong-san! What the hell?
You son of a bitch!
Stop it!
Let go!
Get the fuck off me!
Mom!
Mom…
Hurry.
Run!
Hey, let's go.
Hurry up!
Let's go.
Let's go, Cheong-san.
Pull yourself together, man!
Where are the others?
What?
Where are they?
-What now?
-Did you see them coming?
Cheong-san, please.
-Come with us.
-Let's go.
Mom!
Mom…
They're here. Hurry up!
-Wu-jin!
-Get up.
Come on. We have to go. Let's go!
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
Shut up. You're so heavy.
Mi-jin. Thank you so much.
-Will you go out with me?
-No.
Screw you.
Hold on.
-Why? What is it?
-Shh.
Hear that?
Those goddamn fucking zombies. Shit.
Let's go.
Let's run.
To the mountain.
Aah!
Ji-min. Help me.
Hyo-ryeong!
Get up!
Get up.
Sister.
-Wu-jin.
-What are you doing here?
Come on.
Get going.
-Hey!
-Hyo-ryeong. You go first.
-Come on! Let's go!
-Let's go.
What's wrong, Nam-ra?
Run.
Let's go.
Oh, shit.
Run!
I'm gonna die tonight!
-Run! Go!
-Just save yourselves!
Just go! You'll die! Believe me!
Whatever!
-Over here!
-This way! Hurry!
Come on!
Are you crazy? Let go!
Hey! No! No!
No!
What are you doing?
No! Let go of me, you assholes!
Let me go!
Let go off me! No!
Get out of here! Hurry!
No! Joon-seong! Joon-seong…
Joon-seong!
No! Let me go!
Shit.
Damn it.
Hey, Cheong-san, I'm…
so sorry.
I didn't know she was your mom.
I'm sorry.
Stop!
Don't do this.
No!
Mommy…
A virus
must have a consistent pattern
for us to create a vaccine.
But the Jonas Virus…
transforms and evolves on its own.
It is an ever-changing monster.
It's impossible to create a vaccine.
There is only one solution.
Slaughter.
Completely burning and killing the host,
so not a single cell remains.
The moment we are consumed by arrogance
and think we can defeat the virus,
humankind will end.
The file was massive,
so we couldn't analyze it all,
but a significant portion
of it is credible, sir.
And where is the proof for that?
Well, KDCA is creating a virus
using the exact method he described.
If they create the same virus,
then the KDCA will conclude it's credible.
Well…
Many soldiers are going insane
from this thing, but…
It's scarier when a scientist goes crazy.
Did you hear
they're expanding martial law?
Martial law?
Why would they do that
if we're handling it well?
My friend in the NIS analysis team
said they're discussing pulling back
the blockade to Yangdong
and expanding martial law.
What about Hyosan?
I think they're willing
to make sacrifices.
We may have ceased
our rescue operation for now, but…
there might not be another time
to rescue survivors.
Strengthen the blockade
on the outskirts of Hyosan.
The moment the blockade
is penetrated by the infected,
we'll have to step up and…
abandon Hyosan.
Take this.
LETTER OF RESIGNATION
Childish to think the party leader
came personally to save me.
You came to dump me.
My NIS source says
something is going to happen very soon
in Hyosan.
In your district.
If something bad really does happen,
I'll say you even resigned from your post
thinking it would help prevent it.
No one would even think of blaming you.
Blame me for what?
Trust me, you're gonna sign it.
I'll protect your political career
until the end.
Do you need time to think it over?
You failed Hyosan.
They'll just abandon it?
Sign it within the day,
and hand it to the person in charge
of this place.
Hmm…
Sir, um, can you hear me?
-Let's go.
-Excuse me, sir!
Oh, damn.
Assemblywoman?
You're getting us out now, right?
The party leader came,
so it'll all be resolved very soon, right?
He says he'll save us, right?
Ma'am?
I thought about it all night long.
How do I live?
What do I do?
Why don't we talk about this later?
Tomorrow or the day after.
Or next week, maybe.
Let's get out of here and eat some food,
and shower first, okay?
We'll talk about it then.
Hmm?
We have a lot to talk about, you know?
Let's give it time.
Whatever happens…
please don't give up.
Okay?
Okay.
Never.
Mm-hmm.
You too.
It'll be okay.
What is it?
Do you see something?
The smell is stronger.
I can't really smell anything.
I think they're all coming this way.
The smell is really strong.
Doesn't matter.
We're all trapped in here for good now.
And there's no way to get out.
Please don't say that.
So don't.
I think we're done.
Ah, damn it!
Let them kill us if they want.
Ha-ri.
You didn't fail
in the preliminaries, did you?
No.
I did really well.
Your tournament.
What happened?
Why did you come to the school?
-You're her brother?
-Yeah, I am.
She got a perfect score,
so she made it to nationals.
I saw her.
Really?
Mm-hmm. It's true.
No way. Really?
You're really in the nationals?
Mom and Dad don't know?
Bro, how could they now? Look around.
She jumped out of archery bus
and ran to the school to find you.
Kid.
You be good to her.
And to me too.
Who is she?
Why does she keep
talking for you?
She's my friend.
Yeah. We're freaking besties.
You scared me.
What's your deal?
I…
You?
I think you're the perfect girl.
What? You freak.
Hey.
What's wrong with you?
I watched you
when you were shooting your arrows,
I saw you train every morning.
I went to every tournament
and cheered for you.
Caught myself yelling "copper beauty"
a few times.
I really liked you for many years.
Now…
I wanna be a man, not just a fan.
I'm gonna die, anyway.
I just wanna say what I want first.
Cool.
You're Dae-su, right?
You call my brother "brother-in-law"?
Yeah.
So that means you knew.
Brother-in-law, you told her?
Yeah, I might have.
Must be nice to meet me.
Yes.
-Then you're okay with dying?
-Yes.
What? Today?
Good. I'm pissed off and needed to vent.
Wu-jin, stop her.
-Ha-ri, hey.
-Stop her.
-Come here. Get over here.
-I'm sorry. I was wrong.
-No. I'm glad you told me.
-Hey. No, that's not it.
-Yes, it is. Get over here now.
-No, I…
Why don't you understand?
I really like you.
-Get over here, dear husband.
-Wu-jin. Hey.
-Sorry.
-Stop her, Wu-jin.
-No!
-Beat him up, sis.
Get over here. You punk.
-He needs a good beating.
-Look at him dodging.
What's that?
That's not it!
Guys.
Come here. Gonna get you, asshole!
-Hey, hey, stop it. Stop it. Stop her.
-I don't want to come between you two.
-Right now.
-Okay. Only if you promise not to hit me.
Where did those shitheads run off to now?
What are you doing?
Can we move this?
Do you think it's possible?
We can tie all the carts in a circle,
then we can just use them as a shield.
This way.
We need strings or something
to tie them together.
Is this it?
This?
Cut as many as possible.
Hey. There's no way this is going to work.
We should flip it over completely,
so that we can hide underneath.
Uh… We should stand it up.
Yeah, zombies sure can't climb that?
That's enough.
Don't be stupid. Okay? Let's redo them.
It's too short if we close the lids.
Unless you want us crawling?
Pulling rank right now?
Hey.
Say it to my face!
If you don't like it, make your own.
There.
Oh, shit. Are you crazy?
What's wrong with you?
-Sis, stop her.
-Come on. Say that again.
Do everyone a favor
and stay out of our way.
Hey, you.
Shithead!
"Shithead"? Shithead. What the fuck?
Stop it.
Joon-yeong, you too.
Who the hell is she to tell us
we have to redo it?
"Who the hell is she?"
Your fucking nightmare.
-You're coming with us, right?
-You're the ones coming with me.
You won't just leave them here, right?
I wish, but no.
We're going together, anyway.
Why fight now, huh?
Just do as I say
unless you wanna die out there.
Which you might.
We're tryna make it that high,
so we don't die out there.
Enough already.
How many people have died on our way here?
We can't lose anyone else.
We shouldn't waste energy
fighting among ourselves.
I'm not fighting to die.
I'm fighting because I wanna live.
Then do as I fucking say, asshead.
Unless we split up.
Problem solved.
-Get back here. You hear me?
-Joon-yeong.
Get back here!
Let go of me, asshole!
You think I'm doing this,
because I wanna die?
We'll vote on it.
You are?
Class prez.
One. Split up.
Two. Stay together.
-Okay, we voted to stay together, then.
-Is it smart to vote
on life and death matters
and just follow the majority?
What if we collectively decide
to do the wrong thing?
You know, there's such a thing
as collective intelligence.
There are too many
unintelligent people here.
You can't make intelligence
with a bunch of idiots.
So then what do you suggest?
Do we vote about voting, huh?
Fuck! How the hell did
your kids survive up to now?
Sorry, but can you mind your own business?
You started the fight, now we're voting.
Give me an arrow, so I can stab him.
Anyway, let's move on now.
One. We make the outside higher.
Five votes.
Two.
We fold the lids, make a box.
So that's four.
What the hell? I thought you were with us?
I changed my mind.
Option one received the majority vote,
so make the walls high.
Wait. Your vote.
If you're for option two, it's a tie.
Option one.
Oh, shit.
Okay. Let's do it.
Okay, but don't resent me
when the zombies climb over
and kill us all.
Don't worry, I'll take the front
and any blame.
You hold back.
Oh, what an asshole. Fuck.
Why are kids so damn rude these days?
And you're not?
Don't say that in front
of the underclassmen.
This is the virus that was created
using Lee Byeong-chan's method precisely.
This is a sample from an infected.
The two viruses
are 98 percent match.
Are you saying everything he says
in the videos is true?
Yes. When someone gets infected,
their heart stops.
Only the virus survives.
It stimulates the brainstem
and moves the body.
They're like moving corpses.
We haven't found any way to save the dead.
You're telling me that he's dead?
Staff Sergeant Lee Jae-jun is dead
from a medical perspective.
But she's, ugh…
Difficult to explain.
She was found alive.
There has never been a virus with such
a fast rate of infection in history.
Our only solution
is getting rid of the host.
I'm not going to tolerate
the sign of indifference!
Your only job is to find me a cure.
Commander, sir.
They broke through the barricade.
It's spreading into Yangdong.
How bad is the spread?
They're taking route 643
into downtown Yangdong.
We sent army reservists
in the area to the barricades.
Send all the reservists to create
a lockdown zone in Yangdong
and evacuate the city.
-Call in all the advisers.
-Yes, sir.
You said you had a friend in the NIS?
Yes.
Ask him to meet officially.
Yes, sir.
You have to tie
the knots harder.
Here too?
-I hope we're not doing…
-Can you do it?
-…anything stupid.
-My hands hurt.
-Just do it.
-Hey, that looks good.
Hand it to me. We're gonna die, anyway.
-Hey, come here.
-Me?
-I almost got killed confessing…
-Hey. Chocolate bar.
Let me see.
You think we can eat it, huh?
Oh, no, expired.
Okay, so what?
Okay, yeah, you're right.
Only take a tiny bite.
It needs to feed all of us. Okay?
Oh, shit. I said a tiny bite.
I only ate freaking this much.
Selfish bastard.
I'm full, so…
Mmm.
I really don't want that. Here.
-Hey.
-What?
Joon-yeong didn't have any.
How could you eat it all?
I…
I… I thought I was last. I'm really sorry.
I guess we just… armor up, right?
-That asshole.
-Joon-yeong, you put on the best armor.
Take off your shoes
and I'll do yours first.
Just hold on a sec.
Hold on tight.
Hey, Cheong-san.
What?
Do you really hate me?
Mm-mmm.
Why not?
Crazy.
I've never hated you at all.
That amazes me too.
This is it.
Here we go.
Hold on.
This will work?
It will work.
-Just stay next to me, okay?
-You stay next to me.
And don't get killed.
You don't want it, so we both can't move.
I'm scared.
I'm gonna take the lead.
You take the back.
Are you ready?
Shit.
You better be right with this.
We've seen so many zombies already.
They're not smart enough for this.
Push!
Hurry!
Let's go!
More!
Turn!
Get in! Get in!
Close it!
Did you tie it?
Done! Push!
Push!
Damn it!
They're climbing over!
It won't budge!
Push harder!
We can do this!
-Push harder! Harder!
-It won't move!
Be careful!
On-jo!
What are you doing? Push!
Su-hyeok! Above you!
Fuck!
Hey, are you okay?
Oh, shit.
Shit. I said I'd take responsibility.
-Where are you going?
-Hey, wait!
-Joon-yeong!
-Hey! Hey!
Joon-yeong!
-Where are you going?
-Hey! Don't go!
Get off!
Push! Push!
Hurry up and push!
Go home! Make it home!
Go home!
Make it home!
No! Hey!
-Ugh! Joon-seong!
-Keep going!
Keep going!
Keep going! Keep going…
No! No, stop it!
No! Wait!
I'm sorry!
Push!
Damn it!
HYOSAN
Each of those red dots
is the location
of a random cell phone in Hyosan.
At first, they begin with erratic movement
and that gives us nothing to analyze.
But slowly, they move collectively.
If you look at them as a whole,
they're traveling outward.
Because there is nobody left
in the city to eat.
They're slowly beginning
to increase their territory.
Consider them like a dangerous animal
in the mountains
entering civilization
when they run out of food.
Let's just cut to the chase.
You predicted a spread, right?
That's why you proposed
expanding martial law
to the NSC when Yangdong's gone.
So it isn't entirely precise.
But look.
In one week, it reaches Seongnam,
Hanam, Gwacheon, Anyang,
and Gwangmyeong.
Coming right after, the city of Seoul.
Seems a bit of a stretch, if you ask me.
Just one person.
It's a simulation of what will happen
if just one infected person
gets out of Hyosan.
That's what will happen.
Her heart rate
is reaching 250.
Abnormal heart rate detected!
I'M HUNGRY
Tell Tactics to come up
with a strategy to bomb Hyosan.
To bomb the city, sir?
Do you really plan to blow up Hyosan?
Hyosan may fall, but Korea will remain.
Act like a damn soldier.
We can't.
The infected are one thing,
but what about the civilians
that we haven't rescued?
Don't think about the ones
we have to kill.
The ones we will save
will justify everything.
WARNING: NO TRESPASSING
PRIVATE PROPERTY OWNED BY THE SCHOOL
Just a little bit more!
Untie it! Untie it!
It's untied! Push!
Push!
The door won't open!
Fuck.
What are you talking about?
The door won't open!
Ha-ri!
Fuckers! Get lost! Get out!
Let go! Damn it!
Come on. Hurry up already!
It won't open.
It's locked from the outside.
Shit.
Dad, you…
ALL CHARACTERS, LOCATIONS, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND EVENTS IN THIS SHOW ARE FICTIONAL.
Subtitle translation by: Jeong Lee
Ripped by TTEOKBOKKIsubs