The ones who get bullied
have a problem too.
The kids must have
a reason for bullying you.
Look.
It's okay.
Fuck off.
You did nothing wrong?
There's nothing you're sorry about?
The kids must have
a reason for bullying you.
PROVIDING AN EDUCATION
THAT WARMS AND STRENGTHENS LIVES
I wish the school would burn down.
So that nothing remains.
So that everything disappears.
Hey, Dae-su!
What about the others?
Is it really just you?
It's just me.
Downstairs? In the classrooms?
There's no one down there. It's just me!
Hold tight!
You're sure there's no one else, right?
They're all zombies.
They all died.
Pull it tighter, guys.
Give me your eye.
What the hell? Fuck!
Why didn't you die?
DOOR WILL OPEN AUTOMATICALLY
IN CASE OF FIRE
Guys!
The door's open.
-Let's go!
-One, two, three!
-Look! A chopper!
-Over here!
-Hey!
Here!
We're here!
Help!
Come back!
-Help!
-Come back!
-Come back here!
-Over here!
-Hey!
-Where are you going?
-Over here!
-Hey!
-Come back!
-Over here!
-Help!
-Hey!
-Why are you leaving?
-We're still here!
Where are you going?
We're here…
Fuck! Damn it.
HYOSAN HIGH SCHOOL
Mom…
Fuck.
He's gone.
What the hell?
-Who's gone?
-Gwi-nam.
It's his smell.
I hear his breathing too.
HYOSAN HIGH SCHOOL
What happened?
Didn't Gwi-nam fall from the fourth floor?
He did. I threw him.
So how did he survive?
Look for ones with colors.
Maybe he doesn't die.
Or maybe he dies and comes back to life.
-It has to be visible from the sky.
-He's neither human nor zombie.
Do you remember
that girl in the teachers' office?
I'll kill you!
Give it to me, fucker! I'll kill you!
-She was weird too.
-Gwi-nam's like her, isn't he?
I think so.
Maybe Nam-ra is the same.
What are you doing, Dae-su?
Look I found an "O."
That's what you found?
She'll be fine.
You can't guarantee what will happen.
There's nothing we can guarantee
right now.
We don't know if we'll live or die.
Let's go make the SOS sign.
Bare-su.
If On-jo were like that,
could you just dump her?
It's totally visible from up there.
It came and left, didn't it? A chopper?
Yes.
Maybe they started the rescues.
Let's get to the rooftop.
What if that's the end of the rescue?
But it only came once.
We don't know
whether or not it'll come back.
I don't think we should go to the roof.
If it comes back, will you take the blame?
What will you do then?
-Nothing.
-Hey.
We can't make it to the roof anyway.
How can we carry him up there?
Hey.
-Just leave me and go.
-For real?
Yes. You should just go.
You mean it? You know how I am, don't you?
I'll leave you.
Should we?
Should we not?
Don't act tough.
There's a ton of tough bastards outside.
I won't die from this, will I?
Fuck, I don't know.
Anyway, we should put up
a sign or something.
How would anyone know
we're in here and save us?
Doesn't this building have a rooftop?
There's no way up there?
They'll see us up there.
Well, there is a ladder
that leads to the roof, but--
Right? There is, right? Where is it?
-Outside.
-Outside?
Yes, outside.
You fucker. Come here.
-What? Why?
-You bastard.
-What? Outside?
-Sorry!
Get back here. Fuck.
Stay back!
-Let me throw you out for five seconds!
-Help!
This is too big.
How about this?
-Break it apart.
-Here's a big one.
How's this?
Not that one. Put it down.
Not this?
-Gather anything big and colorful.
-Can I take this?
Joon-yeong, go up there and look.
Hey, be careful.
How does it look?
-First…
-Yes.
The "O" is a bit narrow.
He said the "O" is too narrow.
Dae-su, hand me that long one.
It should be much bigger than this.
Nam-ra, can you carry this?
-Guys, keep it up.
-That goes over there.
It goes like this.
And the "S" is too short.
-Get more of these.
-Is this enough?
Fill that spot too. That's it.
I got this part.
They're too tight.
Spread them out.
Let's put it all away.
Come take a look. We did a good job.
-Look.
-You can't miss it.
-We did do a good job.
-Right?
It seems a little crooked.
And the "S" is kind of short.
Hope is…
the cruelest torture
that prevents you from giving up on life.
REALTY
WOOGYEONG GIRLS' MIDDLE SCHOOL
HYOSAN ARTS CENTER
I can't think of anything else,
but I can't stop either.
MYEONHAK-DONG
HYOSAN HIGH SCHOOL
Once body temperature rose,
the white blood cells were activated.
But they were absorbed by the virus
and turned into a different virus.
Gently.
You'll draw the zombies.
Bite down.
Good job. All done.
It isn't broken,
so it'll get better soon
if you leave it like this.
Thank you, detective.
No need for formalities.
Just call me Jae-ik.
Okay, Jae-ik.
Since we're comfortable
with each other now,
may I speak frankly?
Yes, of course. Speak freely.
Okay.
-You crazy idiot. You stupid moron.
-What…
You fucking came here
just to shoot some Internet show?
You're a total moron.
What? Subscribe and like?
Do you like that more than your life?
You're a crazy asshole.
I'm sorry, detective.
Don't call me detective.
I said to call me by my name.
It's fine, detective.
If you were my brother,
you wouldn't need to worry about zombies.
I'd beat you to death right here.
But someone must uncover the truth
and let the world know, detective.
What? The truth?
Hey. Are you a journalist?
Come on.
Journalists don't dig to find the truth.
That's why people like me
must step in, detective.
Seriously. You and that mouth of yours.
Right.
It looked like your colleague dumped you
and took off.
Should I blast him on my show?
I can even interview you if you want.
-Forget it.
-You should take revenge on traitors.
Look.
I learned from
my long experience as a detective.
Assholes fighting to stay alive
and coming at you
hoping to die are impossible to beat.
I'm just worried about the kids.
I have a pretty good number of followers.
I can end him socially for good.
Oysterubbish.
Orangibberish. Not Oysterubbish.
Who gives a shit? Stop gibberishing
and gather everything we can throw.
What? Why?
Why else? It's crazy hot up here.
You want to become human jerky?
Why is everyone I meet like this?
They're not moving.
No. They follow sounds.
Keep handing them over.
What are you doing?
You said you'd clear them out,
not lure them.
They followed sounds earlier.
What the hell? Give me one more.
Stop it. More keep coming.
I said to give it to me, asshole.
-I ought to just…
-It's weird.
MUNPYEONG DAYCARE
Oh God.
Oh my God.
Sir!
-You traitor!
-Traitor.
Jump! Jump on top of the bus!
Jump down!
I got it, asshole. Shut up.
-Let's go.
-What?
-I said let's go!
-But…
Goddamn it.
Fuck. That was close.
Hey. Jump.
What? I can't jump.
Don't give me that bullshit. Jump.
I hurt my leg!
I know. Jump!
You should've taken me with you.
Why did you jump first?
-How would I do that, you moron? Jump!
-My leg hurts.
Do you want to die there
or break your leg here?
This is nuts.
-Jump!
-But my leg hurts.
-You want to die?
-What about my leg?
-Se-bin.
-Yes?
Close your eyes and keep them shut.
Hurry up, will you?
Let's just go!
-I'll catch you.
-No, I can't!
Hey! Wait! Hold on!
Jump, asshole!
Damn it. Hold on. Okay.
Hold on. Wait.
Just leave him!
Can we get going, for God's sake?
Aim for here.
-Shit.
-What the hell are you doing?
Oh no! Wait! Help me, detective!
I mean, Jae-ik. Pull me up.
Please save me. Please.
All clear!
Here we go, sir!
Let's go, Ho-seong!
Wait. Okay, go.
-What does SOS mean?
-It's a distress signal.
I know that. But what does it stand for?
It doesn't stand for anything.
SOS is just SOS.
That makes no sense.
That's just how it is. It has no meaning.
Wait. Rescue quickly…
Why'd you ask
if you don't even believe me?
I thought you'd know.
I do know.
Look it up. You'll see I'm right.
Whatever. How can I look it up?
I don't have my phone.
What's wrong?
I asked On-jo what SOS meant,
but she said it has no meaning.
Just say you don't know.
It's true.
-It is?
-Yes. She's right.
Why don't you believe her?
Hey, Prez.
What does SOS mean?
Why, that--
Forget it. Let him be.
No meaning?
Is it true?
What?
SOS doesn't mean anything?
It's not an acronym?
-You don't believe me?
-No.
The sun's about to set.
Let's start a fire.
Hey.
The sun's going to set.
I think it's working.
Next.
-Already?
-Next.
Let's do this.
You'll get tired. Slow down.
The fire won't start if he does it slowly.
Do it faster.
Come on. Faster. Twist it faster.
-Faster!
-Please.
Did it cramp up?
-My palms. I can't do it.
-I'll do it. Step back.
Should we kill him?
Are you praying?
Don't pray. Rub…
Get lost.
It's hard. It won't work.
Isn't that smoke?
-Hey. Smoke.
-Smoke!
-Su-hyeok.
-Hold on.
-Please. Come on.
-Blow.
Blow. Blow on it already!
-Be careful.
-Blow.
Did it catch on fire? Su-hyeok?
-Please. I'm begging you.
-Fuck.
Shit.
I'll do it.
-Hey.
-Do it faster.
Hey.
Use this.
I smoke.
You had that all along…
You don't want it?
Light it.
MUNPYEONG DAYCARE
Traitor.
I came back and saved you.
You abandoned me and fled by yourself.
I found this bus and came back for you.
Seriously, man.
You need to use your brain.
What did you…
-Do you have a license to drive a bus?
-No.
I have a regular license.
I'll bust you once we get there.
Starting with driving without a license--
What was that? It's a zombie, isn't it?
Since when do zombies ride bikes?
-Dumbass. Hey, Oyster.
-Orange.
Take the baby.
Careful.
Be careful.
Open the door.
Seriously?
You're dead if you betray me again.
If I turn, I'll only go after you.
-I'll bite only your neck. Got it?
-Okay.
Oh my goodness.
Hey.
Are you okay?
You weren't bitten or anything, right?
You're okay, right?
I'm fine.
Come with us. I'm a cop.
Hey!
Mister!
It's okay!
The soldiers are here. They're soldiers.
We're saved!
What was that?
Hey!
Don't shoot!
I'm a cop. Hold on. I'm a cop.
Don't shoot! Here!
Chin down. Extend your left arm.
Don't stick out your chest too much.
This is so damn sexy.
-What's with the face?
-Don't bother if that's your mindset.
Stop being cocky
about shooting some stupid arrows.
Hey. Why did I miss?
Did you think it was easy?
Anything is easier than studying.
You get into Seoul University
if you're in the top 100.
But if we're 100th in the country,
we can't go anywhere.
We can't make the national team,
get into college or a corporate team.
There's nothing we can do.
Everyone knows
you'll make the national team.
You'll go to college
just by shooting arrows so stop whining.
Damn it.
Did you not?
You didn't make the national team?
You can't go to college?
You won't die if you don't go to college.
I really like shooting arrows.
All I did was archery.
I don't know how to do anything else.
As long I can keep doing it,
I don't care whether I go to college
or join a corporate team.
But now
there's nowhere for me to shoot arrows.
I'm only 19.
But I have no hope.
If the zombies kill all the archers,
you'll automatically make
the national team.
Crazy bitch. You call that a consolation?
It's hope.
At least you have possibilities.
It's impossible for me
to get into college even if I live.
The CSAT? Fuck it.
My answers are always C or D.
Why C or D?
I pick C if I'm not sure
and D if I'm clueless.
I swear it's like
I avoid all the right answers.
Enough whining.
Teach me how to shoot arrows.
Even if I suck,
it's better than you shooting alone.
Dae-su.
Yes?
How was your audition?
They told me to lose weight.
You're a good singer.
Sing for us. I want to hear it.
Forget it. I don't want to sing.
I really like that song.
You do?
Yes.
Really?
It's really nice.
You sing well.
It'll cheer us up.
Let's go once it's over
Let's go anywhere
Once we're done studying 12 hours a day
Once the annoying sounds are over
Let's go hand in hand
Let's not run
Let's try walking slowly
Is that drool or sweat pooled on the book?
No one notices the plop, plop
The plop, plop
The falling rain drops
What is boiling? Simmer, simmer
It's Mom's doenjang stew
A bowl of instant noodles
In front of the TV
Which plays nothing but static
Let's go anywhere together
I have to get to the rooftop, damn it.
…but the cops
and firefighters never came.
If anyone sees this later,
please punish
everyone who should have come.
I'm fine. The kids are really good to me.
Want to see them?
Mom.
I want a raise in my allowance.
Here.
-Is it ready to go?
-Yes.
Music and lyrics
by intergalactic superstar Yang Dae-su.
Chicken tastes better fried in olive oil
Pork tastes better than soy meat
What makes me laugh, laugh, laugh
Is trans fat
I'm hungry.
How can you sing right now?
Isn't everyone leaving a final message?
Why is it final? Are we dying?
Hello.
I'm Oh Joon-yeong, class of '23
at Seoul University Business School.
I'll meet you soon, upperclassmen.
And once I'm there,
I want to get a girlfriend.
No, you can't.
What the hell?
Mom.
It's me.
Dad, you're okay too, right?
Mom. Listen. Don't freak out, okay?
You're the only person
I can share this with.
Gyeong-su's dead, Mom.
Because I called him over.
I did it
in case he'd bite the others, but…
it's my fault he died.
Please let his grandma know.
Put it gently so it doesn't shock her…
too much.
Gyeong-su wanted to work part-time
at our restaurant.
But I said no because he'd try
to eat free chicken every day.
I should have just let him.
PTA DONATIONS
You killed him.
You wiped that blood
with your handkerchief.
You rubbed that
on Gyeong-su's wound, right?
Like his blood is clean?
He became a zombie.
Nam-ra, that's enough.
It's true. Na-yeon killed Gyeong-su.
-Calm down.
-How could you--
Why did you kill him?
You're… a murderer.
-Leave.
-You killed me.
Leave.
Please leave.
You killed me.
What a nice song.
You said it sucked.
Now that I actually listened to it,
I think it's nice.
That was encouraging, Dae-su.
When did you
start smoking?
Since the eighth grade.
I had no friends
and no outlet to relieve stress.
Did you ever need a friend?
I'm not sure.
I can't tell.
You always put up a wall.
You always wore earphones
and never said a word.
Wasn't it because you didn't like us?
I never disliked you guys.
I just…
didn't have any friends.
To be honest,
I didn't like you.
Because I thought you didn't talk to us
because we were beneath you.
To be honest,
there were times
when I wished you weren't around.
Aren't you two close?
You're the top two students in our school.
That's why I hated her.
No matter how hard I tried,
I was always second.
But it's okay now.
I think I was able
to come in second thanks to Nam-ra.
Hey. Second place is good too.
I can't even come in 20th
in our class. Right?
Hey.
Don't compare yourself to Joon-yeong.
I was just saying.
Why do you always jump down my throat
when I say something?
Do you like me?
Screw you.
I'll put it out there
so you don't get hurt.
I like someone else.
So don't like me.
I don't like you.
I'm not interested at all.
Dae-su. Who do you like?
He's a total freak.
-His sister.
-Ha-ri from Archery?
You're insane.
I go crazy when I'm in love.
She's like Cupid in my eyes.
Stop it.
If we get out of here alive,
I'll tell my sister.
Will you really?
-Yes.
-About what?
To shoot and kill you.
I said not to like my sister.
-Brother-in-law. You can't do that to me.
-You hog.
-Will you tell her?
-To kill you.
-Don't do that. Seriously. I love her.
-Stop it.
Gyeong-su…
Ms. Park.
It's Gyeong-su.
They're all Gyeong-su.
Na-yeon.
You were scared.
So were the others. That's all.
So make sure you go back to them later.
Go to them and tell them…
and tell Gyeong-su
that you're sorry.
Na-yeon.
Stay alive.
Stay alive…
and help your friends.
Do anything you can to help them--
Na-yeon.
It wasn't your fault.
It was my fault.
I'm sorry for cornering you.
You…
Na-yeon, you have to live.
INSTRUMENT STORAGE
My mom and dad
prepared everything for my transfer.
They said to just go to Seoul.
But I really didn't want to go.
I wouldn't have any friends,
and I was afraid of Seoul kids.
I didn't know what to do.
Then On-jo gave me a great idea.
She said to cut school for five days.
Then the principal couldn't write
a recommendation.
That's why I cut school.
It's all thanks to On-jo…
that I didn't transfer.
But I should've just gone.
Then this wouldn't have happened to me.
My sister was told
she was an archery prodigy
ever since she was a child.
So our family only cared about
whether or not she made it
onto the national team.
They gave me no attention.
I give you attention, brother-in-law.
Don't be sad. You have me--
Thank God I have Dae-su.
I don't really have anything to say.
I wouldn't really know…
but I feel like I made friends.
On-jo
and I…
What's that?
-What are you doing here?
-Me?
I have to go to the rooftop,
but the door's locked.
So I'm going to go that way.
-You're not a zombie, right?
-Zombie? Fuck that.
Is that food?
Are you hungry?
Are you?
Me too.
I just…
I just want some water.
Not things like that.
Be completely honest.
Be completely honest. Do you like someone?
-Yes.
-Really? You do?
Yes.
Why are you stalling? Is it a crush?
Pretty much.
Pretty much? What does that mean?
Who is she?
No one.
Do I know her?
Who?
You.
You, On-jo.
I like you.
Hey. Stop that.
He doesn't mean it. He's just kidding.
We were friends and neighbors
since kindergarten, that's all.
Stop joking.
I'm not joking.
I've liked you every day
for the past 12 years
since we were six years old.
And I'll continue to.
Shocking.
Cheong-san.
-Did you know? I had no idea.
-You're the only one who didn't know.
-Everyone knew?
-Yes.
Why didn't I know?
-I didn't either.
-Because you're you.
Cheong-san's so cool.
On-jo.
I'm sorry.
You don't have to like me.
Stop.
I'm done.
I said it all, so it's all good.
How is it all good? You jerk.
You were my best friend.
I-sak's gone, and you're gone.
What do you want me to do?
Have you… never liked me?
Not even by mistake?
Not even once?
Would you please go away?
I want to be alone.
You don't have to like me.
On-jo!
-Cheong-san!
-What the hell?
Give me your eye, asshole.
ALL CHARACTERS, ORGANIZATIONS,
LOCATIONS, INSTITUTIONS,
AND EVENTS IN THIS SHOW ARE FICTIONAL.
Subtitle translation by: Jeong Lee