PROVIDING AN EDUCATION
THAT WARMS AND STRENGTHENS LIVES
DOOR WILL OPEN AUTOMATICALLY
IN CASE OF FIRE
EMERGENCY DOOR AUTOMATIC LOCK
HYOSAN HIGH SCHOOL
WE ROOT FOR
THE HYOSAN HIGH SCHOOL ARCHERY TEAM
REALTY
WOOGYEONG GIRLS' MIDDLE SCHOOL
HYOSAN ARTS CENTER
MYEONHAK-DONG
HYOSAN HIGH SCHOOL
MUNPYEONG DAYCARE
Let's go once it's over
Let's go anywhere
Once we're done studying 12 hours a day
Once the annoying sounds are over
Let's go hand in hand
Let's not run
Let's try walking slowly
Is that drool or sweat pooled on the book?
No one notices the plop, plop
The plop, plop
The falling raindrops
What is boiling? Simmer, simmer
It's Mom's doenjang stew
A bowl of instant noodles
In front of the TV
Which plays nothing but static
Let's go anywhere together
Chicken tastes better fried in olive oil
Pork tastes better than soy meat
What makes me laugh, laugh, laugh
Is trans fat
PTA DONATIONS
INSTRUMENT STORAGE
ALL CHARACTERS, LOCATIONS, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND EVENTS IN THIS SHOW ARE FICTIONAL.
Subtitle translation by: Jeong Lee