Oh, Dad.
You…
Let me see you.
Get out!
Damn it.
Not here.
Who are you?
How did you get in?
I heard something.
I thought it was in here.
Out of my way.
Where were you? Is it okay there?
It's okay everywhere. I love it.
The school is heaven.
-Later.
-Where are you going?
You'll die if you go out.
Don't go out, asshole!
Do as I say.
Are you hungry?
What?
You…
hungry?
I'm starving.
I'm full right now.
So you get to live.
Count yourself lucky.
What is that smell?
Why do you smell like them?
What? What do you smell?
Let go of me.
You were with Cheong-san, weren't you?
Who's that?
-Where is he?
-What are you talking about?
You wanna know?
Are you okay?
Are you hurt, On-jo?
What took you so long?
I kept waiting for you.
And you kids, are you okay?
Yeah.
Good.
Cheong-san.
Mr. Nam.
Okay. Are you all able to run?
-Yeah.
Good.
Okay. If you go straight
through the tennis courts
and pass the construction site,
you'll hit the mountain.
If you cross the mountain…
…and get to Yangdong--
Mr. Nam!
Dad, no!
Kids. Run!
Shit.
GYMNASIUM
Hurry!
Come on.
Run! Go! Run!
To the tennis courts!
Hurry up!
Go! Go! Get in.
Get in.
Get in! Get in!
Run!
Hey, hey, hey. Wait.
We can't go out there.
We can't go anywhere.
-What should we do, Dae-su?
-Damn it.
What do we do?
-Oh, shit!
-What now?
Step back.
Let's go.
Hurry.
Cheong-san…
Take On-jo with you.
But why?
Dad, where are you going?
Dad. Dad!
Dad!
Dad, no!
Dad, come back!
Run!
Get out! Get out now!
Get out!
Mr. Nam!
Go. Go! Get out!
Hurry. Go.
Why are you?
Dad?
On-jo, look at me.
Go.
Run! Go.
-Go!
-Dad.
Go!
On-jo! Go…
Run.
Dad…
Go, On-jo!
Run!
Dad!
CONSTRUCTION NOTICE
Hurry!
Stop!
Why, why, why?
Go upstairs. Go!
Hurry! To the second floor!
Hurry!
Where do we go?
There's no way out. It's blocked.
There's nothing here.
Go through this way!
-Can we go?
-Let's go out this way.
Get back.
Hurry up.
Shit.
DO YOUR WORK STEP BY STEP
HASTE CAUSES ACCIDENTS
Careful.
Stay away from the edge.
Uh-huh.
-Here. Come here.
-Quiet.
Don't make any noise.
On-jo! Go!
Dad!
It's okay.
Just cry.
It's better to just die.
This virus changes
a person into a different being.
The person I loved
becomes a monster.
You can forget someone who dies…
but it's hard to forget someone
who has changed.
To think that's the very last image
of the people…
I loved the most.
Remember now?
I don't know anyone
named Cheong-san, you freak.
Everyone went to the assembly hall,
and I got out by myself.
The hall?
I don't know who Cheong-san is.
We went with some juniors. That's all.
That means the others are still there.
You're fucking brave.
You'd better run.
Or I'll eat you.
I told you to run. Why didn't you listen?
Damn it. Nothing is working out.
We keep hitting dead ends.
Would you just be quiet?
It's your fault Joon-yeong died.
Dae-su. Don't.
If you hadn't bitched at him
and just shut up,
he would never have jumped out there.
Okay. It is my fault. Happy?
Are you happy, asshole?
You give it a rest too.
Dae-su.
What does it matter who's responsible
for someone's death?
What does living
and dying even mean?
I don't know.
If we make it out,
will it really be living?
Hey, you know our friends died.
And our parents too.
What's the point?
Do you wanna die?
Then will you die?
Try being a senior.
Then you'll really wanna die.
Yeah, big deal, you're a senior.
You try being one.
You'll see what it's like.
You kids.
You better survive till next year
and see what it's like being seniors.
Survive until next year
and tell me which is harder,
zombies or senior year.
Hey.
Your father, he…
He saved all of our lives, you know.
I'll never forget what he did.
None of us ever will.
If many people remembered someone,
that person…
is sure to go to heaven.
Mm-hmm.
Mi-jin.
Let's go.
Where? Why?
Let's look for a good spot
where we can jump off.
We're the oldest.
Sure. Whatever.
It's not like we get any respect.
I'll go this way. You go that way.
She's so cool.
I'll go.
Stay down, kid.
It's okay.
You little…
Get away.
Oh, shit.
I hope no one steps up anymore.
Whatever ends up happening…
I hope no one sacrifices themselves.
It's too hard living for someone.
When there's nothing
you can do for them at all.
It's like you have
to live extra heart for them.
It's too selfish.
You can't die and…
if you don't have the courage to live.
Let's…
talk a little later, okay?
Tomorrow or the next day.
Or maybe even next week.
Let's eat, take a bath
and then we can talk about it.
That's what we agreed to do, right?
That side.
What?
You probably don't remember.
Cheong-san, hold on.
Is it better like this?
Or like this?
Look close. Like this? Or like this?
That side is better.
Left.
What do you mean by that?
I'll tell you tomorrow.
Cheong-san.
ONE HEART
That moron became a zombie.
Watch as we raised the frequency to 24kHz.
Based on tests
that we ran previously in Hyosan,
they respond most at 24kHz.
Let's begin the briefing.
We plan to emit sounds using drones
to lure the infected
into target locations.
This will allow us
to maximize the resulting impact
with minimal explosion.
The targets…
Hyosan Intersection, the sports complex,
Hyosan High, Hyosan Future College.
A total of four.
Expected damage.
Out of 170,000 residents,
110 are in various quarantine camps.
Sixty thousand casualties estimated.
Among them,
we estimate 50,000 are infected
and 10,000 are uninfected or asymptomatic.
We'll send soldiers after the explosion
to evacuate whoever is left.
Play the evacuation warning nonstop
until the explosions are detonated.
Eat him.
It's okay. Eat him.
I'm hungry.
It's okay.
It's not okay.
Yes, it is.
If it happens again,
bite me instead.
If you bite me, I'll end up like you.
I really think that
that's the only way out.
No. It drops into
the basement on that side,
and there are exposed steel bars.
No way we can jump.
That side faces the school,
so there's no point trying it.
The ground is filled with zombies,
we'll die if we go down.
There's a door on the first floor
that leads to the mountain.
We have to go that way.
But it's full of zombies in there.
Can't we reach the roof
if we use that and the windows?
If someone goes to the roof and screams,
the zombies will follow them.
Then I'm pretty sure it'll empty out
in there, and the rest can escape.
I think it can work.
No.
-If that's the only way--
-I said no.
Please stop sacrificing yourselves.
Yeah, I agree with you.
We said we'd all survive together.
Me too.
I feel the same.
I'm with you guys too.
Then we should just wait for now.
And then what?
Do you have a plan?
Maybe if it rains again,
they won't be able to hear us.
Who knows when it's gonna rain?
Don't worry. My knees are throbbing.
It's gonna rain soon.
You'll see.
It's way too clear.
Hear that?
What?
They're saying to take cover.
Who is?
This is a public announcement.
Explosives will be detonated
at the sports complex,
Hyosan High School, Future College,
and Hyosan Intersection.
If you hear this, take shelter
in subways and underground garages.
We need to take cover.
There will be explosions.
What do you mean explosions?
Are you sure about that?
Hyosan Intersection,
Future College…
…and also our school will be blown up.
Hey, are those fucking soldiers
gonna shoot missiles at us?
When is it gonna happen?
I can't really tell.
They're just saying to evacuate right now.
Shit. Where are they expect us to go, huh?
When are they gonna bomb
this whole place, huh?
Initiate operation.
Activate the sound.
Send in all the drones.
CHEONGSAN CHICKEN
CHICKEN AND BEER
Won't we all die if we just stay here?
Do they say where to flee to?
They say that we should hide underground.
What if they drop a nuclear bomb?
Korea doesn't have nukes.
What are you saying?
-Huh?
-Whatever.
They're gonna blow up our school.
Where are we supposed to take cover?
There's nowhere to hide.
Cheong-san!
What?
It's Gwi-nam.
That asshole never dies.
Who's that?
Maybe we heard wrong?
It's quiet now.
Here you are.
-What the hell?
-Cheong-san!
Cheong-san! No!
Cheong-san!
No.
Help! Hurry!
Come on. Shit.
-Cheong-san!
-Don't!
Sir, they've all arrived at the targets.
Execute.
Let me confirm the order, sir.
Fire now!
It's okay.
It's not what you think. It's okay.
Do you hear me?
Don't do it.
You're going to be fine.
On-jo.
No one's dying.
Not here. Not today.
I just…
Just don't say anything.
Let's talk tomorrow, okay? Mm-hmm?
LEE CHEONG-SAN
You hold on to it for me.
And I'll hold onto this.
LEE CHEONG-SAN, NAM ON-JO
Su-hyeok, go to the first floor.
Cheong-san!
Hey!
All of you.
Come after to me!
Today I am…
…the happiest guy in this school!
Hey!
Come on, everyone. This is it.
We have to go.
Nam-ra, let's go.
Come on.
Can you climb up?
Okay. Come down.
Hurry.
Hey!
-Hurry. Hurry, hurry.
-Let's go faster. Come on.
Hey!
CAUTION, RISK OF ACCIDENT
Come at me now.
All of you!
WARNING: NO TRESPASSING
PRIVATE PROPERTY OWNED BY THE SCHOOL
Come on, come on.
Go, go, go.
You know,
I thought it was gonna be super fun
to kill you.
But not anymore.
I'll kill you even if it isn't fun.
Stop acting tough.
What do you think? You look cool?
Nobody thinks that way.
You're just scared
because you'll get caught
for killing the principal.
You're still a coward and a loser.
I have nothing to fear.
I'm not scared of you, either.
I'll gouge out your eye.
Run away.
I'll let you live if you run.
The Sports complex. Bombing complete.
Hyosan Intersection. Bombing complete.
Future College. Bombing complete.
Ah, shit.
Ha-ri!
Are you okay?
Commander.
Commander. Operation, complete.
Sure. Okay.
Send in the troops in the early morning
to take care of the rest.
You're in charge now, officer.
You want me to?
You'll do a good job.
I need a sleep.
I've been up for too long.
You're here to chat?
Or you came to watch?
I came to tell you,
Hyosan was bombed last night.
What was that?
Forty percent of the population
of Hyosan has perished.
You're a murderer.
You should be ashamed of yourself.
I thought about it.
Could anyone…
offered comfort to the people
of Hyosan now?
That is why I came to see you.
Please tell the people of Hyosan…
that I'm truly sorry.
JIN SEON-MOO
This morning,
I watched the final video
of Lee Byeong-chan,
the man who created the virus in his lab.
He tried to save his wife and son
who had already been infected
by the virus,
but he failed.
What he did was his last resort.
Jin-su.
Honey…
Please stop!
I respect the decision he made.
Lee Byeong-chan was a father
and a husband.
I'm sure he couldn't kill anyone.
However, I am a soldier.
So today,
I ordered the bombing
of the city of Hyosan.
No one else has instructed me to attack.
No one ordered me to do anything.
It was my decision and mine alone
as the martial law commander.
I take full responsibility.
WIFE
Hi, it's me.
Did you eat?
Look at the time.
How come you haven't eaten dinner yet?
And the kids?
Mm-hmm.
It's not a big deal
if they miss school a few times.
Better to stay healthy, right?
Yeah.
Well, I guess
we can just look for a tutor.
Mm-hmm.
It doesn't matter if it is expensive.
Okay, well. Maybe not too expensive.
Mm-hmm.
Well, honey.
I miss you.
Hmm?
I'm so sorry.
I love you.
WIFE: I'M SORRY I YELLED AT YOU
I LOVE YOU TOO
WIFE: WHEN CAN YOU COME HOME?
NAM ON-JO
ALL CHARACTERS, LOCATIONS, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND EVENTS IN THIS SHOW ARE FICTIONAL.
Subtitle translation by: Jeong Lee
Ripped by TTEOKBOKKIsubs