A virus, huh?
So you're telling me,
that this whole mess started with a virus
made by a high school science teacher?
This virus.
Tell me why?
Why would you do something like this?
Detective.
Do you have any kids?
Yes, sweetheart.
Yun-a.
Oh, no. Be careful.
You should watch where you're going.
Could you let your child die?
No parent on Earth could do that.
I don't wanna hear that bullshit.
Just answer the question.
What is the virus and how...
Jae-ik. Code red.
Chief needs everyone right now.
Come on, hurry.
It's too late.
We're all dead.
There's no hope for survival.
Oh, shit.
Cheong-san!
Look down. Down, down, down.
I know.
She's got your foot, moron. Look!
- I see that.
- Kick her off or something, idiot.
I'm trying.
What the hell is it taking you so long?
Hey!
Hey. I'm coming down.
No, stay there.
No. I said, don't do it.
- I'm coming.
- Don't!
- Stay there.
- Oh, shit.
Hold on.
Hey, Bare-su, look up.
My back.
Just stay still. I'm helping.
What are you doing?
Hold on, moron.
- Guys, look, Bare-su. Bare-su!
- Cheong-san!
Hang on, Bare-su!
Are you okay?
Shit. Why can't you just kick her...
...like I said?
Hey. Stop hugging me.
I'm not hugging you.
Fuck off.
You like it?
- Are you okay?
- Close it.
Close it before they get in!
Would you just close it already?
What's wrong with you?
Cheong-san still out there.
You want us just to shut him out?
Is it a crime to want the window close?
How can you be so selfish?
I can't stand you, stupid welfie.
- What did you just call me?
- Hey, come on.
What's happening?
- You just hit me?
- Yeah.
Call me that again.
Hey, knock it off.
What's going on over here, guys?
He just hit me.
Only 'cause you called me a welfie.
- Is it not true?
- You just can't say shit like that.
What's a welfie?
Tell me.
What is it?
What's a welfie?
A person on welfare.
- What?
- It means, a person on welfare.
"Welfie" for short.
Na-yeon, that was wrong.
Don't ever say that again.
And Gyeong-su.
When you hit people,
you're the one who ends up losing.
- Do you understand?
- No, I don't.
Listen, we can't be fighting
each other in a moment like this.
We don't know what's going on
out there with those...
Are they zombies?
What about the other teachers?
Has anyone called the cops?
Don't worry, I'm sure someone already has.
I just don't have
my phone on me, right now.
We called them, but they're not coming.
Neither the police nor first responders.
I'm sure they'll be here soon.
We just have to wait a little longer.
Ms. Park. Hyeon-ju's hands were cold too.
So were I-sak's.
What if all of this started with Hyeon-ju?
She went to the hospital.
What if it spread in there as well?
Maybe that's why no one's coming.
But wait. They still work, right?
Uh, internet. The internet.
- Let's see. Sorry, Ms. Park.
- Oh.
- Here. Sit.
- Thanks.
It should work. Is it on?
I think so.
What's the problem?
Why is it not turning on?
- It just did.
- Oh, sorry.
School ones are so slow.
Maybe it's not online?
It must be.
It's gonna take all day.
Is it still loading?
- Su-hyeok, did you see it?
- I don't think it's working.
What?
In the science lab.
SU-HYEOK, WE'RE IN THE
BROADCASTING ROOM - NAM-RA
Well, I was actually in the art room.
What's in the science lab?
Uh, well...
It worked.
- Okay. Open the browser.
- The browser.
Look up "zombie virus."
- Yeah, "zombie virus."
- But...
- No. Try "Hyosan."
- See what's trending.
No.
- I'm checking the news first.
- Look up the emergence alerts.
- The news.
- There'll be no articles yet.
- Yeah, go to the news.
- What are we looking up?
See you later.
- Are you okay? Let me help you.
- Come on.
Stand up. Can you stand?
- Call an ambulance.
- Let's get out of the way first.
- See that?
- What's going on?
Sir, are you all right? Do you need help?
Oh, shit.
No. No, please!
I'll try Facebook.
Or Instagram.
Do you have followers?
Let's do Facebook.
Hmm...
Okay.
How many friends do you have?
Look at your notifications.1,700?
Strange.
Okay, let's check messages first.
- What the hell?
- Oh, shit.
What was that?
Get over here. Come here.
Did someone not make it in?
No. No one.
Wait. Don't go too close!
Cheong-san.
Be careful.
Do you see anything?
It's just the wind.
That scared me.
Look, it's coming in!
Watch out, watch out!
Cheong-san, get back. Get back here.
Look out, look out!
Cheong-san!
- Cheong-san!
- Get back here!
Wait. w-w-wait, wait!
- Push it! Push it off.
- Did you get it?
Push it!
Push it off.
Push it off!
Push it! Come on.
Go! Harder!
- Watch out!
- Remove her hand!
Shit!
Stay back!
Don't go near it!
- Should I go?
- Stay back.
No. Hold on.
Go, Dae-su.
Give me.
Shit. We're completely fucked.
Just push it!
Push it! Push it off!
Push it away already!
- It's coming in.
- Su-hyeok! Watch out for your hand!
Su-hyeok! Fuck it!
Is it gone?
That was crazy.
I'm so dead.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm good.
Where did it come from?
- Hey, you good?
- That was scary. I'm good.
Hey.
You...
RESCUE
HYOSAN CITY COUNCIL
You have to understand
he's the youngest aide we have.
When he got back from the Council building
he just collapsed and started convulsing.
Captain. He smells like a rotting corpse.
And then he got back up, and went like...
...and just attacked Assemblywoman
out of nowhere.
So we tied him up to that chair.
But we didn't know
if we should call the police. You know?
Why are you telling them that?
He'll bite his tongue.
- We have to gag him.
- Copy.
- Ready?
- Yes.
One, two, three.
- Did it get you?
- It's okay. A little.
Wrap him up!
Now.
Message from headquarters. Come in.
Rescue Team One.
Level-three disaster in Hyosan.
Report to temporary headquarters.
Did you say level-three disaster?
I repeat.
Level-three disaster in Hyosan.
Report to temporary headquarters.
What is it?
- This is the director's order.
- Where are they sending you?
- Mobilize immediately. That is all.
- Uh...
The fire department headquarters
was moved out of the city
for an emergency.
The Disaster and Safety Control
will manage the situation.
Is evacuation really necessary?
All right. All right, all right. Hang on.
Okay, so they think
it's an acute infection.
They're saying there will be
an evacuation order for Hyosan soon.
Gyeong-su, you're bleeding.
I am?
Right, it's because
Su-hyeok hit me with a fucking mop.
Stay back. Stay where you are.
You were bitten, weren't you, Gyeong-su?
I wasn't. I wasn't.
Didn't you see Su-hyeok hit me?
What is your fucking problem with me?
You were bitten!
I-sak got a nosebleed
just before she turned.
On-jo. You saw it, right?
That's the same thing
that happened to I-sak.
Gyeong-su.
I-I'm telling you! I swear I wasn't bit!
Shit.
Look.
Your hand. Explain that?
What is it?
I got it from the computer.
Didn't you see that?
Don't you trust me?
I can't believe this.
I got this trying to save all of you.
It's not a bite. It's a scratch.
Whoever wants to check, come look.
It's a scratch?
Yeah, definitely. Just a scratch.
- Ms. Park, look.
- Mm.
Well, it really doesn't look like a bite.
Thank god. It's a scratch.
He's okay.
Done yet?
I said, are you done with me now?
Wait. This means the computer's gone.
No internet...
Couldn't you have thrown something else
instead of the computer?
What was I supposed to do?
It's trying to get in.
No, you did good. Thank you. Don't be mad.
Hey, Na-yeon.
Look. Say sorry. End this.
Why should I?
He did it to save us all.
Why can't you just say that you're sorry?
Because I'm not sorry.
I saw everything.
I saw the creature grabbed you.
I'm right.
He could be infected.
Na-yeon, enough.
It really did.
That thing grabbed his hand.
Wait, can touching his hand infect him?
I have no idea but maybe.
I held I-sak's hand when she fell.
Why is nothing happening to me?
Because he has a cut on his hand.
And since there's an open wound,
it's probably gonna be different.
- That's fucking...
- Don't.
Stop blaming me.
Why don't you just think for yourselves?
Na-yeon.
I know you always hated Gyeong-su,
but I think you're really crossing
the line here.
This is about life and death.
She's always like this.
If it weren't for him,
we would definitely all be dead right now.
And now, he might be the one
killing all of us.
Now you're the one who's killing me.
- Just shut up, Na-yeon.
- Look at my hand, I'm totally fine.
- Don't you see that?
- Hey, that's enough, all of you! Okay?
We're ending this.
- Ms. Park...
- Enough.
- But she...
- No!
Let's do this.
Gyeong-su, you're going to wait
in the recording room for ten minutes.
I know it'll be hard,
but at least it's better
than people thinking you're infected.
No one else thinks that I'm infected.
It's only her.
Gyeong-su, would you please do it?
Fuck ten. I'll do half...
I'll just do a full hour.
There's really no point doing an hour
since it takes less than five minutes.
- Stop overreacting.
- It's just to be sure.
Is that enough?
And if nothing happens,
you'll apologize, right?
Yeah.
And everyone else
is okay with that, right?
Yes.
If we do this,
who's gonna step up next time?
We all be too scared.
You're right, but...
Let's consider this a way
to learn to trust each other.
I do... trust Gyeong-su.
See you in an hour.
Want me to come with you?
What a stubborn asshole.
He only needs to do ten.
He's not that stubborn.
Compared to her.
- Go get it.
- No. I won't.
You stupid little...
Stop. Please.
Go, asshole.
Move. Please don't.
Hey, kid. Down here. Come.
Fuck.
HYOSAN HIGH SCHOOL
Maybe they're drawn to smell.
They do always go after you.
I don't smell.
You sweat a lot, Dae-su.
I sweat, but I don't smell.
What's that smell?
Your sweat.
I think they're more sensitive
to sound than smell.
- Sound?
- Yeah, sound.
This isn't a movie.
That's just how zombies are, you know?
And didn't you see their eyes?
They can't see with those eyes.
- Ms. Park.
- Hmm?
Sound, smell, I don't know.
Some kids probably left school, right?
It's sound.
Mm-hm. Yeah, I think so.
Here, Su-hyeok.
Give me the mirror.
Maybe we're the lucky ones then?
The fact that we're alive
makes us lucky.
Really?
Mm-hm.
Wipe your face.
Are you okay?
I keep thinking about I-sak.
You held on...
until the last possible second.
Stop. That doesn't help.
You didn't do anything wrong.
Stay strong.
Your dad or someone else...
will come save us.
FRIED CHICKEN RESTAURANT
CHEONGSAN CHICKEN
CHICKEN AND BEER
Oh, for heaven's sake.
Do you have to put
your son's face on the sign?
Is there something wrong
with using his face?
You'll end up becoming
an evil mother-in-law.
All protective of your precious son.
Nagged your daughter-in-law constantly.
Anyway, uh...
better go submit these forms.
The series of incidents
occurring in Hyosan
appear to be due to a mass outbreak
of a highly infectious virus.
We'll speak to the
Disease Control Center for more details.
Director Cha Hyeon-seok,
can you tell us what's going on?
Considering the level of spread,
it appears to be
a highly infectious disease.
Those infected
became unusually aggressive.
Victims showed similar symptoms,
so we suspect secondary infection
is possible.
As you've heard, this is very dangerous.
As advised by the KDCA,
the government has raised
the infectious disease alert to "serious."
They stated that
they will do everything possible
to prevent the spreading
outside of Hyosan.
Breaking news. Just in.
The National Security Council
has officially declared
an evacuation order in place
for Hyosan City in Gyeonggi Province.
If you are watching this, please be aware.
You are under evacuation.
Please leave the city immediately.
I repeat. The situation
is extremely serious.
The National Security Council has decided
to issue an evacuation order for the city
of Hyosan in Gyeonggi province.
If you're watching this,
please evacuate the city.
The situation is extremely dangerous.
Hey, I'm just going
to step out for a minute.
Okay.
Are you all right?
Yeah, yeah. I'm fine.
l should be back soon.
A virus?
What kind of virus?
I don't think it's airborne,
but it hasn't been confirmed.
It seems like you
get infected if you get bit,
so don't get bit or make physical contact.
We don't know
how much about the virus yet,
so just avoid as much as you can.
I hear an assembly member is there.
- Hold still.
- Who is it?
Yeong-hwan.
What the...
Yeong-hwan, hey, are you okay?
Captain, what do I do?
Yeong-hwan!
Yeong-hwan.
That, that, that's exactly what happened
to our aide, I'm telling you.
It's the same thing.
Oh, shit.
Is he dead?
U-sin!
Rope!
- Hurry!
- Tie him up!
Tie him up! Now!
Approximately
200 infected at Hyosan Intersection.
Unit 1030, 1040, 1050.
Move to Hyosan Intersection.
Copy that.
This is Unit 1030.
Heading to Hyosan Intersection.
Brace for impact!
Go join the line!
Block them!
Stand firm!
Join the line!
Hey!
Stop! Stop wait.
- Turn around. You can't go through there.
- I'll be fast. I need to get through.
What's going on?
She says she needs to get through, sir.
Ma'am, you have to turn back.
- But my son...
- You need to evacuate.
- Get her out.
- Yes, sir.
- No. Wait.
- Come on. Let's go.
- You need to leave.
- Lady, please.
- Wait. My son, Cheong-san. Wait, please.
- Come on. Let's go.
You go to Hyosan High?
What are you doing here?
Is the school okay?
Hey. Wait.
Do you know my son, Cheong-san?
Lee Cheong-san? Do you know him?
Oh, no.
Hey. Lift me higher.
I can't go any higher.
Stand on your toes.
I am.
Do you see anything?
Oh, shit.
There's a lot of zombies out there.
- Put me down.
- Okay.
Be careful. Careful.
Okay.
Why is this so hard?
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
What do we do?
Well, first...
- You got a cigarette?
- No, I don't smoke.
Shit, you look like you do.
Hey, What about you?
I don't smoke.
- Don't mess with me.
- I don't.
Why are you being rude to upperclassman?
Wanna die?
What the hell do you want?
Hey. Who said you can talk like that
to an upperclassman?
- Sorry.
- No.
To me, not to her.
God, why are athletes
always such douchebags?
Watch your mouth.
Watch yourself.
You're really going
to fight over these now, huh?
What are you, stupid?
Just get along already.
I'm sorry.
I said I was sorry, okay?
We got to go.
How can we leave?
If they see us,
they're gonna attack us all.
If you wanna leave, go ahead.
I'm not going.
- You?
- Leave me alone.
I do whatever I feel like.
Heartless bitch.
Here. Make weapons.
Come on.
Give me that.
Freak.
Han Gyeong-su.
I'll kill you.
What a fucking idiot.
What are you doing?
Thirty minutes.
What's that?
It's been 30 minutes. Come out.
Ms. Park. It's been more than 30 minutes,
but he still doesn't want to come out.
I'll see what I can do.
What's wrong with him?
Looks okay to me.
He's fine. I knew it.
I don't understand
why he's being so stubborn?
He won't come out?
He's always like this.
He's too stubborn.
Huh?
So what did he say?
He won't come out?
He said he's staying the full hour.
He's pissed.
I'll go in.
Why would you go?
If anyone should, it's Na-yeon.
Why should I?
He's like this because of you.
- What did I do?
- Like you don't know?
Was it wrong to suspect him?
You did too. Everyone did.
It wasn't just me.
I always believe him.
Me too.
Well, I didn't. She's right.
But I didn't insult him like you did.
Why are you picking on me?
'Cause you deserve it.
That's enough, Ji-min.
You remember your promise, right?
After 30 minutes you'd apologize.
Okay.
It's been 30 minutes.
All right.
She's doing it. Holy shit.
She's really doing it.
Hey.
I'm talking to you.
You're ignoring me?
What do you want?
Oh, yo. They're talking.
That's good. Right?
Why don't you answer me?
Apologize and get out.
How's your cut doing?
Why do you care?
Show me.
Oh, shit. She's touching him.
Well, that's pretty bold of her.
I suspected you
because the situation called for it.
And I was really mad earlier.
I'm still mad at you.
I guess...
She's Gyeong-su type?
I have no idea.
You know I've always looked down on you.
It's fine. It's all in the past.
Let's just go.
I'm not apologizing.
You deserve to be looked down on.
Our complex banned you welfies,
but you force your way in.
And how dare you push me?
Listen, you fucking...
You thought I'd apologize?
Kiss, kiss.
This is so crazy.
Everyone is taking your side.
I was cornered
because of a nobody like you.
Stay the full hour.
I hope you never come out again.
Fucking welfie.
Oh, they're coming.
They're coming.
Hey!
How cute was that? So cute... Whoa, whoa!
- Gyeong-su!
- Come here you piece of...
- Wait, wait, what?
- Gyeong-su, what's wrong?
You're fucking...
you're such a fucking cheat.
- I don't understand why I have to take it?
- Did you really say that?
You promised me you'd apologize to him.
- Dude, forget about her.
- I did nothing wrong.
You only think about yourself.
You said to close the door
before anyone could get in.
You said it would be safer for us.
That's not right.
We almost died
when Gyeong-su pulled Coach Kang in.
Why aren't you mad at him?
That was not his fault.
How is he supposed to know that
that was gonna happen?
- That's enough. Quiet, everyone.
- We'd be quiet if she were gone.
You're all so annoying.
What if I'm right about this?
Then will you finally admit
I saved you all, huh?
I don't understand.
How can you still be like this?
Look.
Guess I was right after all.
What?
Gyeong-su.
Day 26 of infection.
I told you didn't I?
You still think I'm wrong?
The strong cells are attacking
the hosts weak cells.
Every single cell
is struggling just to survive...
they're attacking each other.
This virus in essence
is like the will to live.
It consumes all cells almost instantly.
Hey, hey. What's wrong with me?
Something's wrong.
Oh, shit.
What's wrong?
It's not true.
Come on. Get rid of him.
Get rid of him now!
- I'm not...
- Gyeong-su. Stay where you are.
Stay back.
I swear fucking I'm not.
I'm sorry, Gyeong-su.
Please, stay back.
I've turned, right?
Cheong-san, what do I do?
No, no. This doesn't make any sense.
Why would you...
Cheong-san.
Let go.
This cannot be true.
Why would you suddenly...
The infected human
feels extreme fear...
and then they attack in order to survive.
No, no. Gyeong-su you weren't...
Stay away. Don't come any closer!
What are you doing?
We need to kick him out.
We're all gonna die!
What...
What's happening...
Fuck.
Get out. I said, get out!
Shut the fuck up!
I'll leave by myself.
I'll leave. I'll go on my own.
Why would I bite you?
We're supposed to be fucking friends.
We're friends.
If I... If I leave,
it will be better for everyone.
Gyeong-su... why don't you just go back
into the recording room
until we can figure out...
If he stays in here
he's gonna kill us all.
Na-yeon!
I'm just trying to stay alive.
I'll leave.
I'll get out of here on my own.
Don't worry.
I'll get out of here.
Gyeong-su.
It's okay.
Thank you for everything.
Stay alive.
- Are you all right, Gyeong-su?
- Stay alive.
What an idiot.
What are you looking at?
Why are you doing that?
You're scaring me. Stop,
Stop it. Cheong-san,
why are you doing this?
Stop it! Please stop!
CHEONGSAN CHICKEN
CONGRATULATIONS
ON YOUR NEW BEGINNING
- Lift it.
- Okay.
Here.
One more.
Fire and Disasters Headquarters
said not to touch the infected.
As you can see, it's highly contagious...
We were notified too, no need to explain.
How long do we have to stay here?
They're sending over a helicopter,
but it's gonna take time.
So it looks like
you'll have to wait a bit longer.
Did you notify them
that I was here as well?
What?
I'm asking if it's taking time
to get a chopper
even though they know I'm here?
No, I did not tell them who was here.
You should've told them.
That way, they'll send one
right away to pick us up.
Per rules of rescue, the weak and ill
take priority over VIPs.
We'll hear back soon,
so please be patient like everyone else.
Shit.
ON-JO'S HOMEROOM TEACHER
The person you have called
is currently unavailable.
This is Captain Nam So-ju.
If anyone knows the status
of Hyosan High School,
please respond.
If anyone knows anything
about the area near Hyosan High School
please respond.
Please respond.
KOREA
RESCUE
That asshole.
Gyeong-su...
...why did you have to turn?
I told you all.
He was infected.
Well, are you happy now?
You were all wrong.
Only I was right.
What would you even do without me?
Hey.
Maybe you did it.
What?
I saw everything.
Na-yeon...
What? What did you see?
You are the one who did it.
Who did what?
I didn't do anything to Gyeong-su.
I didn't say anything about Gyeong-su.
Knock it off.
What do you talking about?
I didn't do anything.
While we were all watching Gyeong-su,
you were in the back alone.
Ms. Park. It's been more than 30 minutes,
but he still doesn't want to come out.
I'll see what I can do.
What's wrong with him?
Looks okay to me.
Why is he not coming out then?
He won't come out?
I don't understand
why he's being so stubborn?
He's too stubborn.
He's always like this.
You wiped that blood
with your handkerchief.
No, I didn't.
You wiped that
on the scratches on Gyeong-su's hand.
- I did not.
- It's in your pocket.
- So what?
- Take it out.
- No.
I said no.
Should I take it out?
Fuck you!
Who the hell do you think you are?
Class president?
You never treated me like president.
Nam-ra, that's enough.
Nam-ra, do you realize
what you're saying right now?
If that is true,
it means Na-yeon killed Gyeong-su.
It's true.
Na-yeon did it.
She killed him.
You fucking cunt.
There.
Happy?
This is blood.
I wiped Gyeong-su's hand.
This is his blood?
You can't tell?
Then put it on your wound.
Wipe yourself with it
if you're so confident.
Like his blood is so clean?
He was a zombie.
He was just fine until you infected him
with your handkerchief.
Na-yeon, you...
Damn it! It wasn't me!
Don't do it. Stop it.
Let go.
I said to stop it.
Give it to me.
Leave me alone! Fuck!
I should just die too then, huh?
That's what you want, isn't it?
Why is Gyeong-su better than me?
That dirty welfie pushed me.
Na-yeon, you didn't...
So, you did do it.
How could you just fucking...
I didn't kill him, okay?
Gyeong-su fell, but he got up and ran.
He's still alive.
He didn't die, he just turned.
Are you kidding me right now?
Stop ganging up on me.
When I said he smelled, you all laughed.
You all made fun of him too.
Don't try to act innocent now.
- Na-yeon...
- Cheong-san, stop.
How could you kill him?
Stop it.
You're...
a murderer.
I...
I have no friends at all.
I don't need any of you.
Fuck you.
Hey!
Listen...
No matter what happens, you stay alive.
Also, you must never take a life.
If you cause
someone else to die,
life becomes completely meaningless.
All right?
Ms. Park! Wait.
Dae-su, don't go.
She's gone.
Fuck!
ALL CHARACTERS,
LOCATIONS, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND EVENTS IN THIS SHOW ARE FICTIONAL.