JUNG YONG-HYEON
RESCUE HEADQUARTERS
HYOSAN EPIDEMIC SPREADS OUT OF CONTROL
MARTIAL LAW DECLARED
FOR THE FIRST TIME IN 41 YEARS
STOCK PRICES PLUNGE AMID HYOSAN EPIDEMIC
KOSPI AND KOSDAQ MARKETS CRASH
HYOSAN DISTURBANCE
TRIGGERS CIRCUIT BREAKERS
NO REFUGEES FROM HYOSAN!
CO-DESTRUCTION OVER COEXISTENCE?
A CHURCH THAT LEADS TO VICTORY
STOP IT NOW!
STOP MURDERING YANGDONG CITIZENS!
REMOVE THE GOVERNMENT!
PROTECT OUR RIGHT TO LIVE
INCHEON AIRPORT RECORDS HIGHEST NUMBER
OF OUTBOUND TRAVELERS IN HISTORY
SUBWAY ZOMBIE PERFORMANCE APOLOGY STREAM
THE REPUBLIC OF KOREA
CHEONG WA DAE
SCAN FINGERPRINT OR DRAW PATTERN
EMERGENCY CALL
CONNECTING
YOU'RE NOT CONNECTED TO A NETWORK
ALL COMMUNICATIONS TO AND FROM HYOSAN
TO BE TERMINATED EFFECTIVE IMMEDIATELY
NO SIGNAL
OCTOBER 21, THURSDAY
WATER FLOW DETECTOR
NAM ON-JO
THIS DOOR DOES NOT OPEN FROM THE INSIDE
INSTRUMENT STORAGE
HELP, WE'RE IN THE BROADCASTING ROOM
AT HYOSAN HIGH SCHOOL!
ABANDONED PRISON IN A SUBURB OF HYOSAN
FIRE RESCUE HEADQUARTERS
DUE TO A VIRUS OUTBREAK,
WE ARE DISINFECTING THE PREMISES
RESCUE
RESTRICTED AREA
EXAMINATION ROOM
ONE HEART
ALL CHARACTERS, LOCATIONS, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND EVENTS IN THIS SHOW ARE FICTIONAL.
Subtitle translation by: Jeong Lee