Hey. Start recording.
Red Cone Foot.
I'll defeat you
and take over as the most powerful!
Not a chance.
Fuck! It hurts like hell!
Fuck!
-That's so funny.
-Stop it, dipshit! It fucking hurts!
-What the hell?
-What's wrong with them?
Hey, run!
What the fuck is that?
Fuck!
That's not possible.
Our students turn in their phones
so none of them could've called.
Yes.
Yes, of course. Everything is fine here.
Have a nice day.
I told you to make sure
to take their phones.
I even got you safes,
and they report a zombie outbreak?
-What's wrong with you?
-How can you say everything is fine?
It's mayhem out there.
We need emergency services
to get the kids out.
Are you the only teacher?
Are you that great?
I told you
to resolve these matters internally!
Get out. Tell the kids to go to class.
But, sir,
I don't think the kids will listen,
given the situation.
Are you deaf? Get out there.
If you'd go out and see for yourself--
Just do as you're told.
I made you the dean for a reason.
Where are you going?
Stay here and don't do anything stupid.
We should at least make
an emergency announcement.
PRINCIPAL'S OFFICE
Hey, you. What's up with your leg?
Hey! What are you--
Hey! What are you doing?
Stop it!
Hey!
What's with you?
Help!
Are you okay?
On-jo. Are you okay?
Hey!
Get up.
Move! Out of the way!
Are you okay?
-Stop!
-Let's go!
Hurry and get up there!
Over there!
Let's go.
Fuck!
Get up there!
You go first.
Fuck!
Damn it.
Get lost. Fuck.
Cheong-san!
Why aren't you coming? Come out!
On-jo.
Hurry, Cheong-san.
Run!
HYOSAN BUILDING MATERIALS
This way.
Wait for me!
Stay away. Stay away, you bastard.
I told you to stay away, you asshole.
Damn it. What's going on?
Don't open the door. Don't!
-We're not sure if they're intact.
-Let go.
Hurry up! Lock the door!
We need to open it.
Hey, open the door!
Move!
Are you okay?
On-jo!
How are things outside? Is it the same?
Hey.
-What the hell? Who are you?
-You motherfucker.
-Your brother-in-law.
-It's Dae-su.
Fuck!
They're fucking aggressive.
What happened to you?
Some crazy jerk
shot a fire extinguisher at me.
-A fire extinguisher?
-Yes, fuck.
What's going on?
Who knows?
Guys.
-It's Train to Busan.
-What are you talking about, moron?
Aren't they zombies? It's the same thing.
Why are they at school?
They should be in movies.
Come and look. I'm serious.
Do I have to?
Gyeong-su, the door!
Right.
Fuck.
What the hell?
-Hey, Bare-su!
-Push him off!
-Quick!
-It's Bare-su!
-Get in here.
-You okay?
Prez! Hurry!
-Come on!
-Behind you! Hurry!
Jump!
-Close it before anyone gets in.
-Are you okay?
It's that, isn't it?
Zombies.
EMERGENCY MEDICAL CENTER
AMBULANCE
One, two, three.
What happened to her?
She came from the school. When we arrived,
she was lethargic and was bleeding.
-When was she injured?
-We got the call half an hour ago.
Why is she unconscious?
She seemed to be having seizures at first,
but she's calm now.
You received your PhD
in cell biology in the US and returned.
You were a researcher
at a pharmaceutical company and quit,
then went into teaching.
With these qualifications,
shouldn't you be a college professor
rather than a high school teacher?
I told you to go to the hospital
and put Hyeon-ju in quarantine.
Why did a teacher abduct a student?
At the school, at that.
If I were a college professor,
a prosecutor, or a reporter,
would you have still disregarded me?
I see. So that's why you abducted her?
Because no one listened to you
or understood how you felt?
You were lonely and sad. Is that why?
Fine.
Let's stop it here.
Who cares if everyone dies?
This world and those bastards…
I can't stand bastards like you.
I hate your kind.
You commit the fucking crime,
but you blame others, society, the world.
Even when you reported your missing son.
"This world swallowed up my son."
Yeah, right. Is this world an anaconda?
Look.
It didn't swallow him up.
Give me a break.
You killed your son,
and you reported him as missing
to avoid being a suspect. Am I right?
Your son isn't missing, is he?
What happened to him?
My son died.
I put a cat and a mouse in the same box.
MINSONG GYMNASIUM
Most of the mice sat in a corner
and were frozen, trembling in fear.
But once in a while,
there would be a mouse
that would lose all reason
due to the overwhelming fear
and attack the cat.
When this happens,
its testosterone level shoots up.
I extracted that hormone and refined it.
For all the mice
in this world trembling in fear.
I thought that if fear turned into rage,
he'd become stronger than anyone.
He bit his mother.
Day 17 since infection.
I stopped the haloperidol
and gave him benzodiazepine again.
He'll be awake in less than ten minutes.
You killed your son, didn't you?
-What the…
-Hold her down.
Turn it off!
Hold her down!
What's that noise?
What's going on?
MRI ROOM
Has there been some sort of accident?
Please help me.
Call the police!
Damn, that scared me. What's her problem?
Okay. Want to hear what happens
if you keep shooting like that?
Jang Ha-ri, stand up.
Yes, sir.
Take a good look.
She's your future.
She's a senior,
but she hasn't won a single gold medal.
Forget making the national team.
She can't even make the reserve team.
She couldn't even pass
the regional qualifiers today.
What will you grow up to be?
You can't get into college.
You can't get onto a corporate team.
You didn't study, so no shot
at the civil service exam either.
Listen up.
Do you know how cruel this field is?
All kids who study that score
in the top 100 get into Seoul University.
But even if you guys get into the top 100,
you can't get anywhere near the Olympics.
You're just garbage.
Your life is screwed. Got it?
HYOSAN HIGH SCHOOL
That crazy bastard.
What the hell are they doing?
-See if it's there.
-It's not here either.
Hey, Joon-yeong!
I'm telling you. They can't open doors.
Let's hold it shut for now.
-Did you find one?
-No, nothing here.
-Damn it.
-Any luck, Dae-su?
Are you okay?
Look over there.
-I don't see any here.
-Here!
I found one!
Whose is it?
This is Yeong-ju's desk.
Oh no. We need the passcode.
Do something.
I just said we need the passcode!
Maybe it's her birthday.
When's her birthday?
I don't know.
She's there. Give it to me.
SWIPE UP FOR FACE ID OR ENTER PASSCODE
Hold it closer.
You don't need to unlock it
to make emergency calls.
AT THE SCENE AS QUICKLY AS POSSIBLE
-Police. What's your emergency?
-Hello?
I'm at Hyosan High School.
Zombies showed up.
Everyone turned into zombies.
You can't say "zombies."
Then what?
They won't believe you.
They're not exactly zombies,
but they're something like that.
Okay. Hyosan High, zombies.
Please state your name and number.
You know there's a fine
for making false reports, right?
This isn't a prank.
Everyone's…
Anyway, come quick.
Okay.
Lee Cheong-san.
Your number is 010-4362…
Stay somewhere safe so you don't get bit.
We'll head out right away.
These fucking brats.
He says zombies are attacking.
Hyosan High, right?
They must be having a festival.
I just got a call about zombies too.
-Students, right?
-Police. What's your emergency?
A patient is attacking people?
Does the person have a knife
or some other weapon?
She's biting them?
Zombie?
Hey. Call the school and check.
Okay.
Police. What's your emergency?
-What? A person is biting people?
-Police. What's your emergency?
SCHOOL MOTTO
HAPPY STUDENTS, SAFE SCHOOL
CLASS MOTTO
SUN-HWA IS WATCHING
Stay away!
What?
-Where are they going?
-Why are they leaving?
-What are you doing, moron? Close it.
-Okay.
You scared me.
Are they coming?
He said they'll come.
Did they believe you?
What if they think it's a prank call
and don't come?
Call again.
-Tell them to come quick!
-Stop yelling.
What if the zombies come back?
Give me that.
-You've reached the fire department.
-Hello.
Do you know Capt. Nam So-ju
from Rescue Team One?
No. We have many firefighters.
What is this about?
Oh. Capt. Nam So-ju is my dad.
Please tell him
to hurry over to my school.
-Who is it?
-This is the call center.
You should call his station
if you want to reach him.
There's a fire.
-Fire?
-Hyosan High School, classroom 2-5.
The fire is huge.
GYEONGGI PROVINCIAL FIRE DEPARTMENT
HYOSAN FIRE STATION
RESCUE
No one's coming, right?
Something's going on at the gate.
Let's call the cops again.
They're not coming.
I'm trying but they won't pick up.
Hey.
Do something.
Tell Ms. Park to come or something.
What can she do?
She should be doing something.
What have you done
as our classroom president?
Stop it.
Should I go out?
Go to the teachers' office? Will that do?
Why are you asking me?
You said to do something.
Isn't that what you meant?
Stop it, both of you.
She's saying that
because you're our classroom president.
-Right. You're the classroom president.
-So just be patient, okay?
You guys are… funny.
What do you mean?
Now that we're in this mess,
I'm your classroom president?
We called the police
so we just have to wait a little while.
But no one's coming!
Stop it. We're all scared too.
That's why I'm telling them to call!
You do it, then!
Hey, guys. Stop fighting.
Who are you to stop us, you fucker?
What? Fucker?
Did you just call me a fucker? Fuck!
-Hey. Stop it.
-Hey, Gyeong-su.
Gyeong-su, let it go.
Stop it.
Hold the door. I said, hold the door.
Who the hell does she think…
-Please stop.
-Forget the door.
-Did you hear what she said?
-Gyeong-su. Hold the door.
Let it go. It's nothing new.
Enough already. I'm going.
-Block it.
-Fine. Seriously--
Mr. Kang.
Are you guys okay?
What about you? You weren't bit?
No. Of course not. I'm fine.
Hey, guys. Let's barricade the door first.
Get moving. Hurry.
It's okay. We are safe. Let's move this.
Like this?
Yes. Stack them high.
High.
You called the cops, right?
We can leave soon, right?
Yes.
What are you doing?
Block the front door and stack it.
Stack it high. High.
Here.
-Stack it high.
-Higher?
Push it closer. Much closer.
On-jo, what do we do?
What?
Look.
His arm.
Mr. Kang.
Your arm.
What are you doing? Block the door.
-You were bitten on your arm!
-What?
What is it?
This isn't a bite.
-He said he wasn't bit.
-No.
I wasn't bit.
It's a bite mark.
I said it isn't. Don't talk back to me.
Were you really bit?
I wasn't!
How many times do I have to tell you?
Then why are you hiding it?
Just show it to us.
Can you please leave?
-What?
-Get out.
You want me to go out there?
After all I did to get here?
You want me to go back out?
You were bit.
Get out.
Get out!
You fucking bitch!
How dare you yell at a teacher?
You little…
Get over here.
Come here.
Come here!
You won't come? Hey.
Hey.
-Stop. Stop it.
-He was bit.
-Wait.
-Stay back.
-Hey, look.
-Let go.
-Are you out of your mind?
-Watch out!
Damn.
-Hey. I think he really was bit.
-Shouldn't we get out of here?
Hey. He's turning.
Get him out of here! Hurry!
Hurry. Throw him out.
-Min-ji!
-Dae-su, wait!
Do something!
No! Dae-su!
Min-ji…
Dae-su.
What do I do?
I don't want to die.
Hurry. Get him out of here!
Cheong-san!
I don't want to die.
Help me.
Stay away.
Get away from me. Get away!
Stop, Min-ji. Snap out of it. Please.
We have to get out.
Get out!
-Get out!
-Let's go!
Cheong-san! Dae-su!
Hurry!
Get out!
Gyeong-su!
Watch your hands!
Hey! Get out of the way!
Get over here!
-Push it!
-Push. More!
Let's go!
We need to turn!
Push!
Run upstairs!
Let's go!
Hurry up!
No! We have to go up!
Hurry up! Go up!
Su-hyeok!
Go to the science lab!
Hurry!
Dae-su! Behind you!
Help me. Help!
Push!
-Push!
-Harder!
-It's locked. Somewhere else!
-Where? We're surrounded!
-It's locked!
-Shit! What now?
Try to open it!
Can't you see it's locked?
Hey, block that gap!
Dae-su, push!
Push!
Watch your hands! Careful!
Why's it taking so long?
Hey!
-Above you!
-Hey, it's climbing over!
Fuck! I can't hold them off
much longer. Hurry!
Hurry!
It's open!
Push!
Hurry! Get inside!
Hurry!
Fuck.
Fuck!
Move the desks!
Block it!
Fuck! That scared the hell out of me.
Block it.
Where's the phone? I'll try calling again.
I dropped it.
How could you lose it?
Who cares about that right now?
This is more urgent.
Who are you to butt in?
-What?
-It's because you didn't hold the door.
If you had,
the gym teacher wouldn't have gotten in.
We almost died because of you.
Then maybe you should have held the door.
You're a fucking asshole.
Gyeong-su.
-You bitch.
-How dare you touch me?
Fight after you move these.
This isn't the time.
She's right. Stop it.
Fight after we finish this, Gyeong-su.
This is so annoying.
Where's Su-hyeok?
Has anyone seen him?
You were with him.
He was behind me, but…
Then where is he?
I don't know.
Oh no.
They've all turned.
I think everyone except us turned.
We're outcasts again.
And this is still hell.
I hope everyone dies.
Every single one of them.
You. Shut your mouth.
We should stay here a bit longer.
Right. Okay.
Do you think they're gone?
What do we do?
Shouldn't we go out and call the cops?
We can't go out now.
I'm sure they're still out there.
Who's smoking in this situation?
Who are you to hide in the girls' room?
Be a man. Wimp.
Why, you… Who are you?
Leave her alone. It's Mi-jin.
Mi-jin? Park Mi-jin?
Yes.
Joon-seong.
I'm really dizzy.
Is it bad?
-What do we do?
-I don't know. It's weird.
Everything sounds muffled, and I'm dizzy.
Ha-lim, it's probably just from the shock.
Let's go to the hospital
once things calm down outside, okay?
Okay.
What is it? Who is it?
Hey, open up.
-Open up. Now!
-Why, you--
-Get out.
-What are you doing?
Don't move.
What's wrong?
-What are you doing?
-Fuck, let go of me.
Mi-jin.
Listen carefully.
You know how to play tag, right?
We're all hiding here
to get away from someone.
But now…
you're it.
What are you doing? Hold the door.
But Ha-lim…
I told you she was bit. Get over here.
Mi-jin, don't do this.
I'm okay.
Let me out.
Be quiet, you zombie bitch.
Joon-seong, don't do this.
Let me out.
We came here together.
I saved you, remember?
If you let her out, we all die.
Shit.
Get it together. Look up.
What do you want from me?
-If she turns, we have to kill her.
-Kill Ha-lim?
She's not Ha-lim. She's a zombie.
But still,
do we have any other options?
I don't know.
Mi-jin. I can hear you.
I know.
Must you do that if you know?
You're going to turn eventually.
I know. But,
I'm going to kill you first.
I'll kill you before I kill anyone else.
Crazy bitch.
Mi-jin.
I'm so scared--
Get ready.
I said to get ready.
For what?
To kill her.
Are you going to hold it forever?
Damn it.
What are you doing?
Hey. Why won't she die?
I don't know. Maybe this isn't the spot.
What…
Don't. We're human.
We're not zombies, you bitch.
Hey, I think they're okay.
Zombies don't curse.
Shoot if they turn.
You crazy bitch. We're not zombies!
Students and teachers
of Hyosan High School.
I'm Park Sun-hwa, the English teacher.
Something strange is happening
throughout the school.
Some students are attacking people
indiscriminately,
so please find a safe place
and take shelter.
And if any student
or faculty hears this and is able,
please call the police
and the fire department.
Students, hide somewhere safe
until help arrives.
If you can get out of the school,
please get out.
I repeat.
Some students are…
Guys.
You're okay, right?
You're not hurt, right?
I don't know
what's going on or why this is happening.
Still,
find a safe place and hide.
I'm sorry
I can't be of any help.
Don't get hurt, okay?
Let's stay alive and meet again.
Okay?
Rescue Team Three,
head to Hyosan Hospital.
Rescue Team Four, head to
the accident at Hyosan Intersection.
Rescue Team Two, you have another call.
Fire at Hyosan High.
Please head there right away.
Rescue Team One, report location.
This is Rescue Team One.
We've arrived at the accident.
This is Rescue Team Two. We'll head
to the fire at Hyosan High School.
Accident reports keep coming in.
All units standby where you are.
Let's go.
You little shit!
-What was that for?
-A fly.
You heard from On-jo earlier, right?
She confessed to Su-hyeok.
So what?
Go and comfort her.
I keep trying, but it won't work.
Forget it. You do it.
Why are you snapping at me?
What's it to me whom she likes?
Forget it.
On-jo.
Don't worry too much.
I'm sure Su-hyeok will be fine.
He's athletic and super fast.
Right.
But
Cheong-san's acting weird.
He's super irritable.
I think he likes you.
I can totally tell.
No, he doesn't.
He doesn't feel things like that.
He's too busy teasing me.
I-sak.
Why are you so cold?
What?
Your hand is really…
What about my hand?
I-sak.
-What's wrong? Are you--
-No, I wasn't bit. Really.
I mean it. I really wasn't.
She was bit.
What's going on?
Were you bit?
No, I wasn't!
Hey. You're okay, right?
On-jo.
I-sak.
No, right?
I'm not like them, right?
I'm not.
I'm not one of them.
What are you guys doing?
Get her out of here!
Get her out now!
Shit. They're going to climb over.
No.
I'm fine!
On-jo.
Let go.
Hurry! Do something!
Throw her out the window.
No. Let go.
Hurry! She's turning into a zombie!
No, not I-sak.
I-sak.
I-sak, don't.
Stop it!
I said, stop it!
Cheong-san!
Have you lost your mind?
-Let go.
-I-sak.
You have to let go.
You want some glitter?
-It's okay. I can do it.
-Go on.
I'll do it for you.
It's nice. Look.
It looks great on you!
Hey!
On-jo.
Come hold this!
Let's go out.
We can't last here much longer.
Where would we go? And how?
The rope from earlier.
Gyeong-su.
Yes?
What?
What is it?
Open it just a little.
Enough for the hose to fit.
Isn't it better to wait
until the rescuers come?
We could all die if we wait.
This might kill us faster. If we--
Is waiting for someone
the best thing we can do?
Screw it.
I've never given my best
at anything other than playing.
Did you get it?
Where are you going?
Prez, hold the door.
Help me make knots.
How?
Wrap it and tie it.
So a hand or foot can fit.
Big enough for a foot?
Zigzag. Tie them in a zigzag.
In 50-centimeter increments.
-Zigzag.
-Is this right?
Move over.
Good enough, right?
Let's go.
Can we make it?
I'll go down and check the empty rooms.
Come when I tell you to.
Be careful.
Hold it.
What are you doing?
Go down.
What?
Gyeong-su,
you go first.
Why? Did you see something?
No. You go.
What's down there?
Just go.
You go, then.
-Go already.
-Step up there.
You should go.
Then you go, asshole.
No. You can do it.
-You can do it.
-Damn it.
But why am I--
Grab it and go.
Rock, paper, scissors?
-Just go.
-I mean…
-Don't be a wimp.
-Hey. Hold on.
Where is it? Hold on.
-Can you reach it?
-Wait, I can't.
Put your foot in.
Oh, I got it.
Careful.
Damn it. Where is it?
Shit. You scared me.
Damn it.
I'll keep going.
I want to go down first.
One person at a time.
You might fall if it shakes too much.
I won't shake it.
-How long do I have to wait?
-Just a little while.
Shit. Why won't it come out?
Gyeong-su!
Ms. Park!
-Are you okay?
-Hurry.
-Be careful.
-Oh, right.
Cheong-san!
Ms. Park is here!
Ms. Park is on the second floor.
Second floor? The broadcasting room?
-Are you okay?
-Yes.
Were you with the others?
They're in the science lab.
They'll come down now.
Come down! Okay?
Come down!
Seriously!
What?
Careful. I got you. Hold on.
-Dae-su.
-You're so heavy.
-Ms. Park.
Come down safely.
Grab the window frame.
-Grab her.
-Let go.
-I have a cramp!
-You okay?
What's wrong?
Straighten your knee.
-Not my legs!
-Watch out for your neck!
Good. You did great.
Go down.
I-sak…
Get it together.
Who here hasn't lost a friend?
Think of all the people who died.
Why are you…
There's no one left that I like.
There are people who like you though.
Like your dad and…
You have to live for them.
Let's go.
SU-HYEOK, WE'RE IN THE BROADCASTING ROOM
NAM-RA
Oh shit.
Hurry.
Hurry up.
Grab her. Okay.
Careful.
ALL CHARACTERS, ORGANIZATIONS,
LOCATIONS, INSTITUTIONS,
AND EVENTS IN THIS SHOW ARE FICTIONAL.
Subtitle translation by: Jeong Lee