Dad.
Let me see you.
Get out!
Damn it.
They're not here.
Who are you?
How did you get here?
I heard something.
I thought they were here.
Out of my way.
Where did you come from? Is it okay there?
It's fucking okay everywhere.
The school is heaven.
-Later.
-Where are you going?
You'll die if you go out.
Don't go out, asshole! Do as I say.
Aren't you hungry?
What?
Aren't you
hungry?
I'm starving.
I'm full right now.
So you get to live.
Count yourself lucky.
What is that smell?
Why do you smell like them?
What? What do you smell?
Let go of me.
You were with Cheong-san, weren't you?
Who's that?
-Where is that asshole?
-What are you talking about?
You want to know?
Are you okay?
Are you hurt?
What took you so long?
I kept waiting.
Are you kids okay?
Yes.
Good.
Cheong-san.
Mr. Nam.
Can you all run?
-Yes.
Good.
If you go through the tennis courts
and the construction site,
you'll reach the mountain.
Go over the mountain and get to Yangdong--
Mr. Nam!
Kids. Run!
Shit.
GYMNASIUM
Hurry!
Run! Hurry!
To the tennis courts!
Hurry up!
Run. Go inside!
Go in.
Get in!
Run!
Hey. Hold on.
We can't go out there. We can't.
What should we do, Dae-su?
Damn it.
What do we do?
We're screwed.
Hey!
Step back.
Let's go.
Hurry.
Cheong-san, take On-jo.
Dad. Where are you going?
Dad!
Run!
Get out! Go out now!
Go!
Mr. Nam!
Go! Get out!
Dad.
Look at me, On-jo.
Go.
Run.
-Go!
-Dad.
Go!
On-jo! Go…
Run.
Dad…
On-jo!
Run!
Dad!
NOTICE FOR CONSTRUCTION WORK
Hurry!
No!
What? Why?
Go upstairs. Go!
Hurry! To the second floor!
Hurry!
Where do we go?
There's no way out. It's blocked.
-There's nothing here too.
-This way!
-Is there a way?
-Let's go out this way.
The bench.
Hurry up.
Damn it.
Careful.
Stay away from the edge.
Okay.
-Come here.
-Quiet.
Don't say a word.
On-jo! Go!
Dad!
It's okay.
Just cry.
It's better to just die.
This virus changes a person
into a different being.
The person I loved
becomes a monster.
You can forget someone who dies…
but it's hard to forget someone
who has changed.
That is the last image…
of the people I loved most.
Remember now?
I don't know anyone
named Cheong-san, you freak.
Everyone went to the auditorium,
and I got out
by myself.
Auditorium?
I don't know who Cheong-san is.
We went with some juniors. That's all.
Then they must be
at the auditorium right now.
You're fucking brave.
You'd better run.
Or I'll eat you.
I told you to run. Why don't you listen?
Fuck. Nothing is working out.
We keep hitting dead ends.
Be quiet.
It's your fault Joon-yeong died.
Dae-su. Don't.
If you hadn't bitched at him earlier,
he wouldn't have jumped out there.
Fine. It's my fault he died. Happy?
-Are you happy, asshole?
-You give it a rest too.
Dae-su.
What does it matter who's responsible
for someone living or dying?
What does living or dying even mean?
I have no idea.
If we get out of here, is that living?
Our friends died.
Our moms and dads died.
What's the point in living?
Do you want to die?
Then will you die?
Have you tried being seniors?
Do you even know
how it feels to want to die?
Is it some badge of honor?
You try being one.
You'll see what it's like.
You juniors
better survive until next year
and see what it's like being seniors.
Survive until next year and tell me
which is tougher, zombies or senior year.
Your father…
He saved all of us.
I'll never forget it as long as I live.
None of us will.
If someone is remembered by many people,
that person…
goes to heaven.
Mi-jin.
Let's go.
Where? Why?
Let's look for a spot
we can jump off from. We're the seniors.
Whatever. It's not like
they show us any respect.
I'll go this way. You go that way.
Damn it. She's so cool.
I'll go.
Stay down.
No.
Why, you…
Move.
Shit.
I hope no one steps up anymore.
Whatever happens…
I hope no one sacrifices themselves.
It's too hard living
because of someone else.
There's nothing we can do for them.
Living life to the full
in honor of the person who died…
It's too selfish.
You can't die even if you want to.
You lack the courage to live,
but you can't die.
Let's…
let's talk a little later.
Tomorrow or the day after. Or next week.
After we eat and get ourselves clean.
That's what we agreed to do.
This side.
What?
You probably don't remember.
Don't remember what?
Cheong-san, hold on.
Is this better
or is this better?
Look closely. This? Or this?
The left side is much better.
What are you talking about?
I'll tell you tomorrow.
Cheong-san.
ONE HEART
This moron became a zombie.
Next we'll raise it to 24 kHz.
Turn it off!
Tests we ran in 17 locations across Hyosan
showed that they reacted
most strongly to 24 kHz.
We'll begin the briefing.
We will emit sounds using drones
and draw the infected to target locations
to maximize the impact
with minimal explosions.
There are four target locations.
The Hyosan Intersection,
the sports complex, Hyosan High,
and Hyosan Future College.
Estimated casualties?
Hyosan has a population of 170,000,
and 110,000 of them are
in quarantine camps.
Thus, we estimate about 60,000 casualties.
About 50,000 are infected,
and 10,000 are uninfected or asymptomatic.
We'll send in ground troops after
the bombing to take care of the rest.
Sound the evacuation warnings nonstop
until right before the operation begins.
Eat him.
It's okay. Eat him.
I'm hungry.
It's okay.
It's not okay.
It is.
If it happens again,
bite me, not yourself.
If you bite me, I'll just become like you.
I really think that's the only way out.
No. It drops into the basement
on that side,
and there are exposed steel bars.
So we can't jump down.
That side faces the school,
so there's no point.
The ground is filled with zombies,
so we'll die if we go down.
There's a door on the first floor
that leads to the mountain.
I think we have to go that way.
But it's full of zombies in there.
Can't we reach the roof
if we climb that and the windows?
If someone goes to the roof
and screams, the zombies will follow.
Then it'll empty out
and the rest can escape.
I think that will work.
No.
-If that's the only way--
-I said no.
Please, let's not have
anyone sacrifice themselves.
I'm against it too.
We agreed to survive together.
Me too.
I feel the same.
So do I.
Then let's wait for now.
And then what?
Do you have a plan?
It might rain again,
and then they'll hear us less.
Who knows when it'll rain?
My knees are aching.
I think it'll rain soon.
Look at the sky.
It's way too clear.
Do you hear that?
Hear what?
They're telling us to take cover.
Who is?
Attention, all citizens.
There will be explosions
at the sports complex,
Hyosan High, Future College,
and Hyosan Intersection.
If you hear this, take shelter in nearby
subways and underground parking lots…
There'll be explosions.
We need to take cover.
Explosions? What explosions?
Listen again.
Hyosan Intersection, Future College…
and our school will be blown up.
Is the army going to
fucking launch missiles at us?
When?
They're not saying.
They're just telling people
to evacuate now.
Fuck. Where are we supposed to go?
So when are the explosions happening?
Initiate operation.
Activate the sound waves.
Begin tactical flight.
CHEONGSAN CHICKEN
Won't we all die if we stay here?
Do they say where to flee to?
They said hide underground
or in bathrooms.
What if it's a nuclear bomb?
Korea doesn't have nukes. Get a grip.
Whatever!
They're blowing up our school.
Where are we supposed to take cover?
There's nowhere to go.
Cheong-san!
What?
It's Gwi-nam.
That asshole doesn't die.
Who is that?
Maybe we misheard.
It's quiet now.
Here you are.
-What the hell?
-Cheong-san!
Hey!
Shit!
Cheong-san!
No.
Help! Hurry!
Shit! Come on.
Cheong-san!
Move. Fuck!
They've all arrived
at the target locations.
Execute.
Let me confirm the order.
Fire!
It's okay.
It's not what you think. It's okay.
I said it's okay.
Don't do that.
You'll be fine.
On-jo.
No one…
will die here today.
Don't say anything.
Let's talk tomorrow, okay?
LEE CHEONG-SAN
Hold onto it.
I'll hold onto this.
LEE CHEONG-SAN - NAM ON-JO
Su-hyeok, go to the first floor.
Cheong-san!
Hey!
Come get me. All of you.
Today,
I am
the happiest guy in this school!
Hey!
Ha-ri. Let's go.
We have to go.
Let's go, Nam-ra.
Let's go.
Can you climb over?
Careful. Step down.
Hurry.
Hey!
-Hurry.
-Hurry up!
Hey!
CAUTION - RISK OF ACCIDENT
Come at me.
Come at me, all of you!
WARNING: NO TRESPASSING
PRIVATE PROPERTY OWNED BY THE SCHOOL
Keep moving.
You know,
I thought it would be really fun
to kill you.
But not anymore.
I'll kill you even if it isn't fun.
Stop acting tough.
Do you really think that makes you cool?
No one thinks that.
You're just scared that people
will find out you killed the principal.
You'll always be a coward and a loser.
I'm not scared of anything.
I'm definitely not scared of you.
I'll gouge out your eye first, fucker.
Yeah, run away.
I'll let you live if you run away.
Sports complex. Bombing complete.
Hyosan Intersection. Bombing complete.
Future College. Bombing complete.
Ha-ri!
Are you okay?
Commander.
The operation is complete, Commander.
Okay.
Send in the troops in the morning
and take care of the rest.
You take charge.
Me, sir?
I'm sure you can handle it.
I need to sleep.
I've been up for too long.
Is this a friendly visit?
You came to watch.
We just bombed Hyosan.
What did you say?
40% of Hyosan's population is dead.
You're a murderer.
How could you be so shameless?
I thought about who would be able
to comfort the people of Hyosan right now.
That is why I came to see you.
Please tell the people of Hyosan
that I am sorry.
JIN SEON-MOO
This morning,
I watched the last video made
by Lee Byeong-chan,
the man who created this virus.
He tried to save his wife and son
who were infected with the virus,
but he failed.
And he made a final decision.
Jin-su.
Honey…
I respect the decision
Mr. Lee Byeong-chan made.
He was a father and a husband.
I'm sure he couldn't kill anyone.
However, I am a soldier.
Today, I ordered
the bombing of Hyosan.
No one ordered me to do it.
It was my sole decision
as the martial law commander.
I take full responsibility.
WIFE
Hi, it's me.
Did you eat?
Come on. Look at the time.
Why haven't you eaten yet?
What about the kids?
Okay.
What's the big deal about missing school?
What matters is staying healthy.
Yes.
Look for a tutor.
It's fine if they're expensive.
Right. Not too expensive.
Yes.
God, honey.
I miss you.
What?
I'm very sorry.
I love you.
WIFE: I'M SORRY I GOT CRANKY WITH YOU
I LOVE YOU TOO
WHEN CAN YOU COME HOME?
NAM ON-JO
ALL CHARACTERS, ORGANIZATIONS,
LOCATIONS, INSTITUTIONS,
AND EVENTS IN THIS SHOW ARE FICTIONAL.
Subtitle translation by: Jeong Lee