A virus?
So what you're saying is
this entire mess was caused
by a virus you created?
Fine. A virus.
Why? Why did you create the virus?
Detective.
Do you have any children?
Mommy.
Yes, sweetheart.
God, you're soaked in sweat.
Yun-a.
Oh no. Be careful.
You should watch where you're going.
Good girl.
Could you let your child just die?
No parent in the world could do that.
Enough of your bullshit.
Just answer my question.
What kind of virus is it and--
Jae-ik. Emergency.
Chief wants everyone to come. Hurry.
It's too late.
Everyone will die.
Don't bother having hope.
Oh fuck.
Cheong-san!
Look down. Down.
I know.
She's holding on, moron.
What are you doing?
-I know that.
-Drop her. Drop her now.
I'm trying.
What are you doing, you moron?
Hey!
Hey. I'll come to you.
No, don't come.
Don't. Don't come.
-I'm coming.
-Don't!
I said, don't!
Wait.
Bare-su, above you!
Hey. My back.
Stay still. I'll help you.
What are you doing?
Wait, will you? Moron.
-It's Bare-su. Bare-su!
-Cheong-san!
It's Bare-su. Bare-su!
Are you okay?
Shit. I told you to drop her.
Why couldn't you do it?
Hey. Stop hugging me.
You're grossing me out.
I'm not hugging you, moron.
Get lost.
Do you like this?
-Are you okay, Bare-su?
-Close it.
Close it already!
Close the window! Please!
Didn't you see Cheong-san coming in?
We can't close it until he gets in.
Is it wrong to say to close it?
Is your own survival all that matters?
I can't stand you, stupid welfie.
-Hey. What the fuck did you say?
-Stop it.
What is it?
-Did you just hit me?
-Yeah.
Say that again.
Cut it out. What are you doing?
He just hit me.
You called me a welfie first.
Was I wrong?
How could you say that?
What's a welfie?
Tell me.
What is it?
What's a welfie?
A person on welfare.
-What?
-A person on welfare.
"Welfie" for short.
Na-yeon, you were wrong.
Don't you ever say that again.
And, Gyeong-su,
if you hit someone for saying that,
you're the one who loses.
-You understand what I mean, right?
-No.
Kids, we shouldn't be fighting
among ourselves right now.
We don't know what's going on--
Aren't they zombies?
Where are the other teachers?
Did you call the cops?
I'm sure someone did.
I don't have my phone.
We called, too, but they're not coming.
Both the police and the first responders.
They'll be here soon.
Let's wait here a little longer.
Ms. Park. Hyeon-ju's hands were cold too.
So were I-sak's.
What if it started with Hyeon-ju?
She went to the hospital.
Then maybe it spread there too.
Maybe that's why no one's coming.
Hold on. This works, right?
Hey, the Internet.
-Excuse me, Ms. Park.
-Okay.
-Here. Sit.
-Thanks.
-Please, work. I assume so.
-Will it work? Is it on?
Why is it not turning on?
-It just came on.
-I see. Sorry.
It's for work, so it's slow.
Maybe it has no connection.
No, I'm sure it does.
-Do we have to wait all day?
-Is it still loading?
-I don't think it'll work.
-What?
In the science lab.
WE'RE IN THE BROADCASTING ROOM
I came from the art room.
What's in the science lab?
Oh, well…
It worked.
-Open the browser.
-The browser.
Type in "zombie virus."
Type in "zombie" first.
-No, just…
-No.
-Type in "Hyosan."
-See what's trending.
-No.
-Damn it.
-Check the news.
-Search "emergency."
-The news.
-There won't be anything.
-Search "emergency."
-What do we type in?
Thanks. I'll see you next time.
-Oh my goodness. Are you all right?
-Are you okay? Get up.
Stand up.
-Call an ambulance.
-All right. Come this way.
-What's going on?
-Are you all right?
Are you okay?
He's badly injured. Call an ambulance.
Someone is in the back.
Come out.
What's the matter with you?
-What's wrong with you?
-Should we take them to the hospital?
Oh my God.
Stay away!
I'll check Facebook.
-I'm on Instagram.
-How many followers do you have?
Check Facebook.
How many friends do you have?
You have so many alerts. You have 1,700!
That's strange.
I'll check the messages first.
Fuck! What the…
-What the hell?
-Fuck.
What the hell?
What was that?
Get over here. Step back.
Did someone not make it in?
No. We're all here.
Don't go!
Cheong-san.
Be careful.
Do you see something?
What is it?
It must be the wind.
That scared me.
It's coming in!
Cheong-san, come back here.
Hey, watch out.
Cheong-san!
Bring Cheong-san back here!
Hey, wait!
-Push it! Push it away!
-Did you get it?
Push it!
Push it more!
The hand!
-Push!
-Hey, watch out!
Step back!
Don't go near it!
-Should I go or should you?
-Move over.
Hold on. I can't.
-Go, Dae-su.
-Should I go?
What are you doing?
-We're fucked.
-Just push it!
Just push it! Push it away!
Push it away already!
-Fuck. It's coming in.
-Su-hyeok! Just throw that away!
-Su-hyeok! Move away!
-Move, Bare-su!
Scared me.
I'm exhausted.
Are you okay?
I'm good.
Where did it come from?
-Everyone okay?
-That was scary.
I'm okay.
Good thinking.
Hey.
You…
RESCUE
HYOSAN CITY COUNCIL
He's our youngest aide.
He collapsed and started convulsing
when he returned
from the council office…
Captain.
He smells like a rotting corpse.
And then he got up,
growled, and charged
at Assembly Member Park.
So we tied him up.
We didn't know
if we should call the police. Yes?
Why are you telling them that?
He'll bite his tongue.
-Let's gag him and move him.
-Okay.
-Ready?
-Yes.
One, two, three.
-Did you get bit?
-It's okay. It's a small bite.
Wrap him up!
Wrap him.
Urgent message from headquarters.
Rescue Team One.
As of now,
issuing level-three disaster in Hyosan.
Everyone report to temporary headquarters.
Did you say level-three disaster?
I repeat.
Issuing level-three disaster in Hyosan.
Everyone report to temporary headquarters.
What is it?
-This is the director's order.
-Report where?
-Mobilize immediately. Over.
-Well…
Our headquarters was relocated
outside the city due to an emergency.
The Disaster and Safety Management
will control the situation directly.
Is an evacuation order really necessary?
All right.
Hang on.
They think it's an acute infection.
They expect an evacuation order
of Hyosan soon.
Gyeong-su, your nose is bleeding.
It is?
This is because Su-hyeok hit me
with the mop.
Stand back. Don't come closer.
You were bit, weren't you?
No, I wasn't.
Su-hyeok hit me…
Why do you keep picking on me?
You were bit!
I-sak got a nosebleed
just before she turned.
On-jo. You know.
That's how I-sak was before she turned.
-Gyeong-su.
-I really wasn't bit! I swear!
Damn it.
Hey.
Your hand. What is that?
What is that?
This was from
when I picked up the computer!
Don't you trust me?
This happened while I was saving you.
How could you do this?
It's not a bite. It's a scratch.
Whoever wants to check, come and check.
It's a scratch?
It is a scratch. I'm sure of it.
-Ms. Park, please take a look.
-Okay.
I don't see a bite.
It's a scratch. Thank goodness.
He's okay.
Satisfied?
I asked if you were satisfied!
But the computer's gone.
Then the Internet…
Did you have to throw that of all things?
What could I do? It was trying to get in.
I'm saying you did good.
Thank you. Don't get mad.
Hey, Na-yeon.
Say you're sorry and end this.
Why should I?
He did it to save us.
Just say you're sorry.
Why should I be sorry?
I saw everything.
I saw it grab your hand.
I'm right.
He may have been infected.
Na-yeon, that's enough.
It really touched him.
Does being touched mean he's infected?
Who knows? It might.
I held I-sak's hand before she fell.
Why am I okay?
He has a wound on his hand.
It's different when it's an open wound.
-Why, that--
-Hey.
Don't yell at me. Think about it!
Na-yeon.
I know you've always hated Gyeong-su,
but this is completely different
from badmouthing him.
This is about life and death.
She's always like this.
If it weren't for him, we may all be dead.
And now he may kill us.
I'm about to die because of you.
-Watch your mouth.
-I'm fine right now.
That's enough, all of you! Shut it.
-Ms. Park--
-Silence.
-She--
-Hey!
Let's do this.
Stay in the recording room
for just ten minutes, Gyeong-su.
I know it'll be hard, but I think
that's better than being suspected.
The others don't suspect me.
It's just her.
Gyeong-su, would you do that, please?
Forget ten minutes. I'll stay half…
No, a full hour.
There's no need for that.
It takes less than five minutes to turn.
-Stop overreacting.
-Let's just be sure.
Will that do?
If nothing happens,
you'll sincerely apologize, right?
Yes.
You guys are all okay with that, right?
-Yes.
He's clearly fine. If we do this,
who would step up next time?
Everyone will hide.
You're right, too, but…
let's consider this a way
to learn to trust each other.
I trust Gyeong-su.
See you in an hour.
Should I go in with you?
That stubborn punk.
Ten minutes would be fine.
He's nothing compared to her.
-Go get it.
-No.
You little…
Stop it.
Go get it.
Move. Stop that.
Hey.
Come here.
Damn it.
HYOSAN HIGH SCHOOL
Maybe they're drawn to smell.
They go after you like crazy.
I don't smell.
You sweat a lot.
I sweat, but I don't smell.
What is that smell?
Your sweat.
I think they're more sensitive
to sound than smell.
-Sound?
-Yes, sound.
This isn't a movie.
That's how most zombies are.
And you saw their eyes.
They can't see with those eyes.
-Ms. Park.
-Yes?
Sound or smell, I don't know, but…
Some kids probably left the school, right?
Really?
Yes, probably.
Here, Su-hyeok.
Give me the mirror.
Should we consider ourselves
the lucky ones?
The fact that we're alive
means we're lucky.
Is that true?
Yes.
Wipe your face.
Are you okay?
I keep thinking about I-sak.
But you held onto her
until the very end.
Stop it. That's not comforting.
You did nothing wrong.
Be strong.
Your dad or somebody else
will come to save us.
FRIED CHICKEN RESTAURANT
CHEONGSAN CHICKEN
Goodness.
Must you put your son's face on the sign?
What's wrong with using my own son's face?
You'll end up becoming
an evil mother-in-law.
Being all protective of your son while
nagging your daughter-in-law like crazy.
Right.
I'll go submit these
at the District Office.
The series of incidents
occurring in Hyosan
appear to be due to a mass outbreak
of a highly infectious virus.
We'll speak to the Disease Control Center
for more details.
Director Cha Hyeon-seok,
what's the current situation?
Considering the level of spread,
it appears to be
a highly infectious disease.
Those suspected of being infected
became unusually aggressive.
The victims showed similar symptoms,
so we suspect secondary infections.
As you've heard, this is very serious.
On advice from the KDCA,
the government has raised
the infectious disease alert to "serious."
They stated that
they will do everything possible
to prevent it
from spreading outside of Hyosan.
This just in.
The National Security Council has decided
to issue an evacuation
of Hyosan in Gyeonggi.
If you are watching this,
please leave the city immediately.
I repeat. The situation is very serious.
The National Security Council has decided
to issue an evacuation
of Hyosan in Gyeonggi.
If you are watching this,
please leave the city immediately.
-I'm going to step out for a minute.
-Okay.
Are you all right?
Yes, I'm fine.
I'm fine. I…
I…
I'll be back soon.
A virus?
What type of virus?
I don't think it's a droplet infection,
but it hasn't been confirmed.
You seem to get infected if you get bit,
so don't get bit or make physical contact.
We don't have
any information on the virus yet,
so make sure to avoid contact.
I hear an assembly member is there.
-Hold still.
-Who is it?
Yeong-hwan.
What the…
Yeong-hwan, are you okay?
Hey. Captain, what do we do?
Yeong-hwan!
Hey.
That's what happened to our aide earlier.
It's the same.
Shit.
Is he dead?
Hey!
U-sin!
Get the rope!
-Hurry!
-Tie him up!
Tie him up! Hurry!
We've got approximately 200 infected
at Hyosan Intersection.
Unit 1030, 1040, 1050.
Move to Hyosan Intersection.
Copy that. This is Unit 1030.
We're heading to Hyosan Intersection.
Brace for impact!
Go join the line!
Block them!
Stand firm!
Join the line!
Wait. Hey!
Stop! Stop right there.
-Go back.
-I'll be quick.
What are you doing?
She wants to get through.
You need to go.
-My son--
-You need to evacuate.
-Get her out of here.
-Yes, sir.
-No. Wait.
-Escort her out of here.
My son, Cheong-san. Wait!
I'm sorry.
Do you go to Hyosan High?
What are you doing here?
Is the school okay?
Hey. Do you know Cheong-san?
Lee Cheong-san? Do you know him?
Oh no.
Hey. Lift me more.
That's the highest I can go.
Get on your tippy-toes.
I did.
Do you see anything?
Shit. There are so many zombies.
-Put me down.
-Okay.
Let me down. Careful.
Okay.
Why is this so hard?
-Are you okay?
-That hurts.
-Yes.
What do we do?
First.
Do you have cigarettes?
I don't smoke.
Damn, you totally look like a smoker.
Hey, what about you?
-I don't smoke.
-Don't mess with me.
I don't.
Is that how you talk to a senior?
Want to die?
Whatever. Look who's talking.
Hey. Who taught you
to talk like that to a senior?
-Sorry.
-Hey.
I'm the one you should apologize to.
Athletes are all douchebags. Fuck.
Watch your mouth.
Watch your body.
Must you guys fight right now?
Don't you have brains? Are you babies?
Sorry.
I said I was sorry.
Let's get out of here.
How can we leave?
They'll eat us all if they see us.
If you want to leave, go by yourself.
I'm not going.
-What about you?
-Don't ask.
I'll do whatever I feel like.
Damn. What a cold bitch.
Hey. Make some weapons.
Come on.
Give me that.
Moron.
Hey.
I'll kill you.
That moron.
What is that?
Thirty minutes.
-What are you saying?
-It's been 30 minutes. Come out.
Ms. Park. It's been more than 30 minutes,
but Gyeong-su won't come out.
Okay. I'll bring him out.
What's wrong with him?
He's fine.
-He's totally fine.
-I knew it.
-Why is he being so stubborn?
-He won't come out, right?
He's so pigheaded.
He's so stubborn.
What?
What did he say?
He won't come out?
He says he'll stay the full hour.
He's sulking.
I'll go in.
Why should you?
If anyone should go in, it's Na-yeon.
Why should I?
He's like that because of you.
-What did I do?
-Like you don't know?
Was it wrong to suspect him?
You did too. Every last one of you.
I didn't suspect him.
Me neither.
I did. She's right.
But I didn't look down on him
like you did.
-Why are you picking on me?
-You're the only one acting that way.
That's enough, Ji-min.
You remember your promise, right?
That you'd apologize after 30 minutes.
Yes.
It's been 30 minutes.
Fine.
She's going to him.
Hey.
I'm talking to you.
Are you ignoring me?
-Are you starting a fight again?
-They're talking. It's looking good.
-Why didn't you answer?
-Unless you're here to apologize, get out.
How's your cut?
What's it to you?
Let me see.
She grabbed his hand. Oh my God.
Talk about being forward.
I suspected you
because the situation called for it.
And I was really mad earlier.
I'm still mad now.
I guess that's…
Does Gyeong-su like that stuff?
I have no idea.
You know I've always
looked down on you, right?
It's fine. It's all in the past. Let's go.
What's fine?
You deserve to be looked down on.
Our complex banned you welfies,
but you still cut through.
And you dare push me?
You fucking…
You thought I'd apologize?
They're going to kiss.
They must be crazy.
Everyone's taking your side.
I was cornered
because of a nobody like you.
Stay the full hour.
Although I hope you never come out.
Damn welfie.
They're coming.
-Hey!
-How nice was that? How nice--
-Gyeong-su!
-You little--
-What's wrong?
-Gyeong-su, what's wrong?
You're really a fucking…
Seriously…
-Why must I always take it?
-Did you really say that?
You promised me.
I did nothing wrong.
You only think about yourself.
You said not to let our friends in.
You said to close the door
before they came in.
That's not right.
We almost died
because Gyeong-su pulled Mr. Kang in.
But you don't say a word about that?
He didn't pull him in.
He didn't know that would happen.
-That's enough. Quiet, everyone.
-We'd be quiet if she was gone.
Whatever.
All of you are so annoying.
What if I'm right?
Then will you admit I saved you?
How could you still be this way?
Look.
See if I'm right or wrong.
What?
Gyeong-su.
Day 26 of infection.
See? You still think I'm wrong?
The strong cells are attacking
the weak cells.
Every single cell
is struggling to survive…
and attacking each other.
This virus is the will to survive defined.
It consumes all the cells
almost instantly.
Hey. What's wrong with me?
Something's wrong with me.
What the fuck.
What's wrong with you?
It's not true.
Get rid of him. Get rid of him now!
-No, I--
-Stop it, Gyeong-su.
Don't do that.
Fuck, I'm not!
I'm sorry, Gyeong-su.
Still, don't do it.
I've turned, right?
Cheong-san, what do I do?
No. No, it can't be. Why would you…
Cheong-san.
Let go.
Moron. It's not true.
Why would you suddenly…
The infected human feels extreme fear…
Then they attack only to survive.
Hey. You weren't bit.
Stay away. Don't come any closer! Fuck!
What are you doing? Tell him to get out.
We're all going to die!
Why…
Fuck, why am I…
Fuck.
Get out. I said to get out!
Shut up! Fuck!
I'll leave.
I'll leave on my own.
Why would I bite you?
We're fucking friends.
If I leave, it'll all be fine.
Gyeong-su,
why don't you just go back
into the recording--
What will you do if we all die?
Na-yeon!
We have to live.
I'll leave.
I'll get out of here on my own.
Sorry, I'll get out of here.
Gyeong-su.
It's okay.
Thank you, guys, for everything.
Really.
Stay alive.
Are you all right, Gyeong-su?
That moron.
What are you looking at?
Why are you doing that?
You're scaring me. Stop that.
Stop it.
Cheong-san, why are you doing that?
Stop it! Stop it, please! I'm scared!
Oh no!
CHEONGSAN CHICKEN
CONGRATULATIONS ON YOUR NEW BEGINNING
-Here. Lift it.
-Okay.
Here.
Lift it.
The Disaster and Safety Management said
not to touch the infected.
As you can see, it's highly contagious--
We were notified too.
No need to explain it to us.
How long will we stay here?
They're sending a helicopter,
but it's taking some time.
So you'll have to wait a while longer.
Did you notify them that I'm here?
Pardon?
Is it taking time to get a chopper
even though they know I'm here?
I didn't report that you were here.
You should've told them
so they'd send one quickly.
As per the rules of rescue,
the weak and critically ill
take priority over people of status.
We'll hear from them soon,
so please wait a little longer.
ON-JO'S HOMEROOM TEACHER
Is the helicopter even coming?
Yes, I'm sure it will.
Why don't we rest for now?
The person you have called is unavailable.
This is Capt. Nam So-ju
of Rescue Team One.
If anyone knows the situation
at Hyosan High School,
please respond. Over.
If anyone knows of the situation
at Hyosan High School or its vicinity,
please respond. Over.
Please respond.
RESCUE
Gyeong-su, that punk.
He was such a good kid.
Why did he have to turn?
I told you
he was infected.
Are you happy?
You were all wrong. Only I was right.
What if you didn't have me?
Hey.
Maybe you did it.
What?
I saw…
what you did.
What? What did you see?
You did it.
I didn't do it.
I didn't do that to Gyeong-su.
I didn't mention him.
Stop that.
What do you mean?
I didn't do it.
While we were all looking at him,
you were in the back alone.
Ms. Park. It's been more than 30 minutes,
but Gyeong-su won't come out.
Okay. I'll bring him out.
What's wrong with him?
He's fine.
-He's totally fine.
-I knew it.
He should just come out.
He's still not coming out?
I guess not.
Hasn't he been in there long enough?
You wiped that blood
with your handkerchief.
No, I didn't.
You rubbed that
on Gyeong-su's wound, right?
-I didn't.
-Your handkerchief is in your pocket.
-And if it is?
-Take it out.
-No.
I said, no.
Should I take it out?
Damn it.
Who the hell do you think you are?
Is classroom president special?
Since when did you consider me
your classroom president?
Nam-ra, that's enough.
Nam-ra, do you realize what you're saying?
If that's true,
it means Na-yeon killed Gyeong-su.
It's true.
Na-yeon…
killed Gyeong-su.
You fucking bitch.
There you go.
Satisfied?
There's blood on it.
I wiped Gyeong-su's wound.
This is Gyeong-su's blood?
Can't you tell?
Then put it on your wound.
Wipe your wound with it if you're so sure.
Like his blood is clean?
He became a zombie.
He was fine until you rubbed him
with your handkerchief.
Na-yeon, you--
Fuck! It wasn't me!
Don't do it. Stop it.
Let go.
I said to stop it.
Give it to me.
Leave me alone! Fuck!
I'll just die too, then.
That's what you want, isn't it?
What makes Gyeong-su better than me?
That dirty welfie pushed me.
Na-yeon, you didn't…
Hey. Did you do it?
-Calm down.
-How could you--
I didn't kill him!
Gyeong-su fell, but he got up and ran.
He's still alive.
He didn't die. He turned.
Are you kidding me?
Why are you all picking on me?
You all laughed when I said he smelled.
You all badmouthed him too.
Why are you acting innocent now?
-That little…
-Cheong-san.
Why did you kill him?
Stop it.
You're…
a murderer.
I…
I have no friends.
I don't need any of you.
Fuck this.
Hey!
Guys.
No matter what happens, don't die.
And don't let anyone else die.
If you cause someone else to die,
living becomes meaningless.
Okay?
Ms. Park!
Dae-su, don't go.
She left.
Fuck!
ALL CHARACTERS, ORGANIZATIONS,
LOCATIONS, INSTITUTIONS,
AND EVENTS IN THIS SHOW ARE FICTIONAL.
Subtitle translation by: Jeong Lee