ZOMBIE APOCALYPSE IN KOREA
HELLO
I'M ALWAYS ROOTING FOR YOU!
DID SOMETHING HAPPEN IN HYOSAN?
WHY ARE YOU GOING TO HYOSAN?
MY DAD IS FROM HYOSAN
IS THIS THE BEGINNING?
I'VE BEEN WAITING FOR TODAY
ZOMBIES?
FINALLY
HE'S REALLY GOING
I'LL BE BACK
WHAT CAR DO YOU DRIVE?
I HAVE TO WATCH THIS LIVE
WORKING HARD FOR SUBS
ORANGE LOOKS GOOD ON YOU
WHY ARE YOU GOING?
ZOMBIELAND!
WHAT'S WITH THE TRAFFIC?
DID YOU DITCH YOUR CAR?
ARE YOU GOING ON A HIKE?
DAMN, HE REALLY WENT!
ARE YOU NUTS, ORANGE?
IS HYOSAN OKAY?
I CAN'T GET A HOLD OF MY FRIEND
WHERE DID YOU PARK YOUR CAR?
ONWARDS TO ZOMBIELAND!
PREPARING HIS FUNERAL LOL
A ZOMBIE VIRUS BROKE OUT THERE
IT LOOKED REAL ON INSTAGRAM
WHAT'S GOING ON AT HYOSAN?
I WANT TO TAG ALONG!
WHAT ABOUT GLOVES?
DON'T LOSE YOUR ORANGE LEAF
SHOULDN'T YOU WEAR A MASK?
WHAT ZOMBIE? IT'S JUST A VIRUS
PLEASE SAY HELLO TO MY GRANDMA
WHERE IS HYOSAN?
WHAT YOU NEED MOST IS A NECK GUARD
IF YOU GO THERE, DON'T COME BACK
WATCH YOUR ORANGES
IT'S JUST A VIRUS
KEEP YOUR MASK ON AT ALL TIMES
AN EVACUATION ORDER WAS ISSUED
ALL THE ROADS TO HYOSAN ARE CLOSED
MY MOM TOLD ME TO STAY HOME
LOOK AT YOU ALL GEARED UP
REST IN PEACE
WHERE IS HE?
RUN! RUN FASTER!
IS THAT REALLY A ZOMBIE?
RUN AWAY!
THIS IS SCRIPTED, ISN'T IT?
YOU'D MAKE A GREAT SCREENWRITER
WHEN IS THIS OVER?
IT SHOULD BE OVER SOON
THIS FOOTAGE WILL HELP US
HIS ACTING IS ON POINT
THIS IS SUPER EXCITING
WHERE ARE THE POLICE?
TAKE OUT YOUR AXE!
WE CAN'T SEE ANYTHING!
WHAT DID WE SEE JUST NOW?
SHOW US THE STREET
YOUR AXE IS USELESS
I DON'T THINK I CAN SLEEP TONIGHT
YOU SURE HAVE SOME BALLS
CAN YOU SHOW US MORE CLEARLY?
I SAY HE'S SCREWED
CAN HE DO MARTIAL ARTS?
JUST RUN AWAY
IT'S SCARY
WHERE ARE THE REAL ZOMBIES?
ZOMBIELAND! AWESOME!
IS IT OKAY FOR HIM TO BE THERE?
YOU SHOULD'VE TAKEN A GUN
IT'S A ZOMBIE!
MUSIC 3
ANYONE ALIVE?
WHY DID YOU GO TO HELL?
HOW DID YOU EVEN GET IN THERE?
WHAT DID WE JUST SEE?
HE'S GONE TOO FAR
IT'S SCARY AS HELL
YOU LOOK HAGGARD LOL
I'LL SUBSCRIBE TO YOUR CHANNEL
HE REALLY WENT THERE?
HE'S AWESOME
WHY VOLUNTARILY WALK INTO HELL?
NO MORE ZOMBIES?
COVID-19 SPREAD BECAUSE OF PEOPLE LIKE YOU
YOU THINK THIS IS FUN?
QUIET DOWN! YOU'RE BEING TOO LOUD!
LET'S HIT THE LIKE BUTTON, PEOPLE
LET ME CALL THE POLICE FOR YOU
MOM, I WANT TO BE ORANGE WHEN I GROW UP
IS THIS REAL?
I RESPECT YOU, BROTHER
I JUST GOT OFF WORK, STILL STREAMING?
THAT MORON LOL
IS HE INFECTED?
WHERE'S YOUR BADASS AXE?
YOUR MOM WANTS YOU TO STAY HOME
HERE LIES ORANGE
MY CONDOLENCES
WHO LITTERED THERE LOL
LET'S NOT GO THERE
ZOMBIES ARE LIVING CORPSES
IS HE GOING TO TURN INTO A ZOMBIE?
I REALLY NEED TO SLEEP...
I CAN'T TURN THIS OFF
COME BACK
MY HEART'S RACING
I HATE ZOMBIES
THE SOUND MAKES IT SCARIER
IT'LL BE FULL OF ZOMBIES IN THERE
YOU'RE WORKING HARD
SHOULD'VE BROUGHT A GUN
WHY'D YOU GO TO HELL?
STRAIGHT TO HELL
YOU SHOULD HIDE
STOP GOING
BE CAREFUL
WHAT IF THEY'RE IN THERE?
IT'S EMPTY, SPEND THE NIGHT
DON'T MAKE A SOUND!
ARE WE GOING TO WATCH HIM TURN?
WHY WOULD YOU GO THERE...
I'M SCARED...
SAFETY FIRST!
IT'S TOO DARK...
IT'S NOT TOO LATE TO RUN...
CAN YOU BELIEVE HOW MANY ARE WATCHING?
IT'S BETTER THAN A THRILLER
THANKS FOR EVERYTHING
BYE BYE
I HEAR SOMETHING
WHAT IS IT?
ALL THIS JUST FOR LIKES AND SUBSCRIBERS
HE'S DONE FOR
YOU'RE INSANE
CUTE ZOMBIES LOL
RUN! RUN!
I WANT TO GO THERE TOO
SO SCARY
IT'S ALL FAKE ANYWAY LOL
I'M SCARED
KEEP STREAMING!
WHAT THE HELL IS HAPPENING?
ZOMBIES!
IS THIS FOR REAL?
DAMN!
SCHOOL VIOLENCE RESOLUTION COMMITTEE
RESTRICTED AREA
INTERNATIONAL SIGNAL FLAGS
INTERNATIONAL DISTRESS SIGNALS
NEW POST
SCHEDULE SETTINGS
PROCESSING...
GWI-NAM
UPLOAD
ALL CHARACTERS, LOCATIONS, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND EVENTS IN THIS SHOW ARE FICTIONAL.
Subtitle translation by: Jeong Lee