Your hand.
Did you slit it?
To kill yourself?
I heard you named me in your note.
That you want to die because of me.
I'm sorry.
-What a piece of shit.
-You fucker.
If you transfer afterward,
how would that make me look?
Have I ever hit you?
No, never.
Damn right, I didn't. Fuck.
Hey.
You asshole.
-Look at me, asshole.
-Sorry, Gwi-nam.
-Stop.
-Hey, Jin-su.
Please stop!
Cut that shit out.
-You motherfucker.
-What the…
Look at you.
Get up. Fuck! You dipshit!
-Hey, it's splashing all over me!
-Shit!
This asshole.
This fucker.
Have you gone mental or something?
Asshole.
Fuck you, you fucking bastard.
Fuck.
Hey, stop it. Stop.
This bastard pisses me off.
You little shit.
Gwi-nam, help me!
Stop it already. Fuck.
What? You scared?
No. I'm not scared.
Yeah, right.
Damn it.
His BP is okay, but he's lethargic.
He has severe cerebral edema.
I suspect TBI,
and tenderness in his left thorax
and side suggests abdominal bleeding.
I'll transfer him right away
for emergency surgery.
If he can't get surgery
within an hour, he'll be DOA.
Yes.
We'll intubate him,
put in a C-line, then send him over.
Yes.
Okay.
What's taking them so long?
I called a while ago.
RESTRICTED AREA
Dad.
Are they okay?
-What?
-Sorry, Dad.
I know it was wrong,
but I wanted to kill them.
I'm sorry. It'll never happen again.
It's okay.
Is it really okay?
It'll all be okay.
What will be okay?
Everything.
All of it.
Has anything gotten better?
Why won't you answer me?
Either I have to die or they do.
It won't get better until somebody dies.
-Jin-su.
-Let go!
I'm going to kill those assholes.
Stop it, Jin-su.
Let go!
Jin-su. I'll fix everything, so stop.
Do you want to die too?
Should I kill you?
Please, stop it!
I'm sorry, Jin-su.
HOLY BIBLE
I love you.
Jin-su.
TEACHERS' OFFICE
Hello.
Hi.
-Ms. Jung. I'll head out first.
-See you tomorrow.
-Okay.
-Bye.
See you.
Goodbye, ma'am.
Keep up the good work.
Don't forget to do your homework.
-I won't.
-Good.
Good afternoon.
The seemingly never-ending heat
has finally died down.
The muggy, scorching heat
has been replaced by a fresh, cool breeze.
Today, we'll talk about
an interesting study.
A psychologist in the US
conducted a study.
He gathered 48 men and women
who had never met before.
To one group, he gave…
You should have scored a goal.
It's your fault we lost.
Hey. You should've passed it better.
Take that.
Hey.
Okay. Hey, I'm throwing this away now.
Where are you going? Wait for me!
What are you doing?
Moron.
WE ROOT FOR
THE HYOSAN HIGH SCHOOL ARCHERY TEAM
-I'm hungry. Let's go eat tteokbokki.
-Again?
Shouldn't we wake Hyeon-ju up?
-But it's yummy.
-Leave her. She'll just snap at us.
I told them to wake me up. Those jerks.
What the heck?
Hey.
Come here.
Where are you going?
Damn it. This little rat is defiant.
Hey.
What the hell? You little shit.
What are you doing here?
Nothing. It bit me. So annoying.
Goodbye.
I heard your restaurant moved.
How about a grand opening?
We're not having one.
What? Why not?
CHEONGSAN CHICKEN
Seriously? I told them to change the name.
I heard you were.
We're not.
The fryer hasn't even come in yet.
I heard it had.
MOM: WHICH ONE DO YOU LIKE?
CHEONG-SAN: TAKE MY NAME OUT.
I'd know better than you, don't you think?
MOM: OKAY. SO WHICH ONE?
CHEONG-SAN: MOM…
My mom's impossible.
Hey. My phone!
You can't run away.
Hey, gopher.
Let's go have some fried chicken.
It hasn't even opened yet.
It has. She said she's testing out
a new recipe today.
You're going, right?
Of course.
-Are you coming too?
-Sure.
Your mom told On-jo to bring friends.
Is this a double date?
What the hell? Annoying.
What's going on? We're not opening today.
What do you know? Let's go, gopher.
-Do you like it that much?
-You bet. I'm going to eat so much.
This is so much!
Thank you.
-Thank you.
-It looks so good.
Why so much?
On-jo eats a lot.
I don't eat a lot. I eat well.
Yes, that's what I like the best.
Eat up, Gyeong-su.
-Thank you.
-You too, A-sak.
It's I-sak, not A-sak.
Did you change your name?
Yes?
Mom. Don't change someone else's name.
Change the restaurant's name.
-Why are you using my name?
-It was called that before you were born.
Exactly. You named me
after the restaurant.
-I don't like--
-Hey. Quiet.
I like it. It has authenticity.
-Right?
-Of course.
-He's right.
So this is a new recipe that we made.
This is slightly hot,
and this is very hot.
What do you think?
You have to be honest.
It's super-crazy-mad good.
It's delicious.
-Really?
-Ma'am!
Right. If you need a delivery boy,
I'll do it for cheap.
You guys need to study.
On-jo. Is it too hot?
It's salty.
It's salty?
What about this one? Is it very hot?
No. It's salty.
Why is it salty? That's bad.
Honey!
-Yes?
-She says it's salty.
It's salty?
-On-jo says it's salty.
-Why?
-That can't be.
-It's good.
-Did you make it extra salty?
-Yes, it is.
-It tastes good to me.
Let me try.
Stop eating. You said it's salty.
But it still tastes good.
Ah, right.
Did you hear about
the science teacher, Mr. Lee?
What about him?
He smells like a rotting corpse.
Jeez.
Na-yeon spread that rumor, right?
It's true. He didn't come to school
for a few days after his son went missing.
Then he came to class and…
Rock, paper, scissors for it?
-Rock, paper, scissors!
-I'm not playing.
…he smelled like a rotting corpse.
How would she know what that smells like?
Has she smelled one before?
She knows every smell except that one.
Since she never smelled it before,
that must be it.
He became weird
ever since his son went missing.
His son was an outcast.
I heard he got bullied badly.
Yes. I feel sorry for him.
I feel sorry for Mr. Lee too.
Remember last week
when he left during class?
BETWEEN TISSUE CELLS
CELLULAR RESPIRATION
-Is class over?
-Did the bell ring?
-What was that?
-What did he write?
He'd never done that before.
They say he was a genius.
And geniuses often go crazy.
I guess you never have to worry
about going crazy.
Hey. Are you looking down on me?
I'm so full.
Hurry up.
We're late anyway.
Cheong-san, hold on.
Why? We're late. I have a Literature test.
I need to ask you something.
What is it?
-Never mind.
-What?
Forget it. What would you know?
What is it?
Is this better
or is this better?
Look closely.
This? Or this?
This looks better, right?
Get lost.
ENGLISH ACADEMY
HYOSAN HIGH SCHOOL
SUPPLY ROOM
COMMENDATION
NAM SO-JU
Exams start next week, right?
You always bring up tests when I'm eating.
When else should I ask?
Hey. We have to finish the vegetables.
Okay?
Hey. You won't get good grades anyway,
so don't stress about it.
Don't give up on me, Dad. I can do it.
I'm not giving up.
I just have no expectations.
That's giving up.
So this is from Cheong-san's place?
Two days ago…
there was an accident by a tollgate,
so I went to the scene,
and whether you're rich or poor,
got good grades or bad,
you're all equal in accidents.
Grades aren't important.
Being safe and healthy is.
I mean it.
I'll make it into tier five this time.
Don't push yourself.
Then I'll make it into tier six.
You shouldn't scam your dad. Here, eat.
It's salty but tasty.
It's Cheong-san.
He's so punctual.
See you later.
Eat another bite. Hey.
Hey, kid!
Are you upset?
That punk. Dang it.
Jeez. She hardly ate.
I should eat her leftovers first.
-Get ready. Rock, paper, scissors.
-Rock, paper, scissors.
-Rock, paper, scissors!
Yes!
I'm seriously going to kill you.
Hey, On-jo!
Nam On-jo!
Play fair, you punk.
Damn, I'm so out of breath.
Carry it.
Look at this.
I got hurt while making breakfast.
Let's go, gopher.
Nam-ra.
Classroom president!
Hurry up!
RESIDENTS ONLY
STUDENTS OF SUBSIDIZED HOUSING STAY AWAY
I'm going first!
Wait for me!
Hey, punk!
-Bye.
-Okay.
Just go! That bastard!
Hey, you punks! Get back here!
You live in the rental apartments, right?
Hey! You punks!
Hey!
Hi.
See you later!
Wait for me! Damn it!
That fucking bum.
Ji-min!
Eat this with your friends during choir.
I said I didn't want it.
Goodness.
She skipped breakfast too.
Seriously?
-Tick-tock. Hurry up.
-Hurry.
-Wake up earlier.
-Get inside.
And that's it. Stop right there! Stop!
-Really?
-Put your names down.
I'm so pissed.
Let's see.
Can you let it slide just once?
Of course not.
-You have been chosen.
-Please.
-Please, sir.
-You get three demerits each.
You three are always late.
Get moving.
Hey.
Is it my fault
that asshole Jin-su went missing?
That's not it.
Then why did you tattle on me?
The teacher said
to write down everything we knew.
And what do you know?
Damn it.
Fuck you, asshole. What do you know?
These assholes are pissing me off.
Hey. Do it.
What are you looking at?
Where are you looking?
Fuck.
It's okay.
Fuck off.
Stay still.
CONSTRUCTION NOTICE
NEW CONSTRUCTION IN PROGRESS
HYOSAN HIGH SCHOOL
You fucking pervert.
You like that?
Hey.
Keep filming.
You asshole.
Film her.
Keep filming, asshole.
-You fucking asshole.
-That's enough.
Let him go.
Fuck. You asshole.
You little dumbass chicken.
You used to party with us.
Don't try to act all holier-than-thou.
Get lost.
Grow up.
You guys, go.
Go ahead.
I dare you.
Move.
Will you live like this forever?
Let's go.
You look really sexy in this.
Should I send it to your mom?
You know I'm friends with her
on Facebook, right?
You crazy asshole. What kind of weirdo
is friends with an old lady?
I can't go.
It's okay. You can.
It's not okay.
If I leave now…
it'll be twice as bad tomorrow.
Take it off.
Should I do it for you?
Hurry up, damn it.
Su-hyeok.
Hey. Morning.
-What?
-Come to the rooftop after lunch.
The rooftop? I don't fight anymore.
Do you think I'd want to fight?
Then why?
See you later.
What was that?
-It's good.
-Are you changing?
-Why are you looking?
-Don't look. Seriously.
-Do you have water?
-Mine's too warm.
Let me have some.
-You heard.
-I can't hear.
-Are you an idiot?
-Do you hear the song?
Hey, this asshole
lost to me big-time yesterday.
-Hey.
-It was because of the keyboard!
-It was the keyboard.
-He sucks.
-But the lady working there seems cute.
-I'm telling you.
I gave you a head start.
-What are you talking about?
-I said I'd beat you, right?
That's not true.
I let you score two goals.
-He went easy on you.
-That's bullshit!
What do I do?
-Don't bullshit me.
-About what?
I don't know.
-What do I do?
-What? Why? What is it?
I don't know.
-I'll tell you later.
-Tell me what?
-What is it?
-The keyboard was crappy.
That's bullshit.
Sleeping again?
-Su-hyeok.
-I smell your feet from here.
I'm sure this guy didn't wear socks.
-Hey.
-It's not okay.
-Take him out.
-Should we?
-Hey.
-Really?
-That's ridiculous.
-Hey, seriously.
What's that called?
Give me a break.
-Let's break his leg.
-Go ahead.
-Hey!
-Then I'll break his fingers--
What the…
Get off of there. You're gross.
Fine. My bad.
What's the big deal?
Stop that! You're dirty.
What the hell?
Let it go. Why are you so grumpy?
What is it?
What did I do that was so wrong?
You punks. Take your seats now. Move it.
Hi.
Hello!
Hi. Good morning.
Hand in your phones.
Anybody in touch with Hyeon-ju?
Nobody?
None of you tried calling her?
We cleaned the science lab
together yesterday,
but I haven't seen her since.
Okay.
If anyone hears from her,
let me know right away, okay?
-Yes, ma'am.
Exams start next week,
so get your acts together.
Hey, your phone.
Hey.
I hear it.
-Why didn't you silence it?
-Hand over your real phones.
-You idiot.
-Dae-su. Seriously?
How stupid is he?
I love getting on his nerves.
Hey.
Seriously, Wu-jin?
-What are you going to do about it?
-On-jo.
This is your phone from last year.
-She's dumber than me.
-Take it.
Take it now.
Hello, Mr. Lee.
-Yes, hello.
-Hi.
You know Kim Hyeon-ju from my class?
She didn't go home last night.
The kids say they haven't seen her
after cleaning the science lab yesterday.
Oh, is that so?
You haven't seen her, have you?
No, I haven't.
You went home
without stopping by the lab, right?
That's what I said.
I see. I'm sorry.
No one has seen her
since she came here, so…
Is someone inside?
Yes.
A lab hamster.
-I see.
-I need to prepare for class now.
Oh, I see.
Okay.
SUPPLY ROOM
A student was bit by a lab hamster.
She has been sedated with benzodiazepine…
It's slowing down the infection,
but only by a few hours at most.
Don't kill me.
Please don't kill me.
Don't kill you?
Don't bother having hope.
A virus
is somewhere between a living organism
and a non-living organism.
Like a living organism,
it adapts to its surroundings and evolves.
Everything that evolves in this manner
should be considered
an independent living organism.
Mr. Lee.
The textbook says a virus is not
an independent living organism.
Whether or not something is
an independent living organism
doesn't depend on its metabolism,
but its will to survive.
If it has such a strong will…
I'M FUCKING SEXY
…the instinct to survive
surpasses intelligence.
The ecosystem is eventually
dominated by that will.
Humanity has never once defeated a virus.
Leucochloridium paradoxum.
This parasite's final target is a bird.
The parasite enters a snail
and infects its tentacles.
It makes the snail go to a high place
and get eaten by a bird.
In other words, the infected snail
commits suicide as the parasite orders.
Tell me.
Is it because the snail
is less intelligent than the parasite?
No.
It's because the parasite's will
to survive was stronger than the snail's.
The teacher's talking.
The evolving and hereditary
will to survive is…
Keep your head up.
…the sole standard by which
independent living organisms are defined.
Then is the textbook wrong?
The textbook?
It's wrong.
Here, "free from" means the lack of.
Who wants to interpret this?
Okay.
Hee-su.
I need to use the bathroom.
Okay, go.
Okay, then.
Who wants to have a crack at it?
Our classroom president?
The truth is, all of us have
some sort of prejudice.
We all have preconceptions
about other people.
Okay. Good.
Next, Bare-su. Stand up.
Hey.
-That moron.
-Yes?
Why are you "Bare-su"?
It's short for Barefoot Su-hyeok. Bare-su.
Okay.
He really hates wearing socks.
So he stinks a lot.
Okay, Bare-su.
What did Nam-ra just say?
Well…
-Well…
He doesn't know. He knows nothing.
She was absolutely correct.
So what was
her absolutely correct interpretation?
He knows.
How could he not?
-So…
-You know, right?
Huh?
What the hell? Isn't that Hyeon-ju?
Hyeon-ju.
Hey, Hyeon-ju.
Hyeon-ju!
Hey. What's wrong? Are you okay?
-Hyeon-ju.
-Is that blood?
-She got hurt!
-Ms. Park.
Yes, it's me. Do you recognize me?
He grabbed me…
The science teacher grabbed me
and locked me up.
He locked you up? The science teacher?
Mr. Lee Byeong-chan? Huh?
He tied me up…
I told you, didn't I?
Just shut up, okay?
Let's go to the infirmary.
That's crazy.
-Nam-ra. Have them study.
-Shouldn't we call the police?
-Stay quiet while I go and check.
-She said he tied her up.
Hyeon-ju. Get up.
I'll carry her.
Okay.
-Someone help him.
-I'll help.
-Good.
-Me too.
Go back to your seats!
Now.
-Hyeon-ju.
-What's wrong?
Guys, hold her still.
What's wrong with her?
What's wrong? Do you feel sick?
What do I do?
Does your stomach hurt? Is it bad?
Let me see.
Please help.
Yes, hold on.
Put her on the bed.
Please take a look at her.
Her temperature is way too low.
Hold this down so she doesn't kick it off.
-Hold her.
-Hyeon-ju.
-It's okay.
-Please call an ambulance.
-I'll sedate her and clean her wounds.
-Okay.
Hyeon-ju. It's okay.
Hyeon-ju. You're okay now.
EMERGENCY CALL
-I'm hot.
-Hang in there.
Your temperature is too low.
I'm hot. I'm too hot.
You'll be at the hospital soon.
I'm here, so don't worry.
The science teacher gave me
a strange shot.
A shot?
Mr. Lee Byeong-chan gave you a shot?
He tried to kill me.
Hyeon-ju, what shot?
I'm going to kill them all.
Hyeon-ju.
Are you okay?
-Hold her down so I can give her a shot.
-Okay.
Just a second, okay? Hyeon-ju. Hang on.
It's odd. Hyeon-ju was really odd.
-Totally.
-It's weird to everyone else too, right?
It's strange that she was gone all day,
and she was all bloody
and talking about the science teacher.
Maybe she went somewhere and got hurt,
and then came back here.
-It must be true.
-What? Did you hear something?
You know how they said
that Mr. Lee's son ran away from home?
I heard that wasn't the case.
-He committed suicide.
-Don't be stupid.
-He committed suicide?
-You believe that?
I'm telling you it's true.
Hyeon-ju hung out with them
and bullied him a lot too.
So the science teacher
is going after everyone
who bullied his son one by one.
To kill them.
Who said that?
-All the kids.
-All the kids who?
I did see Hyeon-ju last
in the science lab.
Hey.
I think
maybe Mr. Lee made Hyeon-ju film porn.
-Porn?
-Moron.
Get your mind out of the gutter.
You fat-ass.
-Why are you cursing at me, moron?
-Because you're a pervert, moron.
So why did he kidnap her?
-Have you ever been kidnapped?
-Of course, not. Moron.
That's no way
to talk to your brother-in-law.
I told you to stop saying that.
Hey, what happened?
-What happened?
-How is she?
How's Hyeon-ju?
It's no joke. She was biting people…
Where's On-jo?
She got hurt.
Where? How bad is it?
Just a little bit.
Hyeon-ju bit her?
I think she went crazy.
Her temperature is low,
but she said she was hot.
-She tried to bite us when we covered her.
-What?
Does she have rabies?
Don't be stupid.
But Hyeon-ju had a strange smell.
-What smell?
-The same as the science teacher.
-A rotting corpse.
-Yes, that.
And she said he gave her a strange shot.
What a total psycho.
Shouldn't we report this to the police?
I don't know.
Ms. Park said she'd handle it.
What the…
She's studying right now.
She's number one in our school.
So? Where's On-jo?
In the infirmary.
I think she went into shock
due to hypothermia.
I gave her a sedative.
Okay. We'll take her to Hyosan Hospital.
Did you contact her parents?
Yes. They just left.
Please take good care of her.
-Okay.
-Thank you.
She'll be fine.
Are you okay?
Look at me. Were you startled?
Totally.
My God.
What's wrong with your friend?
I don't know.
I'll tell you later when I get home.
I'm on call,
so I won't be home until morning.
Make sure not to get it wet.
Call me right away if anything happens.
I'll rush right over. Okay?
-Okay.
-All right. Bye.
-Hurry.
-Okay.
Please take good care of her.
-Given the situation, I can't talk long.
-Okay.
-Go.
-You should go.
Thanks for your help, both of you.
I'll head back in soon,
so don't tell anyone about this yet, okay?
-Yes, ma'am.
-Okay.
Please don't tell anyone
for the time being.
Okay.
Go back to the classroom. Let's go.
Are you okay? Were you bit?
-No, it's just a scratch.
-You didn't get hurt anywhere else?
Hey.
Why did you want to see me on the roof?
-What?
-You said to come up after lunch.
Can you just tell me now?
I'm playing basketball after lunch.
What is it?
NAM ON-JO
Hey. This means… you want to go out.
Yes.
-You're going out with Cheong-san.
-No, I'm not.
We've lived next door
ever since we were kids,
so his mom always gives us chicken…
-I do like chicken.
-Okay.
But not him.
I see.
-On-jo!
-But--
I heard you got hurt. Where?
How bad is it?
You're such a klutz.
I'm fine.
Was she hurt badly?
She was careless again, wasn't she?
No.
She got hurt while trying
to avoid getting bitten by Hyeon-ju.
Hey.
You're going out with On-jo, right?
Right?
Yes. That's right.
Did you expect me to say that? You moron.
If the world comes to an end
and only On-jo, me, and a zombie are left,
I'd go out with the zombie.
Why do you ask?
No reason. Let's go.
What's for lunch today?
Tell me why you asked.
I want tonkatsu.
How much longer?
We're almost there.
Hyeon-ju went to the hospital.
-Mr. Lee. Wait.
-Hey.
-We can't send her to a hospital.
-Calm down.
-What are you saying?
-Let go of me!
No! Explain yourself.
We can't send her to a hospital.
We have to put her in quarantine.
Do you hear me?
Sit down.
You already turned things upside down
at the school because of your son.
How could you say that?
Jin-su was the victim!
And you forced us to bury it.
What kind of nonsense is that?
We have the school evaluation
coming up too. You should've called me.
Before calling an ambulance.
What if the police come?
I already called the police.
You should resolve
these matters internally.
I'll call the police if needed,
so tell them not to come.
-But…
-Mr. Lee.
Police.
It's been a while,
Mr. Lee Byeong-chan.
It's so good.
-What?
-Nothing.
Hey. You'll burn a hole
in Cheong-san's face.
I wasn't looking at him.
Yeah, right. The entire school knows
you two are going out.
We're not.
I mean it.
Actually,
you can't tell anyone, okay?
Tell them what?
I actually…
Never mind.
-Hey.
-Stop that.
What is it?
Nothing.
Did you sleep with him?
You did, right? I guessed it, right?
Are you insane?
I told Su-hyeok that I like him.
What?
You crazy--
-What the hell?
-You scared me.
-What?
-What is she, an attention whore?
-Quiet.
-What the hell?
Are you insane?
Cheong-san… Su-hyeok?
Quiet.
-You eat it. It's okay.
-What?
What did you say?
Did you just ask him out?
I gave him my name tag.
So you just threw yourself at him.
So?
That's all.
What?
He didn't give you an answer?
Or give off a vibe?
You couldn't tell how he felt or anything?
This is driving me nuts.
You're driving me nuts.
It's bad for your ears
wearing them too long.
Earphones. They're bad for your ears.
I know.
Do you want
to visit Hyeon-ju after school?
-Why?
-You're classroom president.
My mom made me classroom president
by donating to the school.
That's why no one considers me
the classroom president.
So why must I act like it?
-What?
-I'm just amazed.
I've never heard you talk
this much before.
I thought you were incapable
of saying more than five words.
-I want to cut class.
-I'm so sleepy.
What the hell?
INFIRMARY
Hey.
Come look.
-What is it?
-Look.
What's with the nurse?
She must be fucking drunk.
Did she get fired? What's wrong with her?
What is she doing in bare feet?
What the hell?
Fuck!
-She hit her head really hard.
-Scared the hell out of me.
What's wrong with her?
-What the…
-Shouldn't we call an ambulance?
You're screwed.
What's wrong with her? Hey.
What are you doing, moron?
Help!
What do we do?
Fuck. Are you nuts?
Out of my way!
What the hell?
Fuck!
Stay away!
-Rock, paper, scissors!
Yes!
Eun-ji.
Don't do it.
Want to come up too?
Eun-ji.
Come down. Let's talk from here.
They said
they'll post it online.
No.
They agreed to delete it.
They promised me.
This is hell.
I'm just escaping from hell.
I'll take care of it.
I can do it.
I'll delete everything.
So,
please,
I'm begging you.
Please don't do it, Eun-ji.
Why are you crying?
Do you… like me?
It would be really funny
if two losers liked each other.
If two losers go out,
they become even bigger losers.
So stay away from me.
Eun-ji.
Stay away
from my dead body too.
Eun-ji!
Prez!
Hurry!
Run!
I have a good idea.
Ask Cheong-san.
Forget it.
Su-hyeok and Cheong-san are close.
Ask him how Su-hyeok feels about you.
No.
On-jo. Listen to Mama.
Su-hyeok may have told him already.
Still, I can't tell him.
He'll tease me like crazy.
Put mine away too, gopher.
Hey, Cheong-san.
On-jo needs to talk to you.
Hey. You and Su-hyeok are close, right?
Totally. Why?
See?
What is it?
Nothing. Get lost.
-So, On-jo--
-Hey.
Want to die?
Fine.
Hey. A real friend would help
in situations like this.
What is it?
What's wrong? Did Su-hyeok say something?
No.
Did you two fight?
I said no.
Then what? Did he say he likes you?
Did he say that?
-What?
-Did he say he likes me?
Su-hyeok?
No? He didn't say anything?
What are you talking about?
Earlier…
-You can't tell anyone, okay?
-What?
You really can't tell anyone.
About what?
I told him that I like him,
but I don't know how he feels.
He won't say anything.
Hey.
Yes?
Can you ask him what he thinks about me?
We're not close.
Yes, you are.
No, we're not.
Can't you help me out for once?
You're not a real friend.
Fuck.
Move!
ALL CHARACTERS, ORGANIZATIONS,
LOCATIONS, INSTITUTIONS,
AND EVENTS IN THIS SHOW ARE FICTIONAL.
Subtitle translation by: Jeong Lee