Jae-jun, are you at your base?
You're not going anywhere, right?
Put on your gas masks!
I'm not going there, Mom. Don't worry.
They said on TV
that all the soldiers are going there.
So you must be going too.
Why would I?
I'm being discharged next week.
When you're about to be discharged,
they don't have you stand guard
or even train.
As if.
Then why was your last leave canceled?
Can you imagine how worried I am?
-You didn't even call--
-Mom.
What?
I have to go.
Did you go somewhere else
instead of coming home?
Where are you going?
To play soccer. Bye, Mom.
Jae-jun!
Why are you playing soccer?
What if you get hurt?
Then what should I do all day long?
I'm bored of playing video games.
All you did was play video games before.
-Status.
-Clear.
Report.
Control, this is Shadow Gamma.
All infected on F1 have been eliminated.
No survivors found within range.
We're moving to the third floor.
I know you're lying.
You're not going to play soccer, are you?
I'm telling you, I am.
Come out. You're safe.
We're saved! Come out.
Hurry.
Walk slowly. Maintain order.
It's safe this way.
Hurry!
Zone three on B2.
Difficulty suppressing the infected.
Okay. Pull out.
Think of me
and don't go anywhere dangerous.
Okay?
I love you, Son.
You know I do, right?
I love you too, Mom.
I'll call you later.
See you when I get discharged.
-Okay?
-Jae-jun.
Get back safely.
Make sure to call me later.
I'll be waiting, okay?
There's hope.
A small number of white blood cells
were detected in the blood.
Even after full transformation,
the white blood cells remained
and were fighting like warriors.
If the body temperature rises,
the white blood cells activate.
Current temperature is 29 degrees Celsius.
In case blood does not flow,
I'll raise the temperature
both internally and externally.
Leave a message if you want.
I don't have anything to say.
You?
We believe you.
You can untie that now.
Why are you doing this?
Because the others are nervous.
Aren't you?
No.
Why not?
Just because.
I'm not.
You know how I said
I wanted to bite you earlier?
It's okay. Don't say things like that.
It felt like I was dreaming.
You gave off such a nice scent.
What kind of scent?
I'm not sure.
It was something
I had never smelled before.
All I could think of was
that I wanted to eat you.
I wanted to bite you.
I kept thinking of biting and eating you.
That was all I could think of.
Then I heard your voice.
Nam-ra.
Your voice woke me up.
You know you never called me
by my name before?
You always call me "Prez."
It was the first time
you called me by my name.
I know.
I was afraid you'd find out
if I called you by your name.
Find out what?
That I like you.
I don't get good grades,
and I hung out with the bullies
in tenth grade.
But you're a model student
and get good grades.
And you're pretty.
Su-hyeok.
I like you.
I'm glad…
I found out before I died.
NIGHT DUTY ROOM
Hello, sir.
Shit. You scared me.
You're…
you're Seon-yeong, right?
It's Eun-ji.
Right. Eun-ji.
Are you all right?
I am.
But I'm starving.
It's driving me crazy.
What?
Hey.
You're not okay, are you?
You were bitten, weren't you?
Yes.
I was.
All right.
God, you must've been very hungry.
Eun-ji.
My God. That must've hurt a lot.
Right?
You should go to the infirmary, then!
Sir, remember what you said
when I told you I was getting bullied?
"Why are you telling me?"
"Go tell your homeroom teacher."
And after the committee, you also said,
"You're an outcast
because you're so dense."
Do I still seem dense?
Okay, I get it. So get out.
Get out. Please.
Stay back.
Get out.
-What is it?
-I heard something strange.
What if she's turning?
-I thought hambies didn't turn?
-You scared me.
My bad.
I hear it.
-What?
-What do you hear?
Someone is puking.
It stopped.
What did?
The puking.
Stop that. You're scaring me.
Don't you hear it?
What are you talking about?
What?
-What is it?
-Are you scared?
Stop that.
It's just that
you're breathing the loudest.
I hate this fucking school.
Do you hear something?
All I hear is that zombie.
What?
Let's get out of here.
This place feels weird.
We can't just leave.
There are too many zombies.
We should've gone to the rooftop
when the music was playing earlier.
Damn it.
Music.
That's right. We have music.
Where do we have music?
Fuck.
What the fuck am I supposed to do?
Ah, fuck!
You moron. Fuck.
You scared me.
Hey, come in here.
What are you waiting for? Move your ass!
Hurry up. Get in here.
Get in here.
Come in, you asshole.
-Are you okay?
-What?
Where were you?
Me?
Obviously, you.
What happened to your eye?
What? My eye?
Stop spacing out, asshole.
What are you looking at, moron?
Hey. Listen carefully. You see that car?
-Run to it.
-Why should I?
Just shut up and run if I say so.
You want me to lure the zombies?
You go that way and lure the zombies.
I'll go that way and scream.
Let's run to the snack shop
while the zombies are confused.
-Got that?
-I'll be going away from the snack shop.
That's why you should run like hell
and circle around.
Go. Get going. Run.
I don't want to.
You chickenshit.
Get out. Go.
I'm not a chicken anymore.
I'm not your gopher anymore either.
Hey. What's gotten into you?
Snap out of it, will you?
Look at me.
It's me, asshole.
Me.
Fine. I'll go.
Hurry.
Hurry up. Now.
Come with me.
What?
Quiet.
The zombies will come.
Watch carefully.
Look.
I'm above you now, got that?
Okay.
You moron. You chickenshit.
Beg for your life.
Come on.
"Save me." Go on.
Save me. Please save me.
I don't want to.
Gwi-nam! Help me, you fucking asshole!
Cheong-san.
I'll gouge your eye out.
We'll build a tall barricade here
and lure them in with music.
We'll use the instruments too.
If we leave the door open,
they'll hear the music and come in.
When the hallway clears,
we'll use the back door and go up.
So you're saying we should
stack desks, chairs, and whatnot
in the middle here,
open the door,
and run out through the back door, right?
Not here. A little farther back.
More room on this side.
Why is that?
There aren't many of us,
but there are many zombies.
I see. She sucks at school,
but she's pretty smart.
Hey.
It's a compliment.
Let's give it a shot.
We can think about the rest later.
We have a TV too.
Let's connect it and make it louder.
We have to look for the cord.
-Ji-min, help me look.
-Okay.
-Me too.
-This way, Ji-min.
Let's give it a shot.
Guys.
What should we do first?
Let's untie that.
We should build a frame first.
I'll do the moving.
You guys work on the frame.
It's okay.
Su-hyeok.
Keep it down.
She can never get close
to the others like this.
And no one will approach her.
How do we do this quietly?
-Hatred is contagious.
-Try this one if that's too heavy.
But so is trust.
Which one? That one?
Not that one.
Put it down here.
Right here?
Nam-ra.
One, two, three.
You should've been
the classroom president.
Joon-yeong, I can't find the cable.
Where is it?
Let's help.
Let's go.
Hey, can you lift this?
One, two, three.
What can I do? That hurts.
RESTRICTED AREA
Hey. Keep it down.
Be quiet.
They'll latch on in swarms.
Make sure to stack it right
so it doesn't fall.
Well…
Over there. Fill the empty spot.
Let's tie it there first.
You need to tie them tighter.
More tightly!
On the other side too.
Is there anything bigger?
It's looking great.
It hurts!
Suck it up.
You're a damn senior.
Must seniors endure everything?
I'm enduring not smoking,
but you can't handle that?
-Do you die from not smoking?
-Yes, you do.
I feel like I'm going to fucking die,
so you suck it up too.
We'll take the trail behind the building.
Once we get past the tennis courts,
we can go through the construction site
and go up the mountain.
Can we make it?
-I don't know.
-Fuck.
Min-jae.
If you don't think you can go on,
just drop it and shoot.
Okay.
What about me?
-Let's go.
-Mi-jin, on three.
Ready? One, two, three!
Hold on. Wait.
Wait.
Hey. Give them the arrows
when they run out, okay?
Let's go.
One, two, three.
Fuck, he's so heavy!
Shit.
Hold on.
Hey. Wait.
Hey. It broke! What now?
-Get back in. Hurry!
-Get inside! Hurry!
-Get back!
-Damn it!
They're coming!
-Oh my God.
-They are coming!
Hey. Just go without me.
Idiot.
You can't take me anyway.
You'll post about it on Facebook
if we leave you behind.
I won't.
I don't trust you.
Hey, stop pretending to be nice.
You killed Ha-lim.
What? You don't care about others.
You're such a dick.
Let's make it again. Stronger this time.
Okay.
What? What the hell do you want from me?
It hurts like crazy.
Do you know how it feels to be dying?
I do.
I feel that way every time I take a test.
But
there's only so much I can take
because you're in pain.
Shut up and stay quiet.
CHEONGSAN CHICKEN
Is that okay? Does it hurt?
Sir.
I think
we should use our mobility
to get out of here first
and send the army for the kids.
I think that's more rational.
Sir?
If we all die,
who will let them know about the laptop--
Ho-seong.
It's Ho-cheol.
Ho-cheol.
Do you know why people run to safety
when there's danger?
It's because others put themselves
in danger for them.
There's no reason for us
to put ourselves in danger for them.
You're so frustrating.
I ought to just…
If you die,
I'll put in a request with the higher-ups
to get a statue of you erected.
One as big as Admiral Yi Sun-sin's.
Okay? Happy now?
Seriously.
If you're scared, you can stay here.
Goodness. Well put.
We'll leave here together now.
We'll go zoom on the motorcycle, okay?
What about Mommy?
Mommy?
Let's come back for her later, okay?
My son is about your age. He's handsome.
I'll introduce him to you later.
I already have a boyfriend.
What did I say to do once we go out?
You said to keep my eyes shut
and hold onto you.
That's right. Good girl. Very good.
Are you ready?
No.
CHEONGSAN CHICKEN
Go faster! Faster!
Speed up! Go faster!
Shut up!
You're drawing them to us, asshole!
Shut up, you idiot!
I said to shut up!
Oh my goodness!
-They're behind us!
-In front of us too, moron!
Turn!
-Where?
-Turn!
-Shit.
-This way, sir. This way.
Watch out! Careful!
Right! Go right!
It's a dead end! Fuck!
-What do we do?
-Wait.
Hey! There's a way!
-There is?
-There is!
Let's go.
What are you doing?
Come this way, assholes! Let's go!
Sir!
Se-bin, we're saved!
Pipe down unless you want more of them.
Help me!
What was that?
-Over here!
-What's that?
Where's it coming from?
Here!
Help me!
Hey!
-Over here!
-What is that?
Hey, you idiot!
-Thank goodness.
-Why's he talking down to us?
-All right. Hang on.
-What took you so long?
-Let's just go. Please?
-What?
Let's just go.
Please help me.
Just go. Let's go.
-Do you have something to drink?
-They're coming.
Where?
No, they're not, asshole.
Can you make it down?
No. I hurt my leg.
-I can't get down.
-I said let's just go.
Let's go. Come on.
What? Why are you getting off?
-What do you plan to do?
-Hey.
Here, take the baby.
Why am I taking it?
Hurry up, sir.
-Hold on.
-What are you doing?
Stay still.
Stay right here.
-Bring the bike close.
-Gosh.
Yes, climb up there.
Bring it close. Hurry.
They're coming. Come on. Hurry.
Screw that.
Ho-cheol!
-What? Where is he going?
-Hey!
-Hey! Ho-cheol!
-Where the hell is he going?
-Hey, Seoul University! Hey!
-Get back here!
I think this is good enough.
Okay.
Aren't you coming over?
Come over. We left a gap.
Let's go.
Come over here.
Someone has to open the door.
Couldn't you use your head
a little better?
It's okay.
-I'll open it and come over.
-Wait.
I'll go with you.
-It's okay.
-It is not okay.
Here.
Something happened
between you and Gwi-nam, right?
He wanted to kill you.
Shit.
I saw him kill the principal.
I said I'd tell the cops,
so he tried to kill me.
Crazy asshole.
Gwi-nam's dead.
Really?
Yes.
He fell from the fourth floor
while we were fighting.
-And I like Nam-ra.
-What?
I've liked Nam-ra for a while.
-The classroom president?
=Be good to On-jo, okay?
Don't treat her like a guy, you moron.
What are you looking at?
I'm going to open the door.
Go. Get over there.
Go.
Damn it!
Oh no.
Fuck!
Dae-su, make some noise!
You zombie bastards!
Again!
God.
Come here, you fucking zombies!
Wu-jin!
We can't go yet! Hang on!
Nam-ra!
It's going to fall!
Fuck.
How much longer? When can we fucking go?
A little more. Hang on!
We need to study him
to create a treatment or a vaccine,
but we don't have
the facilities or the manpower here.
We must take him to the KDCA.
He cannot leave the quarantine zone
for any reason whatsoever.
Recruit scientists and build the facility.
Airlift all the necessary equipment
and medical supplies.
-What's his name?
-He's Staff Sergeant Lee Jae-jun.
He had a week left until his discharge,
but he volunteered for the operation.
Call his parents
and get their consent for research.
We're under martial law,
so we don't need consent.
If you give the go-ahead,
we can begin the experiments
or autopsy right away.
Call his parents.
Even if we're under martial law,
that's our duty
as the military who took in their child.
Yes, sir.
Commander, sir.
There's an assembly member
awaiting testing.
Follow the rules.
It's Park Eun-hee
from the National Defense Committee.
Darn it.
I'm the commander.
It's nice to meet you. I'm--
Even if you are an assembly member,
there won't be any special treatment.
That is what I came to tell you.
Don't harass the people working hard.
I'd appreciate it
if you'd stay quiet and follow the rules.
Fine. I have a favor to ask though.
Please send a chopper
to Hyosan High School.
A firefighter is heading there alone.
Commander. Hey. Wait!
Send a chopper to the school!
We must save the students!
Even wars can't eliminate schools.
Even if we win the war,
we lose if we lose our schools!
How many students have we saved so far?
Zero so far, sir.
We think no one got out
because they were in class.
Are there choppers available?
No, sir.
They've all been sent on missions.
Request a Black Hawk
and have them scan schools in Hyosan.
Yes, sir.
MAP OF HYOSAN
Should we scan Gangha-dong as well?
Isn't that where your mother is?
We can check
once it is selected as a rescue zone.
Yes, sir.
It's clear! We have to go now!
Hurry!
Cheong-san!
-Go!
-You go first!
I think I'm going to shit myself! Go!
-Come on.
-Let's go.
Hurry.
Move.
PROPER EDUCATION BREEDS GOOD CHARACTER!
Alpha is at the rescue zone.
It is impossible to check for survivors
at Cheongmok Middle School.
Alpha lifting.
Going to Hyosan High.
Come on.
Over here!
Here! I'm here!
Open it!
It's locked.
What?
Move.
Wait. Step aside.
Shit.
Is anyone there?
Anyone?
Is anyone there? Anyone?
Open the door!
Nobody's there! Get back.
Hey, brother-in-law.
One, two, three!
THE ROOFTOP IS OFF LIMITS TO STUDENTS
Shit.
They're coming.
What's coming?
We're outcasts again.
And this is still hell.
I hope everyone dies.
Every single one of them.
Mom.
It's me.
Dad, you're okay too, right?
I'm…
I'm doing okay.
Mom.
But Cheongsan Chicken is still lame.
If it were Cheongsan Air, Cheongsan Auto,
or Cheongsan Group,
it would be fine.
CHEONGSAN CHICKEN
HYOSAN HIGH SCHOOL
They're here.
DOOR WILL OPEN AUTOMATICALLY
IN CASE OF FIRE
Get back!
Throw this over!
Out of my way.
Freeze!
Get down!
Are you okay?
What about your friends?
Isn't there anyone else?
Hold onto it!
Pull it tight!
ONE HEART
ALL CHARACTERS, ORGANIZATIONS,
LOCATIONS, INSTITUTIONS,
AND EVENTS IN THIS SHOW ARE FICTIONAL.
Subtitle translation by: Jeong Lee