Give me your hand.
Did you cut it?
You try to kill yourself, huh?
I heard you named me in your suicide note.
You said you can't go on because of me.
I'm sorry.
- What a disrespectful loser.
- You motherfucker.
If you transfer afterwards,
how does that make me look?
- Have I ever fucking hit you, huh?
- No, never.
No, right? That's right.
He's all yours.
There.
You asshole! You asshole!
- Hit me back, asshole.
- No, wait.
- Please, stop.
- Hey.
- Stop.
- Hey!
Just fucking stop!
You psycho.
Get up. You bastard!
- Hey, you splash me!
- Shit!
Are you out
of your fucking mind, man?
Asshole.
Fuck you, you fucking bitch.
Motherfucker!
Fuck.
All right. Knock it off.
Let's go. Come on, we're out of here.
You fucker.
Get him off!
Cut it out already.
Come on.
What? You scared?
Not at all. I'm not scared.
Yeah, whatever.
Shit.
His BP is okay, but he's drowsy.
He has severe edema
in the back of his head
and tenderness in his left thorax
so I say TBI and abdominal bleeding.
I'll transfer him right away
for emergency surgery.
If he isn't in surgery within an hour,
he'll be DOA no question.
Yes.
We'll intubate him,
put in a c-line, then send him over.
Yeah.
Okay.
What the hell is taking them so long?
I called two hours ago.
RESTRICTED AREA
Dad.
Are they okay?
- Huh?
- I'm sorry, Dad.
I knew it wasn't right,
but I wanted to kill them.
It'll never happen again, Dad.
It's okay.
Do you mean that, Dad?
It'll all be okay, son.
What's gonna be okay, huh?
Everything.
All of it.
Has anything gotten better?
Just answer me.
Has anything gotten better, Dad?
Either I die...
...or they die.
It won't get better until someone dies.
Jin-su.
Stop!
I'm gonna kill them all.
Stop it, Jin-su.
No!
Jin-su. I'll fix everything,
just stop, okay? Jin-su.
Do you wanna die, Dad?
Should I kill you?
Son, you need to stop it!
I'm sorry, Jin-su.
HOLY BIBLE
I love you.
Jin-su.
Tag. I got you.
TEACHER'S OFFICE
Over here.
- Hello, everyone.
- Hi, how are you?
- Ms. Jung. I'm heading out, okay?
- See you tomorrow.
- Okay. See you.
- Bye.
- Goodbye, ma'am.
- Keep up the good work
and don't forget your homework, alright?
Good afternoon.
The seemingly never-ending heat
has finally died down.
And the muggy, scorching weather
has been replaced by a fresh, cool breeze.
Today, our topic
is a fascinating study from abroad.
A psychologist in the US
conducted an experiment.
He gathered 48 men and women
who had never met.
To one group, he gave a specific...
Well, maybe next time
you should learn how to pass the ball.
Whoa, look out.
Hey.
Okay, okay, I'll stop.
I don't know about that.
Where are you going? Wait up!
What the...
Idiot. Come here.
WE ROOT FOR
THE HYOSAN HIGH SCHOOL ARCHERY TEAM
Let's go
get tteokbokki later.
Shouldn't we
wake up Hyeon-ju?
But it's so yummy.
Oh, she's just fine.
Ah, shit! I told them to wake me up.
What the?
Hey.
Come here.
Where are you going?
Damn it. Won't listen.
Hey.
Oh...
What the hell? You bastard.
What are you doing?
Nothing. It bit me. I'm pissed.
Goodbye.
So the restaurant moved?
How about a grand opening?
But we're not doing one.
What? What...
CHEONGSAN CHICKEN
Seriously? I told them to change the name.
What about the old name?
We're not doing it.
The fryer hasn't even come in yet.
I heard there'll be one.
MOM: WHICH ONE DO YOU LIKE?
CHEONG-SAN: CAN YOU NOT USE MY NAME?
I mean, I would know better than you,
don't you think?
MOM: OKAY. SO WHICH ONE?
CHEONG-SAN: MOM...
My mom's the worst.
- Hey.
- Damn, my phone!
You can't run away.
Hey, gopher. Let's get some chicken.
But we're not open yet.
Sure you are.
Your mom says she's testing out
a new recipe today.
You're going, right?
Of course.
- Are you going too?
- Mm. Yes.
I mean your mom told On-jo
to bring her friends.
Uh, so, is this a double date?
What the hell?
- Weird, we're not open today.
- Cool.
Uh, what do you know?
Let's get out of here.
- You like chicken that much?
- Oh, you bet.
I'm gonna eat two whole ones.
Looks great. Thank you.
- Thanks a lot.
- It looks so good.
- Why'd you bring out so much?
- Oh, yes.
Remember On-jo eats a lot.
I don't eat a lot.
I just eat well.
Oh, yes, sure. That's what I like to hear.
Eat up, Gyeong-su.
- Yep.
- You too, A-sak.
It's I-sak, not A-sak.
You change your name?
Mom. If you wanna change names,
you should start with the restaurant.
Why are you using my name?
I named it Cheongsan Chicken
way before you were born.
Exactly. You named me
after the restaurant.
- Hey. Ah...
- I don't like...
Quiet. Okay.
I really like it. Sounds like a tradition.
- Yeah?
- Of course.
He's right.
Look, so this is a new recipe
we just came up with.
So this one is just a little spicy,
and this one's really hot.
What do you think?
You can be totally honest with me.
It's super crazy mad good.
It's delicious.
- Really?
- Oh, ma'am, look.
If you ever need a delivery boy,
I'll work for cheap.
You guys need to study.
On-jo. Is it too hot?
It's salty.
Yeah?
Oh...
How about this one? Is it spicy?
No. It's salty.
Wait a sec. That's not...
Uhm, honey!
- Yeah?
- She says it's salty.
It's salty?
- On-jo says it's salty.
- Wait, I...
- It can't be.
- It's good.
- Maybe you left...
- I don't think it's salty at all.
- Yeah, it's good.
- It tastes good to me.
Let me see.
Stop eating. It's salty.
It still tastes good.
Ah.
Did you hear our science teacher?
What about him?
Well, he smells like a rotting corpse.
Oh, Na-yeon spread that rumor, right?
It's true.
He was absent after his son went missing.
But then he came into class...
Oh!
...she said
he smelled like a corpse.
How does she know
what a corpse smells like?
Has she smelled one before?
I swear she knows every other smell
except that one.
Since she never smelled it before,
it has to be a rotting corpse.
When his son went missing,
he started acting weird.
He was an outcast.
I heard he got bullied all the time.
Mm-hm. It sucks.
I feel really bad for Mr. Lee.
Remember last week
when he just left class?
BETWEEN TISSUE CELLS
CELLULAR RESPIRATION
Did the bells ring?
He's never done that before.
They say he was a genius.
Lots of geniuses go crazy.
Well, at least you won't have
to worry about going crazy.
Hey. Are you talking trash?
- I'm so full.
- Come on. Hurry up.
We're late anyway.
Cheong-san, hold on.
Why? We're late.
And I have a music test.
I just need to ask you something.
What is it?
- Nothing.
- What?
Nothing. Don't worry about it.
What is it?
Is this better like this?
Or like this?
Look close.
Like this? Or Like this?
This way, right?
Get lost.
HYOSAN HIGH SCHOOL
SUPPLY ROOM
COMMENDATION
NAM SO-JU
Do exams start next week?
You always bring up tests when I'm eating.
When else should I ask?
Wait a minute.
We have to finish the sprouts.
All right?
I mean, you're not gonna get
good grades anyway.
No point in stressing about it.
Don't give up on me, Dad. I can do it.
I'm not giving up.
Just no expectations.
That's giving up.
Is these from Cheong-san's?
Mmm.
Two days ago...
...there was an accident by a tollgate,
so I went to the scene,
and whether you're rich or poor,
got good grades or bad ones,
everyone's equal in an accident.
Grades are not that important.
Being healthy and safe.
That's all that really matters.
I mean it.
I can make it into tier five this time.
Don't push yourself.
Then I'll make it into tier six, okay?
You shouldn't lie to your dad. Here, eat.
It's salty but tasty.
It's Cheong-san.
Always on time.
Bye, Dad.
Hey, have another bite, okay?
Hey, kid!
Are you okay?
That punk.
Come on. She basically
didn't eat anything at all.
Guess I should start
with her leftovers, huh.
- Rock, paper, scissors. One, two, shoot!
- One, two, shoot!
One, two, shoot!
One, two, shoot! One, two, shoot!
Yeah!
Yes!
I'm seriously going to kill you now.
Hey, On-jo!
Nam On-jo!
Play fair, you punk.
God, I'm spent.
Carry it.
But look at this.
I got hurt making breakfast.
Let's go, gopher.
Nam-ra.
Class president!
Hey, hey! Hurry up!
RESIDENTS ONLY
STUDENTS OF RENTAL APARTMENTS STAY AWAY
- I'm going first!
- Hold up!
Hey, kids!
- Bye.
- Okay.
Hey, kids! You get back here!
Hey you!
You live in the rental apartments.
Hey! You punks!
Hey!
Hello.
See you later!
Wait for me! Shit!
That fucking shithead.
Ji-min!
Share this with your friends
at choir, will you?
I said I don't want it.
Boy, oh, boy.
She skipped breakfast as well.
- Tick tock, tick tock, tick tock.
- Hurry. Hurry, hurry!
- Wake up five minutes earlier, okay?
- All right, that's it!
Stop right there! Stop, stop, stop!
Put your names down.
Let's see.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
You have been chosen.
- Please, sir.
- You get three demerits each.
You three are always late.
Get moving.
Hey.
Is it my fault
that idiot Jin-su went missing, huh?
That's not it.
Then why the hell did you decide
to tattle on me, you little prick?
The teacher said
to write down everything we knew.
And what do you know, huh?
Asshole.
Seriously, what the hell do you know?
You're just
freaking unbelievable.
Hey. Go ahead.
Over here. Huh?
Where you looking at, huh?
Uh, fuck!
It's okay. Take it off.
- Hands off.
- Don't you dare move.
Stay still, yeah?
CONSTRUCTION NOTICE
NEW CONSTRUCTION IN PROGRESS
HYOSAN HIGH SCHOOL
You perverted freak.
You like it?
Hey.
The video.
You asshole.
Go on.
Just press record.
- You wanna die, asshole?
- That's enough.
Stop.
Shit. Son of a bitch.
We're not playing around, you moron.
You used to party with us.
Don't act all holier-than-thou,
you hear me?
Fuck off.
You need to grow up.
Get outta here.
Go ahead.
You might be safe.
Move.
You always gonna be like this?
Go.
You look really sexy in this.
Should I send it to your mom?
You know I'm friends with her on Facebook.
What kind of weirdo
makes friends with an old lady?
I can't go.
It's okay. You can do it.
It's not okay.
Because if I leave now...
it'll be worst tomorrow.
Take it off.
Should I do it for you?
Hurry up, jeez.
- Su-hyeok.
- Hey. Morning.
What?
If you have time,
come to the roof after lunch.
Why? I don't fight anymore.
You think I'd wanna fight you?
Then why?
See you later.
Weird.
Are you changing?
- Give back my ball.
- Seriously.
- You have some water?
- Mine's too warm.
Let me have some.
- Have you heard her...
- I can't hear anything at all actually.
- Are you an idiot?
- Do you hear the song?
Hey, you lost me big-time yesterday.
- Hey.
- No, it's all because of the keyboard!
- I go there all the time.
- Yeah, definitely the keyboard.
- Because the lady who works there is cute.
- I'm telling you, dude
I gave you a head start.
- What are you talking about?
- I said I'd beat you, right?
That's not true.
Gyeong-su beat you, right?
That's bullshit!
What do I do?
Don't bullshit me.
- What?
- I'm serious.
I don't know.
- What do I do?
- Wait. What? Why?
I don't know.
- I'm gonna tell you later.
- Tell me what?
- Uh, It's my crappy keyboard.
- Huh?
- Oh, your keyboard is better than mine.
- That's bullshit.
Sleeping beauty.
- Su-hyeok.
- I smell your feet from here.
This jerk didn't wear socks.
- Hey, hey, hey.
- It's not okay.
- Take him out. Come on.
- Hey.
- Really?
- That's ridiculous.
- Hey, seriously.
- What's the name? Paulo?
- Give me a break.
- Let's break his leg.
- Go ahead.
- Hey!
- Then I'll break his fingers.
Whoa. What the fuck.
Get off of there. You stink.
Oh, okay. My bad.
What's the big deal? Sorry.
Cut it out! You're so dirty.
Hey, what the hell?
Hey, just let it go.
What the hell is your problem?
What I do, huh?
What I do that was so wrong?
- Tell me what I do.
- Hey, you punks.
Come on guys. Take your seats.
Come on, move it.
Attention!
Hi, there.
Hello!
Hi. Good morning.
Time to hand-in your phones.
Who's in touch with Hyeon-ju?
Nobody?
So none of you have tried
calling her today?
Uh, we cleaned the science lab
together yesterday,
but I haven't seen her since.
Okay.
If anyone hears from her
some time the next few days,
let me know right away, okay?
Okay.
Exams start next week,
so get your acts together.
Hey, your phone.
Hey, uh...
I heard that.
Why didn't you silence it?
One more time.
Hand over your phones, please.
- Dae-su. Seriously?
- You idiot.
How stupid is he?
Why is it so much fun to mess with him?
Huh?
What you gonna do about it?
On-jo.
This is your phone from last year.
Take it, please.
Take it now.
Uh, hello, Mr. Lee.
- Uh, hello there.
- Hi.
Uh, you know Kim Hyeon-ju from my class?
She didn't make it home last night.
And...
The kids haven't seen her
since she was cleaning
the science lab yesterday.
Oh, really?
Do you remember seeing her by any chance?
No, I haven't.
Uh, so yesterday you went home
without stopping by
the science lab, right?
That's what I told you.
I...
...I'm sorry.
Apparently, no one seen her
since she was in here, so...
Is someone in there?
Yeah.
It's just a hamster.
- Oh...
- I should probably get ready for class.
Oh, okay.
- Thanks.
- Hmm.
SUPPLY ROOM
A student was bit by the hamster.
I injected her with benzodiazepine...
It's only slowing down the infection
by a few hours...
Don't kill me.
Don't kill you?
Don't bother having any hope.
A virus...
is somewhere between a living organism
and a non-living organism.
Like a living organism,
it adapts to its surroundings and evolves.
Everything that evolves in this manner
should be considered
an independent living organism.
Mr. Lee, the textbook says a virus is not
Whether or not it's categorized that way
doesn't depend on its metabolism,
but its will to survive.
If its will is so strong...
I'M SO SEXY
The instinct to survive
actually surpasses intelligence.
And eventually the ecosystem
is dominated by that will.
Humanity has never once
completely defeated a virus.
Leucochloridium paradoxum.
This parasite's
final destination is a bird.
The parasite enters a snail
and infects its ocular tentacles.
That makes the snail put itself
in the path of predatory birds.
So the infected snail commits suicide
at the whim of the parasite.
Tell me.
Now, is that because the snail
is less intelligent?
It's not.
It's because
the parasite's will to survive
is much stronger than the snail's.
- Shut up when the teacher's talking.
- The evolving...
...and hereditary will to survive is...
Keep your head up.
...the sole standard by which
living organisms are defined.
So is the textbook wrong?
The textbook?
It's wrong.
In fact, none of us
are completely free from prejudice.
We all have
preconceived ideas about others.
Here, "free from" means
the lacking in or unincumbered by.
Anyone want to interpret this?
Okay.
Hee-su.
I need to use the bathroom.
Okay, go.
Okay, then.
Anyone wanna have a crack at it, huh?
Class president?
The truth is, all of us have
some sort of prejudice.
We all have preconceptions
about other people.
Hmm, okay. Nice.
Next, Bare-su. Stand up.
Stand up.
Yes?
What's with "Bare-su"?
Mm...
It's short for Barefoot Su-hyeok. Bare-su.
Ah.
He hates wearing socks.
He's so weird about it.
I can smell it a mile away.
Okay, Bare-su.
What did Nam-ra say a minute ago?
Ah...
She was absolutely correct.
A hundred percent.
What was her absolutely correct
answer then?
Hmm...
All right...
Huh?
Hyeon-ju.
Hey, Hyeon-ju.
Hyeon-ju!
Hey. What's wrong? Are you okay?
- Hey, Hyeon-ju.
- Is that blood?
Ms. Park.
Yeah, it's me. Do you recognize me?
He grabbed me...
The science teacher grabbed me
and locked me up.
He locked you up?
The science teacher?
Mr. Lee Byeong-chan, huh?
He tied me up...
I told you, didn't I?
Just shut up, okay?
Let's go to the infirmary, okay?
- What kind of a psycho does this?
- Nam-ra.
Make sure
they study on their own.
And please don't say anything to anyone
until I come back and confirm the facts.
Hyeon-ju. Can you get up?
I'll carry her.
Okay.
- Can someone help him out, please.
- Here.
- Good.
- Okay.
Go back to your seats!
Now.
- Hyeon-ju.
- What's wrong?
Guys, hold her still.
What's wrong with her?
What's wrong? Do you feel sick?
What do I do?
Does your stomach hurt? Is it bad?
Let me see.
Please help.
- Huh?
- Uh, wait, hold on.
Put her on the bed.
- Please take a look at her.
- Here, lookout.
Her temperature is way too low.
Here, hold it down
so she doesn't kick it off.
Hold her. Hold her.
- Hyeon-ju, Hyeon-ju. It's okay.
- Call an ambulance right now.
I'll give her a sedative
and clean her wounds.
Okay.
Hyeon-ju. It's okay.
Hyeon-ju. You're okay now.
EMERGENCY CALL
- Too hot.
- Hang in there, Hyeon-ju.
Your temperature is a little too low.
Too hot. I'm too hot.
You're going to the hospital soon.
We're all here for you,
so don't worry, okay?
The science teacher gave me a weird shot.
A shot?
Mr. Lee Byeong-chan gave you a weird shot?
He tried to kill me.
Hey, Hyeon-ju, tell me what shot?
I'm gonna kill them all.
Hyeon-ju.
Hey, are you okay?
- Hold her down so I can give her the shot.
- Okay.
Just a minute, okay?
Hyeon-ju. Just hang on.
It's so strange.
Hyeon-ju was really odd.
- Yeah, totally.
- It's weird.
Everyone else saw that, right?
First, she just disappeared all day,
then she comes in all bloody
talking about the science teacher.
She could have gone somewhere
and got hurt,
then came back here
and collapsed all of a sudden.
- It's got to be true.
- Did you hear something?
You know how we heard
his son went missing?
I heard he didn't go missing.
- Suicide.
- Come on, don't fall for that.
- That's silly.
- He committed suicide?
- You believe that?
- No, really. It's true, okay?
Hyeon-ju hung out with the same crowd
that bullied Jin-su all the time.
So the science teacher
went after them one-by-one.
He hunted them down.
- And kill them.
- Who said that?
- All his students.
- Which one?
Last time I saw Hyeon-ju
was in the science lab.
Hey.
I think maybe...
Mr. Lee made porn with Hyeon-ju.
- Porn?
- Hey, you moron.
Get your mind out of the gutter, asshole.
You fat ass.
Why are you cursing at me, dick?
Because you're a fucking pervert,
dumb ass.
So why did he kidnap her then?
- Have you ever been kidnapped?
- Of course not. Stupid.
Easy, I'm your brother-in-law.
I told you to stop saying that.
Hey, tell us what happened?
I-sak, wait, what happened?
- Hey, what happened?
- How is she?
How's Hyeon-ju?
It's no joke.
She was biting people and trashing around...
Where's On-jo?
She got hurt.
Where? How bad?
She'll be fine.
Uh, Hyeon-ju bit her?
I think she went crazy.
Her temperature is super low,
but she said she was hot.
She tried to bite us.
- What the hell?
- So does she have rabies?
What an idiot.
And Hyeon-ju had this weird smell.
- What smell?
- The same one as the science teacher.
- A rotting corpse.
- Yeah, that.
- I knew it.
- And she said,
Mr. Lee gave her some kind of weird shot.
What a total psycho.
Shouldn't we tell the police about this?
I don't know.
Ms. Park said she's gonna handle it.
Look...
She's just been sitting there studying.
Yeah, well, she is the top student.
- So? Where's On-jo?
- In the infirmary.
It seems like she went
into shock due to hypothermia.
I manage to give her a sedative.
Okay. We'll take her to Hyosan Hospital.
Did you contact her parents?
Yeah. I did. They're on their way.
Please take good care of her.
- Will do.
- Thank you.
AMBULANCE
Thank you.
- Are you okay?
- That was scary.
Look at me. Were you scared?
Definitely.
Man.
So, what's wrong with her?
I don't know.
I'll tell you later when I get home.
I'm on calls, so I won't be home.
Just try not to get it wet.
Call me right away
if you need anything at all.
I'll rush right over. Okay?
- Okay.
- Good. Bye, hon.
- Bye, Dad.
- Bye.
Thank you and take good care
of her for me please.
Given the situation,
- I can't stick around.
- Okay.
- Hurry up, Dad.
- You should go.
Thank you for your help, guys.
I'm going to head back in a few minutes...
Please make sure you don't tell anyone
about this just yet, okay?
- Yeah.
- Mm-hm.
All right.
I think it's better not to tell anyone
for the time being.
Sounds good.
Go back to class. Let's go.
Are you okay? Does she bite you?
- No, it's just a scratch.
- You sure you're all good?
Hey. You wanted to meet on the roof?
- What?
- You said come up after lunch.
Can you just tell me now?
I'm actually
playing basketball after lunch.
What's that?
NAM ON-JO
Wait. This means...
you wanna go out with me.
Yeah.
But aren't you with Cheong-san?
No.
We've lived next door
ever since we were little kids,
and his mom always gives me free chicken...
...and I do like chicken.
I love it actually.
But not him, I swear.
Ah, okay.
- On-jo!
- So I...
Where did you get hurt?
How bad is it, huh?
You're such a klutz sometimes.
I'm fine.
How bad was she hurt?
She's pretty clumsy, huh?
No.
Hyeon-ju tried to bite us.
She got hurt
trying to stay out of the way.
Hey.
You're going out with On-jo?
Right?
Mm-hm. Right.
Can't believe you bought that? You freak.
Seriously, even if it was
the end of the world,
and it was her, me, and a zombie,
I'd honestly rather date the zombie.
Why do you ask?
No reason.
Let's go.
Anyway, what's for lunch today?
Do you have any idea?
I want some tonkatsu.
How far are we from the hospital?
We're almost there.
She went to the hospital.
- Wait.
- Mr. Lee. Wait.
You don't understand.
She can't be in a hospital.
- Let all calm down.
- What are you talking about?
No! Let go of me!
No! It's time for you
to explain yourself here.
We can't send Hyeon-ju to a hospital.
We have to put her in quarantine.
Hey.
Sit down, Mr. Lee.
You've already turned things upside down
when you're at school
with the story about your son.
How the hell could you say that?
Jin-su was the victim!
And of course, you forced us to bury it.
Oh, that's some crack of bullshit, huh?
You know how the school's evaluation
is just around the corner.
You should've called me
before calling an ambulance, Sun-hwa.
What do you think
is gonna happen if the police come?
Well, I already called the police.
A teacher should deal
with school matters internally.
I'll call the police
if we need them.
- Tell them not to come.
- I mean...
Mr. Lee.
Police.
It's been a while,
Mr. Lee Byeong-chan.
Huh?
It's so good.
- What?
- Nothing.
Hey, Cheong-san can feel that.
I wasn't looking at him.
Yeah, right.
The whole school knows
you two are going out on dates.
We're not dating.
I'm serious.
Mm-hm, sure. Yeah.
Actually...
You can't tell anyone, okay?
About what?
Well...
It was you, right?
Forget it.
- Hey, come on.
- Stop it.
Tell me.
Stop. No.
You slept with Cheong-san, didn't you?
You did. I got it, am I right?
- Are you insane?
- Ow!
I told Su-hyeok I like him.
What?
You mean?
- What?
- My gosh.
- Quiet.
- Oh, my god. I can't believe it.
- Are you completely insane?
Him? Su-hyeok?
Quiet.
- You eat it. It's okay.
- What?
How'd you do it? What did you say?
Did you ask him on a date or what?
My name tag.
So you threw yourself at him.
So?
Well, that's all.
Huh?
He didn't say anything?
- Mm-hm.
- Not even a vibe?
Mm-hm.
You couldn't tell how he felt or anything?
I'm going crazy.
You're making me go crazy.
Wearing those for too long
is bad for your ears.
Earbuds. They're bad for your ears.
I know.
Do you wanna go visit Hyeon-ju later?
Why?
You're our class president.
You know my mom made me class president
by donating a bunch
of money to the school.
That's why no one else thinks of me
as the real class president.
So why the hell should I act like it?
What?
I'm surprised.
I've actually never heard you talk
that much before.
I thought you never said
more than five words at a time.
I want to cut class.
I'm sleepy.
What the hell?
INFIRMARY
Hey, hey.
Come here, come here.
- What?
- Check this out.
Oh, boy. What's wrong with her?
Probably drunk
out of her mind.
Is she serious?
She's gonna get fired.
What's she doing
in bare feet?
What the hell?
God. Damn.
- She really hit her head.
- That was freaky.
What's wrong with her?
Is she sick?
I think she likes you.
Hey, hey.
What is she doing?
Help!
Shit. What the fuck?
Holy shit, run!
Shit.
Eun-ji.
Don't do it.
Wanna come up?
Eun-ji.
Uh, come down.
Let's just talk down here, please.
Come on.
They said...
they'll gonna post it online.
Huh? No.
They said they delete it.
They, they promised me they would.
This is a living hell.
So I'm just trying to escape from hell.
I'll take care of it.
I can do it.
I'll delete them all.
Just...
Please don't...
I'm begging you.
Please don't do it, Eun-ji.
Why are you crying?
Do you...
like me?
Two losers who liked each other,
that's hilarious.
But when two losers go out,
they get even lamer.
So stay away from me.
Eun-ji.
And stay away from...
my dead body.
Eun-ji. Eun-ji, Eun-ji!
Hey, Prez!
Hurry!
Run!
I have a great idea.
Just ask Cheong-san.
Forget it.
Seriously, he and Su-hyeok
are really close.
Why don't you
just ask Cheong-san how he feels?
No.
On-jo. You have to listen to me.
There's a good chance Su-hyeok
already told him everything.
It doesn't matter. He'll make fun of me.
Put mine away too, gopher.
Hey, Cheong-san.
On-jo needs to talk to you.
Hey. So, you're close to Su-hyeok, right?
For sure. Why?
Told you?
What is it?
Nothing. So get lost.
- So, On-jo...
- Hey.
You're dead.
Understood.
Hey. A real friend
would help out right now.
What is it?
Wait a second? Did Su-hyeok say something?
No.
Did you fight?
I just said no.
Then what's going on,
did he say that he likes you?
Did he say that?
- What?
- That he likes me?
Who? Su-hyeok?
No? He didn't say anything?
Hmm, what are you talking about?
Earlier...
- You can't tell anyone, okay?
- About what?
You really can't tell anyone.
About what, On-jo?
I asked him out earlier, but I don't know.
He hasn't said anything.
Hey.
Yeah, what?
Any chance you could ask him
what he thinks about me?
We're not close.
Yeah, you are.
No, we're not, really.
Can't you help me out for once?
You're not my friend.
Shit. Shit.
Move! Move!
ALL CHARACTERS, LOCATIONS, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND EVENTS IN THIS SHOW ARE FICTIONAL.