RESTRICTED AREA
HOLY BIBLE
TEACHER'S OFFICE
WE ROOT FOR
THE HYOSAN HIGH SCHOOL ARCHERY TEAM
MOM: CHEONGSAN CHICKEN
MOM: WHICH ONE DO YOU LIKE, SON?
CHEONG-SAN: CAN YOU NOT USE MY NAME?
MOM: OKAY. WHICH ONE DO YOU LIKE?
CHEONG-SAN: MOM...
BETWEEN TISSUE CELLS
CELLULAR RESPIRATION
ACADEMY
SUPPLY ROOM
COMMENDATION
NAM SO-JU
RESIDENTS ONLY
STUDENTS OF RENTAL APARTMENTS STAY AWAY
CONSTRUCTION NOTICE
NEW CONSTRUCTION IN PROGRESS
HYOSAN HIGH SCHOOL
MY CLASS 2-5 BABIES
SUPPLY ROOM
CHANG-HOON
VIDEO
EMERGENCY CALL
NAM ON-JO
INFIRMARY
ALL CHARACTERS, LOCATIONS, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND EVENTS IN THIS SHOW ARE FICTIONAL.
Subtitle translation by: Jeong Lee