Mommy…
Your home isn't over there, is it?
No.
I think they're burning Hyosan down.
Hey, Seoul University.
Yes?
To save the majority,
just how heartless are you allowed to be?
You must learn things like that
at your school.
We don't learn
that kind of stuff in my major.
I'm not sure what major does.
Oh no…
Stay still.
Let's go.
Let's go, On-jo.
I can't just go like this.
I'm sorry. Can you wait a bit?
Oh, never mind.
Go ahead. I'll catch up.
I'll go with her.
Let's go together.
I'll go too.
No, you hurt your leg.
Wu-jin, look after Dae-su.
Cheong-san.
Cheong-san!
Cheong-san, you jerk!
Let's go.
I don't smell anything.
There's no one here.
Let's say bye to Cheong-san…
and leave.
Slowly.
Damn it.
CHEONGSAN CHICKEN
THIS IS A SAFE ZONE
One infected eliminated.
Pulling out.
THIS IS A RESTRICTED AREA
THIS IS A SAFE ZONE
The soldiers saw us at school.
They left us there without helping us.
Then they bombed it.
Maybe they want us to die.
That can't be it.
I think it's because of me.
Because we were with zombies,
they must think we're neither
zombies nor humans, like me.
Maybe that's what they thought.
Don't say that.
Is it okay for me
to stay with you guys like this?
You're still our friend
and our classroom president.
We couldn't have made it
this far without you.
Still…
You haven't turned,
and you never will.
Let's do that again later.
It was my first time
sitting around a fire with friends.
We'll be able to do that again, right?
Let's do it tonight.
What the hell?
What's wrong?
Shit. I think we're lost.
-There's no trail?
-There hasn't been a trail for a while.
I feel like we're going in circles.
Why did you come this way
if there was no trail?
We might end up back at Hyosan.
Ha-ri.
Look.
There's something there.
It was tied here.
Who did something so nice?
Maybe a ginseng digger?
What's that?
I see another one.
RESCUE TEAM 1 NAM SO-JU
What state are they in?
It looks like
they're about to die of starvation.
Transport them carefully.
You must not lose or damage them.
Yes, sir.
Didn't he say we should go to Yangdong?
Do you think the zombies are here too?
No way.
They probably evacuated the city
because it's next to Hyosan.
Hey, I'm getting a bad feeling about this.
Why are there no people?
It's okay here.
Why? What's okay?
There are no broken windows,
and there's no blood on the streets.
It wouldn't be this clean
if the zombies had been rampant.
What is it?
Hold on.
What is it, Nam-ra?
What is it? Is something here?
Zombies.
Where?
Everywhere.
Are there a lot of them?
One, two, three…
four, five, six…
seven, eight…
nine, ten, eleven…
Run.
Hey, this way.
Damn it.
-Are you okay?
-Take Dae-su and go.
Forget it.
What are you doing? I said go.
I said forget it.
On-jo.
Fuck.
I have a feeling it'll all end here.
Stay behind me.
Stop messing around. Stay back.
Let go of me!
Ha-ri!
Fuck!
Get off of him!
Get off! Hey!
Wu-jin.
-Fuck.
-Wu-jin.
-Oh no.
-I fucking knew this would happen.
It's okay.
I knew it.
-Wu-jin, look at me.
-Ha-ri.
Did you really make the national team?
Yes, I did.
Bullshit.
You came to school
because you got eliminated.
Otherwise, you'd be at the tournament.
If you got eliminated,
you should've gone home.
Why did you come to school? Fuck.
-I'm sorry.
-Listen.
Stick with archery. Okay?
Okay.
Don't give up.
-Okay?
-Okay.
Wu-jin, I'm sorry.
No. Not Wu-jin.
Don't do it.
Fuck.
I'm sorry.
Su-hyeok.
Wu-jin…
More are coming.
Let's go that way. There aren't any there.
Let's go, Dae-su.
Ha-ri, let's go.
Let go.
Don't die a meaningless death.
If we run now, we can all live.
We have enough time.
I've been killing zombies, too,
but a human being would apologize
for killing her brother in front of her.
Eat them.
Eat them. Eat them all.
Why not? You're hungry.
Kill them.
I'm hungry.
Stop it.
Wait.
What is it?
Nam-ra's gone.
I'll be right back.
-Su-hyeok!
-Hey, Su-hyeok.
-Can you go on your own?
-What do you plan to do?
-Go ahead. I'll catch up.
-On-jo.
Hey, On-jo!
Nam-ra.
Why are you here by yourself?
Let's go.
Stay away.
Come with us.
-Okay?
-I said stay away!
Nam-ra!
Nam-ra. It's me, On-jo.
Nam-ra, don't do this.
Choi Nam-ra!
Nam-ra, please.
You can bite me.
I'm okay.
It's okay, Nam-ra.
On-jo.
Are you okay, On-jo?
Are you okay?
Nam-ra.
Hey, Prez!
Nam-ra!
Hey, Choi Nam-ra!
Up ahead!
Survivors confirmed.
Go! Hurry!
Let's go! Let's go home!
Go!
Ha-ri!
Hey!
Come get me. All of you.
Today, I am…
the happiest guy in this school!
On-jo.
U-sin.
Are you okay? You're not hurt?
What about your dad?
Did you meet your dad?
He went to find you.
RESCUE TEAM 1 NAM SO-JU
I already knew the sorrow
of a survivor.
But I didn't know how heavy
that sorrow would be…
at that time.
Do you know the teacher, Lee Byeong-chan?
I only took morning classes
because I had training.
So, no, I don't.
Has he ever said anything weird
or acted strangely?
That isn't important right now.
I'm a senior. What about the CSAT?
If there's anything you want to say,
say it.
How many times do I have to tell you?
He kidnapped a student
from our class named Hyeon-ju.
I heard he gave Kim Hyeon-ju
some sort of injection.
Why did you
abandon us?
You abandoned us.
-If you cooperate--
-No.
I won't ask adults for anything
ever again.
So…
don't ask for my cooperation.
This notice goes out
to all citizens of Hyosan.
For the safety of everyone in the camp…
HOW MUCH TIME MUST PASS FOR THIS TO END?
I MISS YOU, PLEASE JUST SHOW UP
I MISS YOU
I MISS YOU, PARK JU-YEONG
I LOVE YOU, U-GI
FLOWING WATER ENVELOPS ME
AND FLOWS INTO MY PAINFUL MEMORIES
I'LL LET YOU GO NOW
The National Assembly hearing
on the bombing of Hyosan
has been postponed indefinitely
upon agreement.
The party leaders announced
in a joint statement today
they won't hold the hearing
until the epidemic situation…
They won't hold the hearing
until the epidemic situation
has been completely resolved.
The National Security Council
announced they will end martial law
in Hyosan today.
This comes 3 months
and 17 days since martial law
was imposed due to the outbreak.
However, as a precaution,
Hyosan residents will continue
to be quarantined.
Although it has been more than four months
since the outbreak started,
the Korea Disease Control
and Prevention Agency
has failed to identify the virus.
Since it is impossible
to know its incubation period,
the agency opposed ending
the quarantine of Hyosan residents.
Donations are pouring in
from across the nation
for the Hyosan residents who have been
living in quarantine for four months.
Thank you for your hard work.
This notice is to remind you
of the curfew times.
Curfew lasts from midnight
to 6:00 a.m. the next morning.
During this time,
please remain in your shelters
and refrain from moving
for the livelihood of all.
This time will be used
to inspect facilities
and to clean and disinfect the camp.
These measures are meant
to protect you from infection
and to ensure that public facilities
remain clean for everyone to use.
I-SAK, I MISS YOU
NAM-RA, COME BACK
CHEONG-SAN, I LOVE YOU
LEE CHEONG-SAN
Cheong-san.
ZOMBIE VICTIM SPECIAL ADMISSION
HIGH SCHOOL SENIORS WHO SUFFERED
THE ZOMBIE ATTACK
MUST BE GIVEN SPECIAL ADMISSIONS
INTO COLLEGES
Goodness. My daughter is a senior too.
You poor thing.
Rock, paper, scissors.
-Shit.
-Hang in there. You'll get another chance.
KOREAN RED CROSS
EMERGENCY RELIEF SUPPLIES
Su-hyeok.
Where have you been?
I couldn't find you.
I saw the others a few times.
I wanted to see them,
but I couldn't bring myself to.
In case it would remind me.
Can you forget if you don't see them?
I went to the mountain last night
and saw a campfire.
I think someone lit a fire
on the school rooftop.
The rooftop?
Are you sure?
I may be mistaken, but I'm pretty sure.
Nam-ra said we should light a campfire
if we ever meet again.
I plan to go tonight.
I'll go with you.
I'm sorry about that day.
About what?
That day when Nam-ra tried to bite you.
Sorry I couldn't do anything.
It's okay.
Your choice saved us all.
Don't tell the others.
It could be dangerous,
so let's go by ourselves.
I told you not to tell them.
Hey, I told you not to tell anyone else.
Ha-ri.
I said it was between us.
She said she'd tell the cops
if we didn't take her.
Fuck it.
They won't give me special admission.
How is that related to this?
They'll lock us up if we get caught.
I'd rather go to jail
if I can't get into college.
Let's go.
Just climb over that wall, right?
You're really going?
All of you?
You're not the only one
who feels indebted.
We're all hurting just like you.
Being alone doesn't make it hurt less.
Go on.
Didn't you say there was a rope?
-How do we get up there?
-Move.
-What are you doing?
-Are you sure?
I'm going too.
-Get on the ground.
-What?
-Let's go.
-You heard me.
I MISS YOU ALL
What is that?
Well,
I couldn't throw that away.
Joon-yeong.
I'll buy you a box next time.
I see a light.
-Do you see it?
-Where?
There.
Hey, I think that really is our school.
It's a total wreck.
I know.
Let's go.
Okay.
THIS IS A SAFE ZONE
HYOSAN HIGH SCHOOL
Do you think it's really Nam-ra?
Yes.
I don't know why,
but I think it's her.
Who do you think it was?
Maybe… it was kids
who came back to the school like us.
Maybe it was a YouTuber or something.
Kids who like haunted houses.
No.
It was Nam-ra.
She probably lit it because she misses us.
How do you know that?
I don't.
But I think I do.
You made it.
Hey.
Prez.
Nam-ra.
Am I still the classroom president?
I like that.
Are you okay?
How have you been?
I've missed you.
All of you.
Nam-ra.
I wanted to see you,
but I didn't think I should.
No, it's okay.
Let's go. Come with us.
I still have things to do here.
What things?
There are a few more like me.
Some fled outside of the school,
but there are still a few left.
You're not a zombie.
Don't say that.
You know how students are not children
but not yet adults either?
I'm like that.
I'm neither a human…
nor a monster.
That's not true.
Stay with us.
It's okay if it's just us.
We're friends even if we're not together.
Right?
No?
Yes, you're right.
Wherever we may be, we're friends.
That's good enough.
They're back.
I'll be back.
ALL CHARACTERS, ORGANIZATIONS,
LOCATIONS, INSTITUTIONS,
AND EVENTS IN THIS SHOW ARE FICTIONAL.
Subtitle translation by: Jeong Lee