-Cheong-san!
-What the hell?
Damn it.
On-jo.
Su-hyeok!
Su-hyeok, are you okay?
Shit.
Who the hell are you guys?
What about you?
Are you from the One Heart club?
ONE HEART
It's me.
Me.
Don't you know me?
How the fuck do you not know me?
I know you.
I said it again and again.
You were the bullies' gopher.
Call me that again, and you're dead.
You were never a thug or a good student.
And now you're not a zombie or a human.
Then and now…
you're nothing.
I'm not going to just kill you.
I'll gouge out both of your eyes
and throw you to the zombies.
Yes.
Everyone but Cheong-san, run away.
Unless you want to die with him.
You're all dead.
Cheong-san.
Get out of the way!
Let go.
Let go, fuck!
You smell nice.
You and I are on the same side.
Smell me.
Go on.
Get lost.
Your shirt ripped.
It's okay.
Fuck.
What the hell is he?
He was so strong.
Are you hurt anywhere else?
Did your glasses break?
What the hell is he?
You're bleeding.
-So he's Gwi-nam?
-What? Damn it.
I guess so.
-What about me?
-Let me see.
My legs are shaking.
You're okay.
It hurts like hell.
Damn it.
We're on the same side.
EXAMINATION ROOM
Here you go.
Thank you.
The homology test on the virus
is not producing results.
What does that mean?
All living organisms come from somewhere,
and a homology test shows us the origin.
It's like a genealogy for viruses.
But we can't figure it out.
Are you saying
it's a completely new virus?
The KDCA is also analyzing it,
but they can't identify it either.
We need to identify it
before we can treat them.
You people are the experts.
How could you not have identified it yet?
The strange thing is,
the RNA structure changes
every time we test it.
The virus seems to be evolving on its own.
We rescued a detective
from Hyosan Police Station.
He seems to know about the virus.
There's a laptop
in Hyosan High School and--
Hey.
You need to start from the beginning.
But it's urgent.
Damn it.
The virus that's spreading in Hyosan
is called the Jonas Virus.
Lee Byeong-chan, a science teacher
at Hyosan High School, created it.
There's a laptop
in the science lab of the school.
He said it had everything necessary
to resolve this wretched situation.
Laptop?
-Is his story credible?
-Yes.
The initial reports of the outbreak
were from Hyosan Hospital's ER
and Hyosan High School.
The student that was taken to the ER
was a student from Hyosan High.
Thus, I'm certain
that Hyosan High is ground zero.
Continue to question that detective.
Send a Special Mission Unit
to Hyosan High.
Bring me the laptop.
Yes, sir.
Eun-ji.
Eun-ji!
WAITING STATION
Are you okay?
I thought you had died.
You let me go knowing I'd die.
I'm sorry.
I was--
It's fine.
That's who you are.
Hey.
Want to hear some good news?
I set fire to the school.
It's probably burned to the ground by now.
You set the school on fire?
Yes. You're happy too, right?
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
Why?
You seem strange.
You're not your usual self.
I'm hungry.
I get worked up when I'm hungry.
Do you want this, then?
They're giving these out,
but the line's really long.
You eat first.
I don't want that.
This is all they have.
Not that. I want to eat something else.
Like what?
You?
Me?
Yes.
I want to eat you.
Damn, it stings.
What the hell is with that Gwi-nam guy?
You said he was bitten.
I don't know.
It looks like he became a different being.
I don't think he can die.
What if he climbs up here again?
That asshole is bad,
but to be honest,
I'm scared of Nam-ra too.
You saw her fighting earlier.
I think
it's reasonable to assume
they're both hambies--
What?
You're really okay, right?
You won't do that to us, right?
Will you believe me if I say I won't?
Must you talk like that?
Can't you try to make us believe you?
We're going to be together anyway.
I… have never done anything but study.
Not because I was naive
but because I was a coward.
I was scared my grades would drop
and that my mom would get mad.
So I didn't do anything else.
I was too scared to make friends too.
My mom always asked
about how well they did at school,
what their father did for a living,
how big their house is…
I never thought I'd get to sit
by a fire with all of you like this.
It's really nice.
It's my first time.
If we get out of here,
let's gather around a fire
and hang out like this again.
I really hope we can.
Sure, let's do that.
If anyone lights a fire…
let's all gather together.
Sorry, Prez.
Did she just smile?
That looked so awkward.
God, come on.
What? What now?
Why don't you two just go out?
You're being so loud.
-Are you mad?
-Are you crazy?
Hold on.
Don't you hear that?
Hear what?
Why? Is someone coming again?
They're coming.
What's coming?
What is it?
I don't see anything.
Wait.
I hear a chopper.
ALO Viper.
We've entered Hyosan High's airspace.
TGT 1M, reporting.
Fire.
-Fire!
-It's coming.
-Hey!
-This way. It's this way.
Sir!
-Over here! We're here!
-Over here!
-Please help!
-Here!
-Over here!
-Hey! Over here!
-We're here!
-Here!
Look at us, will you?
Hey!
Can't you see us?
-We're here!
-Over here!
-Here!
-Hey!
-Look at us!
Over here! Look this way!
ALO Viper. We've arrived at Hyosan High.
-Here!
-Here! Over here!
-Sir!
-Over here!
-We're over here!
-Hey!
-Here!
-Over here!
-Help us!
-We're going to live!
He saw us! Over here!
Over here!
We're saved!
We're going to live!
Over here!
-Here--
-Oh my God.
Get down. All of you, down on the ground!
Sir.
Please save us.
-Get down on the ground!
-Get down!
Examining the area.
Hyosan High rooftop.
Nine survivors confirmed.
Their condition?
Checking temperatures now.
Clear.
I think they're checking if we're zombies.
-Clear.
-Don't worry.
Clear.
Temperature is 34.5 degrees.
Providing a warming blanket.
One has hypothermia. The rest are normal.
Rescue them after completing your mission.
We'll rescue them
after completing our mission.
Over.
It's okay. They said they'll rescue us.
It's over now.
You may get up now.
Are you the only survivors?
We don't know.
I'm sure there are more.
We'll go down for a few minutes.
Wait right here.
Aren't you going to rescue us?
We will.
So don't go anywhere.
Don't do anything. Just stay here.
-Understand?
-Yes.
Let's go.
Three soldiers, ready to go.
Chopper, report.
Viper, ready to go. Over.
HYOSAN HIGH SCHOOL
Fuck, let's go.
The zombies went toward the chopper.
Let's get to the rooftop now.
Let's go.
What about him?
Tie him up.
-Be more gentle.
-Slowly.
More gentle.
-Is that okay?
-Yes, it's good.
Don't put any straps on my stomach.
Okay, I won't.
The infected are entering
from the field and front gate.
What's your status?
We're clear. Moving in.
Report on the situation.
Hey.
They plan to kill all the zombies
before they take us, right?
I doubt that. There are only four of them.
Isn't Special Mission the best?
Are they looking for something?
Isn't the science lab that way?
-We're in.
-Do you have the package?
Checking now.
The infected are rushing toward you.
Viper, get ready to move out.
Target not yet obtained.
Decrypting device.
We have to go. Hurry!
Decryption complete. Heading out.
Moving out!
Report your evacuation status
and situation inside the school.
The infected are passing F2
and moving quickly to the science lab.
Rescue the students
and return to the base.
Yes, sir.
Commander, we had an incident
in the quarantine camp.
What is it? What happened?
-Bring up monitor 34.
-Yes, sir.
Rewind ten minutes.
Where's the package?
Come to the pick-up position. Over.
-Master Sergeant. Go up first.
-Yes, sir.
We'll pull you up one at a time.
Stay still even if you're scared.
-Okay?
-Aren't you landing the chopper?
We can't for safety reasons.
He'll pull you in, so don't worry.
You can't go all at once,
so let's go one by one.
You can't take us all?
We're taking all of you,
but you have to go up one by one.
Ji-min. You go first.
You go first. Go.
Go first.
Grab her!
Calm down!
Stay still!
Stand back!
What the hell is that?
I think she's infected but asymptomatic.
She's infected but showed no symptoms?
You're saying normal people
and infected people
cannot be differentiated.
-Connect to the team at Hyosan High!
-Yes, sir.
Don't rescue anyone.
Please repeat. Do you mean everyone?
We just discovered
an asymptomatic infected person.
But their temperatures are fine.
The girl who was brought here
was also fine.
All our agents will be in danger
if one turns in the chopper.
Open fire if they resist.
But they're just students.
Soldiers here have died!
One girl attacked four soldiers!
Understood. Over.
Operation canceled!
We'll take only the package and pull out!
Sir!
I'm going back down.
-She's coming down.
-Hey.
She's coming down!
-Why? What's wrong?
-She's coming down!
Why is she coming down?
-What's going on?
-I don't know!
Why did you take that off? No.
-What do you mean it's canceled?
-What are you doing?
Please pull me back up.
Pull me back up! Fuck! I won't go back.
No!
Take me with you!
Sir. Please!
I want to go!
Take me with you!
-Why won't you take us with you?
-Sir!
Wait a second.
What's wrong?
We're not zombies.
What are you waiting for? Open fire.
Take me with you!
Step back.
Step back, or we'll shoot.
Stand back!
Get in the chopper.
Open fire.
Do you not hear me?
This is an order. Open fire!
Sir. Can't you just take a few of us?
Shoot, you bastard. Shoot them!
Be quiet.
-Quiet.
-Damn it.
To the rooftop, right?
Not that one, right?
We can't get up there.
I mean this building.
-Let's go.
-It's not that way.
-What? Okay. Let's go.
-Hey. Help me.
Shit.
I'm begging you.
Please take just a few of us.
Sir.
I'm sorry.
We have the package.
All agents pulling out.
Return to the base.
Hey. Why is it coming this way?
Did they see us?
Over here! Here! Look here!
Over here!
Damn it.
-We're fucked. Run!
-Shit.
They abandoned us, right?
Right?
No one will come to save us now, right?
Why did they do that?
Maybe
they fucking thought we were zombies.
Then they would've killed us.
They wouldn't have left
without killing us.
What are you doing?
It's useless.
No one's coming. No one is coming now.
A victim stated that you
and your aide were accomplices
in Kim U-sin and Nam So-ju's attack
on our soldiers during their escape.
He kept denying your involvement.
So we want to ask you some questions.
Are you recording this?
-Yes, we are.
-Wait a minute.
Aren't you supposed
to inform us if you're recording?
We will record this conversation.
Do you consent?
Would you please point the camera
straight at me?
Is it set?
Yes.
I'm Assembly Member Park Eun-hee.
I am being interrogated
because I have been accused
of aiding in the escape
of Nam So-ju and Kim U-sin,
the firefighters who saved my life.
I am not an accomplice.
I was the principal offender.
Ma'am! Seriously…
Stop recording.
Stay back.
What are you doing?
Why are you doing this?
Do as you please.
I won't get involved anymore.
Nam So-ju saved us,
notwithstanding the fact
that his daughter was nearby.
Although he tried to go save his daughter,
the Martial Law Control stopped him.
His daughter was everything to him.
I said I'd take full responsibility
and that he should escape using
all means necessary to save his daughter.
Even if it's dangerous
and we're under martial law,
no one can stop
a father's love for his child.
Regardless of the punishment
I may receive…
I will always stand
with the powerless people.
On-jo.
Dad.
Please help us.
My wife and baby--
I can't do it on my own.
We need equipment
to cut through the frame.
Please help us.
I'm sorry.
I need to get to my daughter.
I'm so sorry.
I'm begging you, sir.
Our baby…
Please, sir. Help us.
They will begin sending rescuers soon.
Hang on until then.
Those monsters will come first.
Here.
Here. Take this.
You have to hang on.
You have to help me.
Get back here now.
Move.
There is no more hope.
It's like every sin became concentrated
and entered the human body.
Even if we can conquer this virus,
a world in which humanity rules
will never return.
Can we believe people are beautiful
after seeing them
turn into the absolute worst beings?
If you shoot me,
they'll come running.
We'll die anyway.
This way or that…
My daughter is waiting for me.
Please…
Please don't go.
Don't go.
There was something we'd say
whenever we hit a wall when I worked
at the pharmaceutical company.
"Science begins with imagination
and ends as a mystery."
I went to see a shaman on my way home.
The shaman said
this will solve everything.
Please help me. Help me!
I'm human.
I'm not a zombie!
Crazy bastard!
She tests both positive and negative
depending on when we test her.
What does that mean?
We have to assume
it's a fusion or evolution.
Is it a mutation?
Yes, that's correct.
The virus is hiding
in the RNA of the cells.
It's detected only when it manifests.
It can't be when it's dormant.
That means tests can't tell us
whether or not they're infected.
That's right.
It's like the human
and the monster are fighting within.
Is there a possibility
that others from Hyosan are like her?
As per KDCA's recommendation,
it's best to presume
they're infected
even if they show no symptoms.
From this moment on,
categorize everyone from Hyosan
as being infected but asymptomatic.
Monitor those who were rescued later
separately and more closely.
I know.
You really are amazing.
Using us in that situation.
I would say she made good use of you.
When it rains, you use the rain.
When it's windy, you use the wind.
That's politics.
You'll use that video
for your campaign later, won't you?
Although you saved no one,
you'll get lots of votes
as if you did something huge.
She did do something huge.
She got you out in exchange
for her taking full responsibility.
She never told our captain to escape.
Look here, U-sin.
All disasters create heroes.
Whether or not he saves his daughter,
Mr. Nam So-ju will be a hero.
That is what we're building right now.
Don't you want your captain
to become a hero?
-That's not it. I--
-Then we're good.
Let's look at the big picture.
From this moment on, we are one team.
And we'll move forward together.
What the hell?
To prevent the spread of infection,
you'll be taken to a special quarantine.
For safety reasons,
you'll be handcuffed during transport--
Are we criminals?
Why are you suddenly imprisoning us?
How dare you try to put handcuffs
on the assembly member?
Please comply.
Don't test my patience.
It's martial law.
-Not a military dictatorship.
-Please comply.
We can't follow rules that lack principle.
Just kill me first
if you want to take her away.
-What are you doing? Make a shield.
-Yes, sir.
Hold on tight.
Get in here.
Attention, all citizens
in the quarantine camp.
In order to find those who are infected
but are asymptomatic,
we are separating Hyosan citizens
from those who came from elsewhere,
as per the KDCA's recommendation.
I'm fine.
Until a trusted testing method is found
and the situation is resolved,
stricter quarantine rules will be put
in place effective immediately.
We apologize for the inconvenience,
and we hope you comply.
You said we'd be treated like heroes.
What the hell is this?
Quiet, you bastard.
Did you find the laptop? What happened?
Let's move.
What about the laptop?
You should at least tell us that!
Are you okay?
My ears hurt so much.
Instead of earphones.
It's raining.
Hey, it's raining.
It's fucking raining!
Hey, it's raining!
It's so refreshing.
Fuck this. Seriously…
Joon-yeong.
You know how zombies follow us
if they hear us?
If we move every time there's thunder,
maybe they won't hear us.
No one is coming to rescue us.
Isn't it better to die trying to get out
than die waiting here?
Where can we go? And how?
If we take the back door
of the auditorium to the tennis courts
and go through the English center,
we can reach the mountain.
If we can reach the mountain,
we can make it to Yangdong.
I went hiking there
a few times with my dad.
Don't you think it's too crazy to try?
I'm not going. I'm scared.
What if the zombies catch us?
It's not like anyone will save us
if we stay here.
We're the only ones
who can save ourselves.
Let's go.
If anything happens,
I'll scream and lead the zombies away.
If anything, I'll die alone.
So let's go.
Don't say that.
We should all live.
If anyone has to die,
I'll die in their place.
Because of the rain,
all scents are mixed together.
The rain is really loud too.
I'm sure the zombies' senses are dulled.
If that's what a hambie says,
it should be reliable.
What's a hambie?
A half…
reliable person.
Should we go?
And Prez is strong.
Let's trust her and go.
I'm not strong right now.
Why not?
I don't know.
Some of us may not be able to keep up.
We can't have anyone fall,
so let's pair up and hold hands.
To protect each other.
Hey.
-Wu-jin. Let's go.
-Okay.
Hey.
Stay behind me.
Let's survive first.
We can talk about us later.
-Careful.
-Okay.
Don't let go of my hand.
I get it.
Damn it.
-Damn it.
-What are you doing?
My bad.
-Are you okay?
-Yes.
Move together with me.
Be careful.
Careful.
-What's wrong?
-Hold on.
Are they there?
Let's go.
Hey. They're acting strange.
Be quiet.
Come here and look.
They look like total morons.
Hey.
I'm freezing.
It's the rain.
Hey, let's go.
It's our best chance to escape.
Let's go behind that building
and go up the mountain.
I'll lure that zombie and go that way.
Use that time to get out.
No.
I'll lure that zombie and go…
Let's just go along the wall
and cross over there.
Duck down.
Stay low.
Go along the wall.
Go along the wall over there.
-Back there?
-What?
Hey, I'll go first.
This way.
Cheong-san.
Mom?
ALL CHARACTERS, ORGANIZATIONS,
LOCATIONS, INSTITUTIONS,
AND EVENTS IN THIS SHOW ARE FICTIONAL.
Subtitle translation by: Jeong Lee