Hey. Start recording.
I'll defeat you,
and rule as most powerful! Hah!
Not a chance.
Asshole! It hurts like hell! Shit!
Don't come near me! Aah! Stop! That hurts!
What the hell?
Run!
Shit!
Shit. Shit. Shit. Fuck.
Aah, you must be mistaken.
Our students are required
to check in their phones.
None of them could've called you.
Yeah.
Yes, of course. Everything is just great.
Have a nice day.
Didn't I tell you to make sure
to take away their phones?
I even got you safes,
and they're saying zombies!
What the hell is wrong with you all?
You can't deny
there's a problem out there.
It's complete madness.
We need the police and rescuers
to get the kids out--
Are you the only teacher?
Are you that special?
Whatever happens inside this school
must be handled internally!
Go! Put the kids in their classrooms.
But, sir, I don't think the students
are in the situation
where they will listen to us at all.
What are you still doing here?
Get out there!
And if you'd go out right now,
you can see for yourself
-that it's total chaos.
-Just do as you're told.
I made you the dean
to discipline them, so do that!
Where are you going, Sun-hwa?
Don't do anything stupid. Stay here!
I'm going to make an announcement
to tell all the kids to leave.
PRINCIPAL'S OFFICE
Hey, kid.
What's up with your leg?
Hey, stop that!
Hey! What are you doing?
Cut that out!
Ah…
What's with you?
Help! Help!
On-jo. Are you good?
Hey!
Get up.
Are you okay?
Go! Haste! Let's undo this.
Hurry and get up there!
Let's go over there!
Come on.
Fuck!
You go first.
Oh, shit!
Get out. No!
Cheong-san!
Why aren't you coming? Come on!
On-jo.
Hurry up!
Run!
HYOSAN BUILDING MATERIALS
Come. This way. This way.
Wait up for me!
Stay away. Stay away, son of a bitch.
You should've stayed away, fucker!
Shit. What's going on?
Don't open the door. Don't open it!
Let go.
Hurry up! Lock the door! Go!
I need to open it.
You open it!
Move!
Are you okay?
On-jo!
How's the campus? Are we dead or what?
Hey.
-What the hell? Who are you?
-Asshole. Brother…
-Brother-in-law.
-Oh, come in.
Holy shit.
They're so aggressive.
What happened to your face, huh?
I don't know, some crazy jerk sprayed me
with a fire extinguisher.
-A fire extinguisher?
-Yeah, damn it.
What's happening?
Who knows?
Train.
-Train to Busan.
-The movie?
Aren't they zombies? It's the same thing.
Zombies are at school?
You watch too much TV.
Watch this. It's true.
Really?
The door! Door!
Right.
Shit. What the hell?
What the fuck is that?
-Bare-su! It's Bare-su! Help him up!
-Quick! Quick! Quick!
Get in here. Hurry, man. You okay?
-Nam-ra! Hurry!
-Come on!
Hurry! Come on! Jump!
Close it. Quick.
Are you okay?
It's that, isn't it?
Zombies.
EMERGENCY MEDICAL CENTER
AMBULANCE
One, two, three.
-What happened to her?
-She came from the school.
She was bleeding when we got there.
But we're not sure exactly what caused it.
-When was she injured?
-We got the call about 30 minutes ago.
Why is she lethargic?
She seemed to be
having seizures at first,
but she calmed down now.
You received the PhD
in cell biology in the US,
returned to Korea.
You were a pharmaceutical researcher
and quit, then teaching.
You should be a college professor
with this résumé.
Definitely not
some lousy high school teacher.
The hospital needs to put Hyeon-ju
to quarantine, nothing less.
Why would a teacher decide
to chain a student?
If I were a college professor…
If I were a prosecutor, or a reporter,
would you have listened?
Ah, that's why you did it.
Because no one listened to you
or understood how you felt?
You were lonely, maybe saddened.
Is that it?
Fine.
Let's do nothing.
Everyone will die.
This world and all those damned imbeciles.
I hate you assholes. You're a sick kind.
Can't stand you.
You commit the crime,
but you blame others, society, everything.
When you reported your son missing,
you said, "The world swallowed my son."
What the hell's that supposed to mean?
What, is the world an anaconda?
It didn't swallow him.
Tell me what really happened to him.
You killed your son.
But you reported him missing
to avoid being a suspect. Am I right?
Your son isn't missing, is he?
What happened to him, huh?
Jin-su is dead.
I placed the mouse and cat together.
MINSONG GYMNASIUM
Most of the mice sat in a corner,
and were frozen, trembling in fear.
But once in a while,
the mouse would lose its senses
due to the overwhelming fear
and attack the cat.
When this happens,
its testosterone level shoots up.
I extracted that hormone and refined it.
For all the mice in this world
living in fear, trembling.
I thought if fear turned into rage,
he'd become stronger than anyone.
He bit his mom.
Infection, day 17.
I gave him benzodiazepine
and stopped the haloperidol.
He'll be awake in less than ten minutes.
You killed your son, didn't you?
-What the…
-Get her! Get her!
Turn it off!
Hold her down!
Oh…
-What's that sound?
-What's going on?
Is something going on in there?
Please help me.
Call the police! Please hurry!
God, I almost run her over.
What's the girl's problem?
People, you know what happens
when you perform like that?
Jang Ha-ri, get up.
Okay.
Take a good look.
She's your future.
Ha-ri's a senior…
without a single gold medal.
Forget the nationals
if she can't even make the reserves.
Couldn't even pass
today's regional qualifier.
What will you do, hm?
She can't get into college,
a corporate team…
No civil service exam. You didn't study.
Listen here. Do you know
how cruel this field is?
The CSAT top 100 kids get
into Seoul, yeah.
But if you're top 100 in archery,
you can't get anywhere near the Olympics.
You're the tritest rot.
Wasting away. Got it?
HYOSAN HIGH SCHOOL
Shit. Fucking nut…
What the…
-See if it's there.
-It's not here, either.
Hey, Joon-yeong! I think you're right.
They can't open doors.
Uh… Let's hold it shut for now.
-Did you find one?
-There's nothing here, either.
-Damn it.
-Any luck, Dae-su?
Are you okay?
Look over there.
-It's not here, either.
-Here!
I found one!
Whose is it?
This is Yeong-ju's desk.
Shit. It's locked.
Do something.
What do you want me to do? It's locked.
Maybe it's her birthday.
When is that?
I don't know. Hmm…
She's over there. Give it.
SWIPE UP FOR FACE ID OR ENTER PASSCODE
You're gonna have to get closer.
For emergency calls,
you don't have to do that.
Just call 112.
AT THE SCENE AS QUICKLY AS POSSIBLE
-Hello. What is your emergency?
-Hello?
This is Hyosan High School.
A ton of zombies showed up at lunch,
and they're eating people.
Don't say zombies.
Then what?
They won't believe you.
Did you happen to see
the movie Train to Busan?
Okay. Hyosan High, zombies.
Please give me your name and phone number.
You know you'll get in trouble
for making these false reports, right?
This isn't a joke.
Everyone's…
Anyway, come quick.
Okay.
Lee Cheong-san.
Your number is 010-4362…
Get somewhere safe,
so that you don't get bitten. Okay?
We'll be there soon to check. Okay?
These brats think they're so damn clever.
Zombies are attacking.
Hyosan High, right?
They must be celebrating or something.
I just got a call about zombies too, sir.
Hello. What is the nature
of your emergency?
You're cutting out.
A patient is attacking people?
Does the person have some type of weapon?
She's biting them?
Zombie girl?
Hey. Go and call the school and verify.
Okay.
Hello. What's your emergency?
Hello. What is the nature
of your emergency?
-A person is biting people?
-What did you say?
SCHOOL MOTTO
HAPPY STUDENTS, SAFE SCHOOL
CLASS MOTTO
SUN-HWA IS WATCHING
No!
Whoa, what's going on?
-Where are they going?
-Why are they leaving?
-What are you doing, moron? Close it.
-Okay, fine.
You scared me.
And the police?
He said they'll come.
Did they believe you?
What if they think it's a prank
and decide not to come?
Well, then try again!
-And tell them to hurry up!
-Shh. Stop yelling.
What if those zombies come back?
Give me that.
Fire Department.
What's the nature of your emergency?
Hi. Hello, sir.
Do you know Captain Nam So-ju
from Rescue Team One?
I'm afraid I don't.
We have many firefighters.
What is this about?
Captain Nam So-ju is my father.
Please tell him
to hurry over to my school.
-Who is she calling?
-Sorry. This is the call center.
You should call his station
if you want to reach him personally.
There's a fire.
-Fire?
-Hyosan High School, classroom 2-5.
Hurry up. The fire is massive.
GYEONGGI FIRE DEPARTMENT
HYOSAN FIRE STATION
RESCUE
No one's coming?
I think something's happening at the gate.
Let's call the cops again.
Get them to listen.
I am, but they won't pick up.
Hey.
Do something.
Tell Miss Park to come and help.
Do what exactly?
I don't know. Anything!
What have you done as class president?
-Stop it.
-Huh?
Teacher's office?
So you just want me to leave now?
Well, if you're offering.
You told me to do something.
Do you want me to leave?
Stop it, you two.
She's only saying that
because you're the class president.
-Yeah. You are, right?
-So just be patient, okay?
So stupid. Typical.
What's typical?
Now that we are in this mess,
I'm your class president?
We called the police,
so I'm sure we'll be fine soon.
But no one's coming!
-Enough already. We're all scared too!
-That's why I'm telling them to call!
Why don't you do it, then?
Ladies, ladies,
can you just stop the whining?
Oh, now you're butting in, shithead?
What? Did you just call me a shithead?
Call me a shithead, you shithead?
-Let it go.
-Stop it.
Hold the door. I said hold the door.
Who the hell does she think she is?
Stop it.
-Did you hear what she said?
-Gyeong-su. Come on. Hold the door.
Let it go. It's nothing new.
-Enough already. I'm going.
-Block it. Just go block it.
-Fine. Seriously… Whoa!
-Shit!
Coach Kang.
Are you guys okay?
What about you? You weren't bitten?
No. Of course not. I'm, I'm all right.
Hey, guys. Let's block the door first.
Get moving. Hurry.
I'm fine. Let's move this.
Like this?
Yes, yes. Stack them high. High. High.
Coach Kang? You called the cops, right?
-You and the teachers. Help's coming.
-Yeah, sure.
What are you doing? Move quickly.
Stack it high. High.
Here.
-Stack it high.
-Higher?
Push it closer. Much closer.
On-jo, look.
What?
There. His arm.
Coach Kang.
Your arm.
What are you doing? Come help us.
-You have a bite mark on your arm!
-Is this…
What?
-What is it?
-I wasn't bitten.
-He said he wasn't bitten.
-No, no. I…
I, I wasn't bitten.
It's a bite mark.
I said it isn't.
Don't talk back to me. Okay?
-It looks like you were really bitten.
-I wasn't!
How many times must I tell you?
Then why the hell are you hiding it?
Just show it to us.
I think you should leave right now.
-What?
-Get out of here immediately.
You want me to go out there?
After all I did to get here?
You want me to go back out?
You were bitten.
Come on. Get out.
I said get out now!
Cocksucker!
How dare you yell at me like that?
You little…
Get over here.
Come here.
Now!
-You won't come? Hey.
-Hey, hey, hey.
-Stop. Stop. Stop it.
-He was bitten.
-Wait, wait, wait.
-Whoa, stay back.
Look.
Let go.
-You fucking bitch.
-Watch it!
Wait, wait.
-Holy shit.
-I think he really was bitten.
Guys, we should get out of here
as soon as possible.
Hey. Hey. He's turning.
Get him out of here! Hurry!
Hurry. Throw him out.
Do something!
No! Dae-su!
Min-ji…
Dae-su. I can't…
I don't want to die.
Get him… Get him out of here!
Cheong-san!
I don't want to die.
Help me.
Don't come closer.
Get away from me. No!
Stop it. Step out of the club, please.
We gotta go.
Get out! Get out!
-Let's go!
-Go, Cheong-san! Dae-su!
Hurry!
Get out!
Gyeong-su!
Watch your hands!
Watch out!
Hey! Get out of the way!
Hey! Come!
Come on, girls! Come on!
Push it!
Let's go!
Keep pushing!
Push!
Get out of here!
Girls, upstairs!
Let's go!
Hurry up!
No! No! Get back!
Back! Back! Back!
-Su-hyeok!
-Get to the lab!
Hurry!
Dae-su! Watch out!
Help me. Help!
Push!
-Push!
-Harder!
It's locked. Gotta go somewhere else!
Nowhere to go! We're surrounded!
-It's locked! Didn't you hear me?
-What now?
Try to open it!
-Can't you see it's locked?
-Hey, block the hole!
Dae-su, push!
Push!
Hey, hey, hey! Careful!
Watch your hands!
Why is it taking so long?
Hey!
-Above you!
-Hey, it's climbing over!
I can't hold them off
much longer. Hurry up!
It's open!
-Go!
-Push!
Push!
Hurry! Hurry! Go in!
Hurry!
Oh, shit.
Oh, damn it!
Get a desk!
Block it!
Block it.
Give me the phone.
I'm gonna try calling again.
Sorry, I lost it.
How could you lose it?
Who cares? We got a secured room now.
Like you can talk.
-What?
-It's because you didn't lock the door.
If you had done that, the gym teacher
wouldn't have gotten to us.
We almost died because of you.
Then why didn't you do anything yourself?
You're so fucking annoying.
Gyeong-su, no, no, no. Hey, don't.
-You bitch.
-Don't you touch me!
Fight after you move these.
This is not the time.
She's right. Stop it.
Yeah, fight after we finish this.
Gyeong-su.
Ugh! This is so fucking annoying!
Su-hyeok?
Has anyone seen him?
You were with him, right?
He was behind me.
Then where is he now?
I don't know.
They've all turned.
I think everyone except us turned.
We're outcasts again.
And this is still hell.
I hope everyone dies.
Every single one of them.
Shh! Shut the fuck up!
We should stay here a bit longer.
Right. Okay.
Do you think they're gone?
What do we do?
Shouldn't we go out and call the cops?
We can't go out now.
I'm sure they're still out there.
Also, who the heck is smoking
in here right now?
And who are you that you're hiding
in the girls' bathroom, huh?
Be a man. If you can even do that.
You… Who are you?
Leave her alone. It's Mi-jin.
Mi-jin? Park Mi-jin?
Yeah.
Joon-seong. I'm really dizzy.
Is it bad?
-Oh, no.
-I don't know. It's weird.
Everything sounds muffled,
and I'm dizzy.
Don't worry,
it's probably just from the shock.
We'll go to the hospital
when things calm down, okay?
Okay.
What is it? Who is it?
Hey, open up.
-Open up. Come on!
-What do you…
-Get out.
-What's wrong with you?
Stay still.
What's going on?
-What are you doing?
-I said to stay still, you moron!
Mi-jin.
Listen carefully.
You know how to play tag?
We hide.
We run to get away from someone.
Now…
Now, you are it.
Don't stand there! Help!
But Ha-lim's in there.
She was bitten. You got that? Now, help.
Mi-jin, don't do this.
I'm okay.
Let me out.
Shut up, zombie fucker!
Joon-seong, don't do this.
Let me out.
We ran away together earlier. I saved you.
If you let her out, we all die.
Shit. Shit!
Get it together. Look up.
What do you want from me?
-We have to kill her.
-Kill Ha-lim?
She's not Ha-lim. She's a… zombie.
Still, I don't wanna.
Do we have any other options?
I don't know.
Mi-jin. I hear you.
I know.
Do you really have
to do that to me?
You're going to turn, eventually.
I know. But you…
I will kill you first.
I'll kill you before anyone else.
Bitch.
Mi-jin.
I… I'm so scared.
Get ready.
I said to get ready.
For what?
We gotta kill her.
Are you gonna hold that forever?
Damn it.
What are you doing?
Why won't she die?
I don't know.
Maybe it's not the right spot.
What…
Stop. Not us. We're fine.
Not us, jackass!
Hey, I think they're okay.
Zombies don't curse.
Shoot if they turn.
You crazy bitch. We're fine--
Students and teachers
of Hyosan High School.
I'm Park Sun-hwa, the English teacher.
Something strange is happening
throughout the school.
Some students
are attacking others indiscriminately.
So please flee and find a safe place.
And if any student
or faculty hears this and is able to,
please call the police
and the fire department.
Students, hide somewhere safe
until help arrives.
If you can get out of the school,
please get out.
I'll say it again.
Some students are…
Hey, everyone…
You're okay, right?
You're not hurt?
I don't know
what's going on in here
or how this whole thing happened, but…
Still, find a safe place and hide.
I… I'm sorry…
I can't help.
Don't get hurt, okay?
Please, let's stay alive and meet again.
Okay?
Rescue Team Three,
head to Hyosan Hospital.
Team Four, head to the accident
at Hyosan Intersection.
Team Two, you have another call.
Fire, Hyosan High School.
Please head there right away.
Ambulance One, stay where you are.
Team One. We've arrived at the accident.
Rescue Team Two. We'll head
to the accident at Hyosan High School.
Accident reports keep coming in.
All units, standby where you are.
Let's go.
Fuck you!
-Why'd you do that?
-There was a fly.
You talked to On-jo, right?
She told Su-hyeok she likes him.
Okay, so?
Why don't you go and comfort her?
I keep trying, but you know.
No, forget it.
Why are you getting annoyed?
What does it have to be
my business who she likes?
Never mind.
On-jo.
Don't worry too much.
I'm sure Su-hyeok will be just fine.
He's a great athlete and super fast.
Mm-hm.
But…
Cheong-san's being super weird.
He's so annoying.
I think… he's so into you.
It's totally obvious!
I don't think so.
He doesn't feel things like that.
He's too busy teasing me all the time.
I-sak.
Why are you so cold?
So cold?
Your hand is really…
What about my hand?
I-sak.
-What's wrong? Are you--
-Really. I wasn't bitten.
I mean it. I really wasn't bitten.
She was bitten.
What's going on?
Did you get bitten?
I said I wasn't!
Hey. Are you okay?
On-jo.
I-sak.
No, right?
I'm not, right?
I'm not.
I'm not one of them.
What are you doing?
Get her out of here right now!
Shit. They're going to climb over.
No.
Come on. I said I'm okay.
On-jo.
Let go.
Hurry up! Do something!
Throw her out the window.
No. Let go.
Hurry! She's turning into a zombie!
I-sak, please don't.
I-sak.
I-sak, don't do this.
Stop it!
Stop it, please!
Cheong-san!
Are you crazy?
-Let go.
-I-sak.
You have to let go.
You want some glitter?
-It's fine. I can do it, okay?
-Go on.
I'll do it for you.
It's good. Look.
It looks great on you!
Get ready.
Hey!
Here!
On-jo.
Come block this!
Let's go.
We're not gonna last here longer.
Where would we go?
The hose from earlier.
Gyeong-su.
Yeah?
What?
What is it?
Open it just a few inches.
Enough for the hose to fit.
Isn't it better to wait
for the rescuers to come save us?
We might all die by the time they arrive.
This will kill us faster.
It's just gonna be--
Is waiting for someone to save us
the best thing we can do?
Oh, whatever.
If I turn into zombie… You're so mad.
Did you get it?
Hey!
Nam-ra, the door.
Help me make some knots.
How do you want it?
Wrap it and tie it.
So a hand or foot can fit.
You said big enough for a foot?
Zigzag. Make it a zigzag.
Big enough increments.
-Zigzag.
-Is this right?
We need more.
This is good, right?
Let's go.
Are we gonna make it down there?
I'll go down and check the empty rooms.
I'll call when it's clear, okay?
Okay.
Be careful.
Hold it.
What are you doing?
What is it?
Come on. Go down, dude.
What?
Gyeong-su, you go first.
Why? Did you see something?
No. But you go first.
What's down there?
Just go.
-You go. Go up there.
-Go already.
You should go.
Then you go, okay?
No. You can do it.
-Man, you can do it.
-Fuck.
But why… why am I…
Grab it and go.
Rock, paper, scissors?
-Just go. Come on.
-I mean…
Cowboy. Shit. God.
Where is it? Hold on.
Wait, I can't reach it.
-Put your foot in.
-Oh, I got it.
-Ohh.
-Careful.
Okay.
Damn it. Where is it?
Oh, shit. Okay, shit. Fuck.
Damn it.
I'll go down.
I wanna go down first.
One person at a time.
You might fall if it shakes too much.
Well, I won't shake it then.
-How long do you want me to wait?
-Just a little bit.
Shit. Why won't it come out?
Gyeong-su! Gyeong-su!
Ms. Park!
Gyeong-su!
-Are you okay?
-Quickly. Hurry.
-Be careful.
-Oh, right.
Cheong-san!
Hey, guys! Miss Park is here!
Miss Park is on the second floor.
The second floor? Broadcasting room?
-Are you okay?
-Yeah.
Were you with the other kids
by any chance?
They're in the science lab.
They'll come down now.
Come down! Okay?
Come down!
Seriously!
What?
Careful. Careful. I got you.
Hold on. Hold on.
You're so heavy.
-Dae-su.
-Miss Park.
Be soon.
Grab the window frame. Okay.
-Grab her.
-I got you.
Let go.
-I have a cramp!
-You okay?
-Ah, shit.
-Straighten your knee.
-Not my legs!
-Watch out for your neck!
Good. You did great. You did great.
Go down.
I-sak…
You have to get it together.
Everyone in here lost a friend, On-jo.
Do you know how many people died?
Why are you so…
There's just no one left that I like.
Well, there are people who like you.
Like your dad.
You have to stay alive for them.
Let's go.
SU-HYEOK, WE'RE IN THE
BROADCASTING ROOM, NAM-RA
Oh…
Hurry.
Hurry up.
Grab her. Okay.
Careful. Okay. Okay.
ALL CHARACTERS, LOCATIONS, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND EVENTS IN THIS SHOW ARE FICTIONAL.
Subtitle translation by: Jeong Lee
Ripped by TTEOKBOKKIsubs