Hans Jonas discussed the responsibilities
of modern science in relation to life.
I named this virus the Jonas Virus.
It is my responsibility to find a cure.
I will not give up.
I'M FUCKING SEXY
-Hey. Help me!
-Fuck.
Shit.
Damn it. Come here.
Ji-min!
-Stop her!
-What are you doing?
-Let go.
-What's with you?
Let go of me!
-Please come down.
-Don't.
I want to die! Leave me alone!
Don't be like this.
I don't want to live!
-Ji-min.
-I want to die!
Please leave me alone! Please!
Let go of me!
Please let me go!
My mom and dad both died.
What am I supposed to do alone?
Why would you die, you crazy idiot?
What's the use in living?
Still, you should live anyway.
I have nobody.
I don't have a mom or a dad.
I have nowhere to go
and no one waiting for me.
No one to scold me or praise me.
Do you know how that feels?
No, I don't.
So stop acting like you know everything.
Who are you to tell me to live?
Have you been in my shoes?
-No.
-Exactly.
Just leave me alone.
I almost always come last in every exam.
Well, not completely last.
Whenever I get my report card, my dad says
my grades won't shoot up
and get me into Seoul National University,
so I shouldn't bother having hope.
He says I should just
make sure I don't get hurt or sick
and to just be healthy.
I don't want to hear it.
I don't want to hear anything.
I didn't believe him.
He'd love it
if I got into Seoul University.
He was only saying that.
But…
there was something he said
that I did believe.
He said that if anything happened to me…
he'd be the first one there.
But he didn't come.
He didn't.
But who knows?
Maybe he can't come.
What if
my dad died?
At least you have hope.
I have nothing.
Is there hope?
Should I wait for my dad?
Or should I run away?
I don't know anything.
I-sak died, Gyeong-su died…
I wish no one else would.
What the hell?
Why are you crying?
Please don't die, Ji-min.
I wish no one else would die.
No one.
I want to leave.
I feel like I'll go insane in here.
Okay, let's go.
Let's leave.
I hate it here.
But how do we get out?
And we have nowhere to go anyway.
Ji-min. Sorry, but just a minute.
Gross.
Can't you people smell? It stinks.
Breathe through your mouth.
What are you doing?
I think we can get out of here.
This is where we are.
This is where Cheong-san is.
If we play music only on this speaker,
the zombies will go left.
Then we'll take the stairs on the right,
get Cheong-san, and go to the rooftop
using the center stairs.
The rooftop? Why?
Choppers keep flying around.
If we light a fire there,
they may come to save us.
Will the zombies really go
toward the speakers?
I think she's right
that they're drawn to sound.
That's right. They come running
whenever they hear us.
Can we just turn on certain speakers?
Yes. We'll turn on the ones
in the cafeteria, yard, and library, too,
and draw them there.
That's right. You were
in the broadcasting club in tenth grade.
Yes, because my mom made me.
That's all good, but
how can we play music?
There's no Internet so we can't stream.
That.
That?
This is ancient. Will it work?
Who wants to do it?
I've never done it before.
Somebody do it. Anyone.
I'll do it, then.
Cheong-san, are you there?
-We--
-What are you doing?
Check.
Cheong-san, do you hear us?
It's Su-hyeok.
We'll come to you so stay put.
Got it?
Don't come, moron. You can't come here.
I know what you'll say,
but we can't hear you from here.
Don't come.
So don't go anywhere. Wait for us.
You really can't go anywhere, okay?
We'll come now.
All good.
Let's get out of here.
The smell of poop makes me want to barf.
It's yours.
-It's not just mine.
-Yes, it is.
-Really?
-Yes.
These punks.
Cheong-san.
Please stay still.
I know you never listen to me,
but listen this time.
Why won't it work?
-Isn't it useless, then?
-That's right.
Time for meditation.
Once again, another joyful day
at school has begun.
Everyone, close your eyes
and calm your hearts.
-Broadcasting room first.
-Happy lives come from happy hearts.
Turn off the right and middle speakers.
BUILDING CENTER - RIGHT - LEFT
It sounds distant.
Yes. I only hear it from the left.
-They're going to the speakers.
-Really?
It worked, right?
Damn it.
ONE HEART
Bare-su.
Let's go.
-Hold on.
-What? Why?
There's one more.
What?
I'm really going now.
Let's go.
Walk slowly.
Check the left first.
BROADCASTING ROOM
Fuck.
Close it.
Fuck, I could've been killed.
Asshole, you said it was clear.
-What? Why?
-There's still one left.
Look.
What do we do?
Is something wrong with him?
Not any more than you.
-Shut up, you prick.
-Sorry.
Everyone else followed the sound,
but he's still there by himself.
Maybe he's deaf.
Fuck. How could he hear when he's dead?
What about the others?
They all respond to sound.
Shit. Beats me.
Damn it.
How do we get out?
Hold on.
Let's wait a little bit.
I'll look.
Let's wait.
We are all beautiful.
We are in
the most beautiful times of our lives.
We can't wait any longer.
Take the others and walk past him
as carefully as possible.
I'll do what I can from behind.
Okay.
Let's go.
…will never perish
even when all else withers and dies.
Hold on tight.
Don't let go.
BROADCASTING ROOM
Run!
Damn it.
Lee Cheong-san.
ROOFTOP
Today will be another joyful day.
You moron.
You let this loser get you?
Thanks.
Of course. I saved your life.
Where's Cheong-san?
Cheong-san?
Why do you ask?
I want to kill him.
What are you talking about?
I'm going to kill him.
You're badly hurt.
Are you okay?
I'm good.
I'm so fucking good.
Where's Cheong-san?
Stop it.
You were always like that.
That's right.
"Do this."
"Don't do that."
Always ordering me around.
It's okay.
Since you were a better fighter than me.
But you can't do that anymore. Fuck!
You're nothing special.
Scared, right?
I know you're scared.
Hey.
Aren't you scared?
You crazy asshole.
You weak asshole.
You motherfuckers!
I said stop it!
Let's go.
Hurry up.
There's one coming. Run!
Hey, what's the code?
-Three-two-one-zero!
-Three-two-two-zero?
Three-two-one-zero, damn it!
Three, two, two…
It won't open! What is it?
-Three-two-one-zero!
-Damn it!
Three, two…
Mi-jin!
It worked! It's open!
-Come on!
-Hey! Hurry!
Hurry!
Joon-seong!
Help me.
Come on!
What are you waiting for? Hurry!
Hurry! Get in here!
Get in here!
I'm fucking tired.
-Damn it.
-Are you crying?
You're crying?
How humiliating.
What is this?
What the fuck happened to you?
What do I do now?
Let me see.
Were you stabbed?
Why the fuck did you get stabbed,
you moron?
Get the first aid kit.
I said get the fucking first aid kit!
Where is it?
Hey.
Where were you?
Cheong-san.
Where's On-jo?
On-jo!
Are you hurt? Are you okay?
Asshole.
How did you know I was here?
I told you not to go.
Why don't you ever listen?
Hey, save the lovers' quarrel for later.
Let's go.
-Where?
-We have to get to the rooftop.
-Before the music ends.
-Let's go. Hurry.
Wait.
Where's Su-hyeok? Su-hyeok isn't here.
-Hey. Where are you going?
-Hey!
Are you insane? Don't go by yourself--
-Go in! Go inside!
-They're coming.
Hurry!
The curtains.
There's a zombie there.
It's caught under the piano,
so it can't move.
We can't make it…
to the rooftop, can we?
We're trapped again, aren't we?
There are zombies outside, so…
Let's think a little.
This is so annoying.
Hey.
Hey, Prez.
Were you bit?
That's a bite mark, right?
Don't push, jerk!
Can't you see we're all in line?
We're all waiting!
I'm sick of this food.
I can't eat pork. Is there anything else?
-Hey!
-Take it and go!
-Hold on.
-Get out.
I can't eat pork!
-Give it a rest!
-That's enough!
Do you think this is your home?
I'm okay.
Are our phones still not working?
No. They won't work here either.
Shouldn't an assembly member
be able to find a way out of here?
I know.
I've never been treated like this.
There's nothing
an assembly member can't do.
Don't be sarcastic.
I've never done
anything illegal or improper.
Then can't you do it just this once?
I really need to go.
Wait a little while.
Once we're tested, I'll get you a chopper
and send you to the school.
The test isn't the problem.
Even if we test negative,
we'll still have to quarantine.
It was nine days for MERS,
two weeks for Covid-19,
and three weeks for Ebola.
Then what? We have to stay here
even after we get tested?
It depends on the incubation period--
Please try not to leave leftovers,
and leave your empty food containers
by the door.
Wait.
Special Mission Unit?
I was a master sergeant.
Are you a senior officer?
He was also with Special Forces.
Nice to meet you, sir.
Sorry. I'd buy you a meal
if we had met outside.
It's fine.
How long are they considering
for quarantine?
We don't know.
Yes, you do.
We don't.
They don't know what this is,
so they don't know the incubation period.
From what I hear,
they're thinking a minimum of one month.
What? That means we have
to be here for at least a month.
Wait until you get tested.
Wait a minute.
Yes, sir.
Well,
I'm really sorry,
but I have to get out of here.
Sir.
Even judges and prosecutors
are standing by and waiting.
Connections don't work here.
I know. I'm really sorry.
-I sincerely apologize.
-For what?
What are you going to do?
What are you doing?
I'm sorry, ma'am.
I have to get to the school.
I said I'd follow the protocols
to help you.
In the past, there were too many lives
I couldn't save due to those protocols.
I'm going.
Please help them
so they are not punished too severely.
You created the mess,
but you want me to clean it up?
You're a mother as well.
And I'm a father.
Hey.
Why did you do that?
He tried to get up.
What should I do?
Don't even think about coming.
Stay after what I just did?
You…
We can't go this way.
There are no kids in school uniforms.
No one got out.
No one was saved.
No.
It's not what it looks like.
Move. Step back.
I'm telling you it's not.
Tell him.
You weren't bitten by a zombie.
Why won't you say anything?
It wasn't a zombie.
Gwi-nam bit her.
Who?
Gwi-nam. The bully.
-Yoon Gwi-nam?
-Yes.
Nam-ra. Were you really bitten by Gwi-nam?
Say it clearly.
It's true.
Gwi-nam was bitten by zombies.
What bullshit is that? Moron.
I saw him get bit.
If you get bitten by zombies, you turn.
-So if Gwi-nam bit her--
-You're wrong!
MUSIC ROOM
Gwi-nam wasn't a zombie.
He wasn't.
He spoke. He recognized me.
You saw. He wasn't a zombie.
Are you sure he was bitten by a zombie?
Yes.
Then I'll turn into a zombie too.
Stop that.
I…
Never mind. I'm leaving.
Thanks, Su-hyeok.
Hey, Prez.
You never call me by my name.
You're not one of them.
She won't turn into a zombie.
Don't you trust me?
I saw Gwi-nam get bit.
-It happened while we fought.
-I fought him too.
That's how I know.
See this?
If she turns, I'll throw her
out the window so she can't attack you.
So don't say anything.
-Su-hyeok.
-Don't say anything, asshole.
You don't need to do this.
You stay quiet too.
Don't come closer.
I warned you.
Screw you.
I warned you first.
Stay away.
Gyeong-su was enough.
I won't lose any more friends.
-Get out of the way.
-I said stay away.
I told you to stop it, fucker.
Get out of my way!
Stop it, both of you!
If I feel strange at all…
I'll make sure I die.
I'm sorry, but--
No need to be sorry.
I'm not sorry towards any of you either.
I'm sorry.
Su-hyeok.
Push me if I turn.
Hey!
That's enough.
She should've turned by now.
No.
She was bitten by Gwi-nam.
She should be fine.
He was bitten by zombies.
Su-hyeok says he wasn't one.
I saw it with my own eyes.
Su-hyeok has no reason to lie.
And I do?
Still, Su-hyeok--
I know you like him,
but this is a different matter.
Why are you bringing that up now?
Stop taking his side all the time.
I am not--
Yes, you are.
Does it hurt a lot?
I said we shouldn't come out!
I said we would all die!
We stopped the bleeding.
You'll be fine when you get to a hospital.
How can I go to a hospital right now?
Damn it.
Yes, you can. Don't worry.
It's all your fault. It's your fault.
Stop whining. You won't die.
Hey. No luck?
See? I told you it wouldn't work.
Stop it already! You're not dying!
Su-hyeok.
I feel weird. I'm hungry.
Why do you smell so good?
Nam-ra.
Su-hyeok!
Get out of the way!
-Don't do it.
-Move!
I told you to stop, fuck.
You moron.
Hey. Cut it out. Stop it already!
-Let go of me!
-They're going to come in!
-Let go!
-Don't do it!
-Watch out, On-jo!
-Get out of my way! Let go of me!
Stop it. Are you blind?
Can't you see Nam-ra?
She would have blood on her mouth
if she bit him.
Did you see it?
Is he bleeding? No, right?
She's right. There's no wound.
But if Gwi-nam bit her--
She's still fine so she's okay.
Put that down.
Stop being so stubborn.
Let go.
I got it so let go.
Why won't you drop that?
None of your business.
You're okay, right?
-Why are you taking my side?
-What?
It's weird.
You hated me.
I still do.
But what's wrong is wrong.
She seems fine. Let's…
She should've turned by now.
No.
I'm not okay. I wanted to bite Su-hyeok.
That's not true.
Stop that.
No, I really did.
I wanted to bite him.
What do you mean?
That's all.
I wanted to bite him.
I don't think I should stay with you guys.
If I hadn't come to my senses,
I would've bit him.
Hey, stop that. What's wrong with you?
I'll go.
Wait.
Did you see Gwi-nam get bitten by zombies?
How many times must I tell you?
Did you see him turn?
No, I didn't.
I was busy running away.
Su-hyeok, you definitely fought Gwi-nam?
Yes, I did.
There's no reason
for either of you to lie.
Maybe Gwi-nam was bitten but didn't turn.
In the movies,
there are people who are immune.
Still, she tried to bite him.
And she could have.
Regardless, she isn't normal.
I can't be with her.
Ji-min.
What? Am I wrong?
I don't know.
I don't know what we should do.
So? What do you want us to do?
Please.
Don't fight.
If I leave, it'll solve everything.
Don't go. Where would you go? Stop it.
Please.
Let's not let anyone else die.
Hyeon-ju and I-sak's hands
were very cold before they turned.
Nam-ra's hands are warm.
She isn't a zombie.
So let's just talk about
how to get to the roof.
-No.
-Ji-min!
No!
She may be fine now,
but who knows when she'll turn?
The rest of you say something.
This is wrong.
She said so herself
that she wanted to bite him.
She has zombie blood flowing in her veins!
Zombies killed my mom and dad.
My innocent mom…
Hey.
Give me your hand.
-What are you doing?
-Tying our hands together.
Stop it. Stop.
Stop it.
Happy? She can't go to you
even if she turns.
She can only bite me.
What do you plan to do?
I have to leave.
It won't take long on that.
I don't think it'll start.
Why are you so damn pessimistic?
The one earlier was in an accident.
That one's obviously fine.
How can two people ride that?
Three.
You're really taking the baby?
If we leave the baby here, it'll die.
Here.
Sit in the back
and beat up anyone who gets close.
I can't go. No way.
You bastard.
I'll report you for desertion.
Fine, go ahead.
Given the situation, the court will agree
these were extenuating circumstances.
-Court? Extenuating circumstances?
-Yes.
You're pretty smart.
Yes, I am. I go to Seoul University.
Okay, then.
I'll break all the windows on my way out
so that they can get in.
No!
Damn it.
Let's go.
A person should use his head.
We need to stay alive
to tell someone about the laptop.
CHEONGSAN CHICKEN
-What's that?
-Help!
-Hey.
Come here!
We should've just gone when we decided to!
Are you going
to save everyone in the world?
-Are you an angel?
-I'm a detective.
Damn it.
-Take the baby.
-Okay.
Are you okay?
Are you hurt?
Mommy.
-Mommy is over there.
-Where?
Where's your mommy?
Is…
is that your mommy?
The one wearing red?
Sir. I don't know how to hold babies,
but this baby keeps smiling at me.
-Wait a minute.
-What do I do?
Stay still for a minute.
Fuck.
What's wrong with this world?
It'll all be okay.
Hey. If she's immune,
does that mean she's okay
even if she gets bitten?
Probably.
Fuck. I'm so jealous.
But she still has zombie blood
flowing in her veins.
She isn't completely a zombie.
A hambie?
What's a hambie?
Half zombie?
What the hell?
It's like half-half.
Like half spicy, half fried…
-I want fried chicken.
-Stop it.
We haven't even had water for two days.
Is it true we'll die
if we don't have water for three days?
I don't know.
Don't talk to me. I'm hungry.
Dae-su, don't you want
that soda we had on our way to school?
-Aren't you dying for it?
-Yes.
I want Hot Six with Pocari.
I'll see your soda, Hot Six, and Pocari
and raise you an iced vanilla latte.
How could you think about food
with a zombie right here?
Stop it. Nam-ra isn't a zombie.
Hambie.
That's still a zombie.
Let's not do that among ourselves.
We're all we have.
She's right. Prez is better than Na-yeon.
Don't even say her name. She's subhuman.
Gyeong-su died because of her,
and Ms. Park…
That's true.
If it weren't for Na-yeon,
they'd still be with us.
That's right.
The PTA asked the parents
to send stuff before the competition
and asked my mom to send some chicken.
Chicken?
We would've seen it if it were here.
There's nothing here.
Hold on.
Fuck. Maybe it's in here.
Hey.
-What?
-We don't know what's in there.
We need to eat and survive first.
-Fuck. It's locked.
-It's locked, damn it.
Let's open it.
Find something to open it.
-Hurry.
-Look for something. Hurry.
What do you think?
-That wall is our only way out, right?
-That's our best option.
Security is insane.
We're completely trapped.
-Let's go over it.
-Are you sure? We'll be seen for sure.
That's the only way.
RESTRICTED AREA
AUTHORIZED PERSONNEL ONLY
-What?
-Rope.
Drop me a rope.
-U-sin.
-Yes?
My God.
Stay alive.
What are you doing? Take me with you.
Captain!
Freeze.
Freeze!
What are you doing?
Stop right there.
What the hell?
I told you not to move!
I'm on patrol, punk.
Which unit are you with?
Sorry.
Pardon?
It won't work?
Should we knock it down?
Damn it.
PTA DONATIONS
Hey. Take it easy.
Hey. Keep it down! Quiet!
Hey.
Stop it.
It won't work.
What a waste of energy.
Don't play any music either.
My mom and dad…
came to the school to save me,
but the cops…
and firefighters never came.
If anyone sees this later,
please punish
everyone who should have come.
Everyone abandoned us.
All of them.
I swear I'll make you pay.
Mom.
Dad.
I'll stay alive and get revenge.
I'll get revenge on the zombies…
and everyone else, Mom.
Mom.
Dad.
Hi.
I'm fine. The kids are really good to me.
Want to see them?
Well…
Mom, Dad…
I miss you.
And…
I'm so sorry.
Give it to me too.
Mom.
I want a raise in my allowance.
-Is it ready to go?
-Yes.
Music and lyrics
by intergalactic superstar Yang Dae-su.
Beat.
Chicken tastes better fried in olive oil
Pork tastes better than soy meat
Strawberry cake tastes better
Than plain strawberries
What makes me laugh, laugh, laugh
Is trans fat
Cheong-san?
Mom.
It's me.
Dad, you're okay too, right?
I'm…
I'm doing okay.
Hi, Dad.
You're okay, right?
I waited for you all night,
but you didn't come,
so we're trying our best to hang on.
You said being healthy is the best
even if I don't get good grades.
You said you'd come first
if anything happened.
You're okay, right?
You have to be okay, Dad.
You don't have to come save me.
But still, I wish you'd come.
I really thought you would come.
But I'm okay.
I only say this
when you give me my allowance,
but I'll say it for free today.
Dad.
I love you.
I love you so much.
ALL CHARACTERS, ORGANIZATIONS,
LOCATIONS, INSTITUTIONS,
AND EVENTS IN THIS SHOW ARE FICTIONAL.
Subtitle translation by: Jeong Lee