Jae-jun,
are you still at the base?
-You're not going anywhere, right?
-Put on your gas masks!
I won't go there, Mom. Don't worry, okay?
They said on TV that all
the soldiers were being sent there.
That must include you too.
Why would it? I'm almost discharged.
When you're about to be discharged,
they don't have you stand guard
or even train.
Yeah, right.
Then why did they cancel your last leave?
Do you have any idea how worried I am?
-You didn't even call--
-Mom.
Yes? What?
I gotta go.
Did you go somewhere else
instead of coming home?
Where are you going?
To play soccer. Bye, Mom.
Jae-jun!
What are you doing
playing soccer? What if you get hurt?
I mean, what do you want me
to do all day? Hmm?
I'm tired of playing video games.
All you did before
was play video games.
-Status.
-Clear.
Clear.
Report.
Control, this is Shadow Gamma.
We cleared all the infected
on the ground floor.
No survivors founded.
We're moving to the third floor.
I can tell you're lying.
You're not playing soccer, are you?
Promise, I am.
Come out. You're safe.
We're saved! Come out.
-Hurry.
-Thank you.
-Slowly. Walk. Slowly.
Walk in a single file.
It's safe out there.
Zone three secured.
Two infected sighted.
Copy. Take them down.
Just please don't go
anywhere that's too dangerous.
Okay? For me?
I love you, son.
You know that, right?
I love you too, Mom.
I'll see you later, okay?
When I'm discharged.
Jae-jun.
Get back safely.
Make sure to call me later.
I'll be waiting, okay?
There's hope.
A small number of white blood cells
were detected in the blood.
Even after full transformation,
the white blood cells remained,
and they were fighting like warriors.
If I raise the body temperature,
I can activate these cells.
Twenty-nine degrees now.
In case blood isn't flowing,
I'll raise the temperature
both internally and externally.
You guys can leave a message
as well if you want to.
I don't really have anything to say.
You?
We trust you.
You can untie it now.
Su-hyeok, I don't know
why you're doing this.
Because the others are really scared.
And you're not scared?
Mm-mm.
Why?
Because…
I'm just not.
You know how I said
I wanted to bite you earlier?
It's okay.
It's in the past now.
It felt like I was dreaming.
You were just giving off
such a beautiful scent.
What kind of scent?
I'm not sure.
It was something
that I had never smelled before.
All I could think about was eating you.
How much I wanted to bite you.
Bite you and eat you.
I only thought…
Then I heard your voice suddenly saying…
Nam-ra.
It was your voice that woke me up.
You know you never called me by my name.
It was always "Hey," or "Prez."
It was the first time you said my name.
I know.
I was afraid you'd know…
if I said your name.
What?
That I like you.
I don't get good grades,
and I used to hang out
with bullies before.
But you, you're a perfect student.
You get good grades.
And you're so pretty.
Su-hyeok.
I like you.
I'm glad…
to know before I die.
NIGHT DUTY ROOM
Hello, sir.
Shit. You scared me.
You're…
You're Seon-yeong, right?
Eun-ji.
Right. Eun-ji, right.
Are you all right?
I am.
Except that I'm starving.
It's driving me crazy.
What?
Hey.
Are… are you all right?
You were bitten?
Yeah.
I was.
Okay.
Wow, you must have been so hungry.
Eun-ji.
Jeez. That must have hurt a lot.
Huh?
Guess you should go to the infirmary!
Remember what you said
when I said I was an outcast?
"Don't tell me about it.
Go tell your homeroom teacher."
'Cause you didn't want them
to have a committee.
"You're an outcast
because you're so dense."
Do I still seem dense?
Okay, I get it. So get out.
Get out. Please, get out.
Stay there.
Stay back.
Get out.
What?
I heard something strange.
-What if she's finally starting to turn?
-Huh?
What if half-bies don't turn?
Oh, my gosh.
My bad.
I hear it.
-What?
-What do you hear?
I think someone is puking.
It stopped.
What stopped?
The sound of puking.
Stop it. You're scaring me.
Don't you hear it?
I'm not hearing anything.
What?
Are you scared?
Stop that.
It's just…
…you're the one breathing the loudest.
I hate this fucking school.
Do you hear that?
All I hear is that zombie.
What?
We should go. It's weird here.
We can't just leave.
There are zombies out there.
We should've gone to the roof
when the music was playing.
Shit.
Music.
Wait a minute. We have music.
What? What music?
Shit.
This is insane.
Oh, what the fuck!
What are you doing
you stupid piece of shit?
You scared me.
Hey, get down. Get down.
Come on, come on. Move your ass.
Get in here. Hurry up.
Get in here.
Get in, you asshole.
-So, you okay?
-Huh?
Where the fuck have you been?
Me?
Well, obviously, you.
What happened to your eye?
What? My eye?
Get it together, idiot.
What are you looking at, moron?
Listen.
Look. You see that car?
-You're gonna go run in that way.
-Why should I?
Shut up. You run if I say,
you little shit.
You want me to lure the zombies?
Mm-hmm. You go that way and lure them.
I'll go over that way and scream.
Then we run to the snack shop
while they're confused.
Got it?
I'll be going away from the snack shop.
That's why you should run like hell
and circle around.
Okay, come on. Run.
No way.
You chicken shit.
All right, go. Go, come on--
Don't talk to me that way.
I'm not your gopher now either.
Hey. Are you fucking out of your mind?
Snap out of it, will you?
Look at me.
It's me.
Do it.
Fine. I'll go.
Go now.
Hurry the fuck up.
Come with me.
What?
Quiet.
They'll hear you.
Watch this.
Look at it.
You're nothing to me now, got it?
Ah, you stupid chicken shit.
Beg for your life.
Come on.
"Save me." Come on.
Save me. Please, please save me. Please.
No way.
Gwi-nam! Save me, you fucking asshole!
Cheong-san.
I'll gouge your eye out.
We're going to have to build
a tall barricade here,
and then we lure them in with music.
Use the instruments too.
If we leave the door open,
they'll follow the music in.
Once it's clear,
we take the back door up to the roof.
In other words, what you're saying is
we stack desks, chairs, and whatever else
we could find in the middle here.
Open the front door
and run out through the back door, right?
Not here. Farther back.
We need more room on this side.
And why is that?
There aren't that many of us,
but there are lots of zombies.
Ah…
She sucks at school,
but she's pretty smart.
Hey.
It's a compliment.
Let's give it a shot.
We can figure out the rest later.
We have a TV too.
We should be able to connect it
and make it louder.
I will have to look for the cord though.
-Hey, can you help me look, Ji-min?
-Sure.
-Me too.
-It should be over here.
Let's give it a shot.
Guys.
We should untie that.
We should build
a frame first.
I'll do the moving.
You guys work on the frame.
It's okay.
Su-hyeok.
Keep it down.
She'll never be able to get close
to the others this way.
And no one will approach her.
Hatred is contagious.
But so is trust.
Nam-ra.
You should've been the class president.
Come on, let's help out.
Let's go.
One, two, three.
POLICE
RESTRICTED AREA
Hey. Be quiet.
Keep it down, okay?
They're gonna swarm all over it.
Make sure to build a strong foundation.
Well…
There. Right there. Empty spot.
Fix it down there first.
Maybe that's too big.
Wait, what?
It's looking great.
Ow. Ow, ow!
Ow, it hurts.
Suck it up.
You're supposed to be a senior.
Why do seniors have to put up
with everything?
I'm not smoking,
and you can't handle that?
-You'll die if you don't smoke?
-Yes, of course.
I feel like I'm going to fucking die,
so you suck it up too, all right?
We'll take the trail.
The one behind the building.
Once we get past the tennis courts,
we can go through the construction site
and up the mountain.
Do you think we can make it?
I'm not sure.
Motherfucker.
Min-jae.
If you don't think he'll make it,
drop him and shoot, okay?
Okay.
Are you talking about me?
-Let's go.
-Up, on three.
Ready? One, two, three!
Hold on. Wait.
Hold on.
Wait. Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Hey. If you drop this.
You pick them up, okay?
Let's go.
One, two, three.
Oh, he's so heavy!
Shit.
Hold on.
Ow. Wait. Hold on.
Hey. Look, it broke! What do we do?
-Get back in. Hurry! Get back!
-Back in?
-Back! Get back!
-Back. Damn it!
They're coming! Hurry.
Oh, shit.
Hey. Go without me. Okay?
Idiot.
You can't take me anyway.
You'll post about it on Facebook
if we leave you..
I won't.
I don't trust you.
Stop pretending to care.
You killed Ha-lim.
You don't care about anyone.
You're such a dick.
Let's try once again. Stronger this time.
Okay.
What the hell do you want from me anyway?
It hurts like crazy.
Do you know what dying feels like?
Yeah.
I feel that way every single time
I take a test.
But…
I can only take so much of your pain.
Shut up and be quiet, all right?
CHEONGSAN CHICKEN
You're okay? Doesn't hurt?
Sergeant…
you know…
I'm thinking that
we should probably use our skills
to get ourselves out of here first.
And then they can send
the army in for the kids after, you know?
I think that makes more sense.
Sergeant?
If we all die,
who's going to tell them
about the important laptop--
Ho-seong.
Ho-cheol.
Do you know why some people run
to safety when they are in danger?
Because there are others
who are running into danger for them.
Why put ourselves in danger
if there's no reason to?
You're so frustrating.
I ought to just…
If you die,
I'll put in a request with the higher-ups
for a statue of you as big as the one
of Admiral Yi Sun-sin.
Okay? Happy?
What's with this guy?
If you're feeling scared,
you could just stay here.
Goodness. Very well put. Yes.
Okay, listen.
We're gonna leave together now.
We're gonna go zoom on the motorcycle, hm?
What about Mommy?
Well, your mommy…
Let's just come back for her later, okay?
My son is about your age.
He's very handsome.
I can introduce you to him if you like.
I already have a boyfriend though.
Uh… Hey, what did I say to do
once we go out?
You said to keep my eyes shut tightly
and hold onto you.
That's right. Good girl. Very good.
Are you ready?
Uh, no.
CHEONGSAN CHICKEN
Go faster! Faster!
-Speed up! Speed up!
-Shut up!
You're drawing them to us,
you fucking idiot!
Shut up, I say!
Quiet, asshole!
Watch it. Oh, my god!
-They're coming!
-Oh, they're right behind us!
Look ahead, dipshit!
Turn! Turn, turn!
Go!
-Turn! Turn!
-Where? Where?
Just go this way, sir. This way. Go.
Watch out! Watch out! Careful!
Right! Go right!
Oh, a dead-end!
-What do we do?
-Wait.
Wait, no! There's a way!
-Oh, my god. There is?
-There is!
Let's go.
Hey, what are you--
Stop doing that.
Right here you fuckers!
Go!
Yeah!
Se-bin, we're saved!
Pipe down
unless you want more of them.
Help me!
Huh? What?
-Here, over here!
-What's that sound?
-Please help.
-Hear that?
Here!
Look up! Over here!
Over here.
-Help me!
-What is that?
Hey, you idiot!
Idiot, asshole.
-What the?
-What took you so long?
-All right, hang on.
-Sergeant, let's just go. Come on.
-Huh?
-Let's just go. Come on, please.
Please help me.
Just go. Let's go.
Do you have
something to drink?
Ooh. There's more, look.
What? Where?
Ah, there's nothing.
Can you climb down?
No. I hurt my leg.
-I can't get down.
-Let's just go.
Come on, please. Let's go.
Wait, wait, wait. What are you doing?
-What are you gonna do?
-There.
-Here, take the baby.
-Huh?
Hurry, sir. Please.
-Hold on.
-What are you gonna do?
Stay still.
Stay right here.
Bring the bike close. Shit.
Yeah, climb up that way.
Bring it close. Asshole.
Come here. Hurry. Hurry.
Fuck this.
Ho-cheol! Ho-cheol!
-Where is he going?
-Stop it!
Ho-cheol! Wait!
Where the hell
is he going?
-College boy! Stop!
-Get back here, you moron.
All right. I think this is good enough.
Okay.
Aren't you guys coming?
We left a gap over there for you.
Let's go.
Why aren't you coming over?
Well, someone has to stay
to open the door.
Couldn't you have come up
with a better plan?
It's okay.
-I'll come over right away.
-Wait.
I'll come.
It's fine.
It is not fine.
Here.
What happened with you and Gwi-nam?
He said he was gonna kill you.
Shit.
It's because I saw him
killing the principal.
I said I was going to tell the cops,
so he tried to kill me.
Prick.
Gwi-nam's dead.
Yeah?
Mm-hm.
He fell from up high
when I was fighting him.
-And I'm in love with Nam-ra.
-Huh?
I've liked Nam-ra for a while now.
You have?
You be good to On-jo, okay?
Don't treat her like she's a guy, moron.
You ready? I'll do it.
Go. Get over there.
Go.
Oh, shit.
Dae-su, you got to make some noise!
Die, zombies!
Fucking die!
Do it one more time.
Shit.
Stupid zombies.
Motherfuckers!
Wu-jin!
We can't go yet! Not yet.
Nam-ra!
It's not going to hold up!
Shit.
How much longer is it gonna take?
Let's go!
A little more. Not yet!
We need to study him
to create a treatment or a vaccine,
but we don't have equipment or scientists.
We'll have to take him to the KDCA.
He cannot leave the quarantine zone
under any circumstances,
do you understand?
Find scientists and build the facility.
We will airlift all necessary equipment.
-What's his name?
-Staff Sergeant Lee Jae-jun.
A week away from discharge,
but he volunteered for the operation.
Get his parents consent to do research.
We're under martial law,
we don't need his parent's consent.
If you decide to give consent,
we can begin the experiment
or autopsy right away.
I said call his parents.
Even under martial law,
that's our duty
for taking away their child.
Yes, sir.
Commander, sir.
There's assemblywoman awaiting testing.
She has to follow rules.
It's Park Eun-hee
from the National Defense Committee.
Damn it.
I'm the commander here.
Nice to meet you. I'm--
Even if you are
an assemblywoman,
around here you're not going
to get any special treatment.
That's all I came to tell you.
Don't bother these people
trying to do their jobs.
I'd appreciate it
if you'd stay quiet and follow the rules.
That's fine. I have a favor to ask though.
Please send a chopper
to Hyosan High School.
There's a firefighter on his way there.
He's by himself.
Commander. Hey. Wait!
You got to send the helicopter
to the high school.
We have to save the children!
Even wars can't rid of schools.
Even if you win,
if the schools are gone, we've lost.
How many students
have we saved so far?
So far, zero sir.
We don't think anyone got out
because all the students
were in class at that time.
Are choppers available?
No, sir. They've all been sent
on missions.
Request a Black Hawk immediately.
Have them scan high schools in Hyosan.
Absolutely, sir.
MAP OF HYOSAN
Gangha-dong as well?
Isn't that where your mother's house is?
Once he's named in the rescue zone,
we can check there.
Okay, sir.
Clear. We have to go now!
Hurry!
Hey, let's go!
-Go!
-You go first.
I'm gonna shit my pants. Go!
-Come on.
-Let's go.
Hurry.
Move!
PROPER EDUCATION BREEDS GOOD CHARACTER!
Cheongmok Middle School.
Impossible to check for survivors.
Alpha lifted.
I'll go to Hyosan High.
Come on.
Over here! Over here!
Here! I'm here!
Over here!
Come on, open it.
It's locked.
What?
Move.
Wait. Get back. Move.
Shit.
Is anyone there?
Anyone?
Is anyone there? Anyone?
Open the door!
Of course not! Get back.
One, two, three!
THE ROOFTOP IS OFF LIMITS TO STUDENTS
Fuck.
Hear that?
What?
We're outcasts again.
And this is still hell.
I really hope everyone dies.
All of them.
Mom.
It's me.
Dad, you're okay too, right?
I'm…
I'm doing good.
Mom.
Cheongsan Chicken
still sounds stupid, by the way.
If it were Cheongsan Auto, Cheongsan Group
or Cheongsan Air
that be different,
that'll be okay.
CHEONGSAN CHICKEN
HYOSAN HIGH SCHOOL
They're here.
DOOR WILL OPEN AUTOMATICALLY
IN CASE OF FIRE
Get back!
Throw this over!
Out of my way.
Freeze! Freeze!
Get down. Get down!
35.6 DEGREES CELSIUS
Are you okay?
Where are the others?
Isn't there anyone else?
-Hold onto it!
-Come on. Hold it tight!
ONE HEART
ALL CHARACTERS, LOCATIONS, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND EVENTS IN THIS SHOW ARE FICTIONAL.
Subtitle translation by: Jeong Lee
Ripped by TTEOKBOKKIsubs