Ahh.
Mm. Those are good worms right there.
Hey, Alex! How's the commute treating you?
Hey, I can't complain.
That never stopped him before. Ha-ha!
Right? Ha.
Well, we made good time today.
Red was one of my students.
Hmm.
Not sure about the dabbing though.
Mom! Mom, did you get my picture?
Well, this is our stop.
♪ The birds in the sky go through the air ♪
♪ All the way there ♪
Today, we're gonna learn
about how Red saved the eggs.
Yay!
I love Red!
I gotta go to the bathroom!
Why didn't you go in the slingshot?
Bomb, anything from Piggy Island?
No.
Chuck. Anything to the north?
Nope. Nothing.
What's that?
Uh-oh.
Incoming pie!
It's coming straight for us.
What do we do?
Duck!
What?
Ah! I got pie all over my face!
Hey, sorry, buddy.
What, what? Yeah!
Those pigs...
Are gonna pay...
For our lunches!
Uh... Because of our hunger to give them...
A taste of their own...
Quesadillas!
What?
It's Red.
I'm sorry, guys.
We're taking over the Blue Line.
Official business.
Yeah!
Anything for you, Red.
Hey, Red!
Isn't it funny how nobody liked you
until you saved Bird Island?
But now we all love you.
Ha. Thanks so much for bringing that up.
Okay, ready?
Three...
Two...
Two!
Bomb, you say "one."
Oh, right.
One!
Yoo-hoo! Hot sauce, please.
Yeah! Got him.
Thank you very much.
Red! Red! Red!
I really want the red one. The red one.
Ha-ha.
Balloonie!
Heh-heh. That's it. A little bit higher.
Ha-ha.
But I was bouncing!
You mess with the hatchlings,
you get the cannonball.
Ready, big guy?
Oh, yeah. You ready, bigger guy?
Cannonball! Cannonball!
♪ I need a hero ♪
Why won't you just take a bath?
♪ And it's gotta be soon
And he's gotta be larger than life ♪
Huh?
This might pinch a little.
Agh! I can't see!
Catch you later. Heh-heh.
You stupid birds.
No! Please, don't!
Not on my watch.
Sorry, guys.
Excuse me, sir,
but I believe this belongs to you.
My hero.
Don't. Stop.
Heh-heh. I said, "Don't stop."
Leonard?
Got him!
Hey, Leonard, you should probably...
Huh?
That's not coming from Bird Island.
What the heck is that?
And where did it come from?
We're gonna need a bigger slingshot.
Another successful day of protecting
the island.
Great job, guys.
Ha-ha. Oh, yeah.
Woo-hoo! Whee!
You saved us, Red.
You're our hero.
What can I say? That's what I do.
Now, why don't you run along
and keep your big, cute eyes peeled
for the next pig prank, all right?
Pigs.
We're going to get you!
Oink, oink, oink.
Ha-ha. Adorable.
Let's finish cleaning up these crabs,
then we can move on to...
Done and done.
Red, what is it?
What the heck?
Is it a per...? Is it a head? What is that?
It seems like it's some kind of note.
What if it's a love note?
A message in a bottle?
Or a genie in a bottle.
Guys, there's no bottle,
so just, you know, stop.
Dear birds,
we humbly request a truce.
Can we talk?
Love, Leonard. X-O-X-O.
Ho, ho, ho. Nice try, piggies.
News flash: we're not idiots.
Hey.
Dear birds,
you are idiots,
but we are serious about the truce.
Oh...
I got it!
Oh, no!
Check it out, everybody.
Let me see that.
A truce! A truce!
A truce with the pigs!
A truce?
The prank war is over! Ha-ha!
What?
No, this is just
another one of their pranks.
What?
Huh?
This is a huge relief, right?
Who else was getting tired
of the constant pranking and retaliation?
Me! This guy!
Tired? No, no, no. Guys, listen.
Imagine all the fun things we can do now.
I can think of one.
You think he'll go?
I think we've piqued his interest.
No, no, no. Guys, we are working tirelessly,
day and night, to save the world.
The world doesn't need saving, Red.
Of course they need us.
Red.
Huh?
Come here, hon.
What are you so afraid of?
Afraid of? I...
What do I have to be afraid of?
♪ All by myself ♪
♪ Don't wanna be all by myself ♪
♪ Anymore ♪
I'm not afraid of anything.
Okay, you know what?
I'll write you a prescription
for one night of fun with your cool friends.
Especially Chuck.
Come on.
Come with us.
What are you talking...? Come with you to what?
We can't tell you because you wouldn't be into it.
Huh?
Oh. Oh, ho, ho, ho!
Oink, oink, oink!
Ha! Now we have all your eggs.
Yeah, and there's nothing
you can do about it, Red.
Oink, oink, oink.
Laugh it up, piggies,
because you're gonna be crying in a second
when I kick your butts and take those rocks back.
Eggs.
What?
You said "rocks" instead of "eggs" again.
Oh, sorry.
I don't know why I keep doing that.
Because they are rocks.
Don't cry, Sam-Sam.
I'll be right back.
Hey, Daddy.
Hrm.
Just borrowing my sisters for a minute.
Hmph.
Ha! Now we really have all your eggs.
Yeah, and there's nothing
you can do about it, Red.
Oink, oink, oink.
Laugh it up, piggies,
because you're gonna be crying in a second
when I kick your butts and take all your...
Uh... Uh... Uh... Um, um, um...
Oh, crap.
Okay, we'll just... Aah!
What is this thing that almost killed me?
Frozen water?
Who's ever heard of frozen water?
Courtney? Courtney, bring me those images.
What, what, what?
Oh, okay, I'm coming. I'm coming.
Give me that.
Oh, that looks cold.
Three umbrellas in one drink?
What kind of extravagant lunatic are
we dealing with?
Mmm.
♪ Nibblin' on sponge cake ♪
♪ Watchin' the sun bake ♪
There goes my toothpaste.
I am tired of this.
Whoo! Yes! Hot shower.
♪ Strummin' my six-string ♪
There we go.
Go, Zeta. You killing it.
Whoo! Zeta!
Come on, baby. Go get it.
Let's go get it.
Go get the stick.
Rrrg.
♪ Some people claim
That there's a woman to blame ♪
♪ But I know ♪
Whoa!
Oh, my gosh!
I can't do this anymore.
Okay, Debbie?
Okay.
I'm done. I'm done living on this frozen,
seal-infested iceberg of an island.
Fire another ice ball!
Uh...
We can't do that, Zeta.
Wait...
You're torturing the engineer.
Uh... Eh... Hello?!
My limbs are beginning to numb.
Ha-ha! Oh, yeah, I forgot about that.
You better tell him to improve his aim.
It's about time we start living that good life.
Good life, here we come.
I deserve to feel the hot sand squishing
between my beautiful talons.
You deserve that and more.
Yes, I do!
Whoo-hoo!
Aah!
Well, here we are.
Are you ready, Red? Love awaits! Huh?
Speed dating? No. No way.
It's mating season.
All right, lovebirds.
You all know how this works.
When you hear this sound,
then it's time to move on to the next table,
where your soul mate just might be waiting.
Yeah, I'm going home.
Absolutely not. You have nothing else to do.
Also, I hid your keys on some part of my body and
I'm not telling you where unless you stay. Ha-ha-ha!
Yeah, let's party!
Hey, yo! Chuck's the name. Speed's the game. Like games?
Well...
You just entered the love lottery, and guess what.
You won! Because here I am.
Hi.
Hi. Heh-heh.
I eat dirt.
Oh! Ew.
Hey, y'all!
Who's ready to party?
Oh, heh... Not me.
No, I'm actually not here for the whole
speed-dating horror-show thing going on.
Shh. This mating dance is for you.
♪ Y'all ready for this? ♪
I'd love to hear a little bit about you.
What's your favorite sign?
This one's mine. Ha-ha-ha.
The flavor can vary greatly,
depending on the minerals in the dirt.
I can tell which kind of worms have
crawled through there.
Or what sort of roly-polies used it
to raise their family in.
Um, are you mad?
No.
I don't know. You look mad.
Well, I'm not.
Yeah, you know what?
Maybe it's your eyebrows.
My eyebrows are fine.
That's just the way I look.
It's like you've got resting bird face.
Oh, yeah? Well, you know,
that's not a thing.
Yes! Amazing.
With utensils. I'm not a total animal.
But I do enjoy eating dirt.
Ugh.
Okay, worms, birdseed
or just garbage from a dumpster?
I'm sorry, what?
Favorite food, silly.
Don't think.
Just answer from your gut. Go!
Uh... Toast?
Okay. Toast.
Favorite color?
Uh...
Oh. Stupid question. Red, duh.
If you could have one superpower,
what would it be?
Um, to disappear, like, right now.
Okay. What do you do in your free time?
Yeah, I mean,
I don't really have any free time.
I protect Bird Island from being attacked,
and that's a full-time gig, so yeah.
I thought I heard something about
a truce.
Ha-ha-ha. No. A truce, no.
That's not gonna last.
You'll have a lot more free time
now that nobody needs you anymore, so... Heh-heh.
Okay. We are done here.
Are you afraid to talk about your feelings?
Hey, you know, just because I don't want
to talk about them doesn't mean I'm afraid.
Okay. So avoids personal questions. Unusually angry.
Talks to herself.
Self-esteem issues.
Doesn't answer her own questions.
Left-handed. Probably a witch.
Looks like we're definitely incompatible.
Oh, and you needed a form
to tell you that. Okay.
I hope you have better luck annoying the next guy.
I don't need luck. I have a formula.
Okay. Have a nice life.
Have fun being alone.
Oh, I will.
Aww. There he goes,
like a ship in the night.
No rudder, no purpose, no crew.
Well, have a good night.
♪ In the arms of the angel ♪
♪ Fly away from here ♪
♪ From this dark, cold hotel room ♪
♪ And the endlessness that you fear ♪
Loser!
Hello! Oh!
Look, Red, I know we've had our differences.
Oh, like when you tried to eat our young?
I come in peace.
Ouch. Aah!
Look, I don't want to see your face
any more than you want to see mine.
We're all in danger!
Yeah. From you.
Ouch!
No, we have a truce.
Didn't you get my note? It was on a balloon.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
You wanted to talk.
This is not how a truce works.
Just say what you gotta say and then get out.
Aagh!
Red, we've discovered that there's a third island,
and they're plotting to destroy us all.
A third island?
Give me one good reason
why I should believe you.
Haven't you noticed any strange objects
falling from the sky?
Giant balls of ice?
♪ But you'll look sweet ♪
♪ Upon the seat ♪
♪ Of my ♪
♪ Bicycle built for two ♪
Nope, nothing. Haven't seen anything.
Well, I have, and I'll show you the proof.
Squeal Team Six!
What the...?
Hey, hey, hey. Easy, easy. Stop.
Everybody stop. Agh!
That image in your hand is Eagle Island,
and those are eagles.
Eagles? How did you get these?
From a drone.
Oh.
And do you spy on us with that?
Yes.
So have you seen me, um...?
Yes, and it's disgusting.
Red, this is bigger than pranks.
We need to put aside our differences
and work together.
To save our whole world
from being destroyed.
Red! Red! Red!
What we really need is a hero.
I'm in.
Wonderful!
We'll have to get a team together.
Yes, we will.
But, hey, I'm in charge.
Actually, that position's been filled.
Booya!
Yeah. By me.
Oh, man, you're gonna love this guy.
Not the smartest bird in the tree,
Aah!
but what he lacks in smarts,
he makes up for in firepower.
Happy birthday!
Aah!
We've got a number two
at the Porta Potty.
Aah!
All right, I'm going!
We're busting you out.
Uh... How?
Like that.
Oh, I love it.
Bomb, what was that noise?
You're still grounded!
I'm an adult, Mom!
Run.
Bomb, get back here!
This guy is so fast,
he can beat time itself in a footrace.
Hey, Chuck, we're putting together a team.
And I think we're on it!
Come on, everybody.
Let's work those booties!
I'm in.
Ha-ha! Great!
But how did you...?
BT-dubs, you misspelled "heist."
It's "EI," not "IE." I corrected it.
Don't worry. It's a common misperception.
Well, thank you.
Ha-ha-ha.
You're right. He's fast.
Now, this guy is kind of a ding-dong,
but he's the only eagle we know.
Well, you've come to the right eagle.
Tell me more.
It's a really exciting mission to a place called Eagle...
Eagle Island?!
Yes.
So you've heard...
Heard of it.
Aah!
Nice to meet you!
Okay, so now we just need to figure out
how this volcanic super-weapon works, huh?
We're gonna need some kind of
engineering wizard, brainiac.
Hmm.
Ooh, ooh, ooh.
♪ Ooh ♪
Yes, Chuck. You obviously have something
you want to say or sing.
I have got just the guy. It's a girl.
My sister Silver.
She goes to Avian Academy, top of her class.
She would be perfect.
Yeah, she totally would.
See you guys back at the dorm!
Yeah, see you, Ella.
Hey, good catch!
I mean, we all just thought
she was weird, you know?
But she skipped four grades,
won a Junior Engineer of the Year Award,
and then got a scholarship at Avian Academy.
Perfect. That is exactly what we're looking for.
You are absolutely gonna love her.
But don't love her too much.
That's my sister, Red.
Or I'll crush every bone in your body!
Ooh. Frisbee!
Hi, I'm Chuck.
Know where the engineering department is?
With a combination of over 30 silk, wire
and cotton-based threads spun together,
I now present to you...
Super String!
Ahem. I said, "It's Super String!"
More like "Stupid String."
I know what you're thinking, Mike.
You're like, "What's so super about it?"
Great question, Mike.
Well, how about that it's very easily able
to withstand the pull of 18,000 more kilos
than any other string known to...
Snooze alert.
Known to bird-kind!
Or pig-kind, for that matter.
What's up, sis?
Chuck?
I'm so happy to... It's really...
great to... Jinx, jinx.
Jinx!
Jinx. One, two, three. I win!
You can't speak until someone says your name.
Hello? You in here?
Hello?
You?
You.
Wait. You know this guy?
I would answer, but you jinxed me.
Oh, okay, Chuck, I unjinx you.
This is one of
my best buddies, Red. These are the guys.
Hi.
We're the guys.
Guys, this is Silver,
the greatest kid sister in the world.
I'm not exactly a kid anymore, Chuck.
Oh, you'll always be my kid sister!
Okay. Hey, everyone.
You know, I don't think this is gonna work.
It's just that I'm not sure
you're gonna be compatible with the team.
Oh, wow, it is such a pleasure
to meet not you, but you!
I've never met a pig before.
Your technological achievements are amazing.
May I shake your hoof?
Why, thank you. Heh-heh.
I like her.
And this has to be Bomb.
Whoa!
How'd you know that?
Because you have a fuse coming out of your head.
Oh, so cool!
Ssst. Shaboom!
Oh! Backflip.
So I hear you're some kind of
engineering wizard or whatever.
Oh, heh. I don't like to brag, but...
Wait. Who's that? And why is she
all over these achievement awards?
The kid's amazing, right?
Not a kid anymore, Chuck.
Toot, toot! Tickle Train arriving at Sister Station!
Chuck, no.
I am a serious academic.
I am a serious... Ha-ha-ha!
Stop!
Look how cute this is.
♪ We're sailing in the ocean, we must ♪
♪ Row! Row! ♪
♪ The eggs are in our sights and we must ♪
♪ Go! Go! ♪
♪ We'll get them back before our parents ♪
♪ Know! Know! ♪
♪ And save the day like Red, the real ♪
♪ Hero! Row! ♪
Gotcha!
Woo-hoo!
We did it.
That was so easy!
Yeah!
A little too easy, actually.
What do you mean by that?
Well, normally, when things are this easy,
some dramatically unexpected setback occurs.
I don't get it.
Me neither.
Well, it's kind of hard to explain.
But it's sort of like, you know how some...?
Oh, see? Like that.
Are you freaking kidding me?
Each of you has been selected
because you're the best in your field.
Oh!
That we could find.
Oh.
Your skills will be put to the test
facing this.
As you can clearly see, this is a vol...
Volcano. Heh.
"A volcano" is
what my assistant was going to say.
Assistant? You're the assistant!
Let go. Let go.
No, I'm the leader.
I'll take that.
Actually, it's a composite volcano.
You can tell by the height
and the clearly apparent vent clusters.
Okay, forget I said "volcano."
This is a, um... It's a super-weapon!
Weird because it looks just like a volcano.
Yep, and here's the scary part.
This is their psychotic leader!
Oop! Heh. How'd that get in there? Next.
Oh, butt shot.
Next.
No, no. Next. Next!
I don't even know what I'm looking at.
Courtney!
I mean, you took them.
Ahem. Ahem!
This is their psychotic leader.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hey. Buddy, do you know her?
What? Me? No.
No, definitely not, absolutely not.
Never seen her before in my life.
Who is that? I don't know!
Not terribly convincing, but moving on.
Great.
What's the plan?
All right, here's what we're looking at,
folks.
Step one: Travel undetected to Eagle Island.
Uh-huh.
Step two:
We're gonna break into the super-weapon.
Got it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And step three:
Hoo-hoo!
Deactivate the super-weapon.
Once we break in there.
No plan...
Hopefully, before both our islands are destroyed
and we all die, so that's, uh... That's it.
Right. I just have a few questions.
Why? I explained everything.
It's a foolproof plan.
Yeah. How do we sneak onto the island?
What is the super-weapon
and how do we deactivate it?
And when you say "escape," how do you plan to do that?
I feel like this is a crucial thing to figure out.
I agree. Why isn't she in charge?
Told you she's super smart.
Hey, guys, hold on a second, please.
Mighty Eagle?
What? What? What are you looking at?
Do you have an Eagle Island map?
What? No. No, there's no map.
Oh, it's a map.
Yeah, that's a map.
Mm-hm.
Okay, I just wanna read it.
Come on!
Wait a minute. Do you guys hear that?
Do we hear what?
Sounds like a whistle.
It almost sounds like a:
Hey, guys?
Run!
Emergency exit, all the way down!
Well, that's not safe.
Wait! Stop!
Holy macaroni!
Oh, boy.
Everyone hop on!
Rewind it. Rewind it. Play it again.
Play it again. Play it again.
Yes, baby! We knocked the top right off of that!
Blow them up!
Glenn, you didn't mess it up this time.
Boom! Up top. Or not.
Nailed it!
Jerry, up top.
That should send him running.
Wait. "Him"?
Who you sending running?
Yeah. Who's "him"?
"Them." I said "them."
Stop asking me stupid questions.
I'm so sorry.
That was crazy.
We could have died.
Thanks for saving our lives, Mighty Eagle!
Well, you can always count on...
Everyone grab the map!
Hey, it's working.
Left! Left! Lean to the left!
Whew.
Please tell me that was your pants ripping.
I don't wear pants!
None of us wear pants!
Uh-oh.
Eight point one seconds.
Silver! No!
Oh!
Uh, heh...
Heh-heh...
Hey! What is this?
Oh, um, well, I mean, she was, you know,
just thanking me for saving everyone, so...
I'm sorry. Saving everyone?
Yeah. I mean, you know, the map was my idea.
It ripped.
Maybe because there's one too many birds on the team.
I...
My mountain!
We are in trouble.
We gotta stop that super-weapon.
We gotta stop that super-weapon. Jinx!
Oh, this is bad. This is really bad.
Eagle Mountain?
Are we gonna be okay?
Oh, my gah...
What happened to Eagle Mountain, Mom?
Wait a minute. Wait. Wait. Wait.
Why isn't anybody leaving? Why they not scared?
Okay. Oh, okay, okay.
Here's what we gonna do.
I want y'all to take all of those ice balls
and fill them up with, ha-ha...
molten lava.
That's not possible.
What?
You never heard of thermal emulsifiers?
Uh... Well, yes, yes.
You just got to get a polyacrylamide
to enhance the nanoparticle
and surfactant association
between the two materials.
Okay.
So you do that,
and I'm gonna go feed my baby.
Yes, I'm finally gonna feed my baby.
There you go. Who's my baby?
You're my baby.
What...? Don't...
You better not wink at me.
Don't you wink at me.
Who could have done this?
Gosh, I can't believe it's gone.
Red, are we gonna be okay?
What are we gonna do?
All right, guys, do not worry.
We got this.
Red here has got your back.
And your front and your sides.
And my floof?
Yeah, even your cute little floof.
Looks like you're gonna be okay.
So are you 100 percent sure
we shouldn't evacuate?
No, Red's gonna take care of us.
Right, Red?
Yes! Everybody, please, just stay calm.
Great news! Thank you!
Hey, y'all, we're gonna be okay. Red's here.
We love you, Red!
We need you, Red!
Oh, thank you.
Your support means the world to me.
Okay, Leonard, so where's our ride?
Aww.
It's so cute.
Wow. Okay. And how are we all supposed
to fit in...?
Oh, I think we'll manage. Boop.
Whoa, okay.
Whoa.
Oh, my gah...
All aboard!
Anyone want to grab their own bag
or anything?
Don't screw this up, Red!
If we die, it's kind of your fault.
Hoo. I got this.
Wow.
Ba-Ba-Ba-Ba-bap!
Ow!
Ladies and gentlemen,
I'd like to introduce you
to our master of gadgetry:
Garry!
This is it?
This is the amazing team
I've been working around the clock for?
Heh. Working with what we got.
Well, that's disappointing.
Wow. Okay.
This is the part where you get up
and follow me!
Welcome to my piggy gadget lab.
Oh, yeah.
Everywhere you look, you'll see inventions
being tested by my team of guinea pigs.
This is so cool.
I know. Right?
All of the gadgets have been designed specifically
with your current mission in mind.
The first being Invisa-Spray.
Need to go undetected in plain sight?
Invisa-Spray does exactly that.
Wow, I'm invisible!
Whoa!
"Whoa," indeed.
That's amazing.
How long does the invisibility last for?
Forever.
Wait. What?
Tina, we're not gonna be able
to see each other tonight.
And what does the next gadget do?
Bury us alive?
What? That would be ridiculous.
Ix-nay the shovel-ay.
And moving right along.
What? What are you guys doing?
This is so fun!
Oh, it's so squishy.
What is this stuff?
Well, that is a special type of
flame retardant we call pig snot.
Why do you call it...?
You know what? Never mind.
Uhh. Yuck.
Uh...
Yeah! Lick it.
Now, everyone, prepare yourselves
because this next one is really something special.
Whoa. So shiny.
Yes, my friend. Bold yet sleek.
Simple while complex.
This device can detect an eagle anywhere
within a 100-foot radius.
Well, how does it work?
Simply push this button,
and it does the rest.
Whoa.
Ooh!
Oh-ho-ho!
There's an eagle nearby.
Uh...
Why, yes. Clearly, there is.
Okay, you got me, guys.
There's an eagle nearby.
This clever little thing will...
no doubt prove to be a...
There's an eagle nearby.
crucial tool during your mission.
Wonderful. That's amazing!
There's an eagle nearby.
Can you turn it off now?
Actually, it'll turn itself off.
There's an eagle nearby.
Oh, thank goodness.
One hour after it doesn't detect
any more eagles.
What?!
There's an eagle nearby.
Hey! Hey!
There's an eagle near...
There.
Oh, thank you.
Okay, guys, these gadgets are Terri...
Hey, hey, Red, can we chat for a sec?
I can tell you're used to running the show.
That's great and all.
But maybe since we're all a team here,
a team you put together,
maybe you can try to be more supportive.
The results might surprise you, huh?
Fine. Fine, fine, fine.
Garry. Whoo! Unbelievable.
Really, really good stuff.
You know what?
I'm sure I can figure out a plan to...
You know, to use all this...
This awesomeness that you've, um... Bomb!
Hi, Red.
Oh... How are we ever gonna get up there?
I want my unborn sisters back.
It's just, the eggs are up there,
and we're down here.
Oh, how are we ever gonna get up there?
Aww.
You're doing great, Zoe.
Now hold it tight, okay?
Uh-oh.
Quick, let some air out!
It won't untie!
Okay, let me try.
Aah!
What's...? What's the prob...?
Problem?!
♪ Ground Control to Major Tom ♪
♪ Take your protein pills
And put your... ♪
Don't worry, guys. I'll get us out of this.
The eggs!
We got you for reals now.
See? I told you I would get us out of this.
A boa constructor.
It is glorious! I'm a genius!
Yes, I love it! This was my idea.
Wait. Wait.
Look out!
Aah! I'm burning!
I told you to look out.
Glenn, I wanted lava balls,
not lava puddles.
Uh-oh. Glenn's messing up.
I mean, we... We're very close.
We just need two more weeks.
Two weeks? Two weeks.
Huh.
Um...
It's quite the undertaking.
Okay, okay, you know what?
I'm doing that thing again.
That thing, you know, like, where I'm not quite sure
I heard what I think I heard.
Hey, skinny, sassy face! Did you hear
"two weeks," or did you hear "tomorrow"?
Um... Uh...
I heard "tomorrow"?
Fat dude, what did you hear?
Uh...
Definitely what you said?
Okay, you know what I'm gonna do?
I am gonna call my old engineer, Steve.
And you know what? You're a lot like him.
Hey, it's Steve!
Sorry I can't come to the phone right now,
but you know what to do.
Oh, yeah. I had to discipline Steve.
So, what was that that you had said to me?
Tomorrow.
That's what I thought you said.
See, everybody happy now.
♪ Turn down for what ♪
No. No, no, no. Oh.
Ha-ha! Uh-oh. Whoa. Whoa.
Careful, buddy. That's not...
Whoa.
Okay, guys, let's do this.
Here we go.
We got an island to save, kids.
Two islands. We have two islands to save.
I can't do this.
I've made a terrible mistake.
What are you talking about?
Zeta.
Who is Zeta?
The leader of the eagles.
The one who's been trying
to destroy our islands.
And my ex-fiancée.
Wait. What?!
Did you say "fiancée"?
Beyoncé?
And you're just telling us this now?
Better late than never. Heh-heh.
It was many years ago,
in the 1990s.
She was the smartest girl in school.
And I had an incredible sense of fashion.
Whoa.
Hey.
It was love at first sight.
Whoo!
Ha-ha-ha.
♪ I don't wanna wait ♪
"I miss you"? Aww.
Whoa.
Whoa!
She was the best thing that
ever happened to me.
♪ Will it be yes
or will it be sorry ♪
But since I wasn't quite ready
to mate for life...
Oh. Wow. Uh...
An engagement ring?
Um...
Naturally, I, uh...
I...
I abandoned her.
How could you leave her like that?
Because I am a coward.
Many of you didn't know that about me.
Well, actually...
I assume she's been heartbroken ever since.
It's all my fault.
So this is Beyoncé we're talking about?
You know what? I just remembered.
I have something to do back home!
Thanks for the help.
Well, that got dark.
Okay, gang, listen up.
This place is crawling with security,
but if you guys follow me...
Hey, hey, hey, what's going on?
What do you think, guys? Should we show him?
Show me what?
Harvey!
Super lifelike disguise, right?
Disguise?
We thought we'd let you drive.
And I'm gonna help you pedal.
Wait. You guys came up with
this idea without me?
Yeah.
♪ All by myself ♪
♪ Don't wanna be all by my... ♪
Yeah, well, it's not gonna work.
We think it's our best chance of getting past
the guards to the super-weapon.
I'm with Silver.
Me too.
Yeah, she's smart.
Everyone is counting on me to make sure that...
Us. Everyone's counting on us, Red.
Fine. Whatever. So your plan is to get
into the super-weapon with that?
Harvey, don't take offense.
He does not mean it.
Ugh... Fine. Fine.
You know what?
I'll just be up here saving the world.
Just like I should have been doing this whole time.
Guys?
I 100 percent believe in you
and this Harvey idea,
but I think this one's gonna need me.
Well, they didn't see us.
This isn't an "us" thing, Silver.
I've got this covered. Go away.
Is this a good time to talk about your feelings?
No, it's not a good time!
No. No, I don't need your help, okay?
I meant to slip. Leave me alone!
Your hat fell off.
Yeah, I got rid of it
because it was getting heavy.
All right, guys, beak action is a go.
Arms, what say you?
Armed and ready.
Two fully functional armies.
Right above our leggies.
Okay, leggies, show me what you got.
Oh, yeah.
Woo-hoo! We got this!
We must look amazing!
Okay, guys, we're going live.
Come on, Jerry.
You know there's no snacking
while we're on duty.
But I had a really small breakfast.
All right, I'll do the talking. Ahem.
Hello, fellow eagle guards.
Hm?
Oh, no. He's doing a voice.
I'm running late to the old job.
Commute was rough today for some reason.
But the good news is I made it!
Ninety-degree turn. Quick!
But the good news is I made it.
ID, please.
Oh, uh... ID?
Ha. Not sure I have it on me.
Act like you're checking your pockets.
It's stuck!
Stuck? Aah! What the heck are you doing?!
Guards, be on the alert
for a possible intruder.
Wait a minute.
What's happening? Leonard?
Shh. He's on to us.
Hmm.
We are so dead.
All right. I know what's going on here.
I'm picking up what you're putting down.
Jerry, are you getting a load of this?
Yeah, I think I am.
Yeah, Jerry, I know exactly what's going on.
This right here...
is obviously...
a new guy!
Yeah, impostors in a costume. Wait. What?
Oh.
Uh?
Huh?
Yeah! You're the new guard
for the east tower.
Yes.
Yes, I am.
Ha-ha-ha. I knew it.
Jerry, swipe the new guy in.
Okay.
Thank you so much.
Okay, guys, we're in.
Oh, yeah.
Woo-hoo!
We did it.
Work it. Work it.
Okay, okay.
Wiggle the butt.
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Uh-huh.
Huh?
♪ I'm on fire ♪
Come on, come on. Let's go. Let's go!
♪ Baby, baby, baby ♪
Get to the top of the super-weapon. Check!
Oh...
Yay! You did it.
Okay, so how's it looking down there?
Ooh. Do you see that?
Oh, it's the super-weapon.
No, the power supply to the super-weapon.
All we gotta do is get down there
and cut it.
Okay, assuming we don't get electrocuted,
there are guards there, there and there.
And we don't have enough rope to...
Watch and learn.
What? What are you doing?
He's not clipped in.
Red, are you crazy?
Trust me. I know what I'm do...
So yeah. Rope wasn't long enough.
I know that.
It wasn't supposed to be.
That's part of my plan.
Except I wanted to be over on that side.
Okay, but...
Watch this! Aah!
Nope. No, no, no.
Oh. Hello.
Hi. Now my plan really starts.
Hi again.
I swung back over to tell you something,
but I forgot what it was. Okay, bye.
Got it. Got it. Okay, there we go.
There we go. Grip, grip, grip. Okay...
Huh?
You hear something?
So you want a push?
Yes.
Hi.
Oh, no. Your feather!
The guards!
Watch out.
Silver, what are you doing?
Oh, no.
Where's Red?
Hey, Silver.
Check it out.
This is how a hero saves the world.
Ha-ha!
Oh, come on! Nothing works around here!
Now we escape.
You two are coming with me.
I, uh...
Nice abs.
I know.
Okay, try zero-zero-zero-zero.
Okay, now try one-two-three-four.
Now try four-three-two-one.
Try 1-800-OPEN.
Aah! I don't know.
Chuck, what's your birthday?
Nothing's working!
Oh, no. Someone's coming.
Quick. Hide.
Ouch.
There's an eagle nearby.
There's an eagle nearby. There's an eagle near...
Shh, shh, shh.
You get started on the lockdown sequence.
I'm gonna hit the john.
Yes, sir.
We gotta get that key card.
Okay, Courtney, get that card.
There's something in the way.
Chuck, what's going on down there?
There's a divider in the way.
Maybe it's on the other side.
Okay, hold on.
Pretend to pee-pee.
Oh, no. He's leaving.
Chuck, get that card.
I got it.
Yeah, I'm just gonna...
Boop!
We're home!
We're home, everybody.
Oh, we missed you so much, Bird Island.
"Bird Island"?
This is Piggy Island, sillies.
Bird Island is way over there.
We're in!
Oh, my goodness gravy.
I want to see.
Chuck, hold on!
We don't have time for this.
You're stepping on my face.
Uh-oh.
What? What's happening?
I think he's challenging us
to a break-dance battle?
Oh, it's on!
What's happening?
Looks like a little popping and locking.
A little what?
Pop, pop, pop!
Hey, handsome.
Hey.
Take those two and put them on ice.
They've got Red and my sister. We've gotta go.
But the super-weapon.
That's my sister, mister.
And I'm gonna save her.
Chuck, slow down.
Slow down. Stop!
Oh, yeah!
Hmm?
Huh?
Hey.
Hey. You done?
What happened?
Oh, let's see.
You got us captured and trapped in ice
on top of giant pool toys.
Good job.
I just thought that maybe if I could...
Stop me?
Yeah, you two lovebirds just thought
y'all could sail over here and stop me.
Lovebirds? No way.
Whoa. No, no, no.
I mean, we're barely, like, friend birds.
So typical.
Type-A male paired with a strong female,
and you just can't stand it, can you?
Well, I...
Let me guess. You prefer to fly solo.
I have to save everybody
all by myself!
Just like a man.
Ooh. Ouch. That is kind of true though.
Maybe she was a little clingy at times.
Maybe she gave you that engagement ring
a little bit too early.
I don't think she's talking about us.
Maybe she's talking about Mighty Eagle.
Debbie! Turn on the TV.
Yes.
Okay...
It's the one with the red button on top.
Red, Debbie.
What I'm planning to do is take
these little-bitty, undeveloped islands
and turn them into my own personal paradise.
You're insane!
I am putting myself first.
Because you know what?
I worked hard for it, and I deserve it.
All I gotta do is clear out
all these inhabitants.
You're a monster!
Ha-ha-ha!
Glenn, show them what I'm talking about.
Uh-huh.
Excuse me? Are you getting smart
with me right now?
I can't believe we're soaring
through the sky! Sky!
All thanks to our pig pals,
they are cool guys!
Guys!
No!
What the heck was that?
Piggy Island?!
Attention, everyone! It is imperative that
you all run for your lives!
Bird Island?!
My mommy and daddy.
Huh?
Terence? Where are the kids?
Hmm?
Where are the kids?!
I don't understand.
I thought Red was supposed to save us!
Oh, my gah...
Huh. Oh, my gah.
Oh! Ha-ha-ha.
It actually worked.
Yes, yes, yes!
Those islands are filled
with innocent birds and pigs!
You all had the chance to evacuate.
But for some reason, you didn't.
So you are 100 percent sure
we shouldn't evacuate?
I am sure. No one needs to evacuate.
Everybody just stay calm.
Sorry. Ha-ha-ha.
Not sorry. I'm truly not sorry.
Whoo! Dodged that bullet.
Ha-ha!
This is all my fault.
Red, it's not your fault.
No. It... It is my fault.
I put myself before everyone else.
I was afraid if I wasn't a hero anymore,
they'd all stop...
They'd all stop liking me.
Oh, Red. So you did all of this
because you were afraid of not being liked?
I...
Yes.
My fellow eagles,
who's tired of living in an icy wasteland?
We are!
What is she doing?
Who is tired of sipping hot chocolate
and getting brain freeze?
Aah! Me!
Who's tired of frozen dinners?
Whoa, frozen dinners?
Come on, Bomb, let's go.
Who's tired of playing only Vanilla Ice,
Ice-T and Ice Cube?
I am.
Who wants to live worry-free under
a beautiful tropical sun?
Me! I want to be hot!
I want it hot!
There's no turning back!
The future we deserve is about to be ours!
Glenn! Activate the weapon!
Start the countdown.
Ten minutes to launch.
All right, stand back.
Wait, did you hear that too?
Bomb?
What in the...?
Really, guys?
What? No. We weren't...
Uh, yeah, they were.
Guys, why is that clock counting backwards?
We've only got 10 minutes.
It's now or never.
Pig-kind and bird-kind are depending on us.
What are we gonna do, Red?
Well, I, uh...
I think...
in times like these,
we need someone who can lead.
We need a hero.
You know what we need? We need Silver.
Huh?
Oh.
Got any ideas?
I've got a few, actually.
Okay.
That's the heart of the super-weapon,
and if you look closely, you can see that
it's powered by air pressure.
Moisture around a composite volcano
instantly vaporizes,
sending a plume of highly pressurized steam
to the surface.
That steam is contained
by the pressure chamber.
And that's the part we need to destroy.
Only problem is,
it's surrounded by armed guards.
Bomb. Do you think you can take out those guards?
Huh?
Some of them look kind of tough.
It won't be easy.
Yeah, right. Of course. Got it.
Great. Chuck, I need you to disable
the security cameras.
There's a bunch of them, so you'll have to work fast.
Fast?
Don't even worry about it, sis.
Red, you and I have to get inside one
of those ice balls.
Inside an ice ball?
I... Sure. Okay.
Leonard, Courtney, Garry, do you see
that giant lever near the orange lava tube?
Copy that.
I need you to pull it all the way down.
That will create a ramp so that
when Red and I roll down in the ice ball,
we'll be launched through the air
at the perfect trajectory to take out the super-weapon.
Got it?
Now you're talking.
Great plan, Silver.
Great.
Mama would be so proud.
Okay, everyone put your wings and hooves in.
Go, team!
Chuck, let us know
when you've disabled the cameras.
Okay. On it.
Easy, boys.
Huh.
Huh? Hey, Jerry.
Yeah?
Come here. Look at this.
What's up?
Uh, it says everything's normal.
Jerry, are you seeing this?
Uh, I don't see anything.
No, not that one.
Not over here.
Oh, I think this one's it.
♪ Hello ♪
♪ Is it me you're looking for? ♪
♪ I can see it in your eyes ♪
I'll be here when you get out.
Same.
♪ You're all I ever wanted ♪
We just need to get over to that track
and follow it up to the lever.
Okay.
Phew.
Ow! Don't touch the lava tube.
I don't know if I'm gonna fit.
Just suck in your butt.
Whoa, whoa! Whoa, whoa!
Does anyone smell bacon?
Ow.
No one can see me. Light on my toes.
♪ I'm sneaking
I'm sneaking up real quiet ♪
♪ Who took you out?
I don't know ♪
♪ Because I didn't hear them coming
Because they snuck up on me ♪
Captain, you seeing this?
No one sees me.
Take them out.
So why didn't you just team up with Chuck?
He's definitely faster than me.
Nope, he's too light.
Why not Bomb, then?
You know, he's heavier than me.
Too slow. You're perfect.
Oh, that's funny.
I thought we weren't compatible.
Yeah. Um, well, you know...
Some of the variables changed, so...
Oh, variables, huh?
So, what are we doing here?
We're on a mission.
Oh, yeah, the mission. Of course.
Okay, Bomb, we are in position.
Time to take out those guards.
Copy that.
Come on, Bomb, hold it together.
Tighten up. You can do this.
We got a 10-91G in the control room.
Roger that.
Oh!
You can do this, Bomb.
Just take them out. Just take them out!
Thanks for taking us out, man.
Even Glenn's having a good time!
♪ Baby shark, doo, doo, doo, doo, doo, doo ♪
♪ Baby shark ♪
All together!
Silver, baby sharks have taken the bait.
Roger that. Okay, Leonard. Time for Plan X.
Plan X? I thought you said spandex.
Spandex?
♪ I'm too sexy for my shirt ♪
♪ Too sexy for my shirt ♪
Well, I'm working with what I got.
Looking good, guys.
Looking good.
You gotta swing your arms.
I am swinging my arms.
I'm swinging them like this.
Yes!
Three minutes to launch.
Debbie, we are starting over, girl.
This is like New Year's.
Oh, my gosh, yes, okay.
I'm gonna get some glitter and decorations.
This is gonna be so much fun!
Zeta!
We have a problem.
Oh, my good... Aah!
Go find them!
Okay. That's where the ice balls are made.
We've gotta jump in that hole
at the exact moment that the jaws open up.
Are you sure about this?
Uh, actually, no.
Going with my gut this time.
Whoa. Didn't expect that.
Attention, all eagles.
The prisoners have escaped.
♪ Doo-doo, doo-doo ♪
♪ Daddy shark ♪
All right, guys, back to work!
Go! Let's do this!
Guys, guys, guys! Hold on!
We're not done hanging out
and having a good time.
Silver, we've got a problem.
♪ Back to work, doo, doo, doo, doo, doo, doo
Back to work ♪
We'll jump on the count of three.
Got it.
One, two...
three!
Whoa!
Ha-ha! It worked! Red?
Ha-ha!
We did it!
Oh, no. What the...?
Lava injectors!
I got this one.
Oh, whoa, Red!
Well, it's all downhill from here.
Okay, now what?
If my calculations are correct,
we should be tall enough to reach that lever
if all three of us...
Garry?
Uh, hang in there!
Whoa.
Okay, new plan.
We need to get to 65 miles per hour.
Left, right, left, right.
At least we're gonna get all our steps in today.
Two minutes to launch.
Two minutes, everybody!
Two minutes to launch!
Left, right, left, right.
We gotta break that super-weapon!
Leonard.
Yeah?
Is the ramp elevated?
We're working on it.
Ow!
What are we gonna do?
Uh... I have an idea.
Okay, let's just figure this out.
Yeah, yeah. Now is not the time, Courtney.
I'm just trying to figure out
how we're gonna get up to that lever.
Hey. Leonard.
Huh?
Oh, that could work!
Silver! How we doing on speed?
We're maxing out at 59 miles per hour.
We need to get to 65!
It's stuck! We need more weight!
Okay. Here goes.
It... It's moving!
Oh, that's not good.
Sixty-three, 64...
One more minute!
Yes!
One minute.
Let's just clear these houses from your beachfront view.
Silver, the lever is broken!
Broken?
Leonard, don't you have any gadgets you can use?
We're almost to the ramp.
Gadgets? Gadgets!
Forty-five seconds.
Attention, all personnel.
Initiating launch sequence.
Initiating.
Garry, any way you can bring me the gadgets?
No, there isn't.
Chuck, I need Garry's backpack.
On it.
Garry, where are you?!
Chuck, over here!
Yes! We've reached 65 miles per hour!
Fifteen seconds.
Fifteen, 14...
Ha-ha! Let's do this!
13, 12...
11...
Ten. Nine.
Leonard, it's now or never.
Oh, no.
Got to raise that ramp!
Seven. Six.
Five.
Four. Three.
Boom!
Two.
And one!
There's an eagle nearby.
No!
Huh?
That's my sister!
Oh.
It didn't work?
I... I don't get it.
Of course it didn't work.
You must really love your little islands,
to risk your lives trying to save them!
Ha-ha-ha. Well, guess what.
I don't care.
Because this right here is ice-cold, baby.
No!
Zeta!
What?
Wait!
What? What...?
Mighty Eagle!
Yeah!
I'm the cause of all this.
I ran out on you on our wedding day.
And ever since then,
you've been tormented inside.
Right now?
This is when you choose to do this?
So take me!
Not these islands.
You have got some flipping nerve!
I know!
I ripped your heartstrings right out.
That's it. Super String.
What?
has been burning a hole in your sanity!
Set yourself free...
Okay, I'm seeing it.
Yeah.
Go ahead. Do your worst to me.
Chuck.
I deserve it.
Ugh.
Aah!
You think this is about you, Ethan?
Ethan?
Oh, that is so hilarious
slash embarrassing
slash I hadn't thought
about your fat butt in 20 years.
Wait, what?
You are a lazy,
uncoordinated, fish-eyed fool.
You ain't worth the salt in your bread.
You are nothing to me! You are nothing!
I don't think about you at all.
I don't think about your stinking feet.
I don't think about your rusty hands.
I don't think about your rusty elbows...
Wait, so you have
or you haven't thought about me?
News flash, bro:
I am over you, I'm over this place,
and I am ready to get that upgrade situation
going for me and my daughter.
Hey.
Well, our daughter.
What?
That's my dad?
I have a daughter?
Yes, you do!
And I raised her all by myself
in this icy wasteland.
But now I'm gonna be sipping piña coladas
on those warm tropical islands
like I deserve to!
Stop!
Oh, no.
Huh?
Hey, it's working!
Yes!
Oh, no.
Gotcha!
You can do it!
Hold on to that string!
The hatchlings.
Oh, no! They're in trouble!
Jump!
Everyone, run!
Run!
Let's go!
No, no, wait. This is not happening.
Gotcha!
I'm freaking out!
Me too!
We did it.
Debbie?
Where is she? Where's Debbie?
Debbie, no.
What have I done?
Oh, Debbie.
Are you okay?
Sweetie?
Honey pie?
Love of the last one minute of my life?
Dad?
Yes.
You are so strong!
He saved my life!
Oh, Debbie.
Mom, can we keep him?
Please?
Oh, I, uh...
Mm.
Wait. Wait.
Before you answer, you should see something.
Uh...
Wait, wait, wait.
Mm-hm.
And the one closest to my heart.
♪ I don't want to wait ♪
♪ For our lives to be over ♪
♪ Will it be yes or will it be ♪
♪ Sorry? ♪
Oh, no.
You are so pitiful.
♪ Yeah ♪
I've never been to a wedding before!
Oh, okay, who's getting married again?
Oh, Terence, this is like our wedding
but expensive.
Flowers for you, flowers for you.
Flowers for you.
Ladies and gentlemen, birds and pigs,
we are gathered here today
because of these two characters.
Not only because they're being joined
in holy matrimony,
but also because one of them tried to destroy
our islands for her own selfish reasons.
Guess who.
Oh, it's such a beautiful wedding.
It really is.
But Mighty Eagle swooped
in at the last second
and got all the credit for stopping her.
Yes, you did, baby.
I love you.
Wrap it up.
I now pronounce you eagle and husband.
You may now kiss the...
Come here, you.
Ugh.
All right. Get it, Mighty Eagle.
Oh, that is disgusting!
Go, Zeta! Go, Dad!
Attention!
Attention, everybody. Eyes on me. Hi.
Hi. Look up here.
I would like to propose a toast
to the bird who made all of this possible.
Our hero, Red.
Give it up for Red!
Yeah!
Red! Red! Red!
You're our hero, Red!
Oh! Uh, easy, guys. Hollow bones.
I've got hollow bones.
Who loves you, Red?
Yeah, Red!
Uh, wow. I mean, thanks, guys.
I... Thank you.
Speech, speech, speech!
Looks like they still love you, Red.
Uh, oh...
Okay, well, you know, I'm, um...
I'm honored, everybody.
Really, I... And I just, um...
Uh, two seconds. Give me two seconds. I'll be right back.
Whoo!
Good speech! Yeah!
Excuse me. Excuse me. Pardon me.
Excuse me. I'm just trying to squeeze through here.
Oh! Hey, hey, hey! Silver!
Huh?
Wow, I, um... Thank you, guys.
Thank you for this.
And for all the support and love.
You know, it means, um...
Well, it means everything to me.
But, um, I don't deserve it.
She does.
What just happened?
Is that the nerd from our physics class?
This is the real hero right here.
Silver is the one who came up
with the plan to stop the super-weapon
and ultimately saved all our lives.
Red, I didn't do this all on my own.
Right. Because we're a team.
We couldn't have done anything
without Chuck and Bomb,
or Courtney and Garry.
Thank you.
Or Leonard.
Actually, we probably could've done it without Leonard.
Let's be honest, huh?
Leonard's the man! I did everything!
I got the sub!
And even Mighty Eagle.
So handsome.
Ethan!
And last, but certainly not least,
those adorable hatchlings.
We are strongest when we all band together.
Just like Super String.
Let's hear it for Silver!
Yes!
I want to be an engineer.
All right! Yeah, Silver!
We love you, Silver!
Okay, Garry, now.
On it.
Oh, my gosh!
We're famous!
Wow. Look at that.
Oh, look! It's me!
You see, these guys are the real heroes.
They're the ones who deserve your love,
not me.
We love you even more now, Red!
Yeah, Red! We love you!
See? You're not in this alone.
I'm married now.
Let's party, y'all! I's married!
Ha-ha-ha. Woo-hoo!
Debbie, get away from the punch bowl, girl!
Come over here and dance with your mama!
♪ Me and you ♪
Hey, y'all!
Mom, watch this!
Oh, yeah! Hey, where's Red and Silver?
♪ It had to be ♪
♪ The only one for me is you ♪
Okay, worms or birdseed?
Huh?
Kidding. I know it's toast.
Ha-ha.
Toast.
I was actually being sarcastic
when I said that was my favorite food,
just for the record.
What? You?
Sarcastic?
Oh.
No way.
I see what you're doing.
Okay.
Maybe you can teach me sometime.
Maybe I will, when you're not
too busy saving the world.
Oh. You know, I actually just finished
doing that, so I'm pretty free.
Oh, no way. Because I'm pretty free too.
Well, I don't have anything to do either!
Wait a minute. What's that sound?
Tickle Train?
Coming to Third Wheel Station!
Chuck, no!
Jinx, jinx, jinx!
Laugh it up, everybody. Ha-ha-ha.
No one can stop me.
I'll stop you, Zeta.
Ha-ha-ha!
Well, you can't stop me from...
showing you how cute my little sisters are
when they're sleeping.
Yay!
They're so cute.
I kind of thought they'd be hatched by now.
They're hatching!
Yay!
Here they come!
Oh, my gosh! I see one!
Mama!
Uh-oh.
Can I help you?
Oh.
Sorry.
Mama?
Hi.
Oh! My baby sisters!
Yay!
Bye.
Mama!
Oh, baby sisters.
We love you so much.
We should take good care of them
and never let them out of our sights.
Yeah. We'll never let them out
of our sights. Huh?
Bye-bye.
♪ This is gonna be the best day of your life
Of your life, of your life ♪
♪ Hey, you ♪
♪ This is gonna be the best day of your life
Of your life, of your life ♪
Of your life ♪
♪ Uh, I took a walk this mornin'
The sun was shinin' for me ♪
♪ It got me feelin' like uh, uh, uh, oh-ooh ♪
♪ The sky is lookin' so blue
So I do what I want to ♪
♪ I'm feelin' myself like uh,
uh, uh, oh-ooh ♪
♪ I'm feelin' so nice
I ain't got no negative energy ♪
♪ High fives and good vibes
Wrote this one for all my friends ♪
♪ And enemies ♪
♪ Hey, you ♪
♪ This is gonna be the best day of your life
Of your life, of your life ♪
♪ Go live it up ♪
♪ Hey ♪
♪ Oh, I tell them it's my birthday ♪
♪ Who doesn't want that free cake? ♪
♪ Let's celebrate like uh,
uh, uh, oh-ooh ♪
♪ I'm dancing in my foyer ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm my own employer ♪
♪ Why don't you all come over, yeah? ♪
♪ I'm feelin' so nice
I ain't got no negative energy ♪
♪ High fives and good vibes
Wrote this one for all my friends ♪
♪ And enemies ♪
♪ Hey, you ♪
♪ This is gonna be the best day of your life
Of your life, of your life ♪
♪ Go live it up ♪
♪ This is gonna be the best day of your life
Of your life, of your life ♪
♪ You're from one side of the tracks
And I live on the other ♪
♪ Why we don't see eye to eye
Really ain't a wonder ♪
♪ But you got the rock
And I got the roll ♪
♪ You got the heart
And I got the soul ♪
♪ So let's just be friends ♪
♪ Ain't gotta fight about it
Let's find a way around it ♪
♪ Let's just be friends ♪
♪ Hey, what do you say? ♪
♪ If we don't even know
What we were fussing about ♪
♪ Don't you think
it's time we work it out? ♪
♪ Let's just be friends ♪
♪ Hey, let's just be friends ♪
♪ Yeah, we're pretty good alone but
I bet that together ♪
♪ We could make some noise
This town would talk about forever ♪
♪ We've been back and forth
Picking sides ♪
♪ When you ain't wrong
And I ain't right ♪
♪ So let's just be friends ♪
♪ Ain't gotta fight about it
Let's find a way around it ♪
♪ Let's just be friends ♪
♪ Hey, what do you say? ♪
♪ If we don't even know
What we were fussing about ♪
♪ Don't you think
it's time we work it out? ♪
♪ Let's just be friends ♪
♪ Hey, let's just be friends ♪
♪ You're big city
and I'm small town ♪
♪ Best of both worlds is
what it sounds like ♪
♪ Let's just be friends ♪
♪ Ain't gotta fight about it
Let's find a way around it ♪
♪ Let's just be friends ♪
♪ Hey, what do you say? ♪
♪ If we don't even know
What we were fussing about ♪
♪ Don't you think
it's time we work it out? ♪
♪ Let's just be friends ♪
♪ Hey, let's just be friends ♪
♪ Oh, let's just be friends ♪