(SOFT EERIE MUSIC PLAYING)
(CREATURES GRUNTING)
(CREATURES GROANING)
(WHOOSHING)
-(GASPS)
-(SOFT BLAST)
-(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
-(JANET BREATHING HEAVILY)
(PANTING)
(WIND BLOWING)
(GROWLS AND CHITTERS)
(CREATURE HISSES)
(JANET GASPS)
(HISSES)
(SNARLS)
(GRUNTS)
(YELPS)
(SNARLS)
(JANET GRUNTS)
(BOTH PANTING)
What is this place?
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC
BUILDING UP)
(WELCOME BACK
BY JOHN SEBASTIAN PLAYING)
(BUS BRAKES HISS)
SCOTT: My life doesn't
really make sense.
-Hey.
-Oh...
SCOTT: I used to ask myself
a lot of questions
-about that.
-(WHISTLING ALONG TO SONG)
"Scott, you're
a divorced ex-con.
"How are you an Avenger?
"Why are you time traveling
with Captain America?
-"That doesn't make sense."
-(WHISTLES)
A lot has changed
about my life.
But everywhere I go,
people ask me the same thing.
Can you take a picture
with my dog?
-"Scott, what about now?"
-(BARKS)
-"What's next?"
-(DOG GRUNTS)
"Where does
the ride take you?"
-(DOG YIPS)
-(CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS)
If I knew that,
it wouldn't be a ride.
SCOTT: All right.
(GASPS)
-It's been a crazy few years.
-Hey, guys.
-Hey, hi. How are you?
-For everyone.
RUBIN: Everything
is ready for you.
You're too much.
RUBIN: No, no, no.
Your money's no good here.
Aw. Are we still talking
about that?
Yes, of course.
Rubin, you are the best.
Thank you, Spider-Man.
SCOTT: So, let's make time for
the stuff that really matters.
Like friends.
Friends you didn't
even know you had.
Remember the people
who got you here.
You couldn't have done it
without them.
Hey, I'm just a guy who
got fired from Baskin-Robbins.
Sometimes you just get lucky.
I'm lucky I met Hope Van Dyne.
I think you know who she is.
She's taken back
her dad's company.
Now she's using
the Pym Particle
for global change.
A lot of people say they want
to save the world,
but Hope,
she saves it every day.
-Thank you.
-(AUDIENCE APPLAUDING)
Thank you so much.
SCOTT: Reforestation.
Affordable housing.
Food production.
-She's not wasting a second.
-(THUDS)
(WELCOME BACK
BY JOHN SEBASTIAN CONTINUES)
SCOTT: I still can't believe it.
None of this
should have happened.
But it did.
It's a pretty good world.
I'm glad we saved it.
"Do I miss the action?
-"Sometimes."
-(SONG CONCLUDES)
"Will I be there
when the Avengers need me?
"Absolutely.
"I'd never turn my back
on them.
"But right now, the only job
I want is being a dad.
"I love you, Cassie.
"Thanks for being my hero.
"And I'm sorry
I missed some birthdays."
(SOFT LAUGHTER)
"And for the rest
of you kids out there,
"word of advice.
"Look out for the little guy.
"Make mistakes.
"Take chances.
"Because if there's one thing
life's taught me,
"there's always room to grow."
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Sorry, that's me.
Why is jail calling?
(CELL GATE BUZZES)
Lang!
-Lang!
-I'm here.
All right, come on. Let's go.
Come on.
Hey. Is she okay?
Have you heard anything?
-Not yet. No. Oh.
-(DOOR CLACKS)
Hi, Hope.
Hey, Dad.
Cassie. What happened?
Sign here.
Oh, you know, just jail stuff.
Give it back.
-Hmm?
-I know it was you.
Are you sure?
I mean, it was
kind of hard to see
through all that tear gas
you fired into the park
full of peaceful protestors.
Where is it?
I'm sorry. This must be
really embarrassing for you.
(SIGHS)
Oh! (SIGHS)
I did find this though.
(SIREN WHOOPING)
SCOTT: You shrank a cop car?
What were you thinking?
What was I supposed to do?
Look the other way?
They were clearing out
a homeless camp
-in the middle of the night.
-No, I'm not saying that...
CASSIE: And where do
they expect them to go?
It's not their fault that they
lost their homes in the Blip.
I... I know that.
No one can even
afford rent right now,
unless you're
some trust-fund asshole.
I'm not telling you
what to do.
-I'm just saying...
-Telling her what to do.
Telling me exactly what to do.
No, you do what you want.
(FUMBLES)
I'm suggesting
another way to do it.
Okay.
You know,
I promised your mom
that you would
only use this stuff
when one of us was around.
It's really dangerous tech.
I know it's dangerous.
What if the cops
took it from you? Huh?
What if you lost it?
I didn't lose the suit.
You have a suit?
Wait, you have a suit?
I know how to
take care of myself, okay?
Trust me.
I'm pretty good at it by now.
Ouch.
-I didn't mean it like that.
-I know.
-I'm sorry.
-That's okay. It's all right.
I get it.
I just think you should get
to have a normal life.
Dad, a guy dressed like a bee
tried to kill me in my room
when I was six.
I've never had a normal life.
How about some music?
SCOTT: (ON SPEAKERS)
"And in that moment,
"all I could think was,
"'How did the Hulk
turn me into a baby?
"'Will I be a baby forever?
"'Am I the Hulk's baby?'"
Dad, are you listening
to your own book?
"But I was ready
for anything."
Hmm? No, that's, uh...
It's just the radio.
"Steve and I
grew close over that."
-(LAUGHS) Dad, turn it off.
-SCOTT: It's so weird.
Something's wrong with this
switch. It won't turn off.
I said turn it off.
What's that? Turn it up?
All right.
-(VOLUME INCREASES)
-"A little after that,
"a raccoon from space
showed up.
"I don't think
he knew my name.
"I was just happy to meet
a raccoon who could talk."
-HANK: Mm.
-Excuse me.
-CASSIE: Oh.
-Thank you.
JANET: Mm-hmm.
HANK: Hmm.
All right.
Your Nobel Prize
is in the mail.
It better be.
I just saved eight bucks.
God, I admire you.
Thank you.
I missed this.
No pizza in the Quantum Realm?
(CHUCKLES) No. No anything.
You know, Mom,
you can talk about it.
If you want.
Sweetheart, I spent
30 years down there.
I wanna live right now.
Yep.
So, Cassie, did you make
any new friends
in the slammer this time?
(WHISPERS) Grandpa.
"This time"?
Was there a last time?
I mean,
last time barely counts.
I didn't know that.
Why didn't you call me?
'Cause I knew
you'd be like this.
I would've just broken you out
with ants.
All right, you know what?
Family meeting.
Can we have a family meeting?
Isn't that what we're doing?
Yeah, I mean about this.
About everybody
being so fine with this.
Look, you wanna help.
I get it.
-I do, Cassie. I really do.
-(SIGHS)
But I don't want you
wasting your life.
At least I'm still trying
to do something with mine.
I literally saved the world.
Oh, did you?
Well, yeah, you never
mentioned that before.
Hey, everybody,
Scott saved the world.
How was that for you, Scott?
You should write a book
about it.
Ha ha. Hilarious.
Yeah, you're welcome
for all not being dust.
And what do you do now?
Sign books?
Aren't you the guy
who broke into VistaCorp?
Aren't you the guy who flew
all the way to Germany
just to fight Captain America
at the airport?
Fight with Captain America
at the airport.
Wouldn't fight
Captain America.
Not insane.
People still need help, Dad.
At least we're trying
to do something that matters.
Who's "we"?
Hmm?
What are you three up to?
-(LOW ROUSING MUSIC PLAYS)
-Science.
With ants.
Ant science.
I don't believe you.
Let's just show him.
(ANTS CHITTERING)
SCOTT: Whoa.
What are they building?
Are you doing this?
HANK: Actually, no,
they built their own tech.
Pretty smart ants.
Okay, so when you were all,
like, gone those five years,
I had a lot of time.
And I started reading
Grandpa Hank's old journals,
and I got really into
the Quantum Realm and...
Whoa. The Quantum Realm?
CASSIE: I know we all
have a history there,
and I didn't want
to freak anyone out,
but we've been talking
about it.
She had some questions, okay?
I can't help if people
are inspired by me.
(MACHINE TURNS ON)
So, you've been studying
the Quantum Realm?
Mm-hmm.
Why didn't you
ask me about it?
I tried, Mom.
A lot.
You never wanted
to talk about it.
Cassie's just been curious
and we gave her some pointers.
This isn't exactly
ant science, is it, Henry?
You know how dangerous
the Quantum Realm is.
HOPE: Yeah, we all do, Mom.
Nobody's going
to the Quantum Realm.
That's why we made this.
It's like a satellite
for deep space or the ocean.
-But...
-(MACHINE TURNS ON)
...Quantum.
-(MACHINE WHIRRING)
-We just need a map.
And then we can study
and explore
the entire Quantum Realm.
Never even have to go.
Your daughter built
a subatomic Hubble Telescope
in a basement.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
You know,
if I had something like this
when you were gone...
then I could have found you.
It's amazing.
I'm blown away.
How does it work?
It's kinda like that
two-way radio we used to have.
You send a signal down
from here,
and then it collects the data,
and it sends it back.
Wait. Wait a minute.
You're sending a signal
down to the Quantum Realm?
Yeah.
-Shut it down now.
-Janet...
-HOPE: Why would we shut it...
-What's wrong?
You have to turn it off!
Stop and tell us what's wrong!
(MACHINE TURNS OFF)
Janet?
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
There's something
I should have told...
(MACHINE TURNS ON)
(MACHINE BEEPING SOFTLY)
(ELECTRICITY LOADING)
(ALL SCREAM)
(ALL GRUNTING AND SCREAMING)
(BOTH STRAINING)
(BOTH SCREAM)
-Dad?
-(TRILLING)
(GRUNTS)
JANET: No!
-(SCREAMS) No!
-Mom!
-(SCREAMING)
-HANK: No!
HOPE: Damn it!
(GRUNTS)
-Dad?
-(GRUNTS)
(CASSIE SCREAMS)
(DISTORTED SCREAMING)
(ANTS SCREECHING)
(BOTH GRUNT)
CASSIE: (ECHOING) Dad!
Dad!
(SCOTT GASPING)
(GRUNTING)
(SCOTT PANTING)
Cassie.
(CASSIE PANTING)
(GRUNTS) Dad!
Oh, Dad. Come on. (GRUNTS)
Okay.
Are you okay?
Yeah. I'm okay.
(BOTH PANTING)
(ATMOSPHERIC RUMBLING)
(MYSTERIOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
CASSIE: Where are we?
(HOPE BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GRUNTS)
Mom!
Dad!
HANK: Hope. Over here.
Are you okay?
We should be dead.
Why aren't we?
I don't know.
HOPE: Are we where I think we are?
HANK: I would say yes,
but, uh, it wasn't like this.
Janet!
Mom!
(CREATURES SQUEALING)
(SINISTER MUSIC BUILDS UP)
(BREATHLESSLY) Do not move.
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(ELECTRICAL CRACKLING)
(SIGHS IN RELIEF)
We need to find
Scott and Cassie.
Right now.
-(STATIC WHINING AND HISSING)
-SCOTT: (ON COMMS) Hope?
Hope?
Hank? Can you hear me?
-Can anyone hear me?
-Oh, my God.
-It's okay.
-What are we gonna do?
It's okay. It's okay.
We're okay.
It's gonna be okay.
You're saying "okay" too much.
Okay. All right. Okay.
Well, it's 'cause we are.
We're okay.
We are fine.
Hey, we're gonna find them,
-and we're gonna go home.
-Mm.
-(EXHALES HEAVILY)
-In the meantime, look around.
It's beautiful.
All right? We're outside.
It's like we're camping.
We love camping.
We've never been camping.
But we've always
talked about it.
(EXHALES)
Is that sun moving?
(EERIE MUSIC PLAYING)
Get back!
-(GRUNTING)
-(CASSIE CRIES OUT)
Oh, my God.
-SCOTT: I don't think this is a sun!
-(GASPS)
It's fine. (STRAINING)
-Dad!
-SCOTT: Honey, it's okay.
Still okay.
(GRUNTING)
Dad. Oh, my God.
That was weird.
-(RUMBLING)
-(LOW GROWLING)
Run.
-(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
-(WHIMPERING)
(CASSIE GROANS)
-(CASSIE GASPS)
-(CREATURE GROWLS)
(SCREECHING)
There's Quantum people
in the Quantum Realm?
Yeah.
I didn't know that either.
What was that back there, Mom?
What was that ship
looking for?
Keep your voice down.
You said there was nothing
down here.
Why didn't you tell us
about all of this?
Hope, I will explain
everything, but right now,
-I just need you to trust me.
-Then make me trust you!
Let's just calm down,
all right?
We can talk about this...
We don't have time
to talk, Henry.
No, you need
to tell us what's...
And why didn't you listen?
I told you
to stay away from here.
Janet, I... I'm so sorry.
I should have told you
what we were doing.
I had no idea...
I know. It's...
We'll talk later.
Right now, we stick together,
we find Scott and Cassie,
and we go home. Okay?
-Okay?
-Okay.
Stay close.
(CREATURES CHITTERING)
HANK: This is incredible.
I've studied
the Quantum Realm for years.
Why didn't I see any of this?
You weren't able
to look deep enough.
Not through
the Void and Subatomica.
There are worlds here,
worlds within worlds.
It's a place
outside time and space.
It's a secret universe
beneath ours.
(ENTHRALLING MUSIC PLAYING)
(CREATURE SQUEALS SOFTLY)
(MAN SPEAKING
ALIEN LANGUAGE)
Hey, get your hands off me!
(PEOPLE SPEAKING
ALIEN LANGUAGE)
SCOTT: Cassie?
(MEN YELLING)
Where's my daughter?
Where is she?
Cassie?
(PEOPLE GRUNTING
AND CHATTERING)
Where's my daughter?
(CROWD JEERING)
(EXCLAIMS IN ALIEN LANGUAGE)
Cassie!
(MALE ALIEN GROWLS)
CASSIE: Dad!
Cassie!
Drink the ooze.
What?
(CREATURES BELLOWING)
I'll handle this.
(NOMAD DRIVER SHOUTS
IN ALIEN LANGUAGE)
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(ENGINES REVVING)
Mom.
-(ALL GRUNT)
-(ARTILLERY LOADING)
(GROWLS LOWLY)
(NOMAD DRIVER GRUNTS)
(GROWLS)
(GRUNTS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(NOMAD DRIVER GROANS)
(ALL LAUGHING)
(BOTH GRUNT SOFTLY)
Was that a... a good stab?
I got us a ride.
(CREATURE BELLOWING SOFTLY)
(CREATURE GRUNTING)
(CREATURE PURRS)
He's friendly.
Quite a ride.
Says the man who invented
flying on the back of an ant.
I like ants.
And I love that you love them.
Here.
These will help us blend in.
Where exactly
are we going on this?
We're not too far
from an old friend of mine.
If anyone's heard
where Scott and Cassie are,
it'll be him.
After you.
Saddle up, Ant-Man.
(CROWD CHANTING
IN ALIEN LANGUAGE)
(DRUMS AND WEAPONS
POUNDING RHYTHMICALLY)
Let me go! Let me go!
(MALE ALIEN
EXCLAIMS PLAYFULLY)
(DRAWLING IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
I don't know
what you're saying!
I don't know what you...
-(MALE ALIEN SCREAMS)
-(CHANTING CONTINUES)
(LIQUID BUBBLING)
(GASPS)
No! No!
(YELLS AND GURGLES)
(CROWD CONTINUES CHANTING
IN ALIEN LANGUAGE)
(FAST DISTORTED CHATTER)
CROWD: (CHANTING IN ENGLISH)
Drink the ooze!
-Hello.
-Whoa!
Hi. (CHUCKLES) Hi.
Did you drink the ooze?
Why can I understand you?
Oh. Great. That's the ooze.
Hey, everybody, it worked!
Ooze worked!
(ALL CHEERING)
MAN: We can finally be friends.
Hi. I am Veb.
You just drank me.
I did... What?
Oh. Do you need
some more ooze? Here.
I can pour some ooze
into your hole...
No, I'm okay.
-I'm okay. I'm okay.
-VEB: Oh, wow!
A big hole.
How many holes do you have?
I'm sorry.
Is that a personal question?
-I don't have any holes.
-(ELECTRICAL RINGING)
MAN: His name is Scott Lang.
(ELECTRICAL RINGING)
He has seven holes.
(GASPS)
Yeah, that's right.
How did you...
How did you know that?
He's Quaz. He's a telepath.
(SCOTT GASPS)
You can read minds?
Yeah, and I really wish
I couldn't.
Everyone is disgusting.
-Hmm.
-(ELECTRICAL RINGING)
Could you please
stop thinking that?
-Sorry.
-(RINGING)
-Please, stop.
-Thinking?
(RINGING)
-Thinking that.
-I'm trying.
-(RINGING)
-Well, not very hard.
And I think
you look weird too.
I don't think you look weird.
I think you look really cool.
I wish my head glowed.
(RINGING)
No, no, you don't.
I know I don't. I just...
I'm nervous, okay?
And it just came out.
What are you doing here?
-Are you a spy?
-What? No. No, no.
MALE ALIEN:
We should torture him.
Guys. No, it's okay.
We're not... We're not spies.
He's my dad.
CROWD: Oh!
-(SQUELCHING)
-Oh... Thank you.
Welcome.
-(ELECTRICAL RINGING)
-Then who is San Francisco?
-It's where we're from.
-It's a place.
-Then what's Earth?
-It's also where we're from.
MALE ALIEN:
We should torture them.
Why are you always
trying to torture people?
We have other options.
Do things come out
of your holes,
like milk, juice...
Veb, stop asking
about his holes.
Some of us have holes.
What are you doing here?
Where are you from?
-(GASPS) Okay.
-Up there. Up there.
-CASSIE: See, above this...
-The Earth.
-...it's a different universe.
-Big Earth.
It's the same universe,
but it's bigger.
SCOTT: This is Earth,
but it's a very small Earth.
CASSIE: Sometimes, I guess.
SCOTT: I get big. I shrink.
And it's like...
But I wrote a book about it,
actually.
-CASSIE: I don't know.
-SCOTT: This is the Quantum Realm.
You have to shrink to
get in the Quantum Realm.
We shrunk.
Right now, we're really small.
It's bigger where we're from.
-So, we're small right now.
-It's bigger.
(MUTTERS)
(RINGING)
Okay, they're telling
the truth.
WOMAN: It doesn't matter.
You come from above.
Like him.
So, he is hunting you.
He will burn the world
to find you.
Who?
The Conqueror.
(STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING)
(CREATURE GRUNTING)
(CREATURE WHOOPS)
(ANNOUNCEMENT IN ALIEN LANGUAGE
ON SPEAKERS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
HANK: There are beings
down here.
Intelligent beings.
I always theorized it was
possible, but to be here,
a subatomic universe.
This changes everything
we know about life,
evolution,
our place in the galaxy...
Holy shit!
That guy looks like broccoli.
(GRUMBLES)
(DEVICE BUZZES)
(SPEAKING ALIEN LANGUAGE)
Keep your head down.
(ANNOUNCEMENT IN ALIEN LANGUAGE
ON SPEAKERS)
(ELECTRICAL THRUMMING)
(TRILLING)
(MELLOW LOUNGE MUSIC
PLAYING ON SPEAKERS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER
IN ALIEN LANGUAGE)
JANET: Follow me.
(SPEAKING ALIEN LANGUAGE)
Drink those.
I'll be right back.
(CHATTER TRANSITIONS
TO ENGLISH)
I'm here for Krylar.
Oh.
It's... It's you.
Let's keep that between us.
And Krylar.
Hello.
I don't know
your ways or customs,
but I assume
that you have a beverage
that can get me drunk?
Absolutely, sir.
Hmm.
So, what's your story then?
(SCOFFS)
God.
(CHUCKLES)
JANET: Move.
It's time.
Follow me.
(LOW ELECTRICAL WARBLING)
Right this way.
-MALE PATRON: Hmm.
-Oh.
How exactly
do you know this guy?
Old, uh, freedom fighter
friend of mine.
Sorry, you were
a freedom fighter?
Or terrorist.
Depends on who you ask.
But, trust me, he can help.
(RUMBLING)
(CROWD GASPS)
(TABLEWARE RATTLING)
(ENGINE HUMMING)
(ELECTRICITY BUZZES)
(GLASSES RATTLING)
(GRIPPING MUSIC PLAYING)
Janet Van Dyne?
(MUSIC STOPS)
I thought you were dead.
Been a long time, Krylar.
Officially, Lord Krylar now.
I fought like hell
against that.
It sounds so elitist.
You have got to be Hank.
(CHUCKLES)
I've heard so much
about you and your ants.
What are ants anyway?
Do we have 'em down here?
I don't think so. No.
Oh. That's too bad.
Hope.
You have to be Hope.
She talked about you
every day.
That's strange,
she never said
anything about you.
I don't think I would have
told my kid either.
-(PATS ON BACK)
-(CHUCKLES)
-Wild stuff.
-Funny.
-Hmm.
-How wild?
Very wild, Henry. Yeah.
JANET: Uh...
Krylar, we need your help.
Janet, after all
we've been through, together,
just ask me.
Tell me, how can I help?
But...
is anyone starving?
I'm starving.
Boys...
Now. (CHUCKLES)
(RINGING)
(SIGHS)
They don't know anything.
About... anything.
WOMAN: Then get them
out of here.
Excuse me.
Look, he's right.
I don't know what's going on.
We're just trying
to find our family.
Do you have a map?
All we wanna do is go... Whoa!
(ARTILLERY LOADING)
Wait, wait. Don't shoot.
They're with us.
(ARTILLERY POWERING DOWN)
Is that building alive?
Yours are dead?
SCOTT: Look. Excuse me.
We just wanna go home.
At least you still
have a home.
What happened here?
The Conqueror
burned our homes.
Our stories.
He built his citadel
on the bones of our people.
Some of us escaped,
found others on the run.
We gathered
who we could to fight.
It was never enough.
I'm sorry.
We can help.
-Uh, Cassie...
-Dad, you're an Avenger.
(WHISPERS) They need help.
No. What I need to do
is get you home.
Why don't you wanna help?
We don't know anything
about this place.
I mean, I don't even know
how time works down here.
Have we been gone
for 10 seconds?
Or have we been gone
for 10 years?
Think about your mom
right now.
Can you imagine
what she must be...
Don't use Mom as an excuse.
-You just don't care.
-No, I do care.
I know you wanna help. I do.
But this is not our fight.
Just 'cause it's not
happening to you,
doesn't mean
it's not happening.
Hey.
(SIGHS)
Would you look at me?
(ELECTRICAL RINGING)
She's disappointed in you.
-I got that. Yeah. Thank you.
-You're welcome.
We'll talk about it later.
Right now,
let's just find the others.
No one knows this place
better than Janet.
What did you say?
What?
That name.
Janet Van Dyne.
Where is she?
That's what we're trying
to find out. You know her?
I know her.
She shouldn't be here.
Hey, bring a round
of the chasers, please.
Yes, thank you.
If you haven't had this,
don't try it
unless you want
to change your life.
(WHIMPERING)
(CREATURE SQUEALING)
(CRUNCHING)
Mmm.
Krylar, we're looking
for friends of ours.
Two of them.
Human, like us.
Human, that's the word.
Totally forgot what you call
yourselves up there.
Human.
Are you not human?
Not technically, but yes.
In the ways that matter.
(DOOR OPENS)
(GUNS LOADING)
No!
(GASPS)
Let us talk.
(GUNS POWERING DOWN)
So, what is it that brings you
to us, Janet?
If I remember correctly,
you left.
You left all of us.
With him.
Janet, what is
he talking about?
You didn't tell them
about him.
Did you say anything
about what you did here?
How many people died
because of you?
Does your family even know
who you are?
Your mommy
is full of secrets.
You're lying.
I lie.
A lot.
Not about this.
Let them go.
He just wants me.
KRYLAR: But you want them.
So they're coming too.
Along with those
other friends of yours.
I heard about them.
But he did too.
And, uh, he sent the Hunter.
What kind of hunter?
Uh, not a man.
Not a machine.
A mechanized organism
designed only
for killing.
(UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING)
Where are they?
No clue.
Dead.
(SUIT POWERING UP)
Probably dead.
(ENGINE WHIRRING)
Oh, this is so sad
when all of this
could have been avoided,
Janet.
Just give him what he wants.
What happened to you?
We fought against him.
He can be very persuasive.
Let's pay him a visit.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC BUILDS UP)
I think we're done here.
(GRUNTS)
(YELPS)
(BOTH GRUNT)
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
(YELPS)
Can that ship
get us out of here?
(GROANS)
-Cover me?
-Always.
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(SCREAMS)
(CREATURE CHITTERING)
(KISSES)
(GASPING)
(SCREAMING)
JANET: Henry, take the helm.
I'm gonna hot-wire this thing.
(SQUELCHING)
Where are the controls?
Those are the controls.
(GRUNTING)
What the hell?
You'll be great.
It's like flying a bike.
(SHIP POWERS UP)
Is the bike alive?
(ENGINE REVVING)
-Hands, all the way in!
-(GROANS)
Like stuffing a turkey.
Ugh.
(CONTROLS SCREECH)
(ENGINE THRUSTS)
-Really, him?
-He used to be charming.
That guy?
I was down here
for 30 years, Henry.
-I had needs.
-Oh, my God.
Look, I get it.
I've got needs too.
Oh, my God!
I had dinner with someone
a few times.
Her name was Linda.
It didn't work out.
What went wrong?
She wasn't you, baby.
Get everyone in the ships.
We're leaving.
All right.
-And, Xolum.
-XOLUM: Right here.
Take them as far away
from here as you can.
-Why?
-What?
If you're looking for Janet,
he's looking for you.
(SPOOKY HUMMING)
You led them straight to us.
-(GASPS)
-SCOTT: Come on, come on.
Take as many as you can.
We'll hold them off.
(PANICKED SHOUTING)
(SCREAMS)
(YELLING AND GRUNTING)
Go!
Come on! Hurry, hurry!
VEB: We gotta go! We gotta go!
Get on. Get on now!
We have to go now. Now!
(GRUNTING)
(YELPS)
(SCREAMS) Oh, my God!
(GASPS)
(GRUNTING)
(XOLUM SCREAMS)
Cassie, let's go!
Get to the sanctuary.
Wait for my message.
XOLUM: Veb, we're leaving.
VEB: No. No, wait!
XOLUM: Move! Move!
VEB: All my friends.
(GRUNTING)
(WHIMPERS)
(BOTH SCREAM)
QUANTUMNAUT:
Give up the travelers.
The Conqueror
will show you mercy.
I know his mercy.
(GRUNTING)
(YELLS)
(GROANS)
Stay here. I'm...
Cassie?
Oh, no.
(PANTING)
(GROANING)
(CASSIE GRUNTING)
(YELPS)
-(GUN LOADS)
-(GRUNTS)
Okay. I have a suit.
Yeah, I noticed.
-You okay?
-Yes.
Look, momentum, right?
Jump, tap, right?
One move. Jump, tap.
I know how to do it, Dad.
-Oh, do you? Really?
-CASSIE: Yes.
'Cause it didn't look like it
from my end.
I just... I messed up
on the timing.
Jump... (GRUNTS)
(ALL GRUNTING)
Like that.
You see what I did?
No. You're like this small.
-I jumped and tapped.
-(GASPS)
(PANTING)
(RINGING)
Jentorra, we have to go.
(GROANS)
Get to the ship!
(PEOPLE SHOUTING)
(GROANING)
(EXPLOSIONS)
(GUNFIRE CEASES)
(UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING)
(MECHANICAL HISSING)
(HEAVY THUDDING)
MALE ROBOTIC VOICE:
Welcome back
to the Quantum Realm, Scott.
I've been waiting
a long time for this.
What?
Is someone in there?
MALE ROBOTIC VOICE: Oh, yes.
The destiny you cannot escape.
Our fates have always
been forged together...
ever since that day we met.
(LAUGHING)
Wow.
Scott Lang.
Get away from us!
DARREN: The day you broke me.
(GROANING)
(SCREAMING)
-Banished me down here.
-SCOTT: Wait.
Darren?
Surprised to see me?
Yeah.
It's the bee guy?
(BREATH TREMBLING)
-It's the bee guy?
-DARREN: Cassie?
I almost didn't recognize you.
How are you not dead?
I became the ultimate weapon.
That... That...
That's what this is?
-(GRUNTS)
-Look, Darren.
-(GROWLS)
-(CASSIE SCREAMS)
(BOTH GROANING)
DARREN: Darren is dead!
There is only M.O.D.O.K.!
And there's no place
you can run, Scott.
Not from me.
And not from him.
He's the future.
He's the past.
And now all he needs is you.
Mom?
What's after Scott and Cassie?
We have to find them.
There's something
I have to do first.
They could be dead!
Hope, please.
And you're still
hiding things from us.
I am trying to protect you.
From what?
Who are you so afraid of?
SCOTT: Third time in jail?
Four.
(SOFT WHIRRING)
M.O.D.O.K.: And here we are again.
Face to face.
That's a face. It's a...
It's a big face.
Why are you
just a floating head?
Maybe you could
walk us through this, Darren.
You left Darren to die
in the Quantum Realm.
But the Conqueror found me.
Rebuilt me.
-Made me the ultimate weapon.
-(M.O.D.O.K SCREAMING)
A mechanized organism
designed only for...
Oh, M.O.D.O.K.?
Oh, uh, MO... Oh, I get it.
It's an acronym.
Mechanized organism
designed only for killing.
Actually, that's M.O.D.O.F.K.
I bet you thought
you'd seen the last of me.
Just now noticing
the baby legs.
They're not baby legs.
A little bit like a Björn.
You think you're so smart.
Scott Lang, the man
who took everything from me.
Who stole my whole life.
But I did it.
(GASPS)
I got you here.
I found your signal, Cassie.
Thanks for that, by the way.
Couldn't have done it
without you.
(M.O.D.O.K. LAUGHS DERISIVELY)
You're looking
at a man set free.
I've created so much more here
than you could
possibly imagine.
All for him.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
I wasn't the only one stranded
in the Quantum Realm.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
What is this place?
JANET: He said
he was a traveler.
A scientist
who crashed off course.
(RUMBLING)
He had a ship
beyond anything
I had ever seen.
A ship that could travel
the Multiverse.
The Multiverse?
As in alternate dimensions?
Parallel realities?
I didn't believe it at first.
But it's real.
Just like we theorized.
Can this take us home?
-(INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYS)
-It can take you anywhere.
(CREATURE GRUNTING SOFTLY)
-Yah!
-(CREATURE GRUNTS)
JANET: I'd never met
anyone like him.
He felt so
lost.
I guess we both were.
But we had a way out.
We tried everything
to recharge
his ship's energy core.
Nothing worked.
But after so many years alone,
it was nice to have a friend.
I lied to Hope.
I told her I was coming home.
(PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING)
I can see her by the door.
Waiting for me.
That's the last thing I did...
was lie to her.
I just thought
I'd have more time.
I can give that to you.
Time.
It's not what you think it is.
It's a cage.
And it does everything it can
to break you.
It's not until you free
yourself from it that you see
just how small
it always was.
We're going
to get out of here.
(JANET SIGHS)
-She's gonna open the door...
-(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
...and you'll be there.
I promise.
-Let's get to work.
-Okay.
(INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYING)
JANET: It took ages,
but we did it.
(POWERING UP)
We brought it back to life.
Let's go home.
His ship was neurokinetic.
Connected to his thoughts.
When I touched it...
(ELECTRICAL BLAST)
I saw his mind.
(ELECTRICITY BUZZING)
JANET: I felt...
(WOMAN SCREAMING)
JANET: ...what he had done.
(SCREAMS)
(PEOPLE SCREAMING IN PAIN)
JANET: Entire worlds,
entire timelines.
Gone, like they
never even existed.
(JANET GASPS)
-(BREATHES HEAVILY)
-(MUFFLED PEOPLE SCREAMING)
(SCREAMING CONTINUES)
(SCREAMING STOPS)
Janet?
We can leave.
Right now.
Who is Kang?
Who I need to be.
He didn't crash here.
He was exiled here.
Outside space and time.
The only place
that could hold him.
Exiled?
By who?
I don't know.
But they sabotaged his ship.
And trapped him here.
And because of me,
he was getting out.
Janet?
(UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING)
Stay away.
You saved my life.
I made a promise.
Just let me take you home.
And then?
What are you going to do?
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC
BUILDING UP)
Win.
(MENACING MUSIC PLAYING)
I told you
time isn't what you think.
I can make it...
so you never left her.
Hope is going
to open the door
and you'll be there.
And how many worlds
will die...
if you get out?
Not yours.
She'll never know.
Don't you want
to see your daughter again?
I can't let you leave.
Why do you think
you can stop me?
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC BUILDS UP)
(JANET GRUNTS)
(KANG GRUNTS)
(SCREAMS)
-(GRUNTS)
-(JANET SCREAMS)
(GROANS)
Give it to me, Janet.
Give it to me!
I couldn't beat him.
He was too powerful.
What did you do?
(PANTING)
(BREATH TREMBLING)
(WHISPERS) I'm sorry, Hope.
No!
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(STRAINING)
(SCREAMS)
(GRUNTING)
JANET: I blew up his core.
Cut him off from time.
And trapped us both
down here forever.
But I gave him back enough.
Now that he had his suit back,
he became what he always was.
A conqueror.
He's got weapons
and technology
centuries beyond anything
we can dream of.
He took his prison
and made it his empire.
I spent years fighting him,
running from him,
hiding from him.
And then you saved me.
You brought me home.
But I didn't deserve it.
(SIGHS)
I unleashed a monster
on this place
and ran away.
Janet, you couldn't
have known.
I'm sorry I never told you.
I just wanted to forget.
I just wanted
to be your mom again.
(SNIFFLES)
I'm so sorry you had to
go through all of that alone.
But you are not alone now.
We'll stop him together.
He's after the core.
But he needs Pym Particles
to reach it.
And if he's got
Scott and Cassie,
he's got Pym Particles.
-And a head start.
-Exactly.
-We gotta get out of here.
-JANET: Hope.
He cannot get out.
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
You're an interesting man...
Scott Lang.
Um, I don't know who you are,
but you've made a big mistake.
Okay? (CHUCKLES)
I'm an Avenger.
I've called
the other Avengers...
You're an Avenger?
Have I killed you before?
(SCOFFS) What?
They all blur together
after a while.
You're not the one
with the hammer?
No, that's Thor.
We get confused a lot.
Similar body types.
Who are you?
Just a man
who's lost a lot of time.
Like you.
But we can help
each other with that.
M.O.D.O.K. tells me
you're a good thief.
Yeah, he stole something
from me.
(GRUNTS)
Do not speak
when I am in the room.
-(GASPS)
-(M.O.D.O.K. STRAINING)
(GROANING)
(GASPS)
Gotta say,
Janet was a lot more helpful.
You know Janet too?
Does everyone down here
know Janet?
She didn't tell you about me?
I guess that's not a surprise.
Janet stole something from me.
My ticket out of here.
And you're the only one
who can steal it back.
And why would I do that?
Because you want
to get out of here.
And I need to get out of here.
Because I know how it ends.
CASSIE: How what ends?
All of it.
I don't live
in a straight line.
And with time,
it's hard
not to skip to the end.
So, if you want
to stop what's coming,
and trust me,
you do...
I am the only shot you have.
What's coming?
Me.
A lot of me.
They exiled me, down here.
They're afraid of me.
But I'm the man
who can get you home.
So,
do we have a deal?
No, I don't think we do.
(BREATHES SHAKILY)
-(GROANS)
-Dad!
Let me make this easy for you.
You will bring me what I need
or I will kill your daughter
in front of you,
then make you
relive that moment
over and over
again in time, endlessly,
until you beg me to kill you.
Do we understand?
(SCOTT GRUNTS)
Don't do this.
(GRUNTS, GROANS)
I'm a man
who likes to be understood.
-(ELECTRICAL CRACKLING)
-(GRUNTING IN PAIN)
CASSIE: Dad.
Don't listen to him.
-(SCREAMS)
-No! No!
Look, we can talk about this.
Don't do it!
You really should do it.
SCOTT: Please.
-(ELECTRICAL CRACKLING)
-(GROANING)
(STRAINED)
That's my daughter, please.
Do you want her to live,
or do you want her to die?
Please!
You think I'm lying?
(GROANS)
Do I look like a liar to you?
-(SCREAMS)
-Stop!
-CASSIE: Dad!
-I'll do it. I'll do it.
I'll do it. Just let her go.
Let her go. Let her go!
(PANTS, YELPS)
(GROANS)
(GRUNTS IN PAIN)
You're out of your league.
Ant-Man.
Just be glad I need you.
Don't touch her again.
Then give me what I need.
Where is it?
(GASPS)
(RUMBLING)
What is that?
It was a multiversal
engine core.
A power source
that can take you
anywhere in space and time.
Then Janet blew it up.
It's in that?
JANET: It is that.
And we have to get
to the center.
(SIGHS) That's good to know.
M.O.D.O.K.: You'll have
to shrink down
and pass through
the eye of the storm.
Once you're inside,
find the core
and size it back down.
What does it look like?
When I steal something,
I usually know
what I'm stealing.
You'll know it
when you see it.
Get in and out
as fast as you can.
The longer you're in there,
the more your mind
will come undone.
Better hurry.
(GRUNTING)
Dad!
-(WHISPERING) I'm sorry.
-(SHUSHES)
This is all my fault.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
No.
I messed up.
Cassie.
My whole life happened
because I messed up.
The only thing
I didn't mess up is you.
(GRUNTING)
Dad!
SCOTT: It's okay.
It's okay.
I love you, Peanut.
(SNIFFLES) I love you too.
(INHALES SHARPLY)
(SIGHS)
(FRAGMENTS CLINKING)
(ROUSING MUSIC PLAYING)
(MUSIC STOPS)
(SOFT BLAST)
(PANTING HEAVILY)
Okay. I'm in.
Darren, can you hear me?
Darren?
M.O.D.O.K., can you hear me?
M.O.D.O.K.: (ON COMMS) What?
-I'm in.
-M.O.D.O.K.: Okay.
Okay, so what do I do?
What's the plan?
Don't die?
Thanks. Big help, M.O.D.O.K.
-M.O.D.O.K.: Do you see it?
-(SIGHS)
Yeah. I see it.
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
I'm heading in.
Whoa!
(GASPS) What the hell?
What the hell?
M.O.D.O.K.: I told you, Scott.
Getting in
was just the beginning.
You never said that.
Why am I looking
at another me?
I'm not another me.
You're another me.
You just came out...
Why am I looking
at another me?
M.O.D.O.K.: You're looking at the
possibility of another you.
You're in a Probability Storm.
What does any of that mean?
-You don't know?
-Why would I know?
Because you got me in here.
Oh, so,
I am the real one, huh?
No. I didn't say that.
(BOTH GRUNT)
-What the hell?
-Wait. Wait, wait.
What the hell?
What is this place?
M.O.D.O.K.:
It's a Probability Storm.
Every choice you could make,
existing all at once.
What is he saying?
What's he saying?
-(SHUSHES)
-What's he saying?
M.O.D.O.K.: You're inside
Schrödinger's box.
And you're the cat.
-That doesn't make sense.
-Oh, I get it.
Nobody move! All right?
Nobody move!
Why should we listen to you?
You're not even the real one.
-What the hell?
-Am I real?
-I am the real one!
-What the hell?
What the hell.
I'm the real one.
Whoa, whoa, guys. Hey, relax.
Take it easy. Breathe.
We'll figure this out.
Together.
Who are you?
Why are you dressed like that?
Because I work
at Baskin-Robbins.
This is my uniform.
These are normal clothes.
Why are you dressed like that?
-OTHER SCOTT: Do you have ice cream?
-Enough! Let's do this!
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(MUSIC STOPS)
Oh, we're all gonna die.
(PANICKED CHATTER)
Wait. Whoa, whoa.
Wait. Wait!
No! No!
-(RADIO STATIC)
-SCOTT: No! Wait! No!
I've got a read on Scott.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
OTHER HOPE: Out of the way!
-HOPE: Mom! What is this?
-What are you doing?
JANET: Don't look at them.
They're just possibilities.
(OTHER HOPES SQUABBLING)
JANET: They're not you.
HOPE: (SHOUTS)
Scott, where are you?
(FRIGHTENED SCREAMING)
-Why am I here?
-(PANTING)
OTHER SCOTT: Don't worry.
It'll work this time.
What are you...
Wait, wait, no, no. Stop.
-Stop! No!
-I got this, guys.
(SCOTT SCREAMING)
I got this! I got it!
(GRUNTS)
(SCREAMS)
HOPE: Scott, where are you?
Scott! (PANTING)
(WHISPERS)
Where are you, Scott?
-I can't breathe.
-OTHER SCOTT: Ow, that's my neck.
(SCOTTS GROANING AND GRUNTING)
-Stop kicking me!
-(GRUNTING)
OTHER SCOTT: Help!
-Oh, my back!
-We're all gonna die!
OTHER SCOTT: Get off me!
(GASPING) Dad.
(OTHER SCOTTS
TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
CASSIE: Come back.
Dad,
if you can hear me,
come back.
Just come back.
-Don't give up.
-(SOFTLY) Come on.
-CASSIE: Dad, just come back...
-Come on.
CASSIE: ...one more time.
OTHER SCOTT 1: She needs us.
CASSIE: Please.
-OTHER SCOTT 2: Yes, come on.
-CASSIE: Come back.
She needs us.
Let's do it together.
-Get him up! Get him up!
-Grab him! Grab him!
Let's go.
-Come on, lift him!
-Yes!
-I got ya, I got ya! Go.
-Come on. That's it.
-Come on!
-Give him a boost!
Give him a boost!
Come on, we're doing it
for Cassie! Fellas, let's go!
Everyone together!
What are you doing?
How are you able to do that?
SCOTT: I'll tell you how.
We all want the same thing.
And I'm coming, Cassie.
(OTHER SCOTTS
TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
(STRAINS)
(BOTH GRUNT)
Go get her, pal.
(OTHER SCOTTS GRUNTING
AND SHOUTING)
(GRUNTING)
Everyone, let's go!
Come on!
(FALLING SCOTTS SCREAMING)
Come on, closer.
Get him higher!
Hang on, guys, hang on.
Careful. Steady, steady.
-(FALLING SCOTTS SCREAM)
-(SCOTT GASPS)
Steady. That's it.
Let's go.
(DEVICE WHIRRS)
(SCOTT GRUNTS)
(THUD)
SCOTT: What?
(ENERGY LOADS, FIRES)
-SCOTT: No.
-What happened? Did it work?
-Sorry, buddy!
-(PANICKED CHATTER)
SCOTT: No, no, no.
OTHER SCOTTS: No, no, no.
(WINGS BUZZING)
(TRIUMPHANT MUSIC PLAYING)
SCOTT: Hope, are you real?
HOPE: I'm real.
SCOTT: Then let's do this.
HOPE: You ready?
SCOTT: Ready.
(HOPE GRUNTS)
(BLASTING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(HOPE PANTING)
(CORE POWERS OFF)
(BOTH PANTING)
HOPE: Come on.
We gotta get
that thing out of here.
No, no, no. Wait.
He's got Cassie.
-What?
-JANET: Scott.
-Janet.
-Give that to me. (PANTING)
-We have to go now.
-No.
He's got Cassie.
We will save her.
I promise you
we will save her,
but you cannot
give that to him.
KANG: I wouldn't trust her.
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
Janet has a way of...
changing her mind.
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
Hello, Jellybean.
So...
what's it gonna be, Scott?
M.O.D.O.K.: (DISTORTED) Well, well.
If it isn't my old mentor.
(GASPING)
Hi, Hank.
Darren?
Didn't expect to see
your protégé again
after all...
Holy shit, Darren.
What happened to you?
(YELLING)
I'm the ultimate weapon!
(SHUDDERS)
(M.O.D.O.K. GRUNTING)
Do I need to take it?
Where is my daughter?
Scott.
Don't.
We had a deal.
She'll be fine without you.
(BOTH GASP)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(M.O.D.O.K. GRUNTING)
M.O.D.O.K.: So long, Hank.
(GRUNTING)
Henry.
(GRUNTS)
You left me right here to die.
Let's see how they do.
(HEAVY FOOTFALL)
(LOW GROWLING)
(CHITTERING)
What did you see?
We didn't really get a chance
to talk about it last time.
But I always wondered.
When you touched my mind...
what did you see?
A monster
who thinks he's a god.
When you can see time
the way I do,
you don't get
to close your eyes.
And you're the only one
who sees?
I am the only one
that can see it's broken.
And who broke it?
I did.
Every version of me.
My variants.
Throughout the Multiverse.
Playing with time,
like children.
But I saw how it ends.
I saw their chaos
spreading across realities.
Universes colliding.
Endless incursions.
I saw the Multiverse.
And it was dying.
All because of them.
So, I took control.
You mean you started a war.
And now you wanna wipe away
any universe
that's a threat to you.
That's what monsters do.
That's what conquerors do.
They burn the broken world.
And they make a new one.
You don't care about saving
anything or anyone.
You only want revenge
because they beat you.
Because you lost.
I have lost.
You have no idea
what I have lost.
And I will burn them
out of time
for what they've done to me.
You'll be wiping out
entire timelines.
Murdering trillions of people.
I wish that mattered, Janet.
-(CASSIE GRUNTING)
-(GROANS)
(GASPS)
-(CASSIE GRUNTS)
-(SCREAMS)
(PANTING)
CASSIE: Oh, God.
What am I doing?
(SCOTT GROANING)
-(SCOTT GASPS)
-(CHITTERING)
SCOTT: What?
Hank!
Are these your ants?
From the ant farm?
Yes, Scott, they're my ants.
How did you find them
down here?
I've been picking up strange
signals ever since we crashed.
(LOW ELECTRICAL WARBLING)
First I thought
maybe it was a malfunction.
Some kind of interference.
What is that?
But it wasn't.
It was the ants.
They were reaching out
the whole time.
Apparently,
they passed through
some sort of time dilation.
They've lived thousands
of years in a single day,
expanding their knowledge,
their science,
becoming more advanced
than I could
have ever thought.
I didn't find them.
They found me.
I told you they were smart.
They've already
built something
of a technocratic
Class-Two civilization.
I mean, I know socialism
is a charged word,
but we could
learn a lot from these...
Dad.
Yeah, they're my ants.
And ants don't give up.
I don't care who this guy is.
I don't care what he can do.
I'm getting Cassie.
So, how do we
even the odds against Kang?
(CHITTERING)
We've got some ideas.
What are you thinking?
Well, as a great writer
once said,
"There's always room to grow."
You read my book?
Every goddamn word.
Come on. Let's go to work.
(BREATHING DEEPLY)
(TINY FOOTSTEPS PATTERING)
-(GRUNTS)
-(GASPS)
Hey! I'm sorry. (PANTING)
That was probably terrifying.
What are you doing here?
I'm rescuing you.
How?
That's a good question.
Does this thing
have like a key?
-Or a card? Like a room key?
-(KEYPAD BEEPING)
Do you know, like a...
(GASPS)
Shit!
(CASSIE GRUNTING)
Jump and tap.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
-(GRUNTS)
-(KEYPAD CHIMES)
Jentorra.
I'm sorry
I got your people hurt.
How can I help?
(QUANTUMNAUT GROANING)
(GRUNTS)
Wow.
Let's hurt 'em back.
Damn, you're cool.
Do you have a plan?
Freeing you
was basically my plan.
Do you have a plan?
We need to get a message out
to anyone who can still fight.
Then free our people
from the detention cells below
and launch a counteroffensive
from within.
Yeah, you have a plan.
So, how do we get
a message out?
-Follow me.
-Okay. Great.
I built an empire
down here, Janet.
And I'm taking it with me.
(MAJESTIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(MARCHING FOOTSTEPS)
You really should've
let me out
when you had the chance.
(CONTROLS TRILLING)
History is not written.
It is forged.
Today, we ascend.
From this fortress,
I will take my revenge
on those who banished me.
Today we conquer eternity.
And the dynasty of Kang
shall...
(BROADCASTING STOPS)
CASSIE: Hello?
Is this working?
Cassie?
I can't tell
if this is working.
Okay. I think we're on.
I'll hold them off.
Get the message out.
I thought you were getting
the message out.
Now!
(GRUNTS)
We're inside.
We breached the tower.
And I'm with Jentorra.
He's not invincible.
(GASPS)
(PANTING)
I know it might feel like
it's too late,
like all we do is just lose.
But the family I've lost
taught me to keep fighting.
And if they were here,
they would too.
We need to look out
for the little guy.
My dad taught me that.
'Cause when people
needed help,
-he didn't look the other way.
-(GROANS)
And neither do we.
(BOTH GRUNT)
We need to move!
Come to the tower! Fight back!
I know you've been waiting.
Now is the time to strike.
He knows
he can't take all of us.
Come to the...
Cassie.
I think I found the signal.
Mom's gotta be there, too.
-Let's go.
-I'll drive.
(CONTROLS SQUELCHING)
(ENGINE ACCELERATING)
Find Lang's daughter.
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
Kill her.
(GASPS, GRUNTS)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYS)
(ALL GRUNTING)
(GUARD GROANS)
JENTORRA: Let's go. Let's go!
If you want to fight,
follow me!
(WOMAN SCREAMS)
M.O.D.O.K.: It's over, Cassie.
Free the others. Go!
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
(CASSIE GRUNTS)
He's gonna see us coming.
Yeah. I'll make sure of it.
Begin the launch.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(MACHINE POWERING UP)
-(EXPLOSION)
-(GRUNTS)
(GRUNTS)
(SCREAMS)
(GRUNTING)
M.O.D.O.K.: Your dad's not here, Cassie,
but I guess
that's not a big surprise.
-(GUNS COCKING)
-(PANTING)
-(LOUD THUD)
-(GASPS)
(RUMBLING)
(THUDDING CONTINUES)
(FOOTSTEPS THUNDERING)
SCOTT: (DISTORTED) Kang!
We had a deal.
You took my daughter!
-Holy shit.
-(BREATHING HEAVILY)
That's big.
(QUANTUMNAUTS SCREAMING)
(ROUSING MUSIC PLAYING)
SCOTT: You lied to me!
Our word is our bond.
Without that, we're nothing!
(QUANTUMNAUTS SCREAM)
-Bring him down.
-QUANTUMNAUT: Yes, sir.
HOPE: Keep going.
I've got them.
Yeah, come on!
(GROANING)
SCOTT: There's so many!
HOPE: Scott!
I can't hold them!
SCOTT: They came.
Way to go, Cassie!
Yes!
SCOTT: Come on! Let's go!
-QUANTUM FIGHTER: Revolution!
-(ALL SHOUTING EXCITEDLY)
VEB: Burn it all down.
-XOLUM: Fight!
-(ALL SHOUTING)
(CONTROLS BEEPING)
(XOLUM GRUNTS)
Cover! Get down!
(ALL GRUNTING)
(CHOKING)
What is the bridge code?
QUANTUMNAUT: I'll die first.
-(ELECTRICAL RINGING)
-One-eight-one-four-seven.
QUANTUMNAUT: Damn!
-(GRUNTS)
-(QUANTUMNAUT GROANS)
(QUANTUM FIGHTERS
SHOUTING BATTLE CRIES)
XOLUM: You'll need this.
VEB: Hi.
This is our home!
Let's take it back!
(ALL SHOUT)
(VEB GROANING)
XOLUM: No!
(QUANTUM FIGHTERS EXCLAIM)
(WHIMPERING)
VEB: I have holes.
I have holes!
(SCREAMS)
(QUANTUMNAUTS SCREAMING)
(VEB WHOOPING)
I didn't know
he could do that.
(ALL CHEERING)
(SCOTT GRUNTING)
SCOTT: Kang!
Where is she?
Launch now!
(CONTROLS TRILLING)
(MACHINE POWERING UP)
SCOTT: Whoa.
What is that?
HOPE: He's getting out.
SCOTT: Oh, no, he's not.
(HEROIC MUSIC PLAYING)
Keep him away from the rings.
(PANTING)
(GRUNTS)
(SCOTT GRUNTS)
(CASSIE GRUNTS)
(SCOTT GRUNTING)
(STRAINING)
CASSIE: Whoa! Dad!
(GASPING)
Dad, I'm coming!
(SCOTT GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
(PANTING)
Dad!
(GROANS)
(M.O.D.O.K. LAUGHING
MOCKINGLY)
Nowhere left to run.
(PANTING)
(GASPS)
(WHISPERS)
Please let this work.
(GRUNTS)
(M.O.D.O.K. SCREAMS, GRUNTS)
(M.O.D.O.K. GRUNTING)
M.O.D.O.K.: Hey, where do you
think you're going?
Let's go.
You think this is over?
Come on! Let's go.
CASSIE: Darren, just stop
trying to be whatever this is.
I don't know what to be.
Tell me what to be.
I don't know.
Just don't be a dick.
It's too late.
Look at me.
I'm such a dick.
It's never too late
to stop being a dick.
(FOOTSTEPS THUNDERING)
HOPE: We've gotta stop him.
SCOTT: I have an idea.
HOPE: Ready?
SCOTT: Probably not.
-One, two, three. Now!
-(HOPE GRUNTS)
(SCOTT SCREAMING)
(ALL SCREAMING)
(MACHINE POWERING DOWN)
(SCOTT GRUNTS)
Dad!
Cassie?
You're huge.
I'm huge. (SQUEALS)
(CASSIE LAUGHS)
I love you, Peanut.
I love you too.
I'm so proud of you.
I feel like
I'm hugging Godzilla.
I know. It feels so cool.
I know, right?
I'm so hungry.
Yeah, that happens.
-I could eat everything.
-Everything. I know.
But I really want like a lime.
Right?
-Citrus. It's weird. I know.
-Citrus.
SCOTT: It's...
(BOTH PANTING)
(QUANTUM FIGHTERS YELLING)
(GRUNTS) Take the tower!
(ALL YELLING)
(GROANS SOFTLY)
(GASPS)
(GROANS)
(PANTING)
(MUFFLED EXPLOSIONS)
It's over.
You still can't see it.
It's never over.
(PANTING)
(SINISTER MUSIC PLAYING)
(GRUNTING)
(QUANTUM FIGHTERS SCREAMING)
(YELLS)
(QUANTUM FIGHTERS GROANING)
-(KANG GRUNTS)
-(SCREAMS)
-(JANET GRUNTING)
-(GUARDS GROANING)
(QUANTUM FIGHTERS SCREAMING)
(GRUNTS)
(XOLUM YELLS)
(ELECTRICITY LOADING)
(KANG GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
(SCREAMING)
(GRUNTS)
(GRUNTING IN PAIN)
(PANICKED SHOUTING)
-We have to go, right now.
-No.
-QUAZ: Come on.
-No!
VEB: I know, I know,
but we have to go.
-No! (SOBBING)
-VEB: Come on.
(SCREAMING)
(QUANTUM FIGHTERS
SHOUTING IN PANIC)
(SCOTT GRUNTS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(HOPE GRUNTS)
(ALL GRUNTING)
(KANG GRUNTS)
(FIRING)
(HOPE GRUNTS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
SCOTT: You son of a...
-(GRUNTS)
-(SCOTT GROANS)
CASSIE: Oh, God.
HOPE: Scott.
Come on.
(GRUNTS)
KANG: You think
this is new to me?
Do you know how many
rebellions I have put down?
VEB: No, no, no, no, no.
How many worlds
I've conquered?
How many Avengers I've killed?
And you think you can beat me?
I am Kang!
You...
You talk to ants.
(TRUMPETING IN DISTANCE)
(ANTS SQUEAKING)
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(QUANTUMNAUT SCREAMS)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(SCREAMS)
(ANTS SCREECHING)
(KANG GRUNTING)
(ENGINE ACCELERATING)
(ENGINE WHINES)
(GRUNTS)
(SCREAMS)
(YELLS)
My name is Darren,
and I am not a dick!
(GRUNTS, SCREAMS)
(GROANING)
(SCREAMS)
(MUSIC OUTRO SWELLING)
(MUSIC ENDS)
Sorry I'm late.
Lotta ants.
Oh, is this you?
(M.O.D.O.K. GROANS)
Maybe you were right
about me, Cassie.
SCOTT: Darren.
Are you okay?
(COUGHS)
Probably not.
-Darren?
-Hi, Hope.
You changed your hair.
(CHUCKLES AWKWARDLY)
What the hell happened?
Yeah. No, it's...
It's a whole thing.
I'll tell you later.
That was... I...
I don't know what to say.
Thanks, Scott.
You always were
a brother to me.
I was?
I was.
(WISTFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(COUGHING)
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
And at least I died
an Avenger.
Yeah.
-You did.
-Yeah. No, it's...
-You're in.
-(DARREN SIGHS IN RELIEF)
(WISTFUL MUSIC CONTINUES)
(DARREN EXHALES)
A lot has happened today.
-JANET: Henry?
-Janet?
-Mom, where are you?
-JANET: I'm in the tower.
I think I can give us
one shot back.
But we don't have much time.
If we wanna go home...
we have to go now.
We'll finish this.
Thank you.
VEB: Thank you.
Oh, wow! (CHUCKLES)
Come on! Let's go!
All right. Good luck.
Good luck.
Come on.
-(BREATHING HEAVILY)
-(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
-Thanks, buddy.
-(CHIRPS)
(JANET SIGHS IN RELIEF)
You did it.
Let's go home.
(BOTH GRUNT)
(GRUNTS)
-(PORTAL RUMBLES)
-(GRUNTS)
-(CASSIE GASPS)
-(SCOTT YELPS)
(CASSIE GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
Where's Scott?
He was right behind me.
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
(CRACKLING)
(GROANS)
(GRUNTING)
-(YELLS)
-(SCOTT GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
(KANG GRUNTS)
-(GRUNTS)
-(SCOTT GROANS)
(BOTH PANTING)
You should've
looked the other way.
Yeah, well,
never been great at that.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
And you're not getting out.
-(GROANING)
-I want you to remember.
You could've gone home.
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
You could've seen
your daughter again.
(GROANS)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(GRUNTS IN PAIN)
But you thought you could win.
(GRUNTING)
(YELLS IN PAIN)
-(SCOTT SHOUTS)
-(GRUNTING)
-(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
-(GROANS)
I don't have to win.
We both just have to lose.
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(KANG GRUNTS)
-(GRUNTS, SCREAMS)
-(THUD)
(HEROIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(SCREAMS, GROANS)
(YELLS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(SCREAMING IN PAIN)
(BOTH GRUNT)
-(FRAGMENTS CLATTERING)
-Dad!
(BOTH GROANING)
Where... Where...
Where is she? Is she...
-No, she's okay.
-Where is she?
She's okay.
She's okay. She's okay.
-Scott, they're all okay.
-She's safe?
They're all okay. You did it.
You did it.
(GROANS IN PAIN)
-Sorry. Sorry, sorry.
-No, no, no.
No, don't let go.
Don't let go.
Don't ever let go.
HOPE: I got you.
(HOPE SIGHS)
You came back.
(HOPE PANTING)
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
(HOPE SIGHS)
(WHISPERS) I love you, Hope.
I love you, Scott.
(SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES)
(PEOPLE CHEERING
IN DISTANCE)
(SENTIMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(CHEERING CONTINUES)
(KEYBOARD CLACKING)
(BEEPING)
Let's go home.
Home's good.
(WELCOME BACK
BY JOHN SEBASTIAN PLAYING)
(STREETCAR BELL DINGING)
SCOTT: My life
doesn't make sense.
I used to ask myself
a lot of questions about that.
-Ah.
-"Scott you just saved
"the Quantum Realm
with your family
"and drank a guy
without holes.
"Why does this kind of stuff
keep happening to you?
"That doesn't make any sense."
But you know what?
Who said life
has to make sense?
Rubin!
You are the bug!
(CHUCKLING)
I was wrong. Yeah.
You are the other bug.
You're the bug man.
You get big and get small
like a big bug!
You're right. That's me.
Just a coffee, please.
Twelve dollar.
Oh.
Twelve!
I used to wonder if this
chapter in my life was over,
but as Cassie reminded me,
"There's always someone
you can help."
Came out of cake making
retirement for you.
Wow.
You... You made this yourself?
Yeah! I don't usually
make the cakes.
I know.
This is the first one
I've made since 1997.
You're a real artist.
It's been a pretty wild ride.
One day you're fired
from Baskin-Robbins,
the next you're beating
a time-traveling space king.
We did beat him, right?
I mean, yeah,
that's what happened.
He... He was getting out
and he didn't get out.
I think.
But he also said
something bad was coming
and that everyone would die
if he didn't get out.
(SONG FADES)
Wait.
So, did I just kill everyone?
Is everyone gonna die
because of me?
-Oh, my God.
-(UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING)
Oh, my... What did I do?
What... What did...
What did I do?
-(UNEASY MUSIC STOPS)
-You know what?
-It's probably fine.
-(SONG RESUMES PLAYING)
Like I said,
life doesn't make any sense,
so maybe stop asking
so many questions, Scott.
Stop overthinking it.
(PATRONS CHATTERING)
Surprise!
(SINGING)
Happy Birthday to you
It's not my birthday.
I know. But I missed a few.
(CHUCKLES)
SCOTT: This is good.
We're all together.
You're fine.
Everything's probably fine.
Kang's gone. You did it.
Don't have to worry
about that guy anymore.
Ah. Thanks.
Happy fake birthday, Cassie.
(CASSIE CHUCKLES)
Oh. (GAGS)
(GRIPPING MUSIC PLAYING)
(MUSIC CONCLUDES)
(CROWD CHEERING)
MAN: So, the exiled one
is dead.
You sure he's dead?
If it wasn't true,
I wouldn't call you.
Must really eat you up,
that you're not
the one who killed him.
None of us
killed him.
They did.
They're beginning to touch
the Multiverse.
And if we let them,
they will take...
everything
we've built.
So let's stop wasting time.
We're late.
How many did you call?
All of us.
(CROWD SHOUTING EXCITEDLY)
(EXCITED SHOUTING CONTINUES)
(INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING)
MAN: Time is everything.
It shapes our lives.
-But, perhaps, we can shape...
-(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYS)
...it.
(WHISPERING) It's him.
(WHISPERING) What?
You made him sound
like this terrifying figure.
He is.
(OMINOUS MUSIC BUILDING UP)