Promo Bonus 300%. Bonus Langsung setiap hari
Gabung sekarang di mantulbanget.net
Situs dengan Winrate terbesar di Indonesia
Stark!
He doesn't seem happy.
Hello, Hank.
You're supposed to be in Moscow.
I took a detour...
Through your defense lab.
Tell me that isn'twhat I think it is.
That depends if you think it'sa poor attempt to replicate my work.
Even for this group,that takes nerve.
You wereinstructed to go to Russia.
May I remind you, Dr. Pym,that you're a soldier...
I'm a scientist.
Then act like one.
The Pym Particle is the mostrevolutionary science ever developed.
Help us put it to good use.
I let you turn meinto your errand boy,
and now you try tosteal my research?
If only you'd protected Janetwith such ferocity, Dr. Pym.
Ah...
Easy, Hank.
You mention my wife again
and I'll show you ferocity.
Don't look at me. You said it.
I formallytender my resignation.
We don't accept it. Formally.
Hank,
we need you.
The Pym Particle is a miracle.Please.
Don't let your pastdetermine the future.
As long as I am alive,
nobody will everget that formula.
We shouldn't let himleave the building.
You've already lied to him.Now you want to go to war with him?
Yes.
Our scientists haven't come closeto replicating his work.
He just kickedyour ass, full-size.
You really want to find out what it's likewhen you can't see him coming?
I've known HankPym for a long time.
He's no security risk.
Unless we make him one.
You like that?
Come get you some now.
You didn't even move.
Nah.
What if I come in on the left side, right?Just down here.
You see this right here?
I'm gonna miss you, Scott.
I'm gonna miss you,too, Peachy.
Man, you guys gotthe weirdest goodbye rituals.
All right, break it up.
Break it up!Break it up!
Scotty!
What's up, man!
Damn! Hey.
Ha-ha! Hey, man.
Hey, what's up with your eye?
Oh. Well,what do you think? Peachy.
It's a going-away present.
Oh, yeah.I still got my scar from a year ago.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
You know what? I'm still theonly one who knocked him out.
Well, I definitely didn't.
Thanks forpicking me up, brother.
Bro, you think I'm gonna missmy celly getting out?
Hey, how's your girl, man?
Oh, she left me.
Oh.
Yeah, my ma died, too.
And my dad got deported.
But I got the van!
It's nice.
Yeah, right?
Thanks for the hook-up, too.I needed a place to stay.
You wait till you see this couch.You're gonna be really happy.
You're gonna be on your feetin no time. Watch.
- I hope so.- Yeah.
And I gottaintroduce you to some
people.Some really skilled people.
- Not interested.- Yeah, right.
No, I'm serious, man.I'm not going back.
I got a daughterto take care of.
You know that jobs don'tcome easy for ex-cons, right?
Look, man, I got a master'sin electrical engineering, all right?
I'm gonna be fine.
Welcome to Baskin-Robbins.
Would you like to try ourMango Fruit Blast?
Uh, no, thanks.
Um, I will have...I'll have a burger, please.
Oh, we don't...We don't make that.
Pretzel.Hot pretzel. Like, mustard...
Do you have mustard dip?
It's ice cream.Baskin-Robbins.
I'll just do, like,whatever's hot and fresh.
Dude.
Can I see you in the back,chief? Pronto.
Sure thing, Dale.
Darby, could you just, uh,take care of this idiot? Thanks.
Hey, Dale.
Come on in.
Pull up some chair.
Three years at San Quentin, huh?
You found out.
Baskin-Robbinsalways finds out.
Look, I'm sorry, all right?But I...
No one would hire me.
Breaking and entering.Grand larceny.
Look, I'm sorry.
I don't do it anymore.I just...
Respect.
I couldn't be happier about it.
- Really?- Yeah.
Thank you. Thank you.
You really stuck itto those billionaire SOBs.
The more I read aboutwhat you did and stuff...
I'm like,"Wow, I know this guy?
"I'm in charge of this guy?"
Well,I'm very happy in this job,
and I really just appreciatethe opportunity to...
Well, you're fired, of course.
I can't really keep you on.
Wait, what? Fired?
Yeah.
Dale, look, it wasn't a violent crime.I mean, I'm a good worker.
No, it wasn't a violent crime.It was a cool crime.
I'll tell you what, though.
This will be totally off the books,off the records,
but if you want to grabone of those Mango Fruit Blasts
on your way out the door,
I'll just pretendI didn't see it.
Hey, Scotty. What's up?
I thought you weresupposed to be at work.
I was. I got fired.
Damn.They find out who you are?
Yeah.
Baskin-Robbinsalways finds out, bro.
Baskin-Robbins don't play.
You want some waffles?
Yeah, I'll take a waffle.
Oh. That's Kurt.
He was Folsom for five years.He's a wizard on that laptop.
Nice meet you.
Yeah. Nice to meet you, too.
Who are you?
Dave.
Nice work on the Vista job.
Vista job, yes.
No, no.I have heard of this robbery.
Well, technically, I didn't rob them.Robbery involves threat.
I hate violence.I burgled them.
I'm a cat burglar.
You mean you're a pussy.
Yeah.
They were overchargingthe customers, right?
And it added up to millions.
He blowsthe whistle and he gets fired.
And what does he do?
He hacks intothe security system
and transfers millionsback to the people that they stole it from.
Posts all the bank records online.
And he drove the dude's Bentleyinto his swimming pool.
What are you doing?
Hmm?
Why are you telling mylife story to these guys?
What do you want?
Okay.
My cousin talked to this guytwo weeks ago
about this little perfect job.
No way.
No, no, no. Wait!This guy... This guy fits your M.O.
No!
I'm finished, man.I'm not going back to jail.
It's some retired millionaireliving off his golden parachute.
It's a perfect Scott Lang mark!
I don't care. I'm out.
Dr. Pym?
Yes. I'm still alive.
ID?
Perhaps that will suffice.
Very sorry, sir.Please come in.
Is that Hank Pym?
Good morning, Hank.
Hope.
Would it killyou to call me Dad?
Dr.Cross will be so pleased that
you could findthe time to join us today.
More like "thrilled."
I was surprised to receiveany kind of invitation from you, Darren.
What's the occasion?
Oh, you'll see.Won't he, Hope?
We're ready for you inside.
Ouch.
I guess some old woundsnever heal, huh?
Don't worry,she's in good hands.
You're in for a treat.
Long time, no see, Dr. Pym.How's retirement?
How's your face?
After you.
Now, before we start,I'd like to introduce a very special guest.
This company'sfounder and my mentor,
Dr. Hank Pym.
When I took over this companyfor Dr. Pym,
I immediately startedresearching a particle
that could changethe distance between atoms,
while increasingdensity and strength.
Why this revolutionary idearemained buried
beneaththe dust and cobwebs of
Hank's research,I couldn't tell you.
But just imagine,
a soldierthe size of an insect.
The ultimate secret weapon.
An Ant-Man.
That's what they called you.Right, Hank?
Silly, I know.
Propaganda.
Tales to astonish!
Trumped-up BS toscare the USSR.
Hank, will you tell our guestswhat you told me
every single time I asked you,
"Was the Ant-Man real?"
Just a tall tale.
Right.
Because how could anythingso miraculous possibly be real?
Well, I was inspired by the legendof the Ant-Man.
And with my breakthroughshrinking inorganic material,
I thought, could it be possibleto shrink a person?
Could that be done?
Well,it's not a legend anymore.
Distinguished guests,
I am proud to presentthe end of warfare as we know it.
The Yellowjacket!
Oh, no.
The Yellowjacketis an all-purpose weapon of war
capable of alteringthe size of the wearer
for the ultimatecombat advantage.
We live in an era
in which the weaponswe use to protect ourselves
are underminedby constant surveillance.
It's time toreturn to a simpler age.
One where the powers of freedomcan once again operate openly
to protect their interests.
An all-purposepeace-keeping vessel,
the Yellowjacketcan manage any conflict
on the geopolitical landscape
completely unseen.
Efficient in both preventativemeasures and tactical assault.
Practical applicationsinclude surveillance,
industrial sabotage,
and the elimination of obstructionson the road to peace.
A single Yellowjacket
offers the userunlimited influence
to carry out protective actions.
And, one day soon,an army of Yellowjackets
will createa sustainable environment
of well-beingaround the world.
The Yellowjacket.
So, it's a suit?
Don't be crude, Frank.
It's not a suit,it's a vessel.
What's the matter?You're not impressed?
No, I'm impressed.I'm also concerned.
Imagine what our enemiescould do with this tech.
We should have a longerconversation about that, Frank.
I really value your opinion.
Thank you for coming. Hope?
Thank you very much, everybody.I will escort you out now.
Thank you.
You seem a bit shocked.
Darren, there's a reasonthat I buried these secrets.
So you finally admit it!
We could have done this together, Hank.But you ruined that.
That's why you're the pastand I'm the future.
Don't do this.
Dr. Cross?
You sell to me first,20% over your asking price,
I can have the cashhere in two weeks.
Deal.
We have tomake our move, Hank.
How close is he?
He still can'tshrink a live subject.
Just give me the suit and let mefinish this once and for all.
No.
I have Cross' complete trust.
It's too dangerous.
We don't have a choice.
Well,that's not entirely true.
I think I found a guy.
Who?
Daddy!
Peanut! Oh!
Happy birthday!
I'm so sorry I'm late.
I didn't knowwhat time your party started.
It was on the invitation.
He didn't get an invitation.
But he came anyway!
Well, I'm not gonna missmy little girl's birthday party.
I'm gonna go tellMommy you're here.
Oh, you don't...
What are you doing here, Lang?
You haven't paida dime of child support.
You know, right now, if I wanted to,I could arrest you.
It's good to seeyou too, Paxton.
Mommy's so happy you're here,she choked on her drink.
Hey, look what I have for you.
Can I open it now?
Of course, sweetheart.It's your birthday.
You're my bestest friend.
What is that thing?
He's so ugly!
I love him!
Can I go show my friends?
Of course, sweetheart.Go ahead.
You're my bestest friend.
Look, the child supportis coming, all right?
It's just hard finding a jobwhen you have a record.
I'm sure you'll figure it out.But for now, I want you out of my house.
- No way! It's my daughter's birthday.- It's my house!
- So what? It's my kid!- Scott!
You can't just show up here.You know that. Come on.
It's a birthday party.
Yeah, I know,but you can't just show up.
She's my daughter.
You don't know the first thingabout being a father.
Maggie,I tell you this as a friend,
and as the firstlove of my life.
Your fiance is an asshat.
He's not an asshat.
Hey, watch your language.Okay?
What language? I said "hat."
Stop it.
Really, Maggie? That guy?
Come on! You could marryanyone you want,
and you have toget engaged to a cop?
At least he's not a crook.
I'm trying, okay?I've changed. I'm straight.
I had a job and...
I wanna provide.
I had a lot of time to think about itand I love her.
So much.
I've missed so much timeand I wanna be a part of her life.
What do I do?
Get an apartment,
get a job, pay child support.
And then we will talk about visitation,I promise.
You're her hero, Scott.
Just be the personthat she already thinks you are.
I'm sorry you have such deep concernsabout the Yellowjacket, Frank.
Yeah. Well, uh...
Unfortunately,we can't just do whatever we want.
It'd be nice though, right?
But there are laws.
What laws? Of man?
The laws of naturetranscend the laws of man.
And I've transcendedthe laws of nature.
Darren, I don'tthink you understand...
Hmm.
We still haven'tworked out all the bugs.
Goodbye, Frank.
Thank you.
You know, I've been thinking a lotabout gratitude lately.
And today,during my morning meditation,
an interestingthought occurred to me,
and I think itmight apply to you, too.
How's that?
Gratitude can be forgiveness.
I've spent years carrying aroundmy anger for Hank Pym.
I devoted my genius to him.
I could have worked anywhere.
I chose my mentor poorly.
You didn't even have a choice.
He never believed in you.
It's a shamewhat we had to do,
but he forced usto do it, didn't he?
But we shouldn't be angry,we should be grateful.
Because hisfailures as a mentor,
as a father,
forced us to spread our wings.
You're a success, Darren.
You deserve everythingcoming your way.
Ooh.
Stop cheating.
Hey, what's up, hotshot?
Maybe he didn't hear you.
How was the party?
Tell me about that tip.
What?
I wanna know about that tip.
Oh, baby, it's on!It's so on, right now.
Calm down, all right?I just need to know where it came from.
It's gotta be airtight.
Okay.
I was at a wine tastingwith my cousin Ernesto.
Which was mainly reds,and you know I don't like reds, man.
But there was a rose that saved the day.It was delightful.
And then he tellsme about this girl,
Emily,that we used to kick it with.
It was actually the first pair of boobsI ever touched.
It's the wrong details.
It has nothing todo with the story.
Go.
So,uh, he tells me that she's
working asa housekeeper now, right?
And she's datingthis dude, Carlos,
who's a shot callerfrom across the bay.
And she tells him about the dudethat she's cleaning for.
Right? That he'slike this big-shot CEO
that is all retired now,but he's loaded.
And so, Carlos and Ernestoare on the same softball team,
and they get to talking,right?
And here comes the good part.Carlos says, "Yo, man.
"This guy's gota big-ass safe just
"sitting in the basement,just chilling."
Of course Ernestocomes to me because
he knows I gotmad thieving skills.
Of course, I ask him...
"Did Emily tellCarlos to tell you
"to get to me whatkind of safe it was?"
And he says, "Nah, dawg.
"All she said isthat it's super-legit
"and whatever's in it,it's gotta be good."
What?
Old man have safe.
And he's gone for a week.
All right.There's an old man,
he's got a safe,
and he's gone for a week.
Let's just work with that.
You know what I'm saying?
Landline's cut,cell signal's jammed.
No one will be makingfor distress call tonight.
Comm check.
- Check.- Check.
Hey, if the job goes bad,you know I got your back, right?
Don't worry.
It's not gonna happen.
I love it when he gets cocky.
Damn!
Alarm is dead.
Nice.
All right,I'm moving through the house.
There's a fingerprintlock on the door.
It's got what?Ernesto didn't tell me nothing about that.
Aw, man, are we screwed?
Not necessarily.
I'm in.
No alarms have been triggered.He's in like the Flynn.
Oh, man.
What is it?
Well, they weren't kidding.This safe is serious.
How seriousare we talking, Scotty?
It's a Carbondale.
It's from 1910.
Made from the samesteel as the Titanic.
Wow.
Can you crack it?
Well, here's the thing.It doesn't do so well in the cold.
Remember what that iceberg did?
Yeah, man. It killed DiCaprio.
Killed everybody.
Did not kill the old lady.
She still throwthe jewel into the oceans.
What are you doing?
I poured water in the locking mechanismand froze it with nitrogen.
Ice expands. Metal doesn't.
- What are you doing now?- Waiting.
Waiting.
Nice.
What is it?Cash? Jewels?
- There's nothing here.- What did you say?
It's a suit.
What?
It's an old motorcycle suit.
There's no cash,no jewelry, nothing?
No.
It's a bust.
I'm really sorry, Scotty.
I know you needed to score.
I thought we were using mice.
What's the difference?
Commence Experiment 34-C.Organic atomic reduction.
Darren, maybe we should think...
Shrinking organic tissueis the centerpiece of this technology.
I can't go to the buyerswith half a breakthrough.
Experiment 34-C results,
negative.
Sanitize the work station.Bring in subject 35-C.
Why would you lock this up?
This is so weird.
Scotty, what's up, man?
I wonder...What is this?
The worldsure seems different
from down here,doesn't it, Scott?
What? Who said that?
Luis, down here!
It's a trial by fire, Scott.Or, in this case,
water.
Guess you're tougherthan you thought.
Oh, I don't want to see this!
Luis!
Son of a...
What the hell?
Not bad for a test drive.
Keep the suit.I'll be in touch.
No! No! No, thank you!
Get down on the ground!
You are under arrest!
No, I didn't steal anything!I was returning something I stole.
Oh...
Don't move.
You know,you almost had us convinced
that you weregonna change your ways.
They were reallyrooting for you.
It's gonna break their hearts.
You got a visitor.
Who?
Your lawyer.
My lawyer?
I told you I'dbe in touch, Scott.
I'm starting to think thatyou prefer the inside of a jail cell.
Oh, man.
Sit down.
Sir,I'm sorry I stole the suit.
I don't even wanna knowwhy you have it.
Maggie was right about you.
How do you know about...
No wonder she's tryingto keep you away from Cassie.
The moment things get hard,
you turn right back to crime.
The way I see it,you have a choice.
You can either spendthe rest of your life in prison,
or go back to your cell
and await further instructions.
I don't understand.
No, I don't expect you to.
But you don't have many optionsright now, and quite frankly,
neither do I.
Why do you think I let yousteal that suit in the first place?
What?
Second chancesdon't come around all that much.
So, next time you thinkyou might see one,
I suggest you takea real close look at it.
You're my bestest friend!
Are you sure youdon't want a different toy?
No, I love this one.
Okay. Well,get some sleep. I love you.
- Mommy?- Hmm?
Is Daddy a bad man?
I heard somegrownups say he's bad.
No.
Daddy just getsconfused sometimes, you know?
Smart choice.You actually listened, for once.
Under the door.
Okay, where to now?
- Hang tight.- Oh, God.
What, what?
Where the hell did he go?
I have no idea.He just vanished.
Set up a five-block perimeter.Now!
Get back! Get back!
Scott,these are my associates.
Is that a camera on an ant?
Yeah, sure. Why not?
Where's the car?
No car. We've got wings.
Incoming!
Put your foot on the centralnode and mount the thorax.
- How safe is...- Just get on the damn ant, Scott!
Why am I on a police car?
Shouldn't I notbe on a police car?
So they can give you a lift
past theirfive-block perimeter.
All right.
- Now, what's the next move?- Hang on tight.
Oh, this is easy!I'm getting the hang of this.
Yank up to go up.It's like a horse.
You'rethrowing 247 off balance.
Wait, his name is 247?
He doesn't have a name,he has a number, Scott.
Do you have any ideahow many ants there are?
Whoa!
Maybe it's...Maybe it's 248.
No, no!Vertigo, vertigo!
No, I think it's 247.
Wait.
Hang on tight!
I thinkI'm getting the hang of this.
I am controlling 247.He is not listening to you.
What?
- Can I make one little request?- No.
Stop, 247!Time out, time out.
Time out.
All right, hold on.
Just wait! Whoa!
What happensif I throw up in this helmet?
It's my helmet, Scott.You do not throw up.
Let's sether down, all right?
I'm getting light-headed.
Hang on, Scott.
I'm getting a little light...
I need a snooze button.
Hit me in 5 minutes.
Hello.
Who are you?
Have you been standing there,watching me sleep, this whole time?
Yes.
Why?
Because the last time you were here,you stole something.
Oh. Oh.
Hey, look...
Whoa!
Paraponera clavata.
Giant tropical bullet ants,
ranked higheston the Schmidt pain index.
They're here tokeep an eye on you when I can't.
Dr. Pym's waitingfor you downstairs.
Who?
Hey!
Um... Whose pajamas are these?
How am I supposed to do this?
All right,just one step at a time.
Ugh!
You don't bite me,I don't step on you. Deal?
I could take down the servers
and Crosswouldn't even know it.
We don't need this guy.
I assume that you've alreadymet my daughter, Hope.
I did. She's great.
She doesn't thinkthat we need you.
We don't.We can do this ourselves.
I go to all this effortto let you steal my suit,
and then Hopehas you arrested.
Okay, we can try this and when he fails,I'll do it myself.
She's a little bit anxious.
It has to do with this job,
which, judging by the factthat you're sitting opposite me,
I take it thatyou're interested in.
What job?
Would you like some tea?
Uh... Sure.
I was very impressed with
how you managed to getpast my security system.
Freezing that metalwas particularly clever.
Were you watching me?
Scott, I've beenwatching you for a while.
Ever since yourobbed Vista Corp.
Oh! Excuse me.
"Burgled" Vista Corp.
Vista's securitysystem was one of
the most advancedin the business.
It was supposedto be unbeatable.
But you beat it.
Would you like some sugar?
Yeah, thanks.
You know what? I'm okay.
How do you make them do that?
Ants can lift objects50 times their weight.
They build, farm,they cooperate with each other.
Right. But how do youmake them do that?
I use electromagnetic wavesto stimulate their olfactory nerve center.
I speak to them.
I can go anywhere,hear anything,
and see everything.
And still knowabsolutely nothing.
I'm late to meet Cross.
Uh... Dr. Pym?
You don't need toraise your hand, Scott.
Sorry,I just have one question.
Who are you, who is she,what the hell's going on,
and can I go back to jail now?
Come with me.
40 years ago,I created a formula
that altered atomicrelative distance.
Huh?
I learned how to changethe distance between atoms.
That's what powers the suit.
That's why it works.
Wow.
- Whoa!- But it was dangerous.
It was too dangerous.
So I hid it from the world.
And that's when I switched gearsand I started my own company.
Pym Tech.
Yes.
I took on a young protegecalled Darren Cross.
Darren Cross.
He's a big deal.
But before he was a big deal,he was my assistant.
I thought I saw something in him.The son I never had, perhaps.
He was brilliant,but as we became close,
he began to suspectthat I wasn't telling him everything.
He heard rumors aboutwhat was called the Pym Particle,
and he became obsessedwith recreating my formula.
But I wouldn't help him.
So he conspired against me andhe voted me out of my own company.
How could he do that?
The board's chairmanis my daughter, Hope.
She was the deciding vote.
But she came back to me
when she saw how closeCross was to cracking my formula.
The process is highly volatile.
If one isn't protectedby a specialized helmet,
it can affectthe brain's chemistry.
I don't thinkDarren realizes this,
and, you know, he's notthe most stable guy to begin with.
So, what do you want from me?
Scott, I believe that everyone deservesa shot at redemption.
Do you?
I do.
If you can help me,
I promise I can help you bewith your daughter again.
Now, are you readyto redeem yourself?
Absolutely.
My days of breaking into placesand stealing shit are done.
What do you want me to do?
I want you to break into a placeand steal some shit.
Are you gonna be homefor dinner tonight?
Uh, yeah.I'll pick something up.
Text me.
Okay. Good news?
Uh... I don't know. It's news.
Are you tryingto find my daddy?
Yeah, I am, sweetheart.
I just want yourdaddy to be safe.
Hope you don't catch him.
This isn'tthe first time these guys
have tried to get their handson game-changing weaponry.
That's Mitchell Carson,Ex-Head of Defense at S.H.I.E.L.D.
Presently in the businessof toppling governments.
He always wanted my tech.
And now, unless we break inand steal the Yellowjacket
and destroy all the data,
Darren Cross is gonna unleash chaosupon the world.
I think our first move should becalling the Avengers.
I spent half my life
trying to keep this technologyout of the hands of a Stark.
I'm sure as hell not gonnahand-deliver it to one now.
This is not some cute technologylike the Iron Man suit.
This could changethe texture of reality.
Besides,they're probably too busy
dropping citiesout of the sky.
Okay, then why don't youjust send the ants?
Scott, they are ants.
Ants, they can do a lot of things,but they still need a leader.
Somebody that couldinfiltrate a place
that's designed toprevent infiltration.
Hank, I'm a thief, all right?I mean,
I'm a good thief,but this is insane.
He's right, Hank.And you know it.
You've seen the footage,you know what Cross is capable of.
I was against using himwhen we had months,
and now we have days.
I'm wearing the suit.
Absolutely not!
I know the facility inside and out.I know how Cross thinks.
I know this missionbetter than anybody here.
We need you close to Cross.Otherwise, this mission cannot work.
We don't havetime to screw around!
Hope, pleaselisten to me...
He is a criminal!I'm your daughter.
No!
She's right, Hank.
I'm not your guy.
Why don't you wear the suit?
You think I don't want to?
I can't.
I spent years wearing it,
and it took a toll on me.
You're our only option.
Before Hope lost her mother,
she used to look at me likeI was the greatest man in the world.
And now she looks at meand there's just disappointment.
It's too late for me,
but not for you.
This is your chance.
The chance to earn that lookin your daughter's eyes.
To become the herothat she already thinks you are.
It's not aboutsaving our world.
It's about saving theirs.
Damn. That was a good speech.
Scott,
I need you to be the Ant-Man.
In the right hands,
the relationshipbetween man and suit is symbiotic.
The suit has power.The man harnesses that power.
You need to be skillful,agile, and above all,
you need to be fast.
You should be ableto shrink and grow
on a dime.
So your sizealways suits your needs.
Now dive through the keyhole,Scott.
You charge big, you dive small,then you emerge big.
Ow!
Ahhh!
Useless.
When you're small,energy's compressed,
so you have the forceof a 200-pound man
behind a fist a 100th of an inch wide.You're like a bullet.
You punch too hard, you kill someone.Too soft, it's a love tap.
In other words,you have to know how to punch.
I was in prison for three years.I know how to punch.
Show me.
- Terrible.- You wanna show me how to punch?
Show me...
That's how you punch.
She's beenlooking forward to this.
No kidding.
Hope trained in martial artsat a difficult time.
Oh, by "difficult time,"he means when my mother died.
We lost her in a plane crash.
It's bad enoughyou won't tell me how she died.
Could you please stoptelling me that lie?
We're working, here.
All right, princess.Let's get back to work.
Were you going for the hand?
You know, I think this regulatoris holding me back.
Do not screwwith the regulator.
If thatregulator is compromised,
you would go subatomic.
What does that mean?
It means that you would entera quantum realm.
It means that youwould enter a reality
where all conceptsof time and space
become irrelevant
as you shrinkfor all eternity.
Everything that you know
and love,
gone forever.
Cool.Yeah, if it ain't broke...
You've learned about the suit,
but you've yet to learnabout your greatest allies,
the ants.
Loyal, brave,
and your partners on this job.
Paratrechina longicornis.Commonly known as crazy ants.
They're lightning fastand can conduct electricity,
which makes them usefulto fry out enemy electronics.
You're not so crazy.
Hey!
You're cute.
That was a lotscarier a second ago.
It looks like the Futures Labhas its own isolated power supply.
There's a securityguard posted around the clock.
We'll need you to take him outto deactivate the security systems.
Okay, who's next?
Paraponera clavata.
I know.Bullet ants, right?
Number 1 onthe Schmidt pain index?
Hey, guys.Remember me from the bedroom?
The Yellowjacket podis hermetically sealed,
and the onlyaccess point is a tube
we estimate to be about5 millimeters in diameter.
Why do I have a sick feelingin my stomach?
The tube is protectedby a laser grid,
and we can onlypower that down for 15 seconds.
You're gonna need to signalthe crazy ants to blow the servers,
retrieve the suit,and exit the vaults
beforethe backup power comes on.
Camponotus pennsylvanicus.
Alternatively knownas a carpenter ant.
Ideal for groundand air transport.
Wait a minute,I know this guy.
I'm gonna callhim "Ant-thony."
That's good. That's very good.
Because this time,you're really gonna
have to learnhow to control him.
Tell them to putthe sugar in the teacup.
Aw! You okay? Did I hurt...
Hank wants you outsidefor target practice.
The suit has no weapons,so I made you these discs.
Red shrinks.
Blue enlarges.
Solenopsis mandibularis.
Known for their bite,
the fire ants have evolvedinto remarkable architects.
They are handy toget you in and out of difficult places.
You can do it, Scott. Come on.
They're not listening to me.
You have to commit.You have to mean it.
No shortcuts, no lies.
Throwinginsults into the mix
will not doanyone any good, Hope.
We don't have time for coddling.
Our focus shouldbe on helping Scott!
Really?
Is that where ourfocus should be?
Hope!
I don't know why I came to youin the first place.
We can't do this without her.
Oh, God.
You gotta lock your doors.
I mean, really, there's some weird folksin this neighborhood.
Do you think this is a joke?
Do you have any idea whathe's asking you to risk?
You have a daughter.
I'm doing this for her.
You know, when my mother died,I didn't see him for two weeks.
He was in grief.
Yeah,so was I, and I was seven.
And he never came back.Not in any way that counted.
He just sent me offto boarding school.
You know, I thought,
with all that's at stake,
just maybe we might havea chance of making peace.
But, even now,he still wants to shut me out.
He doesn't wanna shut you out.He trusts you.
Then why are you here?
It proves that he loves you.
Hope. Look at me.
I'm expendable.
That's why I'm here.
You must haverealized that by now.
I mean, it's why I'm in the suitand you're not.
He would ratherlose this fight than lose you.
Anyway...
You know, I didn't knowyou had a daughter
when I called the cops on you.
What's her name?
Cassie.
It's a pretty name.
You have to clearyour mind, Scott.
You have to makeyour thoughts precise.
That's how it works.
Think about Cassie.
About how badly you want to see her.And use that to focus.
Open your eyes
and just think aboutwhat you want the ants to do.
That's good!
Your mother convinced me
to let her joinme on my missions.
They called her the Wasp.
She was born to it.
And there's nota day that goes by
that I don'tregret having said yes.
It was 1987.
Separatists had hijackeda Soviet missile silo in Kursk
and launched an ICBMat the United States.
The only way tothe internal mechanics
was through solid titanium.
I knew I had to shrink betweenthe molecules to disarm the missile.
But my regulator had sustainedtoo much damage.
Your mother,
she didn't hesitate.
Janet! No!
She turned off her regulator
and went subatomic
to deactivate the bomb.
And she was gone.
Your mom died a hero.
And I spent the next 10 years
trying to learn all I couldabout the quantum realm.
You were tryingto bring her back.
But all I learnedwas we know nothing.
It's not your fault.
She made her choice.
But why didn't you tell me that sooner?
I was trying to protect you.
I lost your mother.
I didn't meanto lose you, too.
I'm sorry.
This is awesome.
It's awesome, you know?
You guys are breaking down walls,you're healing.
It's important.
I ruined the moment, didn't I?
Yes, you did. Yes.
I'm going to make some tea.
Nailed it!
That's a good boy, Ant-thony.
The final phase of your trainingwill be a stealth incursion.
It's freezing!
You couldn't make a suitwith a flannel lining?
You must retrieve this prototypeof a signal decoy.
It's a device that I inventedduring my S.H.I.E.L.D. days.
We need it to counteractthe transmission blockers
that Cross installedin the Futures vault.
It's currently collecting dust
in one of Howard Stark's oldstorage facilities in upstate New York.
Should be a piece of cake.
You're over the target area.
Disengage now, Scott!
Squadron A, go!
B, go!
C, go!
All right, Ant-thony,please don't drop me this time.
Oh, it feels like a big leapfrom sugar cubes to this!
Stay calm.
Guys?We might have a problem.
Hank, didn't you saythis was some old warehouse?
It's not!
You son of a bitch!
- Scott, get out of there.- Abort!
Abort now!
No, it's okay. It doesn't looklike anyone's home.
Ant-thony, get me to the roof!
He's gonna lose the suit.
He's gonna lose his life.
All right, I'm on the roofof the target building.
Somebody's home, Scott.
What's going ondown there, Sam?
It's the Falcon!
I had a sensor tripbut I'm not seeing anything.
Wait a second.
Abort, Scott! Abort now!
It's okay. He can't see me.
I can see you.
He can see me.
Hi. I'm Scott.
Did he just say,"Hi, I'm Scott"?
What are you doing here?
First off, I'm a big fan.
Appreciate it.So, who the hell are you?
I'm Ant-Man.
"Ant-Man"?
What? You haven't heard of me?
No, you wouldn'thave heard of me.
You wanna tellme what you want?
I was hoping I could graba piece of technology.
Just for a few days.I'm gonna return it.
I need it to save the world.You know how that is.
I know exactly how that is.
Located the breach.
- Bringing him in.- Sorry about this!
What the hell are you doing?
Breach is an adult male,
who has some sortof shrinking tech.
Sorry!
Look, I'm sorry about this.Sorry.
That's enough!
Ant-thony! A little help!
I've lost visual.
He's inside my pack!
Sorry!
You seem likea really great guy.
It's really important to methat Cap never finds out about this.
That was completely irresponsibleand dangerous!
You jeopardized everything!
You got it.
Well done.
Wait a minute.
Did you just compliment me?
He did, didn't he?
Kind of sounded like he did.
I was good, wasn't I?
Hey, how about the fact thatI fought an Avenger and didn't die?
Let us not dwell on the past.
We gotta finish our planning.
Don't mind him.
You did good.
Darren.
How the hell didyou get in here?
You leftthe front door open, Hank.
It's official.
You're old.
The plans.
He will kill him.
Well, to what do Iowe this pleasure?
I have good news.
Really?
What's that?
Pym Tech,the company you created,
is about tobecome one of the most
profitableoperations in the world.
We're anticipating $15 billion in sales,tomorrow alone.
You're welcome.
I know this is odd,but I'd like you to be there.
This is my moment.I want you to see it.
Sure, Darren. Yeah, sure.
I'll be there.
What did you see in me?
I don't know what you mean.
All those years ago,you picked me.
What did you see?
I saw myself.
Then why did you push me away?
Because I sawtoo much of myself.
He knows.He's baiting you.
We have to call it off.
We're all taking risks.
What if he saw me here?
He didn't. There's no way.
How do you know that?
Darren, hi.
Hope, where are you right now?
I'm at home. Why?
I just saw Hank.
I still get nothingbut contempt from him.
Don't let him rile you up.He's just a senile old man.
We need to starteveryone working around the clock.
Get the assemblyline up and running.
And I'm tripling security.
Full sensors at all entrances
and exterior air ventsfitted with steel micro-mesh.
Great. Good idea.
Thank you, Hope.I'm so lucky to have you on my team.
He's tripling security.He's lost his mind, and he's onto you.
But he is not onto you.
He's adding full body scannersto all entrances
and closing exterior vents.
How are we gonnaget Scott inside?
The water main.
You can't addsecurity to a water main.
The pressure is too strong,but if we can decrease it,
that's how I get in.
Somebody would have to reachthe building's control center
to change the water pressure.
Hank and I willbe beside Cross.
How are wesupposed to do that?
So we expand our team.
What do we need?
A fake securityguard on the inside
to de-pressurizethe water system,
somebody else to hack into the power supply
and kill the laser grid,
and a getaway guy.
No, no. No, no, no.Not those three wombats.
No way.
Thank you forthe coffee, ma'am.
It's not too often that you rob a placeand then get welcomed back.
Because we just robbed you.
You know that he was arrestedfor stealing a smoothie machine, right?
Two smoothie machines.
Are you sure theycan handle this?
Oh, we can handle it.We're professionals.
You'll forgive us if we're notinstilled with confidence.
Well, hey, everybody just kick backand relax a little bit, man.
We know our business.
We broke into thisspooky-ass house, didn't we?
I let you.
Well, one could saythat I let you let me.
Look, it's okay.They can handle this.
Yeah, we can handle it.
- You got their credentials?- He's in the system.
I'm in the system?
You're in the system.
The system?
Yeah, we're doomed.
All right.
There's somethingyou guys need to see.
When you get to this corner,
there's gonna be three officeson your left side.
Damn!
Whoa! That's so cool, bro!
Now, look,this is gonna get weird, all right?
It's pretty freaky,but it's safe.
There's noreason to be scared.
Oh, no, no.Daddy don't get scared.
- Really?- Yeah.
Good.
This is the work of gypsies.
That's witchcraft.
Wow, that's amazing.
That's like someDavid Copperfield shit.
That's some kind of wizardry.
This is sorcery!
How'd you do that, bro?
Don't freak out.Look at your shoulder.
Ahhh!
Get off! Get off!
Wait, I thoughtDaddy didn't get scared!
I gave them each half a Xanax
and Hank explained the scienceof the suit to them.
They fell right asleep.
Hey, look,I wanna thank you for...
No, please don't.
We're all doingthis for reasons
much biggerthan any one of us.
I'm just gladthat you might have
a slight chance ofmaybe pulling this off.
Hey, thank you, you know,for that pep talk.
You know, the honest truth is,I actually went from despising you
to almost liking you.
You reallyshould write poetry.
Get some sleep, Scott.
All right,just so we're clear,
everyone here knowstheir role, right?
- Dave?- Wheels on the ground.
- Kurt?- Eyes in the sky.
- Luis?- Oh, man, you know it.
You know what?I get to wear a uniform.
- That's what's up.- Luis.
I'm sorry. I'm good. I'm good.I'm just excited.
Plus,your girlfriend's really hot.
So, you know,that makes me nervous, too.
And you are very beautiful,ma'am.
- Oh, my Lord.- She's not my...
You know what?I was thinking of
a tactic,like when I go undercover.
Like a whistling. You know what I'm saying?To like, blend in.
No.Don't whistle. No whistling.
It's not The Andy Griffith Show.No whistling.
All clear in Sector One.
Step out.
All clear.
We're set.
Wish me luck.
Utilities online.
Hey! What are you doing?
Uh... Boss-man said to secure the area,so I'm securing it.
I'm the boss.
- Oh.- Utilities 1.3...
Water level is dropping!
Coming up on extraction pipe.
All right, I see it.
All right, come on,I gotta get up there.
That's it.That's it, guys! Yes!
Yes! You got it!You got it! Come on!
All right,let's fly, Ant-thony.
The Ant-Man isin the building.
Pym's pulling up.Right on time.
Got a Crown Vicright outside there.
This is problem?
Considering the Crown Vic'sthe most commonly used car
for undercover cops, man,
yes, this is problem.
That's Pym.
Oh, no.
I'mdeploying the bullet ants.
Papanera Clairede Merna Merna...
I don't remember what it's called,but I feel bad for this guy.
- What's up, man?- Hey.
Ow! Ow!
See? That's whatI'm talking about.
That's what I callan unfortunate casualty
in a very serious operation.
Signal decoy in place.
Mean,pretty lady did good, Scott.
Looks like Pym's getting arrested.
Scott, we have problem.
Problem?What's the problem?
Dave! Dave,that's not part of plan!
Listen to me.
If I don't get into this building,people will die.
That's awfully dramatic.
Are you kidding me?
Problem solved.
Well...
How do I look?
There he is.
Just in time. Come on.
12-point verification.
Little over-the-top,don't you think, Darren?
Confirming authorization level.
Well,you can never be too safe.
Access granted.
Gotta hand it to you, Darren.
You really did it.
And you only knowthe half of it, Hank.
Arriving in second position.
All right, top speed,Ant-thony. Let's go!
Proceeding to command position.
I'll be right back, Ant-thony.
All right, guys.I'm in position.
I'm gonna signal the ants.
No, no, no, no, no!
Did you see that?
Assume formation.
All right,you cute little crazies,
let's fry these servers!
Let's go get 'em, buddy!
Servers are fried.
Data backup completely erased.
Heading to the particle chamber.
Hello, Dr. Cross.
My associates have agreedto your terms.
Wonderful.
Mr. Carson introduced meto these fine gentlemen here.
They'rerepresentatives of Hydra.
They're not what they were.
They're doing someinteresting work.
And I'm enjoying myself.
You tried to hideyour technology from me.
And now it's gonnablow up in your face.
Wow.
Wow! I mean, I saw that punch cominga mile away,
but I just figured it'dbe all pathetic and weak.
Well, you figured wrong.
I know this van.
Anybody home?
All right, guys. I'm here.
I'm setting the charges.
Great job, guys.I'll take it from here.
Good boy, Ant-thony.
Final position.
Guys, how we lookingon that laser grid?
- Almost.- No, you're not.
- I'm getting close!- No, you're not.
San Francisco P.D.!
Out of the van!
I know you're in there!
Make it go faster.
Dude, seriously.
Ready to jump.Do you read, Kurt?
So close.
- Okay, hold up! Wait a minute!- Freeze!
There was a black guythat looked exactly like me
who attacked us and put usin the back of this disgusting van.
- Get out of the van!- Okay, I'm coming.
Take it easy!
No, I will not move!Go now!
Wait!
What?What do you mean, "Wait"?
Phew!
What? What?
Hey, little guy.
I always suspected you hada suit stored away somewhere.
Which begs the question,
who is the new Ant-Man?
Who is the manthat my beloved mentor
trusted even more than me?
Scott Lang.
A martyr
who took on the systemand paid the price,
losing his familyand his only daughter in the process.
Exactly yourkind of guy, Hank!
He escapes his jail cellwithout leaving any clue as to how.
And then hedisappears magically,
despite having nomoney to his name.
And now he bringsme the Ant-Man suit.
The only thing thatcan rival my creation.
Darren, don't do this.
If you sell to these men,
it's gonna be chaos.
I already have.
And for twice the price,
thanks to you.
It's not easy to successfully infiltratean Avengers facility.
Thankfully, word travels fast.
I'll sell themthe Yellowjacket,
but I'm keepingthe particle to myself.
They don't run on diesel.
If you want the fuel,you'll have to come to me.
What do you call the only man
who can arm the mostpowerful weapon in the world?
The most powerfulman in the world.
You proud of me yet?
You can stop this, Darren.It's not too late.
It's been too latefor a long time now.
Darren!
What are you doing?
He wasn't any more capable ofcaring for you than he was for me.
This is not who you are.
It's the particles alteringyour brain chemistry.
Wait! Wait, wait, wait, wait.
You're right. I haveto be the one to do it.
Here we go.
Drop your gun.
You know, I came to the housethe other night to kill him,
but you were there.
You're sick and I can help you.Just put the gun down.
I wasn't readyto kill you then,
but I think I am now!
Drop your gun now!
You pickedthe wrong side, Hope.
Dad!
Hank, no.
No, Hank.
Hank?Listen, you're gonna be okay.
All right? You're gonna be just fine.
Take the suit off, or I'll blowyour brains out and peel it off.
Thanks Goldenbeard
We got a 10-33 at Pym Tech.
Request immediate backup!
Go, go, go!
Get me to the roof.
And radio ahead.
I want to make sure the helicopteris ready to take off.
You two,
kill anything thatcomes out of that vault!
Dad, can you move?
We need to gethim out of here.
Go get that suit.
Hey, Scotty.
Hey, did I save your life?
Scotty?
Thank you, Luis.
- Are we the good guys?- Yeah.
We're the good guys, right?
Yeah, we're the good guys.
Feels kinda weird, you know.
Yeah, but we're not done yet.
Get out of herebefore this place blows!
Damn it! That guy.
Hey!We're getting out of here!
The charges are set.
We've gotta find a way out of here.And fast.
Don't worry.
I'm not gonna die.
And neither are you.
It's not a keychain.
It's total chaos in here!Multiple shots fired!
And there's a tank.
A little help!
I got it.
We need a doctor!
We've got him.
Thank you.
Let's go!
Ant-thony!
Go!
You're gonna regret that.
Wait a minute!Get out of that van!
- What?- Get out of that van!
It's too loud, there's a tank.I can't hear you!
Hey! Hey!
Are you crazy?Put the gun down!
The windows!
Did you think you couldstop the future with a heist?
It was never just a heist!
Put the gun down!
Okay, I got him, I got him.There he is! Go, go, go!
We gotta set herdown somewhere.
I'm gonna disintegrate you!
Playing Disintegrationby the Cure.
Call 911!
It's okay.
Freeze! Put your hands up!Get them up!
Scott?
Paxton,you have to listen to me!
Paxton, turn around!Take me back!
I am taking you back.To prison.
There's something in that backyardthat needs to be destroyed.
In the bug zapper. There...
You need to desist right now!Your delusions are out of hand.
All units, we have a 2-36
in progress at840 Winter Street.
- Cassie!- That's my house.
Don't be scared.
Paxton, let me help!
Don't move.
Let me help!
Maggie! What's going on?
He's got Cassie!
- Who's got Cassie, honey?- That thing.
- Thing?- I don't know! I don't know!
Are you a monster?
Do I look like a monster?
I want my daddy!
I want your daddy, too.
There you are.
Daddy, is that you?
Hi, peanut.
Why don't you pick onsomeone your own size?
Now,where did you go, little guy?
There you are.
Not just me!
Damn it!
Go! Go!
Scotty needs us,you know what I'm saying?
Ain't nothing gonna stop us.
Back it up.
Back it up, slow.
Yeah.
- Back it up.- Yeah.
- Back it up.- Okay.
- We just back it up, okay?- That's it.
- Back it up.- That's right.
Backin' up?
Yep, just backin' up.
No, no. Just back it up.
You insult me, Scott.
Your very existenceis insulting to me.
You know, it'd be much easier to hit youif you were bigger.
Yeah, I agree.
Cassie!
I'm gonna show youjust how insignificant you are.
Cassie! I'm coming!
That'sa messed-up looking dog.
I'm gonna destroy
everything you love.
Freeze! S.F.P.D.
I can't break through.
It's titanium, you idiot!
- Get her out of here.- Come on.
Sorry, sweetheart.
You have to help Daddypay for his mistakes.
- You stay behind me, okay?- Okay.
Stay behind me.
I'm gonna have to shrinkbetween the molecules to get in there.
Get away from us!
Daddy, help!
I love you, Cassie.
Daddy, where are you?
You could go subatomic.
Oh, no.
You would enter a reality
where all conceptsof time and space...
All concepts of time and spacebecome irrelevant.
...all concepts of time and spacebecome irrelevant.
Come back, Daddy!
...as you shrink for all eternity.
Everything that you know
and love,
gone forever.
Daddy, where are you?
Where are you?
- Daddy!- Cassie.
Come back, Daddy!
Do not screwwith the regulator!
Daddy!
I love you so much.
I love you, too.
So much.
You know, there'sa big hole in the roof.
Sorry.
- Is she all right?- Yeah, she's fine.
Mommy!
She's fine, she's fine.
Scott, please.
You don't remember anything?
Hank. I don't.
There must be something else.
Well, I suppose the human mind
just can'tcomprehend the experience,
but you made it.
You went in,
and you got out.
It's amazing.
Scott,
I'll walk you out.
Get some rest.
Is it possible?
When did this happen?
Nothing's happening.
Whoa. Hold on.Something's kind of happening.
Well, if that's the case,
shoot me again.
Yeah. I don't knowwhat you were doing,
grabbing andkissing me like that.
I'm a little surprised myself.
I have to get somewhere.I'll see you later, Hank.
Really, Hope.
- Scott.- Yeah?
- You're full of shit.- Oh, yeah.
Scott,I met with my captain today.
He wanted a report on the nightthat you got out of jail.
Something happenedwith the cameras.
Some circuits got fried.
But I told him thatyou were processed correctly.
Really?
Well, yeah.
Can't be sending Cassie's dadback to jail on a technical glitch, right?
Thank you, Paxton.
I'm blown away.
Thank you for everythingyou do for Cassie.
Well, that's my pleasure.
But, no.This one, I did for you.
- This is awkward.- Yeah.
Yeah.
I mean, what do we even talk aboutafter all of that?
- Oh, I know.- What?
I did my firstcartwheel today.
What?
Yeah. She has beenpracticing all week.
But today was the magic day.
I recorded it on my phone.Here.
No, that can't be Cassie.That's not you.
- Yeah, it is.- Yeah, it is.
This is a professional gymnast.There is no way that's you.
Yeah, that's her.
Good boy.
Sweetie, that'spretty amazing, peanut.
Sorry.
It's work.
Yeah.
All right.
Here's the deal.Just give me the facts.
Just the facts.Only the facts.
Breathe.Focus. Keep it simple.
No, no, no.No doubt, no doubt. Okay.
So, I'm at this art museumwith my cousin Ignacio, right?
And there was this, like,abstract expressionism exhibit.
But you know me, I'm morelike a Neo-Cubist kind of guy, right?
But there was this one Rothkothat was sublime, bro! Oh, my God!
Luis.
Okay, sorry. Sorry.
You know,I just get excited and stuff.
But anyway, Ignacio tells me,
"Yo, I met thiscrazy-fine writer chick
"at the Spot last night.Like fine-fine.
"Like crazy-stupid fine."And he
"goes up tothe bartender and goes,
"Look at the girl I'm with.You know what I'm sayin'?
"She'scrazy-stupid fine, right?"
The bartender's all like,"Yeah, crazy-stupid fine."
So this writerchick tells Ignacio,
"Yo, I'm like a bossin the world of guerrilla journalism,
"and I got mad connectswith the peeps behind the curtains,
"you know what I'm saying?"
Ignacio's like, "For real?"
And she's like,"Yeah, you know what,
I can't tell youwho my contact is,
"because he workswith the Avengers."
Oh, no.
Yeah, and this dude soundslike a badass, man.
Like,he comes up to her and says,
"Yo, I'm looking for this dudewho's new on the scene,
"who's flashinghis fresh tack,
"who's got, like, bomb moves, right?Who you got?"
And she's like,"Well, we got everything
nowadays.We got a guy who jumps.
"We got a guy who swings,we got a guy who crawls up the walls.
"You gotta be more specific."
And he's like,"I'm looking for a guy that shrinks."
And I'm, like, "Damn!"I got all nervous
'cause I'd keep madsecrets for you, bro.
So I asked Ignacio,
"Did the badass tellthe stupid-fine writer chick
"to tell you to tell me,because I'm tight with Ant-Man,
"that he's looking for him?"
And? What'd he say?
He said, "Yes."
There's somethingI want to show you.
I realized youcan't destroy power.
All you can do is make surethat it's in the right hands.
This is an advanced prototype
that your mother and Iworked on together.
She never got to use it.
But now I realize that we were...We were working on it for you.
Maybe it's timewe finished it.
It's about damn time.
Hey, Cap!
This would havebeen a lot easier a week ago.
- If we call Tony...- He won't believe us.
Even if he did...
Who knows if the Accordswill let him help.
We're on our own.
Maybe not.
I know a guy.