jmg subs
AMNESTY BAY, MAINE 1985
Jules Verne once wrote :
"Put two ships in the open sea,
without wind or tide,
it will come together."
That's how my parents met.
Like two ships destined
for each other.
We are something else.
Try our new features.
It's okay.
Easy, easy, easy.
You weren't breathing.
They were from
different worlds.
But life, like the sea, has a
way of bringing people together.
Um...
I was going to make
you some eggs.
Just don't eat my dog, okay?
It's okay.
I made tea.
Come on, try it.
It'll make you better.
So, um, who are you?
Atlanna.
Queen of Atlantis.
Wow.
I'm Tom.
Keeper of lighthouse.
Huh.
She had fled an arranged marriage,
left her whole world behind.
But in my father's lighthouse
she found something
unexpected.
And my father...
...found the love of his life.
Category 4 hurricane 'Arthur' is
due to make landfall sometime...
You know, how
about Arthur?
After the hurricane?
After our own ancient.
He's a king, isn't he?
He's more than that.
He's living proof our people
can co-exist.
He could unite our
worlds one day.
And the Trident could only be
wielded by the strongest atlantean.
And it gave king atlan
mastery over the seven seas.
It made him so powerful that the
ocean itself became  jealous,
and sent a terrible earthquake
to destroy Atlantis.
Oh, down it fell to the
bottom of the ocean.
But, legend has it that one day
a new king will come
who will use the
power of the Trident
to put Atlantis
back together again.
Tom, take him!
Queen Atlanna, by the
authority of King Orvax,
you're ordered to
return to Atlantis.
Atlanna!
But Atlanna's
memory is long.
And it's a king who
refuses to let her go.
- Atlanna!
- Tom!
- My weapon!
- Here!
Their two worlds were
never meant to meet
and I was a product of a love
that never should have been.
You don't have to do this, Atlanna.
Please.
No.
They will always find me.
Next time they will
send an army.
I have to go back.
It's the only way
to save him.
To save you.
Where I come from..
..the sea carries
our tears away.
Not here.
Here you feel  'em.
I will return to you
when it's safe.
One day...
right here, at sunrise
we'll be together again.
You stay strong,
my little prince.
I'll always be with you.
Don't let him forget me.
Hm?
All life came from the sea,
so if we want to
understand ourselves
we must journey to
where we began.
Now today, we have
better maps of Mars
than we do of
our own sea floor.
Come on! Come on!
Come on fishy!
- Come over here.
- Boys!
- Stop that.
- Come on!
Hi!
Hi, fishy.
My name's Arthur.
What's yours?
- You guys hungry?
- Check it out.
Me too.
Arthur is
talking to the fish.
- You're such a prick, Arthur.
- Ah!
Stop!
- What are you gonna do about it?
- Freak!
Stop it!
Let me go!
AQUAMAN
PRESENT DAY
Who are you?
Let's go! Move it!
Come on, hurry up!
Sir, we've secured the captain.
Distress signal is disabled.
We're running dark in here.
But they heard it.
You can count on it.
I'll make you a deal.
I won't tell you
how to captain.
And you don't tell me
how to pirate.
Where's the rest of the crew?
They've decided discretion was
the better part of valour
and sealed themselvs
up in a torpido bay.
Our reputation precedes us.
Your reputation.
This is your win.
Here.
You take this piece of junk
as a part of your life.
I never told you
the story behind it.
This was your grandfather's.
He was one of the navy's first
frogmen during World War 2.
He was so stealthy in the water.
His unit nicknamed him Manta.
But after the war, his country
forgot about him.
So he went back to the seas,
scavenging and surviving with his wit.
And this knife, he gave it to me
when I was your age.
And now,
it's yours, son.
We just hit something.
No. Something hit us.
- Sir, there's something out there.
- Another submarine?
Um...no.
I think it's a man.
That's not a man.
Alpha, to the right.
Bravo team,switch the passageway.
Permission to come aboard?
No way!
Aquaman!
I've waited a long time for this.
Am I supposed to know
who you are?
I scavenge the high seas.
You're the Aquaman.
We were bound to
meet at some point.
Let's not make it a habit.
Up!
Ow!
Dad!
Dad? Ow!
That's your kid?
Shame on you.
You get yourselves into this mess,
get yourselves out of this.
Bastard!
Dad!
Wait! Help me!
He's trapped!
You can't leave him like that!
Please!
You killed innocent people.
You ask the sea for mercy.
Get out of here!
I've got this!
Shut up!
I'm not leaving you!
Hey! Hey!
You need to live so you can
kill that son of a bitch.
- Now, go!
- No!
- Go!
- Shut up!
Go!
No!
Damn you!
Go.
I'll always know
where to find you.
Old habits.
- Come on, I'll buy you breakfast.
- Oh, yeah!
You want me to have them
put that in a sippy cup for you?
How is it that I can
breathe underwater
but can still drink
under the table ?
That's my superpower.
---late last night by
high-tech pirates.
The same pirate
who are suspected
in connection with the
disappearance of the Navy's
highly classified prototype
stealth submarine.
And in further development, we
now have unconfirmed reports
that the meta-human dubbed by
social media as the 'Aquaman'
was responsible for
this daring rescue…
- It's not me.
- Oh shit.
You're doing it,
aren't you? Hah?
What Vulko trained you to do.
I knew you couldn't stand
on the sidelines forever.
Your mother always
knew you were special.
Don't even start.
She believed you'd be the one
to unite our two worlds.
Please, stop.
Whatever Atlantis's problems
are, you're bigger than them.
Atlantis murdered
my mother.
- You don't know that for sure.
- Yes, I do.
They killed her
for loving you
and having me.
And you know it.
Son, one day you're going to
have to stop blaming yourself.
Hey, buddy.
Are you that fish boy
from the TV?
Oh, great!
It's Fishman.
What do you want?
I'll tell you what I want.
Can I get a picture
with you?
You're like our
local hero, man.
It would mean a lot.
Just.. quick...
- Whatever.
- Alright. Let's do this.
-  Dont' touch me.
- That's right.
That’s exactly right.
I’d want to go down here.
There we go.
Everybody smile.
SOMEWHERE IN THE ATLANTIC OCEAN
He understands the
significance of this meeting.
He'll hear you out.
King Orm.
King Nereus.
You've picked the meeting at a place too
close to the surface of my liking.
You don't recognise the
council of the kings?
King Atlan's times the
seven kings were one.
Our ancestors
gathered here.
Liked to sat here with
the head of the table.
Xebel was always by his side.
Brine, Fishermen,
Deserters and Trench
had not yet fallen.
Lost nation had
not yet vanished.
Together, we were the greatest
empire the world had ever seen.
And now, our throne shackled
by archaic laws and politics,
while the threat above
us grows undeniable.
Violence has always
plagued the surface.
They will destroy themselves.
Not before destroying us first.
We have been
hiding long enough.
The time has come for
Atlantis to rise again.
We honour you
King Nereus…
by inviting Xebel to be the first kingdom
to join King Orm's alliance.
As if you had a choice, Vulko.
By law, you need four to seven
kingdoms to send an attack.
The lost nations and the
Deserters have long perished.
The Trench are
nothing but anglers.
The Brine wouldn't join you, and
the Fishermen are cowards.
Without me and my
army to convince them,
your plans are a stillborn.
But I know what'd
you really want.
Once you've obtained the
pledge of the four kingdoms,
you will be ordained
Ocean master.
That's merely a title.
I'm no fool, king Orm.
As Ocean master you'll be commander of the
greatest military might on this planet.
I'm the natural
choice to lead it.
Are you?
What about the rumours
that there is another?
An Atlantian living
among the surface.
One of royal blood.
You may sit on the
throne of Atlantis.
But your claim is
too weak.
How can you possibly hope
to unite the empire?
My mother's bastard has never
even been to Atlantis.
His loyalty is to the sur---
Surface dwellers!
Launch!
The king is injured!
I'm not trying to
start a war.
The war has already begun.
Then it's time we send them
a message that we're here.
- I'm good.
- Yeah?
- Here's the key.
- Thank you.
Let's go home and
work on your ---
If your grandpops was still alive,
he'd be banging our heads
when we're not finishing it.
But there's plenty
of time for that.
We've got to
get you to bed.
Got it.
- I've been looking for you.
- Oh no. No. No.
I need you to come
with me to Atlantis.
Listen, I'm gonna tell
you the same thing
I told that rusty
starfish Vulko.
Except, nice way
considering you're a lady.
No, thank you.
I'm not interested.
You defeated Steppenwolf
and saved Atlantis.
That had nothing
to do with Atlantis.
Your half brother, king Orm, is about
to declare war upon the surface world.
Billions will die.
Your people and mine.
We must stop him.
And how do you
propose we'd do that?
You re the first born son of
queen Atlanna.
The throne is yours
by birthright.
The only way to stop this war
and save both worlds
is for you to take your rightful
place as King.
You think if I just show up,
Orm's gonna give up the throne?
I'm the bastard son of a
queen your people executed.
Trust me.
I'm no king.
- I agree.
- That's awesome. Go.
But, Vulko seems to believe
in you for some reason.
And that's why I'm here.
Volko has learned the location
of the lost trident of Atlan.
Ooh. Fairy tales.
It's a myth.
It's not a myth.
With the sacred trident,
the people will listen to you.
You can then claim your
birthright and dethrone Orm.
My birthright?
It died with my mother.
But I'll promise you this.
If Orm attacks,
I'll treat him exactly the same
way your people treated her.
With no mercy.
SOMEWHERE IN THE NORTH SEA
That submarine was
barely operational.
But it served its purpose.
One of your kind
intervened.
He is not one of us.
He killed my father!
Our transaction has ended.
Keep the money.
I want Aquaman.
Dad!
Pops!
Come on!
Come on.
- He's not breathing.
- Move! Let me help.
Come on, pops...
Oh!
You know, I don't
even know your name.
It's princess Y'mera
xebella challa﻿.
You may call me Mera.
Thank you, Mera.
Dear god!
This was Orm's doing.
The worst has yet to come.
There's a flash flood warning…
90 percent of the building
have been destroyed…
….unprecedented sites from
all over the world today…
we're seeing warships and trash
washed up by massive waves.
These extraordinary
scenes of coastlines ---
Governments stated emergency
in multiple countries.
Decades of pollution has
been thrown back on to land.
Many are asking the question :
was this a natural disaster?
- Or something else?
- No, no. No.
This was no natural disaster.
They threw out our garbage
and our warships.
This was our first contact
with the people of Atlantis.
There you go again, with your
insane Atlantean theory.
You have absolutely
no proof, Dr. Shin.
Open your eyes.
We already have an Atlantean
living among us
and his name is Aquaman.
What is it?
This is the exact spot that Vulko
gave me my first swimming lesson.
You have to forget all the
teachings of the surface world.
Go deeper, to uncover
your Atlantean instincts.
But I already know
how to swim.
Not even close.
So, we're clear,
I'll help you
stop this war,
then I'm done.
Maybe that's for the best.
The ocean is more than
our life source, Arthur,
it's who we're.
Wait. You can talk
underwater?
Hey, I can talk
underwater too!
This is awesome!
Oh,we can do more
than just talk.
Being an Atlantean means
more than just being
able to breathe water.
Your body is equipped to survive
the extreme cold, and pressure,
and your eyes adjust
to see in the dark.
This is awesome!
So, Vulko...
when can I meet
my mother?
Soon, my young prince.
When you're ready, I will take you to
Atlantis to meet the Queen.
I hid my ship in here.
Listen. I'm not
getting in that thing.
Well, to get to where we're going,
you're gonna have to.
Your fish ship has been
marinated in chum butter.
I might come out
smelling like swamp Butt.
That'd be an improvement.
Yup.Hm.
KINGDOM OF ATLANTIS
What's the point in having
a bridge underwater?
The gateway bridge is
a reminant of the old world.
Source to the only way in
or out of the capital.
Why can't they just
go over the walls?
Security is impenetrable.
Even if they did managed
to evade the guards
they don't get past
the hydro-cannons.
People try to sneak
in all the time.
Yeah, well.
Allright.
What is this?
Customs in border control.
Don't worry.
I've a deplomatic clearence.
Welcome home.
There is a safe house
down in the old city.
The high-borns never
ventured to the sea floor.
We're here.
What is this?
These are air pockets we use as
natural air precaution.
Only the high-borns can
breathe water as well as air.
Plus, it keeps the animals out.
They get kind of messy.
Vulko. Here I am old man.
After all these years,
you finally get what you wanted.
Arthur, I wish it was under
better circumstances.
I can't believe Orm attacked.
It wasn't an attack.
Legally, he's not allowed to yet.
What he did to your surface
warships was merely a warning.
What provoked him?
King Orm and your father were
ambushed by the surface.
By the surface?
I don't think so.
They're still think
Atlantis as a fairytale.
I was there.
A surface warship fired at us.
Now, Xebel sides with Atlantis.
Giving Orm a fleet big enough to force
the other two kingdoms to join him.
If we're gonna prevent this war,
you must dethrone him now.
How many times do
I have to tell you?
-  I don't want to be a king.
- You don't understand.
Once he's named Ocean
master, it will be too late.
The power at his disposal will be
unlike anything you've ever seen.
I'm from the surface. No one's
gonna take me seriously.
Okay?  I don't even
know where to begin.
By winning the hearts
and minds of the people.
By proving to them that you're
worthy, and retrieving this.
I already got one of those.
Not like this one, you don't.
This is the lost
Trident of Atlan.
- Oh, I know the story.
- It's more than a story.
It's real.
It was forged by the greatest
weapon masters in history.
Crafted from Poseidon's
steel, for king Atlan,
the first ruler of Atlantis.
Legend says, the Trident was build
with the power to command the sea.
So what happened to it?
To know that, is to go back to
the time before the Great Fall,
When King Atlan ruled
over all that was.
when the kingdoms of
atlantis were one.
It was a time of great prosperity and
technological advancement.
We've had unlocked the secret of
unlimited energy at a time
when the rest of the world's still
thought the earth was flat.
But we became
too ambitious,
too hungry for power.
The ocean swallowed us
and Atlantis sank.
But the very power that
collapsed our civilisation,
also paved the way
to our future.
It gave us the ability
to breathe underwater.
And so, we evolved.
Others regressed,
became savage.
And the king lived out
the remainder of his days
in self-imposed exile.
Neither he, nor the Trident
were ever seen again.
One of our archeological teams
uncovered this a few months ago.
It's an ancient recording dating
back to the first dynasty.
I believe it containes Atlan's
final message to his people,
and the whereabouts
of the sacred Trident.
So what does it say?
We don't know.
The technology's too old.
The cylinder bears the markings
of the deserters kingdom.
You must take it there
and retrieve the message.
The clue to Atlan's final resting
place is inside of this.
Border defense. You're under
arrest for illegal entry.
No!
You mustn't be seen here.
I don't suppose you want to
talk about this, do you?
Neither do I.
In the name of his
highness king Orm,
I place you under arrest.
Welcome to Atlantis,
brother.
I can't believe
you're finally here.
I've heard so many
stories about you.
All these years,
I'm ashamed of my mother for
fall in love with a surface dweller.
Ashamed of the fact that I
have a half breed brother
who's heart I wanted to
run my trident through.
But now that you're
finally here before me...
I must admit…
I'm conflicted.
You want conflict?
Would you take these
chains off, little brother?
And we'll see who
gets a run through.
Yes, I see you brought
our mothers weapon.
Is that why you've come
here after all this time?
To kill me?
I came here to stop a maniac
from destroying the world.
I see.
And how do you plan
to stop the atrocities
that the surface
continues to commit?
Because for the centuries
they've polluted our waters
and poisoned our children.
And now, the sky's burned
and our ocean's spoiled.
You've come all this way to take
side against your own people?
There are no sides
on a war like this.
You've clearly chosen a side and
come here to challenge the throne.
If that's what takes
to stop your war!
Are you invoking the
combat of the kings?
Call it whatever you want.
I call it an ass whooping.
Well then perhaps
that's how we'll proceed
- Your majesty!
- Orm please.
Don't you see?
If I defeat the first born son
of Atlanna in front of everyone,
then all seven kingdoms
will have to concede that
I am the one true king.
Your majesty. There is no
victory in feeding the ignorant.
Your brother is
clearly an imbecile.
Your highness, he doesn't
know our ways.
But he's about to
get an education.
Are you officially
challenging me?
Hell, yes! I challenge you.
And when I win---
If you win
I will cease all immediate action.
The war is over.
But if I win,
you're over.
- Let's do it.
- So be it.
Challenge has been made,
and I accept.
Prepare him for
the ring of fire!
Wait. "Ring " what?
How could you be so foolish
to let Orm bait you into a fight?
It seems to me that's
solved all of our problems.
I beat him in battle, the war's over.
I get to go home.
You're a formidable
fighter on land,
but here, you're out of
your element, literally.
Orm has spent his
entire life underwater
training to be a warrior,
training to be the best.
You taught me how
to fight, Cobra kai.
Let's see if you
remember anything.
- So,what's with the big fork?
- That's a Trident.
Now defend yourself!
What the hell is this?
I'll teach you this movement
when you've mastered the Trident.
It's not fair.
This thing is so big and awkward.
Why can't I use a sword?
That's your mother's Trident.
A traditional weapon of royalty.
You'll never be a King
until you've mastered it.
Why'd she never come
to see me, hah?
I told you, when you're ready--
Stop lying to me!
I've done everything
you've ever  asked.
And everytime I pass a test,
you make up another one.
When am I gonna
be good enough?
Did she not love me?
Your mother loved you more
than anything in the world.
But she had to return to Atlantis
to keep you safe.
Her marriage to king Orvax
was arranged a long time ago
so she had to marry
him and bear him a son,
Prince Orm.
When Orvax eventually
found out about you,
he became overwhelmed
with jealousy
and sacrificed her to the
creatures of the trench.
Are you saying
they executed her?
Because she had me?
I remember .....everything.
I have something for you.
It belonged to my mother.
Tell me.
Do you think she would've enjoyed
watching her sons murder each other?
I understand your fear,
your reluctance, Mera.
I surely do...
- I don't want war. I---
- Don't patronize me.
I know you.
What you're doing is
against everything
your mother taught us
when we were children.
- If she were here---
- But she's not here, is she?
What my mother taught
us was treason.
Don't follow her wake.
Alright, so this would be
your 'ring of fire', hah?
How is it work?
Keep your
ass right here?
Vulko, will you escort my
betrothed to the royal box.
Let's go, lady Mera.
Down here, we have a
legend called the Karathen.
An ancient sea
monster so powerful
that even King Atlan
himself feared it.
So he imprisoned it
in the depths of the ocean.
And in that abyss, the
creature bides its time
waiting to rise again.
Atlantis has been
lying and wait.
And now the beast
has awakened.
You know, there was a time
when I wanted to meet
you more than anything,
get to know
my little brother,
let him know
that he wasn't alone.
Then we ran in together.
If only I had known what a
dick you turned out to be.
You're the reason our
mother was executed.
And I've hated you
for it ever since.
But I do not want
to kill you, Arthur.
I'm going to give
you one chance.
Go home.
Do not ever
come back to Atlantis.
You re not going to win this.
A war is coming to the surface,
whether you like it or not.
And I'm bringing the wrath
of the seven seas with me.
You know I can't
let that happen.
I know.
What the hell is that?
The ring of fire!
Shit!
People of Atlantis, hear me.
My brother has come
from the surface
to challenge me
for the throne!
Let us settle this
in the ancient way.
By bloodshed till the gods
make known their will!
Traitor!
You'll get a beating!
Never thought I'd see the
day when my own father
would bow before the
king of Atlantis.
The surface dwellers
drew first blood.
What would you have us do?
Beg them for mercy?
I detest the surface
as much as you do.
But don't you find the timing of
all of this a bit convenient?
You wouldn't be that
gullible, would you?
You want this war
too, don't you?
It's past time the surface dwellers
learn their place in the world.
If this is I must be
done, then so be it.
You have my mother's trident.
powerful....
but flawed like her.
I wield my father's,
and it has never known defeat!
I promised Atlanna
I would protect him.
This isn't a competition.
It's an execution.
I am the one true king!
You waiting for an invitation?
Get in!
Mera!
Hell, yeah!
So what's the plan?
The plan was to recover Atlan's
trident, then challenge Orm.
Ok. So we do things not in order.
Shit happens.
Heads up. We've got
a bogey on our six!
- What does that even mean?
- Bad guys behind us.
- Then just say that!
- Bad guys behind us!
Woah, woah, wait. You said we
shouldn't go over these walls
- I did!
- You said they're hydro-cannons!
I did!
Just shut up!
Oh, shit!
We are not dead yet!
----
Jump!
Here, hold this.
- What are you doing?
- Listen, it worked for Pinnochio.
- Who?
- Never mind, come here. Get in.
Come on!
Great! So, we're
getting eaten.
How'd you even
doing this anyway?
I dont know.
I can hear them sometimes..
and they can hear me.
Right, 'cause you're
both big dumb animals.
- Hey, I just saved your life.
- I saved yours first!
He said, coast is clear.
So, where to now?
To the ocean of sand your
people called the Sahara.
Alright.
WESTERN SAHARA
This plane isn't a passenger one,
hence we get paid
in pirate tresure.
Thanks for the ride buddy.
Oh , my god...
Are you okay?
I've never been so high up.
We're so far from home.
At least you have a home.
Not anymore.
I can never go back.
I betrayed everything when I
saved you from the Coliseum.
Yeah, but you're engaged with the king.
They have to take you back.
Atlantis has many
wonderful things.
- But forgiving does not.
- But you're royalty.
So was your mother.
If  I go back now, I would
be sacrificed to the trench.
Even my own father
wouldn't take me back.
Well,you know...
look on the bright side.
Now you don’t have to marry someone
that you’re not in love with.
My obligation isn't a love.
This is my family
and my nation,
and I've turned
my back on both.
Sometimes we have
to do what's right,
even if our heart
aches against it.
Your highness!
The tracking puts
princess Mera here,
in the deserter kingdom.
You said she was dead.
Apparently not.
Does your brother
still lives as well?
Not for long.
Captain Murk, assemble
a strike force immediately.
No! Mira is to be arrested
- and safely returned to me.
- She betrayed the throne…
She's a daughter of Xebel.
If any harm befalls her,
our coalition is over.
Your highness..
we are now entering the waters
of the Fishermen kingdom.
Securing the alliance of
the other two kingdoms
should be our
immediate concern.
My vizier is correct
as usual.
Arrest them
and bring back King
Nereus's daughter unharmed.
We're here.
Hey, is there anything nearby?
Nothing but deserts for
hundreds of Ks, mate.
- Nothing but deserts---
- He's wrong!
Hey! What are you doing?
Mera, wait ,wait!
No!
- What the---?
- She just jumped without a parachute.
Redheads,you
got to love 'em.
Shit!
Oh,you're crazier
than I thought.
A-ha!
This way.
SOMEWHERE IN THE INDIAN OCEAN
You were defeated the last time because
your surface weapons failed you.
Ours will not.
It's prototype armour for the next
generation Atlantean soldier.
Revenge is something we
Atlanteans understand.
You will lead my finest
commandoes as your personal army
to hunt the half
breed abomination.
I can't touch them but you can.
He's fled to your world.
Kill him and the woman he's with
and you will be rewarded.
Killing him is my reward.
The crown jewel is
too experimental.
It converges water into beams
of energised plasma.
Hmm...
I think I'm gonna
need a bigger helmet.
One of the tribes of Atlantis
broke off and settled here
when the region was
still an inland sea.
When the water dried up,
they perished along with it.
Perished?
Yeah, that's perfect.
- We're getting close now.
- Oh,yeah? Close to what?
Dying of thirst?
I’m close to giving you
a punch in the face.
Look, fight club, I  know you're
new how things work up here.
Why don't you look
around, we are lost.
You see that over there.
What is that? Nada!
This place's a wasteland.
You're the one who call this
'wasteland' a home.
This isn't my home.
It's not like the whole
surface look like this.
Oh, no. Of course not.
You've also got disgusting cities with
sewers emptying out into our ocean
and whole mountains
made out of trash, and...
Oh, you've got great factories
that do nothing but melt ice.
Okay, okay! Okay,
point taken. Listen.
Yeah, we got some idiots
running the show.
But we got some good
things too, alright?
We got green forest
and big mountains,
and beautiful lakes.
You'd love them. There
are like little baby oceans.
Are you trying to
provoke me?
I'm just saying you cannot judge
a place before you even see it.
You judged Atlantis on far less.
No, no, no. Will you
just stop it with that?
No!
Your stupid Atlantean GPS just
told you to jump out of an airplane
over the middle of the desert.
And now we are stranded.
If you are the next
true king we're doomed.
KINGDOM OF THE DESERTERS
That was awesome.
Oh! Look what
I've found.
- What you've found?
- Yeah.
Check this place out.
This is badass!
This is the hall of armoury
where the legend says
Atlan's trident was forged.
I don't think that is
a  legend anymore.
Vulko was right.
It's real.
Nothing.
Of course it's not working.
It's been sitting here
collecting dust since before
the Sahara was a desert.
Man!
"Since before the
Sahara was a desert."
Thank you for repeating
what I've just said.
It's completely dried out.
You do your best thinking when
you’re not thinking at all.
- Right. Now, hold still.
- Hey?
- What are you doing?
- We need water.
You are the closest source.
Now, hold still.
Show off, eh?
I could've just peed on it.
King Atlan.
In this trident resides
the power of Atlantis.
In the wrong hands, it
would bring destruction.
But In the hands
of the true heir,
it will unite all our
kingdoms above and below.
If you seek my power,
you must prove your worth.
Journey beyond the edge of
the world to the hidden sea.
Look inside the bottle
for the chartered path.
Only in the hands
of the true king
can he truly see.
We can't let Orm find this.
Hey! Hey, wait! Oh!
What?
Shouldn't we have
written it down first?
I memorized it,
didn't you?
Oh.
Oh, yeah,totally.
What did he just said?
Something-something Trident.
" Look inside the bottle
for the chartered path"
It's our next stop.
SICILY, ITALY
I'm starting to think you're
actually like these surface dwellers.
It'd be wrong to judge a place
I had never seen before.
I'll be right back.
Don't go anywhere.
Well....
apparently its right up on
the hill at the old castle.
You know , I’ve just learnt
something very interesting.
Pinocchio.
You risk our lives based on something
you've read in a children's book?
Wait, it's a book? Huh.
How about that.
No. I got it from a movie.
Andiamo !
King Nereus, I had hoped
that our people had evolved
KINGDOM OF THE FISHERMEN
beyond that ancient illusion
that war with the
surface is inevitable.
It is the position of the Fishermen
that when the time comes to make
ourselves known to the lands men,
it shall be to educate them,
not to destroy them.
I admire your lofty
aspirations, king Ricou.
But I suspect they
are clouds of ink
hiding the heart of a coward.
How dare you!
Please, I implore you.
Your kingdom has bloated
philosophers and flaccid poets
whose waters have gone
stagnant, and it sickens me.
- My king!
- The king is dead.
Long live his heir.
Princess.
Prepare your armies,
Your Highness.
We move against the
Brine kingdom at once.
What was the
recording said ,again?
"Journey beyond the edge of
the world to the hidden sea.
Look in the bottle for
the chartered path.
Only in the hands of the
true king can he truly see."
"Look in the bottle for
the chartered path."
Oh man.
- What?
- Wow, Hah-ha. That's---
Let me see.
Wow! But how do you
know where to point it?
Let me see.
What was the last line?
"Only in the hands of the
true king can he truly see."
"--in the hands of
the true king--"
Marcus Agrippa..
He was a great General,
but he wasn't a king.
And there was Scipio.
- How do you know all this stuff?
- It was my pops.
He made sure
I know my history.
None of these guys
were kings except ....
..this guy. Romulus.
First king of Rome.
"Only in the hands
of the true king
can he truly see."
Ha-Ha!
There it is. That's
where we're heading.
What? Let me see.
We did---!
It's not bad for
an imbecile, huh?
Not bad at all.
"Loathsomeness waits
and dreams in the deep
and decay spreads over
the tottering cities of men."
Get back!
Arthur!
I order you to stand down!
Princess Mera, you have been
charged with high treason.
- Who the hell are you?
- Maybe this will jog your memory!
You're the guy from the sub.
- That's right!
- Ah!
But now I have
Atlantean steel.
Call me 'Black...
..Manta!
You thought you
could walk away?
I thought I told you
not to make this a habit.
Mi scusi!
You can't run!
- You owe me a blood!
- How did you find me?
Your lady friend has people
who like to keep tabs on her.
No!
Go!
Everybody! Inside!
Inside!
I'll show you the same mercy
you showed my father
and cut you like
the fish you are.
Arthur!
Mera...they are
tracking you.
- What?
- They are tracking you.
Arthur!
Arthur, Stay with me.
Arthur, wake up.
Arthur.
Um...
Did you steal a boat?
Are the boats at the marina
not for public use?
No. Those belong to people.
Hah?
Those were Orm's
elite commandoes.
The one who lead them
wasn't a Atlantean.
I've never seen him before.
Yeah, I have.
He and his father were pirates.
He blames me for
his father's death.
He picked a dangerous
line of trade.
It's not your fault.
It's not how it feels.
It was up to me, I let him die.
I could've save
him, but I didn't.
And now, I made an enemy.
And he could've hurt you,
that would've
been my fault.
Well, he's behind us now.
It's what lies ahead
that should concerns us.
The chartered path leads to
the kingdom of the trench.
Is that the same creatures
that killed my mother?
Yes. She was taken there
and sacrificed to them.
It has become
a place of death.
And I know next to nothing
about what's down there.
We should turn back.
We can still warn the surface, try to
prepare them for what's coming.
Turn back?
Look. I learned from a young
age not to show weakness.
Okay? it's not my problem's
with my anger and my fist.
I'm a blunt instrument
and I'm damn good at it.
I've done nothing
but get my ass kicked
this whole trip.
I'm no leader.
I'm not a king.
I do not work or
play well with others.
And I can't let you die trying to
turn me into something that I'm not.
You think you're
unworthy to lead because
you have two
different worlds.
But that is exactly
why you are worthy.
You are the bridge
between land and sea.
I can see that now.
The only question is...
...can you?
The tracking on lady Mera is still
dark, Your highness.
Vulko...
my trusted vizier.
You stood by the throne
since my father sat upon it.
You have any advise for
me before this war begins?
I've already given it, my king,
that I will stand by
your decision as always.
My decision?
To protect it…
..while you betray it.
You think I do not
know of your treachery?
That you have been loyal to
my mother's bastard son?
That you have spent years training
him to take the throne from me?
Do not deny it.
- I do not.
- Why?
I am the pure blood.
I have devoted my
life to Atlantis.
He wanted nothing
to do with it.
- You swore to serve the throne.
- I do serve it.
Arthur may only be
half Atlantean,
but he is already twice
the king you'll ever be.
Take him.
But make sure
he has a view.
What the hell are these things?
The Trench!
We're here!
-There're too many of them!
- Come on! inside!
They re from the depths.
They're scared to the light.
Here!
Come on!
Get ready to jump!
Over there!
KINGDOM OF THE TRENCH
That thing will tear us apart.
We don't have a choice.
Arthur!
Mera!
THE HIDDEN SEA, EARTH'S CORE
Arthur.
Mom?
King Orvax sacrificed
me to the trench.
But I survived, fought my
way through as you did,
and I ended up here.
You've been here alone
for twenty years?
- Yes.
- Ah!
Come, sit here.
You must forgive me.
Forgive me for everything.
This happened
because you had me.
Not for having you.
None of this is your fault.
I made a choice.
I had to leave to save you.
To save your father.
Tell me. tell me about him.
Is he….
He still walks to
the end of that dock?
Every morning.
…Every day.
Waiting for you.
Why didn't you
ever come back?
Because the portal that brought
you here won't let us return.
The trident is
the only way back.
But it is guarded
by the Karathen.
The creature from
our legend is real.
It lies beyond the waterfall.
We'll go with you.
We can fight it together.
No.
It's too powerful.
I've tried many
times over the years.
The creature will only allow
the true king to pass.
You're afraid.
Yes.
Good.
You're ready.
Atlantis was always had a king.
Now it needs
something more.
Well, what could be
greater than a king?
A hero.
A king fights only
for his nation.
You...
..fight for everyone.
You do not belong here.
I have guarded the trident
against false kings
since the beginning and
for a thousand years.
I have seen greatest
champions try...
...and fail,
but never have I sensed
one as unworthy as you.
You dare  come here
with your tainted
mongrel blood
to claim Atlantis's
greatest treasure?
So be it.
Half breed!
You thought yourself worthy?
You thought yourself a king?
You dishonour this place
with your presence.
Stop!
You're right.
I am a half breed
mongrel.
But I did not come here because I
thought I was worthy.
I know I'm not.
You understand me?
I do.
No mortal has conversed
with me since king Atlan.
Who are you?
I'm nobody.
I came because
I had no choice.
I came to save my home,
and the people that I love.
I came because the trident
is our only hope.
And if that's not
good enough....
...then screw you.
No man has ever freed
the trident from
Atlan's grip.
Should he deemed
you unworthy...
well, I haven't
fiested in years..
and I am damaged.
The one true king.
Remember, the Brine are
a powerful savage group
..its tend to change the sides indirectly
after their leadership turn the tide.
Defeat the Brine king
and you will command the greatest
military might on this planet.
Today we unite our kingdoms.
Tomorrow we scorch the surface!
Rise, Atlantians!
Death to atlantean!
KINGDOM OF THE BRINE
Take this!
We do not fail to atlantis!
We're going to give them a fight
that they will never forget!
No, we need him!
Join me or die!
You expect me to address
you as Your Highness?
Not Your Highness.
Call me...
..."Ocean master".
You can take my army,
you soft bellied slut!
But you will never
have my allegiance!
So be it!
What the---?
The King has risen.
Attack!
There're too many casualties.
We have to stop the fighting now.
I'll find my father.
You must defeat Orm.
And what if I can't?
Last time he was
in his element.
This time, make him
fight in yours.
Um...
- What's the plan again?
- Plan is to not gonna get killed.
Yeah. Good plan.
Don't get killed.
The trench!
He commands the trench!
Impossible!
Stand down!
Let her pass.
Please, father,
he has the trident.
I know you think
this war is necessary.
But Arthur is king by
our most sacred law.
And if you turn your
back on that now
then the Atlantis you're
fighting for is already dead.
It's true.The half breed
wields king Atlan's trident.
He commands the sea.
Then that half
breed is your king.
Vulko! Come on,
he needs our help.
We can't. Look.
The people must bear witness.
That trident doesn't
change what you are.
Half breed bastard.
Atlantis will never
accept you as its King.
Well then, by bloodshed
till the gods make
known their will!
Yield the throne.
- Finish it.
- Yield the throne.
Mercy is not our way.
Maybe you haven't
noticed ,brother,
- but I'm not one of you.
- Do it!
- Kill me!
- No!
That is enough killing!
Mother?
Orm, my son.
It's a long story.
I'll tell you later.
Come on.
I don't understand.
We thought you…
I know.
Arthur saved me.
- You're with him?
- I am.
You're both my children,
and I love you so much.
But you have been misguided.
Your father taught you
that there were two worlds.
He was wrong.
The land and the sea...
...are one.
My Queen.
Vulko.
Take him.
But make sure
he has a view.
When you're ready…
..let's talk.
People of Atlantis, today
began with  bloodshed.
let it end in joy.
I give you...
...King Arthur of Atlantis.
Hail to the king!
So, what do I do now?
Be their king.
This is going to be fun.
You came back!
You're back.
Yes. Yes.
My father was
a lighthouse keeper.
My mother was a queen.
They were never
meant to meet.
But their love saved the world.
They made me what I am.
A son of the land,
a king of the seas.
I am the protector of the deep.
I am ....
...Aquaman.
AQUAMAN
Hey!
I've spent 15 years..
..at the united states
institute of marine science studying--
- Weren't you fired?
- studying oceanic phenomenon,
and this is the most conclusive
evidence we have today.
Deep sea seismographs have recorded
explotions on the ocean floor.
We have sattelite imagery...
a debrie from atlantean warship
floating on the surface.
- Doctor.Shin!
- Would you,please, let me finish?
Here we go again.
Yes, the government dosen't
want us to know about the threat
that excists right here
on our world---
Yeah, I wouldn't do
that if I were you.
This is atlantean
technology, isn't it?
Could you tell me
how you've got this?
Sure.
But first..
..you've got to tell me
how to find him.
Who is Aquaman ?