Jules Verne once wrote,
"Put two ships in the open sea
"without wind or tide,
they will come together."
That's how my parents met. Like
two ships destined for each other.
- We are something else.
- Try Arthur Treacher...
It's okay.
Easy. You weren't breathing.
They were from different worlds.
But life, like the sea,
has a way of bringing
people together.
Uh...
I was gonna make you some eggs.
Just don't eat my dog, okay?
It's okay.
I made tea.
Go on, try it.
It'll make you better.
So, uh, who are you?
Atlanna.
Queen of Atlantis.
Wow.
I'm Tom. Keeper of lighthouse.
She had fled an
arranged marriage.
Left her whole world behind.
But in my father's lighthouse,
she found something unexpected.
And my father found
the love of his life.
Category 4 Hurricane Arthur
is due to make landfall
sometime after 2:00 p.m.
How about Arthur?
After the hurricane?
After a legend.
He's a king, isn't he?
He's more than that.
He's living proof our
people can coexist.
He could unite
our worlds one day.
And the trident could only be
wielded by the strongest Atlantean.
And it gave King Atlan
mastery over the seven seas.
It made him so powerful that
the ocean itself became jealous
and sent a terrible
earthquake to destroy Atlantis.
Down it fell, to the
bottom of the ocean.
But, legend has it that one
day a new king will come
who will use the
power of the trident
to put Atlantis
back together again.
Take him!
Queen Atlanna,
by the authority of King Orvax,
you are ordered
to return to Atlantis.
Atlanna!
But Atlantis' memory is long...
And its king
refused to let her go.
- Atlanna!
- Tom!
- My weapon!
- Here!
Their two worlds were
never meant to meet,
and I was a product of a
love that never should've been.
You don't have to do
this, Atlanna. Please.
No. They will always find me.
Next time, they'll send an army.
I have to go back. It is
the only way to save him.
Save you.
Where I come from...
The sea carries our tears away.
Not here.
Here you feel them.
I will return to
you. When it's safe.
One day.
Right here, at sunrise.
We'll be together again.
You stay strong,
my little prince.
I'll always be with you.
Don't let him forget me. Hmm?
All life came from the sea,
so if we want to
understand ourselves,
we must journey
to where we began.
Now, today, we have better maps of
Mars than we do of our own sea floor.
Come on, closer. Come on, fishy.
- Come on. Come over here.
- Boys!
Stop that. Come on.
Come along.
Bye, fishy. Bye.
My name's Arthur. What's yours?
- You guys hungry? Me, too.
- Check it out.
Arthur is talking to the fish.
Such a freak, Arthur.
- Stop!
- What are you gonna do about it, freak?
Stop it! Don't!
Let me go!
Improved by KID
Resynced by KID
Enjoy the movie(s) / show(s)
Who are you?
Come on, let's go. Move it.
Come on. Hurry up.
Sir, we've secured the captain.
Distress signal's disabled.
We're running dark again.
But they heard it.
You can count on it.
I'll make you a deal. I won't
tell you how to captain...
And you don't tell
me how to pirate.
Where's the rest of the crew?
Decided discretion was
the better part of valor
and sealed themselves
up in the torpedo bay.
Our reputation precedes us.
Your reputation.
This is your win.
Here.
Can't take that piece of junk.
It's the love of your life.
I never told you
the story behind it.
This was your grandfather's.
He was one of the Navy's first
frogmen during World War II.
He was so stealthy in the water,
his unit nicknamed him Manta.
But after the war, his
country forgot about him.
So, he went back to the sea,
scavenging and surviving with his wit...
And this knife.
He gave it to me
when I was your age.
And now it's yours, son.
Did we just hit something?
No. Something hit us.
Sir, there's
something out there.
Another submarine?
Uh... No. I think it's a man.
That's not a man.
Alpha, to the right. Bravo
team, sweep the passageway.
Permission to come aboard?
Aquaman!
I've waited a
long time for this.
Am I supposed to
know who you are?
I scavenge the high seas.
You're the Aquaman.
We were bound to
meet at some point.
Let's not make it a habit.
Up.
Ow.
Dad!
Dad? Ow.
That's your kid?
Shame on you.
Boys got yourselves
into this mess.
Get yourselves out of it.
Bastard!
Dad!
Wait!
Help me! He's trapped!
You can't leave him like this!
Please!
You killed innocent people.
You ask the sea for mercy.
Get outta here! I got this!
Shut up, I'm not leaving you!
You need to live, so you
can kill that son of a bitch!
- Now, go!
- No!
- Go!
- Shut up!
No!
Damn you!
Go.
I always know where to find you.
Old habits.
- Come on, I'll buy you breakfast.
- All right!
You want me to have them
put that in a sippy cup for you?
How is it that I can
breathe underwater,
but you can still drink
me under the table?
That's my superpower.
A Russian submarine
hijacked late last night
by high-tech pirates.
The same pirates
who are suspected
in connection with the disappearance
of the Navy's highly classified
prototype stealth submarine.
And a further development, we
now have unconfirmed reports
that the metahuman dubbed by
social media as "The Aquaman"
was responsible for
this daring rescue.
That's not me.
Bullshit. You're doing
it, aren't you? Huh?
What Vulko trained you to do.
I knew you couldn't stand
on the sidelines forever.
Your mother always
knew you were special.
Don't even start.
She believed you'd be the
one to unite our two worlds.
Just stop.
Whatever Atlantis' problems
are, you're bigger than them.
Atlantis murdered my mother.
You don't know that for sure.
Yes, I do.
They killed her. For
loving you and having me.
And you know it.
Son, one day you're gonna
have to stop blaming yourself.
Hey, buddy.
You that fish boy from the TV?
Oh, great.
It's "fish man."
What do you want?
I'll tell you what I want.
Could we get a picture with you?
You're like our local hero, man.
It would mean a
lot. Just a quick...
Whatever.
- All right. Let's do this.
- Don't touch me.
Right, that's exactly right.
I'm gonna go down here.
There we go. Everybody smile.
He understands the
significance of this meeting.
He'll hear you out.
- King Orm.
- King Nereus.
You picked a meeting place too
close to the surface for my liking.
You don't recognize
the Council of the Kings?
In Atlan's time, when the
Seven Kingdoms were one,
our ancestors gathered here.
Atlantis sat here at
the head of the table.
Xebel, as always, by his side.
Brine. Fishermen.
The Deserters and the
Trench had not yet fallen.
The Lost Nation
had not yet vanished.
Together, they were the greatest
empire the world had ever seen.
But now, I sit
on Atlan's throne,
shackled by archaic
laws and politics.
While the threat above
us grows undeniably...
Violence has always
plagued the surface.
They will destroy themselves.
Not before destroying us first.
We have been hiding long enough.
The time has come
for Atlantis to rise again.
We honor you, King Nereus,
by inviting Xebel to
be the first kingdom
to join King Orm's alliance.
As if you had a choice, Vulko.
By law, you need four
of the Seven Kingdoms
to ascend and attack.
The Lost Nation and the
Deserters have long perished.
The Trench are
nothing but animals.
The Brine will never join you,
and the Fishermen are cowards.
Without me and my army to
convince them, your plans are stillborn.
But I know what you really want.
Once you've obtained the
pledge of the four kingdoms,
you will be ordained
Ocean Master.
That is merely a title.
I'm no fool, King Orm.
As Ocean Master,
you'll be commander
of the greatest military
might on this planet.
I am the natural
choice to lead it.
Are you?
What about the rumors
that there's another?
An Atlantean, living
among the surface.
One of royal blood.
You may sit on the throne of
Atlantis, but your claim to it is weak.
How can you possibly
hope to unite the empire?
My mother's bastard has
never even been to Atlantis.
His loyalty is to the surface.
Surface-dwellers! To arms!
Your king is injured!
I'm not trying to start a war.
The war has already begun.
Then it's time we send
them a message they'll hear.
- I'm good.
- Stop.
- Here're the keys.
- Thank you.
Let's go home and work
on your ta moko. Huh?
If your grandpops
was still alive,
he'd be banging our
heads for not finishing it.
Yes, he would, but there
is plenty of time for that.
We gotta get you to bed.
Got it?
I've been looking for you.
Oh, no, no, no...
I need you to come
with me to Atlantis.
Listen, I'm gonna
tell you the same thing
that I told that
rusty starfish Vulko.
Except nicer,
because you're a lady.
No, thank you.
I'm not interested.
You defeated Steppenwolf
and saved Atlantis.
That had nothing
to do with Atlantis.
Your half-brother King Orm is about
to declare war upon the surface world.
Billions will die.
Your people and mine.
We must stop him.
And how do you
propose we do that?
You are the firstborn
son of Queen Atlanna.
The throne is
yours by birthright.
The only way to stop this
war and save both worlds
is for you to take your
rightful place as king.
You think if I just show up,
Orm's gonna give up the throne?
I'm the bastard son of the
queen your people executed.
Trust me. I am no king.
I agree.
That's awesome. Cool.
But, Vulko seems to believe
in you for some reason,
and that's why I'm here.
Vulko has learned of the
location of the Lost Trident of Atlan.
Ooh, fairy tales. It's a myth.
It's not a myth.
With the Sacred Trident,
the people will listen to you.
You can then claim your
birthright and dethrone Orm.
My birthright? It
died with my mother.
But I promise you
this. If Orm attacks,
I will treat him exactly the same
way your people treated her.
With no mercy.
That submarine was barely
operational, but it served its purpose.
One of your kind intervened.
He is not one of us.
He killed my father.
Our transaction has ended.
Keep the money. I want Aquaman.
Dad!
Pops!
Come on, Pops.
Come on! He's not breathing.
Move! Let me help.
Come on, Pops.
Come on.
I don't even know your name.
It's Princess Y'Mera
Xebella Challa.
You may call me Mera.
Thank you, Mera.
Dear God.
This was Orm's doing.
The worst is yet to come.
There's a flash
flood warning here
that was just extended
for a couple hours.
Unprecedented sights
from all over the world today.
We are seeing warships and
trash washed up by massive waves.
These extraordinary scenes
of coastlines deluged with waste
and garbage are taking
place all over the world.
Decades of pollution has
been thrown back onto land.
Many are asking the question,
"Was this a natural
disaster or something else?"
No. This was no
natural disaster.
They threw out our
garbage and our warships.
This was our first contact
with the people of Atlantis.
There you go again with
your insane Atlantean theory.
You have absolutely
no proof, Dr. Shin.
Open your eyes.
We already have an
Atlantean living among us,
and his name is Aquaman.
What is it?
This is the exact spot that Vulko
gave me my first swimming lesson.
You have to forget all the
teaching of the surface world
and go deeper to uncover
your Atlantean instincts.
But I already know how to swim.
Not even close.
Just so we're clear,
I'll help you stop this war.
But then, I'm done.
Maybe that's for the best.
The ocean is more than
our life source, Arthur.
It is who we are.
Wait, you can talk underwater?
I can talk underwater, too!
This is awesome!
Oh, we can do
more than just talk.
Being Atlantean means more
than just being able to breathe water.
Your body is equipped to survive
the extreme cold and pressure,
and your eyes adjust
to see in the dark.
This is awesome!
So, Vulko, when can
I meet my mother?
Soon, my young prince.
When you're ready, I'll take
you to Atlantis to meet the queen.
I hid my ship in here.
Listen, I'm not
getting in that thing.
Well, to get where we're
going, you're gonna have to.
Your fish ship has been
marinating in chum butter.
I'm gonna come out
smelling like swamp butt.
That'd be an improvement.
Yup. Okay.
What's the point in having
a bridge underwater?
The Gateway Bridge is a
remnant of the Old World.
It's also the only way
in or out of the Capital.
Why can't they just
go over the walls?
Security is impenetrable.
Even if they did manage
to evade the guards,
they'd never get past
the hydro-cannons.
People try to
sneak in all the time.
Yeah, right.
What is this?
Customs and border control.
Don't worry. I have
diplomatic clearance.
Welcome home.
There's a safe house
down in the Old City.
The Highborns never
venture to the sea floor.
We're here.
What is this?
We use this air pocket as
an extra layer of precaution.
Only the Highborns can
breathe water as well as air.
Plus, it keeps the animals out.
They get kind of messy.
Vulko. Here I am, old man.
After all these years, you
finally get what you wanted.
Arthur, I wish it was
under better circumstances.
I can't believe Orm attacked.
It wasn't an attack.
Legally, he's not
allowed to yet.
What he did to your surface
warships was merely a warning.
What provoked it?
King Orm and your father
were ambushed by the surface.
By the surface?
I don't think so.
They still think
Atlantis is a fairy tale.
I was there.
A surface warship fired at us.
Now, Xebel sides with Atlantis,
giving Orm a fleet big enough to
force the other two kingdoms to join him.
If we're going to prevent this
war, you must dethrone him now.
How many times do I have to
tell you? I don't wanna be king.
You don't understand.
Once he is named Ocean
Master, it'll be too late.
The power at his disposal will be
unlike anything you have ever seen.
I'm from the surface. No one
is gonna take me seriously.
Okay? I don't even
know where to begin.
By winning the hearts
and minds of the people
by proving to them that you're
worthy, and retrieving this.
Hmm.
I already got one of those.
Not like this one, you don't.
This is the Lost
Trident of Atlan.
Oh, I know the story.
It's more than
a story. It's real.
It was forged by the greatest
weapon masters in history.
Crafted from Poseidon's
steel for King Atlan,
the first ruler of Atlantis.
Legend says the trident was imbued
with the power to command the sea.
So what happened to it?
To know that is to go back to
the time before the Great Fall,
when King Atlan
ruled over all that was,
when the kingdoms
of Atlantis were one.
It was a time of great prosperity
and technological advancement.
We had unlocked the
secret of unlimited energy
at a time when
the rest of the world
still thought the
earth was flat.
But we became too ambitious,
too hungry for power.
The ocean swallowed
us, and Atlantis sank.
But the very power that
collapsed our civilization
also paved the
way to our future.
It gave us the ability
to breathe underwater.
And so, we evolved.
Others regressed, became savage.
And the king lived out the remainder
of his days in self-imposed exile.
Neither he nor the trident
were ever seen again.
One of our archeological teams
uncovered this a few months ago.
It's an ancient recording
dating back to the First Dynasty.
I believe it contains Atlan's
final message to his people
and the whereabouts
of the Sacred Trident.
So, what does it say?
We don't know. The
technology's too old.
The cylinder bears the
markings of the Deserter Kingdom.
You must take it there
and retrieve the message.
The clue to Atlan's final
resting place is inside of this.
Border Defense. You are
under arrest for illegal entry.
No!
You mustn't be seen here!
I don't suppose you want
to talk about this, do you?
Neither do I.
In the name of His Highness,
King Orm, I place you under arrest.
Welcome to Atlantis...
Brother.
I can't believe
you're finally here.
I've heard so many
stories about you.
All these years, I've been
ashamed of my mother
for defiling herself
with a surface-dweller.
Ashamed of the fact that I
have a half-breed brother
whose heart I wanted
to run my trident through.
But now that you're finally
here before me, I must admit...
I am conflicted.
You want conflict,
why don't you take these
chains off, little brother?
And we'll see who
gets run through.
Yes, I see you've brought
our mother's weapon.
Is that why you've come
here after all this time?
To kill me?
I came here to stop a maniac
from destroying the world.
I see.
And how do you plan
to stop the atrocities
that the surface
continues to commit?
Because for a century,
they have polluted our waters
and poisoned our children.
And now, their skies
burn and our oceans boil.
And you've come all this way to
take sides against your own people?
There are no sides
in a war like this.
You have clearly chosen a side and
come here to challenge the throne.
If that's what it takes
to stop your war.
Are you invoking the
Combat of the Kings?
Call it whatever you want.
I call it an ass-whooping.
Well then, perhaps
that's how we'll proceed.
- Your Majesty!
- Orm, please.
Don't you see?
If I defeat the
firstborn son of Atlanna
in a formal challenge
in front of everyone,
then all Seven Kingdoms will have
to concede that I am the one true king.
Your Majesty, there is no
victory in defeating the ignorant.
Your brother is
clearly an imbecile.
Your Highness, he
doesn't know our ways.
Then he's about
to get an education.
Are you officially
challenging me?
Hell yes, I challenge
you. And when I win...
If you win,
I will cease all immediate
action. The war is over.
But if I win...
You're over.
Let's do it.
So be it.
Challenge has been
made, and I accept.
Prepare him for
the Ring of Fire.
Wait. The ring of what?
How could you be so foolish
to let Orm bait you into a fight?
It seems to me like I just
solved all of our problems.
I beat him in a battle,
war's over, I get to go home.
You're a formidable
fighter on land,
but here you're out of
your element, literally.
Orm has spent his
entire life underwater,
training to be a warrior,
training to be the best.
You taught me how
to fight, Cobra Kai.
Let's see if you
remember anything.
So, what's with the big fork?
It's a trident. Now,
defend yourself.
What the hell is this?
I'll teach you this move when
you've mastered the trident.
It's not fair.
This thing is so big and
awkward. Why can't I use a sword?
That's your mother's trident.
A traditional weapon of royalty.
You'll never be a king
until you've mastered it.
Why has she never
come to see me, huh?
I told you, when you're ready...
Stop lying to me! I've done
everything you ever asked.
And every time I pass a
test, you make up another one.
When am I gonna be good enough?
Does she not love me?
Your mother loved you more
than anything in the world.
But she had to return to
Atlantis to keep you safe.
Her marriage to King Orvax
was arranged a long time ago,
so she had to marry him...
And bear him a son, Prince Orm.
When Orvax eventually
found out about you,
he became
overwhelmed with jealousy
and sacrificed her to the
creatures of the Trench.
Are you saying
they executed her?
Because she had me?
I remember...
Everything.
I have something for you.
It belonged to my mother.
Tell me...
Do you think she would have enjoyed
watching her sons murder each other?
I understand your fear
and your reluctance, Mera.
I truly do. I don't want war...
Don't patronize me!
I know you.
What you're doing flies
in the face of everything
that your mother taught
us when we were children.
If she were here...
But she's not here, is she?
1What my mother
taught us was treason.
Don't follow in her wake.
All right! So, this is the
big, old ring of fire, huh?
How's it work? I just
kick your ass right here?
Vulko.
Will you escort my
betrothed to the royal box?
Let's go, Lady Mera.
Down here, we have a
legend about the Karathen,
an ancient sea monster so powerful
that even King Atlan himself feared it.
So, he imprisoned it in
the depths of the ocean.
And in that abyss, the creature
bides its time waiting to rise again.
Atlantis has been
lying in wait...
And now, the beast has awakened.
There was a time when I wanted
to meet you more than anything.
Get to know my little brother.
Let him know that he wasn't
alone, that we were in it together.
If only I had known what a
dick you would turn out to be.
You were the reason
our mother was executed.
And I've hated
you for it ever since.
But I do not want
to kill you, Arthur.
I'm going to give
you one chance.
Go home.
Do not ever come
back to Atlantis.
You are not going to win this.
A war is coming to the surface
whether you like it or not.
And I am bringing the wrath
of the seven seas with me.
You know I can't
let that happen.
I know.
What the hell is that?
The Ring of Fire.
Yeah!
Shit.
People of Atlantis, hear me!
My brother has come from the
surface to challenge me for the throne.
Let us settle his claim
in the ancient way.
By bloodshed do the
gods make known their will!
Traitor!
You'll never be king!
Never thought I'd see the
day when my own father
would bow before
the king of Atlantis.
The surface-dwellers drew first
blood. What would you have us do?
Beg them for mercy?
I detest the surface
as much as you do.
But don't you find the timing
of all of this a bit convenient?
But you wouldn't be
that gullible, would you?
You want this
war too, don't you?
It is past time the surface-dwellers
learned their place in the world.
If this is how it must
be done, then so be it.
You have our mother's trident.
Powerful, but flawed like her.
I wield my father's.
And it has never known defeat!
I promised Atlanna
I'd protect him.
This isn't a competition.
It's an execution.
I am the one true king!
You waiting for an
invitation? Get in!
Mera!
Oh, yeah. So, what's the plan?
The plan was to recover Atlan's
trident, then challenge Orm.
Okay, so we're doing
things a little out of order.
Shit happens.
Heads up! We got
a bogey on our six!
- What does that even mean?
- Bad guys behind us.
- Then just say that!
- Bad guys behind us!
Whoa, whoa, wait, you said
we couldn't go over these walls.
- I did!
- You said there were hydro-cannons!
I did, now shut up!
Oh, shit!
Shit!
Shit.
We're not dead yet! But
I'm hoping he'll think we are.
Oh!
Here, hold this.
What are you doing?
- Listen, it worked for Pinocchio.
- Who?
Never mind. Come
here, get in. Come on.
Great. So we're getting eaten.
How are you even
doing this, anyway?
I don't know.
I can hear them sometimes,
and they can hear me.
Right. Because you're
both big, dumb animals.
- Hey, I just saved your life.
- I saved yours first!
She said, "Coast is clear."
So, where to now?
To the ocean of sand
your people call the Sahara.
All right.
I don't usually take charters,
but I don't usually get
paid in pirate treasure.
Thanks for the ride, buddy.
Oh, man.
Are you okay?
I've never been
so high up before.
Or so far from home.
But at least you have a home.
Not anymore.
I can never go back.
I betrayed everything when I
saved you from the coliseum.
Yeah, but you're engaged to the
king. They have to take you back.
Atlantis is many
wonderful things.
But forgiving, it is not.
Yeah, but you're royalty.
So was your mother.
If I went back now, I'd be
sacrificed to the Trench.
Even my own father
wouldn't take me back.
Look on the bright side,
now you don't have to marry some
tool bag that you're not in love with.
My obligation isn't to love.
It is to my family
and my nation,
and I've turned my back on both.
Sometimes, you
have to do what's right,
even if your heart
aches against it.
Your Highness.
The tracker places Princess
Mera here, in the Deserter Kingdom.
You said she was dead.
Apparently not.
Then your brother
still lives as well?
Not for long.
Captain Murk, assemble
a strike force immediately.
No! Mera is to be arrested
and safely returned to me.
She betrayed the throne.
She is a daughter of Xebel.
If any harm befalls
her, our coalition is over.
Your Highness,
we are now entering the waters
of the Fishermen Kingdom.
Securing the alliance of
the other two kingdoms
should be our immediate concern.
My vizier is correct. As usual.
Arrest them and bring back
King Nereus' daughter unharmed.
We're here!
Hey!
Is there anything nearby?
Nothing but desert for
hundreds of K's, mate!
- Nothing but desert.
- He's wrong.
- Hey! What are you doing?
- Wait! No! Oh...
She just jumped! She
didn't have a parachute!
Redheads! You gotta love 'em.
Shit!
Oh, you're crazier
than I thought!
A-ha!
This way.
You were defeated the last time
because your surface weapons failed you.
Ours will not.
It's prototype armor
for the next generation
Atlantean soldier.
Revenge is something
we Atlanteans understand.
You will lead my finest
commandos as your personal army
to hunt down the
half-breed abomination.
I cannot touch them, but you
can. He's fled to your world.
Kill him and the woman he's
with, and you will be rewarded.
Killing him is my reward.
- The crown jewel.
- Still experimental.
Converts water into
beams of energized plasma.
Hmm.
I think I'm gonna
need a bigger helmet.
One of the tribes of Atlantis
broke off and settled here
when this region
was still an inland sea.
When the water dried up,
they perished along with it.
Perished? Yeah, that's terrific.
We're getting close now.
Oh, yeah? Close to
what? Dying of thirst?
Close to getting
punched in the face!
Look, Fight Club, I know you're
new to how things work up here.
Why don't you look
around? We are lost.
You see that over
there? Hey, what is that?
Nada. This place is a wasteland.
You're the one who calls
this wasteland a home.
This isn't my home!
It's not like the whole
surface looks like this!
Oh, no, of course not.
You've also got disgusting cities
whose sewers empty out into our ocean
and whole mountains
made out of trash.
And, oh, you've
got great factories
that do nothing but belch
out filth and melt ice caps.
Okay. Point taken. Listen.
Yeah, we got some
idiots running the show,
but we've got some
good things too, all right?
We got green forests and big
mountains and beautiful lakes.
You'd love 'em. They're
like little baby oceans.
Are you trying to provoke me?
I'm just saying you cannot judge
a place before you've even seen it.
You've judged
Atlantis on far less.
No. Would you just
stop it with that? No.
Your stupid Atlantean GPS just
told you to jump out of an airplane
over the middle of the desert,
and now we are stranded.
If you're the next true
king, we're doomed.
That was awesome.
Oh. Look what I found.
What you found?
Yeah.
Check this place out.
This is badass!
This is the Hall of Armory.
Where the legends say
Atlan's trident was forged.
I don't think they're
legends anymore.
Vulko was right.
It's real.
Huh.
Nothing.
Of course it's not working.
It's been sitting here collecting dust
since before the Sahara was a desert.
Man!
"Since before the
Sahara was a desert."
Thank you for
repeating what I just said.
It's completely dried out.
Let's just say you
do your best thinking
when you're not thinking at all.
All right, now hold still.
Hey. What are you doing?
We need water, and
you're the closest source.
Now, hold still.
Hmm.
Show-off.
I could have just peed on it.
King Atlan.
In this trident resides
the power of Atlantis.
In the wrong hands, it
would bring destruction.
But in the hands
of the true heir,
it would unite all our
kingdoms above and below.
If you seek my power,
you must prove your worth.
Journey beyond the edge of
the world to the Hidden Sea.
Look inside the bottle
for the charted path.
Only in the hands of the
true king can he truly see.
Hmm.
We can't let Orm find this.
Hey! Wait!
What?
Shouldn't we have
written it down first?
I memorized it. Didn't you?
Oh, yeah. Totally.
What'd he just say?
"Something something trident."
"Look inside the bottle
for the charted path."
It's our next stop.
I'm starting to think you actually
like these surface-dwellers.
It would be wrong to judge a
place I've never seen before.
I'll be right back.
Don't go anywhere.
Well, apparently, it's just right
up on the hill. A big old castle.
And I just learned
something very interesting.
You risked our lives based on
something you read in a children's book?
Wait, it's a book?
How about that?
Oh!
I got it from the movie.
King Nereus, I had hoped
our people had evolved
beyond that ancient notion
that war with the
surface is inevitable.
It is the position
of the Fishermen
that when the time comes to make
ourselves known to the landsmen,
it should be to educate
them, not to destroy them.
I admire your lofty
aspirations, King Ricou.
But I suspect they are but clouds
of ink hiding the heart of a coward.
How dare you!
Please. I implore you.
You're a kingdom of bloated
philosophers and flaccid poets
whose waters have grown
stagnant, and it sickens me.
My King!
The king is dead!
Long live his heir.
Princess.
Prepare your armies,
Your Highness.
We move against the
Brine Kingdom at once.
What did the
recording say, again?
"Journey beyond the edge of
the world to the Hidden Sea.
"Look in the bottle
for the charted path.
"Only in the hands of the
true king can he truly see."
"Look in the bottle
for the charted path."
Hmm.
Oh, man.
What?
Wow. That's awesome.
Let me see.
Wow. But how do you
know where to point it?
Here, let me see.
What was the last line?
"Only in the hands of the
true king can he truly see."
"Only in the
hands of the true..."
Marcus Agrippa.
He was a great general,
but he wasn't a king.
Neither was Scipio.
How do you know all this stuff?
Because of my pops. He
made sure I knew my history.
None of these guys are
kings, except this guy. Romulus.
First king of Rome.
"Only in the hands of the
true king can he truly see."
There it is. That's our heading.
What? Let me see.
We did it!
Oh!
That's not bad for
an imbecile, huh?
Not bad at all.
Mera.
"Loathsomeness waits
and dreams in the deep,
"and decay spreads over
the tottering cities of men."
Get back!
Arthur!
I order you to stand down!
Princess Mera, you've been
charged with high treason.
Who the hell are you?
Maybe this will jog your memory.
You're the guy from the sub.
That's right.
But now I have Atlantean steel.
Call me "Black Manta."
You thought you could walk away?
I thought I told you
not to make this a habit.
You can't run.
You owe me blood!
How'd you find me?
Your lady friend has people
who like to keep tabs on her.
No!
Come on.
Everybody, inside. Get inside.
I'll show you the same
mercy you showed my father.
And gut you like
the fish you are!
Arthur!
Mera, they're tracking you.
What?
They're tracking you.
Arthur, stay with me.
Arthur, wake up! Arthur.
Um...
Did you steal a boat?
Are the boats at the
marina not for public use?
No, those belong to people.
Huh.
Those were Orm's
elite commandos.
But the one who led
them, he wasn't Atlantean.
I've never seen him before.
Yeah, I have.
He and his father were pirates.
And he blames me
for his father's death.
They picked a dangerous
line of trade. It's not your fault.
That's not how it feels.
It was up to me,
and I let him die.
I could've saved
him, but I didn't.
And now, I made an enemy,
and he could have hurt you.
And that would
have been my fault.
Well, he's behind us now.
It's what lies ahead
that should concern us.
The charted path leads to
the Kingdom of the Trench.
Are those the same
creatures that killed my mother?
Yes.
She was taken there
and sacrificed to them.
It's become a place of death.
We know next to nothing
about what's down there.
We should turn back.
We can still warn the surface. Try
and prepare them for what's coming.
Turn back?
Look, I learned from a young
age not to show weakness.
Okay? I solve my problems
with my anger and my fists.
I'm a blunt instrument,
and I'm damn good at it.
But I've done nothing but get
my ass kicked this whole trip.
I'm no leader. I'm not a king.
I do not work or
play well with others.
And I can't let you die trying to
turn me into something that I'm not.
You think you're unworthy to lead
because you're of two different worlds.
But that is exactly
why you are worthy.
You are the bridge
between land and sea.
The only question is...
Can you?
The tracking on Lady Mera
is still dark, Your Highness.
Vulko.
My trusted vizier
who has stood by the throne
since my father sat upon it.
Have you any advice
for me as this war begins?
I have already
given it, My King.
But I will stand by your
decision, as always.
My decision.
To protect it.
While you betray it.
You think I do not
know of your treachery?
That you have remained loyal
to my mother's bastard son.
That you have spent years training
him to take the throne from me.
Do not deny it.
I do not.
Why?
I am the pureblood.
I have devoted
my life to Atlantis.
He wanted nothing to do with
it. You swore to serve the throne!
I do serve it.
Arthur may only
be half-Atlantean,
but he's already twice
the king you'll ever be.
Take him.
But make sure he has a view.
What the hell are these things?
The Trench! We're here!
- There are too many of them!
- Come on, inside!
They're from the depths.
They're scared
of the light. Here!
Come on!
You ready to jump?
Over there!
That thing will tear us apart.
We don't have a choice!
Arthur!
Mera!
Arthur.
Mom?
King Orvax sacrificed me
to the Trench, but I survived.
I fought my way through as
you did, and I ended up here.
You've been here
alone for 20 years?
Yes.
Come. Sit here.
You must forgive me.
Forgive me for everything.
This happened
because you had me.
Not for having you.
None of this is your fault.
I made a choice.
I had to leave...
To save you, to
save your father.
Tell me. Tell me about him.
Is he...
He still walks to
the end of that dock.
Every morning.
Every day.
Waiting for you.
Why didn't you ever come back?
Because the portal that brought
you here won't let us return.
The trident is the
only way back.
But it is guarded
by the Karathen.
The creature from
our legends, it's real.
It lies beyond the waterfall.
We'll go with you. We
can fight it together.
No.
It's too powerful.
I've tried many
times over the years.
The creature will only
allow the true king to pass.
You're afraid.
Yes.
Good.
You're ready.
Atlantis has always had a king.
Now, it needs something more.
But what could be
greater than a king?
A hero.
A king fights
only for his nation.
You fight for everyone.
You do not belong here.
I have guarded the trident against
false kings since the beginning.
And for a thousand years
I have seen the greatest
champions try and fail.
But never have I sensed
one as unworthy as you.
You dare come here with
your tainted mongrel blood
to claim Atlantis'
greatest treasure?
So be it...
Half-breed.
You thought yourself worthy?
You thought yourself a king?
You dishonor this
place with your presence.
Stop!
You're right. I am a
half-breed mongrel.
But I did not come here
because I thought I was worthy.
I know I'm not.
You understand me?
I do.
No mortal has conversed
with me since King Atlan.
Who are you?
I'm nobody.
I came because I had no choice.
I came to save my home
and the people that I love.
I came because the
trident is their only hope.
And if that's not good enough...
Then screw you.
No man has ever freed
the trident from Atlan's grip.
Should he deem you unworthy...
Well, I haven't feasted in eons,
and I am famished.
The one true king.
Remember, the Brine are
powerful, savage brutes,
but a swift assault aimed directly
at their leadership will turn the tide.
Defeat the Brine King,
and you will command the
greatest military might on this planet.
Today, we unite our kingdoms.
Tomorrow, we scorch the surface!
Rise, Atlantis!
Death to the Atlantean hagfish!
We will not bow to Atlantis.
We're gonna give them a
fight that they will never forget!
No! We need him!
Join me or die.
You expect me to address
you as Your Highness?
Not Your Highness.
Call me...
Ocean Master.
You can take my army,
you soft-bellied slug.
But you will never
have my allegiance!
So be it!
What the...
The king has risen.
Attack!
There are too many casualties.
We have to stop the fighting now.
I'll find my father. But
you must defeat Orm.
And what if I can't?
Last time, he was
in his element.
This time, make
him fight in yours.
Um...
- What was the plan, again?
- The plan is to not get killed.
Yeah, good plan.
Don't get killed.
The Trench! He
commands the Trench!
Impossible!
Stand down! Let her pass.
Please, Father,
he has the trident.
I know you think
this war is necessary,
but Arthur is king by
our most sacred law.
And if you turn your
back on that now,
then the Atlantis you're
fighting for is already dead.
It's true! The half-breed
wields King Atlan's trident.
He commands the sea!
Then that half-breed
is your king.
Vulko! Come on,
he needs our help!
We can't! Look.
The people must bear witness.
That trident doesn't
change what you are.
A half-breed bastard.
Atlantis will never
accept you as its king.
Well, then by bloodshed...
Do the gods make
known their will.
Yield the throne. Yield it!
Finish it.
Yield the throne.
Mercy is not our way.
Maybe you haven't
noticed, brother...
But I'm not one of you.
Do it!
- Kill me!
- No!
That is enough killing.
Mother?
Oh, my son.
It's a long story.
I'll tell ya later.
Come on!
I don't understand.
We thought...
I know.
Arthur saved me.
- You're with him?
- I am.
You're both my children,
and I love you so much.
But you have been misguided.
Your father taught you
that there were two worlds.
He was wrong.
The land and the sea
are one.
My queen.
Vulko.
Take him.
But make sure he has a view.
When you're ready,
let's talk.
People of Atlantis,
today began in bloodshed,
but let it end in joy.
I give you King
Arthur of Atlantis.
Hail to the king!
- Hail to the king!
So, what do I do now?
Be their king.
Ooh.
This is gonna be fun.
You came back. You're back.
Yes. Yes.
My father was a
lighthouse keeper.
My mother was a queen.
They were never meant to meet...
But their love saved the world.
They made me what I am.
A son of the land,
and a king of the seas.
I am the protector of the deep.
I am...
Aquaman.
Hey!
I spent 15 years
at the United States
Institute of Marine Science...
- Weren't you fired?
- ...studying oceanic phenomenon,
and this is the most conclusive
evidence we have to date.
Deep-sea seismographs have
recorded explosions on the ocean floor.
We have satellite imagery
of debris from Atlantean
warships floating on the surface...
- Dr. Shin!
- Will you please let me finish?
Here we go again. Atlantean?
Yes. The government
does not want us to know
about the threat that
exists right here...
Yeah, I wouldn't
do that if I were you.
This is Atlantean
technology, isn't it?
Can you tell me
how you got this?
Sure. But first,
you gotta tell me
how to find him.
Improved by KID
Resynced by KID
Enjoy the movie(s) / show(s)