(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(WIND HOWLING)
ARTHUR: Jules Verne once wrote,
"Put two ships in the open sea
without wind or tide,
they will come together."
That's how my parents met.
Like two ships destined for each other.
(MUSIC PLAYING ON TV)
ANNOUNCER: (ON TV) We are something
else. Try Arthur Treacher...
(POWERING DOWN)
(VOMITING)
(GASPING)
It's okay.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(CHOKING)
Easy. You weren't breathing.
(POWERING UP)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING ON TV)
(GRUNTING)
(WHINES)
(GROANING)
ARTHUR: They were
from different worlds.
(ATLANNA GROANS)
ARTHUR: But life, like the sea,
has a way of bringing people together.
(DOG WHINING)
(GASPS)
TOM: Uh...
I was gonna make you some eggs.
Just don't eat my dog, okay?
(WHINING)
It's okay.
I made tea.
(BLOWING)
Go on, try it.
It'll make you better.
(BOTH BLOWING)
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
So, uh, who are you?
Atlanna.
Queen of Atlantis.
Wow.
I'm Tom. Keeper of lighthouse.
(CHUCKLES)
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
ARTHUR: She had fled
an arranged marriage.
Left her whole world behind.
But in my father's lighthouse,
she found something unexpected.
And my father
found the love of his life.
ANNOUNCER: (ON TV)
Category 4 Hurricane Arthur
is due to make landfall
sometime after 2:00 P.M.
How about Arthur?
After the hurricane?
After a legend.
He's a king, isn't he?
(CHUCKLES) He's more than that.
He's living proof
our people can coexist.
He could unite our worlds one day.
(CLICKS)
ATLANNA: And the trident could only
be wielded by the strongest Atlantean.
And it gave King Atlan mastery
over the seven seas.
It made him so powerful that
the ocean itself became jealous
and sent a terrible earthquake
to destroy Atlantis.
(GASPS) Down it fell,
to the bottom of the ocean.
But, legend has it
that one day a new king will come
who will use the
power of the trident
to put Atlantis back together again.
(DOG GROWLING)
(BARKING)
(GRUNTS) Take him!
SOLDIER: Queen Atlanna,
by the authority of King Orvax,
you are ordered to return to Atlantis.
TOM: Atlanna!
ARTHUR: But Atlantis' memory is long...
And its king refused to let her go.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GRUNTING)
TOM: Atlanna!
ATLANNA: Tom!
My weapon!
Here!
(GRUNTING)
(PANTING)
(WIND HOWLING)
ARTHUR: Their two worlds
were never meant to meet,
and I was a product of a love
that never should've been.
You don't have to do this, Atlanna.
Please.
No. They will always find me.
Next time, they'll send an army.
I have to go back.
It is the only way to save him.
Save you.
(CRYING) Where I come from...
The sea carries our tears away.
Not here.
Here you feel them.
I will return to you.
When it's safe.
One day.
Right here, at sunrise.
We'll be together again.
You stay strong, my little prince.
I'll always be with you.
Don't let him forget me. Hmm?
TOUR GUIDE: All life came from the sea,
so if we want to understand ourselves,
we must journey to where we began.
Now, today, we have better maps of Mars
than we do of our own sea floor.
Come on, closer. Come on, fishy.
Come on. Come over here.
Boys!
Stop that. Come on.
Come along.
Bye, fishy. Bye.
My name's Arthur. What's yours?
You guys hungry? Me, too.
MIKE: Check it out.
Arthur is talking to the fish.
Such a freak, Arthur.
(GROANS) Stop!
What are you gonna do about it, freak?
Stop it! Don't!
Let me go!
(PANICKED CHATTERING)
(PEOPLE GASPING)
(PEOPLE MURMURING)
(SAILORS GROANING)
CAPTAIN: Who are you?
PIRATE: Come on, let's go. Move it.
Come on. Hurry up.
Sir, we've secured the captain.
Distress signal's disabled.
We're running dark again.
But they heard it.
You can count on it.
I'll make you a deal.
I won't tell you how to captain...
And you don't tell
me how to pirate.
(GROANING)
DAVID: Where's the
rest of the crew?
Decided discretion
was the better part of valor
and sealed themselves up
in the torpedo bay.
Our reputation precedes us.
Your reputation.
This is your win.
Here.
Can't take that piece of junk.
It's the love of your life.
I never told you
the story behind it.
This was your grandfather's.
He was one of the Navy's first
frogmen during World War II.
He was so stealthy in the water,
his unit nicknamed him Manta.
But after the war,
his country forgot about him.
So, he went back to the sea,
scavenging and surviving with his wit...
And this knife.
He gave it to me
when I was your age.
And now it's yours, son.
(SONAR PINGING)
(RUMBLING)
(ALARM BLARING)
Did we just hit something?
No. Something hit us.
Sir, there's something out there.
Another submarine?
Uh... No. I think it's a man.
(RUMBLING)
(ALL YELPING)
(ALL CONTINUE YELPING)
(ALL GROANING)
(ALARM BLARING)
That's not a man.
PIRATE: Alpha, to the right.
Bravo team, sweep the passageway.
(HEAVY FOOTSTEPS CLANGING)
(BOTH GROAN)
Permission to come aboard?
(YELLS)
(GROANING)
(WHIMPERING)
(GRUNTING)
(GRUNTS)
(YELLING)
(SCREAMING)
(BODY THUDS)
(PIRATE CONTINUES WHIMPERING)
(GROANS)
(ARTHUR GRUNTING)
(METAL CLANGS)
(ALL GASP)
(BOTH SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
Aquaman!
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
(SAILOR GROANS)
(YELLING)
(GROANS)
(GRUNTS)
(EXHALES) I've waited
a long time for this.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
Am I supposed to know who you are?
I scavenge the high seas.
You're the Aquaman.
We were bound to
meet at some point.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
Let's not make it a habit.
Up.
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
(GROANING)
(GUN COCKS)
(GROANS)
Ow.
(SPEAKING MAORI)
(SCREAMING)
Dad!
Dad? Ow.
(JESSE GROANING)
(STRAINING)
That's your kid?
Shame on you.
(SCREAMING)
Boys got yourselves
into this mess.
Get yourselves out of it.
Bastard!
(SCREAMING)
Dad!
(GRUNTING) Wait!
Help me! He's trapped!
You can't leave him like this!
Please!
You killed innocent people.
You ask the sea for mercy.
(GRUNTS IN ANNOYANCE)
Get outta here! I got this!
Shut up, I'm not leaving you!
You need to live,
so you can kill that son of a bitch!
(SAILOR GROANING)
Now, go!
No!
Go!
Shut up!
No!
(DAVID YELLING IN FRUSTRATION)
(BEEPING)
Damn you!
Go.
(JESSE GASPS)
(GRUNTS)
(GROWLING)
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
(SPLASHING)
(THUD)
I always know where to find you.
Old habits.
(BOTH CHUCKLING)
Come on, I'll buy you breakfast.
All right!
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
(TOM EXHALES)
You want me to have them
put that in a sippy cup for you?
(EXHALES)
(TOM LAUGHS)
How is it that I can
breathe underwater,
but you can still drink me
under the table?
That's my superpower.
(LAUGHING)
NEWS ANCHOR: A Russian submarine
hijacked late last night
by high-tech pirates.
The same pirates who are suspected
in connection with the disappearance
of the Navy's highly classified
prototype stealth submarine.
And a further development,
we now have unconfirmed reports
that the Metahuman dubbed
by social media as "The Aquaman"
was responsible for
this daring rescue.
(SCOFFS) That's not me.
Bullshit. You're doing it,
aren't you? Huh?
What Vulko trained you to do.
I knew you couldn't
stand on the sidelines forever.
Your mother
always knew you were special.
Don't even start.
She believed you'd be the one
to unite our two worlds.
Just stop.
Whatever Atlantis' problems are,
you're bigger than them.
Atlantis murdered my mother.
You don't know that for sure.
Yes, I do.
They killed her.
For loving you and having me.
And you know it.
Son, one day you're gonna
have to stop blaming yourself.
(CHAIRS SCRAPING FLOOR)
CUE BALL: Hey, buddy.
You that fish boy from the TV?
Oh, great.
It's "fish man." What do you want?
I'll tell you what I want.
Could we get a picture with you?
You're like our local hero, man.
It would mean a lot.
Just a quick...
Whatever.
All right. Let's do this.
Don't touch me.
Right, that's exactly right.
I'm gonna go down here.
There we go. Everybody smile.
(CAMERA CLICKING)
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
(SEAGULLS CAWING)
(SEAHORSES WHINNYING)
He understands the significance
of this meeting.
He'll hear you out.
(WHINNYING CONTINUES)
(SHARKS SNARLING)
(WHINNYING)
(GROWLING)
King Orm.
King Nereus.
You picked a meeting place too
close to the surface for my liking.
You don't recognize
the Council of the Kings?
In Atlan's time,
when the Seven Kingdoms were one,
our ancestors gathered here.
Atlantis sat here
at the head of the table.
Xebel, as always, by his side.
Brine. Fishermen.
The Deserters and the Trench
had not yet fallen.
The Lost Nation had
not yet vanished.
Together, they were the greatest
empire the world had ever seen.
But now, I sit on Atlan's throne,
shackled by archaic laws and politics.
While the threat above us
grows undeniably...
Violence has always
plagued the surface.
They will destroy themselves.
Not before destroying us first.
We have been hiding long enough.
The time has come
for Atlantis to rise again.
VULKO: We honor you, King Nereus,
by inviting Xebel
to be the first kingdom
to join King Orm's alliance.
As if you had a choice, Vulko.
By law,
you need four of the Seven Kingdoms
to ascend and attack.
The Lost Nation and the Deserters
have long perished.
The Trench are nothing but animals.
The Brine will never join you,
and the Fishermen are cowards.
Without me and my army to convince
them, your plans are stillborn.
But I know what you really want.
Once you've obtained
the pledge of the four kingdoms,
you will be ordained
Ocean Master.
That is merely a title.
I'm no fool, King Orm.
As Ocean Master,
you'll be commander
of the greatest military might
on this planet.
I am the natural choice to lead it.
Are you?
What about the rumors
that there's another?
An Atlantean,
living among the surface.
One of royal blood.
You may sit on the throne of Atlantis,
but your claim to it is weak.
How can you possibly hope
to unite the empire?
My mother's bastard
has never even been to Atlantis.
His loyalty is to the surface.
(ALL SCREAMING)
(WHINING)
(SCREECHING)
Surface-dwellers! To arms!
(GROANS)
(SEAHORSE WHINNYING)
(GRUNTING)
Your king is injured!
(NEREUS GROANING)
(ROARING)
(GRUNTS)
(GRUNTING)
I'm not trying to start a war.
The war has already begun.
Then it's time we send them
a message they'll hear.
TOM: I'm good.
ARTHUR: Stop.
TOM: Here're the keys.
ARTHUR: Thank you.
TOM: Let's go home and
work on your tā moko. Huh?
If your grandpops was still alive,
he'd be banging our heads
for not finishing it.
Yes, he would,
but there is plenty of time for that.
We got to get you to bed.
Got it?
(SPLASHING)
I've been looking for you.
Oh, no, no, no...
I need you to come
with me to Atlantis.
Listen, I'm gonna
tell you the same thing
that I told that
rusty starfish Vulko.
Except nicer,
because you're a lady.
No, thank you. I'm not interested.
You defeated Steppenwolf
and saved Atlantis.
That had nothing to
do with Atlantis.
Your half-brother King Orm is about
to declare war upon the surface world.
Billions will die.
Your people and mine.
We must stop him.
And how do you propose we do that?
You are
the firstborn son of Queen Atlanna.
The throne is yours by birthright.
The only way to stop this war
and save both worlds
is for you to take your
rightful place as king.
(LAUGHING)
You think if I just show up,
Orm's gonna give up the throne?
I'm the bastard son of the queen
your people executed.
Trust me. I am no king.
I agree.
That's awesome. Cool.
But, Vulko seems to
believe in you for some reason,
and that's why I'm here.
Vulko has learned of the location
of the Lost Trident of Atlan.
Ooh, fairy tales. It's a myth.
It's not a myth.
With the Sacred Trident,
the people will listen to you.
You can then claim your birthright
and dethrone Orm.
My birthright?
It died with my mother.
But I promise you this.
If Orm attacks,
I will treat him exactly the
same way your people treated her.
With no mercy.
(TRUCK DOOR CLOSING)
(ENGINE STARTING)
(SHIP APPROACHING)
That submarine was barely operational,
but it served its purpose.
One of your kind intervened.
He is not one of us.
He killed my father.
Our transaction has ended.
Keep the money. I want Aquaman.
(SEAGULLS SCREECHING)
(BOTH YELPING)
(GRUNTS)
Dad!
Pops!
(ARTHUR GRUNTS)
(EXHALES DEEPLY)
Come on, Pops.
Come on! He's not breathing.
Move! Let me help.
ARTHUR: Come on, Pops.
(COUGHING)
Come on.
(TOM EXHALES)
(ARTHUR SIGHS IN RELIEF)
I don't even know your name.
It's Princess Y'Mera
Xebella Challa.
You may call me Mera.
Thank you, Mera.
(ARTHUR GRUNTS)
(SIREN BLARING)
Dear God.
This was Orm's doing.
The worst is yet to come.
REPORTER 1:
There's a flash flood warning here
that was just extended
for a couple hours.
REPORTER 2: Unprecedented sights
from all over the world today.
We are seeing warships and trash
washed up by massive waves.
REPORTER 3: These extraordinary scenes
of coastlines deluged with waste
and garbage are taking place
all over the world.
REPORTER 2: Decades of pollution
has been thrown back onto land.
REPORTER 4:
Many are asking the question,
"Was this a natural disaster
or something else?"
No. This was no natural disaster.
They threw out our garbage
and our warships.
This was our first contact
with the people of Atlantis.
There you go again
with your insane Atlantean theory.
You have absolutely no
proof, Dr. Shin.
Open your eyes.
We already have
an Atlantean living among us,
and his name is Aquaman.
MERA: What is it?
This is the exact spot that Vulko
gave me my first swimming lesson.
VULKO: You have to forget all
the teaching of the surface world
and go deeper to uncover
your Atlantean instincts.
But I already know how to swim.
Not even close.
ARTHUR: Just so we're clear,
I'll help you stop this war.
But then, I'm done.
Maybe that's for the best.
The ocean is more than
our life source, Arthur.
It is who we are.
Wait, you can talk underwater?
I can talk underwater, too!
This is awesome!
Oh, we can do more than just talk.
Being Atlantean means more than
just being able to breathe water.
Your body is equipped to survive
the extreme cold and pressure,
and your eyes adjust
to see in the dark.
(SQUAWKS)
(WHOOPING)
This is awesome!
(CONTINUES WHOOPING)
So, Vulko,
when can I meet my mother?
Soon, my young prince.
When you're ready, I'll take you
to Atlantis to meet the queen.
I hid my ship in here.
ARTHUR: Listen, I'm not
getting in that thing.
Well, to get where we're going,
you're gonna have to.
Your fish ship
has been marinating in chum butter.
I'm gonna come out
smelling like swamp butt.
That'd be an improvement.
(SNIFFS)
(COUGHS)
Yup. Okay.
ARTHUR: What's the point in
having a bridge underwater?
MERA: The Gateway Bridge is
a remnant of the Old World.
It's also the only way in or out
of the Capital.
Why can't they just
go over the walls?
Security is impenetrable.
Even if they did
manage to evade the guards,
they'd never get past
the hydro-cannons.
People try to sneak
in all the time.
Yeah, right.
ARTHUR: What is this?
MERA: Customs and border control.
Don't worry.
I have diplomatic clearance.
Welcome home.
There's a safe house
down in the Old City.
The Highborns never
venture to the sea floor.
We're here.
What is this?
We use this air pocket
as an extra layer of precaution.
Only the Highborns can
breathe water as well as air.
VULKO: Plus, it keeps the animals out.
They get kind of messy.
Vulko. Here I am, old man.
After all these years,
you finally get what you wanted.
Arthur, I wish it was
under better circumstances.
I can't believe Orm attacked.
It wasn't an attack.
Legally, he's not allowed to yet.
What he did to your surface
warships was merely a warning.
What provoked it?
King Orm and your father
were ambushed by the surface.
By the surface? I don't think so.
They still think
Atlantis is a fairy tale.
I was there.
A surface warship fired at us.
Now, Xebel sides with Atlantis,
giving Orm a fleet big enough to force
the other two kingdoms to join him.
If we're going to prevent this war,
you must dethrone him now.
How many times do I have to tell you?
I don't wanna be king.
You don't understand.
Once he is named Ocean Master,
it'll be too late.
The power at his disposal will be
unlike anything you have ever seen.
I'm from the surface.
No one is gonna take me seriously.
Okay? I don't even
know where to begin.
By winning
the hearts and minds of the people
by proving to them that you're
worthy, and retrieving this.
Hmm.
I already got one of those.
Not like this one, you don't.
This is the Lost Trident of Atlan.
Oh, I know the story.
It's more than a story. It's real.
It was forged by the greatest
weapon masters in history.
Crafted from Poseidon's steel
for King Atlan,
the first ruler of Atlantis.
Legend says the trident was imbued
with the power to command the sea.
So what happened to it?
To know that is to go back to
the time before the Great Fall,
when King Atlan ruled
over all that was,
when the kingdoms of
Atlantis were one.
It was a time of great prosperity
and technological advancement.
We had unlocked
the secret of unlimited energy
at a time when the rest of the world
still thought the earth was flat.
But we became too ambitious,
too hungry for power.
(ALL SCREAMING)
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
VULKO: The ocean swallowed
us, and Atlantis sank.
But the very power
that collapsed our civilization
also paved the way to our future.
It gave us the ability
to breathe underwater.
And so, we evolved.
Others regressed, became savage.
(SNARLS)
And the king lived out the remainder
of his days in self-imposed exile.
Neither he nor the trident
were ever seen again.
One of our archeological teams
uncovered this a few months ago.
It's an ancient recording
dating back to the First Dynasty.
I believe it contains
Atlan's final message to his people
and the whereabouts
of the Sacred Trident.
So, what does it say?
We don't know.
The technology's too old.
The cylinder bears the markings
of the Deserter Kingdom.
You must take it there
and retrieve the message.
The clue to Atlan's final
resting place is inside of this.
(ALL GROAN)
Border Defense.
You are under arrest for illegal entry.
No!
You mustn't be seen here!
(GRUNTING)
I don't suppose you want
to talk about this, do you?
Neither do I.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(GROANING)
In the name of His Highness, King
Orm, I place you under arrest.
(SCREAMING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GRUNTING)
ORM: Welcome to Atlantis...
Brother.
I can't believe
you're finally here.
I've heard so many
stories about you.
All these years,
I've been ashamed of my mother
for defiling herself
with a surface-dweller.
Ashamed of the fact that I have
a half-breed brother
whose heart
I wanted to run my trident through.
But now that you're finally here
before me, I must admit...
(YELLING)
I am conflicted.
You want conflict, why don't you take
these chains off, little brother?
And we'll see who gets run through.
Yes, I see you've brought
our mother's weapon.
Is that why you've come here
after all this time?
To kill me?
I came here to stop a maniac
from destroying the world.
I see.
And how do you plan
to stop the atrocities
that the surface
continues to commit?
Because for a century,
they have polluted our waters
and poisoned our children.
And now, their skies burn
and our oceans boil.
(GROANING)
And you've come all this way to
take sides against your own people?
There are no sides
in a war like this.
You have clearly chosen a side and
come here to challenge the throne.
If that's what it takes
to stop your war.
Are you invoking
the Combat of the Kings?
Call it whatever you want.
I call it an ass-whooping.
Well then,
perhaps that's how we'll proceed.
Your Majesty!
Orm, please.
Don't you see?
If I defeat the
firstborn son of Atlanna
in a formal challenge
in front of everyone,
then all Seven Kingdoms will have to
concede that I am the one true king.
Your Majesty, there is no victory
in defeating the ignorant.
Your brother is
clearly an imbecile.
Your Highness,
he doesn't know our ways.
Then he's about to
get an education.
Are you officially challenging me?
Hell yes, I challenge you.
And when I win...
If you win,
I will cease all immediate action.
The war is over.
But if I win...
You're over.
Let's do it.
So be it.
Challenge has been
made, and I accept.
Prepare him for the Ring of Fire.
Wait. The ring of what? (GROANS)
VULKO: How could you be so foolish
to let Orm bait you into a fight?
It seems to me like I just
solved all of our problems.
I beat him in a battle, war's over,
I get to go home.
You're a formidable
fighter on land,
but here you're out of your
element, literally.
Orm has spent
his entire life underwater,
training to be a warrior,
training to be the best.
You taught me how to
fight, Cobra Kai.
Let's see if you remember anything.
So, what's with the big fork?
It's a trident.
Now, defend yourself.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
(EXHALES)
(YOUNG ARTHUR GRUNTS)
What the hell is this?
I'll teach you this move
when you've mastered the trident.
It's not fair.
This thing is so big and awkward.
Why can't I use a sword?
That's your mother's trident.
A traditional weapon of royalty.
You'll never be a king
until you've mastered it.
Why has she never come to see
me, huh?
I told you, when you're ready...
Stop lying to me!
I've done everything you ever asked.
And every time I pass a test,
you make up another one.
When am I gonna be good enough?
Does she not love me?
Your mother loved you
more than anything in the world.
But she had to return to Atlantis
to keep you safe.
Her marriage to King Orvax
was arranged a long time ago,
so she had to marry him...
And bear him a son, Prince Orm.
When Orvax
eventually found out about you,
he became overwhelmed with jealousy
and sacrificed her
to the creatures of the Trench.
Are you saying they executed her?
Because she had me?
(GRUNTS)
I remember...
Everything.
ORM: I have something for you.
It belonged to my mother.
Tell me...
Do you think she would have enjoyed
watching her sons murder each other?
I understand your fear
and your reluctance, Mera.
I truly do. I don't want war...
Don't patronize me!
I know you.
What you're doing
flies in the face of everything
that your mother taught us
when we were children.
If she were here...
But she's not here, is she?
What my mother taught
us was treason.
Don't follow in her wake.
ARTHUR: All right! So, this is
the big, old ring of fire, huh?
How's it work?
I just kick your ass right here?
Vulko.
Will you escort my betrothed
to the royal box?
Let's go, Lady Mera.
Down here, we have a legend
about the Karathen,
an ancient sea monster so powerful
that even King Atlan himself feared it.
So, he imprisoned it
in the depths of the ocean.
And in that abyss, the creature
bides its time waiting to rise again.
Atlantis has been lying in wait...
And now, the beast has awakened.
There was a time when I wanted
to meet you more than anything.
Get to know my little brother.
Let him know that he wasn't alone,
that we were in it together.
If only I had known what a
dick you would turn out to be.
You were the reason
our mother was executed.
And I've hated you
for it ever since.
But I do not want to kill
you, Arthur.
I'm going to give you one chance.
Go home.
Do not ever come back to Atlantis.
You are not going to win this.
A war is coming to the surface
whether you like it or not.
And I am bringing the wrath
of the seven seas with me.
You know I can't let that happen.
I know.
What the hell is that?
The Ring of Fire.
Yeah!
(CROWD CHEERING)
Shit.
People of Atlantis, hear me!
My brother has come from the surface
to challenge me for the throne.
Let us settle his claim
in the ancient way.
By bloodshed do the gods
make known their will!
(CROWD SHOUTING)
(CROWD BOOING)
MAN 1: Traitor!
MAN 2: Traitor!
(BOOING CONTINUES)
WOMAN: You'll never be king!
(RHYTHMIC DRUMMING)
Never thought I'd see the day
when my own father
would bow before the
king of Atlantis.
The surface-dwellers drew first blood.
What would you have us do?
Beg them for mercy?
I detest the surface
as much as you do.
But don't you find the timing
of all of this a bit convenient?
But you wouldn't be that gullible,
would you?
You want this war too, don't you?
It is past time the surface-dwellers
learned their place in the world.
If this is how it must be done,
then so be it.
You have our mother's trident.
Powerful, but flawed like her.
I wield my father's.
And it has never known defeat!
(ORM YELLING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
I promised Atlanna I'd protect him.
(ARTHUR GRUNTING)
This isn't a competition.
It's an execution.
(GRUNTS)
(YELLING)
(CROWD GASPS)
(ALL CHEERING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(YELLING)
(ALL CHEERING)
(SHOUTING)
(CHEERING CONTINUES)
I am the one true king!
(YELLS)
(GROANS)
(GASPING)
(VOMITS)
You waiting for an invitation?
Get in!
(ECHOING) Mera!
Oh, yeah. So, what's the plan?
The plan was to recover Atlan's
trident, then challenge Orm.
Okay, so we're doing things
a little out of order.
Shit happens.
Heads up!
We got a bogey on our six!
What does that even mean?
Bad guys behind us.
Then just say that!
Bad guys behind us!
(ARTHUR YELPS)
(SCREAMS)
(BOTH SCREAMING)
Whoa, whoa, wait, you said
we couldn't go over these walls.
I did!
You said there were hydro-cannons!
I did, now shut up!
(ARTHUR YELPING) Oh, shit!
(BEEPING)
(HIGH-PITCHED BEEP)
(GROWLS)
(BOTH GRUNT)
ARTHUR: Shit!
(SCREAMS)
Shit.
We're not dead yet!
But I'm hoping he'll think we are.
ARTHUR: Oh!
(YELPS)
Here, hold this.
What are you doing?
Listen, it worked for Pinocchio.
Who?
Never mind.
Come here, get in. Come on.
MERA: Great.
So we're getting eaten.
How are you even doing
this, anyway?
I don't know.
I can hear them sometimes,
and they can hear me.
Right. Because you're both big,
dumb animals.
Hey, I just saved your life.
I saved yours first!
(BOOMING SOUND)
(ARTHUR LAUGHS MOCKINGLY)
She said, "Coast is clear."
So, where to now?
To the ocean of sand
your people call the Sahara.
All right. (GRUNTS)
(HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYING)
(CHICKENS CLUCKING)
PILOT: I don't usually take charters,
but I don't usually get paid
in pirate treasure.
Thanks for the ride, buddy.
Oh, man.
Are you okay?
I've never been so high up before.
Or so far from home.
But at least you have a home.
Not anymore.
I can never go back.
I betrayed everything
when I saved you from the coliseum.
Yeah, but you're engaged to the king.
They have to take you back.
Atlantis is many wonderful things.
But forgiving, it is not.
Yeah, but you're royalty.
So was your mother.
If I went back now,
I'd be sacrificed to the Trench.
Even my own father
wouldn't take me back.
Look on the bright side,
now you don't have to marry some
tool bag that you're not in love with.
My obligation isn't to love.
It is to my family and my nation,
and I've turned my back on both.
Sometimes,
you have to do what's right,
even if your heart
aches against it.
(BEEPING)
Your Highness.
The tracker places Princess Mera
here, in the Deserter Kingdom.
You said she was dead.
Apparently not.
NEREUS: Then your brother
still lives as well?
ORM: Not for long.
Captain Murk,
assemble a strike force immediately.
No! Mera is to be arrested
and safely returned to me.
She betrayed the throne.
She is a daughter of Xebel.
If any harm befalls her,
our coalition is over.
VULKO: Your Highness,
we are now entering the waters
of the Fishermen Kingdom.
Securing the alliance
of the other two kingdoms
should be our immediate concern.
My vizier is correct. As usual.
Arrest them and bring back
King Nereus' daughter unharmed.
(DEVICE BEEPING)
We're here!
Hey!
Is there anything nearby?
Nothing but desert
for hundreds of K's, mate!
Nothing but desert.
MERA: He's wrong.
Hey! What are you doing?
Wait! No! Oh...
She just jumped!
She didn't have a parachute!
Redheads! You got to love 'em.
(WHOOPING)
ARTHUR: Shit!
(YELLS)
(ARTHUR GRUNTING)
(BOTH COUGHING)
(ARTHUR LAUGHING)
Oh, you're crazier than I thought!
(BEEPING)
A-ha!
This way.
You were defeated the last time
because your surface weapons failed you.
Ours will not.
It's prototype armor
for the next generation
Atlantean soldier.
Revenge is something
we Atlanteans understand.
You will lead my finest commandos
as your personal army
to hunt down the
half-breed abomination.
I cannot touch them, but you can.
He's fled to your world.
Kill him and the woman he's with,
and you will be rewarded.
Killing him is my reward.
ORM: The crown jewel.
Still experimental.
Converts water
into beams of energized plasma.
(POP MUSIC PLAYING)
(BEEPING)
Hmm.
I think I'm gonna
need a bigger helmet.
MERA: One of the tribes of
Atlantis broke off and settled here
when this region
was still an inland sea.
When the water dried up,
they perished along with it.
Perished? Yeah, that's terrific.
We're getting close now.
Oh, yeah? Close to what?
Dying of thirst?
Close to getting
punched in the face!
Look, Fight Club, I know you're new
to how things work up here.
Why don't you look around?
We are lost.
You see that over there?
Hey, what is that?
Nada. This place is a wasteland.
You're the one who calls
this wasteland a home.
This isn't my home!
It's not like the whole surface
looks like this!
MERA: Oh, no, of course not.
You've also got disgusting cities
whose sewers empty out into our ocean
and whole mountains
made out of trash.
And, oh, you've got great factories
that do nothing but belch
out filth and melt ice caps.
Okay. Point taken. Listen.
Yeah, we got
some idiots running the show,
but we've got
some good things too, all right?
We got green forests and big
mountains and beautiful lakes.
You'd love 'em.
They're like little baby oceans.
Are you trying to provoke me?
I'm just saying you cannot judge a
place before you've even seen it.
You've judged Atlantis on far less.
(ARTHUR GRUNTS)
No. Would you
just stop it with that? No.
Your stupid Atlantean GPS just
told you to jump out of an airplane
over the middle of the desert,
and now we are stranded.
(SCREAMING)
(SCOFFS) If you're the next true
king, we're doomed.
(GRUNTS)
(HOLE BELCHES)
(MERA YELPING)
(MERA SCREAMING)
(ARTHUR GRUNTS)
(LAUGHING)
(PANTING)
That was awesome.
(STONE CLATTERING)
Oh. Look what I found.
What you found?
Yeah.
Check this place out.
This is badass!
(ECHOING)
MERA: This is the Hall of Armory.
Where the legends say
Atlan's trident was forged.
ARTHUR: I don't think
they're legends anymore.
MERA: Vulko was right.
It's real.
MERA: Huh.
Nothing.
Of course it's not working.
It's been sitting here collecting dust
since before the Sahara was a desert.
Man!
"Since before the
Sahara was a desert."
Thank you
for repeating what I just said.
It's completely dried out.
(SIGHS) Let's just say
you do your best thinking
when you're not thinking at all.
All right, now hold still.
Hey. What are you doing?
We need water,
and you're the closest source.
Now, hold still.
ARTHUR: Hmm.
(CHUCKLES)
Show-off.
I could have just peed on it.
King Atlan.
In this trident
resides the power of Atlantis.
In the wrong hands,
it would bring destruction.
But in the hands of the true heir,
it would unite all our kingdoms
above and below.
If you seek my power,
you must prove your worth.
Journey beyond the edge of
the world to the Hidden Sea.
Look inside the bottle
for the charted path.
Only in the hands of the true king
can he truly see.
ARTHUR: Hmm.
We can't let Orm find this.
Hey! Wait!
(GROANS)
What?
Shouldn't we have
written it down first?
I memorized it. Didn't you?
Oh, yeah. Totally.
What'd he just say?
"Something something trident."
"Look inside the bottle
for the charted path."
It's our next stop.
("SHE'S A MYSTERY TO ME" PLAYING)
(BICYCLE BELL RINGING)
(GASPS)
(BOTH CHUCKLING)
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
I'm starting to think you actually
like these surface-dwellers.
It would be wrong to judge a place
I've never seen before.
I'll be right back.
Don't go anywhere.
Well, apparently, it's just right
up on the hill. A big old castle.
And I just learned something
very interesting.
Pinocchio.
You risked our lives based on something
you read in a children's book?
Wait, it's a book? (CHUCKLES)
How about that?
Oh!
I got it from the movie.
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
RICOU: King Nereus, I had
hoped our people had evolved
beyond that ancient notion
that war with the
surface is inevitable.
It is the position of the Fishermen
that when the time comes to make
ourselves known to the landsmen,
it should be to educate them,
not to destroy them.
I admire your lofty aspirations,
King Ricou.
But I suspect they are but clouds of ink
hiding the heart of a coward.
How dare you!
(WEAPONS POWERING UP)
Please. I implore you.
You're a kingdom of bloated
philosophers and flaccid poets
whose waters have grown stagnant,
and it sickens me.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
My King!
The king is dead!
Long live his heir.
Princess.
Prepare your armies, Your Highness.
We move against the Brine Kingdom
at once.
ARTHUR: What did the
recording say, again?
MERA: "Journey beyond the edge
of the world to the Hidden Sea.
Look in the bottle
for the charted path.
Only in the hands of the true king
can he truly see."
"Look in the bottle
for the charted path."
Hmm.
Oh, man.
What?
Wow. (LAUGHING)
That's awesome.
Let me see.
Wow. But how do you know
where to point it?
Here, let me see.
What was the last line?
"Only in the hands of the true king
can he truly see."
"Only in the hands of the true..."
Marcus Agrippa.
He was a great general,
but he wasn't a king.
Neither was Scipio.
How do you know all this stuff?
Because of my pops.
He made sure I knew my history.
None of these guys are kings,
except this guy. Romulus.
First king of Rome.
"Only in the hands of the true king
can he truly see."
(ARTHUR CLEARS THROAT)
(ARTHUR LAUGHING)
There it is. That's our heading.
What? Let me see.
We did it!
ARTHUR: Oh!
That's not bad for an
imbecile, huh?
Not bad at all.
(BOTH GROANING)
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
Mera.
BLACK MANTA: "Loathsomeness waits
and dreams in the deep,
and decay spreads over
the tottering cities of men."
Get back!
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
Arthur!
I order you to stand down!
Princess Mera, you've been charged
with high treason.
(SIZZLING)
(GROANING)
Who the hell are you?
Maybe this will jog your memory.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(GROANING)
(ALL GRUNTING)
(CHOKING)
(SCREAMING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
You're the guy from the sub.
BLACK MANTA: That's right.
(GROANS LOUDLY)
But now I have Atlantean steel.
(ARTHUR GROANING)
Call me "Black Manta."
(ARTHUR SCREAMING)
(MUSIC PLAYING ON RADIO)
(ARTHUR GROANS)
BLACK MANTA: You thought
you could walk away?
(BOTH GRUNTING)
I thought I told you
not to make this a habit.
(BLACK MANTA GROANS)
(APOLOGIZES IN ITALIAN)
(ARTHUR SCREAMING)
You can't run.
You owe me blood!
How'd you find me?
Your lady friend has people
who like to keep tabs on her.
(GROANS)
(PANTING)
(GROWLS)
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
(YELPS)
(BELL TOLLS)
(SCREAMING)
(GROANING)
(SCREAMING CONTINUES)
(TOLLS)
No! (GRUNTS)
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
(PANTING)
(MAN SCREAMING)
(GRUNTING)
Come on.
(ARTHUR SPEAKING ITALIAN)
(IN ENGLISH) Everybody, inside.
Get inside.
(CONTINUES SPEAKING ITALIAN)
(SCREAMS)
(IN ENGLISH) I'll show you the
same mercy you showed my father.
And gut you like the fish you are!
(ARTHUR GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(GROANING)
(CHOKING)
(GRUNTING)
(GASPING)
(SIGHS)
(YELLING)
(SUIT SPUTTERING)
(GRUNTING)
(ALARM BEEPING)
(GRUNTS)
Arthur!
(GROANING)
Mera, they're tracking you.
What?
They're tracking you.
(ARTHUR GRUNTS)
Arthur, stay with me.
Arthur, wake up! Arthur.
(FLUTE PLAYING)
(GROANING)
(CONTINUES GROANING)
(PLAYING SOFT TUNE)
ARTHUR: Um...
Did you steal a boat?
Are the boats at the marina
not for public use?
No, those belong to people.
Huh.
(CHUCKLES)
MERA: Those were
Orm's elite commandos.
But the one who led them,
he wasn't Atlantean.
I've never seen him before.
Yeah, I have.
He and his father were pirates.
And he blames me for
his father's death.
They picked a dangerous line of trade.
It's not your fault.
That's not how it feels.
It was up to me, and I let him die.
I could've saved him, but I didn't.
And now, I made an enemy,
and he could have hurt you.
And that would have been my fault.
Well, he's behind us now.
It's what lies ahead
that should concern us.
The charted path leads
to the Kingdom of the Trench.
Are those the same creatures
that killed my mother?
Yes.
She was taken there
and sacrificed to them.
It's become a place of death.
We know next to nothing
about what's down there.
We should turn back.
We can still warn the surface.
Try and prepare them for what's coming.
Turn back?
Look, I learned from a young age
not to show weakness.
Okay? I solve my problems
with my anger and my fists.
I'm a blunt instrument,
and I'm damn good at it.
But I've done nothing but get
my ass kicked this whole trip.
I'm no leader. I'm not a king.
I do not work or play
well with others.
And I can't let you die trying
to turn me into something that I'm not.
You think you're unworthy to lead
because you're of two different worlds.
But that is exactly
why you are worthy.
You are the bridge
between land and sea.
I can see that now.
The only question is...
Can you?
The tracking on Lady Mera
is still dark, Your Highness.
Vulko.
My trusted vizier
who has stood by the throne
since my father sat upon it.
Have you any advice for me
as this war begins?
I have already given it, My King.
But I will stand by your decision,
as always.
My decision.
To protect it.
While you betray it.
You think I do not know
of your treachery?
That you have remained loyal
to my mother's bastard son.
That you have spent years training
him to take the throne from me.
Do not deny it.
I do not.
Why?
I am the pureblood.
I have devoted my life to Atlantis.
He wanted nothing to do with it.
You swore to serve the throne!
I do serve it.
Arthur may only be half-Atlantean,
but he's already twice the king
you'll ever be.
Take him.
But make sure he has a view.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(GASPS)
(GROWLING)
(ROARING)
(GRUNTS)
(MERA GRUNTING)
(SNARLING)
(GRUNTING)
(SCREECHES)
(GRUNTS)
(YELLS)
(ARTHUR GRUNTS)
ARTHUR: What the hell
are these things?
The Trench! We're here!
There are too many of them!
Come on, inside!
(CREATURES SNARLING)
(SCREECHING)
They're from the depths.
They're scared of the light. Here!
(CREATURES SNARLING)
ARTHUR: Come on!
You ready to jump?
(THUNDER CRASHING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(CREATURES SCREECHING)
Over there!
(CREATURES SNARLING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(CREATURES SCREECHING)
MERA: That thing will tear us apart.
We don't have a choice!
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Arthur!
Mera!
(GROWLING)
(CREATURE CAWING)
(MERA PANTING)
ARTHUR: Mera!
Mera!
Arthur.
Mom?
(CREATURES CAWING)
ATLANNA: King Orvax sacrificed me
to the Trench, but I survived.
I fought my way through as you did,
and I ended up here.
MERA: You've been here
alone for 20 years?
ATLANNA: Yes.
(MERA GROANS)
Come. Sit here.
You must forgive me.
Forgive me for everything.
This happened because you had me.
Not for having you.
None of this is your fault.
I made a choice. I had to leave...
To save you, to save your father.
Tell me. Tell me about him.
Is he...
He still walks to
the end of that dock.
Every morning.
Every day.
Waiting for you.
(CRYING)
Why didn't you ever come back?
Because the portal that brought
you here won't let us return.
The trident is the only way back.
But it is guarded by the Karathen.
The creature from our legends,
it's real.
It lies beyond the waterfall.
We'll go with you.
We can fight it together.
No.
It's too powerful.
I've tried many
times over the years.
The creature will only allow
the true king to pass.
You're afraid.
Yes.
Good.
You're ready.
MERA: Atlantis has
always had a king.
Now, it needs something more.
But what could be
greater than a king?
A hero.
A king fights only for his nation.
You fight for everyone.
(RUMBLING)
KARATHEN: You do not belong here.
I have guarded the trident against
false kings since the beginning.
And for a thousand years
I have seen the greatest champions
try and fail.
But never have I sensed one
as unworthy as you.
You dare come here
with your tainted mongrel blood
to claim Atlantis'
greatest treasure?
(GRUNTS)
So be it...
Half-breed.
(GROANING)
You thought yourself worthy?
You thought yourself a king?
You dishonor this place
with your presence.
Stop!
You're right.
I am a half-breed mongrel.
But I did not come here
because I thought I was worthy.
I know I'm not.
You understand me?
I do.
No mortal has conversed with me
since King Atlan.
Who are you?
I'm nobody.
I came because I had no choice.
I came to save my home
and the people that I love.
I came because the trident
is their only hope.
And if that's not good enough...
Then screw you.
No man has ever freed the trident
from Atlan's grip.
Should he deem you unworthy...
Well, I haven't feasted in eons,
and I am famished.
(GASPS)
(YELLING)
The one true king.
NEREUS: Remember, the Brine
are powerful, savage brutes,
but a swift assault aimed directly
at their leadership will turn the tide.
Defeat the Brine King,
and you will command the greatest
military might on this planet.
Today, we unite our kingdoms.
Tomorrow, we scorch the surface!
Rise, Atlantis!
Death to the Atlantean Hagfish!
(BRINE SNARLING)
(ORM YELLING)
(ATLANTEANS GROWLING)
BRINE KING:
We will not bow to Atlantis.
We're gonna give them a fight
that they will never forget!
(SOLDIERS SHOUTING)
(SCREECHES)
(GRUNTS)
(CHITTERING)
(ATLANTEAN SCREAMS)
(CREAKING)
(YELLING)
(BRINE KING GROANING)
(YELLS)
No! We need him!
Join me or die.
You expect me
to address you as Your Highness?
Not Your Highness.
Call me...
Ocean Master.
You can take my army,
you soft-bellied slug.
But you will never
have my allegiance!
So be it!
(YELLING)
(GROANING)
(ALL YELPING)
What the...
(ATLANTEANS SCREAMING)
(ROARING)
(YELLING)
The king has risen.
Attack!
(SCREECHES)
(ROARING)
(YELLING)
(SCREECHING)
(ATLANTEANS YELPING)
(SEA CREATURES CALLING)
(SCREAMS)
(RIDERS GROANING)
(ROARING)
(GROANS)
(GRUNTING)
There are too many casualties.
We have to stop the fighting now.
I'll find my father.
But you must defeat Orm.
And what if I can't?
Last time, he was in his element.
This time, make him fight in yours.
ARTHUR: Um...
What was the plan, again?
The plan is to not get killed.
Yeah, good plan. Don't get killed.
(URGING SEAHORSE)
(WHINNYING)
(CREATURES SCREECHING)
(GRUNTS)
(ALL GROANING)
(YELLING)
The Trench! He commands the Trench!
Impossible!
(ORM YELLING)
(BOTH SCREAM)
Stand down! Let her pass.
Please, Father, he has the trident.
I know you think this
war is necessary,
but Arthur is king
by our most sacred law.
And if you turn your
back on that now,
then the Atlantis you're
fighting for is already dead.
XEBEL SOLDIER: It's true!
The half-breed wields
King Atlan's trident.
He commands the sea!
Then that half-breed is your king.
(YELLING)
(URGING SEAHORSE)
(CONTINUES YELLING)
(CREATURE ROARING)
(GRUNTS)
Vulko! Come on, he needs our help!
VULKO: We can't! Look.
The people must bear witness.
That trident
doesn't change what you are.
A half-breed bastard.
Atlantis will never accept you
as its king.
Well, then by bloodshed...
Do the gods make known their will.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Yield the throne. Yield it!
(STRAINING)
(ORM YELLING)
(GROANING)
(ARTHUR GRUNTS)
Finish it.
Yield the throne.
Mercy is not our way.
Maybe you haven't
noticed, brother...
But I'm not one of you.
Do it!
Kill me!
ATLANNA: No!
That is enough killing.
Mother?
Oh, my son.
It's a long story.
I'll tell ya later.
Come on!
I don't understand. We thought...
I know.
Arthur saved me.
You're with him?
I am.
You're both my children,
and I love you so much.
But you have been misguided.
Your father taught you
that there were two worlds.
He was wrong.
The land and the sea
are one.
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
My queen.
Vulko.
Take him.
But make sure he has a view.
When you're ready,
let's talk.
People of Atlantis,
today began in bloodshed,
but let it end in joy.
I give you King Arthur of Atlantis.
Hail to the king!
ALL: Hail to the king!
(ATLANTEANS CHANTING)
So, what do I do now?
Be their king.
Ooh.
This is gonna be fun.
(CHANTS IN MAORI)
(WHOOPING)
(ALL CHEERING)
(ROARING)
(GASPS)
You came back. You're back.
Yes. Yes.
ARTHUR: My father was
a lighthouse keeper.
My mother was a queen.
They were never meant to meet...
But their love saved the world.
They made me what I am.
A son of the land,
and a king of the seas.
I am the protector of the deep.
I am...
Aquaman.
(MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING)
DR. SHIN: Hey!
DR. SHIN: I spent 15 years
at the United States Institute
of Marine Science...
JAMES: Weren't you fired?
...studying oceanic phenomenon,
and this is the most conclusive
evidence we have to date.
Deep-sea seismographs have recorded
explosions on the ocean floor.
(GROANING)
DR. SHIN: We have satellite imagery
of debris from Atlantean warships
floating on the surface...
JAMES: Dr. Shin!
Will you please let me finish?
JAMES: Here we go again.
Atlantean?
DR. SHIN: Yes. The government
does not want us to know
about the threat
that exists right here...
Yeah, I wouldn't do
that if I were you.
(BLACK MANTA SUIT POWERING UP)
This is Atlantean
technology, isn't it?
Can you tell me how you got this?
Sure. But first,
you got to tell me how to find him.