Stay down!
Don't move!
Yeah!
Mayday! Mayday!
This is the Sawyer-Two.
We're under attack by pirates.
Requesting immediate aid.
They say everybody's
good at something.
Me? I talk to fish.
That's how I met my friend, Storm.
He's always there when I need a lift.
- Hey.
Some people think
that makes me a joke
but I don't care. You know why?
'Cause I'm also good
at something else.
And that's breaking heads.
Pow! Papa took on all the pirates.
I was like,
"Well, the pirates think that..."
Hi-ya...
Papa kicked their butts.
Those chumlickers
didn't stand a chance.
Papa kicked their asses
and took their names.
Yeah! Come on!
Watch out!
Sorry, Pops. My bad.
Oh, yeah, this is my son, Arthur Jr.
See, four years ago,
everything changed.
I met a woman, fell in love,
and the next thing I know
we're getting married
and having a kid.
This little guy's the best thing
that ever happened to me.
But this kid, he doesn't sleep.
Okay...
And he never misses.
What the...
And then, I'm up at the crack of dawn
because on top of getting married
and having a kid...
I finally got a job.
That's right.
I'm the king of fricking Atlantis.
How did I score that, you asked?
Well, I stopped my brother, Orm,
from attacking the surface world.
And in doing so,
I claimed the throne from him.
At first, I was like...
Yeah!
The territorial waters
are long-held...
But then, as it turned out
being king wasn't all
it was cracked up to be.
I would kindly remind King Nereus...
It's just meetings all day,
and politics.
I'm so bored, I don't even know
which end of the Brine King
I'm supposed to be looking at
half the time.
Yeah! That was awesome!
And as if that's not bad enough
turns out there's this whole
Council of Houses thing
that nobody told me about
which basically gets to shoot down
everything I want to do.
The only thing
that makes all the hard work
and sleepless nights worthwhile
is hanging with my little man.
Hey! You missed me!
But of course,
there are fun parts of the job.
I get to keep the sea safe
the best way I know how.
Especially when I get to take down
an illegal cage fight or two.
But for everything I get right,
something else gets screwed up.
Ah, fu...
(Daddy... Daddy)
- Oh, yeah.
- Here you go.
(Gaelic)
Sláinte.
So...
he's gonna need a little brother
or sister to play with.
He's got a dog.
Hey, I'm serious.
I saw how lonely it was for you
growing up.
An only child.
I always regretted
I couldn't give you that.
Yeah, well, don't be
too hard on yourself.
Turns out I have a brother
and he's a total dickbag.
Come on.
Your relationship with Orm
isn't how it usually is.
Sure, siblings bicker and fight
but at the end of the day,
they're family.
You should be able
to count on them for help.
Yeah, well, I'll still take the dog
over him any day.
Hey, look at that.
Holy crap.
Hi, baby boy.
Are you talking to the fishies?
Oh, man. Pops,
this is blowing my mind.
My whole life I've wanted
to share this gift with someone.
Yeah, but you and me, son,
we're different. We're special.
We're connected
to the land and the sea.
I can't wait to introduce you to all
the majestic creatures on our planet.
And show you how awesome
this world can be.
Yeah, you and me.
I cross-referenced the coordinates
from Dr. Shin. Nothing.
Still no sign of Atlantean remnants
under the ice.
Looks like he's led us
on another wild goose chase.
Every day I don't fix my power suit
is another day Aquaman gets to live.
Check again.
We're close this time. I can feel it.
Expedition log, day 463,
Dr. Stephen Shin recording.
My quest for Atlantis has brought me
to the ends of the earth.
David Kane is losing his patience.
If I don't turn up the Atlantean
technology he's looking for soon
they're probably going to...
You know what?
Let's not even go there.
I'm sure everything will be fine.
Dr. Shin, take a look at this!
Please tell me you found something.
Seismic array is going crazy.
Where's the epicenter?
We're standing on it.
Run!
What just happened? An earthquake?
No. I think it was a piece
of ice sheet breaking off.
Come on, get up!
- I think I broke my ankle!
- Come on, let's go!
Come on, get up!
Go, we gotta go! We gotta go!
Come on, we gotta move!
Come on, let's move!
Help, please!
Help... Please! Don't let go!
What the hell happened to you?
There's something back there.
Astounding.
My readings show something's
down here.
And it's definitely big enough
to be an Atlantean ship.
If it is, we might be able
to scavenge
the tech you need to fix your suit.
How is this place even possible?
This was all probably solid ice
until we started heating the planet.
Well, thank God
for global warming, am I right?
Yeah, that's not exactly
a good thing.
The tracks lead down there.
Suit up.
Wait. The tracks lead down there,
which means...
the monster's down there.
Okay. I guess we're going down there.
I don't believe this.
It's a structure of some kind.
And there's more buried in the ice.
Here I thought we were just going
to find a ship.
- Everyone, fan out and search.
- Yes, sir.
We've stumbled upon
something big here, Doc.
This has to be
a few thousand years old.
Astounding.
What is this place?
At last, you are here.
Free me from my prison
and I will grant you the strength
to kill the man
who murdered your father.
You can't leave him like this!
You ask the sea for mercy.
Get out of here! You need to live
so you can kill that son of a bitch.
You will take from him
what he stole from you.
His home will burn
and his kingdom will fall
before my legions.
David. No, David.
David!
David. David, it's okay.
You're all right.
What the hell is that thing?
Just unbelievable footage
coming in from all around the world.
Good evening, folks.
In the past five months, we've seen
an extraordinary rise in temperatures
reported around the world.
And that has resulted in some of
the wildest weather we've ever seen.
Yes, this is thundersnow
in Dallas, Texas.
Visibility is near zero, and there's
more snow expected tonight
than Dallas usually sees
in an entire year.
It's only one part
of a worldwide weather phenomenon
unlike anything
we've ever seen before...
Arthur.
The Council's called
for an emergency gathering.
There's been another plague outbreak.
in which scientists
are at a loss to explain.
But the real question is
how long will it continue?
And how much hotter
is it going to get?
Where did it hit this time?
The Ninth Tride of Atlantis
and there are now reports
of outbreaks
in the Fishermen Kingdom as well.
There haven't been outbreaks
like this in centuries.
Why now?
Increased ocean acidity, decreased
oxygen levels, toxic algal blooms.
Take your pick.
The surface has been poisoning
our atmosphere for over a century.
You can't expect them to care
about what happens to us
if they don't even know we exist.
If you want to be a part
of the conversation
we have to take our seat
at the table.
It's time for Atlantis
to reveal itself to the surface.
Your Majesty is well aware
of the Council's position on this.
Listen, we can talk
to their scientists
and combine our technologies
to reverse the damage
that they've already done.
And I know this is
against our traditions
but the world is shrinking
and the old ways aren't gonna
protect us anymore.
Times have changed.
Atlantis wants this.
There's a whole generation out there
that don't want to hide anymore.
Have you already forgotten
that this plague
killed your own beloved mentor
and you want to negotiate with them?
We gave your brother war powers
and made him
Ocean Master for a reason.
If we ever decide to make ourselves
known to the surface dwellers
it will be to eradicate them,
not to co-exist.
Hey, not bad.
Used to take me twice as long
to get you to go to sleep.
I don't know how you did it, Pops.
Mera and I have
the whole kingdom helping us
but that little baby boy is still
kicking our asses.
And you...
taking care of me,
raising me on your own...
You're the real superhero.
To single parents.
Well, my job was a little less
stressful than yours.
Yeah, well,
I just plain suck at my job.
Vulko told me to bring
the land and the sea together.
The problem is, half of Atlantis
still wants to destroy the surface.
They won't listen.
I can't bring shit together.
Vulko believed in you. Aye.
I know.
I miss him.
Hey.
You can't save them all, son.
You really want to know
how I raised you here? By myself?
I just keep going.
You celebrate the wins,
you mourn the losses.
And you wake up the next day
and you do it again.
Sometimes not giving up
is the most heroic thing you can do.
(Māori) Kia kaua e tuohu.
(Bow to no one.)
Koira te tikanga o te toa.
(That's the way of a warrior.)
Humans were not made
to live at these depths.
Yeah, don't worry about that.
You just remember
who built this ship.
I'm more worried about
how long ago they built it.
We're coming up on it.
Engage stealth mode.
Hey, Doc.
You stand ready
with that big gun of yours.
Expedition log, day 613.
Kane is off on
our most dangerous mission yet.
A three-man octobot
infiltration team.
It's incredible that these
ancient machines we found
still function after all these years.
All I did was retrofit them
to our needs.
But they require
a very specialized fuel
to keep them running.
Kane calls it orichalcum.
I don't know how he knows about this
but it all started the day
he found that trident.
Suddenly, he knows secrets
that he couldn't possibly know
including the only way
to obtain this orichalcum
is to steal it
from highly protected storage vaults.
And we're about the hit
the most dangerous one of them all.
Okay, you have 15 minutes
to get in and out.
No margin for error.
Okay, this should take you through.
We don't want any confrontation.
David, we can't fight
their entire army.
Stay vigilant.
We have no idea
what kind of security measures
they have down there.
Commencing extraction.
Be careful. It's highly volatile.
Loading barge now.
Stingray. Change of plans.
I need an extraction now!
All hands to battle stations!
(Portuguese)
Postos de combate!
Tudo a seus postos de combate!
Astounding.
Attention, unidentified vessel.
- You are out of the transit zone.
- Doctor.
Power up the sonic battery.
Illegal border crossing will be met
- with deadly force.
- Now!
Commencing charge.
Border Control, intruder approaching.
Arm hydrocannon and lock target.
Hydrocannon at front border gate
locking in on target.
Chargers set to maximum power.
Intruder in sight.
Take them out!
What are you waiting for? Fire!
Sir, Atlantean hostiles
are approaching.
Split up. Make your way
to the extraction point.
Roger.
They've raided the storage vault.
We can't let them get away.
Don't worry, they won't.
I'm on this one.
Hold your fire! They're cutting
through the Night Market.
Watch out for the civilians!
Warning. Warning.
Illegal entrance into hypertube.
Exceeding maximum speed of 600kts.
Reduce speed immediately.
Oh, shit.
David, we're here
at the extraction point.
The orichalcum
is on board and secure.
Come on, let's go!
Not yet!
I'm gonna kill me a dead mermaid.
Get away from my wife!
Your wife?
First, you steal
your brother's throne
then you steal his woman?
Aquaman, shame on you.
David, we gotta go.
The entire Atlantean army
is headed this way.
If we don't leave now, we're dead.
Twenty degrees port!
Fire the sonic cannon!
Come on, Shin!
Lady Karshon has called
an emergency session
of the High Council
to discuss a motion that would strip
the throne of its executive power.
The throne is the heart of Atlantis.
Too often now it stands empty
while our king
spends half his time on land.
And now his surface-world enemies
have followed him home.
This tragedy is merely a taste
of the havoc that will be brought
if Atlantis ever becomes known
to the surface.
Because if he cannot protect
his own family
how is he supposed to protect us?
He's different now.
He's stronger than before.
And he can fight me
without the power suit.
And where the hell did he get
all the new toys from?
The technology seems ancient
but we've never seen
anything like it.
That weapon he used fires
some kind of ultrasonic energy
that disrupts the nervous system.
Do we know what was stolen?
He escaped with a large stockpile
of orichalcum.
Am I supposed to know what that is?
Orichalcum is a power source
that was used in ancient times.
It emits tremendous amounts
of greenhouse gases
that are highly destructive
to our planet.
In fact, we almost destroyed
the oceans ourselves
before we realized
what we were doing.
It can't be disposed of safely,
so the remaining stockpile
has been buried in 12 storage vaults
deep underground.
Well, we should warn the other places
that are storing the stuff.
He's already been there.
It's all gone.
We think he's been
launching secret raids
for at least five months.
This is just the time he got caught.
Well, this spike
in global temperatures
that's causing disasters
on the surface
and making the sea dwellers sick
happened five months ago.
He's using the stolen orichalcum
to heat the planet.
Why would he do that?
I don't know, but I'm gonna find out.
If he is using the orichalcum
to heat the planet
we don't have much time.
He is pushing this past
the tipping point.
He must be stopped or a global
climate meltdown is imminent.
We need to find him, but he has
completely vanished off the radar.
I think I know someone
who might be able to help us.
But you're not gonna like it.
Your brother?
Believe me, he's the last person
I wanna go begging for help
but he's dealt with Manta in the past
and he's the only one who might know
how to find him in time.
The Fishermen will never allow you
to speak to Orm.
He killed their king.
I wasn't exactly
gonna ask for permission.
Arthur, Atlantis cannot extract Orm
from an allied nation.
It would be an act of war.
Atlantis isn't gonna do it.
I'm gonna break him out myself.
Arthur, Karshon is looking
for a reason to seize war powers.
You will be nothing more
than a figurehead if she does that.
My place is out there where I belong,
where I'm actually good at what I do.
I'm tired of nothing
ever getting done.
I've got to do this.
If anyone finds out,
if you're caught...
it will tear the kingdoms apart.
Then help me not get caught.
Xebelian intelligence
has recently learned
that your brother is being held
on the surface in a secret
one-of-a-kind underground facility.
They're assuming no sea dweller
would ever dare cross the desert.
And here's a special outfit for you.
What is that? A boy's extra medium?
It's supposed to be tight.
The chromatophores change color
and camouflage you for up to a minute
making you undetectable
to most sensors.
They'll never see you coming.
What are we doing for comms?
Open comms are too risky.
I'll be sending a cephalopod
with you to act as a messenger.
That's an octopus.
Tactical Operations
and Pursuit Operative.
Topo, for short.
Genetically-engineered intelligence
for infiltration and espionage.
He also plays a variety
of musical instruments.
Just try and lay low
when we get in there, okay?
You might be invisible,
but your hectocotylus
is starting to smell like
warm chum butter.
Topo, you dumb squid!
God, come on!
Is ink piss?
The prison is guarded
by fearsome Deserter remnants.
Death-worshipping ascetics who
survived when the Sahara went dry
by turning to blood for sustenance.
If they catch you,
they'll bleed you dry.
When you find Orm, he'll be weak.
They're limiting his water supply
just enough to keep him alive.
And if you do see Orm,
you tell him that I love him.
You tell him
that I think of him every day.
I will.
Look, I know he's family
but you can't forget
who you're dealing with here.
Once you've broken Orm out
you're not gonna be able
to turn your back on him.
You need him,
but you can never trust him.
You look rough.
What the hell are you doing here?
I'm here to break you out.
Have you lost your mind?
You're the one who put me here.
Why you bringing up old shit?
Come on, we'll talk about it later.
You cannot break me out.
There's a treaty
with the Fishermen Kingdom.
Look, I gotta stop David Kane
from destroying the world.
And you're the only one that
can help me. So you do the math.
Oh, shit.
Come on, Cast Away.
Grab Wilson, let's roll.
Come on. Let's go.
This changes nothing.
Wouldn't have it any other way,
little brother.
Do not call me brother.
(Spanish) ¿Hermanito?
(Little brother?)
Come on.
Come on, Topo, you stupid squid!
Wake up and open the door.
Topo?
The cephalopod?
Trust me, it wasn't my idea.
Topo!
All right, come on.
Wait.
Did you... bring water?
Yeah.
No, sorry.
I drank it all on the way here.
- What?
- Bro, it's hot up there.
Easy.
- You know how to ride one of these?
- Are you kidding?
I don't even know
what the hell it is!
What?
Yeah!
No!
All right, the water's right there.
Let's go, skinny jeans.
Yeah. All right.
Good job, little brother. High-five.
No.
All right. Good job.
You know, I got a bunch
of king shit to do
back in Atlantis, so we should go.
Come on, Topo!
This is worse
than I could have possibly imagined.
The safety and security
of Atlantis is a sacred trust.
No king has allowed
the Great City Wall to be breached
in a hundred generations.
A hundred generations? Really?
How many years is that?
I'm bad with geology.
What is that, like, a million years?
You're calling me one in a million?
How can you make jokes
at a time like this?
It's undignified for a king to jest.
Oh, excuse me, Your Highness,
if I use comedy
to mask my feelings
and deal with stress.
Otherwise,
I'd end up looking like you.
A very tight butthole.
Super tight.
You know, if the pressures
of leadership are too stressful
perhaps you should leave
and let someone
who knows what they're doing be king.
You know what?
I cannot wait to throw your ass
back in prison when this is all over.
You won't have to.
Once I stop David Kane
I'll surrender myself
to the Fishermen.
That is my honor to Atlantis.
You're so dramatic.
Whatever.
Just help me find this asshole.
Well, my contact
will at least know where to look.
What happened to him?
David Kane that I knew was ruthless,
but he wasn't insane.
This guy just put a gun to the
world's head and pulled the trigger.
Without even making any demands.
Congratulations, Dr. Shin.
That cannon of yours worked
exactly how you said it would.
Well, you found it. All I did
was figure out how it worked.
I didn't think we'd ever actually
have to use it on anyone.
Yeah, well, what can I say?
Things don't always go as planned.
But that's what I'm afraid of.
David, this stuff could reshape
the entire planet.
Hey, Doc.
We are this close to unlocking
the greatest power in human history.
Are you really telling me
you want to walk away now?
If I said yes, would you let me?
Sure.
You want to see
how long you last in that jungle?
Be my guest.
Yeah, I'll stick around.
Yeah.
Welcome to the last frontier.
They scavenged ships from around
the world to build this place.
The Sunken Citadel.
It is the one place in the world
where the scum
of the land and sea mingle.
It is where people come to disappear.
It's an impressive shithole.
How have I never
heard of this place before?
It is not meant to be
common knowledge.
It's a pirate haven.
Pirates?
Listen, I don't know
if you know this about me
but I'm not too popular with pirates.
Oh, I'm well aware.
Relax. It was the only way
to get us both in.
You could've at least
given me a heads-up.
Would you have gone along with it?
- Hell, no.
- Then put a hook in it.
There. That's Kingfish.
He is the one who put me
in contact with David Kane.
He brokers deals with pirates,
mercenaries, slavers, you name it.
Cool.
I'm gonna go pick a fight.
Just let me handle this.
He's our best shot at finding Manta
and he's not going to
tell us anything if you go in there
flexing your muscles at him.
You're so lucky we didn't
grow up together, little brother.
Do not call me "brother."
Well...
this is a bit of a surprise,
isn't it?
I didn't realize
you'd been released from prison.
It is a recent development.
Outlaws, aren't we all?
We need to find David Kane.
Bad news, I'm afraid.
David Kane is no longer
on the market.
Not for sale at any price.
He's solely running
as an independent operator.
Where is he holed up now?
In exchange, I offer a favor...
from the King of Atlantis.
You seriously expect me
to play footsie with someone
with that kind of blood
on their hands?
I don't have hands!
Or feet!
Listen, if the information
checks out good
I promise you that
I won't immediately come back here
and tear this place apart.
That's too bad.
Traditionally, the kings of Atlantis
have turned a blind eye
to the Sunken Citadel.
Now, we have to blind it for you.
Fine. Flex your muscles.
Smash his stupid head in!
Boom!
Gotcha, fatback!
Okay! Okay!
We can work this out. We can.
Talk.
I don't know where he is,
but there have been rumors.
A dormant volcano
in the South Pacific
called Devil's Deep.
Talk faster.
It's been barren for years.
But travelers say
there's a jungle there now.
Navigation gets scrambled
as soon as you start to get close.
And if you get too close,
you don't come back!
If I was a betting man,
and believe me, I am
I'd say that's
where Kane is hiding out.
We got all we needed. Let's go!
Rise up, come
Rise up through the fire
Soon you'll be
more powerful than he is.
But you're not ready yet,
and you involved him far too soon.
I sense them closing in on us.
Do I seem concerned?
If anything, it's even easier now.
We couldn't have planned it
any better than...
Hey.
I just wanted to tell you
that the orichalcum furnace
is now running at peak output.
I win.
Topo, go back to Atlantis
and give them our coordinates.
(Japanese) Hayaku shite kudasai.
(Hurry up, make it quick.)
You know
what'd be amazing right now?
Reinforcements?
Great, big, greasy cheeseburger
and a pint of Guinness.
You gotta admit,
the food is so much better up here.
I find that hard to believe.
Hold up.
Are you telling me you never went
topside to have a cheeseburger?
- What?
- Or a slice of 'za? Pepperoni?
Or a thick, juicy, medium-raw steak
with fries and a shake
and you dip it...
Even the words that surface dwellers
give their food sound disgusting.
You've let your prejudices stop you
from enjoying half the world.
You should think about that.
It's your loss, dude.
Oh, yeah.
Bet you never had one of these.
- What is it?
- It's a cockroach.
You eat it?
Oh, yeah. Shrimp of the land.
That's good. Here, drink this.
Okay, you first.
Are you seeing this?
That's not normal?
Definitely not normal.
Let's get out of here.
You see how dangerous
the orichalcum can be?
I bet it mutated the flora and fauna
in a short amount of time
turning them mons... trous.
Oh, shi...
Run!
Come on!
Faster!
What the hell are you doing?
I don't know.
I'm not used to running!
Just do what I do.
Use your arms,
use your legs. Come on!
Like this?
- Holy shit.
- Yeah!
- Wait up!
We have to jump.
We'll survive the fall.
Are you crazy? It's gonna hurt.
So, what do you wanna do? Stay here
and fight the hopping demons?
What is that? What does that say?
The writing is ancient Atlantean.
"A true king builds bridges."
What are you doing?
Got any more krill-brained ideas?
See? A true king builds bridges.
That's a metaphor!
Hey! I forgot to tell you!
Mom says she loves you!
She thinks about you all the time!
Why the hell are you
telling me this now?
I don't know. I'm just tired
of waiting for the right moment.
Come on!
Looks like my metaphor
just saved your ass.
David? I just ran more tests,
and this data is really disturbing.
We have to stop
burning the orichal... cum.
David?
Okay, Doc, you want to know
my plan so bad.
Here it is.
I'm gonna kill Aquaman
and destroy everything he holds dear.
I'm gonna murder his family
and burn his kingdom to ash.
I will avenge my father.
Even if I have to make a deal
with the devil to do it.
David, you can't trust the trident.
I never draw this blade
unless it's gonna taste blood.
Pray I never show it to you again.
We must be getting close
to the radiation source.
We should wait for Atlantis
to receive your message.
We can conduct reconnaissance
in the meantime.
Yeah. Look, Loki, I'm not asking
for your advice on this.
You've already lived up
to your end of the deal.
So you can go on back
to Azkaban for all I care.
So, what's your plan?
I don't have one yet.
But he came after my wife,
which means
I'm gonna pull his tongue
out of his butt.
Arthur, you are the king.
You cannot let this get personal.
This coming from the guy who turned
the entire nation of Atlantis
into his own private ego trip?
My ego?
You're the one
who swam to the front gate
and challenged my claim
for the throne.
Only because you're trying
to destroy the surface world.
If you weren't such an asshole,
you'd still be king.
Unbelievable.
Wait... wait.
You took my throne
and you don't even want it?
Are you kidding me? I hate this job.
Only reason I'm doing it is to keep
Atlantis from destroying the surface.
And I might even be screwing that up.
You really had no ambition for it?
Absolutely not.
From the day
my father found out you existed
he prepared me for the moment
that you would come
and challenge me for the throne.
Wow, that's really sad.
Especially when you think
how easily I kicked your ass
with basically no prep time
whatsoever.
Roasted.
That is not how it happened.
- That's exactly how it happened.
- Mera saved you.
No, she didn't. I kicked your ass.
Nope. She made the little
water tornado, I fell in it.
Okay, shut up. I think we're here.
Sleep, aloha.
Come on, let's do this.
Once this is over with, we should
go get some burgers and beers.
- Don't push it.
- Tacos and tequila.
I don't even know those words.
Hey.
Brother.
(Māori)
Sassa!
It's an orichalcum furnace.
All that stolen orichalcum.
They're just burning it up.
He's heating the atmosphere
on purpose.
This is catastrophic.
This whole place
must be heat-shielded
to protect it from the surface's
thermal satellites.
Question is, how do we stop 'em?
To take out this reactor, we would
have to crater the entire island.
Get away from there! Now!
This blaster may be ancient, but it
was built for killing Atlanteans.
Okay, I am so sorry.
I did not mean that.
I just didn't want you to break me
in half before I could surrender.
Please take me with you.
Knock him out and then
help me hide these bodies.
No, no. Wait, please.
I didn't want any of this.
All I wanted was to see Atlantis
with my own eyes.
I thought I could share
its wonders with the world.
I'm a scientist and I just wanted
to be taken seriously.
David Kane said he could help me,
but now he won't let me leave.
You expect us to believe
you have nothing to do with this?
I know.
I've done things I'm not proud of.
But he would've killed me
if I hadn't.
Knock him out.
No.
- Then I'll knock him out.
- No!
- What?
- No.
Fine.
You can come with us.
Thank you.
But you better start talking,
or I'm gonna give you one sassa.
Okay, okay.
It's the Black Trident.
It's a direct link
to some ancient evil.
It gives Kane great powers
and in return...
I hate when that happens.
Stop them!
(Portuguese) Tu, e tu...
(You, and you...)
levem-no daqui.
(take him away.)
No!
No... no! Not the orichalcum!
You wanna blow us up?
- This stuff blows up?
- Yes!
My bad!
Then stop using it!
Just shut up
and let me save your ass.
Again.
He's going to fight us
without the power suit?
I told you, he's stronger now.
He's still just a surface dweller.
Bro.
I never expected to see you two
fighting side by side.
We're making a special exception
just for you.
No one hits my brother but me.
I was gonna kill you last,
but thanks for dropping by.
You're making this easy.
Yeah!
Come at me.
The killer of kings.
Take that island down!
Fire at will!
We've got to get out of here.
Malfunction. Malfunction.
Warning. Warning.
Shin, let's go!
What are you waiting for?
Fire the goddamn cannon!
I'm sorry to drag you all into this.
But the Fishermen can't think
that Atlantis was involved.
Atlantis does not command
the armies of Xebel. I do.
And the Brine Kingdom
has not forgotten its debt to you.
You may count on us always.
Something happened to me
when I touched that Black Trident.
Why is he even here?
He should be
on his way back to prison.
We should hear what he has to say.
I made that mistake once.
That's why I know
he can't be trusted.
And he cut off my claw.
This thing took a whole year
to grow back.
Look, he wants to stop Manta
same as we do.
And just for the record
the only reason we made it this far
is because of him.
I saw the Lost Kingdom.
Mom, I don't know enough about this.
Is that even possible?
All anyone knows for sure
is there once was a seventh kingdom
and then one day,
just before the fall
every record of it was stricken
from the chronicles.
How do you know what you saw
was the Lost Kingdom?
No one even knows
what it was called anymore.
It's called Necrus.
And I didn't just see it.
I knew it.
It's almost like I was...
remembering it.
Flashes of someone else's memories.
During King Atlan's time, there were
seven united kingdoms of Atlantis.
And the Black City
was a curse upon them all.
By exploiting orichalcum
Necrus rapidly became
a superpower unlike any other.
But it came at a terrible price.
Poisoning the land, the sea.
Even the mind of the tyrant
who ruled Necrus.
Atlan's own brother, Kordax.
Atlan pleaded with him
to stop using it
before the world
was irrevocably damaged.
However, Kordax resented Atlan
thinking his own brother
was trying to steal his power.
So he resorted to dark magic
and crafted an instrument of evil.
That Black Trident.
He transformed his people
and himself into monsters...
to fight Atlantis.
So the two brothers went to war.
But Atlan defeated Kordax
and imprisoned him and all of Necrus
with a spell cast
with his own blood...
to ensure that Kordax's dark power
would never be found.
And that is why Necrus
is stricken from the chronicles.
This evil was supposed
to remain frozen for eternity.
But David Kane has found it.
And it's slowly possessing him.
But even with the ice cap melting,
Kordax still can't be freed.
Atlan used blood magic
to seal Kordax in his prison.
Only Atlan himself could release him.
Manta doesn't need Atlan himself.
Manta needs Atlan's blood.
Blood magic isn't really magic,
it's DNA.
The key to Kordax's prison
is the royal bloodline itself.
That means he needs blood
from either you, me, or Arthur.
We're the end of the bloodline.
No, we're not.
Wildfires would have
made headlines across the world.
But now, they're almost
a weekly occurrence.
We're witnessing unprecedented
weather events across the globe
and meteorologists are at a loss
to explain this rapid change
in climate.
From sweltering heat waves
and droughts
which are shattering
temperature records
to torrential rains and flooding.
- What is going on?
- Hurricanes have been bearing down
on the East Coast, leaving
one million homes without power...
Make that a million and one.
I gotta get the flashlight, bubba.
I'm gonna leave you alive,
so he can watch you die.
Dad!
- Tom!
- Dad!
Tom!
No! Dad!
Where's Junior?
No!
I'm sorry, son.
Where's Junior?
Manta... took Junior.
- No!
No!
The medics have
stabilized his condition.
He will be okay.
We just picked up a signal.
It's faint, but it's broadcasting
on an old Atlantean sonar frequency.
Headed to Antarctica.
- Bring our little one back.
- I will.
I've dreamed of this.
The two of you standing together
as brothers.
Promise me
you will protect each other.
Promise me, Orm.
Go.
Great waves, Nereus.
Your warship is powerful,
but it's slower than a sea cow.
I say we ditch all this dead weight
and travel light. Hmm?
And what are you gonna do
when he turns on that sonic cannon?
Our only chance is to hit him
with total overwhelming force
from every direction.
- Not with Junior in the crossfire.
- What choice do we have?
We have no defense
against that cannon.
Well, wait a minute.
So this cannon
sends out soundwaves
that messes
with our nervous system, right?
That's right. Ultrasonic echoes.
Well, what if we disrupt those echoes
with another soundwave
on the same frequency
but just much, much louder?
You wanna disrupt their disruption?
Well, that's gonna be the easy part.
Take your weapons.
And ready your steeds.
Really doesn't like you, does he?
Made a lot of progress, Doc.
They destroyed the furnace
before we could finish the job
but we were damn close.
One well-placed missile
should do the trick.
My God, what did we do?
Nothing the world
wasn't already doing.
All we did was fast-forward things
a few years.
The ice hasn't fully melted yet,
but our scanning reveals a weak spot.
Here.
This will lead you
straight to Kordax.
Power up the sonic cannon.
Bag the child and suit up.
Captain, we have multiple
incoming hostiles.
You're too late.
No.
Commence charge.
You've gotta be kidding me.
Astounding.
This place is immense.
It could be anywhere.
The throne of Necrus
is in the heart of the city.
- I sense something in the water.
- Everyone, light it up.
Didn't you say that Kordax turned
his people into an army of monsters?
Yes. I did.
Just keep your eyes open.
Well, that'll be easy.
Mine don't close.
Everyone, stand ready.
Something's coming.
Fire at will!
We need to find a way out of here!
I think this goes
all the way through.
My men and I can deal
with these worms.
Go now and save the prince.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Come on, you spineless worms!
Bring it on!
Help me!
Give me the child.
You picked the wrong day
to grow a spine, Doc.
Get behind the portcullis!
We need to close the gate!
Get away from my son!
Your blood will do just fine.
You want blood? Come get it!
Aquaman!
You wear my brother's armor,
and wield his trident
but you're only half the man he was.
How pathetic.
Mera!
Go!
Mera...
Run!
Free me from my prison
and all my power will be yours
to wield as you desire.
Kill him, and you will be
Ocean Master again!
Well, now this is certainly
an improvement.
Powerful, Atlantean body.
And this one hates you more
than the other one did.
It's not true.
Come on, little brother.
I know you're in there.
Don't you see? You can't win.
Either you kill your brother,
or you die.
By Atlan's blood,
this magic is broken.
My eternal night is ended.
I'm done fighting
your puppets, Kordax.
I'm coming for you.
- Give it to me!
- No!
- I can end this.
- Don't let him take it!
Hasn't he taken enough already?
Yield the throne.
It's time for me
to reclaim my destiny.
It would be foolish
to think he could ever change.
I knew you would do this.
You are the one true king.
Atlantis deserves its one true king.
I am the one true king!
You know, there was a time
when I wanted
to meet you more than anything.
Let you know that you weren't alone,
that we were in it together.
Promise me you'll protect each other.
Come on, little brother,
let's end this bastard.
I meant what I said
when I first met you.
No matter what, you are not alone.
We're in this together.
You are my brother...
Orm.
Let go.
Orm, let it go.
I live again!
I have waited countless centuries
in the dark for this moment.
Shit.
Arthur!
(Māori) O Kou hopena kēia.
(You did this.)
Never.
Arthur, we've gotta go.
The magic is broken.
Let's get outta here!
Hurry!
That's right!
Come on, baby! Yeah!
Yeah!
My love.
Hi, baby boy.
Shin.
Thank you.
Astounding.
All here looking intact.
That's good. That's good.
Well, I'm not.
My claw got cut off.
Again!
You're one tough crustacean,
Your Highness.
As far as I'm concerned,
your debt is paid.
Not everybody's gonna see it
that way, though.
It's too bad you went
and had yourself killed back there.
Yes.
All this ice.
It'd be impossible to find the body.
Just lay low for a while.
But don't go too far.
I may need to call you up
for some advice.
You know, with the whole
running the kingdom thing.
Thank you...
brother.
You're not as bad at this
as you think.
The people of Atlantis
are lucky to have you.
You were everything I was not.
You do the right thing when doing
the wrong thing is much easier.
And you're willing to ask for help,
even from your worst enemy.
I know it may not feel like you know
what you're doing sometimes, but
keep trusting your instincts.
If you lead, Atlantis will follow.
After all, a true king
builds bridges, right?
I thought that was just a metaphor.
Well, your metaphor might have
just saved the world's ass.
We've got breaking news.
We are witnessing history.
A moment
the ramifications of which...
...simply cannot be overstated.
(Spanish) Un primer contacto con...
(Korean)
A first contact...
...with the undersea nation
of Atlantis.
An entire civilization
hidden for thousands of years
about to be revealed.
I think it's safe to say
the world will never be the same.
The King of Atlantis has reached
out to the United Nations
and will be officially
seeking membership.
And is expected
to propose a joint effort
to reverse the climate issues...
We are told that this was the result
of weeks of secret negotiations
with the United Nations.
We now go live to Ellis Island
where the first official ambassador
from Atlantis
is about to address
the United Nations.
I come here today
as the representative of two worlds.
The land and the sea.
And I stand here as proof...
change is coming to both.
And I'm calling for global unity
for a global crisis.
To finally bring harmony between us
and the natural balance of our world.
Atlantis stands ready
to help contribute
its science and technology.
And with your knowledge of the air,
and our knowledge of the seas
together we can write
the next chapter in our story
rather than its ending.
Sometimes it's gonna seem like
our differences are too extreme
but all we have to do
is look beneath the surface
to see that we're all here
on this planet
with the same goals and aspirations.
- Even when our customs might...
- Here you go.
- seem strange and unfamiliar.
- Beer and a cheeseburger.
Extra greasy, like you asked for.
And by overcoming our prejudices
we'll become stronger
and learn more about ourselves.
We can seize this moment to create
a better more hopeful future
for our children, and our families.
My name is Arthur Curry.
I'm the rightful sovereign
of the undersea nation of Atlantis.
I'm a father, a brother...
a warrior and a friend.
I'm the King of Atlantis.
I am Aquaman.