[thunder crashing]
- [grunts]
- [man] Stay down!
[woman shrieking]
[man grunts]
Don't move!
[people yelling]
Yeah!
[triumphant yelling]
Mayday! Mayday!
This is the Sawyer-Two.
We're under attack by pirates.
Requesting an immediate aid.
[Aquaman] They say everybody's
good at something.
Me? I talk to fish.
- That's how I met my friend, Storm.
- [whinnying]
He's always there when I need a lift.
[echoing thud]
[all muttering]
[Aquaman] Some people think
that makes me a joke, but I don't care.
You know why?
'Cause I'm also good at something else.
[resounding clang]
And that's breaking heads.
- [aggressive yell]
- [all yelling]
["Born To Be Wild"
by Steppenwolf playing]
- Pow! Papa took on all the pirates.
- [mimicking blows]
I was like,
"Well, the pirates think that..."
- Hi-ya!
- [baby giggling]
Papa kicked their butts.
[makes fighting sounds]
[all grunting]
[Aquaman] Those chumlickers
didn't stand a chance.
Ooh! [grunts]
Papa kicked their asses
and took their names.
[all cheering] Yeah! Come on!
- [baby giggling]
- Watch out.
[grunts]
Sorry, Pops. My bad.
[Aquaman] Oh, yeah,
this is my son, Arthur Jr.
See, four years ago, everything changed.
I met a woman, fell in love,
and the next thing I know,
- we're getting married and having a kid.
- [baby crying]
This little guy's the best thing
that ever happened to me.
- [camera clicks]
- [baby crying]
- But this kid, he doesn't sleep.
- [crying continues]
[murmuring to baby]
[yawning] Okay...
[spluttering]
And he never misses.
- [giggling]
- What the...?
And then, I'm up at the crack of dawn
because on top of getting married
and having a kid...
- [sniffs]
- ...I finally got a job.
That's right.
I'm the king of freaking Atlantis.
["Born To Be Wild" continues]
How did I score that, you asked?
Well, I stopped my brother, Orm,
from attacking the surface world.
And in doing so,
I claimed the throne from him.
At first I was all like...
- [yelling] Yeah!
- [all roaring]
[Brine King] The territorial waters
are long held...
But then, as it turned out, being king
wasn't all it was cracked up to be.
- I would kindly remind king nereus...
- [Aquaman snoring]
It's just meetings all day and politics.
I'm so bored, I don't even know
which end of the Brine King
I'm supposed to be looking at
half the time.
Whoo!
Yeah! That was awesome!
[Aquaman] And as if that's not bad enough,
turns out there's this whole
Council of Houses thing
that nobody told me about.
Which basically gets to shoot down
everything I want to do.
The only thing
that makes all the hard work
and sleepless nights worthwhile
is hanging with my little man.
Hey! Ha-ha! You missed me!
[laughing]
- [spits]
- [baby squealing]
[laughing]
[Aquaman] But of course,
there are fun parts of the job.
[crowd cheering]
Whoa!
[Aquaman] I get to keep the sea safe
the best way I know how.
- [powerful roar]
- [grunts]
[Aquaman] Especially when I get
to take down an illegal cage fight or two.
[yells]
[cheering, yelling]
[Aquaman] But for everything I get right,
something else gets screwed up.
[toy siren wailing]
- [growls]
- [siren warbles and dies]
[clock ticking]
[baby crying]
Ah, fu...
["Born To Be Wild" continues]
[song ends]
[groaning]
[sighs, groans]
- [Aquaman] Oh, yeah.
- [father] Here you go.
[groans loudly]
Sláinte.
So...
...he's gonna need a little brother
or sister to play with.
[scoffs]
He's got a dog.
Hey, I'm serious.
I saw how lonely it was
for you growing up.
An only child.
I always regretted
I couldn't give you that.
Yeah, well, don't be too hard on yourself.
Turns out I have a brother
and he's a total dickbag.
Come on.
Your relationship with Orm
isn't how it usually is.
Sure, siblings bicker and fight,
but at the end of the day, they're family.
You should be able
to count on them for help.
Yeah, well,
I'll still take the dog over him any day.
[chuckles]
[Arthur Jr. babbling]
Hey, look at that.
Holy crap.
Hi, baby boy.
Are you talking to the fishies?
Oh, man. Pops, this is blowing my mind.
My whole life I've wanted
to share this gift with someone.
Yeah, but you and me, son, we're different.
We're special.
We're connected to the land and the sea.
I can't wait to introduce you to all
the majestic creatures on our planet.
And show you how awesome
this world can be.
Yeah, you and me.
[deep rumbling]
[woman] I cross-referenced the coordinates
from Dr. Shin. Nothing.
Still no sign of Atlantean remnants
under the ice.
Looks like he's led us
on another wild goose chase.
Every day I don't fix my power suit
is another day Aquaman gets to live.
Check again.
We're close this time. I can feel it.
[man] Expedition log day 463,
Dr. Stephen Shin recording.
My quest for Atlantis
has brought me to the ends of the Earth.
David Kane is losing his patience.
If I don't turn up the Atlantean
technology he's looking for soon,
they're probably going to... um...
You know what, let's not even go there.
I'm sure everything will be fine.
[recorder clicks off]
[sighs]
Dr. Shin, take a look at this.
Please tell me you found something.
Seismic array is going crazy.
Where's the epicenter?
We're standing on it.
[metal clanking]
[resounding thuds]
- [heavy thudding]
- [both gasp]
[rumbling continues]
Run!
[panting heavily]
[both yelling]
[yelling, grunting]
[groaning in pain]
[panting]
[yells in pain]
[man] What just happened?
An earthquake?
No. I think it was a piece
of ice sheet breaking off.
- [loud thud]
- [gasping]
[crying out]
[pounding thud]
Come on. Get up.
[grunts in pain]
- I think I broke my ankle!
- Come on, let's go!
Come on, get up. Go, we gotta go!
We gotta go!
Come on, we gotta move! Come on!
[steady beeping]
[shrieks]
[screaming]
Please, please. No, no!
Help, please! Don't let go!
[yelling]
[scream echoes, fading]
[Dr. Shin panting]
What the hell happened to you?
[whispering] There's something back there.
[Dr. Shin] Astounding.
My readings show something's down here.
And it's definitely big enough
to be an Atlantean ship.
If it is, we might be able to scavenge
the tech you need to fix your suit.
[David] How is this place even possible?
[Dr. Shin] This was all probably solid ice
until we started heating the planet.
[David] Well, thank God for global warming,
am I right?
[Dr. Shin] Uh, yeah,
that's not exactly a good thing.
[David] The tracks lead down there.
Suit up.
Wait. The tracks lead down there,
which means...
...the monster's down there.
[sighs]
Okay. I guess we're going down there.
[heavy splash]
[laughs] I don't believe this.
It's a structure of some kind.
And there's more buried in the ice.
Here I thought we were just going
to find a ship.
- [David] Everyone, fan out and search.
- [man] Yes, sir.
We've stumbled upon
something big here, doc.
This has to be a few thousand years old.
Astounding.
Whoa.
[screaming]
[all yelling]
[grunting]
[panting]
What is this place?
[rasping voice] At last, you are here.
[violent grunting]
[screaming]
Free me from my prison
and I will grant you the strength
to kill the man who murdered your father.
You can't leave him like this!
You ask the sea for mercy.
Get out of here. You need to live
so you can kill that son of a bitch.
[voice] You will take from him
what he stole from you.
[yells]
[voice] His home will burn
and his kingdom will fall
before my legions.
- [yells, groaning]
- Whoa, whoa, whoa!
David. No, David.
David! Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
David. David, it's okay.
You're all right.
What the hell is that thing?
[news anchor] Just unbelievable footage
coming in from all around the world.
Good evening, folks.
In the past five months we've seen
an extraordinary rise
in temperatures
reported around the world.
And that has resulted in some
of the wildest weather we've ever seen.
Yes, this is thundersnow in Dallas, Texas.
Visibility is near zero,
and there's more snow expected tonight
than Dallas usually sees
in an entire year.
It's only one part
of a worldwide weather phenomenon
unlike anything we've ever seen before.
[report continues faintly]
Arthur.
[starts, panting]
The Council's called
for an emergency gathering.
There's been another plague outbreak.
[news anchor] ...in which scientists
are at a loss to explain.
But the real question is,
how long will it continue?
And how much hotter is it going to get?
[Aquaman]
Where did it hit this time?
[councilwoman]
The Ninth Tride of Atlantis,
and there are now reports of outbreaks
in the Fishermen Kingdom as well.
There haven't been outbreaks like this
in centuries.
Why now?
Increased ocean acidity, decreased
oxygen levels, toxic algal blooms.
Take your pick.
The surface has been poisoning
our atmosphere for over a century.
You can't expect them to care
about what happens to us
if they don't even know we exist.
If you want to be a part
of the conversation,
we have to take our seat at the table.
It's time for Atlantis to reveal itself
to the surface.
[council members murmuring]
Your majesty is well aware
of the Council's position on this.
Listen, we can talk to their scientists
and combine our technologies
to reverse the damage
that they've already done.
And I know this is against our traditions,
but the world is shrinking,
and the old ways aren't gonna
protect us anymore.
Times have changed.
Atlantis wants this.
There's a whole generation out there
that don't want to hide anymore.
Have you already forgotten
that this plague
killed your own beloved mentor,
and you want to negotiate with them?
We gave your brother war powers
and made him Ocean Master for a reason.
If we ever decide to make ourselves known
to the surface dwellers,
it will be to eradicate them,
not to co-exist.
[thunder rumbling]
[music box chiming]
[father] Hey, not bad.
Used to take me twice as long
to get you to go to sleep.
[Aquaman] I don't know
how you did it, Pops.
Mera and I have
the whole kingdom helping us,
but that little baby boy is still
kicking our asses.
And you...
taking care of me,
raising me on your own...
[sighs]
You're the real superhero.
- To single parents.
- Mm.
Well, my job was a little less
stressful than yours.
Yeah, well, I just plain suck at my job.
Vulko told me to bring
the land and the sea together.
The problem is half of Atlantis
still wants to destroy the surface.
They won't listen.
I can't bring shit together.
Vulko believed in you. Aye.
I know.
I miss him.
Hey.
You can't save them all, son.
You really want to know how
I raised you here? By myself?
I just keep going.
You celebrate the wins,
you mourn the losses.
And you wake up the next day
and you do it again.
Sometimes not giving up
is the most heroic thing you can do.
[speaking Maori]
[groans]
Humans were not made
to live at these depths.
Yeah, don't worry about that.
You just remember who built this ship.
I'm more worried about how long ago
they built it.
[sniffles]
We're coming up on it.
Engage stealth mode.
[heavy thudding]
[metal clanking, rattling]
[engines humming]
[David] Hey, doc.
You stand ready
with that big gun of yours.
Expedition log, day 613.
Kane is off on our most
dangerous mission yet.
A three man octobot infiltration team.
[trident ringing]
[Dr. Shin] It's incredible that these
ancient machines we found
still function after all these years.
All I did was retrofit them to our needs.
But they require a very specialized fuel
to keep them running.
Kane calls it orichalcum.
I don't know how he knows about this,
but it all started the day
he found that trident.
Suddenly, he knows secrets
that he couldn't possibly know,
including the only way
to obtain this orichalcum
is to steal it from highly-protected
storage vaults.
And we're about the hit
the most dangerous one of them all.
[metal creaking]
[engines whining]
Okay, you have 15 minutes
to get in and out.
No margin for error.
Okay, this should take you through.
We don't want any confrontation.
David, we can't fight their entire army.
[deep rumbling, creaking]
[Dr. Shin] Stay vigilant.
We have no idea what kind
of security measures they have down there.
[chittering]
[man] Commencing extraction.
[Dr. Shin] Be careful. it's highly volatile.
[man] Loading barge now.
[alarm blaring]
[thud echoing]
Stingray. Change of plans.
I need an extraction now!
- [alarm wailing]
- All hands to battle stations.
[yelling in Portuguese]
Astounding.
[male voice]
Attention, unidentified vessel.
- You are out of the transit zone.
- Doctor.
Power up the sonic battery.
[male voice]
illegal border crossing will be met
- with deadly force.
- [Stingray] Now!
[machinery whining]
[Dr. Shin] Commencing charge.
[woman]
Border Control, intruder approaching.
Arm hydro cannon and lock target.
[man] Hydro cannon at front border gate
locking in on target.
[man 2] Chargers set to maximum power.
[man] Intruder in sight.
[woman] Take them out!
What are you waiting for? Fire!
[throbbing sonic hum]
[both screaming]
[man over radio]
Sir, Atlantean hostiles are approaching.
[David] Split up. Make your way
to the extraction point.
[man] Roger.
They've raided the storage vault.
We can't let them get away.
Don't worry, they won't. I'm on this one.
[people screaming]
Hold your fire!
They're cutting through the Night Market.
Watch out for the civilians.
[gentle piano music playing]
[grunts]
[yells]
[powerful grunts]
[grunts]
- [pulsating sonic hum]
- [cries out]
[groans]
[robotic voice] Warning. Warning.
Illegal entrance into hypertube.
Exceeding maximum speed of 600 knots.
Reduce speed immediately.
[engines whining]
[yells]
[loud grunt]
[David] Oh, shit.
[Mera grunts]
[soldiers yelling]
[Dr. Shin] David, we're here
at the extraction point.
The orichalcum on board and secure.
Come on, let's go!
[straining] Not yet!
I'm gonna kill me a dead mermaid.
[heavy grunt]
Get away from my wife!
Your wife?
First you steal your brother's throne,
then you steal his woman?
Aquaman, shame on you.
[growls]
[grunts with impact]
Uh, David, we gotta go.
The entire Atlantean army
is headed this way.
If we don't leave now, we're dead.
[people screaming]
[growls]
[straining]
[grunting]
[people yelling]
[grunting roar]
[men yelling]
[Stingray] Twenty degrees port!
[screaming in agony]
[grunts, groans]
[David] Fire the sonic cannon!
Come on, Shin!
[echoing grunt]
[newscaster] Lady Karshon has called
an emergency session of the High Council
to discuss a motion that would
strip the throne of its executive power.
[Karshon]
The throne is the heart of Atlantis.
Too often now it stands empty,
while our king spends half
his time on land.
And now his surface world enemies
have followed him home.
This tragedy is merely a taste
of the havoc that will be brought,
if Atlantis ever becomes known
to the surface.
Because if he cannot protect
his own family,
how is he supposed to protect us?
He's different now.
He's stronger than before.
And he can fight me
without the power suit.
And where the hell did he get
all the new toys from?
The technology seems ancient,
but we've never seen anything like it.
That weapon he used
fires some kind of ultrasonic energy
that disrupts the nervous system.
Do we know what was stolen?
He escaped with a large stockpile
of orichalcum.
Am I supposed to know what that is?
Orichalcum is a power source
that was used in ancient times.
It emits tremendous amounts
of greenhouse gases
that are highly destructive to our planet.
In fact, we almost destroyed
the oceans ourselves
before we realized what we were doing.
It can't be disposed of safely,
so the remaining stockpile
has been buried in 12 storage vaults
deep underground.
Well, we should warn the other places
that are storing the stuff.
He's already been there.
It's all gone.
We think he's been launching secret raids
for at least five months.
This is just the time he got caught.
Well, this spike in global temperatures
that's causing disasters on the surface
and making the sea dwellers sick
happened five months ago.
He's using the stolen orichalcum
to heat the planet.
Why would he do that?
I don't know, but I'm gonna find out.
If he is using the orichalcum
to heat the planet,
we don't have much time.
He is pushing this past the tipping point.
He must be stopped
or a global climate meltdown is imminent.
[King] We need to find him, but he has
completely vanished off the radar.
I think I know someone
who might be able to help us.
But you're not gonna like it.
Your brother?
Believe me, he's the last person
I wanna go begging for help,
but he's dealt with Manta in the past,
and he's the only one who might know
how to find him in time.
The Fishermen will never allow you
to speak to Orm.
He killed their king.
I wasn't exactly gonna ask for permission.
Arthur, Atlantis cannot extract Orm
from an allied nation.
It would be an act of war.
Atlantis isn't gonna do it.
I'm gonna break him out myself.
Arthur, Karshon is looking for a reason
to seize war powers.
You will be nothing more
than a figurehead if she does that.
My place is out there where I belong,
where I'm actually good at what I do.
I'm tired of nothing ever getting done.
I've got to do this.
[King] If anyone finds out,
if you're caught...
...it will tear the kingdoms apart.
Then help me not get caught.
["Spirit In The Sky"
by Norman Greenbaum playing]
[King] Xebelian intelligence has recently
learned that your brother is being held
on the surface in a secret
one-of-a-kind underground facility.
They're assuming no sea dweller
would ever dare cross the desert.
And here's a special outfit for you.
What is that? A boy's extra medium?
It's supposed to be tight.
The chromatophores change color
and camouflage you for up to a minute,
making you undetectable to most sensors.
They'll never see you coming.
[Aquaman] What are we doing for comms?
Open comms are too risky.
I'll be sending a cephalopod with you
to act as a messenger.
That's an octopus.
Tactical Operations and Pursuit Operative.
Topo, for short.
Genetically engineered intelligence
for infiltration and espionage.
He also plays a variety
of musical instruments.
- [Topo chittering]
- [Aquaman grumbles]
Just try and lay low
when we get in there, okay?
You might be invisible,
but your hectocotylus
is starting to smell like
warm chum butter.
- [Topo chitters grumpily]
- [spluttering]
Aw, Topo, you dumb squid!
God, come on!
Is ink piss?
[King] The prison is guarded
by fearsome Deserter remnants.
Death-worshipping ascetics who survived
when the Sahara went dry
by turning to blood for sustenance.
If they catch you, they'll bleed you dry.
[cackling roar]
[King] When you find Orm, he'll be weak.
They're limiting his water supply...
...just enough to keep him alive.
And if you do see Orm,
you tell him that I love him.
You tell him
that I think of him every day.
I will.
[King] Look, I know he's family,
but you can't forget
who you're dealing with here.
Once you've broken Orm out,
you're not gonna be able
to turn your back on him.
You need him, but you can never trust him.
[deserter croaking]
[grunting]
[deserters growling]
[groans through teeth]
[bellows]
- [Orm grunts]
- [deserter croaks, roars]
[yells]
- [surprised grunt]
- [Aquaman yells]
[yells]
[exhales]
Whoo... You look rough.
What the hell are you doing here?
I'm here to break you out.
Have you lost your mind?
[panting] You're the one who put me here.
Eh, why you bringing up old shit?
- Come on, we'll talk about it later.
- [sharp growl]
You cannot break me out.
There's a treaty
with the Fishermen Kingdom.
Look, I gotta stop David Kane
from destroying the world.
And you're the only one that can help me.
So you do the math.
- [sharp alarm wails]
- [Aquaman] Oh, shit.
Come on, Cast Away.
Grab Wilson, let's roll.
- Come on. Let's go.
- [claps hands impatiently]
[growls]
[rising grunt]
[panting heavily]
This changes nothing.
Wouldn't have it any other way,
little brother.
Do not call me brother.
¿Hermanito?
Come on.
[growls]
Come on, Topo, you stupid squid!
Wake up and open the door.
Topo?
The cephalopod?
Trust me, it wasn't my idea.
Topo!
[chittering urgently]
All right, come on.
[Orm panting] Wait.
[breathless] Did you... bring water?
Yeah.
Uh, no, sorry.
I drank it all on the way here.
- What?
- Bro, it's hot up there.
[deserter grunts]
[Aquaman whoops]
[deserter mount huffing and snorting]
[Aquaman yells]
Whoa! Easy.
- Whoa!
- [mount roaring]
[surprised yell]
- You know how to ride one of these?
- Are you kidding?
I don't even know what the hell it is.
- Hyaah!
- What?
Yeah! [whooping]
[both yelling]
[Aquaman grunts in excitement]
Yeah!
[whooping]
Whoa.
[angry yell]
Whoa, whoa, whoa, no!
[groaning]
[grunts]
[low rumbling]
[both yelling]
[tumbling grunts]
[groaning]
All right, the water's right there.
Let's go, skinny jeans.
[grunts]
[deserters roaring]
[roars]
[all chattering]
[energy booming]
[Orm yelling]
[all grunting]
[panting]
[yells in pain]
[mount shrieks]
[groaning]
[yells]
[Aquaman] Yeah. All right.
Good job, little brother. High-five.
No.
All right. Good job.
[Topo chittering urgently]
["Spirit In The Sky" resumes]
[hooves thundering]
You know, I got a bunch of king shit to do
back in Atlantis so we should go.
Ahh! Come on, Topo!
[song ends]
[Orm] This is worse
than I could have possibly imagined.
The safety and security
of Atlantis is a sacred trust.
No king has allowed
the great city wall to be breached
- in a hundred generations.
- [Aquaman scoffs]
A hundred generations? Really?
How many years is that?
I'm bad with geology.
What is that, like, a million years?
Oh? You're calling me one in a million?
How can you make jokes
at a time like this?
It's undignified for a king to jest.
Oh, excuse me, Your Highness,
if I use comedy
to mask my feelings and deal with stress.
Otherwise, I'd end up looking like you.
A very tight butthole.
Super tight.
You know, if the pressures
of leadership are too stressful,
perhaps you should leave and let someone
who knows what they're doing be king.
You know what?
I cannot wait to throw your ass
back in prison when this is all over.
You won't have to.
Once I stop David Kane,
I'll surrender myself to the Fishermen.
That is my honor to Atlantis.
You're so dramatic.
Whatever.
Just help me find this asshole.
Well, my contact
will at least know where to look.
What happened to him?
David Kane that I knew was ruthless,
but he wasn't insane.
This guy just put a gun to the world's
head and pulled the trigger.
Without even making any demands.
Congratulations, Dr. Shin.
That cannon of yours worked
exactly how you said it would.
Well, you found it.
All I did was figure out how it worked.
I didn't think we'd ever actually
have to use it on anyone.
Yeah, well, what can I say?
Things don't always go as planned.
But that's what I'm afraid of.
David, this stuff could reshape
the entire planet.
Hey, doc.
We are this close to unlocking
the greatest power in human history.
Are you really telling me
you want to walk away now?
If I said yes, would you let me?
Sure.
[creature trumpeting]
You want to see how long you last
in that jungle?
Be my guest.
[heavy, thudding footsteps]
[guttural roaring]
Yeah, I'll stick around.
Yeah.
[Orm] Welcome to the last frontier.
They scavenged ships from around the world
to build this place.
The Sunken Citadel.
It is the one place in the world
where the scum of the land and sea mingle.
It is where people come to disappear.
[Aquaman] Wow.
It's an impressive shithole.
How have I never
heard of this place before?
It is not meant to be common knowledge.
It's a pirate haven.
Pirates?
Listen, I don't know
if you know this about me,
but I'm not too popular with pirates.
[loud horn blast]
Oh, I'm well aware.
Relax.
It was the only way to get us both in.
[roaring]
You could've at least given me a heads up.
Would you have gone along with it?
- Hell, no.
- Then put a hook in it.
[scoffs]
[female voice singing]
[singing in Atlantean language]
[guzzling]
[chiming music playing]
[overlapping energetic chatter]
There. That's Kingfish.
He is the one who put me in contact
with David Kane.
He brokers deals with pirates,
mercenaries, slavers, you name it.
Cool.
I'm gonna go pick a fight.
Just let me handle this.
He's our best shot at finding Manta,
and he's not going to tell us anything
if you go in there
flexing your muscles at him.
You're so lucky we didn't
grow up together, little brother.
Do not call me "brother."
[Kingfish] Well...
This is a bit of a surprise, isn't it?
I didn't realize
you'd been released from prison.
It is a recent development.
Outlaws, aren't we all?
We need to find David Kane.
Bad news, I'm afraid.
David Kane is no longer on the market.
Not for sale at any price.
He's solely running
as an independent operator.
Where is he holed up now?
In exchange, I offer a favor...
...from the King of Atlantis.
[chuckles]
You seriously expect me
to play footsie with someone
with that kind of blood on their hands?
I don't have hands!
Or feet!
[howling laughter]
Um...
Listen, if the information
checks out good,
I promise you that I won't immediately
come back here and tear this place apart.
That's too bad.
Traditionally, the kings of Atlantis have
turned a blind eye to the Sunken Citadel.
Now, we have to blind it for you.
[sighs]
Fine. Flex your muscles.
[roaring]
[grunts]
[both yelling]
Smash his stupid head in!
Boom!
[screaming]
[grunting]
[whooping]
Gotcha, fatback!
[air hissing]
Okay! Okay!
We can work this out. We can.
Talk.
I don't know where he is,
but there have been rumors.
A dormant volcano in the South Pacific,
called "Devil's Deep."
Talk faster.
It's been barren for years.
But travelers say
there's a jungle there now.
Navigation gets scrambled
as soon as you start to get close.
And if you get too close,
you don't come back!
If I was a betting man,
and believe me, I am,
I'd say that's where Kane is hiding out.
[explosions booming]
We got all we needed. Let's go!
[gasping]
[soldiers roaring]
♪ Rise up, come
Rise up through the fire ♪
[faint, rhythmic thudding]
[rasping voice]
Soon you'll be more powerful than he is.
But you're not ready yet,
and you involved him far too soon.
I sense them closing in on us.
Do I seem concerned?
Hmm?
If anything, it's even easier now.
We couldn't have planned it
any better than...
[Dr. Shin] Oh. Oh.
Hey. [nervous chuckle]
Uh, I-I just wanted to tell you
that the orichalcum furnace
is now running at peak output.
[Orm grunts]
[gasps, groans]
[both panting]
[cackles]
I win.
[chittering]
Topo, go back to Atlantis
and give them our coordinates.
[Aquaman speaks Japanese]
[plaintive chittering]
[Aquaman] You know
what'd be amazing right now?
[Orm] Reinforcements?
Great, big, greasy cheeseburger
and a pint of Guinness.
[makes guzzling sound]
You gotta admit,
the food is so much better up here.
I find that hard to believe.
Hold up.
Are you telling me you never went topside
to have a cheeseburger?
- What?
- Or a slice of 'za? Pepperoni?
Or a thick, juicy, medium raw steak
with fries and a shake, and you dip it...
Even the words that surface dwellers
give their food sound disgusting.
You've let your prejudices
stop you from enjoying half the world.
You should think about that.
It's your loss, dude.
[Aquaman cackles]
Aw, yeah!
Bet you never had one of these.
- What is it?
- It's a cockroach.
You eat it?
Oh, yeah. Shrimp of the land.
[crunches loudly]
- Mm. Mm.
- Eh?
That's good. Here, drink this.
[groans]
Okay, you first.
[both grunting]
Are you seeing this?
[Orm] That's not normal?
Definitely not normal. Ugh.
[Orm] Let's get out of here.
You see how dangerous
the orichalcum can be?
I bet it mutated the flora and fauna
in a short amount of time,
turning them mons... trous.
Whoa.
[heavy chewing]
[chittering]
Oh, shi...
[screeching]
Run!
[Orm exclaiming]
Come on.
[Orm panting]
[Aquaman] Faster!
What the hell are you doing?
I don't know. I'm not used to running.
Just do what I do.
Use your arms, use your legs.
Lift them up.
Like this?
- Holy shit.
- Yeah!
- Wait up.
[yelling]
- [yelping]
- Whoa!
[both panting]
[Orm] We have to jump.
We'll survive the fall.
Are you crazy? It's gonna hurt.
So, what do you wanna do?
Stay here and fight the hopping demons?
[growls] What is that? What does that say?
[Orm] The writing is ancient Atlantean.
"A true king builds bridges."
- [Orm] What are you doing?
- [whoops]
[prolonged yell]
[grunts]
Got any more krill-brained ideas?
- [groaning weakly]
- [stone crumbling]
[grunts] See?
A true king builds bridges.
[laughs]
[giant bugs chittering]
That's a metaphor!
[Aquaman] Hey! I forgot to tell you.
Mom says she loves you.
She thinks about you all the time.
[Orm] Why the hell are you
telling me this now?
I don't know. I'm just tired of waiting
for the right moment.
[both yelling]
Come on.
[Aquaman yells]
[screeching]
[distant rumbling thud]
Looks like my metaphor
just saved your ass.
[rhythmic thudding]
Uh, David? I just ran more tests,
and this data is really disturbing.
We have to stop
burning the orichal... cum.
David?
[quietly] Oh.
[screaming]
[overlapping shrieks and growls]
[yells]
[gasping]
Okay, doc, you want to know
my plan so bad.
Here it is.
I'm gonna kill Aquaman
and destroy everything he holds dear.
I'm gonna murder his family
and burn his kingdom to ash.
I will avenge my father.
Even if I have to make a deal
with the devil to do it.
David, you can't trust the trident.
- [steel knife rasping]
- [yelps]
I never draw this blade
unless it's gonna taste blood.
Pray I never show it to you again.
[breathing shakily]
[gasps]
[door bangs open]
[door closes]
[Aquaman] We must be getting close
to the radiation source.
[Orm] We should wait for Atlantis
to receive your message.
We can conduct reconnaissance
in the meantime.
[Aquaman] Yeah. Look, Loki,
I'm not asking for your advice on this.
You've already lived up
to your end of the deal.
So you can go on back
to Azkaban for all I care.
[Orm] So, what's your plan?
[Aquaman] I don't have one, yet.
But he came after my wife, which means
I'm gonna pull his tongue out of his butt.
Arthur, you are the king.
You cannot let this get personal.
This coming from the guy
who turned the entire nation of Atlantis
into his own private ego trip?
My ego?
You're the one who swam to the front gate
and challenged my claim for the throne.
Only because you're trying
to destroy the surface world.
If you weren't such an asshole,
you'd still be king.
Unbelievable.
Wait, wait! Wait!
You took my throne
and you don't even want it?
Are you kidding me? I hate this job.
Only reason I'm doing it is to keep
Atlantis from destroying the surface.
And I might even be screwing that up.
You really had no ambition for it?
Absolutely not.
From the day
my father found out you existed,
he prepared me for the moment
that you would come
and challenge me for the throne.
Wow, that's really sad.
Especially when you think how easily
I kicked your ass
with basically no prep time whatsoever.
[clicks teeth] Roasted.
That is not how it happened.
- That's exactly how it happened.
- Mera saved you.
[Aquaman] No, she didn't.
I kicked your ass.
[Orm] Nope. She made
the little water tornado, I fell in it.
[Aquaman] Okay, shut up.
I think we're here.
- [Aquaman mimics bird call]
- [gasps]
[grunting]
Sleep, aloha.
[Orm] Come on, let's do this.
[Aquaman] Once this is over with,
we should go get some burgers and beers.
- [Orm] Don't push it.
- Tacos and tequila.
[Orm] I don't even know those words.
[deep, rhythmic thudding]
[men shouting in distance]
[Aquaman mimics bird call]
- Huh?
- Shh!
[attacking grunts]
Hey!
- [helmet clangs]
- [groaning]
[heavy groan]
[grunting]
[yells]
Whoa, brother.
[cusses in Maori]
It's an orichalcum furnace.
All that stolen orichalcum.
They're just burning it up.
[Aquaman] He's heating
the atmosphere on purpose.
[Orm] This is catastrophic.
This whole place must
be heat-shielded to protect it
from the surface's thermal satellites.
Question is, how do we stop 'em?
To take out this reactor,
we would have to crater the entire island.
Get away from there! Now!
This blaster may be ancient,
but it was built for killing Atlanteans.
Okay, I am so sorry. I did not mean that.
I just didn't want you to break me in half
before I could surrender.
Please take me with you.
Knock him out
and then help me hide these bodies.
No, no. Wait, please.
I didn't want any of this.
All I wanted was to see Atlantis
with my own eyes.
I thought I could share its wonders
with the world.
I'm a scientist
and I just wanted to be taken seriously.
David Kane said he could help me,
but now he won't let me leave.
You expect us to believe
you have nothing to do with this?
I know.
I've done things I'm not proud of.
But he would've killed me if I hadn't.
[scoffs] Knock him out.
No.
- Then I'll knock him out.
- No!
- What?
- No.
[frustrated growl] Fine!
You can come with us.
Oh... thank you.
But you better start talking.
Or I'm gonna give you one sassa!
Okay, okay.
It's the black trident.
It's a direct link to some ancient evil.
It gives Kane great powers and in return...
[yells]
[glass tinkling]
[grunting loudly]
[coughing]
I hate when that happens.
[suit sizzling]
[alarm blaring]
Stop them!
[speaking Portuguese]
[yells]
[both yelling, grunting]
[gasping]
[screaming]
[grunts]
[yelling]
[groaning]
[grunts]
[yelling]
Whoaa! [heavy grunt]
[groaning] Ow!
[straining]
No, no, no, no, no!
Not the orichalcum!
You wanna blow us up?
- This stuff blows up?
- Yes!
My bad! [yells]
Then stop using it!
Just shut up and let me save your ass.
Again.
[gears whining]
[heavy grunt]
[servos winding down]
[groaning in pain]
[grunts]
[coughing]
He's going to fight us
without the power suit?
I told you he's stronger now.
[scoffs]
He's still just a surface dweller.
- Bro!
- [growls]
I never expected to see you two
fighting side by side.
We're making a special exception
just for you.
[pained groan]
No one hits my brother but me.
I was gonna kill you last,
but thanks for dropping by.
You're making this easy.
[both grunting]
Yeah!
Come at me.
The killer of kings.
[pained grunt]
[hoarse scream]
[heavy grunt]
[thundering boom]
Take that island down!
- [alarm blaring]
- [yells]
Fire at will!
[blaring alarm continues]
We've got to get out of here.
[gasps in pain]
[computer voice] Malfunction. Malfunction.
Warning. Warning.
[David] Shin, let's go!
What are you waiting for?
Fire the goddamn cannon!
[prolonged roar]
[yelling]
[straining]
[Aquaman screaming faintly]
[grunting with effort]
[seabirds calling]
[Aquaman] I'm sorry
to drag you all into this.
But the Fishermen can't think
that Atlantis was involved.
[King] Atlantis does not command
the armies of Xebel. I do.
[Brine King] And the Brine Kingdom
has not forgotten its debt to you.
You may count on us always.
Something happened to me.
When I touched that black trident.
Why is he even here?
He should be on his way back to prison.
We should hear what he has to say.
I made that mistake once.
That's why I know he can't be trusted.
And he cut off my claw.
This thing took a whole year to grow back.
Look, he wants to stop Manta
same as we do.
And just for the record,
the only reason we made it this far
is because of him.
I saw the Lost Kingdom.
[waves crashing]
Mom, I don't know enough about this.
Is that even possible?
All anyone knows for sure
is there once was a seventh kingdom
and then one day, just before the fall,
every record of it was stricken
from the chronicles.
How do you know what you saw
was the Lost Kingdom?
No one even knows
what it was called anymore.
It's called Necrus.
And I didn't just see it.
I knew it.
It's almost like I was... remembering it.
Flashes of someone else's memories.
During King Atlan's time, there were
seven united kingdoms of Atlantis.
And the Black City
was a curse upon them all.
By exploiting orichalcum,
Necrus rapidly became a superpower
unlike any other.
But it came at a terrible price.
Poisoning the land, the sea.
Even the mind of the tyrant
who ruled Necrus.
Atlan's own brother, Kordax.
- [Atlan speaking indistinctly]
- [Orm] Atlan pleaded with him
to stop using it before the world
- was irrevocably damaged.
- [angry yell]
However, Kordax resented Atlan,
thinking his own brother
was trying to steal his power.
So he resorted to dark magic
and crafted an instrument of evil.
That black trident.
[yelling]
[screaming]
[guttural chittering]
[Orm] He transformed his people
and himself into monsters...
[groans, screaming]
[Orm] ...to fight Atlantis.
So the two brothers went to war.
[distant yelling]
[screaming]
[Orm] But Atlan defeated Kordax
and imprisoned him and all of Necrus
with a spell cast with his own blood...
...to ensure that Kordax's dark power
would never be found.
And that is why Necrus
is stricken from the chronicles.
[hoarse screaming]
This evil was supposed to remain frozen
for eternity.
But David Kane has found it.
And it's slowly possessing him.
But even with the ice cap melting,
Kordax still can't be freed.
Atlan used blood magic
to seal Kordax in his prison.
Only Atlan himself could release him.
Manta doesn't need Atlan himself.
Manta needs Atlan's blood.
Blood magic isn't really magic, it's DNA.
The key to Kordax's prison
is the royal bloodline itself.
That means he needs blood
from either you, me or Arthur.
We're the end of the bloodline.
No, we're not.
[tv newscaster] Wildfires would
have made headlines across the world.
But now, they're almost
a weekly occurrence.
We're witnessing unprecedented
weather events across the globe,
and meteorologists are at a loss
to explain this rapid change in climate.
From sweltering heatwaves and droughts,
which are shattering temperature records,
to torrential rains and floodings.
- What is going on?
- Hurricanes have been bearing down
on the East Coast, leaving
one million homes without power...
Make that a million and one.
I gotta get the flashlight, bubba.
[Arthur Jr. fussing]
[toy squeaks]
[thunder crashes]
[grunts]
I'm gonna leave you alive,
so he can watch you die.
[crying]
[groaning]
Dad!
- [Mera] Tom!
- Dad!
[Mera] Tom!
[Aquaman] No! Dad!
[Mera] Where's Junior?
[Queen grunting] No!
I'm sorry, son.
Where's Junior?
Manta... took Junior.
- No!
No!
[roaring]
[roaring echoes and fades]
[Arthur Jr. crying]
[crying continues]
[man] The medics have
stabilized his condition.
He will be okay.
[King] We just picked up a signal.
It's faint, but it's broadcasting
on an old Atlantean sonar frequency.
Headed to Antarctica.
- Bring our little one back.
- I will.
I've dreamed of this.
The two of you standing together
as brothers.
[shaky sigh]
Promise me you will protect each other.
Promise me, Orm.
Go.
[Brine King] Great waves, Nereus.
Your warship is powerful,
but it's slower than a sea cow.
I say we ditch all this dead weight
and travel light. Hmm?
And what are you gonna do
when he turns on that sonic cannon?
Our only chance is to hit him with total
overwhelming force from every direction.
- Not with Junior in the crossfire.
- What choice do we have?
We have no defense against that cannon.
Well, wait a minute.
So this cannon sends out soundwaves that
messes with our nervous system, right?
That's right. Ultrasonic echoes.
Well, what if we disrupt those echoes
with another soundwave
on the same frequency,
but just much, much louder?
You wanna disrupt their disruption?
Well, that's gonna be the easy part.
Take your weapons.
And ready your steeds.
[Brine King] Hmm.
[sets down gun]
Really doesn't like you, does he?
[laughs]
[Storm whinnying]
[faint rumbling]
[David] Made a lot of progress, doc.
They destroyed the furnace
before we could finish the job,
but we were damn close.
One well-placed missile
should do the trick.
[breath shaking]
My God, what did we do?
Nothing the world wasn't already doing.
All we did was fast forward things
a few years.
The ice hasn't fully melted yet,
but our scanning reveals a weak spot.
Here.
This will lead you straight to Kordax.
Power up the sonic cannon.
Bag the child and suit up.
[Arthur Jr. crying]
[Dr. Shin shushing]
- Yah!
- [Storm bellows]
[Stingray] Captain, we have multiple
incoming hostiles.
[David] You're too late.
No.
[sonar pinging]
Commence charge.
[machinery humming]
[rhythmic sonic pulses]
[whales singing]
[whale song pulsating]
You've gotta be kidding me.
[pulsating whale song intensifies]
[all screaming]
[metal creaking]
Astounding.
[Nereus] This place is immense.
It could be anywhere.
[Orm] The throne of Necrus is
in the heart of the city.
- [Mera] I sense something in the water.
- [Nereus] Everyone light it up.
Didn't you say that Kordax turned
his people into an army of monsters?
Yes. I did.
[Aquaman] Keep your eyes open.
Well, that'll be easy. Mine don't close.
[Nereus] Everyone stand ready.
Something's coming.
[overlapping shrieks]
Fire at will!
[screeching]
[grunting fiercely]
[yelling]
[Orm] We need to find a way out of here.
[Nereus] I think this goes
all the way through.
My men and I can deal with these worms.
Go now and save the prince.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Come on, you spineless worms!
Bring it on!
[gate booming]
[hinges creaking ponderously]
[ice creaking]
[both panting heavily]
[grunting]
[yells in pain]
Help me!
[screams]
[yells]
[howling yell]
[attacking grunt]
[creature shrieking]
[guttural scream]
[both panting]
Give me the child.
[timer beeping]
[yelps]
[heavy grunt]
[monsters shrieking]
[growls]
[rasping roar]
[panting]
[Arthur Jr. fussing]
You picked the wrong day
to grow a spine, doc.
[yelling]
[Orm] Get behind the portcullis!
[Nereus] We need to close the gate!
[crying]
[anguished groan]
[Arthur Jr. crying]
[energy pulsating]
Get away from my son!
Your blood will do just fine.
You want blood? Come get it!
[growling]
[yelling]
[grunting]
[panting heavily]
Aquaman!
[yells]
- [Aquaman yells]
- [David grunts heavily]
Oh!
[grunts]
[explosive grunt]
You wear my brother's armor,
and wield his trident,
but you're only half the man he was.
[dry chuckle] How pathetic.
[angry yell]
[yelling]
[groaning weakly]
[Aquaman] Mera!
[Arthur Jr. fussing]
[Aquaman] Go!
[trident clangs]
[Orm] Mera...
Run!
- [gritty scream]
- [Kordax] Free me from my prison,
and all my power will be yours
to wield as you desire.
[screaming]
[panting]
[yells, grunts]
[groaning in pain]
[Kordax] Kill him,
and you will be Ocean Master again!
[both grunting]
Well, now this is certainly
an improvement.
Powerful, Atlantean body.
And this one hates you more
than the other one did.
It's not true. Come on, little brother.
I know you're in there.
Don't you see? You can't win.
Either you kill your brother or you die.
[heavy grunt]
By Atlan's blood, this magic is broken.
[ice cracking]
[grunts]
My eternal night is ending.
I'm done fighting your puppets, Kordax.
I'm coming for you.
- Give it to me!
- No!
- I can end this.
- Don't let him take it!
Hasn't he taken enough already?
Yield the throne.
It's time for me to reclaim my destiny.
It would be foolish
to think he could ever change.
I knew you would do this.
You are the one true king.
Atlantis deserves its one true king.
[yelling]
I am the one true king!
You know, there was a time when I wanted
to meet you more than anything.
Let you know that you weren't alone,
that we were in it together.
[Queen] Promise me
you'll protect each other.
[exhales shakily]
Come on, little brother,
let's end this bastard.
I meant what I said when I first met you.
No matter what, you are not alone.
We're in this together.
You are my brother.
Orm.
Let go.
Orm, let it go.
[bones creaking]
[ice shattering]
I live again!
I have waited countless centuries
in the dark for this moment.
Shit.
Arthur!
[speaks Maori]
[howling scream]
[shrieking scream echoes]
[ice and rock cracking]
[groaning in pain]
[screams]
[David panting]
[straining]
Never.
[Orm] Arthur, we've gotta go.
The magic is broken.
Oh! [grunts]
[monsters croaking]
Let's get outta here!
[grunting]
[gasping]
Hurry!
[both yelling]
That's right!
Come on, baby! Yeah!
[Storm whinnying]
[Topo chittering]
Yeah!
[Aquaman whoops]
[whinnying]
My love.
- [Arthur Jr. cooing]
- Hi, baby boy.
Shin.
Thank you.
Astounding.
[heavy thudding]
[grunting heavily]
All here looking intact.
That's good. That's good.
Well, I'm not.
My claw got cut off.
Again!
[Nereus chuckles]
You're one tough crustacean,
Your Highness.
[Brine King growls]
As far as I'm concerned,
your debt is paid.
Not everybody's gonna see it
that way though.
It's too bad you went
and had yourself killed back there.
[Mera] Yes.
All this ice.
It'd be impossible to find the body.
Just lay low for a while.
But don't go too far.
I may need to call you up for some advice.
You know, with the whole
running the kingdom thing.
Thank you...
...brother.
[clang]
You're not as bad at this as you think.
The people of Atlantis
are lucky to have you.
You were everything I was not.
You do the right thing when doing
the wrong thing is much easier.
And you're willing to ask for help,
even from your worst enemy.
I know it may not feel like you know
what you're doing sometimes, but...
...keep trusting your instincts.
If you lead, Atlantis will follow.
After all, a true king
builds bridges, right?
I thought that was just a metaphor.
Well, your metaphor
might have just saved the world's ass.
[newscaster] We've got breaking news.
We are witnessing history.
A moment the ramifications
of which simply...
...cannot be overstated.
[speaking Spanish]
[speaking Korean]
A first contact...
...with the undersea nation of Atlantis.
An entire civilization hidden for
thousands of years about to be revealed.
[reporter] I think it's safe to say
the world will never be the same.
[reporter 2] The King of Atlantis
has reached out to the United Nations
and will be officially seeking membership.
[reporter 3] And is expected
to propose a joint effort
to reverse the climate issues.
[reporter 4] We are
told that this was the result
of weeks of secret negotiations
with the United Nations.
[reporter 5]
We now go live to Ellis Island,
where the first official ambassador
from Atlantis
is about to address the United Nations.
I come here today
as a representative of two worlds.
The land and the sea.
[applause, cheering]
And I stand here as proof
that change is coming to both.
And I'm calling for global unity
for a global crisis.
To finally bring harmony between us
and the natural balance of our world.
Atlantis stands ready to help
contribute its science and technology.
And with your knowledge of the air,
and our knowledge of the seas,
together we can write
the next chapter in our story,
rather than its ending.
Sometimes it's gonna seem like
our differences are too extreme,
but all we have to do
is look beneath the surface,
to see that we're all here on this planet
with the same goals and aspirations.
- Even when our customs
- Here you go.
- might seem strange and unfamiliar.
- Beer and a cheeseburger.
Extra greasy like you asked for.
[Aquaman] And by overcoming our prejudices,
we'll become stronger
and learn more about ourselves.
We can seize this moment
to create a better more hopeful future,
for our children, and our families.
My name is Arthur Curry.
I'm the rightful sovereign
of the undersea nation of Atlantis.
I'm a father, a brother,
a warrior and a friend.
I'm the King of Atlantis.
I am Aquaman.
["Born To Be Wild"
by Steppenwolf playing]
[joyful whoop]
Mm.
[crunches loudly]
["Deep End" by X Ambassadors playing]