The day
I went missing...
was the day I died.
Five years in hell
forged me into a weapon,
which I use to honor
a vow I made to my father,
who sacrificed
his life for mine.
In his final moments,
he told me the truth...
that our family's wealth had been
That he failed our city,
and that it was up to me to save it
and right his wrongs.
But to do that without endangering
the people closest to me,
I have to be
someone else.
something else.
Who's that?
Where'd he come from?
What's going on here?
Get the chopper back now.
Who's is guy?
Whoa, whoa!
Easy, wait, wait!
No, please...
Marcus Redman,
you failed this city.
Please, don't!
Please! Don't!
Cell phone, inside pocket,
call your partner.
Tell him to give those pensioners
back their money.
Do it now.
Okay.
Over the past 15 years,
Mr. Redman has withdrawn more than
$30 million from the plan's account.
Mr. Redman claims refunding
the Halcyon pension plan
has always been his intent.
But sources say Redman
was coerced by the vigilante.
This guy gets more air-time
than the Kardashians, right?
Five years on an island
and you still know who they are.
I've been catching up.
It's nice to see how much our culture
has improved while I was away.
But the city used to be different.
People used to feel safe.
Aw, what's the matter, Mom?
Afraid we're gonna be next?
Do you have
any questions about today, Oliver?
It's a simple
proof-of-life declaration.
Just read out a brief,
prepared statement to the judge,
and then your death-in-absentia judgment
will be voided.
It's fine, Walter,
I've been in a courtroom before.
Four times
by my estimate.
You know,
there was the DUI,
the assault on that
paparazzi douchebag,
stealing that taxi,
which was just awesome, by the way,
and who could forget
peeing on the cop?
I wish everyone would.
I'd hang, but we're
headed to court.
I know, that's why
I'm here.
My best friend
is getting legally resurrected,
- I wouldn't miss this for the world.
- Right. Okay.
What about you?
Oh, I think the first four times of you
in court was enough for me.
Fair enough.
Mrs. Queen?
Car's ready.
Walter.
Are you going to testify as to
what happened when the yacht sank?
Are you going
to talk about the boat crash?
Mr. Queen, did you
see Sarah Lance die?
Sarah!
There was a storm.
The boat went down.
I was the only survivor.
She's not there!
Sarah!
My father
didn't make it.
No!
I almost died, I...
I thought that I had,
because I spent so many days
on that life raft
before I saw land.
When I reached it,
I knew...
I knew that I was
gonna have to live for both of us.
And in those five years,
it was that one thought
that kept me going.
Your Honor, we move to vitiate
the death-in-absentia
filed after Oliver's
disappearance at sea
aboard the Queen's Gamut
five years ago.
Unfortunately we will
not be requesting
that the declaration of death filed
for the petitioner's father,
Robert Queen,
be rescinded.
The Queen family is only
entitled to one miracle, I'm afraid.
Now, onto the offices.
Everyone is waiting to meet you there.
Uh, Mom, that was...
...a little bit heavier than I was
expecting it to be.
Can we do that
tomorrow? Please?
Of course.
Thank you.
Last week, you couldn't
wait to get to the company.
Tommy, I'd just spent
five years away from civilization.
I wasn't exactly
thinking straight.
I... Hi.
What are you
doing here?
Oh, they were bringing me
back from the dead.
Legally speaking.
- What are you doing here?
- My job.
- Right.
- More like the D.A.'s.
- Hi, Oliver Queen.
- Emily Nocenti.
Oliver just got back from five years on
an uncharted island.
Before that,he was cheating on me
with my sister.
He was with her
when she died.
And last week, he told me
to stay away from him.
It was really good advice.
Excuse me.
- It was nice to meet you.
- Yeah. Let's go.
Come on, buddy,
shake it off. Let's go.
Mr. Somers!
What do you have to say about the
accusations made by Laurel Lance?
I don't know what I've done
to earn this witch-hunt
from Miss Lance
and her bosses at the CNRI.
But I can tell you this.
I am an honest businessman,
and I will fight this slander
to my last dime and breath.
That's all I have
to say, thank you.
Oh, there's Mr. Queen...
- Mr. Queen, do you want to follow up?
- What happened in there, sir?
Tell us what happened
inside, Mr. Queen...
Step back
everybody, please.
Can you give us
a couple comments
about the island, Mr. Queen?
Before you go, sir, please.
- Couple of comments about the island, sir.
- What happened in there?
Everybody, step back.
Hey man, I'll make you
swallow that Nikon. Back!
This happens to you
a lot, doesn't it?
How much is a life worth?
A life of a man,
a good man,
a stevedore on the docks
of the city in which we live.
A father.
A man with a daughter.
The plaintiff will prove
by a preponderance of evidence
that Victor Nocenti
learned that his boss,
that man sitting right there,
Martin Somers,
was taking bribes from
the Chinese Triads
to smuggle drugs
into our city.
And when Victor Nocenti
threatened to tell the police,
Martin Somers had him killed.
Mr. Somers is
very well-connected,
and has friends in the
District Attorney's office.
Which is why,
if Emily Nocenti
is to get justice
for her father's death,
if Martin Somers
is to get justice for his crimes,
then someone is going
to have to do it for them.
Martin Somers.
Laurel's targeted
the worst of Starling City,
so it's no surprise
his name is on my father's list.
The city's police and
the D.A. can't stop him...
or won't.
Laurel thinks she's the only one
willing to bring him to justice.
She's wrong.
You, listen up.
The longer this goes on, the more
likely the media is gonna crucify me.
You shut this trial down,
do you understand me?
What the hell?
- Martin Somers...
- Who the hell are you?
...you've failed this city.
No!
No, no, no, no, no!
You're gonna testify
in that trial.
You're gonna confess
to having Victor Nocenti killed.
There won't be
a second warning.
♪ Arrow 1x02 ♪
Honor Thy Father
Original Air Date on October 17, 2012
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
I hired you to
protect my son.
Now, I'm not
a professional bodyguard,
but it seems to me that the first
requirement would be managing to stay
next to the man
you're hired to protect.
With all due respect, ma'am, I never had
a client who didn't want my protection.
I hired you. That
makes me the client.
Now where do you think my son is going
on these chaperone-less excursions?
Ma'am, I truly
do not know.
And he truly doesn't.
Then perhaps you'd
like to share with me
you know, where it is you run off to.
I've been alone
for five years.
- I know that, Oliver.
- Mom...
Alone.
I see.
I promise to introduce
her if it ever gets
to the exchanging
first names stage...
No, I'd rather you promise to take
Mr. Diggle with you on your next rendezvous.
It's not safe, you've
already been abducted once.
There is a maniac out there,
hunting the wealthy.
That maniac saved my life.
This isn't a game.
I lost you once.
And I am not going
through that again.
Okay.
Digg's my guy.
Thank you.
Sorry to give you
so much grief.
I served three tours
in Afghanistan, Mr. Queen.
You don't even come close
to my definition of grief.
But I tell you what...
You ditch me
one more time,
no one will
have to fire me.
Where you going?
Uh... Somewhere
loud and smoky.
And don't bother trying to
pickpocket my stash this time,
because I'm gonna go
get drunk instead.
Thea,
do you think this is what
Dad would want for you?
Dead people
don't want anything.
It's one of the
benefits of being dead.
I was dead.
And I wanted a lot.
Except for your family.
You've been home
a week and all you do
is avoid Mom, ignore
Walter, and judge me.
Don't wait up.
Well, I owe you
an apology, Mr. Somers.
We come all the way
down to your docks,
and it turns out, you don't
need the police after all.
Which is exactly
what I've been saying.
Yeah. So I guess that 9-1-1
call we got last night
from your stevedore, saying
that you were getting attacked
by a guy in a green hood
and a bow and arrow...
I guess... Well, was that
a practical joke?
These guys like
to fool around.
Yeah.
Well, you know, I'd be
very much inclined
to believe an honest, upstanding
businessman like yourself,
except, well,
one of my men
found this
at your docks.
You see, there's this
vigilante running around.
He thinks he's some
kind of Robin Hood.
He's robbing the rich, he's trying
to teach them a lesson I guess.
I don't know, I don't know.
But the point is,
the man's a killer.
And nothing, and no one, is going
to stop me from bringing him down.
But like you said...
Hmm!
...clearly, nothing
happened here last night.
Isn't this a conflict
of interest, Detective?
After all, your
daughter is suing me.
I'm pretty good at keeping
my emotions in check.
I'm not.
You and your daughter don't want
to find out what I'm capable of
when I get emotional.
As you can see, Oliver, we've
modernized quite a bit.
Hi.
- Are you enjoying yourself?
- Yes, I am.
I remember when your father used
to bring you here when you were a boy.
You always
were so excited.
Dad let me drink soda
in the office.
Ah! So that's why
you enjoyed coming.
The Queen Consolidated's
success of late
is a result of its
targeted diversification.
We have been making impressive
inroads in cutting-edge fields
like bio-tech
and clean energy.
That's neat.
Excuse me?
Can I get a sparkling water,
or something cold, please?
Sweetheart, Oliver,
Walter and I have something
to discuss with you.
Come, please sit.
Mom, it makes me nervous
when you ask me to sit down.
The company's about to
break ground on a new site
for the Applied
Sciences division,
and we would like
to honor your father
- by dedicating the building in his name.
- Nice.
And we'd like to make an
announcement at the dedication
that you will be taking a
leadership position in the company.
No.
No, your... Your company.
No, I don't want
to lead anything.
Besides, Walter is doing
a very good job here.
You said that you wanted
to be a different person.
And you are
Robert Queen's son.
I don't need to be
reminded of that.
Well, obviously you do.
Everyone here understands that this
transition is really difficult for you.
Thank you, Walter.
Which part, though?
Everyone fantasizing that I got
my MBA while I was on the island?
Or the fact that my father's CFO
now sleeps down the hall from me?
You know, five years ago, your
irresponsibility was somewhat charming.
It is a lot less so now.
There he is!
The driver will
be here in a minute.
Okay.
You know, I spent the first 27
years of my life in Starling City,
and the next five
in Afghanistan.
You want to know
what I learned?
There's no place
like home?
No, just the opposite.
Home is a battlefield.
Back home, they're all
trying to get you.
Get you to open up, be somebody
you're not sure you are anymore.
Or I could be wrong.
Maybe after
five years alone,
you're not as messed up in the head
as you have every right to be.
Hey!
Hey, get away!
Dad?
Hey! Hey, stay away
from him!
Well, we anticipate
that Somers' attorney
will try and paint you as blinded
by grief or looking to make a buck.
This isn't about
the money.
I just want justice
for my father.
Emily, there are a lot of people who
don't want this trial to proceed.
Dangerous people.
My mother died
when I was a baby,
and my father has been the
only family I've ever known
and they slit his throat.
They are going to
have to kill me
if they want me
to give this up.
Well let's hope
it doesn't come to that.
And it won't.
What's going on?
What's going on
is that the three of you
are getting around-the-clock
police protection. Okay?
Get used to their faces,
because they're going with you
everywhere you go, no arguments.
I'm a lawyer.
I live to argue.
I'm your father.
I live to keep you safe.
Um, Emily, let's go grab
a cup of coffee, okay?
Yes, why not do that? Thank you.
Please, go with them.
Stay there.
Protective custody?
I seem to recall you trying that
once I discovered boys also.
Didn't work then either.
This isn't
a joke, Laurel.
Martin Somers got
attacked last night.
- What?
- Yeah.
- By who?
- It doesn't matter.
Point is, you have whipped
up a storm with these guys,
and until the dust settles
you'll be protected, okay?
End of discussion.
That might have worked
when I was eight.
But it's not gonna
work anymore.
End of discussion,
Laurel!
You're insistent on doing
your job, that's great.
But this is me
doing mine, okay?
And not just as a
father, but as a cop.
These people, they are more dangerous
than you are willing to admit.
And you've made them angry.
- Thank you for coming.
- Anything for a friend.
We're not friends.
You smuggle drugs,
I let you use my port.
For which you're paid
a lot of money.
I don't get paid enough
to have arrows shot at me.
You need to take
this guy seriously.
He is a bigger threat to your
operation than Nocenti ever was.
Except now it's Nocenti's
daughter who's the problem.
Unlike your friend with the hood,
we know where to find her.
Don't be an idiot.
You take out Emily Nocenti, and
Laurel Lance will never let this go.
She won't stop until
she burns you,
me, and then the entire
Triad to the ground.
Then we kill Miss Lance.
Attorney for shipping
magnate, Martin Somers,
has confirmed his client has
no intention of testifying,
maintaining his innocence in the
wrongful death of Victor Nocenti.
Nocenti's body was
found four weeks ago.
We'll keep you updated as more
information becomes available.
Wait, how did
you get those?
Don't you knock?
No, wait... Mom said
that there were scars, but...
I'm... Oliver, what
happened to you out there?
I don't want
to talk about it.
Of course you don't.
You never want to talk
to me about anything.
- Except for my social life.
- Wait!
Where are you going?
Why should I tell you?
I'm sorry, Thea.
I need to get better at talking
about what happened to me there.
But I'm not ready yet.
Okay?
Do you have a second?
Yeah.
Good.
I wanna show you
something out back.
Sometimes, when I
felt... Whatever...
I'd come here.
About a month after the funerals,
Mom stopped going out.
Pretty soon, she stopped
talking altogether.
The house got so quiet,
so I'd come here.
To talk to you.
I mean, stupid stuff.
Like what I was doing that day,
what boy I had a crush on...
And then sometimes,
I'd ask you,
beg you, to find
your way home to me.
Now, here you are.
And the truth is, I felt closer
to you when you were dead.
Look, I know it was
hell where you were.
But it was hell here too.
You gotta
let me in, Ollie.
You gotta let
someone in.
Hi.
Are you okay?
There are two
cop cars outside.
How am I supposed
to stay away from you
if you won't
stay away from me?
- I...
- What are you doing here, Ollie?
My sister took...
She pointed out to me that I have been
distant since I got back and that...
It would probably be a good
idea if I let somebody in.
So, you thought you'd start with
the first person you pushed away.
I did that
to protect you.
And then I
saw you yesterday,
and I realized
that I hurt you.
Thank you.
Wow.
This place hasn't changed
in five years.
I haven't really had
time to redecorate.
I'm a jerk.
Before the island, I was a
jerk, and now I'm just a...
I'm a damaged jerk.
What's in the bag?
I thought about many
things on the island,
but there was one thing that
I thought about every day.
I actually
dreamed about it,
and I promised myself that
if I ever got a chance
to do it again,
I'd do it with you.
Eat ice cream.
This is as good
as I remember.
My mother wants me
to join the company.
Yeah. Take my
rightful place.
I can't exactly picture you
as master of the universe.
You know,
after five years,
I have plans.
I have things
that I have to do.
I can't do that if I'm...
I don't know...
Attending board meetings
and stockholder briefings.
Oliver?
Hmm?
You're an adult.
You can say no.
Oh, I tried.
Didn't take.
Well, then
don't tell her.
Show her.
Be the person that you
want her to see you as.
Trust me.
I have plenty of experience
with disapproving parents.
I have been on the receiving end
of your father's disapproval.
He blames himself
more than he blames you.
He thinks that, you know, maybe
if he and Sarah were closer,
she would have told him
about the boat trip.
And he could have stopped
her from going with you.
I am sorry.
You apologized already.
And it'll never be enough.
Did you hear that?
What?
There's someone
on the fire escape.
- Hey, come on..
- What are...
- Are you hurt?
- No.
- Are you hurt, Mr. Queen?
- No! No.
This is why it's a good
idea to have a bodyguard.
You okay?
- Daddy!
- Oh, thank God.
- Thank God. Are you all right?
- I'm okay.
Those cops that you
put on me...
They...
I went outside to ask for a light and
they were both dead in the squad car.
Mr. Diggle, thank you.
Feel free to run as many red
lights in the city as you want.
I was just
doing my job, sir.
No, your job
is protecting him.
It seems like whenever you're with
one of my daughters, people die.
You stay away
from Laurel,
or I swear the next
time you disappear,
- it will be permanent.
- Dad!
- No, Laurel...
- It's okay.
I understand.
Yeah.
Here!
I'd say thank you, but I don't
think that would cover it.
Well, like I told your cop
friend, I was just doing my job.
Besides, I think it should
be you that I'm thanking.
- What for?
- The knife.
The knife.
- I got lucky.
- That was a kitchen knife.
It wasn't even
weighted properly,
yet you threw it with accuracy
across a 10-foot room.
Exactly.
I got lucky.
I'm not the kind of man you want to take
for a fool, Mr. Queen, you understand me?
Yes.
And I think I'm just beginning to
understand the kind of man you are.
Shouldn't take
you very long.
I'm shallow.
And very tired, so...
Good night.
Good night, sir.
It wasn't how
I wanted things to go.
I wanted to give Martin
Somers the chance to confess
and face a court's justice,
but he chose to go after
someone I care about instead.
He's still going
to face justice.
It'll just be
a different kind.
Everyone wants to know
what kind of man I am.
Martin Somers is
about to find out.
Triad bitch screwed up
the hit on Lance.
Now, the Triad is gonna
erase every ounce
of evidence of their smuggling
operation, including me.
Except that's
not gonna happen.
Tell Wallace to get the boat ready.
I'm leaving tonight.
Wallace?
Wallace, you copy?
Wallace isn't here.
But I am.
We need to move, now.
- Move!
- Sir, we've got six men out there.
It's not enough.
Move it!
You're gonna go back into
that courtroom tomorrow
and you're gonna recuse yourself
from this case, all right?
Or drop it.
Either way, you're done.
If you think I'm gonna
abandon Emily Nocenti,
then you don't know me
all that well.
You don't know me well,
young lady.
I will lock you in a cell
if that's what it takes.
Well, I guess that's what
it's gonna take then.
Damn it, Laurel!
I thought after what
happened with Sarah,
you'd stop being
just so reckless.
It's not about
being reckless!
It's just the opposite.
I'm trying to make this
city safer, just like you.
Sweetie.
You're my only
daughter, Laurel.
You're all I have
left to live for.
But what you want
from me isn't living.
Having cops around, not
being able to do my job.
Your job is not going after
people like the Triad or Somers.
My job is to use the law
to fight for what is right.
Just like you taught me.
Well, that's dirty.
Using me against me.
You can't do that.
Well...
Maybe I picked that up
along the way, too.
Lance.
I'll be right there.
I gotta go.
Something's going on
at the docks.
Somers!
Oh, God, no, no, no.
He can't help you.
I want the truth
about Victor Nocenti.
I can't.
The Triad will kill me.
The Triad's not
your concern right now.
All right, all right,
all right.
It wasn't me that killed him.
It was the Triad.
Acting on whose
instructions?
Whose?
All right, all right. It was mine.
It was mine, all right?
Nocenti said he was gonna
testify against me.
Put down your weapons
or we will open fire.
I repeat,
lay down your weapons.
Freeze!
You twitch and you're dead.
Bow down, hands up.
All right, all right.
It was mine. It was mine, all right?
Nocenti said he was gonna
testify against me.
You son of a bitch.
Laurel will be safe.
She was right.
I can't be the Oliver
my mother wants me to be
and still keep the promise
I made to my father.
I have to be the person
I need them to see me as.
Oh!
Excuse me, ladies.
Okay, this is a surprise.
Did you show up
here by mistake?
By invitation.
Oliver invited me last night.
Last night?
Is that surprise
or jealousy I'm hearing?
Look, I just don't want him
to find out anything, okay?
Oliver has been
through a lot.
Tommy, we've all
been through a lot.
Good afternoon.
And thank you
all for coming.
Welcome to the future site of the Robert
Queen Memorial Applied Sciences Center.
Now, this is a building that
will stand as a monument
to the man whose company and
vision are his greatest legacies.
Whoa! Whoa!
What about me? Right?
I'm a legacy.
Hey! Thanks for
warming them up, Walt.
All right.
Ow! Fine, fine shovel. I got it.
- Whoa! Ow!
- He must be drunk.
I got it. I got it.
Some of you may not know me.
My name is Oliver Queen.
Watch some television,
read a newspaper,
I'm kind of famous
right now.
Mostly, though, I'm famous
because I'm Robert Queen's son.
Uh, but as Walter,
who's my new dad...
Huh? Who is... Sorry.
As Walter was saying,
I'm not much of
a legacy, per se.
Oliver, you don't
have to do this.
No, sit. Sit!
Gosh.
See, I was supposed
to come here today,
and I'm supposed to take my
rightful place at the company.
Prodigal son returns home
and becomes the heir apparent.
But I'm not my father.
I'm not the man he was.
I'm not half
the man he was.
I never will be.
So, please,
stop asking me to be.
Martin Somers,
the CEO of Starling Port,
was arrested last night for
the murder of Victor Nocenti.
He is also being accused of accepting cash,
including over $10 million in bribes.
Well, we can pursue the
civil suit if you want,
but the D.A.
now has no choice,
with Mr. Somers' confession,
to prosecute him.
He's going to jail, Emily.
For the rest
of his life.
Thank you so much
for fighting for us.
Well, thank you for being
brave enough to let me.
Hey.
I thought I didn't need
police protection anymore.
I thought I didn't need a
reason to see my own daughter.
You don't.
Hmm. You look tired.
Yeah, I was filling out reports on
the shootout at the port last night
and getting grilled about how
I let that archer get away.
I have to admit,
I'm kind of glad he did.
He brought down
Martin Somers.
He hurt a bunch
of people doing it, okay?
He is no hero.
He is an anarchist.
Yeah, well, whoever he is,
it seems like
he's trying to help.
The city doesn't need
that kind of help, okay?
It's like I always told
you, you don't need to go
outside the law to find justice.
Now I believe that.
All right? And I promise
you, when I catch this guy,
he's gonna
believe it, too.
Well, you saw
for yourself.
My son knows nothing.
Robert didn't tell him
anything that could hurt us.
And he has no idea that
the yacht was sabotaged.
All that time on the island,
plotting my return,
I didn't realize
how hard it would be.
To reconnect
with Mom, Thea,
Laurel. Okay, I didn't...
I didn't know how painful it
would be to keep my secrets.
You asked me
to save the city.
To right your wrongs.
I will.
I swear.
But to do that,
I can't be the Oliver that
everyone wants me to be,
which means
that sometimes...
To honor your wishes...
I need to dishonor
your memory.
I'm sorry.
Take it down.
Will you be
going out tonight, sir?
Definitely.
No, no...
== sync, corrected by elderman ==