Welcome to St. Walker's, alderman.
Or should I call you mayor?
SEBASTIAN: Thank you for letting me
come by so late.
WOMAN:
Oh, I can imagine how busy your schedule is.
It's really great of you taking the time
to come visit your aunt.
Her health has taken a bad turn.
Of course.
She's family.
Maya, look who came to see you.
It's your nephew, Sebastian.
Don't go, please.
We'll be fine. Thank you.
Still worshipping the old gods, I see.
They're the last thing I have of your father's.
They protect me.
He was supposed to protect you.
A friend of mine, Laurel Lance,
came by to visit you a couple days ago.
Do you remember her?
[SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
Yes, she is.
What did you both talk about?
[SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
-Nothing.
-You know I don't like it when you lie to me.
I told her the truth.
That you killed him. Your father.
[SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
[SOBS]
I don't know what came over me.
I am so, so sorry.
I hurt you, mijo.
[SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
But you are my child, my son.
And I hurt you.
I forgive you, Mama.
I forgive you for everything.
[MAYA SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
[BLOOD SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
[MAYA SCREAMING]
[SHOUTING]
Please, I don't...
Look, I don't know anything.
-The man in the skull mask. Where is he?
-I don't know what you're talking about.
He's been experimenting on people
in the Glades.
He's leaving a trail of corpses
with blood running from their eyes.
No, no, no. I deal in stolen merchandise.
That is it.
Don't. Please. Come on.
FELICITY: Ask him what color his shoes are.
-What?
You want this guy to take a polygraph
via Bluetooth, cool...
...but I need to hear him establish a baseline.
I need to hear him tell the truth just once.
What color are your shoes?
What?
They're blue.
He's not lying.
Please.
He's out there.
-Somewhere.
FELICITY: Come home.
We can't do any more tonight.
OLIVER:
Slade?
Thought maybe he'd come back here.
He has the Mirakuru serum in his bloodstream.
He's not thinking clearly.
So, what do we do now?
I don't know, Sara.
The sensor grid is still active.
So at least we're gonna know
if Ivo and his men come back to the island.
So we just sit here and wait?
Do you have any other ideas?
Because right now, I'm open to suggestions.
We find Slade
and maybe we consider Ivo's offer.
What?
Look, if we get the serum back from Slade,
then we can go home.
And I can try to talk to Ivo.
I can get him to listen to me.
Like he listened
before he shot Shado in the head?
-He's just tired and he's frustrated.
-What?
You don't understand what finding
the Mirakuruserum has meant to him.
You're right, Sara. I don't understand.
And I don't get how you could even consider
trusting him after what he did.
He's not evil.
He kept me safe on that ship for over a year.
And I mean, not just safe.
He taught me things.
-And I learned a lot.
-I learned a lot too.
This island taught me
that you can't trust anyone.
Ms. Lance? I have a call for you on line two.
Thank you, Katherine.
[PHONE BEEPS]
Laurel Lance.
DOWNEY [OVER PHONE]:
This is Nurse Downey from St. Walker's.
You asked me to call if there was
any changes in Maya Resik's condition.
I'm sad to report she passed away.
-What?
-Her heart gave out on her, poor soul.
You think Sebastian Blood,
the saint of Starling City...
-...killed his mother?
-He was the last person to see her alive.
-That isn't a coincidence.
-He's visiting a sick relative.
-You're right, that's very suspicious.
-He didn't go there to visit her.
He went there to kill her, to cover up the fact
that as a child, he killed his father.
-Maya Resik told me what happened.
-From inside a padded room.
He had her forcibly committed. She tells me
the truth and two days later, has a heart attack.
-You don't find that strange?
-There's no record Maya Resik...
...was Blood's mother, and the hospital said
she was in the late stages of heart disease.
I need you to call in a favor
with Judge Carlin.
Get a search warrant for Sebastian's
campaign headquarters.
-I have to start somewhere.
-Laurel, this isn't some casual request.
I'm the ADA who took Vertigo on live TV.
I take a shot at Sebastian Blood and miss,
my career is done.
Adam.
-Please.
-I'm sorry, Laurel.
You're on your own.
OLIVER:
Hello, Roy.
[SCOFFS]
Lurking in an alley, that's not at all creepy.
When I ran the club,
I learned all the secret entrances.
I never got a chance to thank you
for saving my mother's life.
Thea told me.
She said that you were very brave.
-I did what anyone would have done.
-Not anyone.
Takes a lot to run towards danger,
not away from it.
That sounded like praise.
I thought where I was concerned,
you didn't approve.
Thea said that you also got hit
by some falling debris.
-How you feeling?
-Actually, it mostly missed me.
I'm fine. Look, I gotta get back to work.
Has Roy mentioned anything about the man
in the skull mask who injected him?
Roy is not the kind of guy who is comfortable
discussing his feelings.
Not like you and me.
Don't yell at me, but I think we need a
new plan to find this creepy mask guy.
Scaring lowlifes isn't yielding results.
Felicity, I am open
to any and all suggestions.
Maybe we're overthinking this.
What if the mask simply got wind that you
were after him and decided to skip town?
He didn't go to the trouble of re-creating the
serum and testing on people just to walk away.
He is still out there
and we need to locate him.
[CELL PHONE BEEPING]
Lance. For the Arrow.
-Yes, detective.
-Can we meet?
GREEN ARROW:
What is it?
Someone wants to talk to you.
Hello, Laurel.
You're late.
I had to circle around to make sure there
wasn't a SWAT team waiting for me again.
That's fair.
Trust me, I wouldn't have asked my father
to put me in touch with you if I had any choice.
-What do you need?
-Sebastian Blood.
He's about to be the new mayor
of Starling City.
-I know who he is.
-No, you don't. No one does.
A few weeks ago, I was approached by
your groupie, Roy Harper, and his girlfriend.
They asked me to investigate
the death of Max Stanton.
You think Blood was involved
in Stanton's death?
Blood or a man that worked for him
named Cyrus Gold.
[GRUNTING THEN SCREAMING]
Gold killed four cops,
including my father's partner, Lucas Hilton.
Blood and Gold knew each other
from the orphanage Blood was raised at.
He would do anything to keep the truth
about his past hidden.
Including murdering his own mother.
Why would he do that?
To hide the fact that he killed his father.
I tried going to the DA.
No one will believe me.
I swear to you,
Sebastian Blood is dangerous.
And you're the only person
in this city who can stop him.
Laurel was right.
I hacked Blood's cell-phone records.
He and Gold stayed buddies
since Zandia orphanage.
So what? They kept in touch.
Doesn't mean Sebastian Blood
is the man in the skull mask.
His last name is Blood.
That can't be a good sign.
He's dedicated his life, risked his life,
to help the people of the Glades.
And in his spare time, he's a murderer
trying to create an army of human weapons?
You're a bodyguard who fights crime
at night with his billionaire boss.
Not a lot of people
show their real face in public.
Oliver, what are you thinking?
Laurel gave me a case number to start with.
We need to know if Sebastian
really killed his father.
Then we figure out if there's a chance
he has the Mirakuru formula.
-I'm on it.
-What if this is just another trap set by Laurel?
She could be setting you up, and this time
you wouldn't have Sara to save you.
Asking a cute girl to meet you
down by the tracks, Harper?
-Good thing Thea and I are tight.
-I have to show you something.
Easy there, tiger.
You're not even bleeding.
-When did you start juicing?
-I'm not.
Then how do you explain what I just saw?
-You remember that night I went missing?
-Yeah, Thea and I were pissed.
I never told you guys
what really happened to me.
You were right about your friend Max.
He didn't OD.
He was murdered.
He was injected with something...
...and I was injected with the same thing.
But it didn't kill me, it made me stronger.
-Thea must be freaking.
-No, she doesn't know.
-I don't want her to.
-Why not?
I can't. Not yet. Not until I know
more about what happened to me.
-I don't wanna scare her.
-And you're not worried about scaring me?
Come on,
I was going crazy not telling someone.
So, what are you gonna do?
Well, the Arrow once told me
all I was good for was taking a beating.
Maybe it's time
I started handing out a few of my own.
I don't follow.
Now I don't need his help to protect this city.
Let's find us a bad guy.
I have good news and bad news.
I suggest the good news first.
Tends to soften the blow of the bad news.
Okay, dealer's choice. Good news is we found
the case file on Sebastian's dad's murder.
-Anything in it to suggest he killed him?
-Oliver, meet bad news.
That file was sealed years ago.
And since the file is over 27 years old,
there is no digital copy for me to hack.
The only hard copy is stored
the old-fashioned way in the city archives.
So I go in and take it the old-fashioned way.
Except security in the file room is so
old-school, you need a keycard to get in...
...which even if you had, you wouldn't
know where to start looking for the file.
An assistant DA would.
You said you needed my help.
Now I need yours.
-What do you need?
-You.
Know what I really miss about being home?
My bed.
[SCOFFS]
I don't know if I even remember
what a bed feels like anymore.
And you probably never will.
And neither will I.
Sara.
We are gonna...
We're gonna find a way off the island.
You just have to trust me.
Last time I trusted you
was right before theGambit went down.
I haven't gotten a chance to say this.
I'm sorry.
I know this is my fault.
And that none of this would have happened
if I hadn't invited you on the boat with me.
That's not exactly true.
I mean, I was the one who said yes.
-And it was only half because of your charm.
-The other half?
Do you remember when you spilled
that beer on me at Tommy's party?
No. But I never left one of Tommy's parties
with my memory intact.
Well, I wasn't even supposed to go.
But I snuck out of the house because
I knew you were gonna be there.
I mean, I had this... Heh.
I had this embarrassing crush on you.
And Laurel, she knew it.
I think that's why the party
got broken up by the cops.
She tipped off our dad.
And I was grounded for a month
and the next thing I knew...
...you and Laurel were together.
You think she did all that on purpose?
Not everybody is what they seem.
We should get some sleep.
[GRUNTS]
-You ready for this?
-Whatever it takes.
We're going in.
FELICITY: At least the security cameras
are from this century.
And now they're toast.
You have exactly seven minutes
until the system reboots.
Hey, check it out.
This could take a while.
You have six minutes.
I'm rebooting the monitors.
There's a Trojan plugging our system.
It's probably some punk.
Uh-oh.
-Oliver.
-What's wrong?
It looks like we got
the one rent-a-cop with a brain here.
If there's a camera nearby,
I recommend hiding.
Look, there.
You gotta send some officers here.
Starling's finest will be there any minute.
Get out now.
We're not leaving without the file.
Laurel.
I can't find it.
Up there. Third floor.
Hurry, Oliver.
Wait. "Case number SC-43878." This is it.
Vigilante, we know you're here!
Close everything off, now!
-They're blocking our only way out.
-Not our only way. Go to the east wall and wait.
Hands where I can see them!
[ALL SHOUTING]
FELICITY: I tried going through
all the security footage...
-...to see if anyone swiped the file.
-Did you see anyone?
Just this.
It's all been erased.
What happened when you reversed
the footprint to see who hacked in?
-I struck out. Must have been an inside job.
-Meaning?
-As a city alderman, Blood would have access.
-Anyone on city payroll could have done this.
He's running for mayor. One hint
he killed his father, his political future is dead.
DIGGLE:
Wait, I thought you two were friends.
Don't you think you ought to give him
the benefit of the doubt?
Please keep digging into Blood's past
and see if there's anything that can help us.
-Where are you going?
-To give a friend the benefit of the doubt.
What, are you still giving me
the cold shoulder?
You still not telling me
what the hell is going on with you?
Am I interrupting?
He and I would actually have to be talking
for you to be interrupting.
Can I try?
Be my guest.
-Tell her.
-No.
What have you got for me?
This guy in the Glades,
the Starling Slasher...
...word on the street is
he's got a thing for prostitutes.
And by "thing," I mean he has a thing
for slicing them up.
-Mostly hunts in Crescent Circle.
-Sounds like a great guy.
Mm. Yeah, problem is, he's some big-shot
lawyer, so no one has the sack to ID him.
Sounds like someone
the Arrow would go after.
-We don't need the Arrow.
-We have to bait him.
What pro is gonna let us
dangle her in front of a psycho?
-No. No. No way. No.
-Hey, Thea. Uh.
Sin has a date.
She was hoping to borrow an outfit.
You know, something slutty.
I have the perfect first-date outfit.
Guarantees a second one.
-Great.
-This guy won't know what hit him.
Or girl. Whatever you're into.
-I could do your makeup or your hair.
-You are not touching the hair, Queen.
Okay.
SEBASTIAN: You looking for me?
-Sebastian. Good to see you.
You too, man. Listen, I'm so sorry
but I'm right in the middle of a polling snafu.
I'll be quick.
I just had a question about Laurel.
-Is everything okay?
-I'm not sure.
I ran into her the other day.
Something seemed off.
I know you've been
spending a lot of time together.
I just wanted to know if you knew anything.
Well, we've traded phone calls,
but she's in trial, I've been campaigning.
-We haven't really been able to connect.
-Nothing happened between the two of you?
Not an argument or a fight or something?
If I didn't know any better, I'd say you were
acting like a jealous ex-boyfriend.
No, just...
No, I'm just looking out for a friend.
-And I hope you'd do the same.
-Of course.
Listen, I will take care of Laurel.
Thank you for letting me know.
You're new.
-Got to start somewhere, right?
-Get in.
Romantic.
-You're pretty.
-You're disgusting.
I see you'd like to play rough.
[GRUNTING AND SHOUTING]
Wait.
-I've got money.
-Keep it.
[GRUNTING AND SHOUTING]
Roy. Roy, stop it, you're killing him.
[GRUNTS]
Sin? Sin, I'm sorry.
We have to call an ambulance.
"Point-blank range.
Single shot to the heart from a low angle."
Obviously the handiwork
of someone quite scared...
...and very small.
How come the police didn't arrest you?
I knew how to cover my tracks.
A skill you've obviously lost
since you've gotten bigger.
You know how close you came to allowing
the vigilante to destroy everything?
Someone spoke out of turn.
I've taken care of the problem.
Your mother was not our problem.
-Laurel Lance is.
-You're the one who told me to get close to her.
You said that it was part of the plan
to hurt the vigilante.
It is. But you being sloppy isn't.
Fix this, Mr. Blood.
You don't want me to fix it for you.
Brother Daily.
I need you to take care of something.
Whoever you are, I'm calling the police.
DAILY:
No need to.
-Remember me?
-Officer Daily, right?
What's this all about?
-What are you doing in my apartment?
-We have a warrant.
-A warrant for what?
-Found these in your bedroom, Ms. Lance.
These aren't prescribed to you.
That's a felony.
This is ridiculous.
DAILY: You're under arrest for possession
of a controlled substance.
You have the right to remain silent.
Anything you say can and will be
used against you in a court of law.
I know what this looks like...
...but you have to listen to me.
I know what's happening.
Sebastian Blood, he's setting me up...
...because he knows I'm onto him.
He's trying to frame me.
So he planted drugs in your apartment?
No, no. Forget about the drugs.
The point is...
...is that he is the one
behind this witch hunt.
Sebastian called your boss.
He's worried about you.
No, no. He wasn't worried about me.
He's just trying to discredit me.
Don't you see what he's doing?
I see that you tested positive for opiates.
I see that you have been lying to me
and I see that you have been stealing from me.
I can explain that.
Every person that stands where you're
standing now says the same thing.
-Dad...
-The DUI, the paranoia about Blood...
...you looking like hell.
-You got a problem, Laurel.
-No.
It's addiction. It runs in our family.
You can't pin it on Sebastian Blood.
Daddy, please, you have to believe me.
Please. Please.
I don't, baby.
No, Dad...
[SOBBING]
How is she?
I don't know.
I don't know anything anymore.
I'll get her home.
Thanks.
Anthony?
-Are you there?
IVO [OVER RADIO]: I'm here, Sara.
I was hoping that you would reach out to me.
Are you alone?
SARA:
Yes.
Are you all right?
You're not hurt, are you?
Do you even care?
You were gonna shoot me.
No. No, Sara, I swear.
You were never in danger, I swear.
So it's okay because you were
just planning on murdering Shado?
-Her name was Shado?
-Yes.
And you killed her, Anthony.
And I'm gonna have to live with that
for the rest of my life.
I never set out to hurt anyone.
I started this quest to save people.
To save the human race.
I know.
Sara.
I know you think
that this ship rescued you...
...when you were stranded at sea.
The truth is...
...you rescued me.
But now the darkness
is threatening me again.
I need you, Sara.
Please.
Save me.
[EKG BEEPING]
How's he doing?
The damage to his head
and lower abdomen is severe.
He ruptured his spleen and he has
massive swelling in his brain.
Thankfully, he got medical attention quickly,
so he's got a shot.
You did a good thing here, Roy.
What happened to you out there?
-I don't know.
-We nearly killed this guy.
THEA:
Roy?
-Are you okay?
ROY: What are you doing here?
Sin called me.
-Why did you do that?
-Because she was worried about you.
Who is that guy?
He was my date. We put him there.
You did this?
-Just drop it, please?
-Roy, something is happening to you.
I'm not judging you.
I'm not angry with you.
I'm on your side.
I just want to help you.
You can't.
I... I got to go.
Roy.
[SOBBING]
You haven't said much.
Quietly working on your lecture?
No lecture.
Suppose you think I was
wrong about Sebastian too, then?
OLIVER:
I think...
...that you have everyone fooled...
...because you want people to think
that none of this gets to you.
And that you don't need anyone's help.
-I don't.
-Except I know you.
This isn't you.
What happened to no lectures?
I just... I need a glass of water.
Do you mind? Please.
BLOOD:
Leave him. He's not important.
Hello, Laurel.
[MUFFLED SHOUTING]
[GASPS]
Laurel.
It's me. Someone kidnapped Laurel.
FELICITY: Do you know where they took her?
-I think I have a pretty good idea.
If that mask is supposed to scare me...
...all that it's doing is confirming
what I've already known for a while now.
You're one sick son of a bitch, Sebastian.
BLOOD: Thirty thousand years ago,
masks invested their wearer with authority.
-Like a god.
-You're insane.
I'm not the one making drug-addled
unsubstantiated accusations...
...against Starling's favorite son.
If I can find out the truth,
then others can too.
You found out nothing.
-You know nothing.
-Ugh!
GREEN ARROW:
Get away from her...
...or I will put you down.
BLOOD: And to think, a few short months ago,
you were trying to arrest him.
GREEN ARROW:
You wanted me here. I'm here.
Let her go.
[GRUNTS]
BLOOD:
No, I think she should witness this.
[BOTH GRUNTING AND SHOUTING]
[SCREAMS]
[GUNFIRE]
Take off his mask.
I need to see.
[SIREN WAILING]
LANCE:
Sweetheart.
Are you all right?
Yeah.
Looks like Daily
was behind this whole thing.
The son of a bitch volunteered
for the raid that got Hilton killed.
And we found the accelerant that he used
to torch the Langford Institute in his apartment.
I thought it was Sebastian.
I was so sure.
Yeah.
Well, that's the thing about
the booze and the pills.
You know,
the same thing that dulls your pain...
...clouds the judgment.
DONNER:
Can we have a minute?
Yeah.
Are you here to say "I told you so"?
We're dropping the possession charges
and you won't be charged in Daily's shooting.
It was clearly self-defense.
You don't seem that thrilled for me.
Are you gonna look me in the eye...
...and tell me you don't have
a substance-abuse problem?
The DA's office has a generous
severance package.
Wait. Wait, let me explain to DA Spencer.
-I can... I can tell her everything.
-This isn't coming from Spencer, Laurel.
This is me. I'm the one that hired you.
I'm sorry...
...but you're done.
[SOBS]
Did Laurel really shoot him?
-She saved my life.
-That's a good thing, Oliver.
You okay?
She really had me believing that
Sebastian Blood was a criminal mastermind...
...and the only reason that I nearly believed her
was because it was Laurel.
I do have a blind spot
where she's concerned.
Not anymore.
Certainly know how to
talk yourself out of a victory.
-It's a gift.
DIGGLE: Take the win, man.
Daily's dead.
You destroyed the serum. It's over.
No, it isn't.
Hey.
Slow night?
-Something I said?
-Don't take it personally.
He won't even make eye contact with me.
Something happen?
He put someone in the hospital.
He's a little stingy with the details,
but you should've seen this guy.
I don't understand how any human
could've done that to another.
Each day he becomes more and more
like somebody I don't even know.
He won't even listen to me.
I know someone he'll listen to.
IVO [OVER RADIO]:
Sara, are you still there?
When you first found me...
...I felt like you were my savior.
And letting me into your work,
I felt like I was a part of something bigger.
You are, Sara.
It was only because I didn't want
to see what you were really doing.
I mean, what you did
to those people on the boat...
...and how you tortured them for science.
How I was glad that I wasn't one of them.
But now...
...I'd rather be dead
than keep being a part of this.
You ungrateful bitch.
You think you know what torture is?
You have no idea. But I will show you.
I am gonna hunt you down,
both of you, and I will show...
[TURNS RADIO OFF]
Let's go find Slade.
It's done.
They think it was all Daily.
He sacrificed himself for our cause.
SLADE:
A good start.
But the magnitude of your negligence
requires a greater sacrifice.
[SHOUTING]
Your incompetence has now cost four lives,
alderman.
Fail me again,
and yours will be the fifth.
[ARROW WHISTLES]
If that was supposed to go through
my other leg, you missed.
You seem to be healing pretty well.
You're stronger, you heal faster,
but you're not in control.
The serum that you were exposed to...
...it changes your body,
but it also warps your mind.
-How do you know so much about it?
-I've seen it before.
It twists men. Turns them into
someone they don't recognize.
Someone dangerous.
Maybe you should
put another arrow through me.
This time through my heart.
There's another way, Roy.
I can teach you to control your new ability.
To control yourself.
Let me help you.
When do we start?