OLIVER:
My name is Oliver Queen.
For five years, I was stranded
on an island with only one goal...
...survive.
Oliver Queen is alive.
OLIVER:
Now I will fulfill my father's dying wish.
To use the list of names he left me...
...and bring down those
who are poisoning my city.
To do this,
I must become someone else.
I must become something else.
NARRATOR:
Previously on Arrow:
Next time your daughter calls
the vigilante, we'll be able to listen.
I know you swore to bring
this guy down, detective...
...but using your own daughter as bait,
that's stone-cold.
- Where'd you get it?
- From your stepfather.
- And where did he get it?
- Belongs to your mother.
[LOCK BUZZING]
MAN:
Ready for transfer, sir.
VANCH:
Hi, George.
GEORGE: Vanch.
- Surprised to see me?
I imagine you would be,
seeing as how you botched my trial.
And from what Viv here tells me,
protecting my interests.
There were contingencies
that couldn't be anticipated.
Yes, Vivian told me. The head
of the Triad getting ventilated...
...Bertinelli getting collared,
and, uh, this archer.
Exactly. What am I supposed to do
in the face of something like that?
Absolutely nothing, Georgie.
Tell you what.
All is forgiven. Give us a hug.
Come on.
You know, I could use a place to stay...
...while I'm getting my sea legs
back under me, George.
And you got a nice place here.
What do you say?
George? George?
[VANCH CLEARS THROAT]
I hope George has been
food shopping.
I'm famished.
So this book contains a list of the names
of the guys you've been hunting.
And this book, your mother's,
has the same list of names.
IfsidenficaL
So where'd your mother get her copy,
Oliver?
For that matter, who gave it to you?
Felicity Smoak. She said
that Walter found it in their bedroom.
And now he's missing.
She's my mother. She's not
the kind of person who would--
Have her husband disappeared?
Because that's really the question.
I understand why you would believe
your mother over your stepfather...
...but I believe the innocent party
is whoever's missing...
...and presumed dead.
Twitch and I will open your throat.
- How many more are with you?
- What?
You have 10 seconds
to tell me something I believe...
...before I cut out your voice box.
Wait, wait, wait.
Yao Fei sent me here...
...and I'm pretty sure
it wasn't so you could kill me.
What?
Yao Fei.
He gave me directions to your...
...plane.
Frank, you gotta be kidding me. You
can't throw me another assignment now.
It's "lieutenant,"
and that's what gives me the authority.
I'm drawing in on the Hood investigation.
I am gonna get this bastard.
Have you considered the possibility
no one wants you to?
- What?
- He saved the Christmas hostages...
...he took down an arsonist
and armored car thieves.
And busted the Vertigo drug ring
when we couldn't.
What was urban legend
is becoming heroic.
If this man's a hero, I don't know
what my life in this city as a cop means.
Find meaning in following orders.
Frank, listen to me. I'm close.
If my lead comes to something more--
Come to me with something real,
Quentin, and we'll talk.
In the meantime,
I'm assigning you another case.
OLIVER:
Hey.
- Heading out?
- Mm, yes.
A meeting with the financial planners.
Are you all right?
There was something that
I wanted to talk to you about.
I wanna talk to you about Walter.
Right around Christmas,
when he disappeared...
...he gave me this.
This is your father's notebook.
He kept a list of all the people
in Starling City who owed him favors.
I had no idea
there were so many of them.
I've been researching
some of those names online...
...and they're not good people.
Oliver, I have no idea what your father
was involved in or with whom.
And you and your sister both now know
that he wasn't exactly honest with me.
- Then we need to find out--
- No.
If what you say is true
and this list is filled with bad people...
...and Walter was looking into it
and now he...
The only way to keep this family safe...
...is for everyone in it
to stop asking questions.
Including you, Oliver. Promise me.
THEA:
So this is really happening.
Four hundred and ninety-eight hours
of community service to go.
Four hundred and ninety-nine.
Orientation doesn't count.
Tell me how this is not cruel
and unusual punishment.
Anastasia, I'd like you to meet
our new intern, Thea Queen.
Interns get school credit.
I'm more like a court-ordered slave.
I can relate.
Anastasia is on a one-year
pro bono sabbatical from her law firm.
And apparently
from my six-figure salary.
The experience of helping others
is its own reward.
I have yet to see evidence of that.
Speaking of lack of evidence...
...Cyrus Vanch was released
from Iron Heights.
We represent a victims' advocacy group
trying to keep Vanch locked up.
- I'm calling Kate Spencer.
ANASTASIA: I did.
She said there's nothing the DA's Office
can do without further evidence.
Then I'm going to her.
She also said
not to show up at her office.
Vanch is connected
to human trafficking, drug running...
...racketeering
and at least 52 different homicides.
Okay. So, what's the play?
Unless you have access
to some private police force...
...Vanch will stay free
to roam the streets.
[PHONE RINGING]
I have to get this.
- Hello?
- How does a night with me...
...and a dozen famous chefs sound?
Like an episode of The Bachelor.
I'm auditioning potential chefs
for the club tomorrow night.
I've arranged a tasting and I could use
an extra set of taste buds.
I'm trying to figure out how to get
a vicious criminal back in jail. I can't.
- Perfect, it sounds like hungry work.
- Tomorrow night?
[OVER PHONE]
Maybe we could do it early?
Look, I gotta go.
- There's someone I have to call.
- I'll see you later. Bye.
You don't find that convenient,
her happening to burn the book?
- She did it out of concern for my safety.
- Or her own.
You said it yourself.
Whoever compiled that list...
...is involved in something dangerous,
and if your mother is lying to you--
She didn't know any of the names.
She said she didn't.
You don't have to take her word for it.
If this were anybody else, you'd be on
your way to an arrow-side chat with them.
This isn't anybody else.
This is my mother. And I know her.
[PHONE BUZZING]
DIGGLE:
What's that?
That is the phone I gave to Lance
so he could contact the Hood.
Is he asking you to turn yourself in?
He gave it to Laurel.
- Hello?
- I need your help.
ARROW:
That's why you have the phone.
Cyrus Vanch was released from prison
on a technicality...
[OVER PHONE]
...living large in his lawyer's house.
There's no evidence of foul play...
...but I know he's Vanch's first victim
and he won't be his last.
- What about the police?
- They can't move on him...
...without evidence
of new criminal activity.
OLIVER:
Laurel, obtaining evidence isn't what I do.
Vanch is dangerous.
Hold onto the phone. I'll call.
Laurel needs my help.
Oliver, are you running to help her...
...or away from the truth
about your mother?
I have work to do.
KELTON: Hey, detective?
- I'm busy, Kelton.
- I'm sure you're gonna wanna hear this.
- Yup?
The bug I put in that phone
from the vigilante just lit up.
Your daughter's playing Maid Marian
to Robin Hood again.
- Where you going?
- Lieutenant Pike's office.
If she's meeting with the Hood...
...there's gonna be a task force there
when she does.
See, we gotta look at all this
as an opportunity.
The Triad and the Bertinelli organization
are leaderless.
The giant sucking sound
you're hearing...
...is the current power vacuum
in Starling City.
One that I plan on filling.
How are you going to convince
the Triad and Bertinelli's crew...
...that they should sign up with you?
Well...
...that's an excellent question.
I need to do something.
[ON RECORDING] Something spectacular
to get their attention and earn their respect.
You know what I learned in prison?
If you want to be respected...
...you find the biggest guy
and put him down permanent.
I think I just found the biggest guy.
[POP MUSIC PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
[GIGGLES]
This is gonna be fun.
I even wore my fat pants.
- I don't wanna know what those are, do I?
- Nope.
[PHONE BUZZING]
[SIGHS]
- This is work. It'll just be a second.
- Okay.
- Hello?
-It's me. I have something.
Can you meet?
Uh, yeah. Where?
Rooftop, Winick Building, 3O minutes.
Good work, Kelton.
Okay, everybody.
Rubber bullets. This is my daughter.
She cannot come to any harm.
But outside of that,
you do whatever needs doing...
...to bring that archer down.
MAN:
You got it, sir.
You sure about this?
I'd do anything to catch this bastard
and this is the only option I've got.
Look, I wanna get this guy
just as badly as you do.
I just don't wanna see anything
come between you two.
I warned her. I said stay away
from this lunatic, she didn't.
You don't think
that turns a knife in my back?
I hope she sees it that way.
Mm, put those puppy-dog eyes away.
- Something's come up at work.
- That can't wait until tomorrow?
It'll only be an hour.
I can meet you at the club.
One hour.
- An hour and a half, tops.
- Mm.
Ricky has been driving me
for six years now...
...and I can't remember the last time
he missed a day.
Thank you for offering to fill in,
Mr. Diggle.
It's my pleasure, Mrs. Queen.
Believe me.
Are you sure my son won't miss you?
Said he was staying in for the evening.
And you believed him?
It's been my experience
when your son wants some alone time...
...there's not much
I can do to stop him.
Much to my chagrin.
You can stop just up ahead.
No need to escort me inside.
I'm fine on my own, Mr. Diggle.
Of course, Mrs. Queen.
MOIRA:
Were you surprised? You were? Ha, ha.
WOMAN:
Look who just came in.
MOIRA:
Mr. Diggle.
Mrs. Queen,
I was just, uh, looking for the restroom.
Excuse me, ladies. Happy birthday.
ARROW:
Hello, Laurel.
- Thank you for helping.
- I couldn't do much.
Vanch's position is too heavily fortified.
But I did get this.
Evidence he's trying
to take over the positions...
...vacated by Frank Bertinelli and--
[DOOR OPENS]
And the Triad.
What's wrong?
- We're not alone.
- What?
S.C.P.D. Get down!
- Hands where we can see them!
- Dad.
Do it now!
You leave a bruise on her
and I will drag you down to hell myself.
Laurel, I'm sorry.
Quentin, don't!
[BOTH GRUNT]
LAUREL:
I don't know what's worse.
The fact that you lied to me
or nearly got me killed.
You were completely safe.
I was on a rooftop with an army of men
pointing their guns in my face.
- You shouldn't have been on that roof--
- No.
You wanted me on that roof.
Wasn't that the whole point
of your trap?
- I'm trying to catch a killer.
- You manipulated me.
Manipulated?
You practically ran to this guy.
I told you. I said stay away--
- Before you gave me the phone.
- What?
That's before you realized
you could use me as bait.
- Your own daughter.
- But you wouldn't listen to me.
You are so blinded by hate
that you don't realize...
...the damage that it's doing
in your own life, to your family.
So, what happens when you catch him?
What happens then, Dad?
You're gonna find another criminal?
Somebody else to blame
for Morn leaving?
For Sara dying? For your drinking?
- That's enough, Laurel.
- Yeah, you're damn right, it is.
Laurel.
The phone.
Give me the phone.
- Laurel could've been hurt or worse.
- And I suppose that was Lance's fault.
What's your point, Dig?
Just that you don't see straight
when it comes to Laurel or your mother.
This is not the time
to bring this up again.
Okay.
Okay. But there's something I should
tell you and it's better now than later.
I'll be driving your mother around.
- You're spying on her?
- Just doing my due diligence.
See if she meets with anyone
we might be interested in.
She's not a suspect. She's my mother.
Which is exactly why someone needs
to take a close, objective look at her.
Oliver, something's going on in this city,
you know it.
That doesn't mean she's involved.
Then there's no harm in me driving her
around for a few days, is there?
I still can't believe it. He used me as bait.
- Who?
- My father.
He was trying to catch the vigilante.
He eavesdropped on my phone
conversation and then lied in wait.
- This was tonight?
- Yes.
While you were working?
This was work.
So you met up with the Hood guy?
Knowingly?
He's contacted me before.
He helped me with the Declan case
and Joanna's arson investigation.
- The Declan case was months ago.
- I know.
- Tommy, I've been wanting to tell you.
- Laurel, he's a murderer.
- You sound like my father.
- I hate to break it to you but he's right.
Are you seriously taking his side?
He's been lying to me for weeks.
Yeah, it feels like crap, doesn't it?
Tommy.
MAN [ON TV]: A sting operation to catch
the notorious Starling City Vigilante...
...wreaked havoc last night...
...despite the police's failed attempt
to apprehend the vigilante.
Police have continued to insist
that their warnings remain.
This archer is to be considered
armed and dangerous.
Should you find yourself in harm's way,
as always, call 911.
Interesting.
Using deception and intimidation
to make a name for himself.
Ha, ha. This guy stole my move.
I have news...
...from my friend
in the police department.
I think I've figured out a way
to get the Hood out and into the open.
Huh.
Astonish me.
Remember that attorney, Laurel Lance?
Hey, what's wrong with this picture?
You look like you're working.
Heh. I'm going over résumés
for the chef's position at the nightclub.
This guy looks good.
He won Top Chef season six.
At this point, it is basically a culinary
prerequisite to be on that show.
Oh.
Can I talk to you about something?
Tommy, every time you wanna talk about
something and that something is Laurel...
...you look like you're about to tell me
you have a terminal disease.
- She's been working with the Hood guy.
- What?
You're letting her work
with that person?
- She could get hurt, Tommy.
- I'm not letting her do anything.
I only just found out about it...
...because she accidentally slipped up
on one of her many lies.
Wait, she's lying to you?
That doesn't sound like Laurel.
Lying, keeping secrets
about who she's with.
Does that remind you
of anybody we know?
Me, in every relationship
that I've been in.
Me too. Except this one.
There's some sort of infatuation thing
going on here.
We both know that she has
a pretty strong track record...
...of being attracted to guys
who are dangerous, who break the rules.
Show me a more dangerous rule breaker
than the Hood.
You need to have
an honest chat with her.
Find out the real reason
she's keeping secrets.
I can't believe that Laurel,
of all people, would lie to my face.
I guess that's the way that it is
with the people that you're closest to.
I know.
But talk to her anyway and fix this...
...before it becomes something
that's unfixable.
[SPEAKS CHINESE]
-It's Chinese. It means--
-"Survive."
What do you think he meant,
besides not getting killed?
There's an airfield 'IO clicks from here.
It's key off this island.
Yao Fei and I had been observing it
for months...
...familiarizing ourselves
with their operations.
We were supposed
to get off this island together.
But then Yao Fei was compromised,
and we were separated.
What's this for?
I think Yao Fei sent you here because he
knows I cannot take the airstrip alone.
Sounds like Yao Fei.
He is a softerjudge of character
than I am.
If you're going to have my back...
...I need to know you can cover it.
What are you doing? Fight back.
[GRUNTING]
Keep your blade up.
Always stay behind your sword.
You have no skill, no strength,
no training.
To say you fight like a girl
would be a compliment.
I told you, I'm not a soldier.
I was shipwrecked here.
I killed the guy that was wearing
this uniform by accident.
Where was Yao Fei?
He told me to run...
...and I did.
TOMMY [ON RECORDING]:
Hey, it's Tommy. Hit me on the beep.
Hey, it's me again.
Please call me back.
I think we should talk.
[DOORBELL BUZZES]
I was just leaving you a message.
[LAUREL GASPS]
[ALL GRUNTING]
I love a girl
who can take care of herself.
[LAUREL GASPS THEN TASER BUZZES]
But can't block a Taser.
No need to get out of the car,
Mr. Diggle.
It's just my accountant.
The only threat is boredom.
It's no problem at all, Mrs. Queen.
It's my job.
Yes. Well, then, take the night off.
I'm quite all right.
MOIRA:
What do you want?
[MOIRA CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY]
MOIRA:
It's taken care of. I've taken care of it.
Carl Ballard
will not be a problem anymore.
Given your propensity
for squeamishness...
...I'm assuming that
Mr. Ballard remains in good health.
I made it clear to him, persuasively,
that his plans endanger the undertaking.
- I didn't have to make the usual threats.
- Excellent.
Now, one more matter to attend to.
I need you to have
the contents of this address...
...removed and disposed off
thoroughly.
The warehouse where you're storing
the remains of the Queen's Gambit.
I already told you,
I knew Robert's yacht was sabotaged.
And I don't think it serves for anyone
to find evidence of that.
[DOOR OPENS]
MAN:
What the hell are you doing?
Nothing. Just hanging.
I work for Mrs. Queen.
And I work security
for the man she's meeting with.
- Guess we're on the same team.
- I don't think so.
And I'm gonna need to see
what you put in your pocket.
- What are you, man, the police?
- Show it to me.
Do it now.
Right.
Just thought I could come in here
and ruin my lungs a little bit.
I know it's a filthy habit.
Laurel, it's me. Can we talk?
Laurel?
[BEEPING]
VANCH [ON RECORDING]: Make sure
this message finds its way to the vigilante.
Do it fast, because at sunrise
I'm gonna leave pieces of this girl...
...all over Starling City
unless he pays me a little visit.
You know, give us a chance
to get to know each other better.
What do we do? Can your CSls...?
I don't know. Can they track this
or trace it or something?
- How did he know about Laurel?
- What?
How does this guy know
Laurel is connected to the Hood?
No idea.
I only found out about it myself
last night.
- She said you knew.
- Well, just me and...
Mr. Lance, that maniac has got Laurel.
You've gotta call in posse
or something.
- I don't know, SWAT teams.
- I can't.
Detective Lance.
I gotta go make a call.
Thanks for coming. It didn't seem
like a good idea to talk at your house.
Would've been awkward
for you to explain to my mother...
-...that you're spying on her.
- No, man.
- The awkward part's coming up.
- You bugged my mother?
Just listen.
MOIRA [ON RECORDING]:
It's taken care of. I've taken care of it.
Carl Ballard
will not be a problem anymore.
MALCOLM:
Given your propensity for squeamishness...
...I'm assuming that Mr. Ballard remains
in good health.
MOI RA:
I made it clear to him, persuasively...
...that his plans endanger the undertaking.
I didn't have to make the usual threats.
MALCOLM:
Excellent.
Now, one more matter to attend to.
I need you to have the contents
of this address...
...removed and disposed off
thoroughly.
The warehouse where you're storing
the remains of the Queen's Gambit.
MOI RA:
[already told you...
...I knew Robert's yacht was sabotaged.
- I'm sorry, man.
- The yacht was sabotaged?
- Somebody tried to kill my father.
- Your mother was involved somehow.
You do not know
that she was involved, Diggle.
What I do know, Oliver,
and so do you...
...is that she kept this a secret.
Why would she do that
if she didn't have something to hide?
[PHONE BUZZING]
-Isn't that--?
- Yeah.
You have three seconds before I have
this line permanently disconnected.
It's Laurel. She's been kidnapped.
Listen, whoever this is,
he's gonna kill my daughter.
Please believe me.
Sorry.
It's nothing personal.
The airstrip is
a very heavily fortified position.
I've been there.
- And I cannot take it on my own.
- So what?
Huh? You're just gonna kill me?
- Ah.
- Like I said, it's nothing personal.
If you're alive, they will find you.
If they find you, they will torture you...
...until you give up my location,
and I cannot allow for that to happen.
Hey, no, wait.
No, please don't do this.
I'm not gonna say anything to them.
Don't make it more difficult
upon yourself.
I can do this in a way
that you will not feel it at all.
[OLIVER GRUNTING]
[SCREAMS]
[OLIVER SCREAMS]
[SLADE LAUGHING]
- Slade Wilson.
- Oliver Queen.
Well, Oliver Queen...
...there might be a fighter
inside of you after all.
Detective, if this is another trick,
you will not like the consequences.
I'm not particularly happy right now.
I hate you.
I hate everything you stand for.
But this lunatic has my little girl.
He left this behind
as some kind of ransom note.
His name is Cyrus Vanch.
Jeez.
- He'll kill her if he doesn't get you.
- He'll kill her anyway...
...so why come to me?
It's a pretty tight circle that knows about
you and my daughter working together.
If Vanch knows it's because
someone at the precinct talked.
- There isn't anybody else I can trust.
- Vanch is holed up in a mansion.
It's a heavily fortified position.
I was there. I can't take it by myself.
I need your help.
Then I need yours.
Time's running out
and still no visit from your friend.
I might have overestimated
his fondness for you.
[GASPING]
Assault with intent and kidnapping.
You're gonna rot in prison
for life this time.
[CHUCKLES]
That's assuming
your hooded BFF saves you.
And his chances of survival
are not so great.
He's going up against trained men
with their fingers on the trigger...
...of guns that fire
up to 600 rounds per minute.
Now, I'm no Einstein,
but that is a lot of bullets.
[GRUNTS]
[MAN YELLS]
And even if he were to take them out...
...I have two sharpshooters
on the roof.
And even if he were to get by them...
...what's he gonna do against the army of
sons of bitches I've got waiting for him?
Now, as I said, I'm no Einstein,
but I can count to 24.
In case you're wondering, I was,
so I studied up on my news footage...
...24 is the exact number of arrows
he carries in his quiver...
...and fléchettes around his forearm.
[GUN COCKS]
[VANCH CHUCKLES]
Lose the bow, Merida.
Ventilate him.
My daughter. My little girl!
ARROW:
I'm the vigilante, you're the cop.
Doesn't mean I have to read
the bastard his rights, though.
Laurel, are you okay?
Yeah. Yeah.
I'm okay.
All right, you're good to go.
I'll take you home now.
I can take a cab.
Laurel, you had a trauma.
I'll drive you home.
- No.
- What?
I'm gonna need you
to keep your distance for a while.
- Laurel.
- Dad, I love you.
I'll always love you.
But what I can't do right now
is trust you.
I was doing my job.
I thought you'd understand at least that.
That part I do understand.
But lying to me, using me?
It's gonna take longer.
Are you all right?
What would you think
if I said I didn't know?
That you were being honest.
My father has the phone now.
I don't think
he'll be giving it back soon.
Maybe that's good.
I didn't see
how it would put you in danger.
I'm a big girl.
- I knew the risks.
- Now I know them.
And I'm not willing
to take them with you.
- What does that mean?
- It means goodbye.
TOMMY:
Laurel?
Laurel.
Oh, my God, Laurel.
- Laurel, tell me you are okay, please.
- No, no, I'm fine.
I'm so sorry.
No, no, it doesn't matter,
just as long as you're okay.
You know, this does not change
anything between you and I.
It takes two men to take the airfield.
And if you compromise
my getting off this island, I will kill you.
You've had your second chance.
You need me
just as much as I need you.
[CHUCKLES]
So, what's our next step?
Turning you into something
that won't get us both killed.
Choose a weapon.
We're starting now?
That's mine.
You're the lunatic who tortured me.
- No, that was another guy.
- Bull.
This mask, it's my operational
equivalent to a balaclava.
My partner and I wore them...
...to keep our identities classified
during our missions.
You're lying.
Fyers told me that this nutcase
is a prisoner on the island.
And Fyers is such
a trustworthy individual?
He lied to you.
My partner and I came here to free
Yao Fei and get him off this island.
We're ASIS.
Australian Intelligence.
Now, you're going to find
your silver weapon.
Have you considered a sword?
I like swords.
MOIRA [ON RECORDING]:
I made it clear to him, persuasively...
...that his plans endanger the undertaking.
I didn't have to make the usual threats.
I've listened to this 15 times.
It's definitely her voice, Diggle.
I just...
I can't believe it's her.
We all have blind spots
when it comes to family.
Yeah. Laurel's almost got her killed.
Vanch never would've known...
...about her connection to me
if Lance hadn't lied to her.
Guess the lesson here
is blind trust can be dangerous.
MOI RA:
I made it clear to him, persuasively...
...that his plans endanger the undertaking.
- I didn't have to make the usual threats.
MALCOLM". Excellent.
- What's the undertaking?
- I don't know.
But with all this talk about threats,
it can't be good.
You warned me that if she was lying...
...it would be to cover up her
involvement in something dangerous.
I need to know
what the undertaking is.
What are you gonna do?
I need to have another chat
with my mom.
I'll need the Unidac merger finalized
by the end of the week.
We're on something of a clock here.
[MOIRA SCREAMS]
Moira Queen, you have failed this city.
[English - US - SDH]