My name is Oliver Queen.
For five years, I was stranded
on an island with only one goal...
...survive.
Oliver Queen is alive.
Now I will fulfill my father's dying wish
to use the list of names he left me...
...and bring down those
who are poisoning my city.
To do this,
I must become someone else.
I must become something else.
Previously on Arrow:
Rescuing your father and stopping Fyers
is not gonna be some walk in the park.
- Yao Fei.
- Pa.
How did you escape?
I didn't.
You told me to stay away
from your family and I did.
But your family isn't staying away,
which means something must be done.
You're going home.
About my mother and about
her involvement in the Undertaking.
She's working with Malcolm Merlyn,
and they're planning something terrible.
So I was wondering,
there's a late night happy hour at Stella's.
The place across the street.
The place that's always playing
loud salsa music at all hours...
-...when I'm trying to work late?
- That would be the one.
Anyway, I was thinking that, uh,
maybe, you know...
...if you wanted to,
we could perhaps grab a drink?
How about two?
Oh, my God!
Please, I did everything
Mr. Merlyn required of me.
He knows, Dr. Markov,
and he thanks you for your service.
- Open the door!
- Open the--
- Freeze!
Open the door.
- Open the door.
- Get down on the floor!
Open the door.
I've been watching your mother
for days now, Oliver, and nothing.
She goes to work, she comes home.
Occasionally she goes out to dinner.
She seems to like
the salmon tartare at Table Salt.
I'm linked into phone.
Nothing out of the ordinary.
No mention of Walter's abduction
or the Undertaking.
- Just innocuous calls to Malcolm Merlyn.
- Why wouldn't she call him?
They're old friends.
We're all old friends.
Are you okay?
My mom and my best friend's dad
are involved in a conspiracy...
...that may have dire consequences for
the city. I'm sure they murdered my father.
I'm not planning on using the word
okay again anytime soon.
All we know is Malcolm and your mother
are planning something for the Glades.
Walter and I were getting close.
That's why they had him kidnapped.
We have to find out
what this Undertaking is.
I gotta ask her.
Well, no. The last time the vigilante
paid your mom a visit...
...you got shot,
and I got to play doctor with you.
Oh! My brain thinks of
the worst way to say things.
This time it'll just be me asking.
Friendly mother-son chat.
Laurel, what are you doing here?
It's not even 7 a.m.
That's just after closing time, right?
- How's business?
- Well, it's busy.
Busy. It was easier
when Tommy was running things.
- Tommy's a good guy.
- Yeah.
- Are you?
- What do you mean?
Last week, I told you
that I wanted to get back with Tommy.
That I needed you to go to him and explain
that you didn't still have feelings for me.
But instead, you told me that you did.
As I'm sure you can probably imagine,
I haven't been able to think of much since.
- I shouldn't have said that.
- Then why did you?
L-- I didn't have an agenda.
I didn't mean to make it more difficult
for you to fix things with Tommy.
But what if you did?
After you disappeared with Sara...
...I was sorry I ever knew you.
But now things have happened
that I never thought would.
You coming home.
My parents being in the same room.
And you.
What if I'm finally starting to see you
for who you really are?
_No__
- Maybe Tommy was right.
Maybe he and I weren't meant to be.
Maybe I'm finally ready to admit...
...that I still have feelings for you too.
Nothing's changed.
My life hasn't changed.
I haven't changed.
I gotta go. Walter's coming home.
Everything's exactly as you left it.
- How are you feeling, Walter?
- I'm on the mend, thank you, Oliver.
- Oh, I'm so glad you're home.
- That makes two of us.
All of us.
We've prepared a delicious brunch for you.
All your favorites.
Yum, English food.
Actually, I'm more tired
from the drive than I expected.
- So I think I'd like to lie down for a bit.
- Yes, of course.
Walter doesn't really seem like himself.
He's gone through a lot.
It's just gonna take a little bit of time.
I'm really sick of us all
having to go through a lot, you know?
Six scientists and three security personnel
are confirmed killed in the massacre.
Among the dead,
respected seismologist, Brian Markov.
A spokesperson for Unidac Industries
says a comment would be forthcoming.
- Mom, we need to talk.
- Oh, uh, later, Oliver.
--To co-workers, parents and families
of all the victims...
...to see how they're coping
with their loss.
You--
Save it. We don't have the luxury
of indulging in vendettas.
- Pa.
Shade .
You led Fyers right to us, you coward.
Fyers was about to fire bomb
the entire forest just to eliminate you.
This way, you all have a chance.
Pray I don't get the chance
to repay your mercy.
How fitting. Everyone reunited for the end.
The end of what? What is all this for?
HKIA, this is Ferris,
Flight 637 out of Berlin, nonstop to Hong Kong.
We are steady on approach at 33,000 feet
with winds at 15 knots.
ETA, two hours, 15 minutes, over.
Ferris 637, this is HKIA. Adjust course
to 0.6 degrees south, 11 minutes, over.
Roger, HKIA.
Why the course change?
Nothing to worry about, 637. Just looking
to make sure you avoid a little turbulence.
Roger that. Adjusting course now.
They're altering course. The plane
will be in Lian Yu in 26 minutes.
Good. Keep tracking it.
That's a commercial airliner, Fyers.
-It's not like it can land here.
- It won't be landing anywhere, Mr. Queen.
I'm going to destroy it.
Arrows are black, not green.
Copycat archer again.
Psychopaths are color-coding themselves.
That's helpful.
We haven't seen the copycat
in quite a while.
Last time he took hostages
to draw out the vigilante.
This time,
he massacres a bunch of lab nerds?
Want a press lockdown.
Nobody hears about the other archer.
Get a list of all Unidac employees
and what they're working on.
It was a tight group.
Anyone who knows anything
about the project is dead.
The copycat fried their computers
and burned their research.
Ah. Whatever's going on here, someone
doesn't want anyone to know about it.
Where did you even get that camera?
Come to think of it,
where did you get this car?
I borrowed it, illegally.
When I imagined being in a car with you,
this isn't exactly what I had in mind.
You said you'd help me find the vigilante.
I know, but it's been two weeks.
The closest we've come
is snapping photos of the cop...
...who hates the Hood
just as much as you worship him.
- I don't worship him. I just need to find him.
- You don't need to find him to be somebody.
Besides, it's not like
you're gonna meet him any time soon.
Seems like the cops don't have a clue.
We don't know what they know.
- Okay, I officially do not like that look.
- You still work at CNRI, right?
Hey, Mom.
Walter's upstairs resting.
I think he's doing well, don't you?
- Who took him?
- Well, we don't know yet.
I'm gonna make sure the resources
of Queen Consolidated are behind it.
That's the answer
that you gave to reporters yesterday.
Tell me the truth.
- I don't know what you mean.
- I think you do.
When I showed you dad's notebook...
...you seemed to know something.
Something about our family being in danger.
Are you suggesting that I knew
something about my husband's kidnapping?
I'm suggesting you were scared.
That maybe you didn't mean
for any of this to happen.
It was harder than you thought, now you're
barely keeping your head above water.
Please, Mom.
Let me help you before you drown.
You need to stop asking these things.
Do you understand? I need you to stop.
I can't.
I need to know.
- Is that a power outage?
- I don't know.
Oliver. Oliver.
Mom.
Oliver.
- Are you okay?
- Oliver?
What...? We...
- Oh, we've gotta get out of here.
- Moira Queen...
...you have failed this city.
This doesn't make any sense.
Why do you want to blow up a plane?
When the New York Stock
Exchange reopened after 9/11
...the Dow Jones dropped
nearly 685 points.
Imagine what would happen to China,
the world's second largest economy...
...if all air travel in and out of China
were to be grounded indefinitely.
You want to destabilize China's economy?
It's not what I want, but rather my employer.
We have enough missiles to shoot down
any aircraft approaching the mainland.
And that will decimate China's economy.
Especially...
...once a rogue element in China's
own military claims responsibility.
You see, inconvenient
though you occasionally were...
...you're always worth more to me alive
than dead.
Then you should have killed me,
because I won't do it.
Really?
Shade. Shade.
I said I need you alive,
but I can kill everyone you care about.
Help you with something?
Yes, urn, I'm from CNRI and we're investigating
claims of racial bias in SCPD arrests.
So I'm gonna need a copy of each file
from every arrest...
...in Starling City
January, 2011 to present.
-It's almost 9 at night.
- Tell that to Judge Crow.
He's the one who signed the court order.
Wait here.
- I don't know, it seems like a leap.
- What you do when you got nothing...
...because all I know is the copycat,
he torched every record down at Unidac.
And all we got are phone records
and they show that this Markov guy...
...made calls to an unclaimed line
at Merlyn Global.
A couple of calls? Did I say "reach"?
I misspoke. I meant "leap."
Get someone down here from Merlyn
Global to answer questions under oath.
- Did you find anything?
- Lots.
- Anything helpful?
- No, still looking.
What about you?
You learn anything from the cops?
- As a matter of fact.
- I like the sound of that.
- You know that copycat archer?
- Yeah.
Turns out he's connected
to Merlyn Global somehow.
Or at least his victims are.
We're looking for the Hood,
not some crazy wannabe.
Well, the guy with the black arrows seems
to hate the guy with the green arrows, so...
So what, we just show up at Merlyn Global
and hope the Hood shows up too?
Last I checked,
you don't have any better ideas.
Please.
Do not hurt my son.
Tell me what
the Undertaking is and I won't have to.
- No!
- Tell me!
Please, leave my son alone.
- What is Malcolm Merlyn planning?
- I can't tell you.
He'll kill me, he'll kill my family.
You should be
more worried about what I'll do.
No! Malcolm is planning to level the Glades.
He said so he could rebuild it but...
- How?
- There's a device.
- What device?
- He says that it can cause an earthquake.
- How is this possible?
- I don't know.
It was invented by Unidac Industries.
Malcolm used
my company's applied sciences...
...to turn it into a weapon.
Why would you get involved
in something like this?
My husband...
He got involved without my knowing.
He was just trying to do some good.
He was lost. He...
His decisions left me vulnerable to Malcolm
and I had no choice.
I had to protect my family and my children.
This device, where is it?
- I don't know.
- If you don't tell me, I can't stop Merlyn.
Oh, you can't stop him.
It's too late.
No, no, no, I told you everything!
- Oliver. No. Oh, sweet--
- Don't.
Please, I know what you must be thinking,
sweetheart...
...but I never intended any of this to happen.
You know I would never willingly be a part
of anything like this.
I don't know anything anymore.
Oh, my God. You said you were
gonna pull your punches.
- I did.
- Let me get you an icepack for everything.
I'm fine.
I need you to dig up everything you can
on Unidac Industries.
Well, we know Queen Consolidated
acquired them seven months ago.
That's when we met.
I need information about what I don't know.
Unidac is a small research
and development technology company...
...that specializes in seismic infringement.
Merlyn plans on leveling the Glades with a
device that triggers a manmade earthquake.
You're kidding.
What else does it say?
More information on the stock auction...
...and you know the latest,
what the media's calling--
- The Unidac massacre.
- There's no way this timing is a coincidence.
Oliver, there's a website claiming
the police suspect a copycat archer.
- What?
- So the other archer works for Merlyn?
He's tying up loose ends.
Erasing all evidence this device exists so
no one can trace the devastation to him.
- You'll have a conversation with Merlyn.
- Even if I take out Merlyn...
...the other archer is there.
He can set off the device. We need to find it.
Then Merlyn can get his.
Maybe there's another way
to get Merlyn to tell us.
What do you have in mind?
As I keep proving, people keep secrets...
...computers don't.
Felicity, are you hacking
into the Merlyn Global mainframe?
Hacking is such an ugly word. No. I'm...
Yeah, totally hacking
into the Merlyn Global mainframe.
Stop! I'll do it.
I knew your good judgment
could be counted on.
Come along now.
We need to get you back into uniform.
-It's Fyers. It's happening.
- Understood.
That was Fyers.
Everything is proceeding to your plan.
It truly is very kind of you
to come all the way out here.
Walter?
Who are you speaking to?
- Moira. How are you?
- Well. Thank you.
- Actually, you look a little bit out of sorts.
- Oh, no, no, I'm fine.
Malcolm stopped by
to check up on his nemesis.
On the racquetball court.
Didn't get a chance to talk to Walter
at the hospital.
Like everyone,
I'm glad he's back where he belongs.
With his family.
Yes.
I'll let you get some rest.
- Thanks again.
- Yeah.
Uh, I'll Walk you Out.
Your assassin wasn't too subtle
in eliminating those people at Unidac.
Police are focused on the copycat archer
instead of the Undertaking.
As for our collateral damage,
had to limit our exposure.
I see. And does paying Walter a visit
just now fall under the same category?
You held him for nearly six months.
- Surely you had him questioned.
- He was.
I assume if Walter knew something you'd
rather he didn't, agreement be damned...
...I would be a widow again. Am I wrong?
Rarely.
Well, we discovered a few phone calls...
...between one of the Unidac victims
and someone at the Merlyn Global group.
Which is why I asked for someone at your
company to help me with my investigation.
But naturally, they send down the one guy...
...that's been working there 3O seconds
and knows nothing.
Detective Lance, if someone from Merlyn
Global is involved with those deaths...
-...I want them found as much as you do.
- Yeah.
Give me more to go on than phone calls
and I will help you in any way that I can.
Thank you.
Hey-
- What are you doing here?
- Helping your father with an investigation.
Uh...
- Call me if you need anything else.
- Thank you.
One second, sweetie.
Okay, someone at Merlyn Global
could be connected to the copycat archer.
Any chance you can have a little snoop
around their computer systems?
- We'll need a warrant.
- We'll need a judge who owes me a favor.
Hey-
You never did tell me
what had you and Merlyn on the outs.
- No, I didn't.
- You don't have to tell me.
Oliver.
- Come on.
- I know.
I know. Say it.
You think I'm crazy.
I mean, Oliver, he cheated on me,
he broke my heart, he led Sara to her death...
...and you would probably rather drink acid
than see me with him again.
Dad, I am sure you're disappointed in me.
Since Queen's been back, he's different.
I'll deny ever having said that.
Let's eat.
- Ah.
- Anything?
For the record, I will pump my fist
in the air and scream "yes" if I get in.
- You can say this isn't working.
- This isn't working.
There has to be some other way.
Unless I can waltz up to Merlyn's mainframe
and plug in my tablet directly...
-...there's no way of getting that location.
- Then we waltz.
Excuse me?
You need direct access to the mainframe,
so we get you direct access...
-...and figure out where the device is kept.
- Oliver...
...I did mention that the mainframe
is located...
...inside Merlyn Global Group's
main headquarters, on the 25th floor?
- Only accessible via a restricted elevator.
- I know.
We're gonna have to break in.
Hi. Oliver Queen.
I have an 11:30 with Tommy Merlyn.
I have a super deluxe Big Belly Buster
for a Mr. Andrews.
I think he's in security.
- He a good tipper?
- You can go on up, Mr. Queen.
You can wait a second.
- New guy, you order food?
- Yeah, I'm addicted to Big Belly Burger.
- Never had it.
- I'll split it with you.
Keep the change.
Hold that.
- Where you heading, sweetie?
- Nineteenth floor.
Too bad, I'm going to 13th. Damn it!
Mr. Andrews got his lunch?
One Belly Buster with benzodiazepine.
Hold the mayo.
Sleep tight.
Mainframe's on 25, guys.
This is as close as I can get you.
- Don't look down.
- Too late.
I should mention I'm afraid of heights,
which I just learned.
- Felicity. Hold on to me tight.
- Huh?
I imagined you saying that
under different circumstances.
Very platonic circumstances.
- Ready?
- Uh-huh.
Come on.
- You all right?
- I'm fine.
Yeah, this is just my about-to-hack face.
I always...
...oh, look like this right before I,
you know, hack.
Security patrol's on a 10-minute cycle.
I'll have my meeting with Tommy
and be back in nine.
Okay.
Dig, YOU got eyes on her?
Five by five.
Okay.
Sure beats the back of a bar.
I saw your name in my schedule.
I thought it must be a typo.
Why so serious?
Did someone decide that they didn't
want you putting an arrow in them today?
- I thought it was past time we talked.
- About what?
Me leaving the club, you being
a serial killer? We're not lacking for topics.
Let's start with Laurel,
since you're still in love with her.
So are you.
I can't be with her, Tommy.
- You know why I can't.
- So what?
- I'm her consolation prize? I'll pass.
- She's not anyone's property.
Laurel makes her own decisions...
...and she chose you.
Until you couldn't handle it.
Lord knows I am guilty
of a lot of things between us...
...but not you and her.
That's all I came to say.
What exactly do you do here?
I work closely with my father.
- Guys, you got trouble.
- What?
Felicity's about to have some company.
- I'm not there yet on the download.
- Hold tight. I am on my way.
Oliver.
- Mr. Merlyn.
- I must say, I'm surprised to see you here.
Tommy and I just had
a little unfinished business.
Ah. Things have been challenging,
but I trust you're working things out.
- Felicity.
- A few more seconds.
Yes. I'm sorry, I have to go.
There are investors waiting for me
at my club.
I'm heading out to a meeting myself.
I'll walk you down to the lobby.
She's gonna get made, Oliver.
Oliver, did you hear me?
- Felicity.
- What? Just a few more seconds.
- Come on, come on.
- You don't have a few more seconds.
Yes. Wow, I really do do that.
- Oh.
- Oliver, she's in trouble. Where are you?
This is a restricted area.
Let's see some ID.
ID? Uh...
- Tell your mother I said hello.
- I will.
- Got held up. Heading back upstairs.
- Ollie?
- Thea? What are you doing here?
-I, uh, just saw Tommy.
Yeah, me too. I'm gonna run back up.
I don't wanna be late.
Oh, I thought you just came down.
There you are. Thanks a lot, man,
this one snuck past security.
One of Merlyn junior's bimbos.
Pissed he never called her back.
- Copy that. I read the tabloids.
- Yeah. Thanks again.
Let's go, Barbie.
Your new last name ain't gonna be Merlyn.
But I love him. He's my man.
Ha, ha.
You're my knight in shining armor.
Is that your friend Roy?
- No. Uh...
- No?
Yeah, he gave me a ride.
Thea, what are you really doing here?
The truth, please.
- The truth? Uh...
- Mm-hm.
- We're trying to find the vigilante.
- What?
Roy's been kind of obsessed with him
since he saved his life at the subway.
I overheard Detective Lance saying
the other archer...
...was connected to Merlyn Global, some--
Hey.
Roy. We haven't met.
I'm Thea's disapproving older brother.
Yeah, I know. Good to meet you.
Don't mess around with the Hood.
He's a psychopath. He's dangerous.
Anyone who gets near him winds up dead.
That will not be my sister, do you hear me?
Okay.
Take her home now.
What are you doing?
Vigilante's not fond of guys who sell Vertigo.
I know a guy who claims
he has a stash to sell.
Maybe we could stake him out,
hope the Hood shows up for him.
- Did you not hear what my brother said?
- What does your brother know?
Uh, for one thing,
the vigilante once saved his life...
...so if he's telling us to keep away
that should say something.
No offense, but your brother's a wimp.
- Don't say that.
- Why not? It's true.
My brother survived five years alone
on an island.
- Five years I thought I had lost him.
- Yeah? Well, I lost someone too.
- And they aren't coming back.
- Who?
It doesn't matter.
That is why I need to find him.
So he can teach me to be like him.
I'm not losing anyone else ever again.
I can't do this, Roy.
If you don't give this up,
you're gonna lose me.
Better now than later.
Oh, good. I was just coming to check on you
to see if maybe you'd like some tea or...
What is this?
Walter...
...please.
Divorce is an extreme reaction.
Well, considering the circumstances,
I find it somewhat reserved.
You think I believe that my abduction
on the night you told me...
...that I was getting too close
to your conspiracy was a coincidence?
No, you were in danger.
This arrangement, it saved your life.
Well, that's ironic.
Because it feels like you've destroyed it.
- Walter.
- You know...
...I read about people in forced captivity.
Some of them said it was a simple thought
that got them through the isolation and fear.
Returning to their loved ones.
So I don't know really why I'm still alive,
Moira, because I didn't have that.
Walter, please--
What do you think you can say to me
to convince me that everything I knew...
...my whole life, hasn't just evaporated?
Where are you going?
Come here.
Detective?
What did you find?
Merlyn Global's cyber security
is off the charts.
Firewalls, NSA-grade, lPSec protocols.
What's that, tech speak for,
"I struck out, boss"?
Yeah, but I wasn't the only one.
Somebody else tried hacking
into Merlyn Global systems.
Same pathways I used, same result.
You're saying someone was looking
for Merlyn's connection to Unidac?
Someone good. Knew how to
reverse engineer her footprints.
- I almost didn't catch her.
- Her?
Yeah. She works at Queen Consolidated.
Name's Felicity Smoak.
Who the hell is Felicity Smoak?
In addition to the download...
...I also took the liberty of uploading
a Trojan to Merlyn's system.
- Figured it might come in handy.
- That's smart.
If Merlyn thinks he's been compromised,
it'll help if we know.
- Can you locate the seismic device?
- I'm working on it.
But there's at least a teraflop
of data to go through.
You all right?
My father, he told me
that he failed the city.
Asked me to right his wrongs,
but I never knew what he meant until now.
It's the Undertaking.
I promised myself that when I crossed
all these names off the list, I'd be done...
...but taking down these people,
it doesn't honor him.
I was just treating the symptoms
while the disease festered.
I stop the Undertaking...
...I wipe out the disease.
What are you saying, Oliver?
You would hang up the Hood?
Merlyn's plan is what I returned
from the island to stop.
- Where are you going?
- Out.
Hi. Can we talk?
What do you wanna talk about?
Wow, I thought this was gonna
be easier to say.
But now I'm standing here...
-...looking at you and it's--
- Just say what you have to say and go.
Ever since I've been back,
we've been doing this dance.
We come together, and then I pull away.
Something pulls me away.
But I think, finally...
...that something might be over.
- What are you trying to say?
- That you know me better than anyone.
And that you are more important to me
than anyone.
I just hope I didn't wait too long to say it.
You didn't wait too long.
You're right on time.
- What is it?
- Felicity found the Markov device.
Merlyn's keeping it at a warehouse
his company owns in the Glades.
Good. Coordinate an attack.
You take the device, I'll take Merlyn.
- Got a location?
-Yeah.
According to Felicity's Trojan, Merlyn's
logged on to his computer from his office.
I'm on my way.
The uniform suits you, Yao Fei.
Any time you're ready.
To the people of China
and citizens of the world...
...I make this statement voluntarily,
taking responsibility for the shooting...
...of Ferris Air flight 637...
...to protest the People's
Republic of China's treatment of me...
...for betraying and abandoning me
to the island of Lian Yu.
Consider this my righteous delivery
of powerful vengeance.
Thank you.
- No!
- Pa!
Pa!
Sir, the plane is within range.
Very well. I'll be in touch.
Can I help you?
No.
I wasn't talking to you.
Malcolm Merlyn...
...you have failed this city.
- And how have I done that?
- The Undertaking. It ends now.
Oliver, the device...
...it's gone.
Where's the device?
Safe. I don't know how you got that Trojan
onto my system...
...but it prompted me
to take precautions.
There is nothing you can do to stop
what is about to happen.
And you shouldn't.
This city needs what is about to happen
in order to survive.
The people who are destroying it from
the inside need to be erased from the map.
Fine. Let's start with you.
Ironic, isn't it?
Last Christmas, I almost killed you.
A few months ago, you saved my life.
And now you're here trying to kill me.
- You should make up your mind.
- Done.
Oh, no.