You were asleep.
I was dreaming.
Ibn Sirin once wrote
there are three types of dreams.
There are ones about truth...
...there are ones about desire...
...and there are ones about temptation.
What did you dream of?
Rebirth.
As Ra's al Ghul.
There is no greater burden
than the one you are about to take on.
The annihilation of one's home.
It is necessary to complete my ascension.
I will be there to steady your hand
when the time comes.
I appreciate your assistance.
Soon...
...you will wear this...
...and you will command a multitude...
...and I shall call you Ra's.
[THUDDING]
Something's wrong.
[ALL GASPING AND COUGHING]
Not that I'm complaining,
but shouldn't we be dead by now?
Oliver tried to kill us.
Ra's tried.
Oliver was forced to let him appear
to be successful.
Now we're back to trust Oliver,
and while we're at it trust you too?
Yeah. Last time I checked, you tried
to make a deal with Ra's to save yourself.
In order for our plan to work,
Ra's' trust in Oliver had to be complete.
And after that plane fiasco, it wasn't.
Oliver needed to demonstrate...
...one more time his loyalty to Ra's.
Which I guess brings us back to...
...why aren't we dead?
Not that I'm complaining.
Oliver...
...was vaccinated against
the Alpha/Omega virus...
...five years ago.
An associate was able to draw a version
of the vaccine from his blood.
A synthetic skin graft.
Upon our incarceration...
...I was able to vaccinate...
...each one of you cutaneously.
I saved your lives.
I believe the words you're searching for
are "thank" and "you."
[FELICITY CLEARS THROAT]
Okay. Assuming this is all some part
of a brilliant double-double cross...
...or triple cross, I'm losing count...
...your master plan still has one major flaw,
since we're still chained in a dungeon.
Patience, Miss Smoak.
All we have to do is wait.
Wait for what?
[THUNDER CRASHING]
The thunder.
Keep walking.
It's time.
All right.
You guys have a hot tub?
Nice.
Hey, guys.
Wow. I mean, this is, like...
...a real dungeon.
-Barry.
-Thank you, Felicity.
You just outed my secret identity
to a super-villain.
No offense.
None taken.
Now get us out of here.
All right. Uh, stand back.
[GLASS SHATTERS]
DIGGLE:
Excellent.
How many assassins do you figure?
Uh, none. They're all taking
a little nappy-time.
FELICITY:
Thank you.
Not to be greedy,
but we could really use your help...
...on this Starling City super-virus thing.
And you know I would...
...but I am overdue for a very pointed
conversation with Harrison Wells.
I'm sure Oliver's got this.
I wouldn't count on it.
Oliver hasn't been very forthcoming
with his plans lately.
Well, I don't know what's been going on
with him lately...
...apart from a recent wardrobe change...
...but one thing that hasn't changed...
...is he needs you guys.
Even if he doesn't think so.
Good luck.
I'll never get used to that.
Well, there goes our ride home.
Unh. John?
The plane we came in is still secure,
but we need to get to it quickly.
Come on.
Tatsu.
Let's go, we're leaving.
I left a life of solitude
because Oliver asked it of me.
It's time to return to it.
I'm wired.
In direct communication
with my men outside.
I'm gonna count to five.
One.
[GRUNTING]
[GUNFIRE]
[ALARM WAILING]
-What's happening?
-Two engines are down.
We're trying to compensate...
-...but they've been tampered with.
-Sabotage.
You!
This is all your doing.
OLIVER:
Don't.
Nyssa had nothing to do with this.
You were delivered by the prophecy.
You wed my daughter.
Your name is Al Sah-him
and you are Warith Al Ghul.
My name...
...is Oliver Queen.
Oliver Queen is dead.
And soon you will be too.
[GRUNTING]
I handed you my crusade...
...my holy mission.
I already have one.
[GRUNTING]
[ALARM WAILING]
Survive this...
...and I will come for you again and again...
...until your end of days.
But first...
...your city will perish.
It's our only parachute.
[GRUNTING]
Stay strapped in and do exactly as I say.
All right, we've lost hydraulics.
-Is there a red lever by your right leg?
NYSSA: Yes.
Okay, on my go.
You pull it up and you turn it clockwise.
Push it back down.
-You understand?
-Yes.
Three, two, one.
Now!
Back down.
Nyssa, this is gonna hurt.
[REPORTER SPEAKING CHINESE ON TV]
[IN CHINESE]
[IN JAPANESE]
Oh, no. I couldn't.
He loved you.
You were his friend.
Excuse me.
My people will be looking for me.
It's just a matter of time till they find me.
-Do it.
-Do you remember Amanda Waller?
Hm?
She's the reason that I'm in Hong Kong.
She thought I had a special talent.
She taught me things.
Let me show you.
We don't have much time.
For what? I thought you said
Oliver had a plan.
Yeah, and in the event that it doesn't work,
he has a backup.
Us.
John, let's determine the status
of our arsenal.
Laurel, go to your father.
Start mobilizing the police.
Mr. Palmer, I need you to find something
that will neutralize an airborne contagion.
Miss Smoak, let's find out where
our League of Assassin friends might be.
I'm sorry. Did I mumble?
We follow his lead.
For now.
[ALARM BEEPING]
Guys? I set up a proximity alarm to detect
any unauthorized entry to this level.
It's going off like crazy.
Nyssa.
Son of a bitch!
It's okay. It's all right.
Uh, maybe we should
give these guys the room.
Nyssa looks happy.
Are you two on your honeymoon?
What the hell's going on, Oliver?
Start talking.
The reason that I've kept Malcolm close
for the past several months...
...is because he had critical intel
on our enemy.
He knows Ra's. He knows the League.
And he knew that if I was appointed
his successor...
...that meant Starling City
was marked for death.
The only way that we were gonna defeat
the League was from the inside.
I had to get close enough to Ra's to find out
how he was gonna destroy the city...
...and stop him.
You trusted Malcolm Merlyn
more than the two people closest to you.
John, it wasn't about trust.
It was about making sure
that you and you were safe.
-I had to keep the circle as small as possible.
-How did you expect to repair this...
-...once you got back?
-I didn't.
I flew with Ra's and the virus to Starling...
...and I sabotaged the plane.
The plan...
...was to kill Ra's and destroy the virus.
It didn't work.
How did you expect
to survive the plane crash?
You didn't.
You never expected
to have this conversation.
You were planning on dying.
So that was your big plan?
Sacrificing yourself to take out Ra's.
It was the only way.
At least now that it didn't work,
I get a chance...
...to tell both of you how sorry I am.
Sorry won't cut it, Oliver.
Not this time.
But we have bigger problems...
...than hurt feelings...
...and broken trust.
Laurel needs to contact her father.
Ray needs to find a way
to counteract the virus.
I'm sure Malcolm told you.
We don't have a lot of time.
Oliver.
What have you done?
He failed this city...
...and I'm giving him the justice he deserves.
This isn't justice.
It's...
...wrong.
He's still alive.
Just passed out from the pain.
OLIVER:
What'd you find?
My father isn't using any of the League's
ordinary redoubts in the city.
If Ra's is here with the virus,
why hasn't he used it yet?
-Where are we?
-Nowhere.
Ra's is old school, every way I have
of finding him is new school.
Maybe we need to change
the way we're looking for him.
If you're trying to find a sub
that's gone dark...
...you look for what's out of the ordinary
in the water.
We look for what's unusual
and maybe that points us...
...to how or where Ra's plans
to release the virus.
Traffic lights were down for 20 minutes
at Adams and O'Neil.
Computers at Starling Bank are offline.
The top floor of the Essex Hotel's closed.
There's an electrical spike
at 52nd and Robson...
Wait, go back.
The top floor of the Essex is closed?
My father doesn't frequent hotels.
According to e-mails, the floor
was shut down for a Damien Darhk.
A name like that has to be an alias.
Damien Darhk is in Starling City.
My father's most bitter enemy.
That's why Ra's hasn't released the virus.
He wants to use it to kill Damien Darhk.
This was never just about my ascension.
Ra's wants to take out his nemesis.
You weren't the only one
with a hidden agenda.
[SIGHS]
This can work for us.
Ra's wants Damien.
So we give him Damien.
We trade Damien for the virus?
That is remarkably ruthless
and cold-blooded.
I approve.
I count two on the roof.
One on the penthouse floor.
I got two guarding the elevators.
Another three going in and out
of the service entrance.
[THUD]
And a patrol in the stairwell.
[ARROW WHOOSHES]
Same for the northwest corridor.
Keep Darhk's men from joining the party.
Getting into position.
[COMM BEEPS]
[GRUNTING]
Damien Darhk.
You know, the hotel's going to bill me
for that window.
Turn around.
This is bold.
Even for Ra's.
-Ra's al Ghul wants you dead.
-Mm.
He's planning a bio-weapon
to take you out.
Ah. That's a considerable amount
of work to go to.
Ra's certainly must want Mr. Darhk
off the board.
You seem surprised.
Mr. Darhk left Starling
the moment he learned of Ra's' intention.
It's amusing.
The Demon's Head thinks he can catch
my employer unawares.
[CELL PHONE BUZZING]
It's just my phone.
[MAN GRUNTING]
RA'S AL GHUL [OVER PHONE]:
Hello, Al Sah-him.
Apparently, both our plans
did not go as we'd hoped.
I'm gonna find you.
It was a bold gambit,
hoping to leverage Mr. Darhk.
One which would have
done you no good.
I set in motion the death of your city
10 minutes ago.
The Alpha/Omega shall be disseminated
by means of four vessels.
Four instruments of death.
And I doubt that you and your friends
will have time to stop all of them.
Unlike you, Oliver Queen...
...I am a man of my word.
And I swore that you would see
your city perish.
I told you I needed the DD-5s
for the Andreyko case...
...on my desk. And unless I recently
went blind, they're not here.
Now what...?
I gotta put you on hold for a second.
It won't be long.
I thought you and I agreed
to give ourselves some space.
-Not when the city is in danger.
-Heh. I don't have time for this.
Wait, do you remember that chemical spill
in Hong Kong five years ago?
It turns out it was a biological attack
and that bio-weapon...
Let me guess, this is coming from
your buddy Queen? Huh?
The city's under attack. Must be May.
-What do you...?
-You still keep it in the middle drawer?
-What?
-The bottle.
I'm gonna bet that it's Scotch.
It's not what you think it is.
Don't.
If you wanna drink, then drink.
But don't just stand there and lie to me
right to my face.
Doesn't feel good, does it?
It makes you thirsty.
I love you.
No matter what happens between us,
that will never change.
You can hate me for lying. You can blame
Oliver for Sara. You can even blame me.
But falling off the wagon, that's on you.
I got it under control.
Two drinks a day, that's it.
We're alcoholics, Dad, drunks.
There's no such thing as two drinks a day.
And now you have a choice.
You can keep drinking,
and keep being angry at me and Oliver...
...or the rest of the world if you want.
Or you can make
both of your daughters proud...
...and throw away the bottle
and help save this city.
[DOOR OPENS THEN CLOSES]
John, Malcolm and Nyssa
are on their way back.
-What happened with Darhk?
-He was gone.
The man that I found was a cut out.
Ra's plans to release the virus
at four points in the city.
I worked out a system that can neutralize
the virus if we can get our hands on it.
We need four of them and a way to spread
the inoculant if this gets out of control.
I scrubbed through the information
Malcolm gave us on the Hong Kong attack.
The virus gave off a low-level emission
from its RNA, almost like radiation.
If you hack the satellite,
you could tune the band to search for it.
Which you've been doing
the last five minutes.
We need probable locations where he would
release the virus as soon as you get them.
FELICITY:
Mm-hm.
TATSU:
Maseo?
Where are you going?
I don't know.
All I know...
...is I wasn't strong enough...
...to save my son.
Or to do what Oliver did.
What Oliver did was horrible.
He allowed himself to become a monster.
No more of a monster than I am.
I am...
...without a soul, Tatsu.
Only if you abandon your wife...
...when she needs you the most.
Every time...
...I look in your eyes...
...I see my son's.
I see my failure.
I love you.
I'm not worthy of that love.
Where's he going?
Somewhere we cannot follow.
I know I said I would never, ever
bring you coffee again...
...but the city facing a bio-weapon attack
seemed like a valid exception.
So your plan to take out Ra's by dying...
...we should talk about that.
Every night since the mountain...
...I've had the same dream.
You are...
...pleading with me not to go face Ra's,
and I listen to you.
Sometimes, the dream still ends badly.
I end up with this sword in my chest.
But...
...most of the time we escape.
And we're just driving.
And all this seems...
It seems so far away, because it's just...
It's the two of us.
I know you think that's not possible.
That you dead and Ra's dead
is the only realistic best-case scenario.
Felicity...
...I can't defeat Ra's al Ghul.
Oliver Queen can't.
The Arrow can't.
Both those men tried
and both those men failed.
Do you remember what you said to me
during our night in Nanda Parbat?
You're no longer either of those men.
You've become...
...someone else.
Become something else.
This...
...is different now.
Because despite your best efforts,
you've allowed yourself to feel something.
I know you think
that that's a weakness, it's not.
It's your key...
...to beating Ra's.
Don't fight to die.
Fight to live.
[CELL PHONE CHIMING]
Satellite trace is back.
I got four locations.
Okay, let's go.
Felicity?
Thank you.
All right, yeah, got them.
[CLEARS THROAT]
I don't know, we'll talk about that later.
I need all units, I need ESU, all squad cars
converging on these four locations.
We got a potential bio-weapons attack.
I'm on site.
On site.
I'm on site, but I have no idea
what I should be looking for out here.
See anyone in a League of Assassins outfit?
That'd be a dead giveaway.
MAN:
I have no weapons.
And I have no virus.
Ra's al Ghul awaits you
on the Starling City Dam.
He wishes to be in your presence
as your city dies.
And what makes him think that I won't
just stay focused on saving my city?
MAN: Because he knows of your deluded belief
that you can defeat him in battle.
And you know...
...that as long as the Demon's Head lives...
...he will continue to threaten your home.
-I got a runner carrying a briefcase.
FELICITY:The bio-weapon's in the briefcase.
I'm scrubbing footage from surveillance
cameras at the remaining three locations.
[HORNS HONKING AND TIRES SCREECHING]
[DIGGLE GRUNTS]
MAN:
You okay?
[DIGGLE GRUNTING]
Don't move.
-Nice threads.
-Thanks.
DIGGLE:
Felicity, the briefcase is empty.
It's empty.
Where's the virus?
He is the weapon.
Ra's is using his own men
to disperse the virus.
And we will not be stopped.
[GRUNTS]
For the will of Ra's al Ghul...
...is our own.
No, no, no!
RA'S AL GHUL:
I knew you couldn't resist.
The man who survives the sword
of Ra's al Ghul...
...shall become Ra's al Ghul.
So you brought me here to kill you?
Either way, I am victorious.
You either ascend to Ra's
as I have designed...
...or you will die.
And the last thing you will ever see...
...is your beloved city...
...succumbing to disease and death.
Get back! Go, go, go!
Get back, go!
Go, run!
[PEOPLE CHATTERING]
Go, go, go!
Get back, go, go!
[MAN COUGHING]
Everybody get back!
-We gotta get out of here.
SPEEDY: Malcolm inoculated me. Oh, my God.
Starling City appears to be in the throes
of a biological attack.
Outbreak at Nelson Plaza. It's bad.
The virus spreads when infected blood
is exposed to open air.
Even if we find Ra's' men, how do we
stop them from spreading the virus?
Temporary solution. Get them off the streets,
in a secure place, don't let them cut themselves.
Wait, you're not inoculated.
This is my father's doing.
I will see it undone.
You choose a sword
that has already defeated you in battle.
[GRUNTING]
Miss Smoak,
I've taken out one of Ra's' men.
Don't take chances.
Put that body someplace airtight.
And try not to kill anyone else while you're at it.
The virus is spreading.
Can you replicate the inoculant?
That's the easy part. The hard part
is disseminating it over a three-block radius.
Your nanotech.
Can you make them airborne?
That is what I'm trying to do.
[GRUNTING]
I have been a most excellent trainer.
We need to get this guy somewhere
he can't infect anyone.
LANCE:
What the hell's going on here?
We're in the middle of a crisis.
I don't have time for this.
Two suspects on the dam.
Don't know why they're fighting.
Chief says they're responsible
for what's happening.
He ordered me to take them out
as soon as I have a shot.
[GRUNTING]
RA'S AL GHUL:
Something has changed within you, boy.
Your will to live burns brighter,
and yet you rejected my offer of eternal life.
What you were offering wasn't living.
[GRUNTING]
Power serves you no interest.
You'd rather love.
A man who condemns his daughter
to death...
...wouldn't understand.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
-Detective? I mean, captain.
LANCE: We got a problem.
-You're gonna have to be more specific.
-Your boy's at Starling City Dam.
I got officers not listening to me
getting ready to shoot him.
Despite what I think about your guy...
...I don't want him killed
while he's trying to save this city.
Unless you order up a miracle pretty quick,
that's exactly what's gonna happen.
DIGGLE [OVER PHONE]:Got number four.
-Hold on a second, we have a new problem.
You have to get to Starling City Dam.
You have to fly.
I'm uploading the operating code
to the nanotech.
I'm still rewriting on the fly.
I can't leave this station.
-Why?
-Oliver's in trouble, he needs help.
If I can't get the nanotech
to disperse the inoculant...
-...thousands of people in this city will die.
-What? No, Ray, Oliver.
It's one life against the city's.
What would Oliver do?
RA'S AL GHUL:
Unlike you...
...thousands of honorable men
will mourn my death when I leave this Earth.
No.
[GRUNTING]
They will kneel...
...before the next Ra's Al Ghul.
[IN ARABIC]
I knew I chose well with you, boy.
[GUNSHOTS]
[OLIVER GASPS]
If I could figure out how to get this thing off,
I would be kissing you right now.
[CHUCKLES]
The casualty count would have been
much higher if not for an airborne inoculant...
...that rumors credit Palmer Technologies
with developing.
You killed my father.
I had to.
I wanted to be the one.
You're lucky you're still alive.
You wouldn't be had you not been wearing
League armor.
I like to think I had something
to do with that.
When I started this...
...I wanted to keep you
as far away from it as possible.
Because that has always been
my instinct...
...to go it alone.
But the truth is that we won tonight
because I wasn't alone.
I thought that this crusade
would only end with my death.
But even if I had died tonight,
it would live on because of you.
And you.
-Oh. And you.
LAUREL: It's true.
-This city isn't lacking masks.
-Heroes.
Which is why I no longer need to be one.
-What are you saying?
-Ra's took the Arrow identity from me.
I couldn't...
...be that person even if I wanted to be.
And I don't want to be.
I told you that...
...I couldn't be the Arrow and be with you.
I want to be with you.
You told me that I have become someone else,
and I would like to...
...maybe discover a little more
about that person.
If you'll come with me.
With you where?
Um...
Someplace far away from here.
Even without me...
...Starling still has heroes
to watch over it.
John?
I'll talk to him.
Wow.
Yeah. That's the word I've been saying
over and over in my head.
So does that mean
I'm gonna have to find a new...
...vice president?
I think so.
I hope that you find someone
who makes you happy, Ray.
You deserve that.
-John?
-I'm happy for you, Oliver.
Despite our issues...
...you deserve to be happy.
You and Felicity.
And you're right, the city's in good hands.
Including yours.
-I'm no superhero.
-You're a hero.
For three years, you've been a rock.
The city's rock, my rock.
For three years,
you have been the person I can count on.
I'm still counting on you.
I don't know if I can get past
what happened between the two of us.
I'm not asking you to.
I'll think on it.
Okay.
[ELEVATOR BELL DINGS
THEN DOORS OPEN]
OLIVER:
John.
Ahem. If you're gonna keep going...
...you may wanna find a way to conceal
your identity when you're out there.
I'll think on that too.
-You be well, Oliver.
-You too.
OLIVER:
Where will you go?
TATSU:
Kumamoto.
There's a monastery there,
near my childhood home.
I had always hoped to show it to Akio
when we returned to Japan as a family.
I'm so very sorry, Tatsu.
And where will you go?
Back to Starling City?
I tortured Shrieve...
...for hours.
I don't want that darkness
around my mother or my sister.
What of your father?
You told me about his message.
His hope that you would save your city.
I'm not the man my father thinks I am.
Even if I was...
...I should be alone.
I need to be alone.
Be well, Tatsu.
He's upstairs...
...packing.
I'll be leaving Starling as well.
Try to imagine my profound
disappointment.
Thea, I love you.
I know my actions
always haven't shown that.
But I am your father...
...and whatever you need,
I will always be there for you.
Yeah, well, don't wait by the phone.
But a year ago...
...you told me that you could
teach me to be strong.
You've made good by that promise.
[FOOTSTEPS]
Are you sure you really want to do this?
As sure as I was the last five times
you asked me.
[SIGHS]
Be safe out there, okay?
As safe as anybody
with a mask on can be.
But actually I was thinking, um...
...maybe I'd call myself the Red Arrow.
Hm.
I think I already told everyone
to call you Speedy.
As we agreed.
We've come a long way, you and I.
I've always looked at you as a son, Oliver.
And I'm glad we got to work together.
To trust as we did.
I will never forgive you...
...for what you did to Sara.
To my sister.
Ever.
Does that mean we're enemies once more?
That depends on what you do
with your end of the bargain.
[RAY SIGHS]
RAY:
Open new file.
Atom project, update Gamma.
Had an interesting breakthrough...
...while repurposing nanotechnology
for antiviral dissemination.
With the proper modifications...
...the nanotech can be applied
to the miniaturization of key components...
...of the suit.
This will be miniaturization test number one.
Execute.
Why can't anything
ever work on the first try?
Hm?
At least admit this was your goal all along.
My only aspiration was to free myself
of your father's grasp.
A feat we both managed to achieve.
I don't see how it was possible
in your case.
When I was your father's captive
three months ago...
...he tortured me with his blade.
And you survived because my father
chose to release you.
Funny thing, prophecies.
Fate and my father have shown you mercy.
I will not.
You took Sara from me,
and I will have justice.
You are welcome to try.
Until then...
...kneel before Ra's al Ghul.
OLIVER:
My name is Oliver Queen.
After five years in hell...
...I returned home with only one goal.
To save my city.
And I did.
I became a hero who helped people.
But now it's time for me
to be someone else.
It's time for me to be something else.
So where are we going?
I'm thinking a state that can annul
a Nanda Parbat marriage.
[OLIVER CHUCKLES]
Can I say something strange?
I'm happy.