My name is Oliver Queen.
After five years
on a hellish island,
I have come home
with only one goal--
to save my city.
But to do so, I can't be
the killer I once was.
To honor my friend's memory,
I must be someone else.
I must be something else.
Previously on "Arrow"...
There's a new player
we've been tracking.
We've been calling
him...Deathstroke.
I have
a proposal for you men.
Roy was injected
with the serum.
He's alive. But we are going
to have to keep an eye on him.
Stay away from Thea.
No.
She's not safe when
she's around you.
You love her,
and that's why
you're going to do
what I'm asking.
How could you not tell me
Malcolm Merlyn was my father?!
I believed in you.
As of 30 minutes ago,
your company
belongs to me.
Slade. You're working for him.
I know Oliver Queen
is the Arrow.
I don't think
my eye holes line up properly.
Is anyone else
having this problem?
Don't be nervous.
I'm a lot nervous.
This is a big move,
even for us.
And we've cornered
the market on big moves.
Slade didn't
give us any choice.
Yeah, as far as plans go,
this is not a good one.
Felicity.
This was your plan.
I didn't think
you'd actually say yes.
We're here.
Ughhh!
Aahh! Ohh!
Hey! That man
used to work for me.
And how he works
for our enemy.
Security cameras
are down.
You all remember
the skeleton key?
Courtesy of William Tockman,
aka the Clock King.
It can open any lock.
Including this one.
This is where we met Barry.
These are plug n' play.
Fasten them to what
we talked about.
Let the C4 do the rest.
Been a while
since I've blown anything up.
Quick and clean.
I'm a bomber.
I can't believe I'm a bomber.
I wonder if I can list that
on my résume under special skills.
Freeze!
We have to go.
Thermal shows
everybody's out.
It's just a building,
Oliver.
♪ Arrow 2x19 ♪
The Man Under the Hood
Original Air Date on April 16, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Cowards.
Who else would
needlessly destroy
cutting edge, scientific
and medical technology
whose sole purpose
is to make
Starling City
a healthier
and safer place?
As CEO of Queen
Consolidated,
I have a message
to the terrorist
who committed this
unspeakable act.
You will be caught,
and punished.
For the record,
I hated her
before we found
out she was a super villain.
Ok. Slade's goal
is to create an army
of human weapons
using the Mirakuru.
To do that, he needs
an industrial centrifuge.
Which having Isabel Rochev steal
Queen Consolidated
from your family
gave him full access to.
But since Applied Sciences
went kaboom,
he can't use our technology--
well, formerly our
for his warped science experiments.
Slade has had us
on our heels for weeks.
It's about time we took
the fight to him.
All this will do
is set him back.
We have no way of knowing
where the next attack is coming from.
Look, you need
to drop this, ok?
I'm fine. Really.
How is any
of this fine?
Look, you need
to concentrate on you.
Now listen, are you going
to your meetings?
Yes. It's where
I talk about
how my father's
facing prison.
Laurel...
This will all
blow over, ok? Please.
No. It won't, Dad.
You were caught
aiding and abetting the Vigilante.
Working with him last year cost
you your detective shield.
Now, it can cost you
18 months in prison.
They want his name.
Do you know
who the Arrow is?
I don't.
I swear.
Ok, well, what about
the woman in black?
The one the Arrow
works with?
Do you know
who she is?
No.
Well, you must
have some idea.
Honey, I can't tell you
what I don't know.
Time's up.
You girls, you take
care of each other.
Do you really think he doesn't
know who the Arrow is?
It's not like
dad to lie.
Sometimes it's people closest
to us who lie to us best.
Where is Thea?
She should be here
for this, too.
I doubt she's coming.
Well, I can't lie
to either of you--
it's bad.
If Isabel Rochev is one thing,
it's thorough.
She's been laying the foundation
for this takeover for months.
But we still own a majority of stock
in the company, correct?
Yes, but Isabel has diluted
that stock to the point
where it's worthless.
On paper,
you're virtually broke.
And what's the good news?
We can protect
your assets.
We need to move
everything
into a new trust
that Isabel can't touch.
All I need is the beneficiaries
from the current trust
to approve the transfer.
The two of you and Thea.
Thea needs to sign off.
Yes. And quickly.
Thank you, Ned.
Well, now I have
to become mayor.
It seems I'll need
the income.
Losing the company
wasn't your fault.
It was mine.
I let Isabel Rochev
get the better of me.
No. You always see
the good in people,
even if they don't
deserve it.
I know that better
than most.
Isabel is
a vindictive woman.
She would have done this
with or without your trust.
How do you know?
You told me months ago
I couldn't trust her.
Your father
had a weakness
for beautiful,
strong women.
They were together?
Yes.
She was still in business school
at the time.
The pretty intern
that caught the CEO's eye.
All right.
You take this to Thea,
and you convince her,
somehow,
to help us fight back.
Hey. Will you help me up?
Yeah.
Just to my trunk.
Ok.
Ohh, look who's up.
Just in time
for all the fun.
What are you going
to do to him?
Make him scream.
Just like he made us.
Hmm?
They say living well
is best revenge? Ha.
I prefer torture.
You want first turn?
- No.
- Please.
I can help you.
No, doctor.
What was it you said
you needed for research?
An eye?
No!
Let me get you a fresh one.
You can still
stop Slade Wilson!
Anatoly. Wait.
What did you say?
I can help you
stop him.
How? That miracle drug
of yours has turned him
into monster.
I know. I can
turn him back.
Ivo, what are you saying?!
The Mirakuru.
There's a cure.
Hey.
Hey,
is Thea here?
No, I haven't
seen her.
How's your dad?
He's willing
to go to jail for the Arrow.
I know you said
you weren't worried,
but Dig and I went
to Roy's apartment.
It's empty.
Seems like he cleared out
a few days ago.
Where the hell did he go?
Roy will have to wait.
All right, we need to deal
with Slade,
figure out what his next move is.
I know Slade.
He is not going
to stop till...
Aah!
Hello, Sara.
Diggle, stay back!
Aaah!
Don't forget who taught
you how to fight, kid.
Excuse me, I'm looking
for my sister, Sara Lance.
Excuse me.
I'm Laurel Lance.
Is my sister ok?
Oh, she'll be fine.
Just a hairline fracture of her wrist.
We set it.
She's got some nasty
bruises; Looks worse than it is.
Thank you.
Nothing compared
to her previous
injuries.
Previous...Injuries?
Yes, your sister has
extensive scar tissue
over her entire body.
The last person I saw
with that much damage
was a veteran
injured in Iraq.
Has your sister
served in the military?
No.
No, she hasn't.
Sara.
Hey.
What happened to you?
Oh, I'm fine.
Ollie and I just had a little
motorcycle mishap.
It was nothing.
I already got
my discharge papers.
But your back...
Those scars,
where did you get them?
You ok?
I will be. You?
Yeah. Hi.
Hi. So tell me
what happened.
Motorcycle accident.
It was stupid.
We were making a left turn,
this car ran a red light.
Did you file
a police report?
We didn't see the point.
We're both fine.
That's--
that's what counts, right?
Right.
I should really go.
I have a deposition
in an hour.
Ok.
Thanks for
checking up on me.
Always.
I know Oliver Queen
is the Arrow.
Hey.
We missed you
yesterday.
The meeting
with Ned Foster.
Thea, I know that you're mad
at mom and me,
but we may have found a way out
of this financial mess
where we aren't
going to lose everything.
Mom and I both
signed, we just...
We need
your signature,
and hopefully we
can stop Isabel from ruining us.
After you let her
ruin us, you mean?
Yeah.
It says Thea Queen here.
Who's she?
That's you, Speedy.
No, it's not.
Robert Queen
wasn't my father.
Malcolm Merlyn was.
Thea Merlyn.
Kind of has
a nice ring to it.
Merlyn was your biological
father, but Dad raised you.
Only because
he didn't know I wasn't his.
Hey, hey!
He...He loved you.
So do I, and I am
still your brother.
No, you're not.
You're my half brother.
And you know who else
was my half brother?
Tommy.
Tommy,
who I tried to kiss.
I tried to kiss
my half brother--
before my real
father killed him!
That's how
screwed up I am!
And you know
the sad part,
I was actually starting to be
in a good place.
I had the club,
I had Roy,
I had a brother who
wasn't lying to me.
And for the first time
in my crazy life,
everything didn't seem so completely
and totally messed up.
I thought I was
going to be ok.
I'm so stupid.
You're not stupid.
No, what I am...
Is the daughter
of two mass
murderers.
Not one, but two.
So let's face it,
Ollie.
I was never
going to be ok.
It's not in my genes.
Thea...
Oliver.
We need to discuss
that security matter now.
What do we have?
What Slade took.
Took?
He wasn't here
to kill us.
He was here because
we had something
that he wanted.
The skeleton key.
I did a full sweep.
It's the only thing that's missing.
He needs a new way
to mass produce the serum now that
we've dusted
Applied Sciences.
With the skeleton key,
he can get into anywhere
and take anything he wants.
We know what he wants.
We just need to find it first.
Where is the most cutting edge
technology housed in Starling City?
The combined inventory
of every scientist
who ever worked
at S.T.A.R. Labs.
All housed
right in here.
I hereby christen
this building "da bomb."
Nobody says that anymore.
I say it.
I define
my own cool.
I still can't believe Dr. Wells
is shutting this place down.
S.T.A.R. Labs blew a hole
in Central City
when we turned
the particle accelerator on.
It's not surprising that Starling City
cancelled the lease on this facility.
We're not exactly
the poster children
for "let us store our unregulated
prototypes in your neighborhood."
It was an accident,
Caitlin.
Yeah, well, try telling that
to the families of the people who died.
Maybe you can figure
out how to tell that to yourself.
Look, Cisco, let's get this inventory
done so we can go home.
I thought we were
the only ones here...
Maybe it's one of
the security guards.
Oh. Hey, man.
We should be wrapped
up any minute now.
Are you getting
a bad vibe off this guy?
The longer
you make me chase you,
the slower
I will kill you.
Help me.
This equipment
belonged to Arthur Light.
Wells fired him two years ago.
Why?
Because he was
a psycho.
Please tell me
you can make this work.
I take back what I said--
I'll make this quick.
No!
Aaah!
We're too late.
Felicity!
Cisco, Caitlin!
Are you guys ok?
He didn't hurt you, did he?
You said "he" twice.
Do you know
who attacked us?
That lunatic with the mask
and the sword?
Uh, no. I--no,
I don't know.
I--I said "he" twice,
because on the radio,
I heard that the person
who attacked you had man parts,
which would make him a...He.
I'm John Diggle, I work security
for Queen Consolidated.
Do you have any idea what
the masked man may have taken?
An industrial centrifuge,
by any chance?
No. It's a secret.
What kind of secret?
The kind I have to keep.
Well, does Cisco
have to keep it, too?
Yes. He does.
Ok.
We're just so happy
that you guys are ok.
How's Barry doing?
He's the same.
Barry's condition
deteriorated.
They moved him to S.T.A.R. Labs.
They've been looking after him.
That's how I met Cisco and Caitlin.
Right.
Well, I'll come visit again,
as soon as I can.
That would be cool.
Don't worry,
Barry gets lots of visitors.
Iris is there a lot.
Iris?
She's, um,
his...
Something.
Oh.
Sure.
Good.
That's just swell.
Barry's in a coma
and he's already moved on.
I hacked into Harrison Wells'
personal files.
He's the director
S.T.A.R. Labs,
which basically
makes me unstoppable.
And look what I found.
It's a prototype for one of
their new bio-tech projects.
The patent
is still pending,
which is probably why they
didn't want to tell us what it was.
So what is it?
It's a biotransfuser.
It can deliver blood
from one single patient
into multiple patients,
at once.
Why would Slade need
a blood transfusion?
He doesn't.
The prisoners that he freed from
Iron Heights last week
to create his own
personal army do.
With a few tweaks, Slade can
retro-fit it for the Mirakuru,
bypassing what we know to be
a less than desirable
ratio of success
to, you know, death.
Instead of it
metabolizing in the person,
it happens in the machine.
That's going to require
a whole lot of blood.
Even a man with Slade's stamina
can't handle that kind of drain.
Good.
What do you mean?
We let him use it.
He'll be weak,
vulnerable,
and that will be my
opportunity to kill him.
How do we find this thing?
A machine like this
pulls an exorbitant
amount of power
from the grid.
When it turns on,
I'll know when and where.
Right now, we just wait.
I'm tired of waiting.
Don't listen to him,
he's lying!
The cure is
real, I promise!
No, he's just trying
to save his neck.
Anthony, look at me.
Tell us about the cure.
I want to help you,
Sara. But first,
you have to promise
you'll help me, too.
She can't save your life.
No one can, not anymore.
All I ask is for
is a quick death.
You don't deserve
a quick death.
I know.
And I'm still
asking.
It's your call.
Thank you.
Start talking, Ivo!
I was never able to replicate
the Mirakuru serum
from the original
Japanese World War II
research I discovered.
After conducting
experiments
on the prisoners that I
acquired this past year,
I was able
to synthesize a solution
that counteracts,
reverses
the physiological effects
that exposure
to Mirakuru produces.
From more than human...
back to human.
Where is this cure now?
You'll keep your word
about ending my life?
Yes. Tell us.
On the freighter.
In the safe
in my quarters.
Now I believe...
This concludes
my end of our deal.
Whatever you came
here to say, it takes security
about 60 seconds
to reach this floor,
so I would
start talking.
Where's Slade?
I just wanted to give you
the chance to do the right thing.
I'm under 30, and I'm the CEO of
a Fortune 500 company.
I'd say I've already
done the right thing.
And do you even know
who Slade Wilson is?
Or why he's doing this?
I don't care.
I got what I earned.
What you earned?
You think that
sleeping with my father
entitles you
to my family's company?
You have no idea
what you're talking about.
Wow, he fooled around
with a lot of girls.
I don't see any of them
ordering hostile takeovers.
Fooled around?
Yeah.
Is that what
your mother told you?
Of course she would write me off
as a meaningless affair.
Slade Wilson put me
through hell.
His training
nearly killed me.
Would I put myself through all that
just because I was a jilted lover?
Honestly, I don't know
what you are!
I was your father's
soul mate.
He was going
to leave your mother,
leave the company,
leave you.
Our bags were packed.
Really?
Your sister had to go
and break her arm
doing something
ridiculous, no doubt.
She fell off her horse.
We were at the airport
when he got the call.
I begged him not to go.
I reminded him that
Thea wasn't even his.
Are you saying
that my father knew?
Of course he knew.
He was a fool,
not an idiot.
And like a fool,
he loved her anyway.
He promised me that we would
leave the next day.
But instead, my internship
was terminated
and he never spoke
to me again.
Oh, so that's what
this is really about.
He chose us over you.
Please escort Mr. Queen
off the premises.
Don't touch me.
He's no longer
welcome in this building.
My building.
Hello?
Thea, it's Ollie.
Listen, I just need
five minutes
face to face.
What do you want?
There's something
you need to hear.
Five minutes. Come by the club
after we close.
Just spoke
with Felicity.
Someone reached out
to the Arrow.
Wants a meeting.
Who?
Laurel.
You comfortable in there,
officer Lance?
I can see if there's
an extra blanket if you're cold.
Nah, I'm good. But hey,
now that I'm on this side of the bars,
I think
it's just Quentin.
I'm sure it's just
a misunderstanding.
You'll be out of here soon.
Yeah, I appreciate
your optimism.
Hey!
Hey, what are you doing?
Officer! We need help!
We need help!
Whoa, whoa, what
are you doing, man?
Remember me?
You should, 'cause
I remember you, Officer.
No, you can't do this.
Aahh! All right,
take it easy.
'Cause you and that
hooded freak show
are the reason
I'm in this place.
I thought I should be
the one to welcome you.
This isn't over!
This is not over!
I heard about
your father being arrested.
If I could help him, I would.
That's not what
this is about.
It's funny, isn't?
A year ago, he thought
you were a murderer.
And me, I was--
I was drawn to you.
I couldn't
explain why, but...
But a part of me
felt connected to you.
You were always there.
For me...
For my family, and for some reason,
I never asked why.
Are you asking now?
I don't have to.
Because I already
know the answer.
Hello?
Laurel...
It's dad.
What is it?
Laurel, I am so sorry.
We had your father
under protective custody.
There's no such as thing
as protective custody in Iron Heights.
Dad!
Hey.
It's all right, sweetheart,
it's all right.
Hey, whoa,
don't touch the ribs!
The ribs.
I'm getting tired of visiting
my family members in a hospital.
What happened?
Oh, it's just some old
collar paid me a visit.
I guess I'm not the most
popular guy in prison.
Sara, do you mind giving Dad and I
a second alone, please?
Yeah, of course.
I'll be right outside.
Don't go far,
sweetie.
Dad...
What is it,
honey?
I have to tell you something.
What is it?
I know who the Arrow is.
What?
Don't say
another word.
Don't say anything.
Ok.
Listen to me, there was a time
when I would have
sold out my badge to find out his
name. You know that.
But then I realize
I didn't care who he was.
In fact, I didn't even want to know
who he was.
Why not?
'Cause I knew
if I knew who he really was,
then he'd become
a person, right?
Maybe he's got
a family. Friends.
People that
care about him.
Someone with a life.
That he couldn't be
what I needed him to be.
What this city
needs him to be.
It's the Arrow
that matters.
The man under the hood
isn't important.
Look at me.
Can you imagine what
it's like to be him?
What he has to live with
day in and day out,
what that's
got to be like.
Hey. The least I can do
is sit here and do a little bit
of time for him.
How's your father?
He'll be better
once you drop all charges
and sign his release papers.
He is facing
18 months.
Yes. But he is not going
to stay here another day
unless you want me
to resign and embark
on an exciting new career
as a criminal defense attorney
whose sole ambition will be
to sue
the District Attorney's office
for wrongful arrest
and reckless endangerment.
Your father will be
released on his own recognizance
within the hour.
And reinstated.
Tomorrow.
A word of advice--
be mindful
of the battles you choose,
because it will not
always be this easy.
Nice work, counselor.
Thank you.
How's your arm?
Mmm, fine.
Only hurts when I wave.
Ouch.
I'm fine, I promise.
I know you will be.
Thanks.
Thank you for agreeing
to talk to me.
You're talking.
I only agreed to listen.
I just want to start with--
I know you think that--
Ahem. Hold on.
I can't talk
right now, Felicity.
I know. But the grid
at Collins and Main just spiked,
drawing a hell
of a lot of power.
Which means someone either plugged
in the world's largest hair dryer,
or the biotransfuser
just went online.
The power cycle
on this machine is very specific.
You have 30 minutes,
40 tops.
I know this is selfish, Oliver,
and don't hate me for saying this,
but...Don't go.
If you don't get Thea
to sign those documents,
your family loses
all of its assets.
If I don't stop Slade right now,
a lot of people will
lose a lot more.
I wouldn't touch
that if I were you.
Removing him mid-cycle
will surely end his life.
Slade, he's just a kid!
Who's here
only because you
pushed him away.
You were the one person
he looked up to.
And for that,
you crushed his soul.
We found him
at a shelter in Bludhaven.
Pathetic.
Didn't even put up a fight.
I will.
Tell me how to shut it down.
If you could feel the power that is
surging through me...
You would know that
I do not fear an arrow.
I am stronger than
you can even imagine.
And soon...
I will not be alone.
You can't hurt me, kid.
Come on, Roy.
All right, stay with me.
He's lost
a lot of blood.
I don't know what
the biotransfuser did to him.
But his pulse is really weak;
He's barely breathing.
And he needs
a real doctor.
We can't take him to a hospital--
they run tests.
We need to keep what's
in him from getting out.
What do we do now?
The only thing
we can do--we wait.
Well, while we're waiting, we still
have a Slade problem.
He's got 20 guys
just like him,
and we have no way
to stop him.
Yes, we do.
Is that what
I think it is?
Mirakuru.
You weren't thinking
about taking it, were you?
No.
We're going to use it
to make a cure.
Oliver, we don't even know if it's
possible to reverse the affects.
Yes, we do.
Ivo did it.
Why didn't you ever
tell us that, Oliver?
Because I'm ashamed.
Of what?
Five years ago, I had
the chance to use the cure on Slade.
I chose to kill him.
Everything that's happening
right now is my fault.
I saved you
once, Sara.
It feels like
a long time ago now.
Time to return
the favor.
You might not
believe it now,
but I was considered
a good man.
A good doctor.
A good husband.
Until the Mirakuru
drove me mad.
I didn't even
take any myself--
You didn't have
to do that for me.
Once you take a life...
It changes you
forever.
And I don't
want that for you.
Thank you.
Schastlivchik.
So, now what
do we do?
Well, I don't suppose any of you
know how to pilot a submarine?
Thea.
What are you doing?
Just grabbing some stuff.
Something tells me
the mansion's new owner
won't want my clothes here.
Thea, wait.
Now he's not busy.
I'm so sorry,
that couldn't be helped.
May I speak to you now?
Dad knew the truth.
What?
He knew about Merlyn.
How?
He never said
anything to me.
He didn't have to.
Thea, whatever
dad's faults were...
He loved us.
All of us.
Because we were his family.
You were his daughter,
and some stupid blood test
wasn't going to change that.
He chose us.
He chose you.
He made a decision
to be your father,
even though
he didn't have to be.
So what does that tell you?
It tells me
that he's a liar.
Just like both of you.
I need you guys
to do me a favor.
This time,
it'll be our secret.
Oliver.
What's this for?
Because you're
important to me.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man