Previously on Arrow...
This laptop contains 40 million rubles
worth of bank transfers from Kovar
that Gregor hasn't disclosed.
This is most disappointing.
I liked many of you.
Prometheus surprised me
with a very specific unique move.
It was taught to me
by a woman that I met in Russia.
You think you and Prometheus
have the same teacher?
You're accepting the invitation
to join Helix?
Full throttle.
What do I do with your secret? I keep it.
I care about this city,
and you're working double-time.
Can you talk some sense into him please?
Mr. Mayor, Thea, meet my wife Doris.
I thought we could talk.
Can we set up a meeting tomorrow?
I'm late for a dinner.
It's important.
You could call it life or death.
You sure this is the place?
I don't see any other monasteries
on this mountain.
Felicity's notes said something
about a demon?
Oh, wait, maybe that says "lemon."
Anyway, I texted her,
but she has not hit me back.
It says "demon."
- Oliver? I'm losing you.
- I'll see you back in Star City.
Where is she?
- Who are you?
- I'm a former student.
"Former." Which means
you are not welcome here.
Hola!
Leave us.
I would apologize
for my students' enthusiasm,
but you should not have come
to this place.
Well, Talia, it was difficult to find.
Our business together concluded
five years ago.
No.
One of your former students
is trying to kill me.
He doesn't want to kill you, Oliver.
He means to destroy you utterly.
You knew?
If you knew, then why would you train him?
Why wouldn't you warn me?
Two years ago, he sought me out.
He'd already learned much about you.
He is a man of remarkable capacity.
Talia, enough! If you knew what he wanted
then why would you train him?
You killed his father.
And I helped him
in his pursuit of vengeance
because by then, you'd killed mine.
I never told you my full name, did 1?
No, you didn't.
It's Talia al Ghul.
Ra's al Ghul was your father.
Yes.
My father and I came to be at odds,
so I forged my own path.
But he was still my father
when you put a sword through his chest.
So that's why you're not going to help me.
That's why you won't tell me
who this "Prometheus" is.
Of course I will, Oliver.
Because I want you to suffer.
He calls himself...
Adrian Chase.
- Everything okay?
- Yes. Peachy.
Let's do this. Whoa.
Yeah, it's lit, right?
All these people, they're just...
You sound surprised.
Yeah, I mean, I guess I just thought
that a secret hacker organization
would be a little bit more...
Well, I don't know, intimate.
Well, Helix is a worldwide operation.
Kind of like the UN,
if it actually accomplished things.
You have 3D nanoelectrics designed to
interface with a neural network?
We were working on something like this
at Palmer Tech. It...
Who do you think
we stole the prototype from?
What is that?
Real-time feed
from every cell phone camera in the world
running through
a pattern-recognition algo.
Holy... That's...
So much bigger than anything
the NSA is doing, I know.
This is a lot of power for
someone to have, who's not government.
Well, the fact that
we're not government's the whole point.
Power to the people, right?
Yeah.
Power to the people.
Welcome to Helix, Felicity.
We're going to change the world together.
Mr. Queen, I've been
trying to reach you all...
I need Captain Pike
and Quentin Lance in my office
and I need to know
where DA Chase is right now.
Right now?
Mr. Chase is in the conference room.
Treatment for drug addicts
over incarceration.
Mr. Mayor, I didn't think
you'd be joining us this morning.
I guess you know
what I've been up to, huh?
Yeah.
I've been working on addressing
our sentencing policy for drug offenses.
Care to join?
I'd like to see you in my office please.
Actually, can it wait?
The councilmen and I are on a clock.
Besides, you're looking a little ragged.
You tired?
Or is it that you've actually been asleep
this whole time?
All the captains are dead.
Da.
Gregor will promote new ones loyal to him.
They will kill us all.
Gonna try it this way, now?
I gotta tell you, I don't know how
that mask is gonna play here.
Especially since this city's not too fond
of your alter ego these days.
I'll give them the Throwing Star Killer,
see how they feel.
Wait, that's your big plan, arresting me?
Oh, man, that's a bit of a letdown,
I have to say.
Well, I'm not going to kill you.
If only because
that's what you want me to do.
But you've done
everything I've wanted so far.
Did you really think
I'd let all this end in a parking garage?
What did you do?
I gave your girlfriend an exclusive.
Wait. Are you still dating Susan Williams?
I gotta tell you, buddy,
it's been a little hard to keep track.
What did you do to her?
She's fine. Don't worry.
As long as I'm around to make sure
she gets some food and water.
Starvation and dehydration.
Terrible way to go.
Bottom line, I die, she dies.
I don't make it back to her in time,
she dies.
Now, you could try torturing me
for her location.
We both know what you're capable of
in that department.
But I think that we both know
what I'm capable of.
So, Ollie, who do you think
can last longer, Susan or me?
Oh.
I'm ten steps ahead of you
and you haven't even figured out
what game we're playing yet.
That son of a bitch.
Yeah, I'd say that pretty much covers it.
This is a hell of a city you got here.
- District Attorney's a serial Killer.
- He's way worse than that.
Infiltrating the government like that,
at the highest level,
right next to Oliver?
We underestimated this guy.
I underestimated him.
I trusted him.
Where is Felicity?
I've been texting her like crazy,
but her phone's off.
- You don't think that Prometheus is...
- No.
No, his game is Susan.
For now. We have to make sure Thea's safe.
Lyla and JJ are secure at A.R.G.U.S.
I got in touch with Thea. She's fine.
But we have to find Susan.
We cannot make a move on Chase
until we know she's safe,
until we have her here.
Keep looking for Felicity.
You GPS her phone if you have to.
We should go to Pike.
Tell him Chase
is the Throwing Star Killer.
And then he asks for evidence
and you say what?
Look, Quentin's right.
Right now, we keep the SCPD out of this
until we have something.
This guy has us in check.
Yeah, for now.
I sent Curtis and Dinah to Opal City.
For Chase's mother?
He has leverage, we need some of our own.
That's not gonna work.
This guy always seems to be
ten steps ahead.
Well, it was pretty easy
you confronting him in public like that.
- What the hell were you thinking?
- I wasn't thinking.
Where're you going now?
According to city records,
Chase's house has a sub-basement.
Well, Chase does everything sideways, man.
I doubt he has Susan some place obvious.
- I don't know what's obvious anymore.
- Hold on.
I can't let you go out there alone.
I'm going with you.
- I can handle it.
- Never said you couldn't.
Three of us cannot defeat Gregor.
We need more men.
No, we need a way to convince the Bratva
that Gregor sold them out.
We had way.
Well, we don't have anyone
that can pull data
off a bullet-ridden laptop, so...
Without proof, Gregor will say
we are traitors,
rest of Bratva will believe him.
And then they will kill us.
So we gotta kill him first.
Before he tells anyone.
Okay, you've had enough to drink already.
Where would Gregor go?
And where would he go right now?
He'd go to ground.
Bratva stronghold is hockey rink.
But it's heavily protected.
Hmm. We wouldn't even
get through the door.
I think I know someone who can.
I guess Norma Bates
got the hell out of Dodge.
Chase anticipated this play.
I never said that he wasn't clever.
But so am I.
Um...
What's your toy doing?
It's detecting
the resonance frequencies upstairs.
But it's not a toy,
it's a T-Sphere.
Wait.
Every horror movie ever has basically said
that you do not go upstairs at
a creepy serial killer's mother's house.
Help!
Someone.
Help.
Excellent.
Now give us another scream.
So, what, we're supposed to
just to go to work like things are normal?
- 'Cause newsflash, they ain't.
- Tell me something I don't already know.
I can think of one or two things.
This is nice,
everything being out in the open now.
All the cards on the table, as it were.
You got some nerve showing up here.
Why wouldn't I?
I take my job very seriously.
Speaking of, I thought my office
had requested your verifications
on the latest ComStat reports
from the SCPD.
What've you been doing?
I'm gonna kill you.
In ways that'll hurt.
Threatening a city official is a felony,
Mr. Ramirez.
You think you're so clever?
This isn't over, you son of a bitch.
I agree. In fact,
I think we're just getting started.
I want those ComStat verifications
on my desk by tomorrow morning, Dog.
We can't just let that son of a bitch
walk around here. We gotta do something.
We are doing something.
Yeah, Rene and I have got eyes on Chase.
He's at City Hall.
You've got a green light
to move on his house.
Roger that.
Okay, Spartan, you check the upstairs
and work your way down.
I'll sweep the basement.
We can meet in the middle.
Roger that.
- Please don't hurt me.
- Mrs. Chase?
- What are you doing in my house?
- Mrs. Chase, I'm not gonna hurt you.
Get away from me.
Your husband isn't who you think he is.
Get out of my house.
Mrs. Chase, your husband
is the Throwing Star Killer.
He's holding an innocent woman hostage.
And I need your help to find her.
You're insane.
Doris, please.
You need to understand the truth.
You have to know on some level
that your husband has been
keeping something from you.
The police and the Mayor say
that you're the killer. You.
On the floor! On the floor!
Get down on the floor!
Can you hear me?
Get down on the floor! Now!
- You all right, Mrs. Chase?
- I'm fine.
We got a call from your husband.
Don't worry. We've got this handled.
Get her out of here.
Dammit. What do you want me to do?
I'm not getting into a shootout
with the SCPD.
Copy that. I'm out.
Smart move, douchebag.
I wasn't talking to you.
Drop the bow and get on the ground.
The whole thing's about 30 seconds long.
I've been over every frame, and
there's nothing to indicate a location.
At least it's proof of life.
Yeah, she was alive
when this video was made,
but we don't know how long ago.
Sorry.
It's fine. He'll...
He'll keep her alive to keep me in check.
I never should have gotten involved
with Susan.
I don't know what I was thinking.
You were thinking you were lonely, man.
Everyone needs somebody.
Yeah, well, maybe I gave up that right
when I put on the hood.
Hi! Oh, hi. I'm sorry. I know I'm late.
I'm sorry. I got Curtis' messages.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry,
I'm here now, I'm sorry.
Can you give us the room please?
Much appreciated. I usually like my
tongue-lashings to be done in private...
So thank you.
I'm...
- Sorry.
- I'm not angry.
You don't...
You don't work for me. You...
I'm worried.
Right.
Of course, for all you know,
Prometheus could have...
I'm not...
I'm worried about you.
Oh.
Because you're into something,
and you don't want to
tell anyone about it.
Or maybe you just don't want to tell me.
I think we can both agree
that keeping secrets doesn't end well.
So...
Yeah, you're right. It's just that
right now is not really a good time.
With everything going on.
You just have to trust me
on this one. Okay?
Okay.
But speaking of the "something"
that I'm into,
it actually helped me go through
the petabyte of data
we took off
of Chase's mother's computer... This...
- Who's Simon Morrison?
- Adrian Chase.
- What?
- Simon Morrison is his birth name.
That's his real identity.
But his mother's name is Amanda Westfield.
Yes, well, she changed her name
when she went off the grid.
So, runs in the family.
Well, if Adrian Chase is an alias...
Then the proof that his background is fake
will be enough for the ACU
to arrest his ass.
- However you did it, good work.
- Thank you.
Put this all in the drive.
I've got to get to City Hall.
Wait, well... Now?
I mean, it's past 10:00.
Yeah, before the 11:00 news.
I have to make a statement
on the Green Arrow
breaking into the DA's house.
Obviously, this is
a horrifying development.
Uh...
We believe the Green Arrow was retaliating
against this office for speaking out
against his recent crimes.
Mr. Mayor?
This office is in complete agreement
with DA Chase.
This situation has become untenable.
And I'm determined to bring it
to a just and successful end.
I will not let anyone, anyone...
Terrorize this city.
So I'm demanding
that the Green Arrow turn himself in.
He has 24 hours,
before I'm ordering the SCPD
to shoot on sight.
That's all. Thank you.
Thanks for seeing me. I know it's late.
Oh, I think we both know our jobs
don't recognize "late" and "early."
What can I do for you?
What's this?
That is evidence that "Adrian Chase"
is a false identity.
His real name is Simon Morrison.
And with some investigation,
you will learn
that he's the Throwing Star Killer.
That's one hell of an accusation.
That's why I'm giving you that.
And this evidence comes from where?
An investigation that I've been
conducting off the books.
With what personnel?
Work the lead, Captain Pike.
Consider that an order, if it helps.
One last thing.
You didn't get that from me.
I serve at the pleasure of the Mayor.
Very well.
Viktor has confirmed Gregor's location.
Now tell me, why did you want him gone?
And why you are playing Robin Hood?
I met a woman.
She taught me
how to give my darkness an identity.
So that it doesn't consume me.
And you believed her?
Gloopy. Oliver...
Whatever you think is inside you,
is inside you.
You cannot name it like that
and keep it apart from you.
This woman has taught me differently.
This woman does not know
what she is talking about.
And if you're not careful, Oliver,
one day she will be the source
of your greatest pain.
Oh, my God.
- And this is...
- We've been calling him Prometheus
but you helped me ID him
as Simon Morrison.
I've been striking out
on getting a location off this,
but someone with a cell phone at some
point must have entered this room,
which means there should be
pictures of it on your database.
If I can cross-reference the images
of your database with this video,
I should be able
to help the police find her.
And that's, like,
really cool and noble and all.
I mean, she definitely needs your help.
But?
But, Felicity, we gave you Pandora.
We helped you sort through that data pull.
And now...
Well, people are starting to ask
what you're doing for us.
I mean, we didn't invite you in just so
you could check items off your to-do list.
Sorry, that feels gross saying.
No. Uh, no, you're right. Okay.
So quid pro quo. I help you, you help me.
I was kind of hoping you'd say that.
We've been trying to break the encryption
on a certain Homeland Security drone.
- Why?
- Need-to-know, I'm afraid.
Question is, what are you willing to quo
in exchange for your quid?
Yeah, can you check some files for me?
Any legal records you can find
on a Simon Morrison.
Thanks.
Hey. Hey, you okay, buddy?
Need some medical attention or something?
What happened?
Some lowlife attacked him outside
the precinct. SCPD's canvassing,
but the security cameras,
they did not get a shot of his face.
How's Pike?
He's comatose.
This was Chase.
I don't know, Oliver. Murder by lowlife
is not exactly his style.
Earlier tonight, I gave Pike a lead,
connecting Chase to Prometheus.
I thought we didn't have any leads.
Felicity resurfaced with something.
Is Pike's family in there?
No. But somebody else is.
Life is just so fragile, isn't it?
Decades of hopes and dreams,
and in one moment,
one little mistake
and it all just goes away.
I'm not gonna let you hurt anyone else.
Really?
Because so far, you haven't been able
to do much to stop me.
Susan's fine, by the way.
Well, alive at any rate.
Me and my team are going to find her.
Huh.
And when we do, the second that we do,
I'm going to put an arrow
right through your heart.
You do realize
how impotent you sound, right?
You think this is a game.
I don't feel like playing anymore.
You don't have a choice, Oliver.
If you kill me,
you Kill Susan.
And she'll be as dead as your mother.
As Tommy. As Shado. As Laurel.
As your friend Pike here, probably.
All dead, because of you.
So go ahead, kill me.
Let's find out how much more loss
you can take.
Because I don't think it's much.
I think that you're one loss away
from being destroyed.
I guess we'll have to find another way
to end all this, then.
You see, that's the beautiful thing
about all of this, Oliver.
If you kill me,
you'll only really be killing yourself.
Thanks for the assist.
What is thing you're doing
with your voice?
Okay, okay, okay. Oh. Oh.
I'm in. Whoo. We're in.
Whoa. Whoa, whoa.
Did we just accidentally hack
a DHS drone system?
Well, I wouldn't exactly
say "accidentally." Am I right?
Uh-uh-uh. Felicity, please explain to me
why we're hacking Homeland Security drones
instead of finding Susan's location
like you told me we were doing?
Because hacking the drones
is what's going to lead us to Susan.
It's so complicated.
Holy crap. You... You just sent
the receiver false data.
And now you're spoofing the GPS system.
There's nothing slight about this,
this is just straight-up illegal.
Spill. 100% deets. Right now. Right now!
Okay, okay! So, I've kind of made
some new friends. Surprised?
And they have access to inaccessible
amounts of data and intel, tons of it.
They helped me get John out of prison.
And now, they're willing to help us
find Susan, that's all.
If you redirect
a few US Border Control drones.
Hey, don't look at me like that.
I've already gotten chapter and verse
from John and Oliver.
Please don't. Please?
I can't imagine them signing off on you
hacking Homeland Security.
They don't know, do they?
All they need to know
is that I'm a grown woman
making my own grown-up decisions.
Hey.
- Got anything for me?
- Felicity, you can't...
Oliver?
What is it, man?
Is it Susan?
Not yet.
But it's just a matter of time.
And I don't know what I can do stop it.
Oliver, there are always options.
- And you're not alone.
- You think that's the problem?
You've done a wonderful job
of convincing me
that I'm changing for the better.
With recruits and...
Transparency, more optimism, more...
More trust.
You think none of this would've happened
if you hadn't trusted Chase, right?
Trusted anyone.
Because I can't see anything past
me just creating more targets.
We're not targets, man.
We're your teammates.
We're your strength.
You give me strength
until Chase turns it into a weakness.
Look at what happened with Susan.
I let myself get close to Susan,
and in so doing
I gave Chase a way to get to me.
That could happen with you, with...
With Felicity.
With my son.
All of you make me vulnerable, John.
Maybe.
Maybe we do.
But caring about people, Oliver,
that makes you human.
Being human is a luxury
I might not get to have.
Yeah.
Okay, got it. Tell Dinah and Rene.
Felicity found out
where Chase is keeping Susan.
- Let's go.
- No, no, John.
There's something I need you to do for me.
If I'm gonna beat this guy
it'll be by playing his game.
And I know someone
who makes him vulnerable.
This is where Prometheus
is holding Susan?
Or at least he was
when he shot that video.
I'm reading a few dozen
heat signatures inside.
- Chase brought back-up?
- Or he's using decoys.
It's decoys. Prometheus works alone.
Problem is, Susan could be in
any one of those heat signatures.
We should split up,
canvass floor by floor.
Agreed. Overwatch, any word on Spartan?
- Package is en route. ETA five minutes.
- "Package"?
Oliver's got something
up his green sleeve.
These puppies should help
double our search capability.
Uh... Next time,
I get to kick the door in.
Yeah. Whatever floats your boat, Lassie.
Get back!
What was that?
Some sort of explosion.
Dinah, Rene, do you copy?
Yeah, yeah, we copy.
But we're trapped in here.
That son of a bitch.
Yeah. What if those heat signatures
are incendiary devices?
I think we can pretty much confirm that.
We have five minutes
for search-and-rescue
before this whole place comes down.
You get Dinah and Wild Dog out of here.
I'll find Susan.
Assuming she's still here.
Which I'm totally sure she still is.
Oliver!
Hey, are you okay?
- Yeah. Adrian Chase is...
- I know!
Don't worry. I'm gonna get you
out of here.
- What's happening?
- Chase is controlling the elevator.
Susan, we need to get you out,
this building is going to explode.
- What about...
- Chase wants me.
- You're no longer his target.
- No, I was gonna say, what about you?
I'm gonna finish this.
Take the elevator upstairs.
Get to safety.
Hello, Oliver.
- Can you guys hear me in there?
- Yeah.
Just waiting on that rescue.
Good. Step back.
I'm glad Talia told you.
I prefer it this way. Face to face.
There's an honesty to it.
Well, honestly,
I'm going to keep both of us here
until this building comes down
on top of us.
- Then you'd be dead.
- So would you.
Really? You really think
I'd let that happen, Oliver?
Remember, I'm always ten steps
ahead of you.
You know, if that were true,
you probably would have seen this coming.
Adrian?
You shouldn't be here.
How else was
I supposed to find out the truth?
- You've killed all those people.
- It's not that simple.
You killed them, it's simple.
I know, baby, this can't be you.
It's not you.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Why did you make her come here?
To get you to stop.
You have to stop.
And you have to,
you have to turn yourself in.
- I can't do that.
- Please. Whatever this is,
whatever you're doing, it's over.
- You'd tell the police?
- No, you'd tell them.
You're right.
I'm going to take care of this.
John!
I've got an ambulance on route
to your position.
- Oh, my God.
- Oliver's in there with Chase.
Go help him now! Go!
I told you, Oliver.
I'm not going to Kill you.
And you can't kill me.
Yes, Adrian. Yes, I can!
What's going on?
Guys, some sort of sitrep.
Chase is gone.
So is Oliver.
Where's Oliver? Guys?
We have to assume that Chase has him.
What about Susan and Chase's wife?
Susan's at the precinct.
Quentin is with her. Um...
Doris passed away en route
to Starling General.
We gotta work on finding Oliver.
Felicity, you found Susan.
You can find him.
You're right.
Felicity, please tell me
you're not going to see them again?
Dinah's right.
They're the ones that found Susan.
Gregor!
Oliver, is that you?
No.
It's the man who's gonna kill you.
You up for making a statement?
I'm up for anything that puts Adrian Chase
in the electric chair.
Actually we only got lethal injection
in this state, but I like your thinking.
- Hello, Ms. Williams. Long time, no see.
- You get away from her.
Please don't threaten me. I'm in mourning.
Haven't you heard? The Green Arrow
killed my wife earlier tonight.
And, apparently, the Mayor's missing.
You wouldn't happen to know
where he is, Quentin?
Honestly, it doesn't look good, Oliver
disappearing under these circumstances.
You give me one good reason why
I shouldn't have you arrested right now.
Because you don't want
your friend back in pieces.
Right?
Everyone's mega impressed
with the DHS hack you did for us.
That's great.
You've also been chosen
as the first woman to go to Mars.
Sorry.
- Friend of mine is missing.
- The information we gave you didn't help?
- Different friend.
- You have a lot of missing friends.
Yeah. And this time
I have no leads, whatsoever.
You guys have better resources than I do,
and I have to use everything
that I can to find him.
And do whatever you need me to do for you.
I don't believe I taught you
how to escape from shackles, Oliver.
Your father was an honorable man.
You've aligned with a psychopath.
And he'd be ashamed of you.
Well, when it comes
to the shame of fathers,
I shall bow to your superior expertise.
Just make sure he suffers.
That was always the plan.
My friends will find me.
They're my strength.
That's sweet.
But I'm running out of ways to tell you,
Oliver, I'm not interested in killing you.
Then what the hell is this game
that we're playing?
When I had Susan as my guest,
I confessed to her that you'd helped me
discover who I really am.
That's what I'm going to
help you do, Oliver.
English - SDH