[Oliver]Previously onArrow...
I need you to help me find my son.
The men your son investigated,
when they discovered his arrest,
they broke into prison.
Take him. They are called the Jackals.
-You let my boy go.
-We need your son.
After all, he's our boss.
Hello, Father.
It's been a long time.
[Joe] You should have stayed dead.
[Slade] I heard you were in trouble, kid.
So I thought I'd offer my help.
[Joe] My old man.
Here to save me. Last I saw,
you weren't all that concerned
with saving anyone.
Apple doesn't fall that far.
What are you thinking?
-Patricide?
-He's seen our operation.
Makes him a liability.
Yeah, you can have that choice.
But I'll give you another one.
Let me join you.
If I wanted a family reunion,
I would have sent an invitation.
Maybe you did.
But you just haven't realized it yet, kid.
See, I came all this way
to speak with you.
And I will kill anybody who gets in my way
because I got nothing
left to lose, only you.
So go ahead.
And make a decision.
I'd be lying if I said I wasn't
swayed by the poetry of it all.
But can I trust you?
Trust is built upon honesty.
I'm sure you have a lot
of questions to ask me.
And I have a lot
of questions for you, Joe.
That's not my name anymore.
Your mother named you something different
to keep us apart.
Okay.
Guess we got some catching up to do.
[Slade groaning softly]
I'm not leaving you.
[Joe] Father.
Joe!
-How are you feeling?
-How did I get here?
[Joe] Evac found you. Washed up
on the Philippine coast.
They said you were barely conscious.
Just muttering someone's name.
"Oliver." Who is he?
[gasps]
[grunts]
[breathing heavily]
Father?
It's just someone that owed me a debt.
Everyone left you for dead.
But I knew you'd come back.
I won't ever leave you again, Joe.
I promise.
[comms beeps]
Wild Dog, Terrific. You ready to do this?
[Wild Dog] Always, but I got bad news.
These guys aren't just thieves.
They killed a security guard.
Make that two.
These guys aren't playing around.
Neither are we.
[grunting]
Incoming! Fall back!
Now!
Curtis, you're right. The thieves were
after the components of a 3D printer.
Two innocent people get killed
'cause some psycho
wants to print plastic toys?
This wasn't a consumer 3D printer.
This was military grade.
You're saying there's a printer
that can print weapons?
Or drones, or chemicals.
Sorry I missed the fun,
anyone want to catch me up?
Break-in, Cadmus Tech.
Thinking Cayden James?
That's what we were assuming,
but this crew
doesn't look like the type
he usually runs with.
That would track with some new street
chatter SCPD has been hearing lately.
-What kind of chatter?
-New player.
No idea what his game is.
All we have is his street name.
-Dragon.
-Dragon? [chuckles]
-That's colorful.
-Tomorrow's problem.
Why don't we all get some rack time,
hit this fresh in the morning.
[Kane] Excuse the poor accommodations.
Don't plan on staying in this stain
of a country too long.
Well, there's a reason why they say
the money is in the muck.
I did bring one luxury however.
Oh, there's a blast from the past.
My favorite. I never realized
you'd acquired a taste for it too.
Like you told me, always drink good booze.
And only look out for yourself.
[Slade] The Jackals are an unruly bunch.
Must've been hard trying to keep ASIS
in the dark for so long.
It's amazing what an agency overlooks
when it's willing to leave
its own men for dead.
[chuckles]
[Slade] So what kind of operation
are you planning on running here?
Drugs, weapons?
Perhaps a military coup.
Let's call it a re-assignment
of resources.
A lucrative one.
Hey, babe.
Hey.
I didn't wanna wake you.
I am still on Vlatava time.
Besides, I heard a rumor that the
Green Arrow was gonna be here.
-[chuckles]
-And I'd never miss a chance to see him.
You know, when you took this on,
I think I got a pretty good sense
of how you felt when I took
Amanda Waller's place at A.R.G.U.S.
Not that bad, I hope.
But seeing you like this,
being the Green Arrow,
it suits you.
-Let's go to bed.
-Mmm.
Hey. Hey.
Let me clean up first.
Okay.
Don't be too long.
[cell phone vibrating]
So, you and your boy,
one big happy family again, huh?
[Slade] None of your business.
He told me about your new job,
the reassignment of resources.
Tell me about that.
The boss didn't think to tell you.
And that means it's none of your
business, comrade.
Main hall, 30 minutes.
[Oliver] [whispering] Slade.
[whispering] What are you doing here?
You should have gone home.
I don't abandon people.
Even when they leave me drugged.
Now, what is this reassignment
of resources
that your son and his men are planning?
You overheard that?
Just like I overheard
your plan to join his unit.
Your son is dangerous, Slade.
He's just a younger version of me.
No, you were never a gun for hire.
I was a killer.
Listen, kid, you better go home,
before you find yourself in trouble
you can't get out of.
I can't walk away from this.
Can you?
[Nylander] Feeling at home yet,
Slade? Hmm?
Or should I call you Deathstroke?
[Joe] Slight change in plans, gentlemen.
Forty percent of our Semtex
was compromised during transfer.
Conveniently, however, the Kasnian army
is doing some transferring of its own.
I'm gonna take a small team to intercept.
Does this jeopardize our timeline?
Not with the infamous Deathstroke
backing me up.
What do you say, Father?
Interested in showing us how it's done?
As long as your dogs can keep up.
I'll go pack some gear.
[comms beeps]
-Hi, kid.
-Comms are working.
Kane has me making a run for Semtex.
[Oliver] That's a high-yield explosive.
With Nylander involved
I should've expected it.
Well, he'll probably be handling
the detonator.
If you can find the receiver,
perhaps you can corrupt it.
-It might be in Nylander's gear.
-I'm on it.
You good?
Just find the receiver.
Keep varying your pace.
My pace is fine, old man.
So you say.
[both grunting]
Dead.
Come on, get up.
How are you better with one eye
than I am with two?
You must learn to move with your mind.
Not your eyes.
Come on.
Let's go again.
[Joe] Hold on a second.
Here, happy one year
back from the dead day.
[glasses clinking]
[sighs]
-Don't look too excited.
-I can't believe it's been so long.
Thank you.
You might change your mind about
staying home after you see this.
New prototype. Should be ready in a year.
That's gotta be tempting, right?
Not in the slightest. Enough distractions.
Let's train.
Come on.
[both grunting]
[grunts]
[Slade] Come on!
Yes.
Damn it, Father.
[both panting]
[sticks clatter]
I'm sorry.
I think we're done with training today.
[Shado] You tried to forget me.
Shado!
But you can't, my love.
Because you made me a promise. [echoing]
[dealer] You want more drugs?
You got to talk to the boss.
All right, man, make the introduction.
[man] Who the hell is this?
-The loyal customer.
-This the guy you told me about?
Ricardo Diaz. So, you're a bouncer?
-Something like that, right?
-That's right.
You're huge.
Oh...
I wouldn't want to mess with you.
I'm just playing with you.
Till we get our FDA approval,
we got to be careful
-with the roll-out. You understand?
-I get it.
Just trying to make it through a day.
Aren't we all?
-Hook him up.
-Sure thing, Mr. Diaz.
I always knew you'd end up wearing this.
[tires screeching]
Kill the lights.
[Jackals groaning]
We don't leave witnesses.
[groaning]
[grunts]
[door closes]
[clatter]
[grunting]
[Rene] Hey!
Anybody in the mood to stress eat?
Always, what you got?
Quadruple cheese! Must be serious.
What's going on here?
Trying to get a line on this Dragon guy,
find out what he and his crew are up to.
[computer beeps]
At least we know where they are.
Just got a security alert.
Palmer Tech Bio Division.
Suit up and stay sharp.
Remember, these guys
aren't afraid of dropping bodies.
[thief] We got company! Go!
[groans]
[tires squealing]
[Green Arrow] I've got the SUV, cover me.
[tires screeching]
[gasps]
[panting]
You okay, hoss?
I ran facial recognition
off of John's body cam footage.
Meet Ricardo Diaz
and his extensive criminal record.
Does anyone want to guess
what his street name is?
Anyone want to guess?
You guys are no fun.
His street name is Dragon.
[Dinah Drake] This jerk wad's been
out of prison less than a month.
He's already racked up a body count.
[Rene] This guy was doing double jolts
of life plus one.
-[Curtis] What's that?
-[Dinah] It's life without parole.
What's he doing walking around?
State Supreme court overturned
his convictions due to technicalities.
But before he was on the inside,
he was running with a group called
the Scorpions in the Glades.
John, do you know anything
about the Scorpions?
John?
John, John, Earth to John Diggle.
The Scorpions?
The Scorpions, yeah, I know them.
But Diaz is on something different.
New muscle, new crew. Way too organized.
[Rene] Wonder when he got himself
a new crew.
How he got to be the boss of it.
Why he needs a weapons grade 3D printer.
I think I have the answer to that.
Drugs. High-end ones.
I cross-referenced
the two models that were stolen
and what they have in common is
their capacity to simultaneously print
inert polypropylenes
and soft material catalyst composites.
Did anyone understand a word of that?
You think Diaz is making reactionware?
-Anyone normal.
-With this equipment?
Diaz cuts out the middle man.
He can make designer drugs
more cheaply and efficiently
than anyone else on the street.
The hell he is.
Whatever science experiment
he's got going on, we're shutting it down.
Curtis, let's work up a location
for Diaz's operation.
Mmm-hmm.
-You okay, chief?
-Yeah.
Been a while since a perp got
the drop on me. That's all.
We'll make sure Diaz pays for that.
So what are you planning
with all these explosives?
I'd like to know.
You missed your kill shot
with the soldier back there.
Well, when I lost this eye,
I lost my depth perception.
Most of my men think
you joined me under false pretenses.
There's nothing false
about trying to find my son.
But if they doubt me...
Then maybe I don't have your trust.
Of course, you do.
That's why I got you a little gift.
You told me not to worry, brother.
[groans]
[Kane] Nylander found him
with my detonator.
Some might see this as coincidence.
But I see it as fate.
It's time to collect on that debt
he owes your father.
Oliver Queen! I've waited a very,
very long time for this.
An eye for an eye.
[Shado] You're lying to yourself, Slade.
You know he's alive.
You've always known.
But still you do nothing. [echoing]
You know what he did to me.
You know what he took from us.
Yet here you are, hiding like a coward.
[panting]
[Shado] Getting weak. Pathetic.
Give me what you promised.
Get out of my head!
Not until Oliver Queen is dead.
He is dead. He died on the Amazo.
[newscaster] Oliver Queen is alive.
The Starling City resident
was found by fishermen
in the North China Sea five days ago.
Listen, love,
you're the only one who can avenge me.
[echoing]
You're the only one
who can make him suffer.
[sighs deeply]
You know why?
I keep my promises.
[trainee] Sir, is everything okay?
-[bones cracking]
-[screams]
Come on!
[sword clanging]
You are telling me
you became the Green Arrow
after you knew about the tremor?
I was gonna tell Oliver.
But then he asked me to take over
for him. I couldn't let him down.
-I couldn't let the team down.
-But you were physically compromised.
I came up with a temporary solution.
An experimental steroid.
Lyla, I wanted to tell you so bad,
I know it was the wrong call.
-I'm sorry.
-I'm just glad you finally told me.
But now that I have, I need your help.
Is there anything,
anything that A.R.G.U.S. is working
on that could help my condition?
I thought it was just
some kind of steroid.
Yeah, we found out that
the manufacturer's involved in...
criminal activity.
He and his crew have killed
at least two people.
I don't know, maybe more.
Right, so your experimental steroid
is actually an illegal drug.
Look, if this is what it's taken
for you to come clean,
and get this guy off of the street,
then I guess I should be grateful.
What?
[sighs] You're still using the drug.
And I guess that means that
the drug dealer is out there too.
To be Green Arrow means
I have to be physically capable
of protecting the city, no matter what.
Lyla, you make the same choices
at A.R.G.U.S. all the time.
Choices you've condemned me for making.
I know I'm wrong,
but I couldn't let Oliver down.
So you let yourself down instead.
Johnny, you are the most moral man I know.
I can't even begin to fathom
how you could do this.
As soon as A.R.G.U.S. has a solution,
I'll get my guy off the street.
Until then, how many more people
is this guy going to kill?
It's not that simple.
You're the one who taught me that it is.
[sighs]
Lyla, can we please...
No, I just...
I want to be alone right now.
[door closes]
Years ago, I made you a promise.
Do you remember?
I promised that you would suffer
the same way that I suffered.
What are you doing?
You are not this person anymore.
What I am is a father
reunited with my son.
I made him a promise too.
And I'm not going to break it again.
We made each other a promise, Slade.
To save our sons.
To save Joe, to save William.
He has a son.
I'll make sure he suffers too.
Slade.
Do it.
Slade!
[grunts]
That was a little too convincing.
We gotta go.
Come on.
[grunting]
-There's no way out.
-Let's make our own way. Come on.
I'll send out the dogs.
We've got the op.
That's where they'll be.
You sure?
That my father would try to stop us?
That's what fathers do.
And that's why I'm gonna kill him.
[Oliver] Before they captured me,
I saw what Kane was going after.
Attacking the water supply,
it's a death sentence
for half the country.
If we move now,
we might be able to stop them.
If that's what you want.
I spared your life back there.
I know.
Back there, it didn't feel like an act
the same way it did with Chase
back on Lian Yu.
Because when I saw my son,
I was tempted.
I would have done anything
to keep us together.
But when you mentioned William,
I realized that's not my boy.
It's Kane.
And what I fear is there's
only one way to stop him.
Slade.
There are other ways to deal with this
that don't involve killing your son.
Deep down, he's your boy
so you have to reason with him.
And I swear, he will listen to you.
But I didn't tell you
what happened after Lian Yu.
I went home to my son and I promised him
I would stay and never leave.
And I broke that promise.
You broke the promise
because of the Mirakuru.
[Slade] The Mirakuru faded for a while.
But when it came back,
it was like a storm I could not control.
And that monster is what my son
is trying to emulate.
But it's not Mirakuru with Joe.
It's anger and resentment.
And I don't know how that can be redeemed.
Well, I didn't think that
you could be redeemed.
But I'm here, miles from home,
miles from my son,
trying to help you save yours.
And I can do that because I knew
the man that you were
before the Mirakuru.
That is who your son needs to see.
He needs to see his father.
The man you are right now, tonight.
[car door opens]
[man groans]
Father?
Drop your weapon.
No. Not until you tell me
what you're doing.
They were trying to stop me.
What the hell are you talking about?
Stop you from what?
Keeping my promise.
[grunts]
Stay out of my way.
He doesn't show up on traffic cams.
He doesn't leave a paper trail.
Ricardo Diaz is good.
How's the research on
his old associates going?
Going lousy. Everybody mentioned
in his arrest records
is either missing or dead.
Explains why no one's willing to talk
to the department about Dragon.
[John] I've got something.
Diaz's address. His base of operations.
How the hell did you get that?
It's a contact. That's all I can say.
[Felicity] Got it.
Thermal imaging shows a lot
of activity inside.
[Curtis] Got to figure Diaz is in there.
Even if he's not, we can
still disrupt his drug operation.
Let's take this guy down.
Suit up.
[Black Canary cry]
Green Arrow has found us,
and his friends too.
-[distant rapid gunfire]
-Clear out our stash.
Nothing gets confiscated.
Go, go!
[yelps]
[grunting]
[gunshots]
Stop!
We gotta move!
Arrow, let's go.
[Black Canary] Arrow, let's go!
[device beeping]
-[Kane] Where are we?
-[Nylander] All charges are set.
-Looks like it should be you.
-I hired you to pull the trigger.
Move out! Get to a safe distance.
Semtex makes for a pretty big bang.
-You're not coming with?
-I want a good view.
[chuckles] You're crazy. I love it.
Don't forget what you said
about the Semtex, huh.
I knew you'd show up.
I think it's time
we had ourselves an honest talk.
[gunfire]
[groans]
Trust begins with honesty.
That's what you said to me. But you lied.
You know life is not that simple, Joe.
That's not my name.
How could you forgive Oliver Queen
after what he did to you?
Because he forgave me for far worse.
Sins that I have to carry to the grave.
A curse I didn't want to pass on to you.
All of this anger and resentment.
It's time to bring it to an end, son.
No.
This is just the beginning.
[grunting]
[both grunting]
You used to be ruthless. What happened?
What you saw was the Mirakuru.
Stop lying!
I saw you kill before the Mirakuru.
[grunts]
[groans]
Milford Sound.
That little father-son trip.
The one you promised
would be all about you and me.
I saw what you did to that Chinese spy.
-[knife slices]
-[groans]
I was on a mission for ASIS.
Well, here's something you don't know.
Something Mother never told you.
I have a brother.
His name is Grant.
Mother didn't want him in this world.
But me,
I'm my father's son.
I made my first kill six months
after our camping trip.
I slit his throat,
just like you did.
I wanted to be exactly like my father.
Like Deathstroke.
I'm not Deathstroke...
anymore.
Then you're not my father anymore.
You're just in my way.
[sword clatters]
Don't move. Slade, you all right?
Oliver, lower your gun.
I wish that you'd stayed dead.
He's gone.
[Oliver] Thank you.
Spoke with our friend, the Warden.
Jackals are in custody,
and he is very relieved.
You all right?
My son.
He saw me kill a man before the Mirakuru.
Before Deathstroke.
He followed in my path, Oliver.
No. Don't blame yourself, Slade,
it doesn't help.
[Slade] You know why I do.
Never give up on family.
That's what you told me.
It's time for you to go home.
Where will you go?
I'm gonna keep searching for my son.
Both of them.
-I can't give up.
-You ever need my help again,
you don't hesitate to ask.
You have your own son to protect.
I'm not gonna put that at risk again.
You've seen what can happen.
Thank you, kid.
Hey.
I just saw a news report
on the lab explosion.
Looks like you took down his operation.
With plenty of collateral damage.
Yeah, well, that part was all Diaz.
He was willing to blow up the works.
Kill all of his men.
So, you didn't mean to destroy the drugs?
Uh...
I planned to take
as much as I could carry.
When I realized I was losing
the very thing
that allowed me to put on that hood,
I wanted to run
straight into the explosion.
Johnny.
I was a hypocrite and I am sorry.
I'm sorry.
Don't be sorry.
Be safe.
Be okay.
I'll try.
Hey!
Come here, you.
[exhales]
I missed you.
I missed you, Daddy.
I have, uh, one more stop tonight
with some other people,
who deserve an apology,
an explanation.
Okay.
-[William] I'm going to win.
-[Felicity] No! I almost got you.
[both grunting]
-[William] Yes! Yes!
-[Felicity] No!
Rematch? Rematch.
-All right.
-I got you on this one.
-Hey.
Hey, buddy.
Come here.
-Okay. You weren't gone that long.
-I know. I know. [chuckles]
Well, I'm happy to see you, it's allowed.
So, what happened with your friend?
He found his son.
-[William] That's good.
-So what did I miss?
Well, Raisa made me clean my room.
Felice and I ate ice cream for dinner.
And I got an A on my science project.
You got an A?
-Yeah.
-That's fantastic.
-Is it here, can I see it?
-Yeah, sure.
It's a bottle rocket, went 300 feet,
farthest in the whole school.
Unbelievable.
-I'll go get it.
-All right.
Pretty cool!
I hope you don't mind that I'm here.
William said that he was kind of
getting sick of Raisa,
and the ice cream for dinner,
it was Rocky Road, so technically
the nut should count as protein.
-I'm so happy you're here.
-Me too.
Slade got his happy ending?
Not like that. [chuckles]
It's a long story.
[sighs deeply]
It's a sad story.
Sensing a but.
I learned something.
Hmm.
I made the right decision
to not be the Green Arrow.
-For William and for me.
-Good.
If we can go up to the roof,
I can show you how it works.
-Yup.
-Yes.
[cell phone chimes]
The moment I hesitated,
even as the flames grew closer,
[sighs]
that was my rock bottom.
I should have told you all about
the tremor from the beginning.
-I'm truly sorry I didn't.
-So you're saying
the tremor started before
Black Siren showed her face
-in Star City?
-Yes.
And that's why, Rene, I owe you
the biggest apology of all.
You should've known what was going on
before we ever got to that bridge, man.
My pride almost got you killed.
I betrayed your trust.
Put your lives in danger.
All I can ask is that you forgive me,
but I understand if you can't.
Getting shot wasn't great.
But if I'm counting the times
you saved my life
against the times you almost
got me killed,
you're still ahead.
I, for one, am incredibly offended.
And you have every right to be, Curtis.
That you didn't come to me first
for help treating you.
I created a chip to help
a woman walk, people.
He's got a point, John.
Might be time to outsource
this little problem.
Yeah. Yeah.
Outstanding.
So have you already had an electromyogram?
Wait, what am I talking about? We need
to start off with an NCV test first.
Curtis, it's been a long night.
Is there any way
we can do this in the morning?
Sure thing.
It would be my honor.
-It would be my pleasure.
-[fake cough] Kiss-ass.
What the... I'm trying to...
You waiting on a special apology?
Because you deserve one.
No.
Just wanted to make sure you're okay.
-Really?
-Really.
Well, I'm gonna give you one anyway.
Dinah, I lied to you and I'm sorry,
but I'll make one more promise.
There'll be no more secrets
between you and me.
No more secrets.