My name is Oliver Queen.
After five years in hell...
...I have come home with only one goal:
to save my city.
Now others have joined my crusade.
To them, lam Oliver Queen.
To the rest of Starling City,
lam someone else...
...I am something else.
Previously on Arrow:
A lot of good people,
they lose someone.
They come in here to work off that rage.
Roy, are you okay?
You look a little tired.
I just haven't been sleeping much lately.
If I had accepted my life,
I would be a cocktail waitress in Vegas...
...and I never would have believed
some crazy guy in a hood...
...when he told me
I could be more than just some IT girl.
- You're not moving very quickly this morning.
- I just didn't sleep much last night.
You're not boxing, Laurel.
You're not even fighting.
You're just lashing out. Come on.
Impressive.
How do normal people spend their morning?
Eight, nine...
Foun
Come on, ladies, you're almost there...
And 10.
- Five. Ungh.
- Good. Very good.
Yes!
Hold your core strong, push that back in...
Mrs. Fernandes...
...I already told you I
haven't seen your cat.
I haven't seen him either.
Or is the cat a girl?
Was I being misogynistjust now?
Or is it misogynistic? I never know.
Ray, what are you...?
Nice place. Lots of space.
So, what's the one thing
Queen Consolidated has...
...that we don't use
to its maximum potential?
- A doorbell?
- Have you heard of cogeneration?
I haven't even looked
at a cup of coffee yet.
- Cogeneration is a...
- The repurposing...
...of waste heat given off
by electricity production.
A principle of thermodynamic efficiency,
which occurred to me...
...could be applied to a building
which generates over 240,000 watts...
...like Queen Consolidated.
Mmhm.
I, uh, did some preliminary calculations
on the drive over.
You wanna sell QC's excess energy
back to the city?
If by sell, you mean
give away for free, yes.
Energy is something
that should be given freely to the masses.
Uh, you still haven't found Mrs.
Fernandes' cat, I'm guessing.
- Oh, my beautiful girl!
- Very friendly with your neighbors, I see.
- Mom...
- Mom?
- ...what are you doing here?
- Honey, I came to see you.
For a visit. Look. Didn't you get my text?
Mom, to send a text, you actually have
to press "send" on the text.
Oh, okay. Not a big deal.
I'll do it right now.
- Are you adopted?
- Oh.
I'm so sorry. I didn't know you
had somebody staying over.
Oh, no, he's not staying over.
He's not... Like, we're not...
- This is my boss.
- Pleasure to meet you, Ms. Smoak.
- Hi. You can call me Donna.
- Mom.
- I'm Ray.
- Oh, my God. Palmer?
- You're that watch guy.
- We like to call them smart wearables.
I bought one of your watches! Look!
Felicity here thinks I don't pay attention
to all of her techie things.
Yeah, I see you've got a 3GS. I'm actually
wearing a prototype for the new 6.
- It basically replaces your computer.
- Very fancy.
- You know what? It's yours.
- Oh, no. Seriously?
I'll let you two catch up.
Let me know what you think
about those numbers...
- ...and, Donna, hope to see you again.
- Wouldn't count on it.
She'll probably be really busy,
planning my funeral...
...after I die of embarrassment.
You are standing in an open field
west of a white house...
...with a boarded front door.
What are you doing?
I just finished coding
a Linux emulator for Zork.
Hmm. "it is pitch black.
You are likely to be eaten...
...by a grue."
I guess you'll have to protect me.
Why can't you just quietly have sex under
a comforter like most college students?
You found an exploitable node?
Now I just need your super computer virus
to crack the firewall.
I really wish you wouldn't call my X-axis
bionumeric algorithm a super virus.
Spoofing the IF', switching to MD6, and...
Somebody take a screenshot.
We have to post this to Hackerforum
to brag that we actually got in.
- Hold on.
- Thirty seconds until the firewall goes back up.
Cooper, what are you doing?
The world would be a much better place
without student loans.
You can't wipe out all the loans.
They're gonna track us down.
- Ten seconds.
- Cooper!
I'm not going to jail for you, Cooper.
And you shouldn't either.
- Coop!
- I almost had it.
What were you thinking?
Ever heard of hacktivism?
Instead of posting to web forums,
we could be doing some real good.
And going to prison in the process.
It's all about what you wanna be
when you grow up, babe. A hacker or a hero?
Hello?
Speedy?
Just signed the lease. What do you think?
Thea, you're signing a lease on a spot
that you can't possibly afford.
- I can, actually.
- With whose money?
Malcolm Merlyn's. His estate, I mean.
When I left Starling City,
I mentioned something to Ned Foster...
...about Malcolm being my father...
...and there was a lot of legal stuff
I didn't understand...
- He left you money?
- The entire world thinks he's dead, so...
...yes, legally, his estate goes
to his last living heir.
And, ahem, last week when you told me that you
had investors for the club, that was a lie?
I was afraid you wouldn't react well
to the idea of me taking his money.
It's blood money, Thea. You don't know
what Malcolm Merlyn is capable of.
I know what his money is capable of.
Renting me this really sweet loft.
Listen to me. He's alive.
And if you take his money,
he has a hold on you.
I think you're being a little melodramatic.
I'm his daughter, okay?
He's not going to put me in danger.
He's responsible for the death of 503
innocent people, including your brother.
That is a card that you do not get to play.
You are my brother...
...but that does not mean you have the right
to tell me what I can do with my life.
I am my own person.
Movers are coming tomorrow,
so you can stop by with popcorn...
...or not stop by at all.
Oh, please.
Good. So...?
What is going on?
Ollie?
Are you okay?
We are Brother Eye.
Judgment has been rendered
against this city.
A sentence carried out.
An earthquake. A siege.
This is what comes next.
A new life you will live on your knees.
And it will take nothing more
than the push of a button.
We are in control now.
And this is all just the beginning.
Let there be light.
Ooh. A nightclub. Heh.
You know,
I'm really not dressed for a nightclub.
- Really?
- You think?
My friend owns the place. He just needs
a little help turning the power back on.
Oh.
Why don't you...
...come, come, stay put?
- Stay here?
- Right here.
Okay. You gonna go?
Mm-hm.
Hey, any luck tracking this...?
Hello.
Hi. Uh...
- Please tell me this is your friend.
- No.
- Mom, this is Oliver...
- Queen.
- Very nice to meet you.
- Yes, it's so nice to meet you too.
How many billionaires do you know?
Diggle, uh, meet Felicity's morn.
- Mom? John Diggle. Very nice to meet you.
- Hi. Nice to meet you too.
Aw. Hello. Who is this little nugget?
This is my daughter, Sara.
- Mom? Mom? Mom!
- Oh. Aw. What?
- We have to go downstairs.
- I didn't mean to stop you.
I'm so sorry. Little baby moment. So sorry.
- It's great to meet you, finally.
- Nice to meet you. Yes. Definitely.
Why is Sara here?
Lyla's on assignment,
and the nanny called in sick.
But we can't bring her down there.
- Why not, Oliver? Who's she gonna tell?
- Well, she...
- I'm not comfortable with her down there.
- God help me.
My mother loves babies.
- Really?
- Whoever this Brother Eye group is...
...got access to the city's protective
network and uploaded a system-wide virus.
Any way to trace it?
No, it deleted itself
as soon as it completed its task.
- He said the power outage was the beginning.
- Let's find them before there's a next time.
- Hey, Laurel, are you all right?
- I'm fine. I was close.
But why did I get the alert?
Why didn't they call the district attorney?
He's visiting his niece in Coast City.
You are the acting district attorney.
Congratulations.
Hello, detective. Captain.
- You're on this Brother Eye thing?
- We are.
Good. No one here knows computers
better than you.
I gotta go. For the last time,
I am not interested in buying a fake ID.
I am hanging up now. Bye.
My mom says hi.
- You still angry at me?
- I was into the account network.
I had 3000 debts wiped
by the time you pulled the plug.
Think of how many accounts you could go
to prison for if I hadn't stopped you.
Relax. The DNS wasn't configured.
They can't backtrace me.
They can. The subroot was configured.
By accessing the accounts...
...you set off a packets feedback
that anyone could trace back to you.
You are gorgeous
when you're being a chicken.
- I'm serious.
- Cooper Seldon...
- FBI, don't move!
- ...you're under arrest.
- What? No! Let go of me!
No, no, no!
You're under arrest for violation
of U.S. Code Title 18, Section 10-30.
- Don't! It's not his!
- You have a right to remain silent.
Let go of him! Let him go!
We said this was just the beginning.
Electricity is not the only power
in this city.
Consider money, for example.
The banks are next to go dark.
Your beloved dollars wiped away...
...as your accounts will finally
all be equal at zero.
- Felicity.
- I'm working on it.
I set up some trace IP packets.
As soon as he opened the channel...
...I scooped up the crumbs.
Crumbs we can follow?
I hope so.
- Where's Captain Lance?
- Coordinating squad car patrols for Dispatch.
- Why, what's wrong?
- There's a situation at Starling National.
Send in an ESU squad.
- Sorry, but you don't have the power to...
- I'm acting district attorney.
The city charter gives me operational authority
in times of crisis, which this clearly is.
And I'm not letting anyone get hurt.
Send in an ESU now.
- What's going on?
- S.C.P.D. dispatched a riot squad.
That's like fighting a fire with gasoline.
Suit up.
This group has been ordered to disperse.
Go back inside! Get back behind the line!
Oliver, the riot is getting
out of control. You need to hurry up.
You are trespassing!
Please disperse immediately.
We will use force!
Get away from the bank!
Tear gas is dispersing them,
but we can't calm the entire city.
The trace led me to the virus they're
using. It is a mile past complex.
I'm combing through now.
- No, no, no.
- What's wrong?
The virus, I can't stop it.
- How do you know?
- Because it's mine.
I wrote it five years ago.
Okay, before you say anything,
just know that...
...I never imagined the virus being used
for something like this.
I mean, sure, I could have imagined it.
I have a very vivid imagination.
Like Cronuts, I had a vision of them...
Hey.
Relax.
Take a deep breath.
Good. Now start at the beginning.
I was in this,
I guess you could call it a group...
...in college. We were hacktivists.
For lack of a better word.
Civil disobedience via the World Wide Web.
I created this...
...this...
...super virus.
It could give us root access
to any infected server.
We could expose government fraud...
...and start virtual sit-ins
and digitally deface criminals.
I guess you could say it was
my first attempt at being a hero.
Felicity...
...why didn't you tell
me about any of this?
Do we even know a fraction of what happened
to you the five years you were away?
- Who else had access to the program?
- Myron Forest.
He was my... I had a boyfriend in college,
and Myron was his roommate.
And he was a member
of this hacktivist group?
What about the boyfriend?
Oh, he couldn't have done this. He's...
...not in the picture,
but Myron always had somewhat of an edge.
Can you give me an address?
Sure.
There's one small problem.
Not small necessarily, but short.
Just take the alleyway entrance.
Are you okay?
I've been better.
I talked it over with Myron, and I'm going
to tell them I wrote the super virus.
You can't do that.
- I can't let you rot in prison, Coop.
- You can't tell them you wrote that virus.
Because I already told them I did.
- Cooper...
- I always said I'd protect you from the grues.
- This isn't...
- It's better this way.
I wiped out those loans. There's no reason
both of us should be in prison.
I love you.
I love you too.
Hey. Got a minute?
Congratulations, you called in a riot
squad, you nearly started one...
...and you did it behind my back.
You were busy, and the situation
at Starling National was escalating.
You escalated it, Laurel! Please tell
me you can at least see that now.
Okay.
- I'm sorry.
- Laurel, baby...
...what's gotten into you? You're
angry, you're distant, you're reckless.
Tell me you're not boozing again.
- No.
- Then what the hell's going on?
Because this isn't you.
Look, I haven't said anything.
I was hoping you would say something...
...because you are in 1O different kinds
of pain and you won't talk about it.
I can't talk about it with you.
Okay, listen, you don't have
to talk about it with me.
But talk about it with somebody.
Because secrets hurt, baby,
sometimes more than the truth.
Backup generator keeps that locked.
Or so they told me.
I could never get that stupid door to open.
Contractor says the entire sublevel's
flooded, though. A water-main break.
What are you doing here, Ollie?
A super hacker's trying to take over
the city and I'm worried about you.
- I still get to be worried, right?
- Yes.
And if you really have to,
you can even be judgmental.
Occasionally.
But someone told me recently
that family is pretty precious.
And love, in spite of everything,
is what makes it precious.
Right now the Queen family
is just you and me.
So let it just be you and me.
And don't take Merlyn's money.
I'm trying to meet you halfway here, Ollie.
The other half is up to you.
Myron Forest...
...you have failed this city.
He has to retract all the infected packets
from subsystem mainframes.
Tell me how to shut down the virus.
Do it now.
You think I'm behind the cyber attacks?
- Sounds like a Brother Eye to me.
- I swear to God, I'm not.
I head up the IT department
of an accounting firm.
I drive a hybrid. It's blue.
I'm one of the sheep lunatics
like these guys hate. Why would I do this?
His fingerprints are all over this code.
It's an X-axis bionumeric algorithm.
The code's an X-axis bionumeric algorithm
that you've used before!
In college.
My roommate, his girlfriend. Yeah.
We developed it, we called it a super virus,
but that doesn't mean I'm the Eye guy.
- Have you tried Felicity Smoak?
- She's innocent.
Then it's gotta be someone else.
After we graduated, I might have showed
the code off to a few people.
- Who were they?
- I don't remember. It was five years ago.
I didn't think it was a big deal.
We were just kids playing with matches.
I'm running out of expletives.
Track down whoever
Myron shared your code with.
I hacked all of his e-mails and texts...
...from five years ago,
and all I got was depressed.
- Okay, what about your ex?
- I already told you, he didn't do it.
Why? Because he's your ex-boyfriend?
Because“.
...my senior year of college,
Cooper and I did a stupid thing.
He got arrested and he went to prison.
So he went to prison. Maybe he got out.
He didn't.
- How do you know?
- Because he's dead.
He hung himself before sentencing.
Felicity...
I just really need to be alone right now.
Oh. I'm glad you're here.
I launched my plan to rebrand Starling
into Star City.
Didn't count on cyber terrorism.
Uh, I'm looking for a partner
with whom to drown my sorrows...
...and you definitely look like someone
who could use a drink.
I'm sorry.
My mother...
I didn't have anywhere else to go.
You Okay?
You're an inventor.
Did you ever create anything
that you didn't think was important...
...turns out...
...it's very important?
Of course.
Those turned out to be the best inventions.
Not always.
You wanna talk about it?
Of course I'd find you here.
- Could you just wait one second?
- Wait?
I've already waited two hours for you
at your apartment...
...and before that,
it was two hours in that club.
Is there any way
that you could be anywhere else but here?
Thanks, Mom.
That wasn't the least bit mortifying.
Only half as bad as Parents' Weekend
freshman year.
Well, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I've been reduced
to stalking my own daughter.
Because you can't seem to comprehend
that I can't make the whole world stop...
...because you decided to show up
on my doorstep.
I have responsibilities.
Yes, I know, Felicity, you have work.
- You have work, work, work...
- No, no, you don't understand.
It is so much more than work.
All you care about is my love life
or how much cleavage I don't show.
- That is not true.
- That is completely true!
I'm sorry that I'm terminally single.
I'm sorry I have an actual job.
I'm sorry that I don't dress like a porn
star, which is a compliment to you.
I am so sorry
that I am such a disappointment to you!
I'm not as smart as you, Felicity,
or your father.
I know that.
When you were only 6 years old,
I could barely keep up with you two.
And...
...maybe I wasn't always the mother
you wanted, but I was always there.
I stayed, and I tried. He...
He left me.
He left us.
But when I look at you...
...all I see is what he gave you.
There's nothing of me...
...in you.
You know, it's so funny, I was...
I was always so afraid that one day
you were gonna leave me too. Heh.
And now I finally realize...
...you already did.
There are people on the other end
of this thing, right? People we can hit?
We need Felicity.
I'm here.
My super virus has
3407 traceable access nodes.
Hopefully, I didn't put a firewall
on every one, though.
Of course I did,
because I'm smarter than that.
Seriously, if I had two less IQ points,
we never would have gotten in this mess.
- Are you all right? Where's your mom?
- I don't know.
Probably back at my place...
...wishing she had a different daughter.
It's a long story.
- Go see her. Take an hour.
- The city is under attack.
You're our best chance of stopping it,
but not like this.
- Your head's not in the game.
- I will get it together.
Your tracer hack's running.
Take an hour. Go talk to your mom.
I do not have anything to say to her.
You know, earlier today, Thea told me
that she literally has to put up with me...
...because family is precious.
And that it's love, in
spite of everything...
...that makes it precious.
Go.
- Where's Sara?
- The nanny came to pick her up.
Said he was from a company called
A.R.G.U.S. I don't know. Never heard of it.
I think that's the point.
Well, I'm glad you're still here.
You are a terrible liar, Felicity.
Might be the only thing we have in common.
I have blond hair.
You dye it.
You're right.
We're different, and it's always
gonna be that way, and it's not easy...
No, you know what?
It's totally my fault
forjust showing up here uninvited.
Seriously, I think I just got so excited
about this free flight.
What?
My plane ticket. I got an e-mail that said
I'd won some contest...
...free first-class round trip to Starling.
E-mail?
Mom. Morn...
...someone wanted you to be here.
- No!
- Mom!
MQfn!
- Baby!
- Mom!
- Are you okay?
- I'm okay.
Oh, thank God.
Where are we? Oh, honey.
Felicity Smoak.
Just the woman I wanted to see.
What the hell do you want from me?
Who are you?
You really don't know?
I thought you never forget your first love.
You died.
They told me...
That I committed suicide, right?
The NSA needed a hacker
with game for cyber espionage...
...and I needed to not be in prison
for the rest of my life.
Because of what the NSA wanted me doing,
it was advantageous for me to be dead.
When I found out you died...
...I was devastated.
I loved you.
I loved you too.
After I finished my time with the NSA,
I was gonna find you.
To let you in on this.
And then I discovered
you'd become this corporate lapdog.
It broke my heart. You changed.
If you thought I was capable of doing this,
you never really knew me at all.
When you wrote this virus, Felicity,
you knew exactly what it was capable of.
All I'm doing is unleashing
the true potential of what you made.
Why?! This isn't who you are.
Five years with the NSA,
you learn a lot about how the world works.
How it can't be saved or salvaged.
How it's every man for himself.
You also learn that when a city bank
goes under, say, financial cyber attack...
...the mayor will reach out
to the Treasury Department...
...and request an influx of fresh cash.
Cash, which is transported
by armored trucks...
...navigating according
to a closed-end GPS system...
...which directs them to City Deposit.
If the drivers deviate from the route,
the trucks are shut down.
But you are going to hack into the system
and direct the cash to come here.
- It was about money, and I'm the sellout?
- No.
No, babe.
You're the one who's gonna help me.
See, breaking into the treasury's
asymmetric encryption...
...is beyond even my capabilities.
I'm going to politely decline.
- Don't!
- That's why I flew some motivation into town.
She's been MIA for over an hour.
You did tell her to go home.
I had an A.R.G.U.S. agent pick up Sara.
- I could have them go back, check things out.
- Yeah.
Felicity's never more than five feet
from her phone.
Agh. Something's wrong.
Ow!
That terminal's configured to only connect
with the treasury's IP.
I mention this so you don't try to do
anything stupid like alert the police.
I'm so sorry.
Mom, right now's
not really the best time, okay?
But it might be the last time, hon,
and I want you to know...
...that all I've ever wanted...
...is for you to be happy.
What say we hit pause
on the Dr. Phil episode?
It's done. It's done.
- That quick?
- There's a reason you wanted me, right?
They'll be at your front
door in five minutes.
Guards will be armed.
- Let's go. Move out.
- I'll take the front.
Stay put, okay?
Just because we used to screw
doesn't mean I won't use this gun.
What's that?
Huh? Oh. Uh...
It's the watch.
It's the watch Mr. Palmer gave me.
It chimes on the hour and, I guess,
when we're about to be killed.
We're not gonna be killed.
We're going to get out of here.
- It basically replaces your computer.
- I don't know what that means.
It means it has Wi-Fi.
Really?
Okay.
When they're in range, you know what to do.
I did what you wanted.
You don't have to kill us.
Really?
Who would've thought
that I'd become the grue?
Hey! Hey.
You wanna wave that gun at me, fine,
but don't you dare threaten my daughter.
Here I thought you were all nails and hair.
Try single mom
who's worked 60-hour weeks for tips...
...in order to raise that genius child
you see right there.
I mean, I don't understand all this
cyber-whatever, but I know without that gun...
...you wouldn't last 10 seconds
against my girl.
Too bad she doesn't have 1O seconds.
I disagree.
Put the gun down.
You were always good, Felicity.
So good.
But so am I.
Motion-sensored.
They can hit most any target.
Come on.
Something's wrong.
All right, boys, light them up!
Clear.
This is all your fault.
No.
Mom, are you okay? Are you...?
On, baby.
Before, you were right
to keep pressing on Cooper.
Turns out he's not as dead as I thought.
I've had some experience with that.
And you learn not to judge.
Yes.
Are you okay?
I guess so.
Old lovers have a way
of opening old wounds.
Lovers.
Sounds creepy no matter how you say it.
Felicity...
...I want you to know that whatever experiences
you had to go through, I'm glad that you did.
They shaped the person you are today.
And you know how I feel about her.
I should head out.
You were right.
We have to love our families.
No matter what.
Felicity.
You here?
What happened to you?
This is me now.
You were right.
Something is going on with me.
And my father, he noticed it as well.
He told me I should open up to someone.
My sister, she...
She died.
Well, she...
She was murdered.
- Did they ever catch the...?
- No. No one knows she's gone except for me.
And I can't tell anyone. So yes.
- Yes, I am angry.
- I'm gonna help you with that.
See, before, you were swinging
at your sister's killer.
That's a target you're never gonna hit.
Don't train for that, all right?
Train for yourself.
See, now I know how to teach you.
So, what's it gonna be?
Red or black?
Black.
Definitely black.
Maybe I'm lost
It was popcorn, right?
You said you were meeting me halfway.
This is me doing my part.
Maybe I'm lost
Wow.
I missed you, Speedy.
Let's not miss each other anymore.
It was so much easier to be in each other's
lives when we were underneath the same roof.
So why don't you move in with me?
I mean, clearly, I have enough space.
And l...
I swear,
once the club starts making a profit...
...I will donate all of Malcolm's money...
...to a earthquake-relief charity thing.
I can live with that.
You got a TV in here?
Well, I'm officially off.
My flight doesn't leave till tonight, but
I figured you'd be working, so we can...
We can just say goodbye now.
You were right.
- About what?
- I haven't always been appreciative of you.
You were always there for me
every day and night.
So if I haven't said thank you enough...
...thank you.
But you were wrong too...
Mm-hm.
...when you said all you saw
in me was Dad...
...and there was nothing of you in me.
I can't really explain it, but over the
past two years, I have been through a lot.
And I have learned
that I am a lot tougher than I thought.
That"
...I get from you.
Don't cry.
I took another look at those
cogeneration numbers. You wanna...?
Oh.
- Hi again.
- Hi.
How's that new smart wearable
working out?
Oh. It's, um...
- it's a real lifesaver. Heh-heh.
- Yeah.
Mm-hm.
Ray, I can't come in to work today.
I am...
...calling in sick.
- "Feel better."
- Heh. Thank you.
See you later.
Yeah, you need to do something
about that one.
Mom. Shh.
That's actually pretty genius.
- Hello, Sara.
- What are you doing here?
Hello, Sara.
What are you doing here?