My name is Oliver Queen.
For 5 years I was stranded on
an island with only one goal--
to survive.
Oliver Queen is alive.
Now I will fulfill
my father's dying wish--
to use the list of names
he left me
and bring down those
who are poisoning my city.
To do this,
I must become someone else.
I must become
something else.
Previously on "Arrow"...
You told me to stay away
from your family and I did.
But your family isn't
staying away from me.
Which means something
must be done about it.
Where can I find the man
in this picture?
Do you not think it convenient
you captured me so easily?
Run!
Uhh! Uhh!
Do you even know
what this island really is?
It's a prison.
What would you do
in my position?
♪ Yes, sir
♪ yeah, yeah
♪ yes, sir
Whatever you're
listening to, it ain't music.
They're ought
to be a law.
Well, there's not.
Watch it!
Back up! Get out of here!
Tahitian green
or midnight black--
what do you think?
I think that you've been
dropping hints all week, Thea,
and mom still isn't buying you
a car for your birthday.
I could not have said it
better myself.
Oliver got a car
when he turned 18.
Yeah, but I could back it
out of the driveway
without hitting a tree.
That's true.
But I do remember you
taking the paint off
the side of your dad's Maserati.
Yeah, the party planner's
waiting.
Sorry to run off like this.
Don't we have
a convertible to go buy?
Good luck.
How's she holding up?
Oh, she's okay.
Thea thinks she's actually
a little bit too okay.
What do you mean?
Just...
behaving erratically.
Shut-in one minute, running
the company the next.
Well, her husband is missing
and presumed who-knows-what.
If anyone had an excuse
to be erratic,
it's your mom.
That's what I told Thea.
...he's too busy
to comment.
The department has got
the same comment about this heist
as it did the other two.
No comment.
The SCPD may not be willing
to go on the record,
but traffic cameras got the
entire heist in this exclusive.
Shortly after 1 a.m., three masked robbers
approached the armored vehicle,
after launching
what appears to be...
That's why you keep
all your money offshore.
forced the guards outside. One of the
guards was prounced dead on the scene.
While the other died on route
to Starling General...
Their identites have
not yet been released.
With all the guys
working up top,
you might want to think
about a side entrance for your, uh,
Arrowcave.
Just put one in.
South alleyway.
Something
I want to show you.
Finally getting into
online dating
and you need help
with your profile.
Not exactly. But there is
somebody I'd like to meet.
Yeah, I read about it.
This is the third truck
to be hit this month.
I saw it on the news
this morning.
I couldn't figure out
why it seemed so familiar.
Then I remembered this.
Kandahar, '09, when the Marines
took out a Taliban transport vehicle.
Yeah. Well, there's a reason
why it looks so similar.
These guys are running the same
swarming technique. Where'd you find this?
I was researching someone.
Bodyguard who works for
a private security firm.
Blackhawk squad protection group.
His name is Ted Gaynor.
Oliver, Ted Gaynor
was my commanding officer
on my first tour
in Afghanistan.
Dig...I'm sorry.
Gaynor's on the list.
Gaynor's a few hundred thousand
dollars short of making your list.
Well, I never said it was
just one-percenters, did I?
Oliver, this guy
saved my life.
Received
a commendation for it.
I don't care what your book
says. He's not a stick-up man.
You haven't known him
in a long time, Diggle.
We both kept in contact with
each other since we got stateside.
6 months ago he even
offered me a job at Blackhawk.
Now, trust me, you don't
know this man like I do.
I know in Afghanistan
his training specialty
was M-32 multiple
grenade launchers,
the exact same weapon
used in these heists
and not exactly
something that you find
at your local
sporting goods store.
Two months ago,
we found out
this wasn't even
your father's book,
that it was written by whoever
hired the other archer.
Doesn't that kind of
beg the question
what else you could
be wrong about?
I could be wrong.
But the list isn't.
Now, I'm gonna have
a pointed conversation
with Mr. Gaynor tonight.
We'll see what he has
to say about it.
I understand if you want
to take the week off.
Well, thank you.
Sir.
Different day, same slop.
You new?
Yeah.
Don't worry.
It took me a year
to find my way
around the island.
Oh, hey, hey. Hey.
I'm supposed to be
transporting a prisoner.
A Chinese guy
who wears a green hood.
Sounds like the guy they took
to the east camp.
I'm heading over that way. Come on.
You can hitch a ride.
Let's go. Come on.
Hold up! Hold up!
Units one, two.
That wall over there still has
to be taped and textured.
I need you to to grout
the hallway floor
as soon as they are done
with the tile install.
All right.
Yeah?
Hey, Tommy.
Dad, I am really busy.
Tommy, I know things
have been, well,
strained between us since...
Since you cut me off
and told me that I was a loser?
I was just trying
to jolt you into adulthood.
And look at you now.
You've got your first job.
My tough love worked.
What do you want, Dad?
Nothing more than
to share a meal with my son.
Dinner tomorrow night?
Laurel and I have plans.
Bring her along.
I think it's time
I got to know her
a little better.
Tommy...
I've said some pretty
hurtful things,
and I regret them.
But you're still my son.
And I still want
what I've always wanted.
For us to be close.
Let me check with Laurel
and I'll get back to you.
Uhh!
Ted Gaynor, we're gonna
have a conversation.
You make a move,
go for a gun, anything,
things will end
badly for you.
Put the bow down.
♪ Arrow 1x11 ♪
Trust but Verify
Original Air Date on January 23, 2013
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
It's all clear.
You okay?
Uh...
Yeah.
Well, I gotta talk
to my boss,
but after...
what I just saw,
I'd say you're
as good as hired.
Hell of a job interview, Ted.
Usually the Vigilante
only goes after rich schmucks.
Any reason why he would
change his M.O. for you?
You've known me
a long time, John.
What do you think?
That he made a mistake.
Got the wrong guy.
I could've shot you.
I could've killed you.
What the hell
were you thinking?!
I'm not gonna let you
William Tell an innocent man.
Gaynor isn't innocent,
Diggle.
You seem to think that mainly because
of what's in you're damn book,
which you apparently trust
more than you trust me.
I trust my father.
And he explained to me
that every name on that list
has a reason to be there.
I thought you took that book
off your father's dead body.
How can he have been
so chatty?
A few years ago,
I found a message he left me
explaining the list.
Oliver,
how is that possible?
You were on
a deserted island.
I didn't say that
I found it on the island.
Diggle, for the past
4 months,
I have lied to,
hurt, and hid things
from all the people
that I care about.
Do you really think that
I would do all of this
if I wasn't sure?
Oliver, listen. Gaynor
got me into Blackhawk,
and I'm gonna prove
he's innocent.
And if he isn't?
If he's not, I'll be the one
to take him down myself.
You owe me that.
You owe me at least that.
Were you stationed
by the perimeter?
Yes.
And your report?
Uh, everything's good, sir.
No trouble.
How long have you
been stationed here?
Just arrived, sir.
Yes, you do seem
rather green.
Although I don't recall
the submarine
bringing in a phalanx
of new troops lately.
Submarine? I thought everybody
came into the island on the plane.
Indeed they do.
I think you've tried on
every dress in the city.
It's so gonna be worth it.
My friends are gonna freak.
Yes, well, if your father were
still alive, he'd freak, too.
Though in an entirely
different way.
Like when he saw what I was wearing
to my first boy-girl dance.
That poor boy
you went with.
Oh, Robert scared him
to death.
You know, dad used to say
his saddest day would be
when I turned 18.
Now he's gone
and I'm the one that's sad.
Sorry.
I need to take this.
Hello.
Yes, I understand,
but I'm with my daughter.
All right.
I'll be there.
I thought you said we were gonna
spend the whole day together.
I know.
But, uh,
compliance needs
to file the 8k
connected to my assuming
Walter's position in the company
and they can't wait.
I'm sorry.
Is everything okay?
You look worried.
Not worried, just...
My father called.
Oh.
And how did that go?
He invited us to dinner
for tonight.
Oh.
Yeah.
Apparently he wants
to mend some fences,
but thanks to him,
I can't afford a fence,
so I can only assume
he's got some other agenda.
Well, there's only one way
to find out.
Maybe he really is trying
to extend an olive branch.
You really do look for the
best in people, don't you?
Lucky for you.
I'm sorry to have to pull you
away from your family like that.
What do you want, Malcolm?
We have a problem with
your friend Carl Ballard.
He's trying to gentrify
the Glades.
Carl knows that's not
part of the plan.
Which is why you're
gonna shut him down.
You're his friend.
He'll listen to you.
If you want me
to help you with Carl,
I want something in return.
Proof Walter's still alive.
My word isn't enough?
What's that saying--
"trust but verify"?
Words to live by.
Two days later, I am still digging
regurgitated tacos
out of the car vents and he asks
me why I won't turn on the A/C.
All right, you win.
Bodyguarding Queen
was never that bad.
6 years serving my country,
the only thing I'm qualified for
is babysitting spoiled brats.
Well, Ted, they're
not all like that.
I haven't met one yet that would
survive a single day in country.
Sometimes it makes me wonder
what I was doing over there.
Specialty of the house.
Thank you, Carly.
No.
Where is my cake?
Tired of listening
to you complain
about the dry cleaners
shrinking your suit.
Oh, yeah.
Mm.
She likes you.
She's my sister-in-law,
Ted.
Not anymore.
Your brother's gone, John.
But you are here.
Car's waiting outside.
Got a client to drop off
at the Chaykin
Art Gallery opening.
John, you remember
Paul Knox?
He was a couple of ranks
under us back in the 'Stan.
Good to be working with you.
I'll be outside.
I didn't know Knox
worked at Blackhawk.
They recruited him when his
tour ended last month.
Mm-hmm.
People change, John.
And everyone deserves
a chance to prove it.
Knocking is not
just a suggestion.
I need to talk to you.
Thea, I'm not telling you
if mom's getting you a car.
It's not about that.
Remember last week
when I asked you
if you thought mom
was acting weird?
Yeah.
Well, I found out why.
She's hooking up
with Tommy's dad.
That's insane.
I just saw them
together.
It's happening
all over again.
What are you talking about?
A couple of months before you
and dad left on the "Gambit,"
mom and dad
were arguing a lot.
About what?
I don't know.
But she was having
a lot of these...
lunch meetings
with Mr. Merlyn.
And now Walter's gone, too,
and mom and Mr. Merlyn
are back at it.
It's gross.
Mom never would have
cheated on dad.
She's not cheating on Walter.
You don't want to believe it
because you have this perfect image
of mom in your head.
That's not who she is,
Ollie.
She's a liar
and a cheater.
And you really
don't know her at all.
She thinks Malcolm and I
are having an affair?
And that it started
back when dad was still alive.
Why would she think that?
She says you and dad
were fighting.
Mom...
It's not your concern,
sweetheart.
Thea made it my concern.
What was going on?
Robert was unfaithful
to me repeatedly.
It made our marriage
difficult, to say the least.
I'm sorry, Oliver,
but your father
wasn't always the man
you thought he was.
I know you thought
he walked on water,
but, you see, that how I wanted you
to remember him--
as a good man
who loved you.
That's how I want Thea
to remember him.
So promise me
you'll keep it a secret.
Of course.
Mom.
Yes?
Why would Thea think
that you and Mr. Merlyn
are still sneaking around?
Well, I can't imagine.
Have you seen him lately?
Oliver...
He's been the CEO of Merlyn Global Group
for years.
I've been running
Queen Consolidated mere weeks.
Yes, I occasionally
go and ask for advice.
Is my interrogation over?
See, this is where we, uh,
detain prisoners
prone to running off
before I've finished with them.
Uhh!
Prisoners like you,
Mr. Queen.
At Christmas one year,
Tommy wanted a puppy.
He wanted to name it
Arthur,
as in King Arthur,
because he's a Merlyn.
Well, you used to be
so incredibly adorable.
I still am.
My wife would have
liked you, Laurel.
I wish I would have
known her.
She passed away before
Tommy and I became friends.
She was killed, Laurel.
There's no need to be polite about it.
You're just a ray of sunshine
today, aren't you, Dad?
Please forgive me.
Talking about my wife has a tendency
to make me a little bit
maudlin.
And here I was beginning
to think my days of being
Oliver Queen's personal
computer geek were coming to an end.
Is that your way
of saying you miss me?
No. But if it works
for you, go with it.
Heh. So a friend of mine
is running a scavenger hunt,
and there's a case of
Lafite Rothschild 1982 waiting at the end.
Oh...I love red wine.
But in order to find it,
I first need to get
through this.
Hmm. Security fob.
It's pin protected.
Challenge response goes back
to a company called
Blackhawk Squad
Protection Group.
Yeah, my friend had
his bodyguard set it up for him.
Personally, however,
I think it's cheating. But whatever.
This is a military-grade
cryptographic security protocol.
Your friend really
went to all this trouble?
The idle rich
are hard to entertain.
Listen...
You get through it and one
of those bottles of wine is yours.
This been lovely,
Mr. Merlyn. Thank you.
Thank you for joining me.
It's been wonderful
getting to know you better.
And if Tommy doesn't mind me
mixing a little business with pleasure,
I could use your signature
on these.
You want to shut down
mom's free clinic?
It's not hers anymore,
Tommy.
That clinic meant
everything to mom.
You were 8 years old.
I don't think you were in a position
to know what was important
to your mother.
I just need your signature--
Stop.
This dinner
was never about
getting to know Laurel.
It was about this.
You haven't changed
and you never will.
It's about time
that I learned that
and stopped letting you
disappoint me.
We're leaving.
This clinic
was his mother's.
Yes.
And his mother taught him a lesson
I've been trying to,
that the world is a harsh
and unforgiving place.
And when did she
teach him that?
When she was lying dead
in the street
with a bullet in her head.
Good night.
Management keeps things
running smooth, which is nice.
Better than going to war
with the army you got, right?
Indeed.
So, Ted, are you the reason Knox is
working for Blackhawk?
Look, I know you don't
like the guy.
I wasn't his biggest fan,
either,
but jobs are hard to come by
for everybody these days.
And guys like us,
when all anyone thinks you're
qualified for is shooting at people--
if I hadn't gotten Knox
this job,
chances are he'd be out
knocking over liquor stores
or robbing banks.
What did you get?
I think your friend's bodyguard
gave him the wrong security fob.
Why is that?
Well, once I got past
Blackhawk's authentication system,
there wasn't anything
about a scavenger hunt.
Just a directory and...
Well, I think
you stumbled onto,
or got me to stumble onto
something pretty illegal.
Define illegal.
Oh, you know.
Robbing an armored car
with grenade launchers
and tear gas.
What?
Someone at Blackhawk
was using their system to store
detailed routes and schedules
for each of the city's
7 major armored car carriers,
including the 3
that have already been hit.
Mr. Queen, I think we should
provide this information to the police.
With it, they should be able
to predict the next heist.
Hold on. Felicity, I don't want
to get you in trouble with my friend,
so do me a favor.
Forward that directory on to me
and I'll get it
to the police personally.
Thank you.
So, no wine, then?
Uhh! Uhh!
Knox, he's hurt!
Let's go! Let's go!
Aah! Oh, God, check it out!
Check it out! Convertible.
You must be so surprised.
Oh, isn't everything
absolutely perfect?
Except for
dad were here.
If dad were here,
he'd say you look
beautiful.
Oh! Excuse me a sec.
I heard the Hood foiled
an armored car heist this evening.
Gaynor wasn't running
the rocket launcher.
I know. I was with him
the whole time it was going down.
It looks like
you were right.
Listen, if someone
at Blackhawk is involved,
I'd put my money on Knox.
He started right before
the heists began,
and he has military
training.
Okay. I injured one.
He was bleeding pretty badly
when they made off in their van.
Okay, so if any of Knox's
blood is in one of the motor pool vans,
I'm going with you.
We'll know for sure.
No, no, no, listen.
You have this party.
And I told you
I would handle this.
If there's any problems,
you're just a phone call away.
Hey.
Head on a swivel.
That's the way
I was born, man.
Happy Birthday!
I'll miss you!
We have a special
birthday gift for you.
It's called Vertigo. It's supposed
to make you feel all floaty.
Uh, if my mom
caught me with this,
I wouldn't make it to 19.
I'm gonna
go put it upstairs,
and then I'll be
right back down.
♪ Come on down
Moira, I have a little
something for you.
Walter...
I did as you asked.
Now it's your turn
to do as I asked.
I'll take care of it.
Thank you, Moira.
At my party.
Right here in front of me?
No, Thea,
you don't understand.
Walter hasn't been gone
two months
and you're already
cheating on him.
Just like you did on dad.
Thea, I never cheated.
Like I would believe
anything you say.
No. I wish it had been you
that was on that boat.
I had a feeling
you'd show up.
Yeah? Why is that, Knox?
Right after Gaynor
got you hired,
someone hacked
our system.
First person to ever
make it through our firewall.
You want to tell me
how you did it?
I'm not really sure.
He didn't think you'd be
very cooperative.
Who?
Hey, John.
Ted, you're part of this?
No, not part of.
My men. My mission.
Mission?
This isn't Afghanistan.
Oh, don't I know that.
Over there we were trusted
with millions of dollars
in weapons and personnel.
We were conquerors.
Now we're nannies
with tasers.
So that gives you
the right to steal,
to kill innocent civilians?
I'm not gonna convince
you I'm right.
I am gonna convince you
to join the team.
Yeah, now I know
you're crazy.
Earlier tonight
was supposed to be our last score,
but because of the Hood
guy, we struck out.
Now we're down a man.
Good thing you're
qualified to take his place.
Ted, I think your convincing
is gonna have to be
a lot more convincing.
Copy that.
Cavanaugh.
Carly.
You son of a bitch.
Kill her.
No!
Don't! Don't! Wait!
Don't.
Knox.
You both can die
tonight, John.
Or once we do this,
we're on a plane
and she can go home
to your nephew.
It's your call.
Well, you shouldn't have
done that, Dig.
Now you gotta watch us
kill your pretty little girlfriend.
No! Please don't!
You're forgetting
one thing, guys.
Oh, yeah,
what's that?
I'm the one
with the grenade.
Carly, get out of there!
Freeze!
Drop it, Ted,
or I swear...
Don't...posture.
You're not gonna do it.
You can't.
I can see it
in your eyes.
You're late.
You knew I was coming?
Next time you plant
a bug on someone,
be more subtle
about it.
I wish you
trusted me, though.
I trust you, Diggle.
But them, never.
You should get
out of here.
John!
Carly. You okay?
Turn around and put your hands
where I can see them.
Oh, Thea.
Are you okay?
Yeah. Yeah. I'm fine.
I'm just headachy, really.
The car--is--is it--
Thea, the car isn't
important right now.
Do you remember
what happened, sweetheart?
You go away.
Thea, please.
I said I'm fine.
Now, when Larry shows up
tonight,
you gotta show him
and Janet that he doesn't--
Your father's even
beginning to call me now.
Don't waste your minutes.
Your father is a jerk,
but he's still your father.
They're broken up.
They're not gonna
get back together ever.
I think in his own way,
I think he sees himself
as protecting you somehow.
Yeah. He is really good
at using my dead mother
for an excuse
for being a jerk.
You never talk
about your mother.
I was only 8 and I
don't remember much
about what happened.
But after...
My father completely
shut me out.
And then he went away.
He was gone for maybe
a year or two.
I was 8 and he left me.
That is who my father is.
He only cares about himself.
Cops give you a hard time?
Nah. I explained to them to me and
Gaynor were old war buddies.
He tried to rope me in...
When I refused,
he kidnapped Carly,
everything else
happened under duress.
I screwed up, Oliver.
Obviously Gaynor
wasn't who I thought he was.
I was wrong.
Yeah, but...
you were right, too.
When you told me
that I trusted the list
more than I trusted you...
Diggle, the truth is, after what
happened to me on the island...
It's difficult for me
to trust...anything.
But you do.
And that reminded me
why I chose you as my partner.
It's because you see
the best in people.
I learned something, too.
Until you tell me,
I'll never want to know
what other names
are in this book.
She promised me she's
not cheating on Walter.
Like I would trust
anything that woman says.
Miss Queen!
Thea Queen?
Is there a problem?
We received a call
from your doctor.
In the event
of a vehicular accident,
they're required
to report to result
of the driver's
tox screen.
Miss Queen tested positive
for a narcotic called Vertigo.
The drug they're using
in the Glades?
Thea Queen, you're under arrest
for driving under
the influence of narcotics.
Do you know why my men
wear balaclavas, Mr. Queen?
Because it masks
everything but the eyes.
In a man's eyes, one can
always find the truth.
You risked everything
to save your friend.
Someone I warned you about,
yet you trusted him.
But that trust was misplaced.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==