MY NAME IS OLIVER QUEEN.
AFTER 6 MONTHS IN HELL,
I HAVE BEEN RELEASED FROM PRISON
AND RETURNED HOME
WITH ONLY ONE GOAL...
TO SAVE MY CITY,
BUT THINGS HAVE CHANGED.
INSTEAD OF OPERATING
OUTSIDE THE LAW,
I AM NOW WORKING
ALONGSIDE THE POLICE.
I AM NO LONGER INMATE 4587.
I AM ONCE MORE THE GREEN ARROW.
PREVIOUSLY ON "FLASH"...
MAN: DR. JOHN DEEGAN,
USE THIS BOOK
TO RESHAPE THE WORLD
AS YOU SEE FIT.
[ENERGY HUMMING]
I CAN SEE EVERYTHING.
IRIS: BARRY,
ARE YOU OK?
I'M BARRY.
[GRUNTING]
I'M OLIVER QUEEN.
MAYBE IT'S JUST EARTH 1
THAT'S BEEN AFFECTED.
IF WE CAN GET
TO EARTH 38 AND FIND KARA,
IF SHE REMEMBERS US,
THEN MAYBE SHE CAN HELP FIX
WHATEVER'S HAPPENING.
KARA: WHOA, LOIS.
WAIT, WAIT.
THIS IS BARRY AND OLIVER.
THEY'RE FRIENDS.
SO YOU KNOW
THAT I'M OLIVER
AND HE'S BARRY?
-WHY WOULDN'T I?
-WE COULD USE YOUR HELP.
CISCO: I VIBED SOMEBODY
IN THE SPEED LAB,
SOME GUY WITH RIDGES
ON HIS HEAD.
I KNOW WHERE TO FIND HIM.
SO WHAT'S OUR
NEXT MOVE?
WE'RE GOING
TO GOTHAM CITY.
[THUNDER]
CURTIS: OHH!
OK. I KNOW THIS SOUNDS NUTS
AND COMPLETELY UNSCIENTIFIC,
BUT I THINK THAT FREAKING
LIGHTNING IS FOLLOWING US.
JOHN: FOCUS, CURTIS.
CURTIS: THIS IS ME FOCUSING.
THESE ATMOSPHERIC ANOMALIES
ARE PLAYING ALL KINDS
OF HELL ON MY EQUIPMENT,
PLUS YOU DON'T WANT
THAT LIGHTNING TO HIT
WHEN YOU'RE ENGAGING
DEATHSTROKE'S SON.
[BOOM]
I JUST HAD TO SAY IT.
JOHN: KANE WOLFMAN,
YOU'RE UNDER ARREST
FOR 19 VIOLATIONS
OF INTERNATIONAL LAW!
REALLY? DOES THAT
INCLUDE THE MURDER OF...
4 A.R.G.U.S.
FIELD AGENTS?
LAST CHANCE!
ON THE GROUND NOW!
THIS ISN'T PERSONAL.
JUST BUSINESS.
[ARROWS RELEASED]
SON OF A BITCH.
IS THAT ANY WAY TO
GREET YOUR FRIENDS?
JOHN: ALL I KNOW
IS THAT WHENEVER
THE THREE OF YOU SHOW UP,
IT USUALLY MEANS WE HAVE
ONE HUGE PROBLEM.
SO YOU'RE YOU.
AND YOU'RE YOU.
AN IMMORTAL EGYPTIAN,
ALIENS, PARALLEL EARTH NAZIS.
I HAVE NO IDEA WHY
I'M EVEN SURPRISED
AT THIS POINT.
CURTIS: I'M STILL TRYING
TO FIGURE OUT IF THIS IS
MORE LIKE "FREAKY FRIDAY"
OR "QUANTUM LEAP."
NO. IF THIS WERE
LIKE "QUANTUM LEAP,"
I'D ONLY LOOK
LIKE MYSELF
IN THE MIRROR.
YEP. YOU ARE
DEFINITELY NOT
OLIVER QUEEN.
WE THINK THAT
THE RED SKIES
AND THESE LIGHTNING STRIKES
HAVE TO BE RELATED
TO WHATEVER HAPPENED TO
BARRY AND OLIVER SOMEHOW.
WE NEED YOU TO SOLVE
THE SOMEHOW WHILE
WE'RE IN GOTHAM.
NO PROBLEM.
I MEAN, A.R.G.U.S. HAS
ALL THE BEST
ANALYTIC TOYS,
BUT WHAT WE REALLY NEED
IS A PATTERN RECOGNITION
ALGORITHM,
AND, UNFORTUNATELY,
FELICITY ISN'T...
-I CALLED FELICITY.
-WAIT, WAIT.
-YOU CALLED FELICITY?
-YEAH.
OK. RIGHT. WELL,
I GUESS THAT MAKES SENSE
BECAUSE TECHNICALLY,
YOU ARE HER HUSBAND.
I'M CONFUSED.
FELICITY:
I'VE BEEN SUMMONED?
-YES. THANK YOU FOR COMING.
-OF COURSE.
I MEAN, THINGS MIGHT
BE FRAUGHT BETWEEN US,
OLIVER.
THAT DOESN'T MEAN I'M
NOT GONNA SHOW UP.
THEY ARE? THEY ARE?
THEY ARE. YEAH,
WHICH IS...SAD.
SO, UM, THIS
LIGHTNING THING.
UM, COULD YOU HELP
ME OUT WITH THAT?
CAN I KIND OF SHOW
YOU KIND OF WHAT
I'M THINKING?
-YEAH.
-OK.
OK. SO WHY DIDN'T
YOU TELL FELICITY?
WELL, BECAUSE WE TRIED
TO TELL EVERYBODY
AT S.T.A.R. LABS,
AND IT DIDN'T REALLY
GO OVER SO WELL.
OLIVER: FELICITY AND I HAVE
ENOUGH PROBLEMS AS IT IS
WITHOUT INTRODUCING
BODY SWAPPING.
WE THOUGHT WE'D JUST
LET HER THINK EVERYTHING'S
NORMAL AND THAT BARRY
AND I ARE SOLVING
ANOTHER PROBLEM.
KARA: IF YOU FIND OUT
HOW THIS LIGHTNING THING
RELATES TO WHATEVER IT IS
THAT WE'RE DEALING WITH HERE,
CAN YOU PLEASE TELL US?
JOHN: COPY THAT.
HEY. THIS THING ISN'T
GONNA BE PERMANENT, IS IT?
-I HOPE NOT.
JINX.
OH. BARRY, THERE'S
SOMETHING I'D LIKE TO
DISCUSS BEFORE WE GO.
-WHAT'S THAT?
-THAT YOU PROBABLY SHOULDN'T GO.
WHAT?
OLIVER QUEEN IS
A PUBLIC FIGURE
AND AN INFAMOUS VIGILANTE.
IF YOU ARE IN GOTHAM CITY,
YOU'RE ATTRACTING
THE TYPE OF ATTENTION
THAT WE DON'T WANT.
NO. IF...IF GOTHAM
CAN HANDLE
THE BATMAN,
IT CAN HANDLE
THE GREEN ARROW.
THE BATMAN'S
AN URBAN LEGEND.
WAIT. YOU
DON'T BELIEVE
BATMAN'S REAL?
HE'S NOT REAL.
HE'S AN URBAN LEGEND
CONCOCTED BY THE GOTHAM
POLICE DEPARTMENT
TO SCARE CRIMINALS.
AND I'M THE ORIGINAL
VIGILANTE, BARRY.
OK, IF YOU GUYS ARE DONE
FOOLING AROUND...
ACTUALLY, YOU KNOW
WHAT? COULD YOU
PULL THAT THING UP?
BECAUSE, UNLIKE YOU,
MY IDENTITY'S
NOT PUBLIC,
AND I'D LIKE TO KEEP
IT THAT WAY.
THIS ISN'T YOUR REAL FACE!
IT MIGHT END UP
BEING MY REAL FACE
IF WE DON'T SORT
THIS MESS OUT,
SO COULD YOU?
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
-HAPPY?
-ECSTATIC.
APPARENTLY, YOU GUYS
AREN'T DONE FOOLING AROUND.
WELL, I GUESS
I'M RUNNING ALONE.
BARRY: HO HO HO!
THAT IS SO AWESOME.
SO THIS IS GOTHAM.
DOESN'T LOOK
SO TOUGH TO ME.
WHERE'S OLIVER?
HUH. I DON'T KNOW.
GUESS HE'S STILL GETTING
THE HANG OF IT.
YEAH.
HA HA HA!
I'M STILL GETTING
THE HANG OF IT.
KARA: ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT.
SO HOW DO WE FIND
TWO PEOPLE
IN A CITY
OF 1.6 MILLION?
THERE IS A RADIO
PERSONALITY NAMED
VESPER FAIRCHILD.
SHE KNOWS EVERYONE
IN GOTHAM,
AND I KNOW HER.
SHE WAS DOING AN EXPOSÉ
ON WHITE-COLLAR CRIME
BACK IN THE DAY,
AND I WANTED TO PERSUADE HER
THAT QUEEN CONSOLIDATED
WAS ABOVE BOARD.
SO YOU SLEPT
WITH HER, RIGHT?
NO. I...I DON'T KNOW.
GOSH. YOU REALLY GOT
AROUND BACK IN THE DAY,
DIDN'T YOU?
OH. ONE TIME,
OLIVER CHEATED
ON HIS GIRLFRIEND
WITH HER SISTER.
-BARRY!
-OH, NO! OHH!
WHAT?
YOU DID!
SO, WHAT, DEPENDING
ON THIS PAST RELATIONSHIP
WITH THIS WOMAN,
WE MIGHT HAVE TO COME UP
WITH A PLAN "B."
IS THAT WHAT
YOU'RE SAYING?
-YEAH.
-GUYS!
TAKE A LOOK
AT THIS.
YOU STILL THINK
HE'S A MYTH?
YEAH! COME ON.
[WHISPERING]
BATMAN'S REAL.
OLIVER:
IF I REMEMBER RIGHT,
THE RADIO STATION
WAS THIS WAY.
I'M SURPRISED THEY
PUT IT IN THE BAD
PART OF TOWN.
IT'S CUTE HOW YOU
THINK THERE'S
A GOOD PART OF TOWN.
[HORN HONKS]
BARRY: LOOKS LIKE
THE ONE PERCENTERS
BRING THE GOOD PART
WITH THEM.
THIS IS WHY NOBODY
TALKS ABOUT GOTHAM, OK?
CITY MIGHT AS WELL
BE DEAD.
MAN: SOUNDS LIKE
YOU GUYS AREN'T
FROM AROUND HERE.
PROBABLY DON'T KNOW,
BUT GOTHAM TOURISM BUREAU
COLLECTS A TAX
ON OUT OF TOWNERS,
SO PHONES, WALLETS,
WATCHES NOW.
YOU KNOW WHAT, FELLAS?
I...WE DON'T WANT
ANY TROUBLE,
SO MAYBE WE CAN JUST
TALK THIS OUT, OK?
HA HA HA!
TALK IT OUT.
OK. I'LL TALK FIRST.
HEY!
AGH!
[COCKS GUN]
[SIRENS]
KARA: OH, GREAT.
ON THE GROUND NOW!
ALL OF YOU,
ON THE GROUND!
SHOW ME YOUR HANDS!
OH, CRAP.
I NEED SWAT
AT NOLAN AND BURTON.
GREEN ARROW SIGHTED AT
NOLAN AND BURTON.
SIR, WE DON'T WANT
ANY TROUBLE.
YEAH. TELL THAT
TO OLIVER QUEEN HERE.
OLIVER: OLIVER,
STAND DOWN.
[MAN COUGHING]
PATTERN RECOGNITION ALGO
IS LOCKED AND LOADED.
BRINGING IT
ONLINE NOW.
YOU REALIZE THAT THIS
MAY NOT WORK, RIGHT?
LIKE, THERE MAY NOT BE
A PATTERN TO RECOGNIZE.
IS THERE A SUGGESTION
BOUND WITHIN THAT DOSE
OF PESSIMISM?
DOES THE ENERGY
DISCHARGE
OF THE LIGHTNING
LOOK FAMILIAR
TO YOU?
THE QUANTUM AMPLITUDE
IS CONSISTENT WITH
A DIMENSIONAL BREACH.
EXACTLY. WE'RE GONNA
NEED CISCO'S HELP
ON THIS ONE.
CISCO:
I'VE BEEN SUMMONED!
OK. THAT WAS
A DISTURBINGLY
COINCIDENTAL ENTRANCE.
IT WASN'T
COINCIDENTAL.
WE'D BEEN GETTING
THE SAME RED SKIES
AND FREAKY LIGHTNING
IN CENTRAL CITY,
AND I'LL TELL YOU THIS MUCH...
IT WASN'T SPEED FORCE.
FELICITY: WAIT, WAIT.
HOLD UP. "WE'D BEEN,"
"WASN'T,"
AS IN PAST TENSE?
CAITLIN: INTERESTINGLY,
THE ATMOSPHERIC
PHENOMENON CEASED
THE MOMENT BARRY
AND OLIVER LEFT
CENTRAL CITY.
IT'S LIKE IT PACKED UP
ITS BAGS AND FOLLOWED
THEM HERE.
THAT'S WHY WE CAME.
CAITLIN: THE PHENOMENON
HAS TO BE RELATED TO
BARRY AND OLIVER'S...
-OK, CAITLIN. OK?
-BODY SWAP?
AHEM. DON'T...
DON'T SAY...AHEM.
I'M SORRY.
BODY...BODY WHAT?
YOU, UH...YOU
DIDN'T TELL HER?
FELICITY: AGAIN,
TELL ME...HEH...WHAT?
[SIRENS]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
OLIVER: UM, EXCUSE ME,
OFFICER.
WERE YOU ABLE TO GET
IN TOUCH WITH LAUREL LANCE
AT THE STAR CITY
D.A.'S OFFICE OR...
YEAH. SHE SAID, UH,
"I THINK A NIGHT
IN JAIL
WOULD DO THEM
SOME GOOD."
OLIVER: HEH.
WHAT WERE YOU
THINKING?
THAT YOU WERE ABOUT TO
GET YOURSELF SHOT.
-YOU'RE WELCOME.
-I WAS DEESCALATING
THE SITUATION,
YOU KNOW, LIKE, UH...
-LIKE I WOULD?
-UH-HUH!
GUESS WHAT, MAN.
I HANDLED IT EXACTLY
HOW YOU WOULD!
KARA: OK. YOU GUYS,
MAYBE TAKING ON EACH
OTHER'S PERSONALITIES
WORKED FOR AMAZO,
BUT YOU WERE NOT GONNA
TALK YOUR WAY OUT
OF GETTING MUGGED,
AND YOU ESCALATED
THE SITUATION
WAY TOO FAST.
SO WHAT WOULD YOU
HAVE DONE?
WHAT I WOULD
HAVE DONE
IS SUPERSPED US
RIGHT OUT OF THERE.
ALL THEY WOULD HAVE
SEEN IS A GUST
OF WIND.
OLIVER: I MEAN, HINDSIGHT
IS 20/20,
BUT WE'LL FOLLOW
YOUR LEAD NEXT TIME.
BECAUSE THERE WILL
REALLY BE A NEXT TIME
WHEN SOMEONE THREATENS
3 SUPERHEROES
WITH A GUN.
OFFICER: GOOD NEWS.
SOMEBODY POSTED
YOUR BAIL.
-WHO?
-I DON'T KNOW.
GUESS SOMEONE WANTED
TO MAKE YOU GUYS
THEIR HEADACHE
INSTEAD OF MINE.
WE'LL SHOW
OURSELVES OUT.
PLEASE COME WITH ME.
BARRY: I'M GUESSING THIS
BELONGS TO WHOEVER
BAILED US OUT.
I REALLY THINK
WE'VE HAD
ENOUGH DISTRACTIONS
FOR ONE NIGHT.
YEAH. I AGREE
WITH MY FRIEND.
WE APPRECIATE
THE EARLY RELEASE, WHATEVER,
BUT WE'RE REALLY FINE
ON OUR OWN.
I'M AFRAID
MY EMPLOYER INSISTS.
[SIGHING]
OK.
AND YOU SAID IT
WOULDN'T HAPPEN AGAIN.
BRUCE WAYNE GOT
US OUT OF JAIL?
DOESN'T SOUND
LIKE HIM.
NO, IT WASN'T.
WAYNE LEFT GOTHAM
3 YEARS AGO.
WHY?
TO GO WHERE?
NO ONE KNOWS.
SO WHO'S MANNING
THE SHOP NOW?
APPARENTLY AFTER
HE LEFT, BRUCE'S
BOARD OF DIRECTORS
WENT TO TOWN WITH
A BUNCH OF AGGRESSIVE
GET-RICH-QUICK DEALS.
BARRY: YEAH,
BUT AN ABANDONED BUILDING
DIDN'T BAIL US
OUT, RIGHT?
WHOA. THAT IS
DEFINITELY NOT
BRUCE WAYNE.
OLIVER QUEEN.
OLIVER: AHEM.
BARRY: YEAH, YEAH.
I'M OLIVER QUEEN. YEAH.
-AND YOU ARE?
-THE RAIN ON YOUR PARADE.
IF YOU'RE VISITING GOTHAM
TO COMPARE GRAPPLING HOOKS
WITH BATMAN, YOU ARE
OUT OF LUCK.
NO ONE'S SEEN HIM
IN YEARS.
[WHISPERING]
TOLD YOU.
MYTH.
BARRY: I WOULD NEVER COMPARE
MYSELF TO A TOTAL BADASS
LIKE BATMAN.
WHAT I THINK
OLIVER IS
TRYING TO SAY
IS THANK YOU
FOR GETTING US
OUT OF JAIL.
OLIVER: WHAT OLIVER'S
ACTUALLY TRYING TO SAY IS
WHO ARE YOU,
AND WHY ARE YOU
HELPING US?
GOTHAM HAS ENOUGH PROBLEMS
WITHOUT A GUY
IN GREEN LEATHER
SHOWING OFF HIS ARROWS
TO EVERYONE,
SO THE FASTER YOU FIND
WHAT YOU'RE LOOKING FOR,
THE FASTER YOU CAN GET
THE HELL OUT OF MY CITY.
UH, BUT, WHAT...WHAT
SHOULD WE CALL YOU...
RAIN, MS. PARADE?
KANE, KATE KANE.
[WHISPERING UNDER BREATH]
SHE'S COOL.
YOU DIDN'T TELL HER?!
OLIVER...THE ACTUAL
OLIVER THOUGHT THEY HAD
ENOUGH PROBLEMS
WITH FELICITY ALREADY.
OH, AND YOU DIDN'T
THINK TO LOOP US IN
ON THE FACT THAT YOU
WERE KEEPING
THE "FREAKY FRIDAY"
SITUATION ON THE HUSH?
I WAS THINKING IT WAS
MORE LIKE "QUANTUM LEAP."
CISCO: NO. IF THIS WERE
LIKE "QUANTUM LEAP,"
THEY'D ONLY LOOK LIKE
THEMSELVES WHEN THEY SEE
THEMSELVES IN THE MIRROR...
IT DEPENDS ON
WHAT TYPE OF
QUANTUM LEAP...
SHOULDN'T WE CONCENTRATE
ON WHAT THIS LIGHTNING
CAME FROM?
-RIGHT?
-RIGHT, BUT...
CURTIS: OH. AHEM.
FELICITY: OK, GUYS. YOU DON'T
NEED TO TIP-TOE AROUND ME.
IT'S JUST A LOT
TO PROCESS.
IT'S NOT EVERY DAY
THAT YOU FIND OUT
THAT YOUR EX
IS YOUR HUSBAND
AND VICE-VERSA.
CISCO: YEAH. IRIS WAS,
PRETTY FREAKED OUT, TOO,
WHEN SHE SUSSED IT OUT.
FELICITY: WAIT. IRIS.
YOU KNOW, ACTUALLY,
JOHN...RIGHT BEFORE
YOU CAME IN,
JOHN WAS JUST SAYING
THAT WE NEED TO REALLY
HANDLE THAT LIGHTNING...
FELICITY: IRIS WAS ABLE
TO TELL THAT SOMETHING
WAS OFF WITH BARRY?
-NO, NOT EXACTLY.
-OH, TOTALLY. I MEAN,
IT WAS LIKE LOVER'S INTUITION.
-STOP.
CISCO: THAT'S HOW YOU CAN
TELL THESE TWO WERE...
YOU KNOW, FELICITY, UM,
THERE'S SOMETHING VERY
STRANGE GOING ON HERE,
SO I WOULDN'T TAKE THIS
AS A COMMENTARY
ON YOU AND OLIVER'S
MARRIAGE.
NO. MY MARRIAGE
WITH OLIVER IS STRAINED
BY THE FACT THAT WE'VE
BECOME DIFFERENT PEOPLE...
QUITE LITERALLY
IN OLIVER'S CASE.
[SNAPS FINGERS]
IF THE LIGHTNING STRIKES
ARE ATTEMPTED
DIMENSIONAL BREACHES,
THERE MIGHT BE A WAY TO
STABILIZE THE QUANTUM FLUX
TO ALLOW WHATEVER'S
TRYING TO GET THROUGH
TO GET THROUGH, RIGHT?
CURTIS: YEAH. OF COURSE.
CAITLIN: YEAH.
YOU GUYS TRY
FACIAL RECOGNITION?
ONE OF BRUCE'S R&amp;D GUYS
STILL WORKS IN THE BUILDING.
I CAN GIVE THIS
TO HIM.
OLIVER: UH, WE DID TRY IT,
SO THANK YOU,
BUT NO LUCK.
BESIDES, I'D THINK
IF WAYNE'S R&amp;D'S
IN THE SAME SHAPE
AS THIS BUILDING,
IT'S NOT GONNA REALLY
DO US ANY GOOD.
SUIT YOURSELF.
SEEMS STRANGE,
DOESN'T IT,
THAT BRUCE WAYNE
AND BATMAN
DISAPPEARED
FROM GOTHAM AROUND
THE SAME TIME.
KATE: WELL, WHEN BATMAN
LEFT, THE CITY WENT
TO 5 DIFFERENT KINDS
OF HELL,
WHICH FOR GOTHAM IS
REALLY SAYING SOMETHING.
TOOK A TOLL ON BRUCE.
IS THAT WHY HE LEFT?
STILL TRYING TO
FIGURE THAT OUT.
OLIVER: RIGHT, BUT YOU
WORK FOR HIM,
AND YOU DON'T KNOW
WHY HE LEFT?
WHO SAID I WORK
FOR HIM?
[DOOR OPENS]
HOW'D IT GO
WITH VESPER?
BARRY: SHE HUNG UP
ON ME.
APPARENTLY, I DID
SLEEP WITH HER.
KARA: HMM.
KATE: OK. THE BUILDING IS
UNDER RENOVATION,
SO THIS IS
THE BEST PLACE
FOR YOU GUYS TO
WORK OUT OF.
OH, AND THE, UH,
WI-FI PASSWORD'S "ALFRED."
SO IF VESPER'S NOT
GONNA HELP US,
WE'RE JUST BACK
AT SQUARE ONE.
NO, WE'RE NOT.
I LIFTED THIS OFF
OF A COMPUTER
AT THE PRECINCT.
IT SHOULD HAVE
THE ENTIRE GCPD DATABASE.
YOU STOLE DATA
FROM THE POLICE?
NO. NO. THE FLASH
DID IT.
-IT'S NOT FUNNY.
-I'M NOT LAUGHING.
[KNOCKING]
DID YOU LOSE THE COIN FLIP
ON WHO HAS TO COME
TALK TO ME?
WE DIDN'T FLIP COINS.
WE DREW STRAWS.
I'M KIDDING.
ACTUALLY, I WANTED
TO COME TALK TO YOU
BECAUSE I THINK I'VE
GOT A LITTLE BIT
MORE EXPERIENCE
WITH ALTERNATE REALITIES
THAN YOU DO.
SO WHAT WORDS OF WISDOM
DO YOU HAVE FOR ME?
THAT IRIS PROBABLY
HAS A LITTLE BIT MORE
EXPERIENCE, AS WELL,
AND MAYBE THAT'S WHY
SHE WOULD HAVE SEEN
SOMETHING THAT
YOU DIDN'T.
AS FOR OLIVER KEEPING
YOU IN THE DARK,
WHEN HE AND BARRY
TRIED TO TELL US WHAT
WAS GOING ON WITH THEM,
WE KNOCKED THEM
UNCONSCIOUS AND LOCKED
THEM IN THE PIPELINE.
-SERIOUSLY?
-WASN'T OUR FINEST MOMENT.
LOOK. I'M SURE THAT
THAT'S THE REASON
THAT OLIVER DIDN'T
WANT TO TAKE ANY
CHANCES WITH YOU.
I APPRECIATE YOU
SAYING THAT...
BUT IT'S JUST ANOTHER EXCUSE
IN A LONG LIST OF EXCUSES
FOR OLIVER'S BEHAVIOR.
OLIVER DOES LOVE YOU,
FELICITY.
YEAH? WELL, WHAT'S LOVE
WITHOUT RESPECT OR TRUST?
I DON'T KNOW,
BUT AS LONG
AS THERE IS LOVE,
YOU CAN'T GIVE UP
ON IT.
THAT'S THE ONE THING
I DO KNOW
AFTER EVERYTHING
I'VE BEEN THROUGH,
EVERYTHING
I'VE SUFFERED.
[EXHALES]
THANK YOU.
WELL, ONE GOOD THING
ABOUT WHAT'S GOING ON
IS THAT I HAVE SOMETHING
TO DISTRACT ME.
LOOK AT THIS.
-THAT LOOKS LIKE...
-A QUANTUM FLUX ANCHOR.
I'M PRETTY SURE
IF WE BUILD IT,
WHOEVER'S TRYING
TO BREACH THROUGH WILL COME.
LET'S GET TO WORK.
[TYPING ON KEYBOARD]
KARA: YOU REALLY KNOW
YOUR WAY WITH A COMPUTER.
WELL, WHEN I WAS
FIRST STARTING OUT,
I HAD TO HOLD MY OWN
BEFORE FELICITY
SHOWED UP.
GOT HIM.
JOHN DEEGAN.
KARA: OH. ILLEGAL
EXPERIMENTATION, TORTURE.
HMM. SEEMS LIKE HE WAS
CONDUCTING EXPERIMENTS
ON HIS OWN PATIENTS' BRAINS.
SOUNDS LIKE
A REAL CHARMER.
WELL, HE WAS ACQUITTED.
ALL THE CHARGES
WERE DROPPED
ON TECHNICALITIES.
SO WHERE CAN WE
FIND HIM NOW?
-NO KNOWN ADDRESS.
-WHAT ABOUT EMPLOYMENT?
WELL, HE WAS FIRED,
SUSPENDED
BY THE MEDICAL BOARD
FOR TWO YEARS,
BUT THAT WAS...
5 YEARS AGO.
-SO NO IDEA WHERE TO FIND HIM.
-NO.
EXCEPT SOMEWHERE
IN GOTHAM.
NEEDLE IN HAYSTACK.
-ALL RIGHT.
-WHERE YOU GOING?
I'M GONNA PUT ON
MY WORK CLOTHES
AND DO AN X-RAY FLYBY
OF THE CITY.
I DON'T THINK MISS KATE
WOULD BE TOO THRILLED
WITH US RUNNING
AROUND HER CITY.
WELL, UNLESS SHE
HAS SOME KRYPTONITE
STASHED SOMEWHERE,
I'M REALLY NOT WORRIED.
KATE: HEH. YOU LOST?
NO. NO. UM, JUST
NEEDED TO CLEAR
MY HEAD FOR A SEC.
ACTUALLY, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M SORRY
ABOUT THE THIRD DEGREE
EARLIER.
I GUESS THE NAME
BRUCE WAYNE CARRIES
A CERTAIN NOTORIETY.
OH, I KNOW.
BRUCE WAYNE'S MY COUSIN.
YOUR COUSIN?
THAT MAKES
A LOT OF SENSE.
ACTUALLY, I'M
IN THE PROCESS
OF TURNING THIS BUILDING
INTO A REAL ESTATE
DEVELOPMENT FIRM,
SO THIS IS
ME HIJACKING HIS OFFICE.
MY COUSIN'S ACTUALLY
FRIENDS WITH BRUCE.
UM, WELL, FRENEMIES.
-HMM.
-HEH.
DO YOU EVER WONDER
IF TRYING TO KEEP
HIS PRIVATE LIFE
FROM THE PUBLIC EYE
JUST GOT TO BE
TOO MUCH FOR HIM
AND HE BROKE?
HEH. SITTING
AT THAT DESK,
STARING
OUT THAT WINDOW,
WATCHING THIS CITY
THAT WE GREW UP IN
ROT AT ITS CORE,
YOU FIND A WAY
TO NOT BREAK.
BRUCE DIDN'T LEAVE
GOTHAM WITHOUT A FIGHT.
HMM.
YOU KNOW, I GOT TO SAY,
ALL THE CORPORATE
BILLIONAIRES I KNOW
WEAR VERSACE AND HAVE
500 FEWER TATTOOS.
HMM. THOSE ARE THE ONES
THAT YOU CAN SEE.
WELL, THAT'S A MYSTERY.
OH. IS THIS THE...
THE OLD BARD HIMSELF? HA!
HEY. YOU...YOU
WOULDN'T HAPPEN TO KNOW
A JOHN DEEGAN, WOULD YOU?
I WOULD, ACTUALLY.
HE'S A DOCTOR
AT ARKHAM ASYLUM.
AH. I HAVE TO GO
TELL THE BOYS.
UH, HEY. THANKS
FOR THE HELP
AND THE CHAT.
JOHN: HEY, WHAT
THE HELL IS THIS?
FELICITY: NO OFFENSE,
BUT YOU'D NEED LIKE
5 Ph.D.s FOR
THE DUMBED-DOWN VERSION.
HOW ABOUT THE VERY
DUMBED-DOWN VERSION?
IT'S A QUANTUM FLUX ANCHOR
THAT UTILIZES WAVE THEORY
TO FIRE NANO-PARTICULATES
ACROSS
AN EINSTEIN-ROSEN BRIDGE
TO CREATE
A SECURE CLAXON FIELD.
HOW ABOUT THE VERY,
VERY, DUMBED-DOWN
VERSION?
FELICITY MADE A MAGNET
THAT WILL DRAW WHOEVER'S
TRYING TO BREACH THROUGH
TO US.
JOHN: YOU COULD HAVE
JUST SAID THAT.
ALL RIGHT.
FIELD'S STABLE.
ALL READINGS ARE IN THE GREEN.
YOU GUYS ARE GOOD TO GO.
[THUNDER]
[WIND BLOWING]
I'M READING MULTIPLE
QUANTUM SURGES.
I DON'T THINK
THIS IS WORKING!
THIS IS WHAT WORKING
LOOKS LIKE!
MAN, VOICE CUTTING IN AND OUT:
CA...YOU...HEAR ME?
YOU'VE GOT...TO...
GET...BOOK.
JAY?
[VOICE CUTTING IN AND OUT]
ONLY...BOOK...MAKE THIS RIGHT.
IF YOU GET THE BOOK,
YOU CAN FIX THIS.
AM I THE ONLY ONE WHO
THOUGHT THAT WAS VERY COOL?
SO WE'RE SURE
HE WORKS HERE?
WELL, IT'S PROBABLY
TOO LATE FOR HIM TO
STILL BE AT WORK,
BUT IF WE FIND
HIS OFFICE, MAYBE
WE CAN FIND
HIS HOME ADDRESS
OR SOMETHING.
DO YOU THINK YOU HAVE
ENOUGH OF A GRIP
ON YOUR POWERS
TO DO A SUPERSPEED
RECONNAISSANCE?
I DON'T THINK THAT
WE SHOULD RISK IT
IF I DON'T.
OK. WELL, THEN,
WE BREAK IN,
DO SOME
OLD-FASHIONED
SNOOPING.
OLIVER: OHH!
BARRY: AAH!
AAH!
-GOT NEW INTEL.
-THOSE LIGHTNING STRIKES,
THEY WERE A FLASH
FROM ANOTHER DIMENSION
TRYING TO BREACH TO US.
CISCO: WE THINK IT WAS
JAY GARRICK
OR A JAY GARRICK.
HE SAID TO FIX
THE SITUATION,
WE HAVE TO
"GET THE BOOK."
KARA: JOHN DEEGAN
WAS READING A BOOK
IN THE DRAWING
OLIVER DREW.
OK. SO WE FIND
THE BOOK IN THERE
OR WE FIND DEEGAN,
AND WE MAKE HIM
TELL US WHERE IT IS.
BARRY: WAIT, WAIT.
HOLD ON. ANOTHER FLASH
FROM A PARALLEL UNIVERSE
JUST LIGHTNINGS IN,
TELLS US TO JUMP,
AND WE ASK, "HOW HIGH?"
IF WE WANT TO SORT
THIS THING OUT, THEN YES.
OLIVER: I HAVE NO IDEA
HOW WE'RE GONNA BREAK
INTO A MENTAL ASYLUM.
I HAVE SOME IDEAS.
NURSE:
UH, HOW CAN I HELP YOU?
NEW PATIENT TRANSFER
FROM GOTHAM CENTRAL HOSPITAL.
DR. DANVERS SAID ARKHAM WAS
THE MORE APPROPRIATE PLACE
TO TREAT HER...
CONDITION.
WHAT'S THE DIAGNOSIS?
PERSISTENT SUBTHERMAL
HOMEOSTASIS
WITH, UH, INVOLUNTARY
GELID SUBSTANTIATION.
SHE GETS COLD
AND FREEZES STUFF.
[ICE CRACKS]
YEAH. WE GOT A FEW OF THOSE
IN HERE LIKE THAT.
-FILL THIS OUT.
-OK.
WE'LL TAKE IT
FROM HERE.
OFFICER ALLEN,
IT REALLY IS VERY...
THIS IS A GCPD-A.R.G.U.S.
OPERATION.
WE DON'T NEED YOUR HELP.
JOHN: WHEW.
BARRY...I MEAN,
OLIVER, LOOK.
JOHN DEEGAN.
OLIVER QUEEN!
HA HA! WHEW.
IT'S A GENUINE PLEASURE
TO MEET YOU, SIR.
[SOFTLY] HE KNOWS
WHO YOU REALLY ARE.
GENTLEMEN,
I WAS THINKING,
"WHY DID I NOT BECOME
THE FLASH?"
AND IT SEEMS
CHANGING REALITY ITSELF,
IT'S GOT A BIT
OF A LEARNING CURVE,
SO, YEAH.
THIS ACTUALLY EXPLAINS
A LOT.
YOU DID THIS TO US?
YOU CAN UNDO IT.
THAT IS TRUE,
BUT I THINK THE QUESTION IS,
UM...WHY WOULD I
WANT TO?
[ALARM BLARING]
WHAT THE HELL DID
HE JUST DO?
HE BOUGHT HIMSELF
SOME TIME.
[ALARM BLARING]
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
TROUBLE.
THE CRAZY BASTARD LET
ALL THE OTHER CRAZY BASTARDS
OUT OF THEIR CAGES.
ALL RIGHT.
GET THE PATIENTS BACK
IN THEIR ROOMS
AND FIND THAT BOOK.
[PEOPLE GRUNTING]
FINALLY, THE INMATES
ARE RUNNING THE ASYLUM.
JOHN: NOT FOR LONG!
WOMAN: FRIES, FRIES,
FRIES, FRIES.
COME ON. WHERE IS IT?
ARE YOU OK?
MY CRYOSTASIS SHUT OFF
WHEN THE LOCKS DID.
I...I NEED
TO BE COLD.
196 BELOW ZERO.
196, HE SAID.
HOW DOES THIS THING WORK?
OK. MAYBE YOU SHOULD
JUST TAKE A STEP BACK.
JUST GET AWAY FROM ME!
OHH. YOU COLD BITCH.
UNH!
AAH!
AGH!
NO SIGN OF DEEGAN
OR THE BOOK.
WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU SUPPOSED TO BE?
[TIRES SQUEAL]
NICELY DONE. FLOOR IT.
AAH!
WHO'S THIS BADASS?
AGH.
THAT'S...NOT BATMAN.
KATE KANE TOLD YOU
TO GET OUT OF GOTHAM.
YOU SHOULD HAVE
LISTENED TO HER.
KARA: GUYS, I'VE BEEN
ALL OVER THIS PLACE,
AND I CAN'T FIND ANYTHING.
GUYS, I COULD USE
A LITTLE BACKUP.
ON IT.
OLIVER: ON IT.
[SHUDDERING]
THERE YOU ARE.
TOOK THE WORDS RIGHT
OUT OF MY MOUTH.
SLIPPERY.
LISTEN TO ME.
CAITLIN.
BARRY: WAIT. NO, OLIVER.
HEY. REMEMBER WHAT
HAPPENED IN CENTRAL...
OLIVER!
[COUGHS]
MALCOLM MERLYN:
OLIVER'S NOT HERE.
IN FACT...
NO ONE'S COMING
TO SAVE YOU.
YOU SHOULD HAVE KILLED
ME WHEN YOU HAD
THE CHANCE.
YOU LEFT ME TO DIE
ON LIAN YU.
UNFORTUNATELY FOR YOU...
HEH HEH...I DIDN'T.
[GRUNTING]
DOES ANYBODY COPY?
BECAUSE...I THINK WE HAVE
A NEW PROBLEM.
COME ON. YOU CAN DO
BETTER THAN THAT.
YOU'RE A KILLER,
A DEPRAVED MONSTER
WHO FOUND A WAY TO
CHANNEL HIS DARKNESS
AND PAT HIMSELF
ON THE BACK FOR IT!
YOU'LL NEVER BEAT ME.
TOO SLOW, BIG HEART.
MAMA RAISED YOU RIGHT,
SO RIGHT,
YOU COULDN'T STOP ME
FROM KILLING HER.
YOUR FATHER TOOK
THE COWARD'S WAY OUT,
AND ALL THESE YEARS,
YOU TOLD YOURSELF
IT WAS BRAVE,
BUT HE WAS A COWARD
JUST LIKE YOU.
A FAILURE.
SELFISH.
SLOW.
PATHETIC.
WHO THE HELL ARE YOU?
NO. SERIOUSLY,
WHO ARE YOU?
YOUR FRIENDS WERE EXPOSED
TO A POWERFUL HALLUCINOGEN.
ARE YOU GUYS
ALL RIGHT?
DEFINE ALL RIGHT.
SO HOW DOES
A BOOK MAKE PEOPLE
CHANGE BODIES?
DEEGAN SAID HE WAS
USING THE BOOK
TO CHANGE REALITY.
CISCO: SAME QUESTION.
HOW DOES A BOOK
CHANGE REALITY?
WE'LL FIGURE THAT OUT
WHEN WE GET BACK
TO STAR CITY.
GUYS, WE'RE GONNA NEED
SOME HELP WITH THIS LOCK.
GOOD. THEN
YOU'LL BE LEAVING GOTHAM.
YOU GUYS HAVE CAUSED
ENOUGH PROBLEMS
FOR ONE NIGHT.
HEY. WOULD HITCHING
A RIDE IN THE BATMOBILE
BE OUT OF THE QUESTION?
GET...OUT.
SURE.
KARA: SHE REALLY IS LIKE BATMAN.
BARRY: YEP.
I DON'T DO
TEARFUL GOOD-BYES.
NO. I...I JUST WANTED
TO WISH YOU LUCK.
WHEREVER YOUR
COUSIN IS,
I'M SURE HE'S REALLY
PROUD OF YOU.
X-RAY VISION.
YOU REALLY DO HAVE
A LOT OF TATTOOS.
SOMEHOW, I FEEL LIKE
KARA DANVERS DOESN'T
HAVE A SINGLE ONE.
YOU KNOW, IT'S SUCH
A SHAME I HAVE TO GO
BECAUSE I FEEL LIKE
WE WOULD MAKE
A GOOD TEAM.
WORLD'S FINEST.
HEH HEH.
FELICITY: OH. LOOK WHO
FINALLY CAME BACK.
WITH WHAT LOOKS LIKE
A FAIRLY INFAMOUS BOOK.
CAITLIN: A BOOK WITH
A CRYPTOGRAPHIC LOCK ON IT.
OLIVER: CAN YOU
GET TO WORK ON
OPENING IT, PLEASE?
JOHN: WE DON'T HAVE
A LOT OF TIME.
OK. GEEK SQUAD,
FORM UP ON ME!
NOT MUCH
OF A HEARTFELT REUNION.
SHE'S GETTING USED
TO EVERYTHING.
DO YOU WANT ME TO
TALK TO HER AS,
YOU KNOW, YOU?
I THINK I'M IN ENOUGH
TROUBLE WITH FELICITY
AS IT IS,
BUT NO OFFENSE.
HEY. CAN I TALK TO YOU
FOR A MINUTE, THEN?
-YEAH. WHAT'S UP?
-I JUST WANTED TO SEE
HOW YOU'RE DOING.
I'M COMPARTMENTALIZING.
I'LL FIX THINGS
WITH FELICITY LATER.
I DON'T MEAN
WITH FELICITY.
WE BOTH SAW SOME STUFF
BACK AT ARKHAM.
I SAW EVIL FLASH.
EOBARD THAWNE.
I SAW MALCOLM MERLYN.
-OH.
-I KNEW YOU'D BEEN
THROUGH A LOT,
BUT...
I DON'T KNOW, MAN.
I NEVER REALIZED.
I DON'T KNOW
HOW YOU DO IT.
I WOULDN'T BE
ABLE TO LIVE
WITH THE BURDENS
THAT YOU CARRY.
YES, YOU WOULD.
BARRY, I ALWAYS THOUGHT
THAT YOU HAD IT EASY,
EVERYTHING WAS JUST
SUNSHINE AND RAINBOWS
AND...EVERYBODY LIKES YOU.
YOU HAVE REAL STEEL
IN YOU, MY FRIEND.
YOU CAN CARRY ANY BURDEN
THROWN YOUR WAY.
SOME UNSOLICITED
ADVICE?
HMM.
DON'T WAIT TO
WORK THINGS OUT
WITH FELICITY.
OUR LINE OF WORK,
YOU NEVER KNOW HOW
MUCH TIME YOU GOT.
NOT ONLY IS THE LOCK
CRYPTOGRAPHIC...
IT'S METAPHYSICAL.
THE READINGS I'M
GETTING OFF THIS THING
ARE NUTS...AND, YES,
THAT'S A TECHNICAL TERM.
OLIVER: UM, MAY I SPEAK
WITH FELICITY FOR A MINUTE?
CISCO: SURE THING, BARRY...
OLIVER...BOLIVER.
CAITLIN: STOP HELPING.
THIS MUST BE STRANGE
FOR YOU.
OH. WHAT GAVE YOU
THAT IDEA?
I DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE IT'S EASIER
FOR YOU TO HEAR THIS
COMING FROM...
[WHISPERS] BARRY ALLEN.
HEAR WHAT?
THAT WE'RE GONNA BE OK.
PEOPLE CHANGE, FELICITY.
IT MEANS WE'RE GROWING.
IT MEANS WE'RE
EVOLVING,
EXCEPT FOR ONE THING,
ONE THING THAT
WILL NOT CHANGE...
IS HOW I FEEL
ABOUT YOU.
LOVE IS TOO SMALL
A WORD...
AND NO MATTER WHO YOU ARE
OR...OR WHAT YOU BECOME,
NO MATTER WHO I AM
OR...OR WHAT I BECOME...
YOU WILL ALWAYS BE...
YOU WILL ALWAYS BE
THE LOVE OF MY LIFE.
PEOPLE CHANGE.
THAT NEVER WILL.
OLIVER, I...
[THUNDER]
BARRY: JAY?
-NO.
-OH, MY GOD. DAD?
MY NAME IS BARRY ALLEN.
HELLO, JOHN.
DO...DO I KNOW YOU?
YOU'RE NOT WEARING
YOUR RING.
THINGS MUST BE
DIFFERENT HERE.
OLIVER: BARRY,
WHERE'S THERE?
MY EARTH, EARTH 90.
I'VE TRAVELED FROM THERE
TO WARN YOU.
-WARN US ABOUT WHAT?
-HIS NAME IS MAR NOVU,
BUT HE CALLS HIMSELF
THE MONITOR NOW.
HE'S BEEN UNLEASHING
THE BOOK OF DESTINY
ACROSS THE MULTIVERSE
TO TEST DIFFERENT EARTHS.
TEST THEM FOR WHAT?
A CRISIS THAT HE
BELIEVES IS COMING.
NOVU THINKS
THE ELSEWORLDS CREATED
BY THE BOOK OF DESTINY
APPROXIMATES
THE COLLISION OF REALITIES
THAT WE'RE FACING.
GUYS...
WE GOT A SITUATION.
CISCO.
THAT...THAT'S HIM
FROM THE VIBE.
BARRY: MAR NOVU,
YOU'RE GONNA
STAND DOWN.
YOU'RE GONNA USE
THAT BOOK TO HELP US
SET REALITY RIGHT.
WELL, I CERTAINLY
WOULDN'T HAVE PLACED IT
IN DEEGAN'S HANDS
IF THAT WERE MY INTENT.
ENOUGH.
YOU WILL NOT DO
TO THIS EARTH
WHAT YOU DID TO MINE.
I ADMIRE YOUR
PERSISTENCE, BARRY.
HE SAID YOU WERE
TESTING US.
MONITOR: INDEED,
AND THUS FAR,
I AM UNIMPRESSED.
A CRISIS IS IMMINENT.
SOMEONE IS COMING,
SOMEONE FAR, FAR MORE POWERFUL
THAN MYSELF.
I MEAN TO PREPARE.
BY GIVING A NUT BAR
AN ALL-POWERFUL
REALITY-REWRITING
BOOK?
I AM TESTING UNIVERSES
TO FIND ONE, I HOPE,
STRONG ENOUGH TO STAND
AGAINST HIM.
YOU'RE CAUSING CHAOS,
AND YOU'RE BLAMING
EVERYONE ELSE!
IN THE HOPE OF FINDING
THE CHAMPIONS
THAT WOULD SAVE
THE MULTIVERSE ENTIRE.
YOU ARE THE FIRST OF THOSE
I'VE PLACED UNDER FIRE
WHO HAVE MANAGED TO RETRIEVE
THE BOOK OF DESTINY...
FOR ALL THE GOOD
IT DID YOU.
ENOUGH OF THIS.
KARA?
YEAH. I'D LOVE TO.
MONITOR: YOU SHOW POTENTIAL.
LET US SEE IF IT'S
ANYTHING MORE.
WHAT IS HE TALKING
ABOUT, BARRY?
I OFFERED YOU GODHOOD,
AND YOU SQUANDERED IT
ON A PETTY DREAM.
DO BETTER.
THINK BIGGER.
OHH.
[ENERGY CRACKLING]
WHAT THE HELL?
WHERE'D HE GO?
HE WENT TO GIVE
DEEGAN THE BOOK...BACK.
HOW DO YOU KNOW?
HE DID IT AGAIN.
HE REWROTE REALITY.
HOW FAR DO YOU THINK
THE CHANGES GO THIS TIME?
[SIREN]
-FREEZE!
-ON THE GROUND!
NOW!
UH...SPEED US OUT OF HERE.
I CAN'T.
CAN YOU?
NOPE.
OLIVER QUEEN.
I'VE BEEN WAITING
TO DO THIS
FOR A LONG TIME.
DIAZ: UNH!
BARRY: AAH!
SHOULD I FOLLOW YOU? WHAT...
HEY!
[WHOOSH]
THERE'S NO PLACE YOU CAN RUN
WHERE I CAN'T FIND YOU.
IT'S OVER.
MAN: GREG, MOVE YOUR HEAD.