My name is Oliver Queen.
After five years
on a hellish island,
I have come home
with only one goal--
to save my city.
But to do so, I can't be
the killer I once was.
To honor my friend's memory,
I must be someone else.
I must be
something else.
Previously on "Arrow"...
Time to choose, Oliver,
who lives and who dies.
You got what you came for!
Time's up.
No!
I guess you made your choice.
Ivo killed Shado
because of me.
Nothing good comes from telling
Slade that you think you're responsible
for the death
of the woman he loved.
The man who killed Shado
is still out there.
Not for long.
Because we're going
to take the freighter.
We're all going
to die here, just like him.
No, we're not. I think I found our way
on to the freighter.
A parachute.
I'd like you to meet
Slade Wilson.
It's a pleasure to meet you...
Mr. Queen.
What are you
doing here?
Mr. Wilson just made
a sizeable contribution
to my campaign.
How generous of him.
Well, I felt compelled.
It was the least
that I could do for your mother.
And what this city needs
is a pro-business mayor
like Moira to spread growth
through urban investment.
And we were just discussing how
to combat the rising wage gap.
And the answer lies
in your budget proposal.
You know, when I look
at your mother,
I think about everything that you
went through after the quake.
All I can say is, you and
I have something in common.
What's that?
I know how difficult
it is to pick yourself back up
when other people
have written you off.
Indeed.
What's wrong, Mr. Queen?
You look a little piqued.
I'm fine,
thank you.
Ah, thank you, dear.
Oliver, Mr. Wilson
was kind enough to bring
a bottle of authentic
Australian rum.
Will you join us
in a drink?
Yes, of course.
Wonderful.
What shall
we drink to?
To friendship.
Oh, delicious.
This here
is a beautiful piece.
Tell me, does your family spend
much time on the water?
Uh, no.
Not since my late husband.
I'm sorry, Moira,
forgive me.
I do remember reading about that
accident in the paper.
You were a brave soul.
I don't like
to talk about it.
I can understand.
All that time on that island...
It must have been
hell for you.
Shado
would be proud.
Thank you.
But those trees don't move,
or shoot back. Ivo's men
on the freighter will.
Then shoot first.
♪ Arrow 2x15 ♪
The Promise
Original Air Date on March 5, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Ivo's freighter
is located here.
He keeps eight men
on deck. Three on the starboard,
three on the port
and two up in the bridge.
But our bigger concern
are these GP 25 grenade launchers
that they're walking
around with at all times.
Do they have
night vision?
Not according to blondie.
That smells awful.
It'll taste
even worse.
But it'll work?
I spent a year
with Anthony Ivo.
I know how he thinks.
It'll work.
Hey, what about
the Mirakuru?
Well, what about it?
Well, look,
I mean, it can cure,
I don't know,
maybe anything.
Maybe...Maybe
it's a miracle drug.
But it's also something else.
Something that people like Ivo
should never be allowed
to control.
What about Slade?
He might not let us.
Might not
let you do what?
You think we should
destroy the Mirakuru?
This thing doesn't
go our way...
We can't let
Ivo have it.
You're right.
We should burn it.
Anthony devoted his
entire life to finding this.
Nobody even thought
it was real.
It was his dream.
Did he ever say why?
He wanted
to save the world.
We need
to talk about tomorrow.
About what to do with Anthony
once we take the freighter.
What do you mean?
Because Slade
wants to kill him.
I'm not going
to let that happen.
No, Slade wants to
kill him for Shado.
Oliver, you don't
know him like do.
Look, if he's
given the chance,
then he's going
to turn this around.
He's going to make
Slade think
that it's your fault
that she's dead.
That you chose
to save me instead of her.
You can't give him
that chance.
Sara...
I can't.
You've killed before.
That's not what
you are talking about.
You are talking about
executing somebody in cold blood.
Look, Slade has the Mirakuru in him.
He's unstable.
If he loses control;
If he snaps again,
then we're both dead.
You have to kill Ivo.
Who's thirsty?
Where'd
you get that?
Who cares?
Let's drink it.
Ahh, this is one of the few
precious pieces of cargo
to survive the crash.
Billy Wintergreen and I were
planning on saving it for a rainy day
but considering,
God willing,
this is our last night
on the island...
To taking
the freighter.
To getting off
this island forever.
To Shado.
Mmm.
You know, if something
happens to me tomorrow...
You can't
think like that.
If I don't make it...
I need you to...
To tell my mom and my sister
that I wasn't that same,
stupid kid that got
on that boat.
Tell them I was different.
Ok.
And if I don't
make it...
Tell my family that I died
on "The Gambit."
Why?
Let them remember me
the way that I was.
We should all
get some sleep.
I've missed you.
Shado?
How are you
still alive?
I'm not alive.
Remember?
I'm dead.
Because you chose Sara over me.
Why didn't you choose me?
Why didn't you choose me?!
Rise and shine,
kid. It's time.
Glaza zmei!
Better luck next
time, Hendrik.
You cheat!
He cheats!
So do you.
He just cheats better.
Get up,
preacher boy.
I said get up,
coward!
Ivo wants
to see you.
Have faith, my friend.
God will protect you.
There is no God.
If there was...
He's not on this ship.
How is she?
I'm sorry, Anthony.
I wish I had better
news to give you,
but her condition is progressing
quicker than we anticipated.
Have you tried
upping her dosage?
Twice already,
but we both know
modern medicine
has its limitations.
Oh, yes, I know quite well.
Thank you, Doctor.
No. No, wait.
Wait, Mr. Ivo.
My family is Bratva.
Russian mafia.
They pay millions for me.
I'm sorry, I have very
little use for money.
I do, however,
require an eye
for my research.
Well, we don't have all day.
There's a breeze.
They're
on the beach.
Take them.
Alive.
What about him?
They're coming.
Two men, armed.
You know, when
we first tried
to get off
this island,
it was as strangers.
But now it's
as brothers.
See you on the freighter.
Right over there.
Ohh!
You're lucky
Ivo wants you alive.
I told you
I'd come back.
Fantastic.
We're saved.
He likes you.
Don't worry,
he won't bite.
Reverend Thomas Flynn.
Oliver Queen.
This is Abraham.
I remember you from
before. You escaped.
With that blonde whore.
That's Hendrik.
He's a charmer.
Yeah, I hope
she rots in hell.
Hey, Sara was a prisoner,
just like all of us.
Right.
Funny, I never
heard her scream.
How long have you
been here, Thomas?
A little
over a year.
I was working
as a missionary
in Maliku, just off
the coast of India.
This ship docked
there for supplies,
Dr. Ivo asked me
to come aboard
to administer last rites
for a dying man.
My mistake.
I'm sorry.
Don't be.
Can you imagine a better place
for a man in my line of work?
Prochnost.
Mr. Queen.
Welcome back.
My men are still
searching the beach
for your friend
and Sara.
They have
the Mirakuru.
So...
Where are they?
Go to hell.
Maybe you'd like
to rethink that.
Ivo...You torture me
all you want to.
I am never going
to tell you where they are.
No. Not willingly.
What is that?
Oh, this?
See, this is
sodium pentothal.
Its more colloquial,
yet very descriptive name,
is truth serum.
No, wait, wait!
No, no,
I'll tell you everything!
Let's begin.
Are you married,
Mr. Wilson?
Do you have
any children?
Sadly neither.
Well, there must be
someone special in your life.
There was.
But she passed away
a few years ago.
I'm sorry.
My mother and I have had
to deal with a lot of loss,
unfortunately.
And eventually we learned...
That you just have to move on.
I don't believe that.
You know, I heard
that your family
has an affinity
with the fine arts.
Yes, my husband
amassed quite the collection
of 19th century
American landscapes.
Hmm. I'd love to see them.
Maybe another day.
We have some family business
that we need to discuss right now.
I'm sorry. My son
seems to have forgotten
all his manners.
Let me just get my staff to open up
the rest of the house.
Thank you.
Mom?
Ollie?
Not yet, kid.
I'm still going to meet
the rest of your family.
Hello?
Hey, Ollie, have
you and mom talked,
'cause this whole
not speaking thing...
Thea, now is not
a good time.
Who's your friend?
Slade Wilson.
It's a pleasure
to meet you.
I've heard such wonderful
things from your mother.
About me.
Thea, what perfect timing.
This is  Slade Wilson, and I--
They've met.
...was just about
to show him our collection.
But you're far
better suited. Come.
Oh.
Senior year, I was
obsessed with art.
My teacher made me
bring my entire art history class
over here
to show our pieces.
It was exactly
as mortifying as it sounds.
Oh, I'm sure
it wasn't.
But you're a very lucky girl to have
known such privilege.
And I am fortunate
to have your entire family here.
Oliver.
Oliver, what's
your name?
Oliver Jonas Queen.
Oliver, where
were you born?
Starling City.
Why did you build
a bonfire on the beach?
So you'd see it.
I told you.
Was the bonfire
a trap?
Not a trap.
It was a...
a distraction.
How was the bonfire
a distraction?
Where are Sara
and Slade right now?
Where are they?!
They're on the freighter.
Where on
the freighter?
They're in the engine room
because we have a raft.
Sound the alarm.
I want every man
on this freighter
down in that engine room.
Search the entire
floor. Go!
Oliver Jonas Queen.
It'll taste even worse.
But it'll work?
I spent a year with Anthony Ivo.
I know how he thinks.
It'll work.
What is it,
exactly?
Cocculus indicus.
It's a natural source of picrotoxin,
which will counteract
effects of barbiturates--
like sodium pentothal.
Ivo's favorite. But you still got to
act stoned to sell it.
Lucky for me. Before all this,
I had a lot of practice.
They're
clearing the decks.
The top of the ship's
emptying.
Are you ready?
You really don't want
an honest answer to that.
But you've done
this before, right?
Nobody's
done this before!
Here, I think
these belong to you.
We're on a clock,
and she needs to
free the prisoners.
Ivo sent his men to the engine room
just like we planned.
More convenient for me
to take them out.
Go find Ivo.
He can't get off this ship.
But don't kill him.
Son of a bitch is mine.
And here we have
a Curtis Swan from 1882.
Fun fact about this one-
he actually painted it with his left hand
due to severe arthritis.
It's absolutely
exquisite.
I know. I can't tell you
how many offers we've had
from private collectors for it.
But it was
one of dad's favorites.
Wasn't it, Ollie?
Yes, it was.
He loved that one.
Then you must
never sell it.
I believe that when
we lose someone we love,
we have the obligation
to honor their memory.
Oof.
I think eventually
I'd hit something.
Be patient.
Ollie makes it look easy.
Is anyone going
to get that?
I'll take that
as no. No worries.
No matter where I go,
I'm just answering phones.
Hello?
Oliver?
Well, I do think
we have been butt dialed.
And here
is a Joseph Cooper from 1890.
Hey, that's Thea.
That's gorgeous.
Wait, hold on.
I know that voice.
I actually have a painting from his
first solo exhibition in Boston.
Oh, God, no.
Who is that?
His name is Slade Wilson.
And unless we stop him,
he's going to kill Oliver
and his entire family.
We have to move. Now.
Are you sure it was
Slade Wilson?
I thought he was dead.
I'm sure.
That's not a voice
I'd ever forget.
What's the biggest gun
you got down here?
That might work.
Might?
He has
the Mirakuru in him.
So do I.
Can I trust you?
I'll be fine.
Slade was a trained killer
even before he was injected.
You get the chance,
you get a shot, you put him down.
Please save Oliver.
Why are you doing this?
I'm with Oliver now.
Why should I believe you?
Because you don't
want to die! Go!
You helped that maniac
torture us.
No!
Follow me.
Where's Ivo?!
He's heading to the bridge!
Answer the phone.
Hello?
Jessica,
it's me.
Who?
It's Anthony.
Anthony.
I was married
to a boy named Anthony.
I know,
sweetheart.
But he went away.
I went to find a cure.
And I found one,
sweetheart.
I found it, and soon,
we're going to be--
He was a doctor,
but he went away.
It's harder than
it looks, isn't it?
Killing an unarmed man.
It seemed pretty easy when
you murdered Shado.
I didn't murder her, Oliver.
Ivo, you shot
her in the head!
I gave you a choice!
You chose Sara.
You blame me,
but that's because
you can't face your own guilt
I loaded the bullets, yes,
I pulled the trigger.
But you...
you aimed the gun.
And you hold yourself
responsible.
Don't you?
Yes.
But that doesn't mean
I won't kill you.
The question is...
What will he do?
Is it true?
Tell me.
Slade, I tried
to tell you...
Tell him, Oliver.
I was angry,
like you are right now.
And I wasn't thinking clearly.
Shut up!
I acted rashly;
I told him to choose
between Shado and Sara.
Don't listen to him.
He's a monster,
he will say anything.
You know that he will!
Tell him I'm lying, Oliver.
Say it.
I can explain...
You've known...
Slade...
Please...Ivo.
He's dead.
As dead as you are.
Aah!
How many?
This one time,
you can pray for me.
Behind you!
Ollie! Are you ok?
Where's Slade?
He knows!
We've got to get off this ship!
No!
Ollie, it's over!
It's over!
We've got to go! We can still swim
back to the island.
She's right!
We must hurry!
Slade, wait...
Stop. Don't move.
Get in the cell.
I do not take orders
from you.
I am this ship's Captain.
Not anymore.
This is my ship now.
Any objections?
Slade Wilson
is dangerous.
No chances, no mistakes.
I'm in position.
When Slade comes out,
I'll have the shot.
Felicity?
Thermal imaging's
coming up now.
They're in
the northwest hall.
Roy, remember, just get
Thea and Moira away from Slade.
Don't start a fight,
you'll lose. Ok?
Ok.
Let's go.
Thank you again
for such a wonderful
and insightful tour.
You were a remarkable guide.
Did you have
a favorite?
I found "The Promise"
to be particularly
compelling.
Thea, you home?
Roy! I thought I was
meeting you at Verdant.
Oh, yeah.
Uh, this is, uh--
I'm Roy Harper.
Slade Wilson.
That's a particularly firm
handshake you have there, son.
Yeah, you, too.
Ollie.
There you are.
Sara, we didn't
hear you come in.
I didn't want
to interrupt the tour.
Mr. Wilson, this is my son's
friend Sara Lance.
Of course.
You're the girl who came back
from the dead.
Ah, we're just glad
to have her home.
Well, I can see.
I mean, it's hard
to find that special someone
who means
everything to you.
You were very lucky.
So...
What would you like to do now?
Mr. Wilson.
Well, I'd hate
to break up the party...
But I think
I should be going.
I look forward to seeing more
of you, Moira.
Oh.
And your
lovely family.
Dig's got a shot
lined up outside.
Mr. Wilson.
May I walk you to your car?
Cyrus gold,
the men in the skull mask,
all this was you.
They worked for you.
Well, I have my allies,
just as you have yours.
John Diggle, for example.
I suppose you're wondering
why he hasn't taken his head shot.
Don't worry.
He's still alive--for now.
Slade.
What
do you want?
Five years ago,
I made you a promise.
Do you remember?
Well, I'm here
to fulfill it.
I'll see you
around, kid.
We made it!
Where's Oliver?
I need you
to see something.
Ok. Wait.
You need me.
Ok, you have
the Mirakuru in you.
Not just in me.
You burned a box
full of dirt.
I can help
you understand how it works.
I've spent my entire
life studying it, all right?
It was you.
You were the one
who killed Shado.
No. No, he chose.
It was him.
Give him your gun.
Take it.
And show me...
How you killed Shado.
Show me!
Slade...
This isn't you.
It's the Mirakuru.
And you're sick!
I don't care.
I was trying to protect Sara.
But I didn't want Shado to die.
I cared for her, too.
You know that I did!
I don't care.
You said we were brothers.
You said that.
Is that how
you did it?
Is that how you pointed
the gun at her?
Yes.
Get him out of here.
Why don't you just kill me?
To kill you now...
would be a mercy.
You cannot die
until you have
suffered...
the same way that
I have suffered.
Till you have known
complete despair.
And you will.
I promise.
Mr. Wilson leave?
Yeah.
It's getting pretty late,
I'm going to go, too.
Hmm. Oliver.
I know you and I have
our differences,
but they hardly excuse
your behavior tonight.
If this is the way you're going to act
around me from now on,
then don't come by
the house anymore.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man