My name
is Oliver Queen.
After five years
on a hellish island,
I have come home
with only one goal--
to save my city.
But to do so, I can't be
the killer I once was.
To honor my friend's memory,
I must be someone else.
I must be...something else.
Previously on "Arrow"...
Where the hell
did you come from?
What do you think
you're doing, Officer Lance?
This is my daughter.
She was nearly killed tonight.
Well, as a parent,
you're welcome to stay.
But as a beat cop, your more
than free to go.
Let me help you.
Ok, you can help me.
To do what I do,
I need intel.
You can be my eyes
and ears in the Glades.
That's how you
can save the city.
How do I contact you?
Leave that in
the alley wall,
and I'll know
to contact you.
I told you
to stay away from me.
The copycats are still alive.
Tommy Merlyn isn't.
I lost a friend that day, too.
And I would gladly
have given my life for his.
Well, don't worry,
your life is over.
Your life
as a free man.
Put your weapon down.
I'm not your enemy.
Then put
your weapon down.
Don't move!
Nice mask.
Why'd you help me?
♪ Arrow 2x03 ♪
Broken Dolls
Original Air Date on October 23, 2013
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Oh, thank God.
Police scanner's been blowing up
for the past hour.
Laurel called in half the force
with that silent alarm.
Yeah, because going after
actual bad guys is so last year.
To her, I am the bad guy.
Since when?
Since I didn't make it
to Tommy in time.
How did you get out of there?
I had help from a masked
blonde woman in black.
Another copycat
vigilante?
No. She was different.
Trained, and she used
a sonic...thing.
Wait, sonic thing?
Could you be a bit more specific?
She turned it on
and the glass shattered.
Ok, well, who was she
and why would she help you?
And how did she know
to help you?
All good questions.
I don't like the idea
of another player in town.
I'll see
what I can find.
Oliver, what I would
like to know is what
you're doing at Laurel's office
in the first place.
She makes you
public enemy number one
and you figure this is
a good time to chat?
Because I thought
that I could talk to her
and make her understand that
I'm doing things differently this time.
That I'm not the bad guy.
I was wrong.
Wonderful.
Now we have a dead Japanese
soldier in our home.
Those men on the island were
looking for these corpses.
Aren't you the least bit
interested in why?
I'm more interested in how
many more there are of them
and where
they're operating from.
They'll be coming for that,
which means they'll be coming for us.
And as we've already seen,
they're not the friendliest bunch.
So...
It kind of looks like
you've done that before.
Back in Xingjian,
I was pre-med.
She's a woman
of many talents.
Come on.
"Come on" where?
To higher ground.
We need to get to a vantage point
where we can establish
the enemy's position.
What about Shado?
I'll be fine here.
We shouldn't
split up.
Let her play
with her corpse.
We'll be back
before she knows it.
Here you go, Bud.
On the house, Officer Lance.
Hey, no, no, no, here you go,
a dog this delicious?
I'd have to book myself
for robbery. Take it.
All right.
Take care.
All units,
1078 at Second and Fletcher.
Please respond.
Lance, patrol Delta Charlie 52,
10-60, officer responding.
Over.
Negative, DC-52.
Disregard 10-78
and resume patrol.
According
to whose orders?
Lieutenant Pike.
Excuse me.
Bill, what is
going on here, huh?
This is my beat.
Why did Pike wave me off of this?
Quentin, it's under control.
Excuse me,
what is under control?
That's Barton Mathis.
That seems to be
what the M.O. indicates.
He's doing consecutive
life sentences in Iron Heights.
Not anymore.
The quake split open
a section of Iron Heights.
Mathis was among the escapees.
The brass want to avoid
a panic, so they're keeping it quiet.
Are they keeping it
quiet from me, too?
Come on, man. Pike knows
what happened to you last time.
The man got in your head.
Yeah, and I caught him.
And no one knows  Mathis better.
And I've got all your notes
and your files. Pike's order.
If you go anywhere near this,
he's going to have you
arrested for obstruction.
I found a number
of police reports
from the last few months
that may involve our mystery girl.
They describe a masked woman
in black attacking attackers.
She put five would-be rapists
in the hospital so far.
Are you sure
it's her?
Broken limbs, ruptured ear drums...
Your sonic thing.
That's her. She's
targeting criminals.
Misogynist criminals.
First the hoods, now her.
Looks like you started a movement.
I don't want to start a movement,
so we catch her.
I'm not letting the city get overrun
with vigilantes.
Hi, Detective.
So...
Miss Smoak gives you
a way to call me now.
She vouches for you.
And you told me that you're trying
to help the city without dropping bodies.
That true?
What do you think?
Let's just say
I'm willing to be convinced.
This city is hurting.
And the police?
I always thought
we didn't need to go
outside of law
to find justice.
But in light
of recent events,
I'm not so sure anymore.
Barton Mathis.
The media calls him
the Doll Maker.
'Cause he suffocates
his victims with a flexible polymer
that he pours down their throats
and then he dresses them up like dolls.
I put him away.
Because of the quake...
He's out and he's killing again.
These are from
six years ago.
That's my personal file.
Maybe it's not just
the file that's personal.
Mathis killed eight girls
before I got him last time.
I don't want any more
on my conscience.
So why don't you let
the police do their job?
I could say
the same thing to you.
They're spread so thin,
they can't even risk
letting the public know
that Mathis is out.
You said you're trying
another way?
Maybe I am, too.
You have such beautiful skin.
Lance's file
give you anything?
Last time the Doll Maker
was active in Starling City,
he ramped up to one kill
every three days.
That gives us
two to catch him.
Can we connect the victims?
Young. Pretty.
According to Lance's file,
he couldn't figure
out how he chose them.
As if porcelain dolls weren't
creepy enough
all on their own.
Barton Mathis doesn't have
any family or known acquaintances.
Lone wolves
are harder to catch.
But they do have the right
to an attorney.
Call Lance.
Tell him to set up
a meeting for tonight.
Where?
At the office
of whoever represented
Barton Mathis.
So I'm assuming
this takes priority
over finding out the identity of
your secret admirer.
I got that covered.
Hey.
I was wondering when I was going
to see you again.
There's someone new
in town--a woman.
She's targeting men
who target women.
I know.
I've seen her.
Find her, but don't engage.
Leave that to me.
The archer
makes quite a mess.
I'll add that charge
to the indictment.
Well, you called it
right. He showed.
I know him pretty well.
At least better than others.
This place is a mess.
Twice in three weeks,
you're ducking bullets.
I'm fine.
You don't look fine.
You look tired.
I think I'll give
you two a moment.
Did you just come here
to tell me how tired I look?
No, I came here
to check up on you
and check up
on some court records.
Barton Mathis is out.
I'm looking for his attorney.
Why? You're no longer
a detective.
Yeah, well, I'm just doing a little
digging off the books.
Dad, this case...
It took you to such
a dark place last time.
Yeah, well, I think we both know
that it wasn't Mathis who did that.
Look, nobody knows
this guy better than me,
which means nobody's got a
better chance of stopping him, ok?
And that means every girl that he kills
is like another one on my conscience.
No.
No, dad, it's not.
Whatever guilt
you're feeling...
You're just using it
to justify a vendetta.
Well, maybe I'm not
the only one.
Are you ok?
Oh, Thea, you have to stop asking me
that every time you come to visit.
Ah, don't count on it.
Well, then, I'm afraid
you'll be asking me that
for the next
25 years to life.
Please don't talk like that.
Thea, there's not a lot of value
in the power of positive thinking
when you're being put on
trial for mass murder.
Let's just try to take things
one step at a time, ok?
Well, I'd have to check
with my lawyer,
but I don't think
retail therapy
is a viable legal strategy.
Well, I spoke with her,
and she said that you can
wear regular clothes
to your pre-trial hearing.
So I picked these.
Hmm.
I wish the fashion police
was all I had to worry about.
Please don't joke.
Thea, listen to me.
I need you to understand
what's happening here.
503 people are dead
and there is a measure
of guilt that is owed me.
I'm ready to accept
my punishment.
Even if that means spending
the rest of your life in here?
Yes.
Tony Daniel?
Help you with
something, Officer?
Barton Mathis.
According to the D.A.'s office,
you handled his post-trial appeals,
and I'd like to know where he is.
So you can give him
a parking ticket or something?
If you want to talk to me
about one of my clients,
come back
with a detective shield.
Or a court order.
What, you find that funny?
Well, a little bit.
Where do we
find him?
Iron Heights prison.
He got out.
What?
How?
You spent hours
with him!
Where would he run?
Where?!
I don't know, I--I swear!
What the hell are you doing?!
I thought you were done killing people!
He'll live.
Yeah, but he'll report me
to my lieutenant!
He won't talk
to anyone.
What makes you so sure?
Because he has
another shoulder.
Aah! Oh, ok, ok, ok!
There--there is another place.
He was always drawing it.
Sketching.
His cell walls were covered
with the place.
Yeah, well, what's the place?
Was it in Starling City?
Yeah.
The Bisque Museum.
He said the building
reminded him of Germany.
Where porcelain dolls
were invented.
I'm sorry. I guess he just gets
enthusiastic sometimes.
The lady at the desk said a guy
matching Mathis' description
checked in last week,
room 52.
And he paid in cash.
Now listen,
just we're so clear,
when we go through that door,
we're here to arrest Mathis, ok,
not to torture him.
You asked for my help.
Yeah, and that wasn't either,
and neither is aiding and abetting.
And I am still
a police officer.
Do you want
to catch him or not?
Let's go.
Detective.
It's been too long.
Felicity,
I need a trace.
On it.
You sick son of a bitch.
Sick? I've never felt better.
Fresh air agrees with me.
Yeah, well, don't
get too used to it.
I caught you before.
It's just a matter of time
before I do it again.
Fair enough.
In the meantime, however,
I have someone who'd like
to say hello to you.
Say hello, dear.
She's a little inarticulate.
She's done nothing to you.
Please, don't hurt her,
just let her go.
And allow her to wither away
in a mediocre
and forgettable life.
No. No, no, no, no, no.
She deserves so much better.
She deserves to see
her beauty preserved.
Pristine.
Forever.
Don't worry.
I will turn her into
something special.
Pay attention,
Detective.
What comes next
is really quite exquisite.
The sound of an esophagus
slowly hardening.
Like a symphony.
Felicity...
We're trying, but he's
blocked the skip trace.
Barton, don't do it.
I'm begging you, ok?
Is that what you want?
I am begging you. Please, just stop!
It's for the world to enjoy.
After all...
Everyone loves
a pretty doll.
The police
found her body an hour ago.
Does the new victim
give us any forensics we can use?
CSI did a complete
forensics work-up,
but they sent everything out
to a private lab.
Can you get in?
No. They took
their system offline.
It seems like someone hacked
into a lot of police-related
systems last year.
Then we do it like
we did the Merlyn job.
So glad you invited me
to tag along.
Tranq dart. He'll be
out for 36 minutes.
Yeah, I remember.
You're up, Felicity.
So, this is what a typical
night's like for you, huh?
Just a little breaking
and entering.
All right, I got
toxicology first.
What are all these?
Chemical ingredients of all
the make-up found on the victims--
skin cream,
nail polish, lipstick.
Wait, wait,
wait, stop.
Scroll back.
This one. Ethyl paraben.
Sodium laureth sulphate.
I've seen this before.
It's skin cream.
Forensics found traces
of it on her fingers.
Probably something
she used before he grabbed her.
Skin cream.
Mermaid something.
One of the victims from his last run,
she had this in her purse and
I had the lab analyze it,
and it's the same formula.
Felicity...
Already on it.
How the hell
could she do that?
Ethyl paraben
and sodium laureth sulphate
is Mermaiden's
proprietary formula.
Two victims with the same taste
in skin cream.
That can't be a coincidence.
I could never figure out how
he chose his victims.
I think you just did.
We shouldn't have left Shado.
Well, it's her life.
It's her choice.
You listen
to my advice.
What advice?
To avoid attachment.
Yeah. That was bad advice.
But it will
save your life.
Maybe I don't want
to live under those terms.
Yeah, well, maybe
you're an idiot.
Hey, you think that carrying
about people gets you killed.
I think it's what
keeps people alive.
I was wrong about you.
You're definitely
an idiot.
Then that's who I am.
I'm not changing.
Ohh!
You should be happy I haven't
avoided attachment to you.
Harper.
It's been a while, hoss.
I've been busy.
I can see that.
I'll give you a hundred.
Four.
Two-five.
Done.
If you throw in
some information.
Come on, man, you've got
your finger on the pulse.
I'm looking for someone.
A blonde, likes black leather.
Sounds like your type.
And beats the crap
out of guys with a bow staff.
That still sounds
like your type.
But I want to put eyes on her.
What do you know?
Not much.
You know Cindy?
Folks call her "Sin."
She's got short,
spiky hair.
Yeah, I've seen her
a couple times
hanging around with your black
leather girlfriend.
So where can I find sin?
Well, she hangs out
over at Fifth and Boyton.
And that
is what I know.
So this is it.
Skin cream, that's our lead?
It's something.
What do we know
about the product?
It's made from crushed mother of pearl
and it's super high-end.
Only carried
in a handful of boutiques
and it's marketed for women
with extremely delicate complexions.
He picks his victims
for their skin.
The cream is how
he finds them.
Only four stores
in the city carry it
and three have
surveillance systems.
I've ran facial recognition
through all of them looking for Mathis,
but come up empty.
He must be staking out
the stores from the outside.
Fine. So we'll
do the same.
That could take days
we don't have.
He's probably out there
right now looking for another girl.
So that's what
we give him.
I'll go to the stores
that carry Mermaiden,
and buy it in each one
to cover our bases.
It's too dangerous.
More dangerous than going
undercover in a mob casino
or jumping out of a plane?
It's my life.
It's my choice.
There are only two ways
onto this island--
by sea, and by air.
So what, you're going
to steal whatever they use
to get onto the island?
Well, I'm tired
of living here, aren't you?
Oh, my God.
It appears to be
two or three clicks offshore.
What the hell?
It's firing off
its location.
The plane!
They must have found it.
Shado!
Kid!
Left the last store.
You're going to reimburse me
for these, right?
I saved my receipts.
Go to
the rendezvous point.
Stay in public.
Just for the record,
I'm not a huge fan
of dangling helpless girls
in front of psychopaths like meat.
She volunteered.
Well, she must really
believe in you.
So did your daughter.
She suffered a loss.
Grief's got a way of shifting
a person's beliefs.
But then you know
all about that.
You've lost people, too, right?
Why would you say that?
Why else would you be
doing this?
My youngest, she died.
I'm sorry.
Less than a month
after it happened,
I--I ended up catching
the Doll Maker case.
Threw myself into it.
I think on some level,
with each girl I was trying to save...
Sara.
And just like with Sara,
I couldn't.
He killed eight girls
Sara's age before I caught him.
Someone's coming.
I got him.
Ok, I'm going to admit to being
seriously wigged out right now.
False alarm, but next time
I offer to be bait for your serial killer,
please turn me down.
Delta Charlie 52
to Central.
Code 99, possible 207
in progress,
immediate back-up required!
You're all right, you're all right.
Don't move.
She hit her head.
Go, go, go.
I thought there'd be more
ceremony to this moment.
I'm a little disappointed,
to be honest.
Get out of here!
Officer Lance, SCPD.
It's Mathis.
I almost had him.
Search the area.
Whole building.
Sorry.
For what?
Pike's orders. He wants you collared
for obstruction.
What, he--
Quentin Larry Lance,
you have the right to remain silent.
If you give up that right to remain silent,
anything you say can...
They're charging
Lance with obstruction.
He's in custody.
Mathis isn't.
He'll be looking
for another target.
I hacked Mermaiden
and sent out an email blast
from their servers telling stores
the product was defective.
That will slow them down.
Smart.
What about Lance?
One legal problem
at a time.
Docket ending 4587,
State versus Queen.
All right, I'll hear your motions,
ladies first.
Your Honor, we would like to be
heard once again
on the issue of bail.
Ms. Queen has languished
in the Iron Heights prison
now for five months.
And in those five months,
did the 503 people
she's charged with killing
miraculously return
from the dead?
If not, I'm a little unclear
on how the passage
of time is relevant.
Might I remind the court
that the defendant
is presumed innocent?
No need.
I want to law school.
It's where
I learned that bail,
once denied, cannot be set
in the absence
of change of circumstance.
Mr. Donner,
what do you have for me?
Your Honor, the State
has no pre-trial motions
to make at this time.
But we would like
to serve notice to the defense
pursuant to rule of
criminal procedure 15.
Your Honor, I would like
to conference with the district attorney.
There's really no need,
nor any obligation.
What about
professional courtesy?
I would like to have
a conversation with you
before you seek
the death penalty.
Your client aided and abetted
an act of mass murder.
503 conversations
wouldn't convince me
that Moira Queen
shouldn't be the 504th fatality.
Mom, we are going
to fight this.
No one is going
to take you from us.
We won't let it happen.
Oliver!
Shado!
I had to call in
a lot of favors to get those.
The only problem is that I've been
at the D.A.'s office
for less than a month,
and no one owes me any favors.
So how did you get
the charges dropped?
Your friend Pike and
I have been working together
on the anti-vigilante taskforce.
Do you remember?
Hmm. Last year you were
working with the Arrow.
What a difference
a few months makes.
The Arrow?
Yeah. Seems more
appropriate than the Hood.
And now you're working with him.
Guess I'm not the only one
in the Lance family that's done a 180.
This city needs help.
I just became less particular
about where it
comes from.
What's your excuse?
Still Tommy?
What would you tell me
if I said it is?
That a guy with a bow and arrow
can't save a guy
whose had a building
fall on top of him.
What's going on with you
is not about the Arrow.
Then what is it, Dad? Hmm?
I mean, why don't you tell me?
You seem to have
all the answers.
That crack that you made about me
feeling guilty about something.
Tommy's death.
Why would I feel guilty
about that?
I don't know.
I wish I did.
'Cause it's
eating you up.
Your psychoanalysis
would probably have
a bit more credibility
if it wasn't being offered
under police custody.
Laurel, I'm worried
about you--
I'd stay away from Pike
if I were you,
and the Doll Maker case.
Excuse me.
Step off,
Abercrombie.
Cindy?
Sin?
What do you want?
Can't you see I'm busy?
I'm looking
for a friend of yours.
Blonde.
Black leather, head to toe.
So I guess
that's a yes.
He said he would
go inside...
That's what he said.
He said he would go inside.
You all right, pal?
Need a doctor
or something?
No.
I'm fine, thanks.
I checked the order
and you shorted us
half a case
of champagne.
I'm not paying for
booze I didn't get.
That won't help.
Yeah, well, neither
is yelling at my vendors, but...
I want to yell at
someone right now.
Mom's going to be ok.
Because we are going
to help her fight this.
As a family.
They want
to kill her.
I won't let them.
Thea, can you turn
to channel 52, please?
Officer Quentin Lance
and his daughter Laurel
were abducted earlier today.
No ransom has been demanded.
SCPD are urging anyone with information
regarding their whereabouts...
How did he get them?
I don't know
about Laurel.
Detective Lance was abducted from
the precinct parking lot.
Mathis shot a guard on the way out,
which sounded the alarm.
I pulled up the department's
security camera footage,
and a van from Metamorpho
Chemical caught my eye.
Metamorpho was condemned
after the quake.
Perfect place
to make some dolls.
Not tonight.
Cops will use tracers,
Oliver, same as we did.
They won't make it in time.
Hey.
- Wake up, Abercrombie.
- What?
Did they send you?
Did who what?
Not my face!
I have a disapproving
girlfriend.
Are you one of them?
One of who?
That's mine.
Let him go.
Isn't this nice?
All of us here together.
It's like Thanksgiving.
Laurel, just stay calm.
Stay calm.
Barton, I'm sorry.
I know you hate me.
I know you hate me, ok,
and I understand that.
But you hate me.
So please let my daughter go.
Now why would I do that?
Look at her.
She's so lovely.
Maybe a little too much melanin
in the skin,
but...it's the imperfections
that make art sublime.
I am the one who put you away.
She had nothing to do with it!
She had everything
to do with it!
She's your world,
she's your very soul.
You know,
I could kill you,
I could maim you, I could slice you up
into a thousand pieces,
but if your soul
remains intact,
what have I done? Huh?
Nothing.
I will kill you, you son of a bitch!
I will kill you!
You son of a bitch!
Laurel...Sweetheart...
Close your eyes.
I'm here.
I'm here, honey.
If you struggle,
it will take longer.
Do whatever you need to do,
just get him. Get him!
Let's take a better look
at this face of yours.
You have such lovely skin.
You're going back to prison.
No, he's not.
It's ok, sweetheart.
It's ok,
he saved us.
I know.
I know he did,
and after I hunted him.
It's ok,
it's all right.
No. He came.
He came to save me.
Yeah, I know,
he saved us both.
No.
Not him.
Not the Arrow.
Tommy.
What?
Oliver, he--
he told me to stay
out of the Glades,
and he--he told me
to get out of CNRI,
and I didn't.
Tommy was only there
because I was too stubborn!
To stubborn to get out
when I had the chance.
You were right.
I was blaming
the Arrow because...
Oh, my God.
It's all my fault, Dad.
It's all my fault
that Tommy died.
It's all right, honey.
How is she?
She'll be all right.
In time.
I might not always agree
with your methods,
but I can't argue
with your results.
You saved my daughter.
Again.
She needed help.
And she wasn't the only one.
Thanks.
Moira.
I know how hard
this day has been for you.
Yes.
And believe it
or not,
I've actually been
in worse situations.
Listen to me. Donner knows
how strong our defense is.
Don't let him scare you with that
little death penalty stunt of his.
Oh, I'm not afraid
of dying, Jean.
I've made my peace
with this world a long time ago.
Then it's win the case
in the courtroom.
The trial is going to reveal
that you were living
under Malcolm Merlyn's thumb.
It's going to reveal everything.
Yes.
And that's what
I'm afraid of.
Moira, what don't I know?
Don't you do this.
You need to tell me.
I am your lawyer,
and I am also your friend.
Thea and Oliver.
I'm finally in a good place with
my children, Jean.
I have my family back.
But there are
some things...
that must never
be spoken of.
You shouldn't
have come here.
I had no choice.
Ra's Al ghul
has ordered your return.
I'm not going back.
I can't.
That is not your decision.
Tell them that you
couldn't find me.
Tell them I ran.
I won't lie for you.
Fine.
Don't tell them
anything.
Something's going on
with this woman.
She keeps following you
around, helping you out.
We've got to find her.
To stop her,
or to send her
a thank you note?
That depends.
On what?
What side she's on.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man