(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
There's only one way to prevent that.
My father once told me of an elixir
known as the Lotus.
And I will freely give it to you
on one condition.
I want you to kill Malcolm Merlyn.
If you cared about Thea,
then curing her bloodlust
wouldn't come with any condition.
Thea is my sister-in-law.
You are my husband.
I'm not your husband.
But war does not know family bonds
nor friendly sentiments.
Who are you at war with?
I just told you I want you to kill
Malcolm Merlyn. Try to guess.
Hey.
If you have a problem with Malcolm Merlyn,
deal with it yourself.
Do not involve me or my sister.
You put the Demon's Head ring
on Malcolm's hand.
You...
You can't defeat him.
But you can.
-You have!
-And...
That was before I knew
that he was my sister's father.
So he dies so his child might live.
Didn't your father make a similar bargain?
I'm sorry, Oliver.
I would not resort
to this if I had any other choice.
Listen, my sister is dying
because of something that your father did.
I think you have every choice.
Thea is dying
because of what her father did.
I'm only following events
to their inevitable conclusion.
You know what's strange?
Watching your baby girl drink coffee.
Yeah, it would probably be
a little less strange
if you'd seen your baby girl
in the last 18 years.
You're right.
Don't suppose it helps
if I say that I thought
staying out of your life
was the best thing for you.
I was protecting you and your mother.
You were protecting yourself.
You were wanted by the police
and you didn't want to go to jail.
That is why you stayed away.
And you know why the police were after me?
The type of "criminal" I was?
Mom never went into detail.
I assume petty stuff.
Anything else requires commitment.
Well, I'm here now
and I want us to speak openly.
I'll answer any questions you have.
Okay, I just have one at the moment.
Why now?
I was doing a job for someone.
Almost got beat. Almost.
My adversary had exceptional skills.
My curiosity piqued,
I investigated further.
Imagine what I discovered.
Overwatch.
Bye. See you never.
Felicity, wait. It is not what you think.
My employer, my work,
is hardly diabolical.
I'll be sure to tell that to my friend
who you blackmailed.
Short-term legal mischief
for long-term societal gain.
Isn't that kind of hacktivism
exactly what you did at MIT?
Is it really all that different
from the vigilantism you practice today?
We are the same, you and I.
I'm pretty sure that I didn't try
to kill 8,000 people.
An empty threat. I swear to you.
I know I have no right.
I'm asking for a chance.
A chance to prove to you
that I'm not a bad guy.
And that I'm not a bad guy.
What is that?
A record of some of the hacks
I've done throughout the years.
I've selected the ones
that can be verified by news accounts
so you know I'm telling the truth.
This is very simple for me, Felicity.
I want to be back in your life.
I know that doing that will require
earning your trust back.
I hope this is a first step down
that very long road.
So Nyssa's holding Thea's life hostage
until you kill Malcolm Merlyn.
I'll be surprised
if she wasn't the Daughter of the Demon.
Oh, it's not funny, John.
No, it's not. Thea's dying.
She's has one, maybe two days.
And if we can save her
by killing the man that killed my sister,
then how could you
even think twice about that?
I'm not gonna defend Malcolm.
He orchestrated your sister's murder,
he killed Tommy...
Nothing is ever gonna change
the fact that he's Thea's family.
I don't know how much
you remember of my father,
but he was not a good man.
He threw in with Malcolm Merlyn.
And all of that being said,
there is nothing that I wouldn't do
to have him back.
So you tell me, how am I supposed to take
that away from Thea?
But Oliver,
what's the difference if Thea dies?
It doesn't have to come to that, John.
There's more than one choice here.
-Like what?
-Diplomacy.
What does Nyssa want?
I mean, all Nyssa really wants
is control of the League.
So I need to convince Merlyn
to give her the ring,
she gives us the cure,
and no one has to die.
Laurel, can you convince Nyssa to,
to go along with that?
Yeah.
It's easier than talking Malcolm into it.
Well, let me worry about Malcolm.
I don't understand.
Why would you save me,
only to kill my brother?
Vlad attacked me.
Vlad would never do such a thing.
I was defending myself.
And I did not know he was your brother.
Would that have made a difference?
I didn't have a choice.
There is always a choice.
(SIGHS) I couldn't just let him kill me.
I'm done with you.
Taiana,
I have something that Reiter wants.
Where did you get that?
It doesn't matter.
I think that we can use this against him.
I have a better idea.
Hey!
Get Reiter.
Tell him I want to talk to him.
I have something that he wants.
Let me see if I've got this right.
There's a magic potion
that could cure Thea's bloodlust,
that we've never heard of,
but Nyssa "conveniently" has.
I've been holding off telling you
this for years, Oliver.
You're very handsome,
not especially bright.
(SIGHS) Well, bright enough
to have checked.
It's called the Lotus.
Tatsu Yamashiro is part of the order
who guards it.
Or did. They gave it to Nyssa.
And if we don't get her
to give it to Thea now...
We're gonna lose her.
Even assuming such an elixir existed,
even assuming Ms. Yamashiro's order
parted with it willingly,
even assuming Nyssa al Ghul's words
could be trusted, then yes.
Of course, I'd do anything
to save my daughter.
But none of that is true, Oliver.
Look, I appreciate your trying to embrace
a more optimistic viewpoint these days...
Malcolm,
we're talking about your daughter.
Yes.
And I need to do something to save her.
And you need to stop wasting my time
with Nyssa al Ghul's games.
LOA GUARD: We found her at the perimeter.
She claims to be a friend.
And she speaks the truth.
At least until she defiled my beloved
and stood idly by while
I was left to rot in a dungeon.
Leave us.
-Nyssa...
-How is my beloved?
Sara's good. She's whole.
I think she's happy.
If you're here about Thea...
Nyssa, what are you doing?
Protecting my birthright.
By holding Thea's life hostage?
You say that as if she didn't fire
the arrows that felled your sister.
You and I both know that wasn't her doing.
Yes. It was Malcolm Merlyn.
And the time has come for recompense.
I will never forgive Merlyn for all
the horrible things that he's done.
He's taken people,
two very special people away from me.
Don't you think I want him dead?
Then why are you here?
Because if you want Merlyn dead,
then you have to drive that sword.
And if you can't or if you won't,
we will need to negotiate a compromise.
You have my attention.
Oliver convinces Merlyn
to give up the power,
and you...
And you give us the cure.
I would accept those terms.
But Merlyn never will.
Let us worry about that.
And by "us," you mean my husband.
LAUREL: Oliver's speaking
with Merlyn right now.
And Merlyn, he is a bastard,
but there is nothing that he wouldn't do
to save his daughter.
I hope so.
Because if he doesn't, it won't just
be Thea's life that is forfeit.
What do you mean?
NYSSA: There will be war.
And the streets of your home will run red
with the blood of our enemies.
Whomever they may be.
How'd it go with Merlyn?
Not good. Nyssa?
She brought an army. But if you
get her the ring, she'll play ball.
We can get this done
with no one getting hurt.
Everything all right?
No, not really. I mean, it's not great,
it's just not quite the level "my sister's
on her deathbed" kind of bad, so...
-What happened?
-My dad came back.
DIGGLE: And why is that a bad thing?
Well, it's an extremely long story,
but you remember the super-hacker
who blackmailed Roy? Same guy.
-What?
-Your father is...
The Calculator.
He showed up
at my Palmer Tech presentation.
I had coffee with him yesterday,
where he dropped
the Calculator bomb on me.
And why would he do that?
Apparently,
now that he knows what I do,
that we're both "vigilantes,"
we have something in common.
The sickest part is I want to believe him.
I wish there was some sort of test
I could do that would prove
that he is who he says he is.
A test is a good idea.
It's a good idea for you, and for us.
I've got a way to bring Merlyn
to the bargaining table.
I'm not usually one to be summoned
by my prisoners.
I heard you had something for me?
Taiana, please don't.
I have something you want.
Let me out of this cage, and it's yours.
Show me what you have.
(RAGGED BREATHING) Magnificent.
Do we have a deal?
A deal?
-(GASPS)
-REITER: You misunderstood.
It's mine either way.
(GRUNTING) I cannot stay here, Reiter.
This man killed my brother.
REITER: And you will continue to care
for him as if he were your brother.
Mr. Queen is an important piece
of my endeavor on this island.
You'll stay here
with him until he's well.
If his health gets worse,
you'll join him in his fate.
(GRUNTING)
Your left-side block is slow.
Your next opponent won't have my patience,
or my mercy.
Clearly you don't understand
how this is supposed to work, my husband.
You were supposed to bring
the Magician with you.
Well, I need something from you first.
Proof that what you're offering is real.
A stalling tactic.
Al Sa-her thinks me the fool.
Or that you're one.
Or maybe he doesn't trust
the woman trying to take
the Demon's Head ring from him.
I can't imagine why.
Bring me a sample of the Lotus.
I recognize what you're doing.
Part of me even respects it.
But the leadership of the League
of Assassins is in the balance here.
It is naive to think this
can be resolved without bloodshed.
This amount is not sufficient
to cure her permanently.
Only to provide
the assurance Merlyn seeks.
Thank you, Nyssa.
As I said, someone is going to die.
I pray it won't be your sister.
Was it difficult to get her discharged
from the hospital?
No. I spoke to Dr. Lamb.
A friend of the family.
-(MACHINES BEEPING)
-DIGGLE: Nyssa.
She hooked us up
with a sample of the cure.
This buys Thea some more time,
and you get the proof that you need.
Let's see it.
(EXHALES DEEPLY)
What are Nyssa's terms?
You hand over the Ring, she gives us
the rest of the elixir.
And Thea lives.
When can we meet?
Tonight. Laurel's with her now.
Hi. I got your...
Oh, no.
Oh, no, you've Mr. Square Bear face.
What?
Mr. Square Bear.
Oh, my God, you don't remember?
You lost him when you were,
like, four years old.
And you had that exact,
you had that exact look on your face.
Oh, baby. Is it too much to hope
that you lost a plushy toy?
No, but adjusting for age inflation
might be just as bad.
Huh?
Sit.
Well, what's up?
It's Dad.
-Noah. He's in Star City.
-What?
How do you know?
-He came to see me.
-(DONNA SIGHS)
Did you talk to him?
Yeah.
Are you all right?
Yeah, you sound like you think
he'd hurt me or something.
Yeah.
I've just been doing
some checking.
Is it possible that he's not the guy
who we thought he was?
That maybe he's better
than who we thought he was?
No.
Felicity, I would love to think
that your father didn't show up
with some ulterior motive
in your life right now.
But I've been where you are more times
than I care to admit,
and it always ends the same way.
He tells you exactly what you want
to hear and you get sucked in.
And the next thing you know,
you have no job, no money,
and a sweet seven-year-old daughter
who needs a new pair of shoes
and wants to go to space camp.
People don't change.
Even if you want them to.
Okay.
LAUREL: You're doing the right thing.
I'm only entertaining Oliver's naive plan
out of respect for our marriage.
But his hope blinds him to reality.
You've come dressed for battle, Al Sa-her.
Just for the occasion.
In exchange for my daughter's life.
I'm glad you've finally seen reason.
Sadly, the only thing I have seen
is your quick and speedy death.
Malcolm!
I knew you couldn't be trusted.
You knew, and you didn't prepare.
And here you are, outnumbered, outgunned,
outmaneuvered. Per usual.
OLIVER: Nyssa, don't!
Kill him! (GRUNTING)
We have to stop them
before they kill each other.
(PEOPLE GRUNTING)
Retreat!
Don't let her get away!
Malcolm, stop this, now!
-Get out of my way, Oliver!
-Think about Thea!
Do not question my love for my daughter!
Everything I do, I do it for her.
I'm not moving.
So much for the Gandhi method.
Given who we're dealing with,
we shouldn't be surprised.
I cannot believe that being Ra's al Ghul
is more important to Malcolm
than saving his daughter's life.
I know that you're trying a new approach.
But just because you've changed,
that doesn't mean everybody else has.
Yeah. We cannot allow a League civil war.
Too many people will be collateral damage.
And the four of us definitely can't take
on two armies of assassins.
Then we take on the generals.
We need to work on locating
Nyssa and Malcolm.
But mainly Nyssa.
Because she's got the whole
Lotus cure thing.
We find both of them.
No one else dies tonight.
Especially Thea.
You need this to keep your fever at bay.
If it comes back, well,
that would be very bad.
I'm surprised you still care.
Baron Reiter made it very clear
what happens to me if you die.
Taiana, I know what you're going through.
It's this feeling
in the pit of your stomach.
-Just... Emptiness.
-Don't you dare
try to help me mourn my brother,
that you took from me.
-Please, just listen...
-You know nothing about how I feel.
A man with a heart as small as yours
is incapable of such things.
My father sacrificed himself
so I could survive.
So that I could right his wrongs.
He did it by pulling out a gun
and shooting himself in the head,
not three feet from me.
Since that day, I have lost
four more people that I love.
That I cared so much about.
It never gets easier. Ever.
I could see it in your eyes.
From the moment we first met.
That I was good?
No. That you were lost. Shattered.
(INHALES DEEPLY)
There is a Russian saying,
(SPEAKING
FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
"The same hammer that shatters glass,
forges steel."
If you want to be the man
that your father wishes you to be,
then this is how you get there.
You save us from Reiter.
But you cannot do that shattered.
Hey.
Everyone's telling the same story.
Guys in black robes fighting each other.
Yeah. League of Assassins.
They're working out
some leadership issues.
Yeah, but how many more people
are gonna die before that happens?
Yeah. We're working on it.
You gotta work faster.
Or this is just the beginning.
Hey. I think we need to talk.
About what?
About the elephant in the room.
The way this is going down,
it ends one way.
Malcolm Merlyn.
(SIGHS) He has to be taken down, Oliver.
You're the only man who's ever done it.
Malcolm's killed hundreds of people.
He killed Tommy, he killed Sara.
Thea is dying right now because of events
that he set in motion.
I've never hated anyone the way
that I hate him.
You've been in denial, Oliver.
Holding on to hope with both hands
that you don't have to give
in to that hate.
Use that hate to do what needs to be done.
But Oliver, this needs to be done.
You have to kill Malcolm Merlyn.
I'm glad you called.
Well, all your files checked out.
And I did some additional digging myself.
You're right.
You and I, we're not all that different.
This facility is really amazing.
FELICITY: Yes.
After numerous false starts,
we've finally got the R and D section
working like a Swiss watch.
This floor contains most of our
bleeding-edge projects. Ah!
That is an autonomous
communications device,
three generations beyond Bluetooth.
But there are no seams in the casing.
I know. (CHUCKLES)
It's milled
from a single piece of aluminum.
The entire surface connects
to an induction charger.
How did you achieve the heat sink?
Curtis Holt achieved it, actually.
He's quite the genius.
Don't sell yourself short.
You're the Steve Jobs in this equation.
(CHUCKLES)
Thank you for agreeing
to give me a second chance.
Baby steps, then.
Baby steps.
(CHUCKLES)
I have eyes on Nyssa.
Abandoned complex at Seventh and Rucka.
Put the word out among
our assets in Star City.
Whoever leads us to Al Sa-her
will be rewarded handsomely.
OLIVER: (OVER RADIO)
Keep her there. We're on our way.
(BLACK CANARY GRUNTS)
BLACK CANARY: Nyssa, stop.
Step aside, Laurel.
I will not let you wage a war in my city.
I bargained in good faith.
I'm only finishing what he started.
-And I aim to end it, swiftly.
-At what cost?
How many lives will you sacrifice?
For what?
I will only say this once more.
Step aside.
No. You're coming with me.
Am I?
-We're under attack!
-(LOA GUARDS GRUNTING)
-(LOA GUARD 1 GRUNTING)
-(MALCOLM'S ASSASSIN 1 GRUNTS)
-(BLACK CANARY SCREECHES)
-(MALCOLM'S MEN YELLING)
We have to get out of here! Run!
(SCREAMING)
(HORN HONKING)
-WOMAN: Aah!
-(MAN GRUNTS)
Go! Get inside!
(MEN GRUNT)
(GRUNTS)
(GRUNTING)
(ASSASSIN GRUNTS)
(PANTING) Cowards. Just like their master.
-Sorry, Nyssa.
-For what?
For that.
I was in a cell much like this one
barely a year ago.
Nyssa, where is the Lotus?
Safe.
This isn't a game, Nyssa. Thea is dying.
Innocent civilians are dying.
Your own men are dying.
And surrendering my only leverage
will not save their lives.
No. But it'll save Thea's.
How could you be so selfish?
A question better put to Malcolm Merlyn.
He doesn't have the cure. You do.
Using Thea's life as a bargaining chip,
letting people die for a lost cause?
Nyssa, this isn't who you are.
It's who your father was.
But he's gone. He's dead.
And you can finally be free.
Any luck?
Malcolm and the League
have gone to ground.
Nyssa is a brick wall.
John and Laurel
are out searching for the Lotus,
but we are running out of places to look.
Oh, that's depressing.
Oh, we will find it. We have to.
Mmm-hmm.
Is everything all right?
Not really. I mean, it's not as bad
as your sister being unconscious
in our sub-level, but...
Did something happen with your dad?
More like something didn't happen.
What's that?
It's an IR burst receiver.
Incredibly advanced.
It can suck the data out of any room
you put it in to.
Don't worry, I-I turned it off before
bringing it down here.
-It's not yours?
-It's my father's.
I gave him a little tour
of Curtis' R and D lab,
and he left this behind as a souvenir.
He's trying to steal from Palmer Tech?
It's your idea, actually.
You needed proof about the Lotus.
I needed proof about my dad.
You a trap for him as a test?
Unrestricted access to
Palmer Technologies' R and D lab.
He flunked with flying colors.
I don't even know why I'm surprised.
You're surprised because you're hoping
that he's the parent
you've always wanted him to be.
A parent you deserve.
In an extremely ironic role reversal,
my mother was smarter than me...
She said, "People don't change.
"No matter how much we want them to."
-Some people don't.
-Uh-huh.
I'd like to think that there's hope
for the rest of us.
Or I did. As far as Malcolm is concerned,
John thinks I should kill him.
If it helps save Thea, I agree.
Yeah, and I agree
if he wasn't Thea's father, but he is.
We are in this mess because of him.
On, like, a million different levels.
Let's not pretend that this is a typical
father-daughter relationship.
He brainwashed her into killing a friend.
I know all this. I do.
And I'm still holding out
hope that with...
(STUTTERS) With time, and with how much
he says that he loves her,
that maybe they have some chance
at some type of normal relationship.
If I kill him,
my sister never gets that chance.
Thea's father is no more likely
to change than mine is.
(BEEPING)
What now?
-Found Malcolm.
-Where?
Right underneath us.
Malcolm!
The Lotus effect is wearing off.
She will pass by sunrise.
I would like to be by her side.
This has to end. No more games.
You give Nyssa the damn ring!
She was four months old when we first met.
(SIGHS) Your housekeeper,
Raisa, I believe,
was picking you up from our house
with Thea in a stroller.
I peeked my head into the bassinet,
and Thea, all of 16 weeks,
she stuck her tongue out at me.
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
I always knew I was connected to her.
As if, on some primal level,
I knew I was her father.
A real father wouldn't let their child die
just to keep his hands on power.
That is not what I am doing.
What's unfolding here is larger than I.
And it is bigger than my daughter.
It's not just her life that hangs
in the balance, Oliver.
For all your dealings with the League,
you still remain ignorant
to what it is they do for the world.
Enough about the League.
You're a group of assassins.
It is a force of change.
Silently manipulating global events
for hundreds of years.
And I cannot, I will not put
that kind of power
into Nyssa al Ghul's hands!
Let me ask you something.
If Damien Darhk came to you and told you
to lay down your bow,
let him finish his plan for Star City,
would you do it?
Even if it meant saving William's life?
I know everything about you, Oliver.
I am Ra's al Ghul.
But back to the matter at hand,
you will never sacrifice your city
to save your son.
And believe me when I tell you
that I am only making the same choice.
I would look for another choice.
And I wouldn't stop looking
until there was a third option!
Malcolm, what if,
what if you could have
the Lotus and keep your ring?
I don't see how.
Nyssa's forces are stronger
than I'd care to admit.
Not by herself.
You challenge her to a trial by combat.
You do realize your plan
would end in her death.
We're all backed into a corner, Malcolm.
Nyssa made her bed.
This is one of your crazier ideas
and that is a competitive field.
Well, sit tight.
I have a crazier one coming.
In deference to good taste,
we will forgo the removal of shirts.
Let us be finished with the charade.
As you wish.
OLIVER: Hold!
In the eyes of the League,
this woman is my wife.
As your husband,
I wish to fight on her behalf.
I have never allowed anyone
to fight my battles for me.
Do you want to become Ra's
or do you want to die?
Why are you doing this?
You told me yourself,
you couldn't defeat Merlyn.
If I am forced to choose
between your life and his,
then I will see justice done.
I'm a little disappointed, I must say.
You're the one who put us
in this position, Malcolm.
Can I remind you the role you played
in putting this ring on my finger?
No, I remember.
Tonight, I correct that mistake.
I can't believe it.
You've grown even more foolish
with experience.
Three years!
Let's finish this.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(GRUNTING)
-Last chance, Malcolm. Yield!
-Never!
To end this, you must kill me.
But you always knew that, Oliver.
-I don't want it to end this way.
-Spare me your false sympathy.
Just do it.
(MALCOLM SCREAMING AND GRUNTING)
Bring me the Lotus.
You are Ra's al Ghul.
Thank you, husband.
GUARDS AND ASSASSINS: Ra's.
What?
(STUTTERS) What is going on?
Is everything okay?
That, uh, depends.
How are you feeling?
I'm... (GRUNTS)
I'm a little bit tired, but...
What am I doing here?
You know, it's a long story.
But to shorthand it...
Is that you're gonna be fine.
The cure worked.
-(THEA CHUCKLES)
-No more bloodlust.
Come on. Let's go get you
into some regular clothes.
Yeah. Um...
(SIGHS)
Oliver, you did it, man. Thea's fine.
And Nyssa and Merlyn didn't have to die.
Ooh, yeah, not to be the buzzkill,
but when are we going to tell Thea
about Malcolm's...
Shh... Baby steps.
Right.
What's up?
Something my father said.
NOAH: I brought you a portable ramp.
So now any time you come across
a higher surface, just unfold it.
This will get you over almost anything.
Look, I have a meeting in a few.
I just wanted to say goodbye.
Goodbye?
We were just starting
to get to know each other.
I think I know everything I need to know.
Felicity, what is going on? I...
I thought we were making progress.
When I was a girl, I hated myself.
I thought I was broken,
that no one could or ever would love me.
It's the only way a child can grow up
when their father abandons them.
Felicity...
All I ever wanted
to know was why?
What was so wrong with me
that you would leave?
There was nothing
wrong with you, sweetheart.
But there was everything wrong with me.
The police, the FBI. They were never
going to stop looking for me.
I realized a life on the run,
that wasn't the life that I owed you
or your mother.
So I disappeared.
You thought you were doing
the right thing for us.
Exactly.
I have waited my entire life
for that explanation.
And the thing is,
I don't even know if believe it.
It's the truth.
There is only one part of your story
that I know to be true.
And that is that
you are wanted by the police.
Felicity.
I just need you to know one thing.
You were wrong. I am nothing like you.
NOAH: Felicity...
QUENTIN: Noah, come on.
You're under arrest. Anything you say
or do can and will be used
against you in a court of law.
You have the right to an attorney.
NOAH: No! No, don't, don't...
Don't do this.
Felicity!
Thank you both for coming.
How is Thea?
Don't pretend like you care.
I do. She's my sister-in-law.
And her condition is the result
of my father's blade.
You were right. Even after his death,
I remained my father's prisoner.
I allowed him to turn me into someone
you showed me I don't have to be.
And you showed me as well
when you took up the sword
to save my life.
You both showed me what needed to be done.
And what's that?
Patience, please.
We're waiting for one other.
Thank you for coming, Al Sa-her.
You're Ra's. I had no choice.
And so you are mistaken once again.
What are you doing?
(GASPS)
Earlier today,
I disbanded the League of Assassins.
I released its forces,
much as my father
had released you long ago.
No one will be held prisoner
by my father any longer.
I thought of you as a son once, Oliver.
I had more in common with you
than my own blood.
But that's not the reason
why I'm not going to kill you.
Neither the fact
that you are my daughter's brother.
The reason you get to live
is because death would be a mercy
compared to the debt I now owe you.
Don't you dare threaten me, Malcolm.
(SCOFFS)
Taiana,
I promise I will free your friends...
For Vlad.
Vlad is dead. We do this for them.
REITER: Mr. Queen.
I hope you have regained your strength.
The stone you gave me
was the final piece of the puzzle.
The final map. We are going to dig.
-Dig?
-The heaven I seek is not above,
but rather beneath our feet.
We dig at daybreak.
Hey.
Are you feeling any better?
I don't even know why I'm so upset.
Doesn't every long-awaited
father-daughter reunion end
with the dad being
taken away in handcuffs?
You don't have to be funny for me.
-You know that, right?
-I know.
And I know I did the right thing.
But the look on his face when he realized
I had turned him in,
that's going to haunt me
for the rest of my life.
And I can't help but think he doesn't even
deserve that kind of remorse.
I think that remorse
is a pretty clear indicator
that you are a very different person
than him.
Maybe Thea and I could make t-shirts.
We could join a club.
Listen to me.
Don't make the mistake of thinking
that this thing with your dad is over.
I can tell you from experience
that closure does not come that easily.
(GRUNTS)
Speaking of closure,
are you punishing yourself
for betraying Malcolm?
Is that insane?
Yes. But it's part of what makes you
the man I love.
John was right.
You were faced
with an impossible situation
and you found the best way out of it.
Will you marry me?
I think I already answered that question.
Thea's better. Andy's better.
Things are quiet on the Darhk front.
I feel like this might be our window.
And with everything that we have gone
through for the past few months,
I want you to tell me,
why are we waiting?
-Well, I have to plan it.
-Mmm-hmm.
(SIGHS) Maybe just a small ceremony
with a few of our friends,
and no caterers. My mom will hate that.
I'm in.
Mmm.
I don't like to be kept waiting.
My apologies.
I don't have the resources I once had.
Yes. I'm aware
of your recent reversal of fortune.
I take it that's why
you asked for this meeting?
Well, I haven't come empty-handed.
-So to speak.
-(CHUCKLES)
I have some information that you
might find of particular interest.
I know who Oliver Queen cares about more
than anyone in the whole world.
Yeah, so do I. We did a pretty good number
on her over the holidays.
It's not Felicity Smoak.
Who?
His son, William.