My name is Oliver Queen.
After five years
on a hellish island,
I have come home
with only one goal--
to save my city.
But to do so, I can't be
the killer I once was.
To honor my friend's memory,
I must be someone else.
I must be something else.
Previously on "Arrow"...
As much as I would love
to make this city safer,
my first obligation is
to Queen Consolidated
and yours is, too.
I did some reading up
on Lawton.
Lyla, listen--
Did you really think
I wouldn't find out
that he killed
your brother?
That you were using me?
I need to see
this guy in a bag.
You, of all people,
should get that.
Long time
particularly
for Bratva captain.
Mr. Queen.
Anatoly Knyazev,
he speaks
very highly of you.
He should.
I saved his life.
You were supposed
to sign this report
at last night's board meeting.
You know why you didn't?
Probably because I didn't
attend last night's board meeting.
Where were you?
I have other interests
outside of this company.
I don't.
Mr. Queen--
I thought you were serious
when you said
we were partners.
Isabel, I missed
one meeting.
This week.
Last week, it was
two meetings.
Mr. Queen.
Companywide revenue
is at double digits
since you and I
took over.
Oliver!
Yes?
I'm sorry
to interrupt your...
Grr!
Um, I need to talk to you
about your plans
for this evening.
With Mr. Harper?
You'll have
to excuse me.
We have work to do.
It's important.
So are
my evening plans.
I'm sorry.
We are going to have
to work on your excuses.
You're right.
You should be
more careful.
You're
completely exposed.
I knew you were there.
What, you wanted me
to tell you
when the funny money guys
were ready to make a sale?
Here we go.
Not "we." Go home.
I already have help.
Here's the fake.
Let's see the real.
You got two
right above you.
Another at your six.
Stay where you are,
don't move!
I want to make a citizen's arrest.
Don't move.
That's it. I'm clear.
Aah!
Task force X to Mockingbird.
We have the prize,
we're coming home.
♪ Arrow 2x06 ♪
Keep Your Enemies Closer
Original Air Date on November 13, 2013
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Who are you people?
NSA? CIA?
My name
is Amanda Waller.
I thought you A.R.G.U.S. guys
were supposed to be more subtle.
For us,
this was subtle.
Then I want to see Lyla Michaels.
So do I.
Agent Michaels
has gone dark.
Lyla's missing?
What happened?
She was running down
a lead in Moscow.
She's missed two
of her scheduled call-ins.
Well, what are you
doing about it?
Speaking to you.
Even if we knew
where in Russia Lyla is,
my superiors believe sending in
an extraction team
could cause
an international incident.
As far
as they're concerned,
she's already
a framed picture
on our lobby wall.
Why are you
telling me all this?
Because I know how you and
Oliver Queen spend your nights.
And I know
your passport is up to date.
It would help to start
with what Lyla
was doing in Moscow
in the first place.
What was this lead
she was tracking down?
A line on the whereabouts
of Floyd Lawton.
Deadshot.
Lyla
was in Russia for me,
Agent Michaels is an asset
I can't easily replace.
I know you find her
similarly irreplaceable.
Bring her home,
Mr. Diggle.
Thanks.
It's been a while
since I arrested you.
I'd forgotten
how good it feels.
I was working
for...him.
Him who?
The guy who cost you
your shield.
I'm on his team.
You are, too.
Anybody else
having serious deja vu?
That's all right,
we're letting him go.
Our mistake.
He was just in the wrong place
at the wrong time.
Ok, uh, let's just
get out of here
before anyone
changes their mind.
The potentially
catastrophic risk
of turning on this machine
far outweigh any scientific gain
that might come from it.
The people need to understand
just how dangerous
technology like this is.
And the very real possibility
of a cataclysmic event.
Where'd you go?
Is everything ok?
Yeah. Just need
a few personal days.
What's going on?
Have to help a friend.
Who?
Lyla Michaels.
It's his spy girlfriend
that works for A.R.G.U.S.
She went to Russia
looking for Deadshot,
for me. Now she's missing.
Felicity...
I think it's time we visited our
Queen Consolidated
subsidiary in Moscow.
Yeah.
Oliver, what are you doing?
Just need
to help a friend.
I can't ask you to do that.
You didn't.
Sara...
My name's Ivo.
What's your name?
Tommy.
So.
How did you come
to be on this island, Tommy?
I assume it wasn't
by choice.
My, uh...
Boat was shipwrecked here.
And I was the only survivor.
Well, I'm sorry
to hear that.
Did you explore
the island much?
Some of it.
Why?
You didn't happen
to run across
a Japanese Imperial Navy
submarine, did you?
During World War II,
every country was trying to develop
the ultimate weapon.
The United States had the
Manhattan Project, of course;
the Nazis had das Uranverein.
And the Japanese, well,
they had Mirakuru.
Stem cell
and genetic therapies,
decades ahead
of their time.
Every war
advances the cause
of science.
And the Japanese,
they had developed a serum
that caused
increased strength.
Rapid cell regeneration.
They called it Mirakuru.
"Miracle."
Thought they could
create an army of super soldiers.
They were transporting
their only supply
via submarine
when that sub came under
heavy fire by the allied forces.
And it ran aground in
this chain of islands.
Thanks to you...
We now know
it's this island.
You killed my friends.
Which means
it's up to you...
To help us
find that sub.
Are you forgetting
something?
Where do you think you're going?
Tahiti.
That's funny.
The flight manifest
says you're going to Moscow.
Well, we're going
to stop by there,
you know, after Tahiti.
What kind of partner
decides to interact
with our overseas holdings behind
the other one's back?
It was an oversight.
Oh.
Well, lucky
for our partnership,
I'm a fast packer.
Oliver, her tagging along
does not help matters any.
I will take care of her. John.
We're going to bring Lyla back.
Wherever she is.
I've arranged a meeting
with the chief operating officer
of our Moscow subsidiary
tomorrow at 10:00 a.m.
Try your hardest
not to miss this one.
You know, I'm not this person
that you seem to think I am.
That depends.
On what?
On if I think you use
the corporate jet
for a weekend of fun
with your assistant.
Excuse me?
A blonde I.T. girl
all of a sudden  gets promoted
to be assistant
to the C.E.O.?
There are only two ways that happens.
One is nepotism,
and she doesn't look
like your cousin.
That...is...
absolutely not happening.
What were her
qualifications?
Aside from an abundance
of short skirts.
Her skirts aren't
that...short.
What was that about?
Nothing.
Everything
with Knyazev is set.
You have friends
in the Russian mafia?
Color me at not
at all surprised.
You're going straight
to the hotel in a cab.
No, you're leaving me
with her?!
Dig and I need
to get a drink.
Well...I...wouldn't
mind a drink.
Ms. Loring.
Didn't take you
for the club-hopping type.
Well, I'm here
on business.
Is everything ok with my mom?
We need to discuss
something about this case.
Your boyfriend Roy
was arrested last night.
I know, but it was actually
a misunderstanding.
He got released.
Well, a few reporters
got hold of the story
and they now know you're
dating a known felon.
Thea, your mother is on
trial for her life.
Her whole defense pivots
on being seen as a loving mother
who did what she had to do
to protect her children,
what kind of parent
she was.
We need the people
to know that she raised you
to make good decisions.
So if you care
about your mom,
you're going to have to end
this relationship immediately.
Oliver Queen? Ha!
My favorite American!
Dabro pazhalavat.
It has been too long.
John Diggle, this is
Anatoly Knyazev.
Thank you for meeting us.
If Oliver vouches for you,
you're my second favorite
American.
First, a toast.
None for me, thanks.
Prochnost.
To strength.
Now. Business.
This is woman
you look for, yes?
Picture is from two days ago,
from gulag--
prison.
Lyla was arrested?
Not quite. From what I hear,
she was trying to break in.
Why?
I do not know.
But clearly she had issues
breaking back out.
Gulag, worst in Russia.
It's called Koshmar.
The nightmare.
It's full
of violent psychopaths
and killers.
And that's just the guards.
Anatoly, we need a way
into the gulag to extract her.
You get in, you get shot
before you get out.
Or end up like your friend.
Mmm, it's impossible.
The only thing
that's impossible
is us leaving this country
without this woman.
I like this guy.
We have no word
for "optimist" in Russian.
The only way in to Koshmar
is as prisoner.
Now, I have guard there,
owes me favor.
It could work.
I'll give you one shot in twenty.
Set it up. I'll go.
No.
It has to be me.
Oliver, what if something
happens to you in there?
What happens to me,
Felicity, or Isabel, for that matter?
You have to be on the outside
making the moves.
I'll go inside.
I've got this.
Now that is a lot of drugs.
Courtesy of Knyazev.
About enough weight to
land me in the Koshmar.
You need to be wearing this
when they process you.
Guards will take it,
but that's the point.
This...
Is Knyazev's man
inside the prison.
A guard.
He'll know where in the gulag
Lyla is being held.
When all hell
breaks loose,
you need to meet us at the
rendezvous point with Lyla, or...
Or I am
a permanent Russian.
Just thinking out loud...
But, are we sure this is the best plan
we can come up with?
I know Lyla's
your friend, but...
Felicity, Lyla
isn't my friend.
She was my wife.
Explain that sentence.
Lyla and I met in the army back
in Afghanistan.
But we didn't stay married long
once we got stateside.
Couldn't figure out a way to
stay married without a war to fight.
So she joined
A.R.G.U.S.,
and I circled back
for my third tour.
I can't leave here
without her, Felicity.
Just can't.
Two minute warning.
Good luck, John.
They have him.
Clock's running.
Zhivey, zhivey.
Hurry up.
Khoroshaya kurtka.
What, uh, crime
fits your punishment?
Drugs. And you?
I gave speech.
About government corruption.
Right.
It is rare to see one
of your people in Koshmar.
What, American?
Chernokozhiy.
Ehh...
Chernokozhiy
not popular here.
Shocker.
You think Dig's ok?
I think he's doing
the same as he was
when you asked me
five minutes ago.
They're coming.
They sell us Russian
police truck for cheap.
Vot mashina,
kotoraya vam nuzhna.
Sto pyatisot tysyach rubley.
Na koleni.
Yesli vy sde syete eto,
moi lyudi vas,
I vashi deti
osanutsya sirotami.
What'd you say?
Please.
You know, in Russia,
there is gulag.
Almost as bad as this.
Sara--
Don't say my name.
If they find out we know each other,
they'll kill us both.
I thought you drowned.
When I came up,
the boat was gone.
And I thought you were, too.
And I was floating out there
for days when this ship...
They found me.
And they saved me.
Is that why
you're helping them?
I don't have a choice.
I need to warn
my friends.
You said they were dead.
They're not
that easy to kill.
Try not to move.
It smells like puke!
It'll heal your wounds.
You have to go.
Get out of here.
Get to higher ground.
I'm not leaving you.
I will not
be the reason
something
happens to you.
Then we're in agreement.
Because I make
my own choices.
You are a strong woman.
When I care about someone,
there's nothing I won't do for them.
Another thing...
we have in common.
The burns, they're lowering
your body temperature.
Here.
Where you been all night?
Working.
Oh.
Well,
you deserve a break.
Um, actually,
I've been thinking.
Maybe we should
take some space.
I mean, we work together
and live together.
It's kind of getting hard
to breathe.
Since when?
Oh, wait, does this have to with
that lawyer lady dropping by?
No, this has
to do with the fact
that you've been
arrested twice in the last month.
Come on. I've been
trying to stay out of trouble.
My body hasn't
had a scratch on it in weeks.
Well, I mean, excluding the ones
that you put there.
And the other night?
Was a misunderstanding.
Roy...
This just isn't working, ok?
Not for me.
Thea,
you can't mean that.
I do.
I'm sorry.
Those men...
They are Vory.
They are in charge.
It's best
to stay away.
Got it.
Listen, I'm looking for a
guard named Sergei Pavelski.
American...
You are suka now.
Are we seriously
going to do this?
Guess so.
Fighting strictly prohibited.
Vodki, pozhaluysta.
You missed the tour.
What happened
to you?
I saw a Russian vehicle
that I simply had to have.
Is that why you came to Russia?
Car shopping?
Oh, I just ordered one.
One's for me.
This cold room.
Six hours for you.
Six hours? You can't
keep me in here that long.
Now seven hours.
Well, that was
pretty stupid...
Then again,
you never really were
one of the brightest guys.
Deadshot.
Your spine
frozen through yet?
Trust me.
My problem here
isn't with the cold.
What, you still haven't forgiven
me for shooting your brother?
Man, you really
hold a grudge.
I know why you're here.
That girl.
From A.R.G.U.S.
Lyla didn't find a lead on you.
She found you.
Does everyone
really think
that Felicity and I are...
No.
Just everyone who works
at Queen Consolidated.
She's just a friend.
You don't seem like the kind of man
who has female friends.
Can I ask you
a personal question?
With some vodka in me,
I just might answer.
Why does saving
my family's company
mean so much to you?
Despite what Sheryl Sandberg
might say...
It still isn't that easy to make it
as a woman in business.
I've...given up a lot.
Which means if I don't
succeed at everything,
then what was the point?
Hmm.
May I ask you
a personal question?
Others have tried
and failed.
Why do you try so hard to make me
think that you're a lazy idiot?
I know you're not.
Underneath that swagger,
I see you pretty clearly.
Really?
And what do you see?
You're intelligent.
Driven.
And lonely.
How do you see that?
Because it's what I see
when I look in the mirror.
We don't have much time.
There you go.
Let's go, let's go.
Nice seeing you,
John.
You speak Russian.
I was raised in Moscow
until I was nine.
And then adopted by a family
that took me to America.
Took me years
to get rid of my accent.
It isn't easy making friends
in grade school when
you sound like Natasha.
I...Don't have
a lot of time.
I'll be quick.
Five minutes.
Must hurry.
Remind me to get you a pack
of cigarettes when this is all over.
I don't smoke.
You weren't going
to leave without me, were you?
I should kill you
right now!
You won't.
Why?
Because.
I'm the only one who knows
where your little girlfriend is.
You're not stupid.
You wouldn't put yourself
in here without an exit strategy.
I take you to the girl...
You take me out.
Isabel,
I have to go.
Sorry.
Do I strike you as someone
who needs to cuddle?
Hi.
It's time. Ready?
Yeah, I--
I think she can take
the night off. Don't you?
Ohh.
Felicity...
It--what happens in Russia
stays in Russia.
Even when it makes
no sense whatsoever.
Guessin', uh, you want
to hold on to that.
This way.
What
were you thinking?
What?
Over 64 million women
over the age of consent
in Russia
and you sleep with her.
So we're not doing
the "What happens in Russia
stays in Russia?"
We're still in Russia.
There is nothing money cannot buy
in this country.
Diggle should be heading out
Lyla in two minutes.
Well, breaking out
of prison is harder than it looks.
You of all people
should know that.
Stay quiet.
Follow me.
You'll remember
the rest of us...
Yes?
I promise.
I'll come back.
Come on.
Are we making a swim for it?
No. They'd shoot us
the second we hit the water.
You said your friends,
they have one
of the radios
from the ship, right?
Yeah.
You look like you know
what you're doing there.
In the past year, I've learned a lot of
things I never expected to.
You and me both.
They won't respond
unless they hear your voice.
Shado.
Ni néng tingdào wo ma?
Slade.
Can you hear me?
Thank God you're alive.
Yeah, I'm on the freighter--
Sara, what are you doing?
There's only
two of them.
They haven't moved
from the location of the mortar attack.
What the hell is going on here?
You just confirmed
that your friends are alive.
Which means
they're still a threat.
You know, until
we kill them.
You son of a bitch--oh!
If I say she's in there,
what's keeping you
from shooting me?
Honor.
You should
try it some time.
Lyla!
Johnny?
Ready to go home?
You came for me.
I always have. Always will.
Deadshot's here.
In the prison.
I know.
What's your extraction plan?
Depends.
What time is it?
Let's go, go, go,
move, move, move!
This way.
Got it.
I shut down the phones.
The guards can't call for help.
Your friend and that woman
are not here by now,
they will not
be here at all.
Much better.
Oliver, get down!
Follow me! Move!
We're clear.
Stop the truck.
Get out.
Get out!
Move.
That's the thing
about honor, John.
You can't
turn it on and off.
I'm just curious.
How is it you think your brother
ended up dead?
You shot a client
that Andy was protecting,
and you missed.
I don't miss.
Your brother
was the contract.
Who would want to kill Andy?
I don't know the names,
just an alias.
Hive.
Food for thought, John.
Food for thought.
Are we going to discuss what
happened last night?
Why would we?
No reason.
I'll see you
in the office tomorrow.
Thank you.
You had my back.
And now you know
what it feels like.
Wh--what are you--
what are you doing here?
Good question.
I've gotten a lot of calls
from prison,
but never from my
girlfriend's mother.
It occurred to me
that I've never been given
the opportunity
to meet the man in your life.
I don't know
if she told you,
but your daughter
kind of dumped me.
And what you should know
is that she did it for me.
Jean told me
she came to see you.
I told her
she shouldn't have.
Why didn't you just
tell me the truth?
Us being together...
It can hurt her case.
Thea...
Your social life is not
going to be the determining
factor in my trial.
Sweetheart, what you've
had to endure this last year
is more than most people
go through in two lifetimes.
But you've not only survived,
you've flourished.
I think a lot of that
has to do with Roy.
So, as your mother,
I forbid you not to see him.
Thank you.
I have to admit,
this is not how I anticipated
my trip to Russia ending.
I just feel lucky
we made it out of there alive.
Thank you.
Not just for coming for me.
For doing what
you had to once you did.
You mean working
with Deadshot.
You know, me and Carly
broke up because I couldn't love her
and hate him
at the same time.
I'm honored
to be the exception.
Lyla, you're always
the exception.
♪ Wonder if you'd ever settle
♪ and I think you always will
I have a debrief
with A.R.G.U.S. at 0800.
No, no,
let Waller stew.
Stay for breakfast.
Throw in your blueberry pancakes and
you may be able to convince me.
♪ What I feel now
about you then ♪
♪ I'm just glad
I can explain ♪
Can you deliver
this to Isabel's office, please?
Why her?
I mean, besides the...
obvious leggy model reason.
It just
kind of happened.
It didn't mean
anything.
Hey.
Because of the life
that I lead...
I just think that
it's better to not...
Be with someone
that I could really care about.
Well, I think...
I think you deserve
better than her.
We have their location.
This one's no longer
of use to us.
Let's see
how good you are...
At removing a bullet
from your head.
Wait!
He could
still be useful.
She's right.
Once we get rid
of his friends,
we'll need him to lead
us to the graves.
Sometimes I wonder
who gives the orders here.
You...
or your little bouzin.
You're going back
to the island.
Oliver.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man