PREVIOUSLY ON "ARROW"...
-LYLA?
-WE NEED TO TALK ABUT JOHN.
HE'S BACK IN THE COUNTRY,
AND HE'S IN PRISON.
OLIVER: WE ARE GONNA
BREAK HIM OUT.
HEY, JOHN.
I'M NOT SAYING YOU
SHOULDN'T DO YOUR
PENANCE,
BUT DO IT
AS SPARTAN.
ADRIAN: CHURCH IS
PLANNING SOMETHING,
SOMETHING BIG.
YOU'RE TALKING
ABOUT THE TRUST.
AT LEAST WE DEFINITELY
KNOW WHERE CHURCH IS NOW.
WE GOT TO PUT HIM DOWN.
GO! DO NOT DIE!
[THUNK]
-GET HIM TO SAFETY.
-BUT...
GO!
CHURCH: DON'T KILL HIM.
HE MAY HAVE HIS USES.
WE ARE NOT GONNA
WRITE OFF RENE.
WE'RE GONNA FIND HIM,
WE'RE GONNA BRING
HIM BACK...
WHEREVER HE IS.
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLES]
[DRIP]
[CRACK]
HA HA HA!
THE TRUST GOES
TO THE BRACE.
0-4 IN 72.
[MOANING]
HOW YOU FEELING,
MY FRIEND?
YOU CAN KEEP GOING
WITH THE FOREPLAY,
BUT I'M NEVER GIVING
YOU WHAT YOU WANT.
YOU REMIND ME
OF THIS OTHER GUY
I ONCE TORTURED,
MAYBE BIGGER,
A LITTLE MORE MUSCLE
ON THE FRAME.
HEH. I DON'T KNOW.
LOOK.
I WAS CONVERSING
WITH THIS SON OF A BITCH
JUST LIKE YOU AND I
HAVE BEEN CONVERSING
FOR THE PAST, WHAT,
20 HOURS OR SO.
MY KNUCKLES HURT,
EVEN WITH THE BRASS.
I NEEDED A SHOWER,
MY LADY WAS WAITING
FOR ME,
AND THIS GUY WOULD
JUST NOT GIVE ME
WHAT I NEEDED,
NOT UNLIKE YOU.
SO I SAID TO MYSELF,
"TOBIAS, MAKE
THIS GUY FEEL PAIN
LIKE NOBODY WHO'S
EVER LIVED,"
AND THEN IT CLICKED.
IT'S NOT THE PAIN
THAT BREAKS PEOPLE.
IT'S FEAR...
FEAR OF THAT PAIN,
OF WHAT THAT PAIN
BRINGS,
OF WHAT
HAPPENS NEXT.
YOU'RE NOT GONNA
FINISH THE STORY?
CHURCH: HUH? OH.
I GOT WHAT I WANTED
FROM THAT GUY.
HEY.
SO YOU MIGHT WANT
TO THINK ABOUT THAT
THE NEXT TIME I ASK
YOU A QUESTION.
MAN: AGH!
TOBIAS CHURCH...
WHERE IS HE?
DON'T KNOW.
EVEN IF I DID,
WHATEVER YOU'RE
GONNA DO TO ME,
HE'S WORSE.
HOW SURE ARE YOU
ABOUT THAT?
UNH!
HEY. YOU'RE A LOT CUTER
THAN THE GREEN GUY.
AW, YOU'RE KIND OF
CUTE, TOO,
IN A "I FEEL SORRY
FOR YOU" KIND OF WAY.
WHERE'S CHURCH?
YEAH? WHO WANTS
TO KNOW?
OLIVER: THE GREEN GUY!
WHERE'S CHURCH?
LOOK OUT!
YOU OK?
I'M BETTER
THAN THIS SCHMUCK.
CHURCH...ADDRESS NOW!
I HEARD HE'S SOMEWHERE
NORTHWEST OF HERE,
MAYBE BY THE WATER.
HALF THE CITY'S
ON THE WATER.
I SWEAR THAT'S
ALL I KNOW.
[TYPING]
COME ON.
HOW'S IT GOING?
I WOULD PUNCH
THIS MONITOR
IF I DIDN'T KNOW
HOW MUCH IT COST.
ALSO, IT WOULD PROBABLY
REALLY HURT.
CAN YOU GET OFF
YOUR FEET, PLEASE?
OLIVER TOLD ME THAT
YOU WERE BACK TO WORK
A WEEK AFTER YOU
WERE SHOT
BY THE CLOCK KING.
SHOT IN THE SHOULDER,
NOT A KNIFE
IN THE BACK.
I DON'T NEED YOU
TO REMIND ME.
I HAVE EXCRUCIATING
AGONY TO DO THAT.
[VIBRATING]
WHO'S THAT?
HMM? TELEMARKETER.
TELL ME YOU'VE HAD BETTER
LUCK THAN I'VE HAD.
WE MIGHT HAVE
NARROWED IT DOWN
TO THE NORTHWEST
PART OF THE CITY.
EVELYN: YEAH, SO NOW
WE'RE LOOKING
FOR A NEEDLE IN A SLIGHTLY
SMALLER HAYSTACK.
I WILL RUN
AN ALGORITHM,
CROSS-REFERENCING
TRAFFIC CAMS
WITH PROBABLE
LOCATIONS.
WOW! THIS PLACE JUST GOT
REALLY CROWDED.
HEY.
DO PEOPLE JUST
WALK INTO YOUR
SECRET BASE
OF OPERATIONS?
-YES.
-THIS IS...
-SPARTAN...I'M GUESSING.
YOU GUYS MUST BE
THE NEW KIDS
ON THE BLOCK.
MORE LIKE
THE BACKSTREET BOYS.
IT WAS FUNNY
IN MY HEAD.
THIS IS RORY REGAN
AND EVELYN SHARP.
JOHN DIGGLE,
AND YOU ARE
MISSING A MAN...
RENE RAMIREZ.
LYLA CALLED
IN ARGUS FOR
THE SEARCH.
UNFORTUNATELY, SHE'S
TURNED UP NOTHING.
IT'S GOING AROUND.
WE ARE GONNA FIND RENE,
AND WE'RE NOT GONNA
GIVE UP HOPE WHILE
WE'RE DOING IT.
I HAVE AN EARLY MEETING
AT CITY HALL.
I WILL CHECK IN
WITH EVERYBODY SOON.
IS IT JUST
MY IMAGINATION,
OR DID OLIVER JUST
SEEM...
OPTIMISTIC.
THAT'S NOT USUALLY
A WORD I'D ASSOCIATE
WITH HIS DEMEANOR.
THANK YOU.
RENE?
SLOW. WHAT ABOUT
THE ACU?
TOO MANY COPS
ON CHURCH'S DIME
KEEPING HIM
5 STEPS AHEAD,
AND WITH CONAHAN GONE
AND CHURCH'S ASSAULT
ON THE ACU,
I'M THINKING WE GOT TO BRING
MORE MEN INTO THE FOLD.
WELL, DO WE HAVE
ENOUGH GUYS THAT
WE CAN TRUST?
PIKE SAYS THAT A BUNCH
OF HIS MEN HAVE VOLUNTEERED
SINCE THE ATTACK
ON THE ACU,
SO IF YOU WANT,
I CAN VET THEM,
AND I CAN, YOU KNOW,
MAKE SURE THERE'S
NO BAD APPLES.
PLEASE. LET'S
GET THAT DONE.
LOOK. I KNOW THIS IS
ONE OF THE LAST THINGS
YOU WANT TO BE
DEALING WITH RIGHT NOW,
BUT THE REZONING VOTE
IS IN A FEW DAYS.
ALLOWING US TO EXPAND
LOW-INCOME HOUSING
IN ORCHID BAY.
YEAH, YEAH.
OK. WELL, WE NEED
A 4/5 MAJORITY VOTE
FROM CITY COUNCIL
IN ORDER TO PASS
THE ORDINANCE, AND...
WHO ARE THE HOLDOUTS?
ONLY ONE THAT
REALLY MATTERS...
COUNCILMAN KULLENS.
EHH, HE IS DECIDEDLY
ANTIRESIDENTIAL.
I WAS GONNA SAY HE'S
THE MOST STUBBORN MAN
IN THE CITY
COMPARED TO YOU,
BUT THAT WORKS.
LET'S GET INTO IT.
ANATOLY,
WHAT IS THIS?
IT IS TIME,
MY FRIEND.
ENGLISH WILL
SUFFICE, VIKTOR.
FINE.
WHAT DOES BRATVA
MEAN TO YOU, OLIVER QUEEN?
BROTHERHOOD.
ANATOLY: BROTHERHOOD
IS FAMILY.
WHO ARE YOURS?
MY FATHER'S DEAD.
MY MOTHER
AND SISTER...
BOTH DEAD.
BRATVA ONLY KNOW
THEIR BROTHERS.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT
I MEAN BY THIS?
I HAVE NO FAMILY,
I HAVE NO HOME,
I HAVE NO NAME.
[SPEAKING RUSSIAN]
WE'RE AT THE LATEST
PROBABLE, OVERWATCH,
BUT IT'S ANOTHER
DEAD END.
TRY NOT TO USE
THAT PHRASE.
-IS THAT...
-BLOOD? LOOKS LIKE.
SCRATCH THAT.
WE THINK THIS IS
WHERE RENE
WAS BEING HELD.
-WAS?
-BLOOD'S STILL FRESH.
THEY MUST HAVE
JUST MOVED HIM.
KH-10 SHOWS A PANEL VAN
MOVING FROM THAT LOCATION
40 MINUTES AGO.
CAN YOU TRACK IT?
I HAVE BEEN ABLE TO
EVERY OTHER TIME
SOMEBODY ASKED ME
THAT QUESTION.
-GOT IT.
-WHERE?
THIS IS A LITTLE AWKWARD,
BUT OLIVER MADE ME PROMISE
THAT IF WE GOT OUR LOCATION
ON RENE I WOULD ONLY
SHARE IT WITH HIM.
THAT'S ACTUALLY NOT
SURPRISING AT ALL.
LEST I FORGET...
SO YOU CAN PAY
THE FERRY.
HEH HEH HEH.
WHY, MAN?
BECAUSE YOU PISSED
ME OFF.
NO. WHY THIS CITY?
I MEAN, WHY COME HERE?
NOW WHY ARE YOU
ASKING ME THAT NOW?
IF I'M GONNA
DIE TONIGHT,
IT'D BE NICE
TO KNOW WHY.
FROM WHAT I HEARD,
YOU WERE POPPING
IN BLUDHAVEN
AND HUB CITY.
WHY YOU MESSING
WITH US?
AHH.
FOR YOUR
WATER ACCESS.
PSSS.
SERIOUSLY.
THROUGH STAR CITY'S
DOCKS, I CAN MOVE
THOUSANDS OF TONS
OF HEROIN, SLAM,
VERTIGO.
I'M WORKING
ON THE BIGGEST
CONSOLIDATION
OF DRUG ENTERPRISES
ANYBODY HAS EVER SEEN.
ONLY THING I'M WAITING
FOR IS THE GREEN ARROW
TO GET OUT
OF THE PICTURE.
LITTLE MAN,
THAT GRAVE AIN'T
GONNA DIG ITSELF.
SO HOW ABOUT YOU DO
THE DIGGING YOURSELF?
OH, YOU THINK
I'M AFRAID TO GET
MY HANDS DIRTY, HUH?
UNH!
YEAH, DIG!
AGH!
[RENE GROANS]
HEY. ARE YOU OK?
I THOUGHT CHURCH
WOULD PUT UP
MORE OF A FIGHT.
PROBABLY REALIZED
HE DIDN'T HAVE TO.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
I WAS HURTING SO BAD,
IT...IT GOT SO I COULDN'T
EVEN SEE STRAIGHT.
BARELY EVEN REMEMBER
TELLING HIM.
TELLING HIM WHAT?
WHO YOU ARE.
HE KNOWS YOU'RE
OLIVER QUEEN.
SHOULD HAVE BEEN
OUT THERE WITH YOU
TONIGHT, OLIVER.
DIG, YOU SAID
YOU NEEDED TIME.
DON'T BE AFRAID
TO TAKE IT,
AND TONIGHT WOULD
NOT HAVE MADE
ANY DIFFERENCE.
CHURCH DIDN'T
WANT TO FIGHT.
HE WANTED TO RUN.
THAT'S BECAUSE HE KNOWS
KILLING THE MAYOR
IS A LOT EASIER
THAN KILLING
THE GREEN ARROW.
WHAT? WE WERE ALL
THINKING IT.
I TOLD RENE TO
STAND DOWN AND RECOVER.
EVELYN AND RORY
ARE GONNA WATCH
THEA AND QUENTIN
IN CASE CHURCH TRIES
TO GET AT ME THROUGH THEM.
HOW'S CURTIS DOING?
SAYS HE WANTS TO
GET BACK AT IT.
THEN LET'S GET HIM
ON LYLA AND J.J.
WELL, GOOD. I'LL HAVE
FELICITY'S BACK.
OLIVER, I KNOW YOU HAVE
A SECURITY DETAIL,
BUT YOU MIGHT AS WELL
HAVE A BULL'S-EYE
PAINTED ON YOUR HEAD.
JOHN, I CAN
DISAPPEAR AGAIN.
I'M STILL DEALING
WITH THE FALLOUT
FROM NOT BEING AROUND
WHEN THE ACU WAS ATTACKED,
AND THERE IS ACTUALLY
A REZONING VOTE THAT
NEEDS MY ATTENTION.
WHOA. WAIT.
DOESN'T A VOTE TAKE
A BACKSEAT TO
FINDING CHURCH
BEFORE HE TELLS
EVERY CRIMINAL
IN THE CITY WHO
YOU ARE?
I HAVE SECURITY.
I'LL BE FINE.
HAVE YOU EVER...
HAS HE EVER
ACTUALLY SAID THAT
AND IT TURNED OUT
TO BE TRUE?
DO YOU AGREE WITH HER?
WELL, I KNOW I SAID
IT WAS A GOOD IDEA
TO START A TEAM,
BUT WHAT DO WE HAVE...
A LAUREL LANCE WANNABE,
A WEIRD RAG GUY,
A LUNATIC, AND CURTIS?
CURTIS JUST WASN'T
WHO I PICTURED.
UH...AHEM...
THEY HAVE POTENTIAL.
ONE OF THEM GOT
THEMSELVES CAPTURED
AND GAVE UP
YOUR NAME.
AND I'D LIKE YOU
TO DEBRIEF HIM.
DEBRIEF HIM?
CHURCH TOLD RENE THAT
HE'S PLANNING SOMETHING,
SOMETHING BIG ENOUGH
TO INVOLVE 5 CITIES.
SO CHURCH JUST GAVE
UP HIS MASTER PLAN?
HE THOUGHT RENE
WAS GONNA BE DEAD
5 MINUTES LATER.
CHURCH IS TRYING TO
CONSOLIDATE THE DRUG TRADE
THROUGH STAR CITY,
BUT HE WAS WAITING
FOR THE GREEN ARROW
TO BE GONE
BEFORE HE MADE HIS MOVE.
OK. WELL, IF THAT'S
TRUE, I THINK I KNOW
A WAY WE CAN TURN THIS
TO OUR ADVANTAGE.
I'M ALL EARS.
OLIVER, I KNOW A GUY,
VERY SPECIFIC SKILL SET.
I THINK HE CAN BE HERE
IN 24 HOURS.
DID YOU GET MY MESSAGE?
YEAH. QUENTIN AND I
CAN TAKE CARE
OF OURSELVES.
STILL DOESN'T HURT
TO HAVE A SHADOW.
IS COUNCILMAN KULLENS
IN THERE?
YES. HE'S WAITING
IN YOUR OFFICE
WITH SUSAN WILLIAMS.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH,
FELLAS.
I DIDN'T AGREE
TO AN INTERVIEW.
YEAH? WELL, SHE'S
SHADOWING HIM
FOR SOME TYPE
OF PROFILE,
AND I ALREADY TRIED
TO GET HER KICKED OUT,
BUT HE WAS ADAMANT
ABOUT HAVING HER
IN THERE.
ANY ADVICE?
DON'T SCREW IT UP.
COUNCILMAN KULLENS.
HI.
MS. WILLIAMS,
IT'S A PLEASURE
TO FINALLY MEET YOU.
REALLY? HAVE YOU
WATCHED ANY
OF MY PIECES?
I HAVE, AND I THINK
YOU'RE OFF THE MARK
IN CERTAIN
INSTANCES.
IS THAT
ON THE RECORD?
IF YOU WANT TO
GET AN ACTUAL QUOTE,
MS. WILLIAMS,
YOU CAN GO THROUGH
ALL THE PROPER
CHANNELS.
THIS MEETING IS
STRICTLY ABOUT
THE REZONING
ORDINANCE.
YES. COUNCILMAN,
AS YOU KNOW,
I RAN ON A PLATFORM
OF UNITY,
BUT IT IS DIFFICULT
FOR A CITY TO BE UNITED
WHEN SO MUCH
OF THE ZONING WITHIN IT
REMAINS EXCLUSIONARY.
WE NEED TO OPEN IT UP,
ALLOW FOR MORE
AFFORDABLE HOUSING,
GIVE THE PEOPLE A CHANCE
TO START OVER AND REBUILD,
BUT THE SECOND
THE MONEY STARTS
ROLLING IN,
THOSE FAMILIES
GET SQUEEZED OUT
BY CRONY CAPITALISTS.
THAT'S NOT GONNA
HAPPEN HERE.
HARD TO BELIEVE
CONSIDERING YOUR
FAMILY'S HISTORY.
I'M SORRY, COUNCILMAN.
I DON'T FOLLOW.
WELL, THE TYPE
OF REZONING
YOU'RE PROPOSING
HAPPENED DOWNTOWN
25 YEARS AGO,
BUT INSTEAD
OF AFFORDABLE HOUSING,
WE GOT SKYRISES,
AND ONE OF THEM BECAME
THE OFFICES
OF QUEEN CONSOLIDATED.
IS THAT TRUE,
MR. MAYOR?
I'LL CONSIDER THAT
A NO COMMENT.
I CAN TELL YOU HAVE
GOOD INTENTIONS,
BUT POLITICS IS
THE ART OF THE REAL.
I'M SORRY.
I'M NOT CHANGING MY VOTE.
OK. MAYBE YOU SHOULD
JUST PUT AN ARROW IN HIM.
BILLY: THAT WAS A BIT
MORE THAN I EXPECTED
TO GET DONE
ON MY LUNCH BREAK.
HEH HEH.
IS THIS A NORMAL
WEDNESDAY AFTERNOON FOR YOU?
WELL, I HAD TO MAKE UP
FOR LAST NIGHT.
I HATE CANCELING
LAST MINUTE.
I GOT A FEELING
I'M GONNA BE THE ONE
CANCELING ON YOU
FOR A CHANGE.
I GOT A PROMOTION.
I SIGNED ON
WITH THE ACU.
OLIVER'S
ANTI-CRIME UNIT.
THIS ISN'T GONNA BE
WEIRD, RIGHT?
-HMM?
-ME REPORTING
TO YOUR EX-FIANCE.
YEAH. WHAT COULD
POSSIBLY WE WEIRD
ABOUT THAT?
-FELICITY?
-MM-HMM?
DOES MAYOR QUEEN KNOW
THAT WE'RE SEEING
EACH OTHER?
IT REALLY DOESN'T
HELP IF YOU CALL HIM
MAYOR QUEEN.
FELICITY?
DEFINITELY. YEAH.
HE'S DEFINITELY...
DEFINITELY AWARE
OF YOU.
RENE: LOVE WHAT YOU'VE
DONE WITH THE PLACE.
HEH. IT'S NOT MUCH, MAN,
BUT IT'S HOME,
AND IT'S SAFE,
ESPECIALLY NOW THAT
FELICITY'S TECHED UP
THE PLACE.
-THANKS FOR COMING OUT.
-NO PROBLEM, MAN.
LET'S JUST GET THIS
OVER WITH,
BUT I GOT TO TELL YOU
THERE'S NOTHING
YOU COULD TELL ME THAT
I HAVEN'T ALREADY
TOLD MYSELF.
I'M TORN APART
OVER THIS.
IS THAT WHAT YOU
THINK THIS IS,
A LECTURE?
WHAT I DESERVE IS
A BEAT-DOWN.
WHEN'S THE LAST TIME
YOU LOOKED IN THE MIRROR.
BUT MAYBE SOMETHING GOOD
CAN COME OUT OF THIS, MAN,
LIKE...
I DON'T KNOW, MAYBE
YOU SAW SOMETHING,
HEARD SOMETHING THAT
CAN HELP US BRING
DOWN CHURCH.
I ALREADY TOLD
OLIVER EVERYTHING
I REMEMBER, MAN.
I KNOW, BUT...
BUT TRAUMATIC EVENTS
HAVE A WAY OF DOING
FUNNY THINGS
TO THE MEMORY,
AND IF YOU THINK
WHAT YOU WENT THROUGH
IS NOT TRAUMATIC,
AGAIN, I SAY MIRROR.
MY DAD TAUGHT ME
HOW TO TAKE A BEATING.
I KNOW, RENE.
YOU'RE TOUGH.
I GET THAT, MAN,
BUT THIS ISN'T
ABOUT BEING TOUGH, OK?
IT'S ABOUT...
[SIGHS]
LOOK, MAN.
I BEEN
WHERE YOU ARE, OK,
AND I KNOW IT'S
NOT EASY,
BUT IF WE TALK
ABOUT THIS
AND GO THROUGH IT
STEP BY STEP...
LOOK. I SAID
I DON'T KNOW.
I SHOULD BE OUT THERE
TRYING TO FIX THIS,
NOT IN HERE WITH YOU
PLAYING THERAPIST.
OLIVER SAYS STAY PUT.
AND I'M STAYING PUT.
BUT I DON'T REMEMBER
ANYTHING.
CHURCH: YEAH.
YEAH, SURE.
JUST MAKE SURE THE AMERTEK GEAR
GETS TO THE BRACE.
I WANT EVERYBODY
LOCKED AND LOADED.
NO, HE'S NOT GONNA
BE A PROBLEM.
THE GREEN ARROW WILL BE
DEAD BY THEN.
LOUIS, I'M GONNA NEED
TO HIT YOU BACK.
YOU LIKE THIS PLACE?
I'M GETTING
A PENTHOUSE BUILT.
GONNA LET ME SEE
THE WHOLE CITY.
I TOLD YOU
TO STAY AWAY
FROM THE GREEN ARROW.
I DON'T WORK FOR YOU,
AND THE GREEN ARROW
FOUND ME.
YOU KIDNAPPED
HIS PROTEGE.
SERENDIPITOUS ENCOUNTER.
AND YOUR LAST.
WHOO!
AFTER GETTING
THREATENED BY A FREAK,
I HIRED ONE OF MY OWN.
THIS WAS YOUR
SECOND WARNING.
THERE WON'T BE
A THIRD.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE
HIRING ME TO KILL
THE GREEN ARROW.
NOPE. YOU'RE GONNA
KILL THE MAYOR.
[ELEVATOR DINGS]
WHAT IS
SUSAN WILLIAMS DOING
IN YOUR OFFICE?
I AGREED TO
AN OFF-CAMERA INTERVIEW.
OK. COME HERE.
OK. SO DID YOU GO
OUT LAST NIGHT
AS THE G-GREEN ARROW
AND GET HIT
REALLY HARD
IN THE HEAD?
SUSAN WILLIAMS IS
IN OUR LIVES, THEA.
IF WE DON'T MAKE
HER AN ALLY,
THEN SHE'S GONNA
REMAIN AN ENEMY.
OK, BUT SHE'S POISON.
WELL, IT TURNS OUT
THAT IF YOU INGEST
SMALL AMOUNTS OF POISON
OVER TIME
YOU CAN DEVELOP
AN IMMUNITY.
[DOOR SHUTS]
GOOD MORNING.
WHEN I GOT YOUR CALL
LAST NIGHT,
I THOUGHT SOMEONE
IN MY OFFICE WAS PLAYING
A PRANK ON ME.
WELL, I THOUGHT THEA
MADE A GOOD POINT YESTERDAY
WHEN SHE SUGGESTED
THAT YOU GO THROUGH
THE PROPER CHANNELS.
PLEASE.
THE INTERVIEW
I HAD IN MIND WAS
GOING TO BE
ON CAMERA.
BABY STEPS.
MAY I ASK YOU
A QUESTION?
I DON'T THINK YOU
UNDERSTAND HOW THIS
INTERVIEW THING WORKS.
HAVE YOUR ATTACKS
ON MY ADMINISTRATION
BEEN PERSONAL,
OR ARE THEY
JUST GOOD RATINGS?
DON'T SEE WHY THEY
CAN'T BE BOTH.
WHY ARE YOU ASKING?
BECAUSE I'M TRYING TO
FIGURE OUT
HOW HARD I'M GONNA
HAVE TO WORK TO
WIN YOU OVER.
YOU SEEM LIKE
A NICE GUY,
BUT YOU'RE NOT
A REAL POLITICIAN.
I AM UNDERQUALIFIED.
VASTLY, AND THE CITY,
MY HOME, IS SUFFERING
BECAUSE OF IT.
I APPRECIATE
THE FACT THAT
I HAVEN'T EARNED
YOUR TRUST YET.
SUSAN, AS SOMEONE
WHO PROFESSES TO CARE
ABOUT STAR CITY,
I THINK THAT YOU OWE IT
TO THE PEOPLE OF STAR CITY
TO GIVE ME AN OPPORTUNITY
TO EARN THAT TRUST,
AND I PROMISE YOU
I CAN'T DO THAT
IF I'M SPENDING
ALL OF MY ENERGY
DODGING ALL OF THESE
GRENADES THAT YOU'RE
LOBBYING AT ME,
SO HERE'S MY IDEA.
YOU GIVE ME ONE MONTH
WITH NO ATTACKS.
LET ME SHOW YOU
WHAT I CAN DO,
AND IF I DON'T DELIVER...
IT'S OPEN SEASON.
ONE MONTH.
WHAT'S THIS?
MY PERSONAL CELL.
WHY WOULD I NEED THAT?
I THINK YOU CAN
FIGURE IT OUT.
ANATOLY: TO SURVIVORS
OF AMAZO.
MAY WE EXPERIENCE
AS MUCH SORROW
AS DROPS OF WINE
ABOUT TO BE LEFT IN GLASS.
-PROCHNOST.
I GET US MORE DRINKS,
SOMETHING STRONGER.
ALL RIGHT.
IT'S A PARTY, VIKTOR.
LET ME GET YOU
A DRINK.
YOU MAY HAVE PASSED
ALL THE TESTS
AND SAID ALL
THE RIGHT THINGS,
BUT I DO NOT BELIEVE
FOR A SECOND
YOU ARE BRATVA.
THEN YOU WEREN'T
PAYING ATTENTION
DURING THE CEREMONY,
I GUESS.
LOOK AROUND YOU.
THESE MEN ARE HERE
BECAUSE GOVERNMENT MEN
LIKE KOVAR HAVE
TAKEN EVERYTHING
FROM THEM.
THE BRATVA IS MEANS
TO BRING JUSTICE
FOR ALL THOSE CRIMES.
JUSTICE IS WHY I'M HERE.
HEH HEH HEH.
SOME AMERICAN CASTAWAY
WILL NEVER UNDERSTAND,
SO YOU CAN SAY ALL
THE WORDS THAT
ANATOLY FEEDS YOU,
BUT YOU'LL NEVER BE
ONE OF US,
AND YOU SHOULD KNOW
BY NOW WHAT WE DO
TO OUTSIDERS.
VIKTOR, YOU COME
TOAST OUR NEW BROTHER?
YES, OF COURSE.
CONGRATULATIONS,
BROTHER.
WHAT WAS THAT ABOUT?
THAT WAS NOTHING.
WHAT IS THIS?
BEST NOT ASK.
JUST DRINK.
HOW LONG YOU GONNA
BE STAYING HERE, MAN?
I'M A FUGITIVE, RENE.
I LIVE HERE,
AND UNTIL YOU HEAL UP,
WE'RE ROOMIES.
SO YOU FEEL MUCH MORE
LIKE TALKING?
WHY DON'T WE TALK
ABOUT THE TIME YOU
WERE TORTURED?
SURE.
IT WAS ABOUT
A YEAR AGO.
MY BROTHER ANDY DID IT.
YOU GOT TORTURED
BY YOUR BROTHER?
MM-HMM.
HE WAS WORKING
WITH DAMIEN DARHK.
OLIVER SAID YOU
REENLISTED.
THAT WHY?
PARTLY.
THAT ALSO WHY YOU
SIDELINED YOURSELF?
-THAT, TOO.
-HMM.
SO YOU'RE
EX-NAVY, RIGHT?
DISHONORABLY DISCHARGED.
REASON?
YOU KNOW SOMETHING, MAN?
YOU DON'T HAVE TO TELL ME.
WE WERE TRANSPORTING
A PRISONER,
ONE WHO HAD INFORMATION
WE NEEDED.
INTELLIGENCE OFFICERS
COULDN'T GET IT
OUT OF HIM,
SO...
I TRIED TO DO IT MY WAY.
YOU PUT A BEATING
ON HIM.
I'VE BEEN THINKING
A LOT ABOUT THAT
DECISION.
PARTICULARLY SINCE YOU'VE
BEEN ON THE OTHER SIDE
OF THAT BEAT-DOWN,
RIGHT?
BECAUSE I SCREWED UP
AGAIN.
THAT'S MY LIFE, MAN,
AND NOW YOU ASKING ME
TO RELIVE MY LATEST
AND GREATEST.
THAT'S RIGHT, RENE.
IF YOU WANT TO HELP US,
IF YOU WANT TO GIVE US
ANYTHING THAT COULD
BRING DOWN CHURCH,
I'M AFRAID YOU'RE
GONNA HAVE TO.
OK.
WHAT DO I DO?
OLIVER: COUNCILMAN,
THANK YOU FOR
COMING BACK.
I'M AFRAID YOU'RE JUST
WASTING BOTH OF OUR TIMES.
MAYBE. AFTER YOU
EDUCATED US ON
QUEEN CONSOLIDATED,
THEA AND I THOUGHT
WE WOULD DO SOME
OF OUR OWN RESEARCH.
YEAH, WE WERE
VERY CURIOUS TO FIND OUT
WHERE OUR FAMILY'S
BUSINESS WAS LOCATED.
HEH HEH.
HEH HEH HEH.
YOU WOULD NOT
BELIEVE HOW
SURPRISED
AND DELIGHTED
WE WERE TO FIND OUT
THAT YOU WERE ONE
OF THOSE, UM...
WHAT WAS...WHAT
WAS THE TERM
THE COUNCILMAN
USED?
-CRONY CAPITALISTS?
-RIGHT.
THAT YOU WERE ONE
OF THOSE CRONY
CAPITALISTS
WHO PUSHED
POOR PEOPLE OUT OF
THOSE NEIGHBORHOODS,
HIDING BEHIND
A SHELL COMPANY
OF COURSE.
THE SAME COMPANY WHO
OWNS CONTROLLING INTEREST
IN A REAL ESTATE DEVELOPER
WHO JUST FILED
FOR PERMITS TO REDEVELOP
ORCHID BAY
FOR COMMERCIAL USES.
OLIVER: YOUR OPPOSITION
TO THIS REZONING,
IT'S NOT POLITICAL.
IT'S...IT'S PERSONAL.
I GET IT.
YOU'RE TRYING
TO PROTECT
AN INVESTMENT.
SUSAN WILLIAMS
ISN'T SHADOWING YOU
AT THE MOMENT,
BUT TO ME, THIS
FEELS LIKE A STORY
SHE WOULD LIKE,
SO SHOULD
I CALL HER?
UH, SHE ACTUALLY
GAVE ME HER NUMBER
THIS MORNING.
ARE YOU BLACKMAILING
ME, MR. MAYOR?
WELL, COUNCILMAN,
IT'S LIKE YOU SAID,
POLITICS IS
THE ART OF THE REAL.
[BANG]
WELL, THAT WAS FUN.
YOU MADE KULLENS
SQUIRM.
GUY'S A CAREER POLITICIAN.
JUST NEEDED TO KNOW WHERE
TO APPLY THE PRESSURE.
HOW ARE YOU SO SURE
ABOUT ALL THIS?
I'M THE MAYOR
OF STAR CITY, THEA.
THIS IS WHAT I DO.
AGH!
HEY! GET IN THE CAR!
GET IN THE CAR,
GET IN THE CAR.
[GUNSHOT]
[NO DIALOGUE]
IT'S MY SAD DUTY
TO INFORM YOU THAT
AT 1:23 A.M.
MAYOR OLIVER QUEEN
WAS PRONOUNCED DEAD
AT STARLING GENERAL.
IN HIS TOO-SHORT LIFE,
OLIVER QUEEN EXPERIENCED
GREAT HARDSHIP,
BUT HE CAME
THROUGH THE OTHER SIDE
WITH A PASSION FOR SERVICE,
COMMITTED TO MAKING
STAR CITY A SAFER PLACE
FOR US ALL TO CALL HOME.
WOW. HE REALLY DIDN'T
SAY ANYTHING THAT NICE
ABOUT YOU WHEN YOU
WERE ALIVE.
PROBABLY DIDN'T
DESERVE IT.
SORRY ABOUT THE SUIT.
AHH. WE HAVEN'T BEEN
PROPERLY INTRODUCED.
HEADS-UP.
GOD! OHH!
CHRISTOPHER CHANCE.
JOHN REFERRED TO YOU
AS THE HUMAN TARGET.
WELL, THAT WORKS BETTER
AS A JOB DESCRIPTION
THAN IT DOES
AS A NICKNAME.
RIGHT.
FELICITY: THIS IS
SO WEIRD.
[DEEP VOICE]
YOU HAVE FAILED THIS CITY.
HA HA HA HA!
HOW'S THEA?
UH, SHE'S
A LITTLE SHAKEN.
YOU KNOW, I DIDN'T
GET A CHANCE TO
TELL HER
WHAT WAS GONNA
GO DOWN UNTIL
RIGHT BEFORE.
CURTIS: SHE IS GONNA BE
SO PISSED AT YOU.
AND, LIKE,
THE WHOLE CITY.
RORY: THEY'RE GONNA
FIND OUT, THOUGH, RIGHT?
I MEAN, YOU CAN'T STAY
DEAD FOREVER.
NO. JUST UNTIL CHURCH
MAKES HIS BIG MOVE.
FELICITY: WELL, THAT'S
WHAT YOU'RE BETTING ON NOW
THAT THE GREEN ARROW/
OLIVER QUEEN IS...
CCKK...DEAD.
THAT'S THE HOPE.
NOW WE JUST NEED TO
FIGURE OUT
WHAT HE HAS PLANNED.
I DO NOT UNDERSTAND
YOU, OLIVER.
YOU...YOU BECOME
BROTHER,
BUT YOU STILL ACT
LIKE YOU CARRY
WEIGHT OF WORLD
ON SHOULDERS ALONE.
THAT IS WHAT YOUR
BROTHERS ARE FOR.
I'M JUST THINKING
ABOUT WHY I CAME HERE.
BECAUSE THIS
BEST BAR IN TOWN.
ACTUALLY, ONLY BAR.
HEH. NO. I MEAN,
WHY I CAME HERE
AFTER LIAN YU.
YES. YES. YOU
ALREADY TOLD ME.
SOMETHING
ABOUT OLD PROMISE.
I THOUGHT I TOLD YOU
TIME TO MOVE FORWARD.
SHE HAS A FAMILY.
I HAVEN'T...I HAVEN'T
SPOKEN TO THEM.
OH, THIS IS ABOUT WOMAN.
NOW I UNDERSTAND.
THERE IS OLD SAYING
IN RUSSIAN.
OK, MAYBE
NOT RUSSIAN,
BUT IT STILL WORKS.
"THERE'S NO PROBLEM
BEAUTIFUL WOMAN
CANNOT FIX."
NOW GO TALK TO HER
BEFORE I DO.
[WOMAN GRUNTS]
OLIVER, WHERE
ARE YOU GOING?
PARTY JUST START.
GONNA GO GET SOME AIR.
YOU SURE? I THINK
I HEARD ANATOLY WAS
LOOKING FOR YOU.
I'M SURE.
I'LL BE FINE.
SO THANKS
FOR DOING THIS.
BEING KILLED IS
BASICALLY MY JOB.
BUT, UH, NOT JUST
FOR TAKING THE BULLETS.
I...I HEARD THAT YOU GOT
KULLENS TO CAVE.
YEAH, AND SCORED YOU
A VERY PRETTY GIRL'S
PHONE NUMBER.
I...I HEARD THAT, TOO.
NO, BUT THE TRUTH IS
YOU DID THAT.
I WAS UNDER THE IMPRESSION
THAT I'VE BEEN DOWN
HERE ALL DAY.
I DON'T JUST PUT ON
FACES, OLIVER.
I BECOME MY TARGET,
AND TO DO THAT,
I'VE GOT TO LEARN
EVERYTHING THERE IS
TO KNOW ABOUT THEM,
MORE THAN THEY KNOW
ABOUT THEMSELVES.
I'VE GOT TO BECOME THEM.
MY APOLOGIES.
WHAT FOR?
MAN, YOU GOT
A GREAT LIFE. HEH.
YOU'RE THE MAYOR...
BUT YOU'D STILL RATHER
BE THE HOOD THAN
OLIVER QUEEN.
OLIVER QUEEN HAS...HAS
NEVER REALLY BEEN
MY BETTER HALF.
NOBODY MOVES FORWARD
IN LIFE WHEN THEY'RE
HIDING BEHIND A MASK.
TRUST ME.
YOU KNOW, IT'S WHY
YOU'RE STRUGGLING
AS MAYOR,
AND IT'S PROBABLY
WHY YOU WON'T CALL
THAT GIRL.
THAT'S NOT THE REASON.
LISTEN. I'M THE LAST
PERSON TO GIVE
DATING ADVICE,
BUT FELICITY MOVED ON.
YOU SHOULD TOO.
YOU DIDN'T KNOW.
SORRY.
UH, EARLIER TODAY,
I MET WITH A DETECTIVE
WHO JUST JOINED THE ACU,
UH, BILLY MALONE.
HE CASUALLY MENTIONED
THAT HE WAS SEEING
FELICITY ,
SEEMED TO THINK
THAT YOU KNEW.
HMM.
JOHN: YOU'RE SAFE, RENE.
NOTHING CAN HURT YOU.
IS THIS GONNA BE ONE
OF THOSE HIPPIE-DIPPIE
MEDITATION THINGS?
EYES CLOSED.
BREATHE.
DON'T TRY TO REMEMBER.
JUST GO THERE.
GET A PICTURE.
[HEART BEATING]
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLES]
I WAS STARVING.
MY WRISTS HURT LIKE HELL
FROM THE ZIP TIES.
WHAT ELSE?
SOUNDS, SMELLS.
COULDN'T SMELL ANYTHING.
NOSE WAS BUSTED.
WHAT ABOUT PEOPLE?
WHO ELSE WAS THERE?
MUSCLE. LOS HALCONES,
TRIAD.
[CHURCH LAUGHING]
IT'S NOT PAIN
THAT BREAKS PEOPLE.
IT'S FEAR.
THERE'S SOMETHING
ELSE.
WHAT?
THE TRUST GOES
TO THE BRACE
0-4 IN 72.
I KNOW WHAT'S HAPPENING.
-HEY.
-HI.
UM, THANKS FOR
LETTING ME SWING BY.
I KNOW IT'S...
IT'S LATE.
YOU DO REMEMBER THAT
THIS APARTMENT HAS
A FRONT DOOR, RIGHT?
WELL, FRONT DOORS
ARE MORE FOR PEOPLE
WHO HAVEN'T JUST FAKED
THEIR OWN DEATH.
GOOD POINT.
SO WHAT'S UP?
YOUR MESSAGE SOUNDED
CRYPTIC.
SORRY. I...I WASN'T SURE
IF I SHOULD SAY ANYTHING
AT ALL ACTUALLY.
THAT COULDN'T WAIT
TILL TOMORROW?
WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL ME
THAT YOU WERE SEEING SOMEONE?
WELL...MAYBE
ON SOME CRAZY
SUBCONSCIOUS LEVEL,
I WAS WORRIED
YOU'D SHOW UP
ON MY BALCONY
IN THE MIDDLE
OF THE NIGHT.
SNARK PROBABLY ISN'T
APPROPRIATE TO HEAR.
I'M TOTALLY FINE THAT
YOU'RE SEEING SOMEONE,
BUT I'M HURT THAT
YOU DIDN'T TELL ME.
I'M SORRY.
I...I MEANT TO,
AND THEN EVERY TIME
I WENT TO GO
BRING IT UP,
I JUST SORT OF, LIKE...
I JUST
CHICKENED OUT.
WHY?
WERE YOU...WERE YOU...
WERE YOU KEEPING
THE DOOR OPEN FOR US, OR...
NO. OF COURSE NOT.
NO. WE'RE JUST...
YOU AND I WORK
TOGETHER,
AND I JUST...I DIDN'T
WANT TO MAKE IT
A THING, YOU KNOW,
UNTIL IT WAS
SOMETHING...
SOMETHING...REAL.
IS IT REAL?
I DON'T KNOW.
[CELL PHONE CHIMES
AND VIBRATES]
IT'S JOHN AND RENE.
THEY HAVE SOMETHING.
"THE TRUST GOES
TO THE BRACE 0-4 IN 72."
COULD THAT BE
ANY MORE OBSCURE?
0-4 IN 72 COULD BE
THE TIME AND DATE.
4 A.M., 72 HOURS
AFTER HE HELD RENE?
YEAH, THAT'S SOON.
AND THE BRACE IS
WHAT THE GUYS
IN MY HOOD
USED TO CALL
THE PRIVATE AIRSTRIP
OUTSIDE PENNYTOWN.
HALPIN-BRACE
AIRFIELD.
THAT'S THE ONE,
AND THIS TRUST,
I THINK IT'S THE HEADS
OF THE CRIME FAMILIES
THAT CHURCH CONTROLS.
THAT'S A BIGGER LEAP
THAN CURTIS TOOK
AT THE BEIJING
OLYMPICS.
WHEN HE HAD ME DIG
MY OWN GRAVE,
HE TALKED ABOUT BRINGING
THIS TRUST TOGETHER.
THAT'S HIS
BIG PLAY, MAN.
4 A.M.'s
IN 20 MINUTES.
JOHN: MM-HMM.
WAKE UP THE TEAM.
WE DON'T HAVE MUCH TIME.
YOU'RE ALL
GEARED UP.
OLIVER DIDN'T BUST ME
OUT OF PRISON
FOR ME TO WARM
THE BENCH, RIGHT?
SO WHAT'S UP?
YOU READY TO MOVE OUT?
DECIDED NOT TO GO.
LAST THING ANY
OF YOU NEED
RIGHT NOW
IS ME SCREWING
THINGS UP AGAIN.
WHEN IT COMES TO GUILT
AND RECRIMINATION,
THE LINE FORMS
BEHIND ME.
I DIDN'T THINK
I WAS READY TO FACE
WHAT I HAD DONE,
BUT I'M WEARING
THIS SUIT AGAIN
BECAUSE I THINK IT'S
A PATH TO REDEMPTION.
AND IT COULD BE
FOR YOU, TOO.
-GOOD FLIGHT?
-EVERYONE'S VERY INTERESTED
IN HEARING WHAT YOU'VE
GOT PLANNED, TOBIAS.
IT'S CALLED
THE LARGEST
DRUG ENTERPRISE
ON THE WESTERN COAST...
SHIPMENTS 24/7
IN A CITY WHERE COPS
ARE AFRAID
OR ON OUR PAYROLL,
AND AS A ADDED BONUS,
THE MAYOR'S AN ALKIE.
HEH HEH HEH.
SENTRY REPORTS MOVEMENT
ON THE PERIMETER.
I THOUGHT YOU'D TAKEN
OUT THE GREEN ARROW.
AW, IT'S NOT HIM.
IT'S THE JV SQUAD.
[GUNSHOTS]
CHURCH: CHILL OUT, DAMN IT!
DEAL WITH THEM!
SPARTAN IS SUCH
A BADASS.
THE BADDEST.
YOU WERE RIGHT.
FEAR OF PAIN IS
WHAT'S WORSE.
YOU AFRAID YET, BITCH?
NEVER.
I LOST CHURCH.
I'VE GOT HIM.
MOVING SOUTHWEST.
I'VE GOT THESE TWO.
GO BACK UP
MR. CHURCH.
YOU GUYS ALL RIGHT?
GOOD SEEING YOU
AGAIN, BROTHER.
YEAH, YOU, TOO.
NICE HELMET.
TARMAC IS SECURED.
YOU GUYS ALL RIGHT?
YOU LOOK LIKE
YOU'VE SEEN A GHOST.
HEH. YOU SURVIVED.
I GUESS I'LL JUST
HAVE TO KILL YOU
AGAIN, OLIVER.
YOU MIND IF I CALL
YOU OLIVER?
YES, I DO.
[CLANG]
UNH!
GET UP!
[GROANS]
[CLANG]
YOU'RE DONE, CHURCH!
YOU GOT MUCH WORSE
COMING...HEH...
AND YOU DON'T
EVEN KNOW IT.
HE CALLS HIMSELF
PROMETHEUS,
AND HE'S GONNA
END YOU.
UNH!
OLIVER: FIRST OF ALL,
I WOULD LIKE TO APOLOGIZE
FOR PERPETRATING
A DECEPTION ON THIS SCALE.
THE ACU HAD INTEL THAT WE MAY
BE ABLE TO CATCH MR. CHURCH
BUT ONLY IF HIS PLAN
MOVED FORWARD,
WHICH WOULD ONLY HAPPEN
IF HE BELIEVED
THE MAYOR OF STAR CITY
WAS DEAD.
IN MY MIND, THIS WAS
A WORTHWHILE GAMBLE,
AND IT PAID OFF.
MR. CHURCH AND HIS UNDERLINGS
WERE APPREHENDED,
AS WELL AS THE HEADS
OF ORGANIZED CRIME ENTERPRISES
IN BLUDHAVEN, HUB CITY,
KEYSTONE, AND WHITEHOLLAND.
[APPLAUSE]
ONE MORE PIECE OF GOOD NEWS.
I HAVE JUST RECEIVED WORD
THAT THE CITY COUNCIL PASSED
AN ORDINANCE REZONING
FOR LOW-INCOME HOUSING.
AND WITH CHURCH
IN CUSTODY,
I TAKE IT THAT
YOUR IDENTITY'S SAFE.
I HOPE SO.
THANKS
FOR THE ASSIST
AND THE PERSONAL
INSIGHT.
IT'S JUST PART
OF THE SERVICE.
AH. SPEAK OF THE DEVIL.
OH, AM I
THE DEVIL NOW?
THAT WOULD DEFINITELY
BE MY CUE TO LEAVE.
TAKE CARE.
SORRY TO DROP BY
UNANNOUNCED.
IT'S NOT LIKE YOU
NEED AN INVITATION.
YEAH. NO. I KNOW.
I JUST...JUST
BETWEEN US,
THINGS HAVE BEEN
A BIT COMPLICATED...
I MEAN, COMPLICATED'S
PROBABLY NOT
THE RIGHT WORD...
IT'S NOT THE WRONG WORD.
I WANT YOU
TO BE HAPPY,
AND IN THE SPIRIT
OF THAT,
I THINK THAT YOU OWE
IT TO YOURSELF TO
FIND OUT IF WHAT YOU HAVE
WITH BILLY IS...REAL,
AND I OWE IT TO MYSELF
TO EMBRACE
WHATEVER'S NEXT
FOR...FOR ME
WHEN I'M NOT...
YES.
THE...
ERR!
YEAH.
IT'S FUNNY. THAT'S
WHAT I CAME HERE
TO SAY TO YOU.
WE'RE USUALLY
ON THE SAME PAGE.
ABOUT A LOT
OF THINGS.
ALL RIGHT.
UH, HEH. MMM. YES.
I WILL SEE...I'LL
SEE YOU...LATER.
MM-HMM.
THANK YOU.
YOU DON'T NEED
TO THANK ME.
YEAH.
I CARE ABOUT YOU...
AND I WILL ALWAYS
CARE ABOUT YOU.
IT'S A MORTAL LOCK.
MAN: VIKTOR WANTED TO
GIVE YOU A PROPER GIFT.
GUESSING THAT'S NOT YOU.
[GRUNTING]
THAT'S A NICE KNIFE.
MAYBE I KEEP IT
AFTER I KILL YOU.
THIS DOESN'T
CONCERN YOU.
ACTUALLY, IT DOES.
HAVE A NICE NIGHT.
YOU CAN TELL YOUR BOSS
I EXPECT
THE OTHER HALF OF MY FEE
WITHIN THE HOUR.
OLIVER...ARE YOU OK?
I'M FINE.
ANATOLY, WHAT THE HELL
IS GOING ON?
VIKTOR CLEARLY SENT
THOSE TWO TO KILL ME,
AND THEN SOME OTHER GUY
SHOWS UP, KILLS THEM,
AND...AND...
YES, YES. YES.
MY WAY OF HANDLING
VIKTOR PROBLEM.
I KNOW HE WANTED
YOUR DEAD.
YOU DIDN'T THINK IT
WOULD BE A GOOD IDEA
TO TELL ME THAT?
WE CANNOT KILL VIKTOR.
HE'S TOO CONNECTED.
I HIRE SPECIAL MAN.
-COME ON.
-ANATOLY, WHAT DID I GET
MYSELF INTO?
A MOST INTERESTING
QUESTION, MY FRIEND.
I THOUGHT WE AGREED
LAST TIME WAS
THE LAST TIME,
SUSAN.
I KNOW,
BUT THEN I REMEMBERED
MY MONEY WAS STILL GOOD
AND YOU STILL LIKE
GAMBLING A BIT TOO MUCH.
WHAT DO YOU HAVE
FOR ME, IAN?
GUY WHO TOOK THE BULLETS
FOR MAYOR QUEEN WAS
CHRISTOPHER CHANCE.
FELT LIKE HIS WORK.
I THINK I'VE FIGURED
OUT HOW QUEEN KNOWS HIM.
REALLY?
WENT THROUGH
THE DATABASE,
LOOKING FOR DETAILS
OF CHANCE'S PAST OPS.
I CAME ACROSS
THIS LITTLE BEAUTY.
RECOGNIZE YOUR BOY?
THAT WAS TAKEN
5 YEARS AGO
WHEN OLIVER QUEEN WAS
SUPPOSEDLY STRANDED
ON A DESERTED ISLAND.
[SIRENS]
MAN: THOSE COPS
RIDING PROTECTION
AREN'T ON YOUR
PAYROLL, BUDDY.
NOBODY'S BREAKING
YOU OUT.
THAT'S NOT WHAT
I'M WORRIED ABOUT.
YOU GUYS SHOULD
HAVE FLOWN ME
TO IRON HEIGHTS.
YEAH. I HEARD YOU
LIKED HELICOPTERS.
WHAT'S GOT YOU
SPOOKED?
[TIRES SQUEAL]
[POLICE RADIO CHATTER]
MAN: WHERE'D HE COME FROM?
WHAT? HEY...AGH! AAH!
[OFFICERS SCREAMING,
GUNS FIRING]
[SWORDS SLICING,
SCREAMING CONTINUES]
[WOMAN WHIMPERS]
[HEAVY FOOTSTEPS]
DON'T GO OUT THERE.
WHY? SO I CAN PROTECT
YOUR ASS IN HERE?
SO YOU DON'T
GET KILLED.
UNH!
I KNEW WE'D BE
HAVING THIS
CONVERSATION.
JUST HEAR ME OUT.
YOU WANT
THE GREEN ARROW.
I CAN GIVE HIM
TO YOU.
I CAN GIVE YOU
HIS NAME.
YOU WOULD BE THE ONLY
PERSON WHO KNOWS.
IT'S OLIVER QUEEN.
SO WE COOL?
UNH!
YEAH...WE ARE.
[POLICE RADIO CHATTER]