Previously on Arrow...
Got an ID on your not-so-secret
but very crazy admirer.
Carrie Cutter. She's former SCPD.
Love is a bullet in the brain.
My hero.
I'm Cupid, stupid.
And if I don't help you?
I think I made it abundantly clear,
you don't have a choice.
Are you working for Damien Darhk?
I did what I had to do to keep you safe!
Anything you say can and will be used
against you in a court of law.
- Who's William?
- He's my son.
Oliver, we need to talk. I can't do this.
Felicity...
Oh, my God!
Let me call you sweetheart
It's okay. It's okay.
I'm in love with you
That you love me too
Whatever you're thinking of doing,
you don't have to.
Please. Just let us go.
We won't tell anyone.
No one. Absolutely not. Right?
Wonderful! Agreement.
The mortar that holds together
the bricks of love.
So how much do you love each other?
With everything that I have.
And the missus?
How much does she love her mister?
More than anything in the world.
How sweet. And pathetic.
What?
"Love is a bullet to the brain."
Or an arrow to the heart.
Please be seated.
First, I'll hear the parties
on the question of bail.
Your Honor,
the defendant wishes to waive bail
so that the court can focus its attention
on our motion to dismiss.
Your Honor, the defendant was apprehended
at the site of a child abduction.
Because he was being held captive himself.
Your Honor, these documents will confirm
my client's identity as Kenneth Bender,
citizen of Markovia.
Your Honor, this is ridiculous.
The defendant's name is Damien Darhk.
According to whom? You?
Oliver Queen? The media?
Your Honor,
there is absolutely no evidence whatsoever
to suggest that my client
is this Damien Darhk,
much less prove beyond a reasonable doubt
that he committed these acts
that Damien Darhk is even accused of.
Your Honor, we have evidence
and we will present it at trial.
During which time,
what, my client just rots in jail?
I mean, fortunately,
he's no longer in Markovia, right?
Because in America...
We have preliminary hearings to determine
whether the State can meet
its burden of proof.
Your Honor...
You say you have evidence, Ms. Lance.
Get ready to present it.
Mr. Darhk, or Mr. Bender
or whatever he's calling himself,
is hereby remanded to the custody
of the Department of Corrections,
to be held until disposition
of defendant's motion to dismiss.
I worked out a system to maximize
the efficiency of the moving process.
The densest, heaviest boxes
are put into the moving truck first,
creating a solid foundation
for the rest of the boxes,
and providing maximum recovery time
during the most physical moments
of moving.
There's, um, less chance for injury, too.
I hired a mover.
And I would never want to step on the toes
of professionals,
but proper distribution of the mass
and density of the boxes
inside the moving truck
could have a cost-saving effects
for the moving company
in the form of improved gas mileage.
Okay. Great.
So, you're doing great.
It's just amazing how much progress
you've made in such little time.
Paul must be just
a physical therapy genius.
Yeah, like a symphony of the talents,
you know, Curtis and Paul,
they're kind of the perfect team.
You know, marrying tech...
Poor choice of words.
My bad. My specialty.
It's okay. That's fine. l...
You see, it's not like, um...
I don't know what it's like.
We were engaged.
And now we're not together.
That's what it's like.
Could you cancel the venue, please?
Uh...
Yes, I will get around
to canceling the venue.
Great. Thank you.
And I will un-invite the guests.
Okay.
The movers will swing by
whenever you want.
Just give them a call.
I'll see you when I see you.
- Tonight.
- Tonight?
Yeah, tonight I, uh...
I mean, I guess we didn't talk about it,
but I was a part of the team
before we were together. I just assumed...
Oh! Tonight.
Like every night. Um...
Of course. You are a part of the team.
Forever and always.
Keep movin'!
Stop here. This is it.
Okay, well, now that you've found
what you're looking for,
you don't need us, so we can just...
No. This isn't the end, Mr. Queen.
- It's the beginning.
- Of what?
I grew up in a small village in Africa.
A country whose name has changed
a dozen times over the years.
One day, bandits came to my village.
They wanted water and gold and women.
Once they left with them,
the only thing remaining of my village
was ash.
My home and everyone I loved
was wiped from the earth.
And I was helpless to stop it.
And I swore I would never feel
helpless again.
So killing all the people you're holding
hostages can help you not feel helpless?
How does that make you any different than
the people who destroyed your village?
Oh...
it makes me very different.
Let me show you.
How'd it go out there tonight?
It was quiet.
Yeah, this city hasn't had a quiet night
in four years.
Yeah, I can't believe HIVE is silent
just because Damien Darhk's in jail.
- Not for long.
- What are you talking about?
The law's pesky need for evidence.
The Ghosts who took William also took
their cyanide escape plans.
- There's no one to testify against Darhk.
- What about my brother?
You mean the one that was declared
legally dead five years ago?
It should be fun walking him into court.
What about us?
Yeah, Damien kidnapped us
over the holiday.
- We're all witnesses.
- Actually, that's good.
The fiancé to the city's
beloved mayoral candidate,
it makes for a compelling story.
What's wrong?
Oliver and I aren't engaged anymore.
Um, or living together.
Or together together.
- Felicity...
- It's fine.
Which is universal code for
"I don't wanna talk about it."
- Pieces of Darhk's idol, huh?
- Yeah.
How're you holding up?
Felicity tell you guys?
Is this about your son?
The fact that I lied to her about him,
yeah.
Well, you got a kid, man.
That's a whole lot to handle.
But don't worry, she'll come around.
Give her time.
I mean, she wants to stay on the team.
That's a good sign.
- I think.
- Hey.
Lance just called. It's trouble.
HIVE?
He said it was an old friend.
All right, you guys take five.
Hey, you okay?
You do look a little more grim than usual.
Just let me know who did this.
Look familiar?
Cupid.
She's supposed to be in custody
at A.R.G.U.S.
Yeah?
Tell that to them.
What was there?
She left a note for us.
"Love is dead."
So, is nobody else going to say it?
"It's Cupid, stupid."
Well, she's changed up her M.O. a little.
"Love is dead."
Ah! Maybe she's not so insane after all.
I thought she was locked up
in some A.R.G.U.S sub-basement?
Yeah, not anymore.
Just talked to Lyla,
turns out Waller was serious
about prisoners like Cupid
working their way off of Task Force X.
- She's out.
- Then we start with her victims.
- Did CSU ID them?
- They're running prints.
Like, seriously? None of your crime
tech guys read gossip websites?
Uh... Let's assume they don't.
'Cause this is Blaine and this is Shannon.
Okay?
Really, guys? Come on,
it's the wedding of the decade.
Why would Cupid wanna ice
Star City's most high-profile couple?
Well, we figure that out, we figure out
who her next targets might be.
How do you know
there's gonna be a next target?
I don't think that Carrie Cutter
has changed that much.
We got to get to court.
I'm gonna stay here,
work up some leads on Cupid.
It was the Oliver Queen
Campaign holiday party.
There was gunfire.
The security that we had on site
was killed.
And then he walked in.
Let the record reflect that
the witness is pointing to the defendant.
And why did the defendant walk
in to Oliver Queen's campaign office?
He was the leader of the gunmen.
He took myself, Thea Queen,
and Felicity Smoak hostage.
And while you were held hostage...
Damien Darhk, or whatever
he calls himself, was there,
calling the shots, the entire time.
Pass the witness.
This, uh, holiday party.
Were you there as a guest?
No, sir. I work security,
personal security for Mr. Oliver Queen.
I have been for the past three-plus years.
Even after Mr. Queen lost his job
as CEO of Queen Consolidated?
I mean, how much does he pay you?
Ten cents an hour?
Objection. Relevance.
Sustained. Move faster, Mr. Fitzmartin.
Of course, Your Honor.
All right, well, let's talk about
your alleged co-captive, Thea Queen.
Isn't it true that five months ago,
you helped her buy
$74,000 worth of cocaine?
And before you answer that,
you should know that I have a signed
affidavit from Ms. Queen's dealer,
right here.
Which means nothing
because it is irrelevant.
Well, it goes to credibility, Your Honor.
Oliver Queen publicly slandered my client
by accusing him
of ordering a terrorist drone strike.
Now, if Mr. Diggle can work
for Mr. Queen for free,
to help Ms. Queen buy illegal drugs,
I mean,
is it really that much of a stretch to
believe that he'd also perjure himself
in support of Mr. Queen's campaign
of character assassination?
You watched me swear an oath!
And then I saw you break it.
No further questions, Your Honor.
I don't have a law degree,
but I don't think that went well.
It could've been worse.
If Fitzmartin kept pulling
on those threads,
then everything that we've done
for the city could've been exposed.
Worth it to put Darhk away.
Except it wouldn't put him away.
Because vigilantes
don't make good witnesses?
No, but they make excellent inmates.
Yeah.
Okay, so where does this leave us?
We can't just let Darhk walk.
Well, unless I come up with a witness
who Fitzmartin can't tear apart,
then that's what's going to happen.
Then put me on the stand.
I don't have a secret identity.
And I can testify about Darhk
and his connection to HIVE.
And spend the rest of your life in jail.
If it's in a cell next to Darhk,
it'd be worth it.
No. We'll find another way.
- It's Felicity.
- Uh...
Put her on speaker.
Felicity, we have the whole team here.
What's up?
Good news is, I've got Cupid's location.
Good. Where is she?
That's the bad news. Looks like she's
kidnapped another celebrity couple.
Allison Lee and Robert Joyce.
Allibert.
Track the GPS in their phones.
When I said I had their location,
how did you think that I got it?
Okay, Felicity, what's next?
Where are we going?
They're on the move
headed towards Pennytown.
- Got it.
- I'd suit up with you...
No, what you're doing here
is more important. Get Darhk.
Get Cupid.
"'Till death do us part."
Don't worry.
You won't have to wait that long.
Wedding crashers. Hold on tight.
Speedy, look out!
She's in the center.
- I'm okay.
- Stay with Speedy.
- Let them help you.
- I'll get Cupid.
I'd say enjoy the afterlife,
but we both know
that's just eternal nothingness.
I was in love with the Arrow,
but you're not him.
Although I do like the sleeveless.
Got her.
I guess you didn't have her.
Really brings a whole new meaning
to crazy ex-girlfriend,
and you didn't even get to enjoy
the fun parts.
Sorry.
Well, Cutter fell for Floyd Lawton
last year.
Lucky QUY-
She was heartbroken when he was blown up.
No, Thea's right though.
Cutter is pathological.
I mean, targeting happy couples? Come on!
Well, it makes sense
if you look at it from her perspective.
Love betrayed her
and now she wants to go to war against it.
And then that's making sense?
It makes sense to her.
Okay.
She's not just targeting regular couples.
She's targeting celebrity couples.
Probably to bring attention
to her anti-love crusade.
Lance is getting the word out,
he assigned a protective detail.
I'm gonna run forensics on this.
We're gonna hit the streets,
see if we can get a line on Cutter.
Okay. You wanna talk about
the other obvious problem?
- Yeah, the elephant in the room?
- Felicity and I are fine.
If you were
listening to her little asides,
you would know that was not true.
John, you were the one
who told me to give her time.
Okay. Do you want to get back together
with her?
- I do.
- Then tell her that.
Even if you fall on your face, Oliver,
she needs to know where you stand.
She needs to know
that you're willing to say the words.
- I am willing to say the words.
- That's good.
So what's stopping you?
- Why did you do that?
- Don't! Let him die.
What? You're insane!
The difference between insanity and belief
lies only in the number of believers.
This is the power of a single life.
Above us, I have dozens under my control.
The prisoners are gathered topside.
The men are in position.
Tell them to shoot.
Come on! Come on! Go, go, go, go!
Hey-
So how'd the rest of the day in court go?
If it went well,
I wouldn't be here still doing this.
Listen, I was thinkin',
what about all the rest of the people
at the holiday party?
- All right? 'Cause they all saw Darhk.
- Yeah.
It's probably
why they're all too frightened to testify.
We could subpoena 'em.
I did that this afternoon.
One lied,
one in jail
because they refused to testify,
and one actually tried pleading the Fifth.
Well, I told you,
there's one guy willing to take the stand.
Dad, I went to my boss and I asked him
to give you immunity from prosecution.
He said he'd prefer to be re-elected.
- I don't care about immunity.
- But I do.
Dad, I'm not gonna let you
incriminate yourself.
You wouldn't be doing anything.
It'd be me. And it'd be right.
I'm the one who got into bed with Darhk.
But I made those decisions
and I should pay the consequences
to 'em, honey.
And, listen,
it's the only way to bring him down.
Okay. Okay.
If we do this, you will also testify
that you acted under duress.
- That Damien threatened my life.
- Yeah.
'Cause that way I get to say on record
how much I love my baby girl.
Okay.
Felicity Scissorhands.
Struck out
trying to find a line on Cutter.
What's this?
I couldn't exactly fit the entire sleeve
into the gas chromatograph.
Speak of the devil.
The sleeve contains fibers from at least
60 different types of white silk lace.
- White lace. Like in wedding dresses?
- That would be ironic.
And also traces of acid-free
polypropylene.
- What do they use that for?
- Long term storage of fabrics.
Well, maybe Cutter's holed up in a spot
where they store wedding dresses.
Colao Wedding Dress Services is the only
long-term storage facility in the city
that uses polypropylene.
Twenty-eighth and Hamilton.
That is two blocks
from where she posed the first victims.
The only movement
I'm tracking in that building is you guys.
Stay alert.
Got something.
Whoa!
She does love her shrines, doesn't she?
Now we know how she's picking her targets.
The first two couples,
they're both recently gotten married.
Cutter abducted the second couple
after their wedding.
Yeah.
Yeah. But Blaine and Shannon, "Blannon",
had a secret wedding 48 hours
before they were killed.
Now we have to figure out what celebrity
couple in the city's getting married next.
I think I found one we can rule out.
So, by calling off the engagement,
we took ourselves
out of Cupid's crosshairs.
I knew there had to be
at least one silver lining.
Well, if she keeps on targeting
high-profile weddings,
we just got to stake out
whatever the next one is.
That's a big risk
to run with an innocent couple.
We're not gonna take that risk
with an innocent couple.
Hey-
We need to get married.
How romantic.
- It's, Felicity...
- This is the worst idea you've ever had!
Actually, it's not the worst.
Et tu, John'?
We lost our leads on Cutter, Felicity.
This might draw her out.
Oh, so she can kill me?
- Pass. No, thank you.
- Okay.
No, John and I will have your back.
Guess it's too bad I already sent out
all those "un-invitations."
Clearly, none of you guys spend any time
on gossip sites.
Okay, look,
these bloggers love nothing
more than a private, secret wedding.
I leak the news, saying you guys
wanted to keep it under radar...
it becomes the top story on their website.
It's Catnip for Cupid.
Okay, look,
we have to do this quickly, okay?
So Cupid doesn't change her M.O.
and start killing more innocent couples.
- Can we do this tomorrow?
- Tomorrow will work.
The venue still has our deposit, though.
We'll be able to move up the date.
I thought you said you were
gonna cancel that?
I did say that I was gonna cancel,
and I am going to cancel,
but I haven't canceled yet.
Because when I picked up the...
When I pick up the phone to do that,
it means it's over.
It is over.
Hey. Taiana, wait. I think we lost them.
Look. Reiter is not gonna issue kill order
if he doesn't have that thing nearby.
You grabbing it, you saved us.
If that's true,
then we should destroy the damn thing.
- Oliver Queen.
- You took his radio?
I know you're still down here, Mr. Queen.
You should have studied those maps
more closely.
The only way out of these tunnels
is back the way you came.
Which means going through me.
You can either return of your own accord,
or you can force me to come and find you.
But don't bother trying to fight
your way out of this.
After all, I'm the only one of us
who has men and guns.
Last August,
Darhk asked me for the vacation plans
for the Chief of the Fire Department.
Objection.
Darhk. Bender.
Whatever he wants to call himself.
I told him where Chief Reynolds was
staying, the next day the place blows up.
Objection. Conjecture.
Something you're free to challenge
on cross examination. Continue, Ms. Lance.
What else did you do for the defendant?
He wanted me to give him access
to the SCPD computer network.
I did it.
He wanted me to give him
the departmental patrol schedules.
I did that.
He wanted me to break into a federal
server farm to install a computer virus,
and I did that.
He wanted me to give him information
on the city's leadership, and I...
I did that.
And three days later,
the city leadership were all dead.
You did all of these things
for the defendant?
The defendant and the organization
he works for. He called it HIVE.
Objection. Your Honor, it's hearsay.
Statement against interests, Your Honor.
Overruled.
Captain Lance,
why would you do these things?
At first, I didn't know his intentions.
Like with the Fire Chief.
But when I confronted Darhk about it,
he told me that if I didn't do
everything he asked,
everything he told me to do,
he'd have you killed.
No more questions, Your Honor.
Mr. Fitzmartin, your witness.
Captain Lance,
have you ever personally witnessed
my client commit any illegal act?
Well, I'm pretty sure that threatening
the daughter
of a police captain
isn't legal, counselor.
- Objection.
- Overruled.
You know, the fact of the matter is,
I've seen your client in his
little hidey-hole, with his little men.
Ghosts, he calls 'em.
And I've heard him say repeatedly
how he wants to destroy this city.
And that if I didn't help him do it,
then he'd kill my daughter.
By saying all these things,
I'm setting a match to my career.
Maybe my life.
So why would I be doin' that
if everything I'm saying isn't true?
In position.
There's no psychopaths here
other than paparazzi.
I'm tapped into the security cameras.
All clear.
Everything okay?
Yes. Yeah.
You look perfect.
Thanks.
I'd like to assure you I won't breathe
a word of what goes on here to the press.
- I'm just thrilled to be part of your day.
- Thank you.
- Can we get this over with?
- Hmm.
Can't wait to be
married to this guy!
In that case,
I know you've written your own vows.
- Felicity.
- Vows?
Yeah.
Okay.
Um...
Oliver, you have many qualities.
Many astonishing qualities.
And I, for one, cannot wait
to move on to the next chapter.
All right. Oliver?
Felicity...
Before I met you, I had a plan.
I had a way that it was gonna be.
But then you walked into my life,
all right.
I showed up in your cubicle
and you changed everything.
I was in darkness.
But with your kindness,
your generosity, your compassion, your
intelligence, your wit, and your trust,
you brought me into the light.
And you let me know that I deserved it.
You were that light.
And I don't know
if I still deserve that trust.
If I deserve you.
I probably don't.
But whatever's happened,
whatever will happen,
the way that you make me feel,
is the best part of my life.
You could ask me to say
that I don't love you.
And I will never lie to you again.
You are my always.
And I just want the chance to be yours.
Oliver...
Hello, lovers.
Run!
We have eyes on?
Copy that. I'm here.
Yeah, we got that. Hold tight.
Your little speech
was only off by a little.
See, she isn't the best thing in your life
because that means you love her.
And love means you're soft.
And soft, means death.
Here, let me show you.
Oh, sorry I didn't check
your gift registry.
Was an explosion that would bring down
this whole building on your list?
Your engagement, that horrible shooting,
your miracle recovery,
that was all just a fairy tale.
Camelot in Star City.
Thank you.
But once Camelot dies,
everyone will know my truth.
That love is a bullet to the brain.
No. No, it's not.
Kevlar under the tux.
My bodyguard insisted.
What was his plan for C-four?
That's a damn good question.
- You know, you don't have to do this.
- I do.
The two words that start every marriage.
"I'll do."!
True love. People need to see it,
they need to know what a joke that is.
It's not.
I have loved two men in my life.
With all my soul.
They're both dead now.
No matter what, love always ends in death.
That's why it's in the vows.
I'm just cutting out the middle man.
Love is death.
It's not.
You saw all those people outside, right?
They're out there because love is real,
because love is life itself.
And if I die tonight, it'll be okay,
because I was one of those people
lucky enough to have experienced it.
From the moment he walked into my life,
everything changed.
I became a person that I didn't even know
I was capable of becoming.
I became the very best version of myself.
That would have never have been possible
without our love.
Our love gives my life meaning,
it gives my life a purpose,
and it brings us more joy
than you can ever take away from us.
And it's worth living for.
All of it.
You really know how to make a girl
believe in love again.
Are you all right?
Yeah.
Step back, please.
"REPORTER". What happened inside there?
You two give the rest of us hope.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
About what you said in there to Cutter...
Maybe we could meet up and talk about it.
Tonight? Or...
Not tonight.
I think we're both exhausted
from whatever that was.
Tomorrow?
"THEA". Hey, guys. Laurel just texted.
Guess Judge Sakow's holding court late.
And she's making her decision.
I should probably change.
This outfit is a bit of a focus-puller.
Mmm-hmm.
Not for nothing, Oliver.
But I heard what Felicity said in there.
No one likes an "I told you so", John.
I'm just saying, she needs some time.
Watch it. Could be a trap.
They just left it behind?
Why would they do that?
Drop the weapon.
- Maybe you should radio Reiter.
- Why?
Now we have guns, too.
The standard of proof
for a preliminary hearing
is much less severe than one for a trial.
Even so, the evidence against
the defendant is exceedingly thin.
There is no forensic
or circumstantial evidence
that points to the defendant's guilt.
But I found Quentin Lance's testimony
to be particularly compelling.
His credibility is bolstered
by his status as a police captain,
but the fact that he was willing to
incriminate himself to see justice done
makes his testimony especially believable.
On the strength of it,
I am denying
the defense's motion to dismiss
and binding the defendant over for trial.
Mr. Darhk will be held without bail
or possibility of release.
"MAN". The defendant will rise.
Officers, please escort the defendant
from the courtroom.
All right, next step.
Convicting the son of a bitch.
Next step, right.
Are we okay? I wasn't exactly
pulling punches on the stand.
I'm glad you didn't. 'Cause of that,
Darhk's defense is blown to shreds.
He's gonna spend the rest of his life
behind bars.
Hey, Quentin. You have a minute?
Yeah.
Lieutenant Pike,
if I could just talk to you before...
It's all right, sweetheart.
We both knew this was coming. Frank?
You're being suspended
pending an l.A.B. investigation.
I'll need your badge and your weapon.
Yeah.
I'm sorry about this, Quentin.
I'm sure your union rep'll make it clear
to l.A.B.
that you were acting under duress.
Yeah, I'm good either way, Frank. Truly.
It's a temporary setback.
I'll represent you in front of l.A.B.
You just focus on nailing Darhk
to a cross, all right?
I'm proud of you, baby.
We have the results
of the high-profile
preliminary hearing against...
Hi.
- Thought you'd be asleep by now.
- Oh, I can't sleep.
What are you doing here?
I just came to pick up a few things.
It's not exactly
how I pictured our wedding day.
I don't know.
Being kidnapped by psychotic criminals
has sort of been a theme
in our relationship.
I want you to know that...
What I said today during the ceremony,
I meant every single word of it.
I love you.
With everything in me.
But what I said doesn't apply to us.
I can't be with you. I can't marry you.
Yes, you can.
Yes, you can,
because that's what both of us want.
You know, things can be different.
I can be different.
And I'm promising you,
I'm swearing to you,
there will be no more lies.
You know, no matter how much you love me,
there's always gonna be a part of you
that defaults to the man
who was on the island, alone.
Who came back to save the city. Alone.
And sooner than we both think,
you're going to be stuck in a situation
where you have to make a decision that
requires you to hide things from me again.
See, you can't know that...
I do know that. And you know that.
That's this life.
I'm sorry.
You know, five months ago,
I convinced you that we could have it all.
We could come here to this job
and have each other, I was wrong.
And then I thought we could just go back
to the way things were,
before we left for Ivy Town.
God, that was as crazy as Cupid is.
So what does that mean?
It means it is too hard to be here
with you every night and not be with you.
That's not fair to either of us.
You told me how you worked some tech magic
to return all the money that Adam Hunt
swindled out of people.
You don't need me. You'll be fine.
You don't give up.
You know, that's what makes you a hero.
But there's no fixing this.
We have to let each other go.
I want you to keep it for good this time,
please.
I don't wanna let you go.
But I'm already gone.
English - SDH