Jerry.
Jerry, you okay?
-You look a little piqued, man.
-I'm fine, it's, uh...
Ms. Hill wants us to move the Sherwood
into the vault.
Now? It's midday.
I know. She says it's a security threat.
It's all the robberies lately. Heh.
[ALARM BLARING]
That way.
[GUARDS CHATTERING]
Take this thing off me, all right?
I got it like you asked. Here.
Take it off me.
Were you...? Were you bluffing?
Would that thing have detonated?
Violently. Don't worry, though.
You did exactly as I asked,
so it's just unconsciousness for you.
Unconscious?
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLES
&amp; JERRY GROANS]
Might wanna take it easy if you plan
on taking someone off that list.
This is me taking it easy.
So who's the unlucky guy tonight?
OLIVER:
Ken Williams.
His pyramid scheme stole millions.
People didn't just lose their homes,
their lives were ruined.
Why don't you call it in early?
I'm not expecting much trouble.
Felicity. Did you just...?
Computer-override your lock?
Maybe a little.
-What are you doing?
-I pulled up information on Mr. Williams.
Did you know he's a widowed father
of a 10-year-old boy?
I told you, I'm only in this to help Walter,
not to be an accessory to orphaning little kids.
I'm giving him a warning.
Has it occurred to you
you could do some good in the city?
Beyond recovering people's
stock portfolios and saving accounts.
You're not the only one who knows
how to reboot my system.
I made a mistake.
-Getting in my way? I don't disagree.
FELICITY: No.
Signing on with you. Even provisionally.
[SLADE GASPING]
Hey. Hey. Drink.
Tastes like dirt.
You gotta stay hydrated, okay?
Hydration is not my problem.
My problem is getting a bullet
dug out of my arm with a dull blade.
Let me take a look.
-Oh. Ugh.
-Is it infected?
Go figure.
Yeah. Uh...
I gotta stop that before it spreads.
SLADE: When you swing past the drugstore
for those antibiotics...
...you wanna get me a copy of Maxim
or maybe a Sports Illustrated?
Yao Fei had these super herbs back
in the cave that would heal anything.
All right?
I'm gonna go get them.
You're not gonna last an hour out there.
Well, I guess you better hope
I get back in 45 minutes, then.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
MOIRA:
Oh. Thank you for coming.
It is so good to see you, Frank. Mm.
-It's been far too long.
-Yes.
My interests in China
have kept me away more than I'd like.
But with the Undertaking approaching,
I felt a return to Starling City was in order.
Actually, Frank, it's the Undertaking
that I wanted to talk to you about.
I wanna get out.
Is this because of
what happened to Walter?
With Walter. With Robert.
Last week, the vigilante
nearly made my children orphans.
I've reached my limit, Frank.
FRANK:
That's, uh...
...a lot to confide in me, Moira.
Robert did.
I know he reached out to you,
whether I was supposed to know it or not.
He had misgivings.
He sought you out
because he knew you did too.
But then he was murdered.
And that should be a cautionary tale
for both of us.
Yes, I know. And I've gone along with this
for as long as I can stomach it.
We started this to fix the Glades, Frank.
To cure the city, not lay it to waste.
You got into this because of
what happened to your daughter.
Frank...
...what would Amanda want you to do?
Well, maybe we should come back later.
No, maybe we should wait.
This is really serious.
What if her next attack of conscience
leads her to the police?
No, she won't say anything.
I had to make the same calculation
when you found out about me.
Mm-hm. What would you have done
if you were wrong...
...and I decided to make a call
to Detective Lance?
I would've put an arrow in you.
[DIGGLE CHUCKLES]
Really? You really would have done that?
Really?
Hmm. I had a bet going with myself
on how quickly you would visit...
...tell me not to reveal your secret.
Looks like I won.
Actually, I was hoping that
I could get you to change your mind.
[MAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY ON TV]
I was worked up on adrenaline last night,
and I didn't exactly put my best foot forward.
I was hoping you'd give me the opportunity
to do that now.
How about you start with Ken Williams?
Did he also enjoy your adrenaline
last night?
No. He returned the money he stole
in time to put his son to bed.
Like I said, Felicity, just a warning.
McKENNA [ON TV]: We'd like to remind the public
we are coordinating efforts with Interpol...
...as the Dodger operates
primarily in Europe.
They have advised us to warn the public
he is considered armed and extremely...
I heard about this guy.
They call him the Dodger...
...because he avoids getting his hands dirty.
He uses hostages to do his stealing for him.
-How?
-Puts a bomb collar around their necks.
Last year, a guy in Madrid didn't steal what
the Dodger told him to. It took his head off.
-Literally.
FELICITY: Now this psycho's in Starling City?
Too bad his name's
not in your notebook.
Not all people that I target are on the list.
Every once in a while, I make an exception.
Hostage-taking jewel thief, for example.
So why don't you help us take him down?
He's late.
Never.
I maintain a Swiss account
for financial transactions.
Here's the number.
Thanks.
I'll wire you the money.
Assuming I don't misplace the numbers.
My bookkeeping method is a little sloppy.
Really? Heh.
Clearly, you're under the impression that
you can have the Sherwood ruby for a steal.
Well, you're new here in town.
We're not as refined in Starling City.
I am getting that impression.
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLING]
[DODGER CLEARS THROAT]
DODGER:
Don't worry...
...your men are merely unconscious.
In about 17 minutes, they'll wake up with the
ability to tell every other fence in this town...
...that I am not to be trifled with.
[STAMMERS]
What about me?
Uh...
[GUNSHOT]
What about you, indeed.
So to catch this guy we need to either figure
out where he is or where he's gonna be.
This really how you guys figure out how to
get your target? Over burgers and shakes?
Sorry it took me so long. I'm waiting on
a bunch of particularly rowdy customers.
[ALL SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
You need me to handle that?
I appreciate it, but I'm a pro by now.
I'll be here if you need me.
Girlfriend?
No, no, that's my sister-in-law.
-Sort of.
-Carly was married to Dig's brother.
And he passed away.
-Well, looks like she's hot for you.
-Ah. Can we get back to crime-fighting?
Actually, I was thinking
you probably should ask her out.
-Really?
OLIVER: Mm-hm.
I'll do that five minutes
after you ask out McKenna.
Ooh, the detective on the Dodger case.
You have a thing for her?
-Uh...
DIGGLE: Yes.
[OVER SPEAKERS]
This is way too hard
I don't see you asking Carly out.
Felicity, this guy,
he's targeting a very specific type of jewel.
We figure out why...
...and that'll give us the how to catch him.
-I have an idea.
OLIVER: Mm-hm.
Your crush object with a badge said
they were working with Interpol.
-Yeah.
FELICITY: Why don't I work up a little tech...
...you distract her with a little flirty-flirt,
slip said tech onto her phone...
...it'll turn it into a microtransmitter and,
boom, we'll learn everything she knows.
Hmm.
-It's not how I typically get my information.
-How do you typically do it?
I find the person and then I put
the fear of God into them until they talk.
But we can try your way.
You know, Carly, I don't want this to, um...
You know, to come off weird or anything,
it's just...
I never wanted to stop
Because I don't wanna start all over
Would you like to have dinner?
How about tonight?
-Tonight?
CARLY: What...
...we haven't waited long enough?
All that I want
Mm. Who knew street meat
could taste so good?
I had a feeling you needed a break
from the office.
Hank was my first client.
I kept his son from being sent away
for a mugging that he didn't commit.
Then how did that not score you
free hot dogs for life?
CNRI gives low-income people
access to the legal system.
Without them,
his son could have gone to prison forever.
I could've gone to prison too.
He couldn't afford a dream team
of super-lawyers.
So I'm supposed to feel guilty because
I'm lucky enough to have a rich family?
No.
You are lucky.
And hopefully, CNRI will show you that.
Hey!
[HORN HONKS]
Give us the purse
and we won't press any charges.
Yeah, you're right.
I really do feel lucky.
LAUREL:
This got snagged as he vaulted over the fence.
Looks like a chain from his wallet.
-I thought you gave up crime-fighting.
-What?
Well, the business with your sister.
I figured...
-Oh.
-...you'd stay out of police precincts.
[CHUCKLES]
Yeah, I... I saw you on the news
and realized that I never thanked you...
...for everything that you did, so...
Thank you.
So you got promoted.
-Major Crimes.
OLIVER: Wow.
And they assigned me to the Dodger case.
He extorts people into stealing for him.
-How's that going?
-Slow.
It was nice seeing you
the last time that I saw you.
Yeah. It was good seeing you too.
It was like old times.
Except the PG version.
-How do you mean?
McKENNA: Ha, ha.
Well, you and I always knew
how to have a fun time.
Something that's been
missing from my life.
So how about a drink?
Not now.
Would you maybe...? I'll take you for a...
Would you like to have dinner with me,
McKenna?
McKENNA: Ha, ha.
-I was on a deserted island for five years...
...and I am totally out of practice
with this whole...
Mm. Well, dinner would be nice.
In fact, I can make myself free tonight.
-Yeah.
-Great.
So I'll grab you at 8?
That's perfect.
-Okay.
McKENNA: Okay.
-I'm lingering. I'm gonna go.
-Ha, ha. Okay.
[MAN COUGHS]
Who's there?
Help me.
[PHONE DIALING ON RECORDING]
[LINE RINGING ON RECORDING]
LANCE [ON RECORDING]: Lance.
McKENNA [ON RECORDING]: It's Detective Hall.
I have an update on the Dodger case.
A body was found at an art gallery
shot point-blank.
There were three other men,
all rendered unconscious...
...by a highly focused electric current.
LANCE:
Same MO as that guard at the museum.
You got an ID on the vic?
McKENNA:
His name is Cass Derenick.
Pause.
Who's Cass Derenick?
FELICITY:
Arrest, possession of stolen goods.
Arrest, conspiracy.
Conviction, attempted sale of stolen goods.
This guy's a fence. The Dodger's looking
to unload the Sherwood ruby.
Which means he'll be in the market
for a new fence.
One he hasn't, you know, killed.
So we find the fence
and we find the Dodger.
Anyway, I saw online
that you sell a chain wallet...
...with an eight ball on the chain.
I was wondering if you could give me
a name of one of your customers...
...if I gave you a description.
Yeah, sure, you can call me back.
You and every other used-clothing
and leather-goods store I've called today.
What was that about?
-What's up with the fancy-fancy?
-What...? Oh, um... Heh.
I have a date. Contrary to popular opinion,
I do have a life.
Then why do you seem so nervous?
Is it obvious?
Just be your charming and brooding self.
I mean, girls seem to dig that.
This girl's different.
She knew me before the island,
before I was...
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
It's CNRI. I've gotta take this. I'm working
on a very important purse-snatching case.
Yeah.
Hello?
Yeah, he might have been wearing
a red hoodie.
Kind of Abercrombie-looking.
His face, not the hoodie.
Really?
You wouldn't happen to have his name?
[ON STEREO]
You had to sell your gold
Thank you so much.
[LINE RINGS]
Hey, Laurel.
Does your dad still, like, arrest people?
I found the dirtbag.
His name is Roy Harper.
CARLY:
I can't remember the last time I was here.
It's so beautiful.
Yeah, this was the place
to take a girl in high school.
Hmm, I was never lucky enough
to experience that.
I had braces and terrible bangs back then.
[CHUCKLES]
I'm sure you looked amazing.
I'm glad we finally got around to doing this.
Me too.
You know, Andy set a pretty high bar
when it came to first dates.
Hmm.
He faced down armed gunmen for a living...
...but I've never seen him as scared
as he was before that first date with you.
[SIGHS]
Carly, I'm sorry,
that wasn't good first-date etiquette, was it?
To bring up Andy
when we are having a romantic night?
-Probably not.
-Carly, this is difficult and complicated.
It's not like there's a manual, you know?
You know, for a moment...
...I felt like a girl who likes a boy
and nothing else mattered.
Yeah, yeah. Yeah.
If this is too hard for you
or too complicated...
...then please, you know, just get out now
because I've already been hurt too much.
-I'm sorry...
-Can you just please take me home?
[OVER SPEAKERS]
In these little moments
Get your cards out
I am waiting
Mm. No, no, no, it is not possible
for something to be this good.
-Right?
McKENNA: Oh.
-You must have missed soufflés.
-What do you mean?
Five years on an island
away from civilization.
What did you do? What did you eat?
-Where'd you sleep? How did you make it?
-McKenna.
Sorry.
-Didn't mean to drill you.
-It's okay.
I haven't had a conversation
with a guy in a while...
...without it resulting in
me reading him his rights.
Heh. So...
Yeah, but those years,
they must have changed you.
[ARROW PIERCES FLESH
&amp; OLIVER SCREAMS]
From the guy I used to party with
to who you are now.
Yeah.
I had to make some tough choices.
Help me.
You're right.
It changed me.
I am waiting
-What kind of tough choices?
-I don't wanna talk about those experiences.
In these little moments
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Saved by the cell.
Hall. Ahem.
Okay, put what the CI told you
in the warrant application. I'll be right there.
It's work. I gotta go.
Okay.
Felicity, listen. I need you to activate
the bug in McKenna's phone.
I think the police just
got a lead on the Dodger.
Okay.
Who are you?
My name's Alan Durand.
I'm an exchange student.
I was on a fishing excursion with my class.
We got lost and our boat caught fire.
It was some mechanic malfunction.
We had to jump ship.
-When?
-Two days ago.
It was awful. I thought I was gonna die.
[CRYING]
Where are the other students?
Where's the boat's crew? Huh?
I think I'm the only one who made it.
I managed to get to shore.
I thought I was lucky.
What? Somebody found you?
Soldiers or...
Yes!
Yes. They had these masks on.
They attacked me and beat me!
They left me here!
Who are they?
You can untie me at any point, by the way.
DODGER: Nice place you have here.
ABBOTT: Thank you.
Tell me, does every fence
in this town hire muscle?
Heh. I did as soon as I heard
about what you did to Cass Derenick.
Ah, yes, Cass. God rest his soul.
He wasn't a very nice man.
-He tried to steal from me.
-Oh.
I've heard that you have
a better sense of judgment.
And that you'd have no trouble
in moving this.
Well, it's only a recession
for some people.
I take a 15 percent commission
off the top.
Let's call it 12, shall we?
I don't have to remind you
what happened to the last person...
...who tried to screw me over.
S.C.P.D. Grab the floor!
[YELLS]
[GUNFIRE]
[ABBOTT GRUNTS]
-Come quietly.
-I'm afraid I'll have to decline.
Then I'm afraid
you won't be going to jail.
[COLLAR BEEPING]
FELICITY:
I heard on the news the Dodger got away.
Hopefully the night
wasn't a complete waste.
Your dates. How'd they go?
-Great.
-Awesome.
You two suck at lying.
The police and I busted it up
before the Dodger could get himself paid.
-Don't change the subject.
-Is your hacker chip still working?
You two are no fun.
Yeah. Still getting a strong signal.
OLIVER:
You should pull up the police records.
-Everything the Dodger's stolen so far.
-What're you thinking?
We know the Dodger has a taste
for a very specific type of antiquity.
Yeah. These all look like
they're from the ominous decade.
The last ten years
of King Ferdinand's reign.
-And she says we have no lives.
OLIVER: Are there any other places...
...that sell or display items
from the ominous thing?
Decade. Not really.
People in Starling City
prefer the Elizabethan era.
OLIVER:
Starling City Cancer Society.
It says they're holding
a fundraising auction tomorrow.
-We could lure him out into the open.
-With what, a fake?
No. The Dodger has a trained eye
for this sort of thing.
He's not gonna fall for anything
less than the genuine article.
Where are we gonna get
a rare Spanish antiquity?
You really have no idea
how rich his family is, do you?
Roy William Harper Jr.
-Where's senior?
-Norris Cemetery.
-Sorry to hear that.
-You and an army of bookies.
-[OVER SPEAKER] Can I go?
LANCE: No.
You've been ID'd as a suspect
in a purse snatching.
Quite a résumé you've compiled here.
Petty theft, B and E, robbery, petty theft.
Stolen car. It's nice to change things up
once in a while.
And petty theft.
You got something against banks?
Well, it is hard to run
with one under your arm.
Well, maybe you'll learn
a few new skills in prison.
Look, I don't wanna steal, okay?
I don't have any other choice.
My mother, she has a problem.
Yeah, her son's a moron.
No.
Vertigo.
She got hooked on Vertigo last year.
She kicked it,
but I guess she'd done enough that...
...it messed her up.
Hmm.
She hasn't been the same.
And her medical bills... Look, I'm just trying
to help her get out from under.
Look, we're not privileged enough
to have as much as other people, okay?
Fine.
Let him go. It's just a damn purse, right?
They'll meet with you.
It has been arranged.
Thank you for this. There's one more thing
I need you to do for me.
Malcolm's the only one who knows
where Walter's being kept.
I just need a clue.
Some lead to follow.
If our plan works,
I can't let it damn Walter to hell.
No, that's the fate that's in store for us,
I'm afraid.
[ELEGANT CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYING]
[GUESTS CHATTERING]
The police are here too.
Your bait's attracted them, at least.
That's not exactly who I'm looking to catch.
So I'm getting a good signal
from the GPS I put in your family's brooch.
I can track it on my phone.
Speaking of, have you given any thought
to what might happen if this doesn't work...
...and the Dodger absconds
with your family jewels?
I'm sorry, that came out very wrong.
Let's just keep our eyes open, Felicity.
DIGGLE:
Hey, isn't that...?
Mm-hm.
I would rather take my chances
with a deadly jewel thief.
DIGGLE:
Right.
Hey, that brooch was donated
by the Queen family.
If you want it,
you're gonna have to bid.
Actually, love, I thought I'd just take it.
I should see if
the security guard's having problems.
Good idea.
I'm gonna go check on the bait.
I think I have a problem.
Get away from me.
If this thing blows...
That's not gonna happen.
The Dodger said if I called the police, he'd...
I'm gonna get decapitated, aren't I?
All right, tracker's on the move.
If I find him, I can get him to disarm it.
-Talk me in. Stay calm.
-Too late.
You can go. Just go, go, go.
Talk to me, Felicity. Talk to me.
Ahem. Heading towards Adams and O'Neil.
He's gotta be in a vehicle.
Hey, I need your bike.
-Are you kidding me?
OLIVER: No.
[GRUNTS]
[ENGINE REVS]
OLIVER:
I'm mobile. Where is he?
[HORNS HONK]
OLIVER [OVER PHONE]:
Talk to me, Felicity.
First time anyone's ever been
grateful for traffic cameras.
One block from you. If you cut through
Harris Plaza, you'll end up behind him.
OLIVER:
Where is he now?
FELICITY [OVER PHONE]:
I got him, I got him.
Gray sedan driving north
at the light ahead of you.
Dead ahead. Good. Okay, hard right.
OLIVER:
Got him.
Don't do anything stupid.
I had the foresight to collar up
a particularly inquisitive blond.
I assume she's a friend of yours.
Touch one hair on my head
and she loses hers.
You've got quite the choice to make,
don't you?
OLIVER:
Not this time.
Your median nerve's been severed.
You couldn't push that button
if you tried.
[BEEPS]
-Oh, thank God.
-Why are you doing this?
I'm exactly like you.
I only steal from the rich.
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLES
&amp; DODGER GRUNTS]
I'm not Robin Hood.
DURAND:
I don't know when these men are coming back.
You have to believe me.
Untie me, please.
What? Do you think these men,
they planted me here?
Some kind of trap or something?
Well, why'd they tie you up like that
and then just leave you?
Huh? Why not just kill you?
They were going to.
They got called away at some altercation...
...somewhere else on the island.
If they come back, they will kill both of us.
Please, you have to believe me. Please.
All right, turn around.
Thank you.
I'm sorry...
...but I can't.
What? Why? Why not?
Because I don't know you.
Are you out of your mind?
Please! You can't do this!
You can't just leave me here!
DIGGLE: Last night, all I could think about
was how pissed off Andy would be.
How hurt he would be
if he saw us together.
But that's nothing compared to how he'd be
if I did something to hurt you, Carly.
Believe me when I tell you
that war is easier than dating.
In a war, you act or you die.
No time to think,
no time to second-guess yourself.
Maybe that's your problem.
With me, you're thinking. Not feeling.
DIGGLE:
You're right.
ROY:
How'd you know where I live?
A little thing called the Internet.
Look, can we not do this
with a door between us?
I guess you're not pressing charges...
...because you feel like
you can change my life?
So you can tell your rich prep-school
friends what a saint you are...
-...and how you're helping the disadvantaged?
-You don't know a thing about me.
Thea Queen, trust-fund brat.
Totaled her car,
which she got as a birthday present.
Loves designer labels
and is in the tabloids for partying too much.
Did I leave anything out?
Yeah.
Dead father, missing stepdad,
damaged brother...
...and almost served jail time
for that car accident.
Plus, she really wants her purse back.
You showed some real sack
coming down here...
...the Glades in the middle of the night.
You must not know
the value of a vintage purse.
[SCOFFS]
Don't worry, it's all there, except for these.
-That's a really filthy habit you got there.
-Yeah. Tell me about it.
Hey, can I give you some advice?
First, stay out of the Glades.
And second?
Don't fall for every sob story
a guy like me tells the police.
You have a great evening, now.
Do you ever take time off?
I do.
In fact, last night, I went on a date.
The guy was kind of a jerk.
Really?
He might've had a reason.
McKenna, I didn't just lose
five years on the island.
I lost the part of me
that enjoyed being alive.
Listening to music and, uh...
...eating a soufflé with a beautiful girl.
It's the easy things.
But when you asked me about the island,
it reminded me of all the hard things.
And the hard choices that I had to make
that still stay with me.
Made me question how I can trust...
...and even if I'm worthy of being
with anyone.
You are.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
Can I take you to a dinner
that I promise not to cut short?
Um...
-Throw in a soufflé and you're on.
LANCE: McKenna.
I'm glad you're still here. Queen.
-Mr. Lance.
McKENNA: I was just leaving.
Is everything okay, sir?
Yeah. I'd like you to work with me
on the vigilante investigation.
Yes, sir. Well, don't worry.
We'll bring him in...
Oh, yeah.
[McKENNA CHUCKLES]
-Uh, ready to go?
-Yep.
McKENNA:
Okay.
Tastes like an ashtray,
but does the job.
I owe you one.
You didn't get into any trouble
out there, did you?
Hmm?
No. Not a bit.
Frank Chen recommended you.
He said you could help us
with our problem.
He appreciates you agreeing
to meet with me.
Anything for a friend.
So how can we be of assistance?
Malcolm Merlyn.
I want you to kill him for me.