My name is Oliver Queen.
After five years in hell...
1 returned home
with only one goal--
to save my city.
For eight years, I've fought
alongside brave men and women
striving for justice,
but then a Crisis came,
and I had to become
someone else.
I had to become something else.
1 made the ultimate sacrifice,
which helped birth an
entirely new universe.
Now my friends and family
will have to go on without me,
and although I have
become a Spectre,
there is a part of me
that will always be
the Green Arrow.
Both my children will live.
Mom... what are you doing?
-Thea, I love you. No.
Close your eyes, baby.
No!
You possess true courage, Moira.
I'm truly sorry...
you did not pass
that on to your son.
It's just such a
strange thing to learn
that there's a whole other...
world, I guess...
where I died.
The people that knew
my son best tefl me
that when Oliver sacrificed
himself during the Crisis,
that somehow he's the
reason that everything changed,
that the world we're
living in right now is
a kind of gift from him.
I don't know. I'm just
trying to process it.
II think we're all still
trying to process it,
not only Oliver's death...
but what he leaves behind.
It's a hell of a legacy.
Not just a city of heroes,
a world of heroes.
When I started this project,
it was intended to
explore the history
and the pitfalls of
vigilantism in Star City.
I never thought this documentary
would have to be retooled
to be a memorial.
Nothing really ever, um,
happens the way you
expect it to happen,
and that was, uh,
certainly the case...
with Oliver and his mission.
He always said
he would go it alone
and that the mission
would never...
be over.
I'm glad he was...wrong
about the first part...
heartbroken he was
wrong about the second.
Thank you.
That was very moving.
Yeah.
- Hey, hey.
- Hey, man.
You all right?
Everything good.
Why do I get the sense
that answer disappoints you?
I just can't believe it.
Let's go.
When Oliver
rebooted the universe,
he fixed things.
Ever since the Crisis,
crime in Star City
disappeared overnight
literally.
Dig, he...he saved this city.
Yeah.
Come on. It's time.
Prochnost.
Ugh. I didn't know
you speak Russian.
No. That's what
Oliver used to say
every time he drank this stuff.
“What exactly is
this stuff? “Vodka.
Yeah. It tastes like turpentine.
With faint hints of
nail polish remover.
So what's the plan?
I plan on getting as drunk
as humanly possible.
No. I mean after the funeral.
From what Dinah tells me,
there's not much need
for vigilantes anymore.
Lance's term ends in April.
He's endorsing
me to replace him.
-As mayor? No. As a
bald guy with an attitude.
Yeah, as mayor.
What about you, D?
Mayor, uh--for now at
least-- Lance actually
just offered me a
promotion to Chief of Police.
Guys, look. I know
how this looks.
1 just don't feel
like this is over,
Yeah. You're not reading
the same comstat reports I am.
We're a month out
of this Crisis, Dinah,
and there's tons
that we don't know,
what I do know is this.
Though Oliver's
gone, his mission
is far from over.
Finally. What the hell happened?
Jimmy Tarallo gave
me a few problems.
And by a few, you mean a
dozen men armed with knives?
No. I mean 22 with machetes.
Queen, you shouldn't
be doing this alone.
You're not ready to
go into the field, Diggle.
Yeah? Well, when I signed on,
I told you I was here to
keep the body count low.
That includes you.
Well, I'm fine.
And Tarallo?
Alittle less so.
What's this?
The next name on the list.
John Byrne? What's the
CEO of a beer company
have to do to deserve an
arrow between the eyes?
Well, the company's a front.
He's using his trucks to ferry
a very different
type of commodity.
Drugs?
People.
Human trafficking?
Where does this end?
How many names are on your list?
Too many to cross
off. Listen, Diggle.
This doesn't end.
The mission is never over.
You can survive this,
make it home, right my wrongs,
but you got to live
through this first.
Survive.
No!
Hey. “What the frak?
Sorry. Il didn't
mean to scare you.
I meant to time portal
to your front door,
but I guess Il
overshot the mark a bit.
This is a-this is a nice room.
Time portal?
Yeah. I'm a time
traveler, remember?
Right. Okay. Um, and why
did you time travel here?
Because I'm here to take
you to your father's funeral.
You know, I actually
should have tried that sooner.
It's not that hard, actually.
That's because your arms
are the size of telephone poles.
You doing okay?
When am I never not okay?
I don't think any of
us are really okay,
but it seems to be hitting
you particularly hard.
I'm fine, like always.
You ready?
-Yeah. Let's do this. Yeah.
So what did Oliver
call this thing?
He called it the Mark of Four.
So how you doing?
Uh, I'm just--I'm
nervous about the funeral.
Yeah.
Yeah. You know,
Thea's gonna be there.
Imagine both of Oliver's
sisters would be there.
1kind of left Thea abruptly.
Ah. You're worried about
an awkward reunion.
I'm worried about
any kind of reunion.
Well, hey. Look at it this way.
After fighting the
Mirakuru soldiers
and the Thanatos Guild,
seeing your ex-girlfriend
should be cake.
That's why I'm scared.
I don't want her to
be my ex-girlfriend.
So when's Felicity get to town?
I don't know if she's coming.
It's her husband's funeral, man.
Which is exactly why I
think she might miss it.
I don't know, Rene.
She has a nanny
watching Mia right now.
Felicity hasn't even
made it out of bed.
I have no idea how to help her.
At least bring me for backup.
How many times are we
gonna go over this, Diggle?
You know, I went
through Byrne's financials.
Every month, he gives
over a million dollars
to this outfit called
Black Armada.
-You know who they are?
-Private security firm.
Former special forces.
-That's right,
and you don't think
it's a good idea to bring
a former soldier of your own?
No.
You know what I think?
I don't think you
really want me there.
Oh. Thanks for
finally getting my point.
I don't think you want me
there because you're afraid
1 will stop you from
committing cold-blooded murder.
You think that your role is
to keep the body count low.
There's a way you can stop
him tonight without killing him.
You could take him to prison,
you could see that
justice is served.
The man traffics
in human beings.
Killing him is justice.
-But at what cost?
You say your mission will
never end. Well, trust me,
it will end a lot sooner
if you lose who you are.
Mia?
Don't worry. The
Monitor didn't drop me off
because there's
another Crisis coming.
That still doesn't explain
what you're doing here.
Laurel's sister showed up,
thought I might enjoy
going to my dad's funeral.
And what are you
doing with all this stuff?
Trying my best to
channel my mom.
Sorry. Um, when
Sara dropped me off,
she gave me this whole
lecture about not telling people
about the future, SO...
Few weeks before
Sara showed up...
something happened.
William!
Right in front of me. I couldn't
do anything to stop it, and...
I am already failing at
being the Green Arrow.
What we do is not easy.
There are setbacks,
there are tragedies,
but, God, Mia, your father,
he would be so, so proud
of how you're
carrying all of that.
I can't even do
the one thing that
he risked his
entire life to do--
protect my family.
What's this?
Well, your mother's
Archer protocol scans
news stations for
certain key words.
William Clayton, the son of
the late hero Oliver Queen,
was abducted tonight in
his hometown of Central City.
The police have
been unable to confirm
any suspects in the kidnapping.
Hey. Hey.
Look. I'm sorry about
the way that I left.
ljust...
Ollie's just passed away,
and William's been kidnapped,
50...as far as apologies go,
your timing's a
little not great.
If you still think Oliver's
mission's finished,
tell that to William
when we get him back.
We will get him back,
but, John, William
was kidnapped
outside of Star City.
I'm sure that'll make
him feel a whole lot better.
- reached out to Felicity.
-Yeah. Me, too.
Radio silence.
I asked Sara to check on her.
Ah. I haven't seen this many
people down here in a while.
Hey.
It's almost like a party.
Um, I tried running a
quad-grid search task
to a keyhole
satellite array, but...
That array's dark-sided as it
undergoes a firmware upgrade,
but fortunately when
William moved to Central City,
his overbearing stepmom implanted a
subdermal tracking device into his arm.
Ethical--debatable.
Which went dark as soon
as he reentered Star City.
Well, that's
convenient at least.
Just one second as I work
up a statistically correlated list
of possible locations
he could be at.
That is a very long list.
Which is exactly why
we called everyone.
Thank you all for coming,
some on very short notice.
Oliver made the
ultimate sacrifice
for his friends and his family.
Now a part of his
family needs our help.
This is our most
important mission.
Suit up.
Okay. Well, he's not here.
What was the next
place on Felicity's list?
Kord industries.
All right. Well, let's go.
Hey. Can I talk to
you for a second?
You already did back
at the bunker, okay? I...
I get it. You're sorry.
No. I never told you why I left.
And you don't need to.
I understand. You
were going through a lot.
Dying, getting resurrected,
it gave me a whole new
perspective on--on everything,
including you.
You know, I got
my whole life back,
and I realized that
I wanted you in it...
forever and... and always.
And what does that mean?
It means...
will you marry me?
Uh...
Get out.
Get out!
“What the hell is that thing?
-Get outta here!
-Come on. Let's go!
-Go, go, go, go!
Ahh,
Nice. I would have fired
some shots in the air.
My way's scarier.
So, how are things?
It's been a while.
Yeah. Well, a
while is what it took
for these rags to work again.
Since then, I've been
fighting for justice.
To honor your father?
To honor Oliver.
We've had our
differences over the years.
Yeah, I assumed.
Why?
Of everyone,
you're the most like him.
Clear! Clear!
Damn it!
What?
He's not here.
Curtis said there's a bunch
of places he could still be.
-Well, we need to
find him. We will.
We have to find him, Johnny.
We will, Lyla. Are you okay?
Oliver put our
family back together.
What happens if--
if we can't do the same for his?
Lyla, look at me. We can,
and we will, I promise.
We will.
Let him go!
Who the hell are you?
I said, who are you?
You're wearing his
hood. You should know.
No, please, please.
Agh!
Unh!
You stay back!
John Bye...
you have failed this city.
Let him go!
I' brought him up
here to throw him off.
My whole life ended right here!
I don't care! Final warning.
He thought he was saving me.
eight years in Iron Heights
never saved anyone.
So you kidnap his son,
the man who spared your life?
I should put this
arrow in you right now!
Do it! After eight
years in prison,
1 got nothing left
to live for anyway!
Go ahead!
No.
Oliver Queen didn't kill you,
then neither will I,
but your ass is
going back to prison.
This is the riser,
uh, this is the arrow shelf,
and this is the fadeout.
That's really cool.
That's...
Mia.
Must be a lot to take in.
Yeah. That's the...
understatement
of the millennium.
She became a hero.
Well, she had good parents.
Do you...you want to meet her?
I don't know.
She--she might be here,
but she's...she's also at home,
waiting for me,
and I get to see her grow up.
I'm not sure I
want to rush that.
- Hey.
Something on the
news you should see.
What?
William Clayton
was safely recovered
from his kidnapper John Byrne.
Apparently the
abduction was revenge
for Oliver Queen bringing
Byrne to justice eight years ago.
We have exclusive
footage of the rescue.
With Oliver Queen
confirmed dead,
we can only speculate
that he inspired
a new generation of heroes
to carry on his mission.
Like I said...proud.
Diggle!
Don't use just your arms.
Power's coming from your hips.
Thanks for the tip.
Just get real good at that,
and maybe I'll eventually
take you out in the field.
Byrne didn't really have
a good night, did he?
He had a better
night than you think.
He's being arraigned
in the morning.
Hmm.
Plenty of people in this
book that deserve to die,
plain and simple,
probably not everyone.
Let's consider
Mr. John Byrne to be
proof of concept.
That people can be redeemed?
That one day I'll
be able to trust you.
Your mom let me in.
Is it just me, or
does the new Moira
seem to like me a lot
more than the old Moira?
Yeah. She never really
liked you that much,
but in her defense,
you were a criminal.
Well, I regret nothing.
If I never stole your purse,
then I never would have met you,
and even if you do
say no to my proposal,
which II really hope you don't--
loving you has
changed my life, Thea.
If Ollie's death has
taught me anything, it's...
that we don't have a
lot of time in this life.
As long as you promise
if you ever freak out
on me like that again,
you tell me instead
of just leaving.
Yeah, yeah. I--] can
make that promise.
Then yes.
Yes?
1 will marry you, Roy Harper.
Hey. What are you doing here?
Looking for you.
Well, I was just
looking for Dinah.
I think she's, uh, ghosting me.
Do you have a second to talk?
Want to step into not my office?
So, uh, what's up?
It's about Oliver.
Well, not exactly him, but...
who his sacrifice brought back.
-Like me?
-And Tommy and Moira...
but not me
or the other me, your--
your Laurel.
Look. We don't
exactly know the rules
of this whole
resurrection thing.
Yes, we do.
You're all of the
people who Oliver
would have wanted his
sacrifice to bring back,
and Laurel, she--
she would have
been on that list, too,
if it wasn't for me.
Oliver's death, it
fixed everything else.
Why didn't it fix this, too?
Because, sweetheart,
there is nothing about you
that needed to be fixed.
All right.
Dig, what's going on?
The end of the line.
You were right.
The mission's over.
Just took me a
while to accept that.
I think accepting
that meant accepting
that Oliver is really gone.
You know, Sara said
that before Oliver died
that he became something else.
I'd like to think that
somehow, someway,
he's still here.
I'd drink to that.
Just as long as it's no more
of that God-awful vodka.
Okay. Cool. So...
you're moving on.
So what's next for you?
Lyla accepted a promotion
in Metropolis, so...
we're all gonna move
there after the funeral.
Soaml.
I'm not gonna
take the promotion.
Just no point being
police in a safe city,
and there are lots of
cities that still need saving.
Damn.
And here I am getting to
be elected in a few months,
and you guys
decide to move away.
Kind of hard not to
take that personally.
Don't worry, Rene. You
are gonna be a great mayor
because you're a great man.
I learned from the best.
Oliver.
And the two of you.
Who's getting the lights?
1 will.
I'm gonna miss this place.
We all will.
Thank you for coming.
For a long time...
I hated Oliver Queen.
I blamed him for the death
of my youngest daughter,
I blamed him for the
violence in my city,
I interrogated
him, I hunted him,
persecuted him.
I've never been
more wrong in my life.
Oliver Queen wasn't just a hero.
He was a good man.
He was an honorable person.
The fact that he
didn't start out that way
makes him, in my book,
even more honorable.
He stands as a
reminder to all of us
that anyone can change.
So will this.
I just don't understand.
If Ollie could fix everything,
then why couldn't he fix this?
I think that Oliver could
only change the things
that didn't change him,
and if not for
your father and...
what he did for Oliver,
your brother would never have
become the man that he was.
still can't believe
Ollie's really gone.
I know, sweetheart.
I'm sorry to intrude,
but I wanted to meet you.
-I'm-- My sister.
Oliver told me a lot about you.
I'm sorry that it took
something like this
for us to finally meet.
Yes. Emiko, you are
welcome here anytime.
Thank you.
So you're from
another Earth, is that it?
I know it's a lot to take in.
Well, I just found out there's
a reality where I was dead,
so that's the curve I'm
grading on these days.
The Laurel of, well,
this Earth, um...
she was my wife.
So it must be strange seeing me.
Ho! Yeah. Well, strange
enough to blow the curve...
but there's something
nice about it, too.
My condolences on
your husband's passing.
I had our marriage erased.
Feelings cannot be erased.
I had no feelings for him.
Our marriage was
Father's perverse joke,
meant to torment me.
Our father only ever meant
for you to have a normal life.
I have lived a life
far more normal
than the one father
designed for me.
Hey. Thank you for coming.
There's nowhere else I'd be.
Sara, this is my sister Talia.
-Hi. Hello.
Talia, this is Sara,
my beloved.
Hey, Dad.
Hi.
Oh. Hi.
"me - know.
This morning, you were teething,
and now you're-- I mean, wow.
Dad had a very similar
reaction when he first saw me.
You met your father.
Yeah. He trained me.
He taught me to be a hero,
how to be like him.
I can tell you're
a lot like him.
I can only hope.
Felicity.
Hey.
I'm so sorry.
He was a good man.
I was there at the end, and...
every day, I'm tortured
with the thought
that I could have done more,
should have done more.
No. You did everything
that you could, Barry.
How could you know that?
Well, because, you
know, I know you.
I'm sorry.
- Hey. Hey.
- Hey.
Felicity.
I'm so sorry.
There is no body down there, no?
No.
We buried a casket
full of mementos.
Does anybody wanna
say a few words?
I'm barely keeping
it together as it is.
I think that Oliver
would have been worried
that I'd say something
tactless anyway, so...
- don't know what to say. Yeah.
Words seem... meaningless.
Hey.
Should be you.
The Oliver that I
met eight years ago
is not the one that we
say good-bye to today.
Oliver always told me
that in order to save his city,
he had to become someone else,
he had to become something else.
I always thought that meant
becoming the Green Arrow,
but...today, I realized
that meant becoming
a better man,
the best man he knew how to be,
and he took all of us
with him on that journey.
He changed everything.
Oliver brought
heroes into the world,
he inspired heroes,
he inspired all of us here.
I was his brother,
and Oliver Queen... was mine.
Of course, life will go on.
It always does,
but how, what twists
and turns it will take,
I can't say.
I don't know what
the future holds...
except to say fo
expect the unexpected.
bangs]
Oliver may be gone,
but his mission endures.
That mission lives on,
Oliver lives on in the
people he inspired.
Some will take that mission
to the rest of the world...
maybe even beyond that...
because if the past eight
years has shown us anything...
it's that this
universe is far bigger
than any of us could
have dared imagine...
even ifitis a little less bright
without him in it.
Where I'm taking you,
there is no return.
I have waited a very
long time to see him.
I'm ready.
Hi.
Glad you could finally make it.
This is so nice.
Not to complain. I just thought
that the afterlife
would look a little less
like your old office.
It's my mom's office.
I wanted to be
where I first saw you.
Well, that would be in the IT
Department seven floors down.
You sure?
You're cute.
Too bad you're, you know, dead,
which is obviously a lot
worse for you than it is for me.
It's a long story.
Lucky for us...
we have all the
time in the world
for me to tell it to you.
Greg, move your head!