Previously, on "Arrow"...
This city needs someone
to stand up who isn't
hiding behind a mask.
It needs a leader.
So, I've decided
to run for mayor.
Ollie, this is Alex Davis,
the new political strategist
that Walter recommended.
At the house, I looked Sara in the eyes.
She wasn't there.
I'm the one who killed her
in the first place.
That's why she's
after me, you know.
It's blood lust;
She's consumed by it.
It's the same pain I feel
when I think about ra's.
If she kills me, she'll be ok.
Curtis: There's more
to the recording...
something overlapping with it.
Ray: What I need you
to know is,
I'm alive, and I'm in trouble.
Ray: Open new file.
Atom project, update gamma.
This will be
miniaturization
test number one.
Execute.
Why can't
anything ever work
the first time?
Hmm?
All right, guys,
I know it's been
a long haul
figuring out your platform,
but the good
news is, we're
almost done.
Just two more
things here
on the docket.
Mmm, actually, only one.
I figured out where
we're going to hold
Ollie's fundraiser.
It's going to be at Gerard's.
From what I remember,
that place is a little pricey,
leading us to our
last talking point,
the budget.
You have it, right?
If by "you," you mean Felicity,
then, yes. She was
supposed to be here,
but she's just been slammed
at Palmer tech
for the past few days.
She's really taking
this whole ceo thing seriously.
Well, one of us has
to have a job that
actually makes money.
I'll speak with her,
I'll get those
numbers for you.
Alex, thank you so much
for all your hard work.
I'll see you later.
[Exhales]
[Door closes]
I was thinking,
maybe we should
check out Gerard's
tomorrow night.
You know, just to make sure
it's the right type of venue
for introducing our candidate.
Are you asking me out on a date?
[Chuckles]
To be honest,
it's been so long,
I don't even know.
I just am... my life is
really complicated right now,
and I don't think going
on a date with my brother's
campaign manager
is going to make it any easier.
No, you're right.
That was totally
unprofessional;
something I would
normally never do.
I just...
Thought there was
something there.
Probably just consumed
a little too much msg.
How about we just
erase these last
five minutes?
Absolutely not.
It was nice.
I'll see you later.
[Door opens, closes]
Ray: I'm alive,
and I'm in trouble.
I'm alive,
I'm alive...
I thought I said
you could use my lab
if you clean up after yourself.
The keyword being "after,"
which assumes finished,
which clearly, I am not.
[Scoffs] Well, how's it going?
Ughh!
That well?
[Sighs]
Ray: I'm alive...
Do you have that
playing on a loop?
I've been trying
to trace to Ray's message
back to its point of origin,
but he must have ping-ponged it
off of like a thousand servers,
and the back trace algorithm
won't compile, which means
there's no way of finding him,
and...
ok!
You need to stop right now.
I can't.
You have to.
You are no good
to Mr. Palmer in
your current state.
Now, how long
has it been since
you took a break?
I dozed off
for about two minutes
about an hour ago,
does that count?
[Elevator dings]
[Exhales]
You're married,
he's straight,
you're married,
ahem.
Ah, perfect. Oliver queen,
Curtis holt. Curtis, Oliver.
Curtis! Felicity's
told me a lot about you.
She's told me
virtually
nothing about you.
[Chuckles] Ok.
Curtis?
What you doin'?
The green Arrow
showed up right
about the time
that you came back into town.
Nah, it's not you,
though. Jaw's not right.
That's what I keep
telling people.
Would you give us a minute?
Sure thing.
Nice meeting you.
Nice meeting you, too. Ahem.
Hey.
Hi.
I thought
that you were
going to come by
the campaign
offices to go
over the finances.
I thought that meeting
was on Wednesday.
It is Wednesday.
Oh.
What's going on?
Ray: I'm alive...
And I'm in trouble.
That sounds like...
ray. Because it is ray,
because ray isn't dead.
What?
That's impossible.
Ray was...
killed. In an explosion
that blew up the top
of this building six months ago.
But that's obviously
not what happened,
because he sent
this message six days ago,
and dead people
don't generally do that.
Ray's alive.
He's out there somewhere.
I have to help him,
why didn't you
ever tell us about
this place before?
I didn't know it was here.
But it sort of seems
like you did.
I know this island
isn't all that it seems.
You've done well, Mr. queen.
But you let
the British guy
get away.
Whoa, wait. Reiter.
Constantine said that
there was some sort of
barrier, like magic.
I have no interest
in the chamber.
What is that?
A message, from the ancients,
leading to a very special gift.
A heart of water.
Have you seen a cove
on the island,
surrounded by mountains?
Yeah, I know of one.
I want you to go
to that point
and lead an excavation.
Take a dozen
of the laborers
and work them
until you find my gift.
Can I talk to you for a sec?
All right, first,
what aren't you telling me
about what we're doing here?
I mean, apart from everything.
And second?
Queen is a mole.
Don't start trusting him
just 'cause he gave you
a piece of bling.
Accompany Mr. queen
to the cove.
I know.
I know. [Chuckles]
I love you, too, mom.
I love you so much.
Ok, bye, mom.
[Sighs]
How'd that go?
Easier than the last time
mom found out
that I wasn't dead.
[Chuckles]
Hey.
You ok, honey?
Yeah, fine. It was
just something mom said
about how I got lost
when I was walking
home from school once,
and... and how I promised
that I'd always come back.
But I can't remember.
You're probably
better off
not remembering
all the messed up
things our parents
did to us, anyway.
Hey, you two turned out
perfectly, all right,
and more importantly,
you're both home.
I couldn't ask
for anything more.
I tell you Ray's in trouble
and your first response is,
you need a shower.
And a nap.
You're not going
to be able to help...
oh, stop.
You're starting
to sound like Curtis.
Well, Curtis is a smart guy.
Did Ray's message
indicate what kind
of trouble he's in?
If it did, it would have been
the first thing I told you.
Ok. Is there anything
that I can do to help?
Well, have you magically
learned to code
in the last 72 hours?
No.
It was a rhetorical question.
I know.
I will, however,
accept your undying
support and backrub.
You can have
both as soon
as you...
Shower.
And take a nap.
Come on.
Come on, come on.
[Groans]
[Cell phone vibrates]
What?
I set an alert just in case
the back trace program
ever finished compiling.
Felicity...
Two seconds!
It's been taking forever.
What are you doing?
Absolutely nothing.
Felicity, Felicity, is that you?
Felicity: Oh,
my god, ray!
Ray, where are you?
I don't know.
And if that wasn't enough,
I think I'm being held
against my will.
What?!
Yeah, they want my suit,
or at least the tech.
The good news is, the tech is
useless to them
in my current condition.
Ray, if you have
your suit, then
why don't you just...
bust my way out?
Yeah, that's
not really happening.
What, the suit doesn't work?
Actually, it worked
a little too well.
They want my suit,
or at least the tech.
The good news is,
the tech is useless
to them in my current condition.
John is never
going to believe this.
Neither is thea.
And, well, ray is...
the size of a tater tot.
Ray modified his suit
with the same nanites
I injected into him
after bad Arrow shot him.
It's a long story involving
a lot of molecular physics.
The bottom line is that ray
jury-rigged a short-range
message burst
that was intercepted
by whoever's
holding him captive.
Ray thinks they
want the suit
for its technology,
but they can't use
it while its small.
And while he's small,
it's like looking
for a needle
in a city of haystacks.
Ray has something
he thinks could help.
Back at Palmer tech,
I've got schematics
for a machine
that should be able
to resize me.
Well, now that
you're both
filled in...
Where are you going?
To Palmer tech
to pull up the schematics
for Ray's device.
I'll come with you.
Why? Are you going
to build the thing?
No.
There must be
some other way
I can help.
There isn't.
This isn't over, you know.
You and me.
I'm so glad.
[Sighs]
We need to get
a couple people
in the water.
Dive down,
see what you can find.
Everyone is tired.
We've been here
for hours.
If you want them
to work, they have
to be able to.
Are you their leader?
I'm the guy telling you
to let them rest.
Ok.
You brought food.
Take 15 minutes and eat.
Well, ain't you
employer of the month.
I'm going to need
you to keep
an eye on them,
and I'm going
to go enjoy
my lunch in peace.
Hey, Ukraine.
My name is vlad.
Well, vlad,
how'd you like
your life to get
a little better?
Doctor Palmer got
miniaturization to work.
He made the space
between atoms shrink.
I mean, this is like
solving cold fusion
and ultimate theory.
Do you have any idea
how amazing this is?
Yes. But the fact
that ray is being
held hostage
and could be killed
at any moment
because he is the size
of a cheeto has
dampened my enthusiasm
somewhat.
Can you build this?
Yes. Um, all the materials
are here at Palmer tech,
um, except for that.
That is a quantum manifold.
Never heard of it.
Where do we get one?
Only one place...
the manufacturer.
They hold the patent on it...
well, actually, 16 patents.
Where?!
Kord industries. I'd ask
them to do us a solid
and loan it to us, but...
They're our biggest competitor.
The good news is,
things can't get
any worse.
[Woman shrieks]
You just had to go and say that.
There you are!
Mom. Oh.
Ha ha ha!
Whee!
Oh, what are you doing here?
Well, I went
to your office,
miss ceo,
and your assistant
told me you'd be here.
So... Here I am.
Not here-here,
star city here.
Well, Oliver told me
that you've been
working nonstop
this past month, so I suggested
a visit from your mom...
uh-huh.
Is exactly what you needed,
and guess what?
What?
He agreed.
Oh.
Oh, hi.
And who are you?
Oh.
Hi.
I'm Curtis holt.
It is an absolute
pleasure to meet you.
Oh!
I can see where Felicity
got her, uh...
Blonde hair.
[All laugh]
Well, she dyes it, actually.
So, what do you want
to do first?
A trip to the mall,
mani-pedi.
You know what,
you must be exhausted
from your flight.
Why don't I get
a car to take you
back to my place?
A car? No, baby, i...
i came here to see you.
I know! And you
will. It's just
that, right now,
Curtis and I are trying
to figure out how to
build a very important
piece of equipment,
or someone could die.
Die?
Metaphorically speaking!
You start constructing
the machine, and I will
get you the manifold.
But it's proprietary!
How are you going
to do that?
I'm not!
Awesome.
The green Arrow's
going to be kicking
some ass tonight.
If I don't kick his first.
I thought it would be
a good thing.
Felicity:
A good thing?
What on earth made
you agree to this?
Well, you know,
your mom doesn't really
take no for an answer.
You've faced down
Mirakuru soldiers
and the league
of assassins.
Are you honestly telling
me that you couldn't
say no to my mom?
She said she missed you
and then she texted me
one of those emojis
with the single tear.
You have
been texting
with my mother?!
How long has that been going on?
You guys think we can
find a better time
to fight about this?
John? I thought only
Oliver's line was open.
Nope. Mine is open.
And mine.
I don't remember there being
so much chatter
on these missions.
Are you ok?
Yeah.
I need a little normal.
And for me,
this is the kind of
thing that passes.
I hacked the security panel,
but it needs
to be accessed
from the inside.
Only problem is that
the building's interior
is protected by pressure
sensitive flooring,
which means chatty
Kathy, you're up.
Chatty Kathy?
Your new code name,
the only one appropriate
enough I could think of
to use in polite company.
Once the loading dock's
doors are open,
you'll have 90 seconds
to find the manifold
and amscray before
men with guns show up.
Chatty Kathy?
You know, when I get back,
you and I are
going to have a talk.
I'm at the panel.
Felicity: Stand by.
Punch in 4, 5, 8, 7.
90 seconds, clock's running.
Are you sure
it was a good idea
to bring Sara along?
She'll be fine.
[Beeps]
Something's wrong.
The security cameras
are coming back online.
Oliver:
I've got it.
No, don't you understand?!
If kord upgraded their security,
they probably improved
their response time.
[Alarm sounds]
Wait, I think this is it.
Sara, stop!
Sara!
We have to go.
Oliver: We're clear.
Hello?
[Gasps]
Is anyone there?
Ray...
Any luck with the schematics?
I realize the quantum manifold
could present a challenge.
Nothing a little
late night shopping
at kord industries
couldn't solve.
[Exhales] Oh, that's great.
Thank you, Felicity.
Now we just have
to figure out how to...
ray, you still there?
Oh, no.
What happened out there?
Sara, she, um...
Had a moment
with the security guard.
Laurel and thea took her home.
Are you sure it was
darhk that you saw
in Ray's camera?
Just as sure as I am
that ray is not
getting out of this!
It's actually good
that darhk has ray.
This would be the same
level of delusion
that made you think
my mother coming to town
would make me feel better?
Because it's darhk,
that means that
we have an asset.
Lance.
I'll ask him to get
us a location.
And what if between
then and now,
darhk decides to squish ray
underneath his shoe?
If darhk wanted
to hurt ray, he would
have done it by now.
Dig's right.
We stay focused.
We get Curtis
the manifold,
keep him working,
and we unfortunately
just have to wait
and see what Lance finds out.
I hate waiting and seeing.
I have to do something.
Your mother's
in town, spend
some time with her.
We could do dinner.
I'll cook.
You already made
dinner plans
with my mother,
didn't you?
What? No.
Yes.
Oh! Oh, my god!
It is like a sickness with you!
It wasn't intentional.
We were having
a nice conversation;
the subject turned to cooking,
I mentioned that
I make a spectacular
chicken cordon bleu.
She said she'd never had
one. It's just dinner.
He's right, Felicity.
Besides, you look
like you haven't...
Eaten or slept.
A man's life, a friend's life
is in danger.
Doesn't seem like
the right time
for cordon bleu.
I promise you that
there is nothing
that we can do
until we get what we need
from Lance and Curtis.
So, dinner.
7:00 P.M.
I'll be there
as soon as I'm done with Lance.
[Twigs snapping]
[Gasps]
[Exhales]
Nice instincts.
I wasn't sure
you were coming back.
Well... I said
that I would.
I guess it's no surprise to you,
but I have lost faith
in people doing what
they said they're going to do.
Do you notice reiter interested
in anything
other than
the camp or drugs?
Yeah. He also enjoys
stealing people
away from their families.
Well, have you seen
him do anything,
uh, mystical,
or even...
Magical?
He always has been a little odd.
And very religious.
He's even blessed
some of the prisoners.
Claims he's healed
their souls or some craziness.
[Sighs] I'm beginning to think
that drugs are just a front
for what he's really doing here.
What could be more tempting
to a man like him than money?
Power.
I can't stay long.
I can't have Conklin
being any more
suspicious of me
than he already is,
but you still need
to stay here.
I'll come back as much as I can.
This time, I believe you.
Heh, I thought it was
past time that we met.
My engineers have had
no success in restoring you
to your proper size,
so I thought I'd appeal
to your cooperation.
And what do I get
if I help you out?
Apart from probably death.
No.
I don't think it's your life
you should be worried about.
I'm sorry, Felicity,
this is my fault.
And who is this
"Felicity," I wonder?
Certainly not your
former vice-president,
current ceo, girlfriend.
Don't you touch her.
Don't make empty threats.
It's...
Small.
Oh, and by the way,
we weren't listening
for a distress call
from a dead man.
It was pure luck,
really, that we intercepted
your message.
But isn't luck
just another word for destiny?
[Door closes]
Oliver: Sorry I'm late.
I, um, I tried
following the recipe,
but, you know,
I think your oven
might be broken,
because I was supposed
to put in for like
20 minutes,
and, I don't know,
smoke just started
billowing out,
and I think the chicken's
just a little,
slightly undercooked.
I think the technical
term is raw.
It's... it's fine,
it's fine.
I'm home now.
I'll whip
something up.
'Cause you just always
fix everything.
A man who cooks.
You put a ring on that.
How'd that very important
doctor's appointment go, hon?
Uh, good, yes.
Dr. Lance is just
going to find out
where the pain
is coming from.
Pain? You ok, hon?
Fine. I'm just
trying to figure out
what I've done wrong.
I...[Chuckles]
I'm going to go
get some take-out.
The best part
about arguing
is the make-up sex.
[Clears throat]
[Door opens, closes]
Ok.
Inviting your mother
for a surprise visit
wasn't the best idea.
I totally accept that.
What I'm not accepting,
or understanding,
is just you shutting me out.
I am not shutting you out.
I'm trying to focus
on finding ray,
but I can't do that
with all of these distractions.
Distractions? What is
going on with you?
You're acting like it's
my fault that ray...
it's my fault.
What's happening with ray...
to ray... is my fault.
Felicity, it really isn't.
Ray was sending distress calls
for weeks after the accident.
I wasn't here to receive them
because I was too busy
traveling the world with you.
I took the voice's word
for it that no body
could be recovered
because I was so swept up
in being with you.
I'm sorry.
It was my choice
to uproot my entire life,
leave my home and my job,
which turns out,
I am very good at.
I lost myself in you,
and I was never that girl.
That girl who just
loses herself in a guy.
That is not who I am.
This isn't about ray.
It's about us.
No.
Yes.
I don't know.
Ok.
I'm going to give
you some space until
you figure it out.
[Door closes]
It says the traffic
cameras are online.
Yeah, you got to give it
a minute to upload.
What are you doing here, anyway?
I thought I was waiting
for Lance and you were
having dinner
with the smoak ladies.
Went that well, did it?
Do you know what I miss
about our old space?
That trunk, with the bottle
of Russian vodka in it.
Vodka...
Is for wimps, anyway.
[Laughs] Vodka is for wimps?
Tennessee whiskey.
Put some hair on your chest.
It's hard to imagine
dinner with Felicity
and her mother
not going well.
Donna's not the problem.
I am. Felicity
says that she's
lost herself
in our relationship,
which means that she
doesn't know who she is,
and that if we
hadn't have left
star city when we did,
she would have been
around to help ray.
Metahumans, magic,
resurrections...
I thought I'd seen it all,
but Oliver queen jealous?
I'm not jealous.
I just got to know
if Ivy town
was as good
as it gets for us,
because we've come back here.
Everything has
just gotten super
complicated,
and it just makes me wonder,
why did she choose me?
Oliver, I've heard you say
a lot of crazy things
over the years,
but that has to be the prize.
You know what I mean.
It takes me ten minutes
to log into this thing;
Felicity does it in two seconds,
and ray probably invented it.
Yeah, you're probably right.
Except, Felicity
didn't choose ray.
She chose you.
Sure, she has
a lot in common with ray,
but sometimes what looks
good on paper isn't
what works in real life.
What if something
happens to him?
We don't get him back?
Felicity smoak
is one of the smartest,
most bad ass women
on the planet.
She comes through this,
she'll get ray back.
You seem pretty sure.
I married a woman
just like that.
Twice, Oliver, twice.
Yes, you did.
Look, man, relationships
have their ups and downs.
Sometimes you just have
to give it some time,
a little bit of space.
[Cell phone vibrates]
It's Lance.
Meeting with darhk in 20.
You good?
Better.
Thank you.
What the hell?!
Appreciate you meeting me.
I know you're a busy man.
I am.
But I may have
found a way
to make this city
useful for once.
I don't understand.
Oh, you will.
Everyone in this city will.
Well, maybe I could
find out sooner than others.
My daughter, Sara,
she's, uh, she's back,
but, you know, not all the way.
Something about her
is still a little off.
I assure you,
the relevance
escapes me.
Well, I was thinking,
maybe if I could help you
a little more, than maybe
you could help me.
You know your way around
this magic mumbo jumbo.
Mumbo jumbo?
I'll consider it, captain,
but this will be
the last time
you summon me.
John, he just left.
He's heading south
down Victoria street.
[Knocks]
Yeah?
I brought you some hot milk.
I'm not ten, mom.
I'll bring it back downstairs.
No, wait, wait, wait.
Since you went
to all the trouble.
Do you remember
when you were a little girl
and I told you you couldn't
go to space camp?
You locked yourself
in your room for two days.
Well, to be fair,
it was space camp.
But I told you,
I couldn't bear the thought
of sending you away
for eight weeks.
The truth was, hon, I...
I couldn't afford it.
Then why didn't you
just tell me that?
Because, I was embarrassed,
you know, that I had no money;
that I had no idea
where your father was,
and even if I did,
he never paid a dime
in child support, anyway.
I'm sorry.
I had no idea.
I put everything
into your father.
My love, my trust, my twenties.
My point is, you...
Are not me.
You are the ceo
of a bajillion dollar company.
And Oliver, he's not
like your father, hon.
He loves you.
No one has ever looked at me
the way he looks at you.
He's wonderful.
In a million different ways.
But that's the problem.
It's too easy
to lose myself in him.
Baby.
That's how it's supposed to feel
when you love someone.
Believe it or not,
he's lost himself in you.
And you'll find yourself
in each other.
Just don't get in your own way.
And don't ruin something
that most people never get.
'Cause if you do, trust me,
you'll never find another
guy that hot again, who cooks.
[Both laugh]
[Cell phone vibrates]
Thanks.
He is definitely hiding
something in there.
Latin building.
Before the city went to crap,
it was touted as
the most secure building
on the west coast.
Every access point
is protected
by a retinal scanner,
and a voice print.
There is no way
we're getting
in there.
Well, not from
the outside, at least.
How's Curtis doing
on the resizing device?
He said he could have
something functional
in an hour.
I don't think we have
that kind of time.
He's going to have
to assemble it
in the field.
Wait, with us?
Are we sure we want
to have your assistant
in on this?
It's my employee, actually.
And I'm not sure our company
health plan covers
supernatural dismemberment.
We need him. And if
Curtis can re-size
ray on the inside,
then we have another hand
getting us all outside.
Then how about one more?
I don't think
that's a good idea.
Laurel, I don't
know what's
going on with me,
but I need
to know that
I can control this.
Suit up.
Hmm.
These are very nice.
Oops.
Leave us.
Package is delivered.
Ladies?
Ready.
Felicity?
Or as ready as I'll ever be.
When I told hr I wanted
a little bit more
excitement from my job,
this really isn't
what I had in mind.
You were the one who said
you wanted to help ray
and that you were
an accomplished base jumper.
Oh, god, I really do
have too many hobbies.
We're all right,
spartan, let's do this.
Spartan?
We have a guest tonight.
[Chuckles] All right,
disengaging security systems...
Now.
[Shrieking]
Felicity: Oh!
You two ok?
Uh-huh.
We're not dead.
Good.
Let's go.
[Gun clicking]
You mind if I take a little
peeksie? I mean,
I have my suspicions,
of course.
But I just want to see
if I'm right, as usual.
Didn't you learn
anything from
our last go-round?
I guess not.
[Grunting and groaning]
[All grunting]
Ray!
Hey.
How do you open this?
My best guess
is it needs
an asymmetric cipher.
You can open it
with five years and an
NSA-grade computer.
What if we enlarged him now,
and then use his size
to break the cube?
The quantum field
won't be able to
penetrate this polymer.
[Groaning]
You know, it is a shame
that you won't live
to see the new life
that I breathe
into the city.
The new life that I breathe
into this world.
You won't get the chance.
They put mini-cams
in here with me,
and those cameras...
Need to draw power
from somewhere.
Ray, you are a genius.
Well, I don't
know about that,
but I have
siphoned off enough
juice to power up
my exo-suit.
[Powering up]
Dr. Palmer's
doo-hickey's ready.
If you don't mind
my use of
a technical term.
Do it!
[Exhales]
I'm not dead.
[All grunting]
We got ray, let's go.
Copy that.
Don't move!
Sara!
No!
[Neck snaps]
Come on.
We have to go!
Come on!
[Gun cocks]
[Arrow releases]
We have to move.
Good to see you, ray.
Nice suit.
The worst part
wasn't being small...
it was that everything
else was so big.
The explosion at Palmer tech
tossed me
into an abandoned
construction site.
The cockroaches
were the size
of golden retrievers.
I'm not exaggerating.
Uh, I think we don't
need to know that, really.
Ah, the entomologist in me
was actually really fascinated.
I mean, you can't
appreciate the size
of the mandibles until the...
mmm, mmm, no, I've heard enough.
I got a thing
against cockroaches,
and snakes and spiders,
but especially cockroaches.
Sorry, ray, not everyone shares
your enthusiasm for bugs.
But it is good to see
the experience
didn't change you.
Indeed. I got
your medical tests back,
and aside from a very
noticeable iron deficiency,
all your results are positive.
There don't seem to be
any side effects
from the, um,
micro sizing.
Relieved to hear it.
So are we.
So, this guy who wanted
to make me his lab rat?
Damian darhk.
He's the leader
of an organization
we believe to be known as hive.
Oh, like "spectre?"
That's so cool!
And terrible.
Be assured, Palmer,
that if they wanted your tech,
it wasn't for any good reason.
One other thing...
they overheard
my message to you.
I'm a possible target.
I figured.
I wouldn't be doing this
if I couldn't handle
being threatened
by a super villain
every now and then.
Come on. I'll take you home.
I can catch you up
on all the latest
at your company.
Uh, actually,
until I decide to come
back from the dead,
it's your company.
[Both grunting and groaning]
[Neck snaps]
What in the hell?!
You better have a story
to go along with that body.
[Sighs]
Look, thea told me
that this was a side
effect of the pit.
And I thought that
I could fight it.
I just...
I couldn't stop myself.
And the worst part of it was,
I felt better.
Look, Sara, controlling this,
it's not going to come easy, ok?
It's going
to take you some time.
And how many bodies?
Look, I respect the way that
you could deal with this, thea,
but I need
to handle this
in a different way.
Different how?
Laurel, I owe you everything.
You gave me
the greatest gift
that anyone ever could.
You gave me a second chance,
and the ability to start over.
I think it's time
that I really do that.
But Sara...
we just got you back.
Sara, you don't have to leave.
I know it doesn't
seem possible right now,
but you can have a normal life.
It's been a long time since
my normal has ever been normal.
Look, I'll go visit
mom in central city,
and then, somewhere...
Maybe a few somewheres,
just until I figure things out.
If you're sure that
that's what you want to do.
It's your life.
And you have to do
what makes you happy.
I'm just really
going to miss you.
I love you, sis.
Always and forever.
I love you, too.
Hey.
Hi.
How'd it go with ray?
Fine. Until I told him
I sold his condo.
[Chuckles]
I wanted...
before we...
oh. Hmm.
You go first.
No.
You.
I think we should...
Clear the air.
Um...
I wanted to thank you.
For helping save
ray, and for being
so understanding
in the midst of my mini...
gargantuan freak out.
Well, I'm sorry
that I'm not
the best listener.
But all of this is just, it...
it's kind of new to me.
And to me.
I didn't exactly grow up
with the best
example of a normal,
healthy relationship.
Line forms behind me.
It's kind of amazing
that we've made it this far.
We're going to be fine.
How can you be so sure?
'Cause we
found ourselves
in each other.
Donna: Feeling lonely?
You don't even know
the half of it.
I might.
I, um,
I came to town
to visit my daughter,
but she kicked me out
of her apartment
to finish a fight
with the man I hope
will become my future
son in law.
[Laughs]
Ok, it's your turn.
Well, one
of my daughters
is leaving town
after being
back a whole
five minutes.
Sounds like a reason to drink.
Oh, I always got a reason.
But this is club soda.
Quentin.
Donna.
[Chuckles]
[Telephones ringing,
indistinct chatter]
Hey, thea. When
your brother comes in,
could you have him sign
these for me, please?
Yeah.
You ok?
Just a little stressed out.
Maybe, um...
Maybe I need to get a drink.
It's a little early
for a cocktail, but...
Not now. Later?
With you, at Gerard's?
But I thought you...
I just want to have
a normal life.
Meet me there at 8:00?
Yeah, absolutely.
I'll leave these here.
[Exhales]
[Door opens, closes]
Dr. Palmer's
molecular's realignment
was premised on a power draw
from our system,
which resulted...
just because
I understand science
doesn't mean
I'm not bored by it.
Bottom line it for me.
We were able to recover
some residue
from Dr. Palmer's
dwarf star alloy,
and use it to fashion into
a power source.
Good.
Test it out.
On this.
Greg, move your head.