Previously on "Arrow"...
Mr. Ramirez suffered
a traumatic hemothorax.
I'm recommending
he be transferred to a facility
that can provide
the care he needs.
- Where's my dad?
- Have a seat.
He's gonna be ok,
but I need to tell you
about it.
- Unh!
- Want to keep going,
or are you
gonna testify?
We're leaving.
I've seen
what having Felicity
in my life
has done for me.
You deserve that
same kind of happiness.
I've located the heir
of Ra's al Ghul.
So where are we going?
Wherever you want.
It's up to me?
I'm the
well-traveled man.
I've been every place
in the world there is.
But you want to get
out of here
because if the police
knew you were alive,
they'd come after you.
The Arrow, too.
Yes.
If someone knew
where I was,
it would be unfortunate
for both of us.
So why did you reach
out to me?
I don't want to hurt
or get hurt. Never again.
I can teach you to be strong
in heart and body.
I can teach you
to protect yourself
so no one will ever
hurt you again.
That's what every father
wants for his daughter.
Malcolm Merlyn's legacy
lives on.
This is a new dawn.
Al Sa-Her was going to
bestow on us a new golden age
and lead us
into the realm of Thanatos,
yet for what greatness
Merlyn possessed in his soul
he lost in his heart.
He swore that our great journey
would be nothing
without his blood legacy
at our side,
and thus before
he gave up his life,
he made sure this journey
could not commence
until his beloved
was ready.
Step forward.
I have to say
the new uniforms
do not impress me.
We have cleansed ourselves
of your father's sins
for our rebirth,
which couldn't be further
from your fate,
daughter of the Demon.
I would so relish slitting
your throat, Athena.
One thing we have
in common.
Except I've grown a taste
for the contemporary...
such as plastic explosives.
♪ Arrow 6x16 ♪
The Thanatos Guild
Original Air Date on March 29, 2018
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
♪ I still want you... ♪
Oh, my gosh. You'd be
in so much trouble
if your dad saw
you doing that.
You're lucky you have such a cool
aunt, you know,
who approves
of bad behavior.
- I'm gonna miss you.
- And I'm gonna miss you, too.
Just promise me that
you're gonna watch over your dad, ok?
But he's the Green Arrow.
You know, before he was
the Green Arrow,
he actually used to be
really afraid of the dark,
and he needed
a nightlight in his bedroom
till he was, like,
what, six--16?
It was not a nightli--
I was--
it was not a nightlight.
I couldn't sleep
with it being pitch black.
By the way, I did see that.
Go get a fork
and a--and a plate
and get yourself
a reasonable slice
of cake.
Yes.
Thank you
for doing this.
It's actually
pretty cool.
Why do you sound
surprised?
Yeah. I--I don't know.
I just thought that
maybe you would--
you'd be a little more
anti me going.
I'm the one who encouraged
you to go follow your heart.
I know, I know.
It's just that now that it's all real,
I just--I...
I thought that maybe
you would be, like, a tad less supportive.
I am completely supportive
of anything and everything
that makes you happy.
Speaking of which,
I did tell Roy
that the two times
that I shot him with--with arrows
would be nothing compared
to what would happen to him
if you end up unhappy.
- Ah. Yeah.
- Do you understand...?
I spy an overbearing
big brother.
Yeah. No, no.
He's never been like that.
Never. Never.
I know we've said it
a million times,
but we're gonna
miss you.
We're really
going to miss you.
Well, you guys have
to come visit us
once we find out
where we're gonna land.
Where do we think
that's gonna be?
Well, we don't
really know exactly,
but that--that's kind
of the best part.
I mean, we're gonna figure it out
as we go along.
Oh. That's so spontaneous
and romantic.
As long as we're together,
that's really all that matters, right?
- Heh.
- Heh heh.
So how's your
new roommate?
She's just as messy
as my Laurel,
but, uh, surprisingly,
she's a better cook.
- You trust her, Lance.
- I'm not stupid, you know.
I--I know who she is.
I know what she's done,
but, you know, she says she's--
she's trying to get better,
and, you know,
that Intel she gave you last week
on, uh, Diaz,
that panned out.
Yeah. He still got away.
Don't they always,
though?
I see a--
ahem--work conversation,
so where are we
with the SCPD?
Well, uh, Dinah and Curtis,
they're growing a list
of possible cops
on the take,
but that could end up being
the least of our worries.
- How so?
- The D.A.'s office's refusal
to drop your case
without Roy's testimony,
that doesn't sit
right with me.
And who's to say that
the SCPD's the only part
of the city's power structure
that Diaz has got
his fingers in.
Yeah. Oliver, you let me
worry about Diaz.
You spend a little more time
with your sister
before she gets
out of here.
And you think this guy's
gonna stop worrying
about things
all of a sudden?
Well, ever since he trusted
me to take over.
If that's still
on the table.
I'm gonna go grab
some cake.
You brought this
up last week.
I don't know, man.
I thought we were clear.
You wanted out,
I wanted in.
- Has something changed?
- Yeah.
Yeah. It's--it's just
you and me,
and we don't know what Diaz has,
what he doesn't,
and bottom line, I--I don't think that
it should be just you.
This is definitely
one of the jerks
who beat Roy
to a pulp last week.
I wonder what food
they're serving
at Thea and Roy's
good-bye party.
Pizza, apps--
heh--maybe, like,
some mini-desserts.
That's this new thing. Like, you go to a party,
and then they serve you
these desserts, like mini doughnuts, and you
just dip them in the sauce.
I mean, that would be reason
enough to crash the party.
Not that I'm saying I want to
crash the party. I'm not expecting to be invited,
but, you know, Felicity
is my business partner...
- So I just--
- Curtis, focus.
We need to find out
how many of these cops are dirty.
Well, officer Hester
makes 10.
Yeah, and counting.
You know, the more
cops who are dirty,
the harder it is to
believe Captain Hill didn't know.
Who's next?
- Nick Anastas.
- Hoo.
More like hotnastas. Wow!
Well, just because you
have the hots for him
doesn't mean he's not
on Diaz's payroll.
All--all his stats
check out.
He hasn't had any
influxes of cash into his account,
no pressure points
for blackmail.
Look. I'm just saying
you never mentioned to me
that you work with such
a hot police officer,
not even once.
I guess I never
noticed.
Yeah, just like you don't
notice beautiful sunsets and rainbows.
Look. You just don't
see beauty as--hey, Z.!
How was school?
- Good. Hi, Dinah.
- What's up, Zoe?
Feeling like some
Mac and cheese tonight?
- Again?
- Can you get sick
of Mac and cheese?
- Definitely getting there.
- Oh, come on.
Going to my room
to do homework.
Heh heh.
You two seem to be
getting along well.
Yeah. You know, it's nice having
a little munchkin around.
Well, I'm sure Rene
appreciates somebody he trusts
taking care of her.
Yeah. You know, he
should be starting rehab soon.
Hopefully, he'll be back
to normal ASAP.
I really, really
miss that guy.
Me, too.
Hey. It's your boyfriend...
Anastas.
Homicide. Got to go.
You keep digging.
I got to find out who
at work I can trust.
He's not my boyfriend yet.
I'm on it.
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
I can't believe we're
actually doing it.
Yeah. I can't
believe it either.
Happily ever after.
Yeah. Ever after.
Ok. That wasn't
so convincing.
Look, Thea.
I--I'm thrilled.
I just--I don't
want to jinx it.
Ok, and since when do you
believe in superstitions?
Well, ever since
I met your brother,
there's not a lot
I don't believe in.
♪ with an open mind... ♪
Ok. Now I may
believe it, too.
Uh-huh. Are you ok?
Oh, yeah, I'm fine.
♪ Could be south L.A... ♪
Please tell me you've
packed some weapons somewhere.
Ohh!
Follow me. Hurry!
Nyssa, what--
what is going on?
- We need to move.
- What, are there more coming?
Many more. These
are the scouts.
They look
like League of Assassins.
No. The League of Assassins
was disbanded.
This can't be them.
Nothing stays dead
forever.
Your father made
sure of that.
Ok. Well,
I--I don't care, ok?
I'm--I'm sorry.
This is not me anymore.
I have nothing
to do with this.
Like me, you are
an heiress to the Demon.
That is something
you can never truly run from.
Hey. What happened?
Thea, are you hurt?
No. I'm--I'm fine.
I'm ok.
I'm doing pretty fine myself.
Thanks for asking.
They weren't
even at city limits, and they got attacked.
That's because she
jinxed it.
Superstition
played no part.
I hear you've taken
my husband as your own.
Yeah. Well, we can talk
about that later.
In the League, such talk
would take the form
of mortal combat.
What the hell
is going on?
Apparently,
my dear old dad decided
to recruit some loyalists
before...
Nyssa disbanded
the League.
For what?
To start his own,
the Thanatos Guild.
Began hearing whispers
about them shortly
after we all returned
from Lian Yu.
He couldn't have
led for long considering
he didn't leave
the island.
Moses never entered
the holy land,
and yet his legacy endured.
His second in command,
Athena, took charge,
a contemporary
of mine and a rival.
Her involvement alone suggests
a very dark purpose at work here.
Why would this
guild attack Thea?
Before Merlyn
gave up his life,
he discovered
a map that leads
to something
ancient, powerful.
I do not know what it is,
but I do know that he yearned
for Thea to be at his side
when he unearthed it.
It's really funny
he never mentioned this.
Because he knew you
were not ready.
Athena believes Thea to either be
in possession of the map
or at the very least have knowledge
of its whereabouts.
Well, you have fun
on your treasure hunt, ok?
I told you.
You cannot run from this.
Watch me, ok?
I--Roy and I are getting
out of here and back
to our lives.
I need your help
obtaining the map.
You cannot deny
your father's legacy
any more than I can
deny mine.
They will find you.
What do you want
from me?
Merlyn had an associate
in Star City.
If he shared the map's
location with anyone,
it would have been
with her.
You haven't
spoken to her?
She...Does not
care for me.
Ohh!
Ahem.
But she would not
deny Merlyn's daughter.
Ok. Fine. I will go
with you to talk to her.
We--we will help you find your map,
and then that's it.
I'm done,
for real this time.
It's a drug deal
gone bad.
Very bad. Man was shot
over a dozen times.
Maybe he pissed off
the competition.
I'll take it from here,
Lieutenant Drake.
Captain, this is
a drug-related homicide.
Isn't it a little below
your pay grade?
It's part of a larger,
uh, sting operation.
I wasn't aware
of a larger sting--
You weren't aware because
it's above your pay grade, Lieutenant.
Oh. We will head back
to the station, then.
Hey. You can leave
the evidence with me.
Of course.
Now I see why you didn't want
the boys to come.
That is Tigressa.
Looks like the only thing
she knows how to kill is vodka.
She has over 200
confirmed kills,
one of them being her own brother
because he matched her quote.
Al ghul, I should
take your hand
for what you did
to Al Sa-Her.
I never understood your affection
for Merlyn, Tigressa,
but I always
respected it.
- This is his--
- Spawn.
You think I wouldn't
recognize Malcolm's own blood?
Your father had
much faith in you.
Yeah. Well, with that
new League he created running around,
I can't say
the same for him.
So you've met
Athena.
She's not the leader
your father desired. You are.
Yeah. Well, I'm sure death
has cured him of his disappointment.
Look. The only reason
why we're here is because Athena thinks
I can open some map
for her.
With good reason.
Your father made sure
you were the only one
that could actually
unlock its secrets.
Of course he did.
And that is why
Athena needs you.
Your father secreted
the map...Here.
And why didn't you
just take it?
Heh. I rejected
the path
of the League of Assassins
a long time ago.
One day, you're gonna have to tell me
how you did that.
- Thank you for this.
- Well, when you find it,
you may not be
so grateful.
I was being polite.
We should contact
your brother.
There's safety
in numbers.
Overwatch, are you sure
we're alone here?
Yes. It is just the five of you.
No other souls
for two blocks.
Copy.
Be cautious.
Merlyn would have laid traps
to protect this place.
Yeah. What kind of traps
are we talking here?
We talking "Raiders"
or "Temple of Doom" kind of traps?
- You ok?
- Yeah. I will be
once this is all
over with.
Yeah, me, too.
Get down!
- A trap. Excellent.
- Excellent?
We must be close.
Thermal imaging
is showing
that what we're looking at
is what we've got.
No hallways, no doors.
Malcolm had a secret chamber
in his office.
Maybe he has something here.
Clever.
Iodine dixonium,
a component
magnetically attracted
to the same type of steel
my father used
to encase relics.
Ok. That's not
a map.
The map is inside.
It's an ancient League cipher.
- Does it need a code?
- Try my birthday.
There are 18 digits
across 3 alphabets.
Ok. So it's not
my birthday.
Guys, about you being
the only souls for two blocks,
funny thing
about those ninjas.
I want
Al Sa-Her's daughter
and the map.
I'm always merciful
when I get what I want.
I know you better
than that.
Stand down.
Not gonna ask twice.
Come with us, and we
will let your friends continue
to draw breath.
Stay where you are,
and blood will be shed.
I'll go with
shedding blood,
except
it will be yours.
Get that
someplace safe. Go.
Hey. The exit is kind of
blocked right now.
We can help with that.
You've had the same footwork
since you were 8 years old.
Thea!
Kevlar held...
Barely. Let's go.
Make your father proud.
Come with us.
Felicity, I know you
were wondering.
It's from "Raiders."
Kiss the floor.
I've got
Thea and the map.
Let's move!
Unh!
Hold on. Here.
Let me help you.
Ok. Ow. God, that bitch
has a really powerful kick.
I think she might have
broken one of my ribs.
I assure you that will be
the last time
you have to face her.
Yeah. You'll get
no complaints from me.
This Athena doesn't
seem like a type
who will give up easily.
I intend to take
the choice out of her hands
by taking Merlyn's map
far from here.
I know the toll a father
can have on a child
even long after he's gone.
This is my burden,
not yours.
You didn't tell me
that this was the box
from "Hellraiser."
Take care of each other.
Wow. That was a lot
easier than I thought it would be.
Ok. Wait. No.
How are you
gonna open it?
I'll find someone who can
unlock the cipher.
My people invented
mathematics after all.
Yeah. No, no, no.
Not this type of mathematics.
Wait. Look. You can't--
ugh--you can't go out there by yourself,
not with Athena's assassins
looking for you.
She said that's what she wanted
to do, Thea.
Yeah. No.
It's not what I want.
- Speedy?
- You made it clear
once I acquired the map
you'd have no interest
in your father or the League.
And you made it clear
that this map, it leads
to what, something
ancient and powerful.
Ok. You cannot--
you cannot take this on by yourself.
Plus we have the world's
greatest mathematician right there
and the protection
that you are gonna need
to keep that thing safe
while you try to open it.
I appreciate the gesture.
- Can you do it?
- Well, in my experience,
anything locked
can be hacked.
Usually by me.
Thea, are you
sure about this?
Nyssa's right.
You did say that you want
nothing to do
with Malcolm's legacy.
I know, ok? Look.
I can't believe that
I am even saying this,
but...After seeing
those assassins, I--
this all just became
too real.
But Nyssa gave
you an out.
I don't know why
you don't take it.
I don't know how to
explain it to you right now, ok?
I just--I--I need
you to trust me.
All right.
You ready?
To go to prison
for stealing evidence?
No, not really.
I'm doing the stealing.
You're doing the hacking.
Look. Something tells me
the police don't make that distinction.
This could be the last time I'm here
not as a suspect.
How long is this
gonna take?
My worry is 25 to life.
Come on.
Keep watch.
I thought you said
no one else was gonna be here.
We're here,
aren't we?
Oh. This might
take a while.
Crap.
Come on.
This is
police access only.
What are you
doing here?
Nick Anastas. Hey.
It has been a while.
Do I know you?
Yes. Of course.
Curtis Holt.
We met through Dinah Drake.
She's my friend
and your sergeant
or lieutenant,
or was it just Detective?
Uh, either way,
I'm meeting her here for, uh, dinner,
but I kind of got--heh--
lost in this new building.
I mean, I really haven't
seen this place
since--since it was
blown up.
Well, I could give you
a tour if you want
while you're waiting
for Lieutenant Drake.
She usually doesn't
show up for her shift for another hour.
Totally Dinah.
She's, like,
a major slacker. Ha ha.
- Come on.
- Yeah.
Gotcha.
- Nyssa.
- Husband.
Ha. You got to
stop doing that.
I--I do have
a wife now, and, um...
She doesn't
like it.
But that's the fun of it.
Thea might want you
to stay...
Doesn't mean
you have to.
Her point about
Felicity's utility was well taken.
So was her point about wanting nothing
to do with Malcolm.
It is her life, and she must find
her own truth.
I think her truth is
a new life
that she's earned.
She's earned your support
for her actions,
whatever those
may be.
I can understand why
she would be conflicted with Malcolm.
He was her father.
I am not conflicted.
He was evil,
and Thea should not
be charged with righting his wrongs.
My father was
also evil,
and I've dedicated the rest of my life
to righting his wrongs.
From what I understand,
you've done the same.
But my father
asked me to.
With his dying wish,
he asked me to.
Back on Lian Yu, Merlyn gave up
his life for Thea
just as your father
did for you.
I believe Thea owes
him the same debt.
Well, it is convenient
for you to believe that
because Thea gets you
closer to what you want,
so do not pretend
that you are selflessly supporting her
and never, ever
lecture me
on what I owe my sister.
If you think
I would use--
Nailed it!
I nailed it!
I got it! Whoo!
- You've unlocked the map?
- No.
Ok. So what do you mean
by "nailed it"?
Well, I figured out
how to unlock the "Hellraiser" cube.
I just thought you
should do the honors.
Oh.
You've heard of
the Fibonacci sequence, right?
- Let's assume not.
- The Fibonacci sequence is
a mathematical pattern
dating back
to Pingala's formula
in 450 B.C.
- Wow.
- Yeah.
When you said ancient,
you were not kidding.
- I never kid.
- Except where my marriage
is concerned apparently.
The Fibonacci sequence,
every number is the sum
of the two previous numbers,
so finding the two
starting ones,
that's the tricky part.
What are
the starting numbers?
10 and 13.
Is she right?
1013 was the year that
the League was founded.
And Malcolm's birthday.
Ok. Sit.
Try 10....13....
23...36...59.
95.
I was always good at math.
No. That's--
that's right.
Yeah.
What does it say?
- Nothing.
- Noth--
Why are you
burning it?
She's heating it.
The League writes
in hidden text
that can only be revealed
through flame.
- You don't remember?
- I don't want to.
I don't know what's
going on with him,
but just keep
working on it.
Why isn't
the flame working?
There's two
possibilities for that.
Either Malcolm was using
a different type
of invisible ink...
Or?
Or there's nothing
on this,
and we are
wasting our time.
What's this?
I thought since old school
wasn't working,
I'd try some new school.
This scanner can make
a 3-d voxel-based re-creation.
I didn't start using
a computer until I was 25.
Heh. That explains
a lot.
If I can duplicate
the map digitally,
there might be some hidden markers
on there that we can trace.
- Sounds complicated.
- It is. Very.
So it would be
really great
to not be distracted,
you know?
Very true. I'll stay here
to make sure
you remain uninterrupted...
Sister wife.
Ok.
Ok. So somebody's grumpy.
I'm sorry. I'm--I'm
trying to be supportive.
But?
But--but I don't
understand why you think
that this is
your responsibility.
He died for me, ok,
and I don't know
what it is,
but ever since I found out
about this,
I just--i f...
I feel like I can't
run away from it yet.
Well, you see, that's
where we're different.
You see this as us
running away from something,
but I see this as us running
towards something,
something way better.
You know, I just--
I don't know. I just feel like
recently you've just been finding
any excuse you can
for us to stay here.
Unlike all my boyfriends
in the past,
I--I do find it
kind of cute
when you're being
insecure.
I just don't want to
lose you again, Thea.
That map is not
my future.
You are.
I love a good old
murder board.
Yeah. Feeling very
Alan J. Pakula.
Sometimes, I forget
you're not Felicity.
Now, look, I know this
has probably already occurred to you,
but all Hill did was
take the evidence from your hands.
That's not
necessarily proof.
Not to mention her
name didn't pop up at all when--
She's dirty.
Are you asking me
or telling me?
You tell me. If these
drugs are the same kind Diaz pushes...
And Hill took it
off your hands,
that would be
pretty damning.
And the fact that so much
of the department
is so crooked would make
a lot more sense
if it was rotten
from the top down.
- So are they Diaz's drugs?
- I don't know yet.
Maybe we should
just try it.
Or we can read
the analysis.
- Oh.
- What?
It's Vertigo.
I heard of this back
in Central City.
It's a hallucinogenic, right?
Yeah, but, I mean,
the good thing is
that this isn't Diaz's
drug of choice.
- So Hill is clean.
- Looks like.
You actually look
disappointed.
Well, just because
it means we are back to square one.
Yeah.
Think you might take
that thing with you?
100% no.
You ok?
And why wouldn't I be?
I mean, Roy only thinks
I'm gonna leave him,
and a bunch of crazy
assassins my dead dad organized
are trying to kill me,
so my life is just...
Great.
You know, Thea,
you don't have to do this.
You don't have to leave
everything to Nyssa.
Myself and John
and Felicity,
we will stop Athena.
You can go. You can--
you can live
your happily ever after
with Roy.
Here I thought you
were supposed to go live yours.
Felicity--she told me you stopped
being the Green Arrow.
Yeah. That was the plan.
Life interfered.
- John got hurt.
- He did.
He's not hurt
anymore.
I worry that he would be
in over his head
going up
against Diaz alone.
I don't think anything's
over John's head.
You might be right.
I don't know. I--I--
I gave it up
because I wanted to be
a better father,
but William accepts
the idea that I'm the Green Arrow,
plus I don't want to
give it up.
I don't know why.
I do.
Because being
the Green Arrow's
what makes you
feel complete.
- Hmm.
- For some reason, when you--
you put that hood
on, it enables you to become
the best version
of yourself.
We're supposed to be
talking about you.
Maybe we are. Heh.
I don't know.
Maybe that's the reason why
I can't seem
to give
this life up.
I...I don't know.
Maybe I'm hoping
that somehow
I'll get
the same thing
and find the best
version of myself,
whoever she is.
Athena's group
of assassins--found them.
- Where are they?
- Star City gas plant.
They can
cut off the city's entire supply.
Or worse,
they could blow it up.
Why? It's not
their M.O.
It is if they're
using the plant
to leverage us
into giving up the map.
Clearly, Athena
doesn't know you very well.
Yeah? Well, too bad.
It's not Ollie's choice. It's mine.
You can't give
in to them.
I can't let them hold
the city hostage, ok?
This is still my home.
So what,
am I going alone?
Overwatch, do you
have eyes on the Guild?
No, not yet, but I'm reading
a frequency spike,
which means they just
activated a bomb.
Athena's way
of putting pressure on our negotiation.
Let's fan out
and find the bomb.
Multiple heat signatures, guys.
They got you surrounded.
Head on
a swivel.
Well, where are
the new assassins?
Everywhere.
You want your map
so bad?
Come out.
Let's talk.
Perhaps your father
taught you some sense after all,
but you are mistaken
if you think that
all we want is the map.
The map is meaningless
without spilling your blood.
You're really starting
to piss me off.
Your father spoke often
about you.
He was always ashamed
of your weakness.
Don't forget, guys.
We still have a bomb situation.
There's always
a bomb situation.
I can trace the frequency root
of the detonator.
It's 17 feet to your right.
- Lead the way.
- Up.
Merlyn said he tried
to teach you to be strong.
Clearly he failed.
I'm not my father.
This isn't working.
I know.
It's a collapsible circuit.
I can freeze it.
I've done it before.
No. No.
It's a Mercury switch.
That will definitely
set it off.
- What do I do?
- You can...Short-circuit it.
You know, I'm kind of
out of electricity arrows
right now at the moment,
Felicity.
Green Arrow.
On its way!
Got it.
Whoo! Nice work.
Thea!
You have lost.
It's as clear
as your imminent death.
You don't know what
you're talking about.
I know that you bleed.
I win.
You don't want to
do that.
Unh!
Are you all right?
Learned a few tricks
from Merlyn.
Wait. Where did
she go?
That woman is hard
to kill.
Were you really
going to burn it?
To ashes.
The other assassins either fled,
or they're wrapped up.
I really didn't
miss those guys.
Speedy, the map.
They were being literal.
They needed
your blood to spill.
That's definitely not
"X" marks the spot.
- Wait. Where does it lead?
- I believe I know where.
Nanolithography.
The map's printed with bacteria.
- Ugh. That's gross.
- And when exposed
to the enzymes in Thea's DNA,
it will reveal itself.
- Ancient league secret?
- No, no, no.
This is bleeding edge science.
This requires
an atomic force microscope.
- Leave it to Merlyn.
- Nyssa, you said you know
- what this map leads to.
- These are Ley lines.
Oh, great. Ley lines. Yeah. We had
some experience with those with Damien Darhk.
These are different.
I thought they only
intersected in one place on earth.
Doesn't look that way
from this.
Indeed.
These lines are global
and suggest
the existence
of 3 intersections
of the kind I thought
only existed
at Nanda Parbat.
Right, but what only exists
on Nanda Parbat really?
I mean, besides
really depressing decor.
I know now why Merlyn
called his new league the Thanatos guild.
Thanatos is the personification
of death in Greek mythology.
Exactly.
I believe these lines
suggest the existence
of 3 installments.
- But 3 what?
- Your father discovered
the existence
of 3 Lazarus pits.
Of course he did.
I--enh.
Thea, come on.
Hey, Roy.
Just let's give her some space.
Oh. Officer.
Nick, or should I just
call you officer
because we're at work?
Nick's fine.
You're becoming
a regular around here.
Yeah. Well, you know,
I was just stopping by.
To see Lieutenant Drake?
To ask you out
to dinner
or--or drinks
or, like, just coffee,
or we could just, like,
walk down the street and talk.
- I mean--
- Yes.
-Yes?
-I get off of work tonight
at 7:00.
Yeah.
So should we say
8:00?
8:00 is awesome. Heh.
8:00 is perfect. Heh.
Yeah, I mean, I'll
make reservations, and I'll text you.
Sounds like a plan.
See you tonight.
Yeah.
- Hey.
- What are you doing here?
Getting back
on the horse, D.,
back in the game,
back in the saddle.
I'm gonna get really
right into--
What's wrong?
I checked intake
and evidence lockup
for any
Vertigo-related cases.
- And?
- There aren't any.
Is that not
a good thing?
There aren't
any vertigo cases
because they've
all been kicked
and the evidence
released
by Captain Hill.
So she's dirty,
and she did it
for Diaz.
Ricardo Diaz is
pushing Vertigo.
Hey.
Hey. Look.
I'm--I'm sorry
for storming out
last night.
It--I just
really needed some space,
but it--it really had
nothing to do with you.
It's fine. I'm just
trying to figure out
if you packed that
bag to come with me or--or Nyssa.
I mean, it's pretty obvious
she wants to destroy
the new Lazarus pits
just like she did with the original one.
I mean, well,
can you blame her?
I mean, what would happen
if the League
or the Guild or just anyone
got their hands on it,
how dangerous
that would be?
So you--you are gonna
go with Nyssa?
Look. Last night,
Ollie and I were talking,
and we were talking
about how when, you know,
he becomes
the Green Arrow, he--
he feels complete,
and I was thinking
that maybe that's because when--
when he puts that hood on,
he gets to right
our father's wrongs,
and maybe this--
this could be my calling,
this--this could be
what...I've been looking for.
So you've made up
your mind?
You know what?
So have I.
- I'm gonna go with you.
- What?
No. No. You don't
need to do that.
Yes, I do.
I told you it doesn't
matter where we go
as long as we go
together.
God. How did I get
to be so lucky?
Hmm. Let me think.
I think it has
something to do
with a stolen purse.
Heh.
Just--just
be careful, all right?
And if you need anything--
and if you don't need anything,
just--just call me.
Keep her safe.
You know I will.
I missed you.
You drew her back
into this, Nyssa.
That carries with it
a certain responsibility.
Thea's your sister and the daughter
of Malcolm Merlyn.
She has less need
of protection than you think.
This is
a Horchis dagger.
In the League of Assassins,
it symbolizes
the cutting
of marital bonds.
I hereby annul
our marriage.
Heh heh.
Nyssa, as--as
wedding gifts go,
this, uh, isn't
half bad.
Be well, Oliver.
Well...This is it.
Thanks for clearing
a few things up for me.
Of course.
- One more piece of advice.
- Sure.
If you're gonna
wear the hood,
you shouldn't string
John along anymore.
Thought I was the one
who gave the wise sibling advice.
Nope. That has never
been the case.
I am gonna miss you
so much.
You'll be with me
the whole time.
Good-bye, Speedy.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man