[Oliver] My name is Oliver Queen.
After five years in hell,
I returned home with only one goal,
to save my city.
Today, I fight that war on two fronts.
By day, I lead Star City as its mayor.
But by night, I'm someone else.
I am something else.
I am the Green Arrow.
[Oliver] Previously onArrow...
The new police captain,
she's on my payroll,
along with a few other city officials.
See, guys like you never understand.
Why destroy a city,
when you could take it over?
Mr. Ramirez suffered
a traumatic hemothorax.
The injury caused his lung to recollapse.
Oliver Queen, you're under arrest.
On what charges?
Murder, assault, burglary, and kidnapping,
all stemming from your activity
as the Green Arrow.
I think I just found something.
There's a record on how Watson
found out you were Wild Dog.
There's an audio recording.
The FBI's provided definitive proof
that Oliver Queen is the Green Arrow.
I'm gonna release
the defendant on bail.
What's your name?
Laurel Lance.
-Ollie.
-Yeah.
Jean here has some good news for you.
I'm only used to good news
if it's accompanied by bad news.
[Jean] Well,
this news is unequivocal, Oliver.
I can get the case
against you dismissed.
Uh...
Have a seat. Tell me more.
I pored over the discovery documents
produced by the district attorney.
Apparently, the FBI leveraged
Rene Ramirez to testify against you
based on surveillance that was leaked
by a known criminal.
Cayden James.
[Jean] "Fruit of the poisonous tree."
It's a legal metaphor positing that
if the source of the evidence is tainted,
the evidence itself is tainted.
Mr. James' actions were not only illegal,
but his death makes it impossible
to corroborate the evidence
against Mr. Ramirez.
So, if there's no case against Rene,
there's no case against me.
We're going before Judge McGarvey
on my motion to dismiss this afternoon.
Jean, you sure?
You can just make this go away?
Ollie, she's positive.
Okay, I know you're not used
to getting good news,
but this is what it sounds like.
[door opens]
Mr. Mayor, we got an emergency at SCPD.
Like I said, it was accompanied
by some bad news.
Jean, this is wonderful.
I will see you at the courthouse
this afternoon.
Okay.
So?
Laurel just walked into
police headquarters.
-What, to surrender?
-[Quentin] Not exactly.
She told them she's Laurel Lance.
Our Laurel Lance.
Okay, why is she claiming
to be Laurel Lance?
Well, Dinah is out for blood,
and Laurel Lance, public figure,
is a much more difficult target
than Black Siren.
Except it's a lie.
It's all one big lie.
We need to get to her
before she gets to the press.
I woke up in a cell
and I managed to break down the door,
and I just... I ran.
They held you for two years?
I don't remember.
They kept me drugged.
[reporter 1] The Black Canary was
reported dead, killed in a prison riot.
[Laurel]Damien Darhk, he stabbed me.
And the next thing I knew, I was...
I was in that cell.
I don't know how,
but this is really, really bad.
Rather, we should have seen this coming.
Should've known that she'd eventually
try to pull something like this.
Why would Damien Darhk do this to you?
[reporter 2] Why would he fake your death?
I don't know why
he would wanna fake my death.
Maybe... Maybe to torture
the Green Arrow?
[reporter 3] So,
you know who the Green Arrow is?
Ollie! Ollie!
I never thought I'd see you again.
Daddy.
-Daddy.
-[reporter 1] Can you tell us any more
information on...
[Reporter 2] You notably
outed Miss. Lance
as the Black Canary at her funeral.
And now it seems a little suspicious
in light of the recent allegations
that you are the Green Arrow.
It doesn't and it's not.
I have made no secret of the fact
that when necessary,
I have been in contact
with Green Arrow and his team.
He told me about Laurel Lance.
I wasn't talking to myself.
[reporter 3] Is that true, Miss Lance?
[Reporter 4] Miss Lance, is Oliver Queen
the Green Arrow?
I really do think that Miss Lance
could use some time with her family
and some privacy.
Let's go.
[reporters clamoring]
[clicks]
-What do you think you're doing?
-[Laurel] What?
You said you wanted me
to be more like Laurel,
so I thought I'd give it a try.
Oh, I really wish I'd believe that.
Where's the money you stole from the city?
Yeah... About that, slight hiccup.
So, I went to where I stashed it,
and it's been cleaned out.
It's gone. Poof.
So, without the money you, what,
decided to become Laurel Lance,
'cause she's a public figure
and harder to kill?
You're really that afraid
of Dinah Drake, aren't you?
Not just afraid of Dinah.
Afraid of whoever manipulated Cayden James
into thinking I killed his son.
'Cause that's probably
who killed James, too.
Who did it? Anatoly?
Or Diaz?
[Thea] Or you?
I mean, she could've
just easily killed both of them.
I don't exactly have
an airtight alibi for Cayden.
I believe his son was killed
when I was incarcerated at A.R.G.U.S.
[Oliver] Who did it?
Anatoly or Diaz?
Talking out of school
will get me in trouble.
Look, whoever went after James
is clearly coming for you next.
So, why don't you cooperate with us?
Help us find the money,
and maybe we can just protect you.
Little trivia.
There's a Thea Queen on the Earth
that I come from, too.
Only she's not
as pathetically naive as you.
Look.
This is a lot simpler
than you're making it.
You're gonna protect me
and you're going to help protect me
by going along with the story
that I'm the real Laurel Lance.
Yeah?
Why would we do that?
I don't know.
Maybe because of all the reporters
that are just in the next room.
You know, it's only a matter of time
before they ask me
who the Green Arrow is again.
What would you like me to tell them?
We're done here.
Mr. Mayor, may I speak to you
for a minute?
Yes.
-What's all the fuss?
-Laurel Lance just turned up alive.
-Believe it or not, she's actually...
-I know who she is.
Sorry to pull you away,
but payday is Friday.
And my officers
aren't gonna get their checks.
Captain Hill, I'm still working
on recovering the money that was extorted.
And I have an idea to buy us time
that I wanted to run past you.
Let's hear it.
The department has
years of seized assets.
Sports cars, mansions,
even a stuffed polar bear,
if you can believe it.
-Mmm-hmm.
-At least two-thirds of the property
has cleared the court process for sale.
If we auction it off,
we can raise as much as $30 million.
Thirty?
Set that in motion.
Thank you.
-Hello.
-Don't talk to me.
Captain Hill,
can I talk to you for a minute?
-It's about Laurel Lance.
-That's a hell of a thing, isn't it?
She said they faked her death
and then she was
held captive for two years.
Yeah, sure is.
Uh, anyone catch that case yet?
You want it? It's yours.
But right now, she's going
to the hospital for a GSW.
I'm patient.
[knock at door]
-C-Dog.
-Hey, Zoe.
Great. Love that that name's
sticking around. That's amazing.
The babysitter had to go home
two hours ago.
Where's my dad?
Have a seat.
Something happened.
He's gonna be okay,
but I need to tell you about it.
[Jean] This is inappropriate.
My motion should be heard
in open court.
I requested to be heard in chambers.
Oh, to what, hide the embarrassment
of having your case dismissed?
Actually we're taking Mr. Ramirez
off our witness list.
Considering he was your sole witness
against Mr. Queen,
-I renew my motion to have...
-He's not our sole witness.
What? No, no, no, no.
Discovery on this case is closed.
[Armand] This is newly-discovered
information, Your Honor.
We'll make the witness' proffer
available to the defense,
in accordance with Brady v. Marilyn.
Who is the witness?
Someone with enemies
on both sides of the law.
That's why we're doing this in chambers
and why I granted
the district attorney's request
for a suppression order.
All right, I get it, it's sensitive.
What is the witness' name?
Roy Harper.
How did they even find Roy?
I mean, we didn't know where he was.
We didn't even know
what name he was working under.
I didn't think anybody did.
-Did you?
-No. No...
God, I couldn't even find him
for your guys' wedding reception.
[John] It doesn't matter
how they did it. They did.
Now we have to figure out what to do next.
He's definitely not
cooperating voluntarily.
Well, it's been two years.
I mean, there might be some
pressure points we don't know about,
some people he cares about, some...
-It's been a long time.
-[Oliver] Either way,
we need to know
what Roy is going to say in court,
which means we need to know
where he is right now.
[John] Oliver, he's a state witness.
I know our whole thing is extralegal,
but maybe we should let
your lawyer deal with this.
The DA's office does not have
the capabilities of finding Roy.
Which means,
this was either Diaz or Anatoly.
You think whoever's
pulling the strings on this
is still tugging them?
Well, if you're in the mood
for some witness tampering,
I think I have a line
on where the DA is holding Roy.
They rented out several rooms in
the top floor of a hotel downtown.
Hotel. Easily guarded position
with lots of civilians,
we break in, get spotted, Oliver,
we make their case for them.
Guys, if Ollie is right, and Roy
is in trouble with Diaz or Anatoly,
we need to be protecting him.
So we wait until dark to do recon.
And then find possible points of entry.
No exertion or sudden movements.
Don't wanna risk reopening the wound.
[Quentin clearing throat]
Hey, uh, could you...
Could you give us a minute please?
[sighs]
What, is Mom coming
to visit or something?
[sighing] Okay, firstly,
she's not your mom.
And second, no.
I called her right after your
little performance for the cameras
and told her to hold off a bit
while I checked you out.
That poor woman has been burned
enough by this sort of thing.
More of Laurel's stuff.
You know, I was just getting used
to the last outfit.
Well, Forensics has that one.
Anyway, you wanna pass
for the real Laurel,
you better get used to her style.
You call this "style"?
Look, are you here just to make sure
my health insurance is up to date,
or are you here to protect me from her?
Just get dressed.
Hey.
Laurel Lance, she died in this hospital.
I pronounced her. There was an autopsy.
Of course, I've seen my share of things
I once would've considered miraculous.
I mean, in a world where a man
can run faster than light,
I suppose anything's possible.
That's why I need to rule out the chance
that this person could be an impostor.
The DNA test will tell us that.
Excuse me.
-Hey.
Look, I know what you're
doing here, all right?
You're going after Laurel 'cause
of what happened to your friend,
and I get that, okay?
It's what I would do
if someone I loved was dead.
You mean it's just what you'd do
with a criminal, Quentin,
which, by the way, is what she is.
Yeah, but you and I both know that,
but, you know, she's turned herself
into a beloved public figure.
She's also said that she's got
no compunctions about outing Oliver.
I don't think she'll stop with him.
-So you're doing this for my sake?
-For all of our sakes.
I've been making progress with her, Dinah.
Okay? I'm not finished.
But if she lives as my Laurel...
She's not your Laurel.
Your Laurel wouldn't have murdered
Vince or anyone else.
She did.
And you are delusional
if you think you can change her.
No. I'm telling you,
I've been changing her, okay?
All I'm asking for you
is just a chance. Please?
What's taking her so long?
-Where'd she go?
-[nurse] The police officer took her.
Said something about a safe house.
No, no. I am the lead detective
on this case.
-You did this.
-What are you talking about?
I wanna know
where she is, too, you know.
[sighs]
Is my father not coming?
-Where are you taking me?
-To see Mr. Diaz.
[car starting]
[Green Arrow] I'm guessing Roy's
in the room with the police outside?
Yeah. Eating the wrong end
of a phone book.
[sighs] It's risky terrain.
You just told me he's getting beaten on.
You're still not sure we should do this?
Two-man team on the balcony.
[John] If we can get past them,
that's our best bet.
John, he's in there 'cause of me.
He's been on the run for three years.
Oliver, that's his choice.
I know that,
but did I learn anything from it?
Roy put on the hood.
He sacrificed himself for me.
And I asked you to do the same thing,
at the expense of your safety
and your family.
Difference was,
I wanted to put on the hood.
Oliver, listen, I've been good
for the past two months, good.
But instead of giving me back the hood,
you've had Cisco make me a new suit.
There it is. It's a 15-second opening.
That is our window.
[door opens]
We got it from here.
Head back to SCPD before you're missed.
[Anatoly] Laurel.
[speaking Russian]
Is it Laurel or "Laurel" these days?
So confusing, this doppelganger business.
But you seem to have figured it out.
Diaz killed Cayden.
He told me.
No honor among thieves.
Or crime lords, I guess.
Well...
Diaz manipulated the both of us,
lied to the both of us.
This whole time, he's had his own agenda.
That doesn't bother you?
I'm not sentimental.
I am Russian.
I'm in the city for two reasons only.
One is revenge against Oliver Queen,
and two is money.
I'm happy to work
with whoever can get me either.
You're in the city
because the Bratva cast you out.
Well, there's that, too.
There is a 15-second window
where neither roof guard
is watching the HVAC vent.
We can get in that way.
All right, well, did you see him,
is he okay?
-We can get him out.
-I know. And I'm coming with you.
I thought you didn't do this anymore.
Ollie, it's Roy.
Right, but, Thea, you shouldn't do this.
And I understand
it's hypocritical pointing out
that you have a personal involvement.
Doesn't make me wrong.
More importantly,
you have not been field-ready
since you got out of your coma.
I'll be fine. Okay?
And did you guys even measure the vents?
Because you should be asking
if I'm the right size to fit through them.
Don't think either of you two can.
Where are you guys keeping my suit?
You okay?
It's just like riding a bike.
It really isn't.
I can buy you a few extra seconds.
I'm ready.
All right.
What's that for?
There's not a home game tonight, is there?
[grunts]
[officer] You wanna keep going,
or are you gonna testify?
I'm not a lawyer,
but I'm pretty sure torturing your witness
isn't gonna be great for your case.
You don't think we know how to
put you in a world of hurt
without leaving a mark?
No.
[groaning]
Are you getting this?
I'm enhancing their badge numbers.
Just when you thought Oliver took down
all the crooked cops last year.
I'm going in.
[Felicity] I wouldn't.
They got six more guys in the hall.
Stand down.
I know it's hard, but you have to wait.
[Roy grunts]
[groaning, coughing]
I'm working up an appetite here.
Hey.
We're gonna get some Big Belly Burger.
You decide to play nice,
I might give you the fries.
Is that my hood?
It looks good on you.
I'm sorry if you're seeing someone.
I'm not. I didn't take your advice.
No kids, no wife,
and I really, really hate minivans.
How did they find you?
I was in St. Roch,
and the Star City cops, they tased me,
and they threw me in the back of a van.
They knew everything,
they knew about Oliver,
they knew about me faking my death,
they knew it all.
SCPD SWAT incoming.
Speedy, you wanna get out of there now.
Speedy, move.
Okay, we're leaving.
No, you're leaving.
I'm in no shape to be swinging
from the rooftops.
I'm not leaving without you.
-They're coming in hot.
-You gotta go right now.
Damn it, Speedy, get out of there!
I'm getting you out of here.
-No, you can't. You have to go.
-No.
I'm not leaving you.
[Green Arrow] Speedy, they're right
outside the door!
I'm not losing you again.
Just go sit.
Thea.
What the hell do you think you're doing?
I needed some air.
You're gonna need air.
-What the hell did you just do?
-I just saved your life.
There's too many of them in there.
They would have killed you both.
Look...
We will get Roy back.
I am promising you,
we will get him back.
They're really circling the wagons now.
They've upped security tenfold.
He was bleeding internally,
so if we don't get to him soon,
they're going to kill him.
They will not, because they need him
alive to testify against me.
Not "they." Diaz.
I pulled financials
on both the police officers
that were torturing Roy.
They both receive generous
dividend payments
from stocks of a Corto Maltese-based
shell corporation.
They financed the company
that was manufacturing
the drug I used to treat my injury.
Ricardo Diaz's company.
Both officers were on duty
when Cayden James was killed,
and all the officers
that were there tonight,
we have reason to believe
they're working with Diaz, too.
So Diaz has been playing us
since the beginning.
Or he's just been playing you.
She's upset. She's worried about Roy.
Yeah, so am I.
-I had to pull you out of there.
-No, you could've come in.
I come in there, and it's you and me
against a SWAT team, in a tight space,
nobody comes out of there.
Especially not Roy.
You know, there are times
when I feel like my life
completely fell apart when Roy left.
From my bloodlust,
to Malcolm, to the coma...
Knowing he was out there,
that he was okay,
it made my life just a little bit easier.
Ever since Mom died,
I haven't known much of anything
other than the fact
that I want to make sure he is safe.
And I will do whatever it takes
to make sure that happens.
We all will, Speedy.
[John] Felicity may have just
found something.
SCPD just requisitioned
a transport prisoner van.
They're moving Roy to a new safe house.
We just don't know when.
That's it.
That's when we get him.
There's something else.
[Dinah Drake] No, no, no, no, okay.
You know what, who can tell me
where Laurel Lance is?
Can you tell me that?
And when will he be available?
No, no, no, no.
No, thank you. I'll call back.
I swear, this isn't me, okay?
I need to speak with you.
You too.
Turn the cameras off.
[clicks]
Cayden James was murdered right there.
By Ricardo Diaz.
-Oh, my God.
-And it was covered up by the SCPD.
I thought Cayden James
was killed by another inmate
when he was transferred to Iron Heights.
Felicity found out what actually happened.
Never made it to Iron Heights.
The cops on duty are on Diaz's payroll.
They faked the transfer.
Doing that would take...
A systemic breach
of the police department.
Worse than last year's corruption.
I didn't think that was even possible.
Neither did I.
Dinah, I know that
you don't believe in me right now,
and I know the two of you
don't trust each other,
for good reason,
but the both of you believe in the badge.
I need you working together,
I need to know how deep this goes.
I need to know who in that room
we can trust.
Which means you gotta
put your vendetta on hold.
Okay.
[Quentin] We can work it out at my place.
The walls here have got ears.
And this is why I couldn't find Laurel.
'Cause those bent cops sprung her.
Or they took her someplace worse.
Diaz's feelings were so hurt
when you tried to run.
It's as if you don't
trust him or something.
I'm still trying to figure out why you do.
For me, it's more a matter
of money than trust.
Either way, Diaz better.
Why blow up city
when you can control it, yes?
[grunting]
You're as good as they said you were.
Do you know that fighting for trophies
is not the same as fighting for your life?
Break you of your bad habits.
Welcome to the team.
That's a lot of money
for a man with bad foot.
I didn't break it,
I just had to break him.
Building a family, Anatoly.
Family.
Isn't that what "Bratva" means?
-"Brotherhood"?
-Da.
See, family,
they rely on one another.
Family trust each other.
See, when a family does well,
each member prospers.
But if just one person
betrays their family...
Give us the room!
Move!
[speaking Russian]
The money that you stole from Cayden
was also my money.
I earned it, just like you.
Except I didn't take more than my share.
Well, you've got it all back, obviously.
So why am I here?
It's 'cause our business is not concluded.
You might have convinced Anatoly that
you're worth staying in bed with,
but I have a psycho vigilante
coming after me.
[Diaz] Dinah Drake.
Mmm?
I see it all.
I know it all. I control it all.
I've been working on this for months.
See, Cayden, he's just a small piece
of a much larger puzzle.
And so are you.
I just wanna
get the hell out of this city.
Where you wanna go?
Hmm?
-Do what?
-Live.
Without always having to look
over my shoulder.
I don't want you
to worry about Dinah Drake.
to worry about Oliver Queen
or any of those chumps
who can't see two inches past their face.
Anatoly said that you had a plan
to take control of the city.
Now, isn't that something...
Worth staying in bed for?
I don't know, Felicity.
Maybe it's a little soon, bringing up
taking back the mantle from Oliver,
but it's been two months.
A hell of a two months, though.
And Oliver's just not ready to step down,
not with everything that's going on.
It's too much.
It's crazy what's...
They're moving Roy in 10 minutes.
[tires screeching]
Don't move.
Roy, back away from the door.
It's a decoy.
They faked Cayden James' transfer,
they faked this one, too.
So where is Roy?
Mr. Harper. Good to meet you.
You said they were moving him.
Yeah, they must have put Roy
into a different vehicle
when they were in the underground
and I didn't have eyes on them.
Which means he could have been
picked up at any point last night.
How many cars left the hotel
in that time frame?
Nearly 300.
I'm tracking license-plate numbers,
but it's gonna take some time.
If it takes more than an hour,
I'm gonna start breaking fingers.
There's that Queen temper.
I'll contact Lyla, see if A.R.G.U.S.
can help with finding Roy.
How are you holding up?
-I've been better.
-Yeah, I know.
It's because you're blaming yourself
for Roy's situation
instead of accurately
blaming Ricardo Diaz.
Well, Roy wouldn't be in this situation
if he didn't fall on his sword
for me three years ago.
That was his choice, Oliver.
And I believed then
and I still believe it was the right one.
I'm worried that I didn't
rescue him from that hotel room
'cause I wouldn't have been able
to bear the responsibility
if things went bad.
You didn't go into that hotel room
because your gut told you
things would go bad.
And that gut's kept you alive
for 11 years
and it kept Roy alive last night.
Maybe. How do I know?
I could ask Cisco
to find a parallel universe
in which you did.
But in the meantime,
if you could just stop
finding ways to blame yourself,
that would be so great.
-Is that what I'm doing?
-That's what you're always doing.
Maybe you have a point.
Hmm?
Last night, John basically asked me
why I haven't given him the hood back.
Yeah, I know, he told me.
I told him you probably just thought
it wasn't the right time.
Am I on the money?
I don't know.
You have a strength
one doesn't see much.
You wanna join my team?
Sure.
Do you offer medical and dental?
You know, my police friends are
telling me you're not cooperating.
You're not playing ball.
You won't testify against Queen?
If you actually think
that I would do that,
then you're an idiot.
[chuckles] One of us is.
See, but I'm not the type of guy
that believes giving a beating
is the only way
to cause some pain.
How's Speedy?
She came out of retirement.
Why would she do that?
Why the hell would Queen
let his baby sister
dress up like Will Scarlet?
All right, I gotta ask.
That's a moot point.
You see, the real question is,
who do I gotta bring the pain to?
Do I gotta bring it to you?
Or her?
Shift sergeant was definitely
in on it. Look at this.
[sighs] Diaz has got his fingers in deep.
Listen.
Thanks for doing this, all right?
-Backing off Laurel.
-It's temporary.
Until we can get the department
back under control.
[knock at door]
Hi, Daddy.
-Hi.
-Speak of the devil.
-Can I talk to you?
-Yeah.
I've got a lot I'd like to say.
Can we not do the whole screaming thing,
because the only thing that's gonna happen
is my father's gonna have to
renovate his apartment.
Plus, I'm here about Ricardo Diaz.
I'd ask how you're doing, but...
Felicity and A.R.G.U.S.
are working on locating Roy.
You know, it's been a while
since I offered you
a little big-brother advice.
Do you mind?
This should be good.
When we find Roy... Not if, but when
we find Roy,
I think maybe you should go with him.
-Where?
-Wherever he's going.
I mean, Thea, I'd miss you like crazy,
but you said that you haven't
been the same without him.
So maybe you shouldn't be without him.
-You really think I should go?
-I don't want you to go, obviously.
But you've seen what... What having
Felicity in my life has done for me.
You deserve that same
kind of happiness, Speedy.
Wherever it is.
[John] Got news.
-Location on Roy?
-[John] Laurel.
She showed up at Lance's apartment
with intel on Ricardo Diaz.
He has some plan to take over the city,
whatever that means.
I don't exactly have details.
No, he just let you leave
after you stole all that money.
Let you come over here
and tell us all of this.
Well, I'm rather charming.
Don't you think?
So where's Roy?
They had him brought
to some rundown casino.
I heard some guys talking about it
on my way out.
-I can take you there.
-So Diaz can take these guys out?
Is that part of the plan?
Look, we really don't have a choice, okay?
We need to take this chance.
All right, why are you doing this?
Going against Diaz?
Because it occurred to me
that if I'm gonna be Laurel,
I should probably start acting like it.
[sighs]
Yeah, John. We have a location on Roy.
Let's get ready to move.
All right, fine.
-Just this once.
-No.
You don't trust me. I don't trust you.
So I'd rather be in the field shorthanded.
[Green Arrow] Only two guards.
Diaz clearly wasn't expecting us.
Black Siren didn't warn him.
-Let's go.
-Wait.
If we go in there without
knowing our primary objective,
no one is coming out.
Our primary objective is to get Roy.
What about Diaz? He's in there, too.
And we just found out that he's
the one that's behind everything bad
that's been happening in the city
for the past six months.
So let's get 'em both.
-Overwatch, you in yet?
-[Felicity] Uplinking now.
Huffing and puffing and blowing
all those firewalls down,
but before I finish,
if he's a smart guy,
and we know that he is,
this will definitely tip him off
that you're there.
-We need to know where Roy is.
-Copy that.
I pulled the blueprints of the casino
from the city.
I'll guide you through.
Head up the escalator.
Three vigilantes, including your
red girlfriend just showed up.
It's time for a change of scenery.
You know what to do.
Four hostiles with full autos
right in front of you.
-Which way?
-According to thermals,
Diaz has Roy
through the door on the north wall.
Unit 545 requesting backup. Shots fired.
Arrows.
Make that, "Arrows fired."
Get away from him!
On the ground. Now!
I love it when you visit me, Mr. Mayor.
I love it even more when you leave.
No kill shots. I need him alive.
Speedy! No!
[grunting]
Ahh!
We have a problem.
One of Diaz's cops
alerted the legitimate cavalry.
The SCPD is headed your way en masse.
So you're just a hired hand?
I used to be Pakhan.
You cost me that.
I've got him. Go help Speedy.
Ugh!
[groaning]
[sirens blaring]
You okay?
Don't move.
Not all those guys are on my payroll.
Yet.
But even the ones who aren't,
they find the anti-vigilante bill
very motivating.
Speedy.
Get in the van,
and drive Roy away.
-What about Diaz?
-I got Diaz.
No, you don't.
You know that, right?
If you stay here,
you're gonna get yourself a collar.
And it's not like you can
just take me away with you, right?
But you already knew that.
That's why you let your sister drive off.
You made your choice.
Freeze!
-How do you feel?
-[grunts]
Like I've been beaten within an inch
of my life with a telephone book.
[John] Two broken ribs and a bruised lung.
You have to take it easy
for a few days, Roy.
Well, that's the good part
about being a fugitive.
There's nowhere else I have to be.
How's Anatoly?
SCPD. I had to bail. What about Diaz?
Same.
How are Quentin and Dinah doing
with their investigation into the SCPD?
They're working on it.
I'm not a lawyer,
but what are the effects of us
having the government's star witness
in our protection instead of theirs?
[Oliver] Not as much as you would think.
They'll add witness tampering
and obstruction
to their very long list of charges.
Hmm. Cherry on top.
We did it all for Thea.
And for Roy.
I would have done it for any of you guys.
[clears throat]
[sighs] My father's asleep.
I came to see you.
Okay.
[Oliver sighs]
You didn't set us up.
Gee, Ollie, you sound surprised.
So I came by to say thank you.
And yet still unconvinced.
You're not Laurel.
Not our Laurel.
And saying that you are
to a bunch of press...
No. That does not make it so.
You're right. I'm not.
But I'm willing to try.
And I can't make any promises.
I am who I am,
but I'm willing to try if you're
willing to give me the space to.
Well, that sounds fair.
You're staying here?
Quentin, he...
My father offered me his couch.
It's pretty on point with the whole
"rescue Laurel Lance" story, so...
Yeah.
I'll be checking in.
Looking forward to it.
[phone vibrates]
Home sweet home.
Nice.
For the past three years, I've been
sleeping with the cockroaches.
I feel like
I should have been there with you.
Is that too presumptuous or confusing?
I know that last time we saw each other,
I said that we should probably see...
[beeps]
Master. I've located
the heir of Ra's al Ghul.