My name is Oliver Queen.
After five years
on a hellish island,
I have come home
with only one goal--
to save my city.
But to do so, I can't be
the killer I once was.
To honor my friend's memory,
I must be someone else.
I must be something else.
Previously on "Arrow"...
This is my daughter, Helena.
When her father
killed her fiancé,
she changed into something
dark and twisted.
My father doesn't deserve
a second chance--
a second life.
This is about
learning to control your strength.
Ollie, it's over!
We got to get off this ship!
Hugo mannheim.
Warrants out for racketeering,
extortion, murder--
the goombah trifecta.
But he never travels alone,
so watch your back,
watch your partner's back.
Let's go.
Thanks for helping me
keep watch over my dad tonight.
As long as Slade's out there,
neither of our families are safe.
This is the SCPD!
Put your weapons on the ground!
Move, move, move!
Aaah!
Freeze!
Go. Go!
Frank Bertinelli...
My daughter
sent you to kill me.
♪ Arrow 2x17 ♪
Birds of Prey
Original Air Date on March 26, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Hey.
Dad, are you all
right? Are you hurt?
Yeah, I'm fine,
sweetheart.
Listen, I know you don't
exactly believe
in reading perps
their Mirandas,
but you can't just toss a guy
out of a window.
He shot you.
And I'm still
here, ain't I?
Just next time, show
a little restraint.
That was me
showing restraint.
Detective.
We have another problem.
Yeah, I know.
With Frank Bertinelli in custody,
it's just a matter of time before
She-Ro is back in town.
Who is she?
Helena Bertinelli.
Daughter of mafia boss Frank Bertinelli.
Or as I like to call
her, Oliver's psycho ex-girlfriend
hell-bent on revenge
against her father.
Ex-girlfriend?
That's what you took
from that sentence?
Wait, why does
she want her father killed so badly?
He had her fiancé
murdered.
She wants payback.
Puts the many fights
I've had with
my father in perspective.
I've been
keeping tabs
on Helena over
the past year.
Last known sighting
was a month ago,
Palermo.
She's been busy.
If by "busy,"
you mean torturing
and killing mafiosos
that might know
where her father is.
Bertinelli's arrest
just hit the wires.
How long do you think we have
before Helena books a ticket back home?
Go ahead.
Slade, please--
Aah!
Why aren't we moving yet?
We managed to repair the hull.
But the engine is too damaged.
So fix it.
I can't.
I don't know how!
Then find
somebody who does.
Hi, my name's Laurel,
I'm an alcoholic.
Hi, Laurel.
And this is actually
my second meeting today.
It's just, uh...
It's just so hard,
because I don't know
what to do
with myself all day.
I'm a lawyer,
well, I...
was...a lawyer.
I loved it.
But I guess I loved
drinking more.
I know that I can make it down here
with all of you.
I just...I'm not
sure I can make it out there.
Anyway.
Thank you for
letting me share.
Thanks for coming.
Sorry about the way
things ended here.
No, don't be.
You did me
a favor, Adam.
It was the only way I was going
to hit bottom,
and...
And I did.
How about you do me
a favor now...
come back to work.
You want me back?
I'm looking for someone
to try this case that just came in,
and honestly, yours was
the first name that came to mind.
I'm still facing sanctions
from the bar.
Oh, I got a buddy
on the disciplinary committee.
I squared things for you.
An SCPD raid last night
brought in Frank Bertinelli.
He came back to Starling
to collect on some old debts.
Now, the DA's office
is clear to prosecute him;
for you to prosecute him.
I appreciate the offer, Adam,
but why me?
Well, there are Rico counts
that your time at CNRI
make you ideally suited for.
Laurel, it's a case.
If you want it, it's yours.
But only if you're ready.
What's the special occasion?
I got paid.
So, you know,
if you don't think
it's nice enough,
you only have
yourself to blame
for not giving me
that raise.
Oh!
Roy, I love it.
Thank you.
Mm-hmm.
Hey, give me--
give me a second,
I forgot to put
an order in.
Ok.
Hey, what's going on?
I got a line on Michael Statton,
Helena's fiancé.
Felicity, he's been
dead for five years.
Which makes the fact that he rented
a car last night very impressive.
That's Helena.
The car's got GPS,
I hacked into it.
Yeah. She's heading
straight for Starling City.
You ready to get
back in the field?
I thought you'd never ask.
It's over, Helena.
Get out of the car!
Gun!
Aah! Don't hurt me!
Stand down.
Stand...Down!
Don't hurt me!
Speedy!
Enough!
He's just
Helena's decoy.
Where is she?
I don't know!
Some chick just paid
me to take the car for a joy ride.
I swear!
Please don't kill me.
I'm getting married
next month.
Just drive.
According to the SCPD,
the guy that gave Helena
a ride into town is a 22-year-old
Poly Sci major at SCU,
and a member
of Gamma Tau,
which totally
explains the whole
"I didn't know I was aiding
and abetting a known felon" thing.
Anyone with boobs can get
a frat boy to do anything.
I was a frat boy.
I rest my case.
At least she didn't kill
him. That's something.
It's not like Helena
to show restraint.
It sounds like
you have a type.
Keep tabs on the police.
Let me know if they get
any leads on her.
I'll do some canvassing.
Hey...
You ok?
Yeah.
By this time tomorrow,
it'll be like nothing happened.
That's one upside
to Mirakuru.
The only one.
Look, I know what
you're going to say.
I had it under control
last night.
Yeah, so under control that I
almost put another arrow in you.
I was going to back off,
but you never gave me a chance.
The only thing that
snapped you out of it
was when
I brought up Thea.
That's why
you called me Speedy.
I--I thought you were
trying to give me a nickname.
But for the record,
don't call me Speedy.
Noted.
Roy, you're dangerous.
I thought I was
helping you control it.
You are. I mean, I can't look at
a bowl of water without slapping it.
The first time that you're out in
the field in weeks,
and...you're ready
to kill somebody?
Come on.
I'm sorry, I should have asked
you to do this months ago.
Asked me to do what?
Stay
away from Thea.
No, I--I can't.
She's not safe when
she's around you.
I'm not sure anybody is
when you lose
yourself to this rage.
You love her.
And that's why you're going to do
what I'm asking.
Such a big uh-oh.
Helena?
Laurel.
Ada Adam Donner
announced the return
of Laurel Lance to the DA's office
after a brief sabbatical.
She will lead the prosecution
of Mr. Bertinelli.
Jury selection starts today.
Hey.
Hey. What are
you doing here?
I heard you picked up
some big new case on the news.
How come you didn't call me?
I was going to, but it
all happened so fast.
Plus, I thought you and dad
would try and talk me out of
going back
to work so soon.
Which is why
you're here.
I'm just worried about you.
If you're worried
I'm going to slip,
I'm still going to two meetings
a day, and--
Laurel, it's not that.
Everybody knows
what kind of guy Bertinelli is.
And not to mention
his completely psychotic daughter,
who's already on her way back
to Starling City to kill him.
How do you know that?
I don't.
I just want you
to be safe.
And I love you
for caring.
But Sara, you've never seen me be
a lawyer before.
And I am really
good at it.
And I miss it.
I have to run.
I can't be late
for court.
Yeah, this is much better
than the freighter.
You prefer boat, Hendrik,
feel free to swim back.
Sara said Oliver
survived here for over a year.
We can do the same.
Unless Ivo and his men
come find us.
We don't know
what happened on the boat.
Who's alive
and who's dead.
Sara, are you there?
Slade! Is Oliver...
He's in pain, yes.
But he's still
breathing--for now.
Slade, listen, you won, ok?
You have the "Amazo."
Just let Oliver go,
and then you can leave us here!
Well, here's
my problem, Sara.
I can't leave.
Why not?
During our assault,
the ship's engine
was damaged.
She won't sail.
During the attack,
unfortunately
I decapitated
the engineer.
So what can we do
about our problem, Sara?
You want Oliver back,
and I need someone qualified
to fix this boat.
For Oliver's sake,
I sure hope
a Mr. Hendrik
is there with you.
Non-lethal arrows?
It's not like you
to play with kid gloves.
How's Roy?
Like Helena, he is
not too pleased
with my skills
as a mentor.
Laurel won't drop the case.
She's headed to court right now.
Where are you going?
To the courthouse.
Well, hey,
you forgot
your baby arrows.
Look, I get your whole no
killing spree,
but if it comes down
to saving Laurel or killing Helena--
Sara, those aren't
the only two choices.
Well, you were happy enough
to let Dig take the kill shot
when it was Slade
threatening your family.
This is different.
I failed Helena.
I created the Huntress.
Yeah, well,
you created Slade, too.
You're right.
But when it comes
to our families...
Neither one of us
thinks clearly.
Which is why you have
to stay here.
Ollie.
I can't.
I'm not going to let
anything happen to Laurel.
I love her, too.
What do you guys think?
Oh, I think if the Huntress shows up,
you should totally kick her ass.
Please don't tell me
you're worried about me, too.
No, I just wanted
to watch the trial.
I heard the prosecutor
was something special.
That's odd.
Why are they bringing him in
through the front
entrance?
Everybody get down!
Hi, dad.
Sorry I'm late, but you're a hard
man to track down.
But it's fitting
that you came back to Starling.
Where it all began.
Where you killed
Michael.
You know, I almost
feel sorry for you.
Helena...
Stop this.
Oliver,
you know I can't.
Well, what are you
waiting for?
I said, what are you
waiting for?!
Helena Bertinelli,
put down your weapons
and place your hands
above your head.
So this was
a big trap...
with you as the bait.
What did they offer you?
Ah, they didn't have
to offer me anything.
Give up, Miss Bertinelli,
the building's surrounded.
What was it you always
taught me, Daddy?
Be prepared
for anything.
Fall back, fall back!
Take hostages,
and fall back.
Hey, hold your fire, hold your fire!
They have hostages!
Hold fire. Say it again, hold fire.
They've taken hostages.
Where's Laurel? Where's Laurel?
Is she with you?
I'm sorry, Mr. Lance,
we got separated.
She's still inside.
We are live outside
the Starling City courthouse,
where Helena Bertinelli
and an unknown number
of assailants
seized control
of the entire building.
And I'm not being told,
they are holding a number
of hostages inside.
I want snipers
with thermals on top
of every building
for a two block radius.
This was not how it was supposed
to go down, Captain!
You promised me
there wouldn't be any casualties!
This was your idea, huh?
You son of a bitch!
Hey, my daughter's
in there!
What were
you guys thinking,
putting all those
innocent lives at risk?
Listen! I was following orders.
Orders?!
Ms. Bertinelli.
No one has
to die today.
My father does.
And unless
you hand him over to me,
I'm going to start
killing hostages.
See this,
Mr. Donner,
is what happens when you let
freaks with masks
run wild.
Get them the hell
out of here.
It's my mom.
Detective.
Helena Bertinelli
just took ten hostages.
Laurel's one of them.
Yeah, I'm aware
of the situation.
Oliver, where are you?
Are you ok?
I'm with Lance as Oliver,
and he just called the Arrow.
Oh. Oh!
It's getting really hard to keep track of
who knows whose secret identity.
Felicity, Laurel is still
inside the courthouse.
What do you
need, Oliver?
My work clothes.
I'm on it.
Put Sara on the phone.
Uh...
She's not here.
Where is she?
Are you one
of the good guys?
No, but I'm friends with them.
Dude, watch it.
Screw you!
Thea, we need to break up.
What?!
No.
What do you mean, no?
Thea, I'm breaking up with you.
No, you're not.
You can't make me date you.
Roy, yesterday
you gave me a bracelet
worth every dime
that you had,
and now what,
you want to end things?
Look, you're clearly going through
something right now,
and I'm not going
to let you go through it alone.
I'm always going
to be here for you.
Sorry, Thea. The guy
from the private party
said we stocked the wrong vodka,
and he's freaking me out.
Look, we'll talk
about this later, ok?
Oh!
Are you hurt?
I'm so stupid.
Hey.
You don't want
to do that.
Oh, no, trust me.
I do.
What about
your sobriety?
How do you know about that?
The "A" chip on
your keychain.
30 days.
Do you even know
why I'm here today?
Turns out I'm decoration.
Expendable decoration.
What do you mean?
This whole trial was a sham.
I should have seen it.
Sara was right.
Sara, she's...
She's my sister.
She said that I wasn't
ready to come back, and...
I just thought
she was being overprotective.
Well, sisters
can be like that.
You should
meet mine.
She's gone through a lot.
She must have been so strong.
I just...
I wanted to show her,
show myself...
That I was still strong, too.
So show me.
Let's go.
Where are you?
Inside. I've got
Laurel Lance, she's ok.
Is that the Arrow?
I'm headed to an egress point
in the south wing.
Wait.
What about
the other hostages?
You're just going
to leave them?
Look, I need
to get you to safety.
I don't understand! What
is so special about me?
What's going on?
She won't leave.
I know Helena.
She's going to kill
all of those people,
innocent people.
You wanted me to
show you I'm strong.
This is me being
strong. I'm staying.
Are you going
to help me or not?
Get her out of there now!
It's not like I can
just knock her out.
I don't want you
engaging Helena.
What, you're afraid
of what she'll do...
Or what I'll do?
Sara...You're not a killer.
I am what I need to be.
Sara, did you hear me?
I heard you.
Hendrik's not here.
There's someone
I'd like you to say hello to.
Don't give him
anything, Sara.
Ollie!
One last chance.
Oliver for Hendrik.
I told you! Look,
Hendrik, he didn't make it
to the island, he drowned.
To think it was only a year ago,
you were a little college girl,
fretting about boys.
What's your point?
You're not a good liar.
Slade!
Stop, please!
Look, he's
your friend!
That is the sound of electricity
surging through my friend.
Five milliamps,
to be exact.
Seven causes
cardiac arrest.
Aah!
Oliver just passed out with
six milliamps.
He'll be delivered with
the fatal blow of seven
in one hour if Hendrik
is not standing here
by my side!
There's no way
in hell I'm going back there.
I was almost married once.
It's been an hour,
and I'm a woman
of my word.
Just ask my father.
No, please!
Everything's going to be ok.
Behind you!
Oliver sure does like
to dress up his girls.
You all right?
Laurel! She's
still in there.
Nice to see you
again, Laurel.
Helena,
listen to me.
This has to end.
I agree.
And it ends with
my father in a box.
The police are never
going to hand over your father!
No, they won't.
That's why you're
going to do it.
Simple trade--
my father for Laurel.
Hey, guys?
We need more vodka.
Ok...
I'll get it myself.
Where are you taking me?
Safe house.
Listen, front's mobbed
with reporters.
Let's take Bertinelli
out the back.
Bring the van
around.
Ow! All right.
Whoa! What the hell?
Don't worry about it.
What's going on?
Just get in the van!
Hey!
Hey, hey!
SWAT's getting ready to
breach the courthouse.
Then we make
the trade now.
Listen, I'm not going
to lose any sleep over Frank.
But are you really going
to serve him up to his daughter?
No.
No one dies tonight.
Are you ok?
Everything's
going to be fine.
I said...no talking.
We talked that night.
You, Oliver,
Tommy, and I.
At dinner.
I remember you telling me
your fiancé was killed.
I'm so sorry.
Does this make us
girlfriends?
No.
But I know what
it's like to lose someone.
Ohh.
Poor Laurel.
Did Tommy dump you?
No.
He died.
And I couldn't deal with it.
So I became a drunk.
Every problem I had,
I solved with a pill or a drink.
My friends and my family,
they tried to help me,
but I wouldn't let them.
You don't have
to do this, Helena.
It's not too late.
Yes, I do.
Because once you let
the darkness inside,
it never comes out.
Helena.
I have your father.
Hmm.
I want four men teams,
diamond formations.
Move fast, shoot sharp.
One more thing--
vigilantes are not the law.
If they're wearing a mask,
they get a bullet.
Let's move out.
Hands up, Bertinelli!
Do it now!
Please don't
kill me! Please!
She--she told me--
she told me to wear it
or she'd kill me!
Where the hell is she?!
Don't look so scared, Laurel.
You might just live through this.
So you're just going
to hand me over to my daughter?
I thought you were
the good guys!
Shut up.
Remember all that
stuff I said about restraint?
Forget about it.
Hey.
You can't stop someone like Helena
by becoming her.
I'll do what I have to
to protect someone I love.
Hendrik, please,
put the gun down!
Why? So you can send me
back to that hell hole?
I don't think so!
It's not for any
of us to decide
who lives and dies.
But in Hendrik's case,
I'd be willing to make an exception.
I'm leaving.
Don't stop me.
Good at talking,
but you will not kill me.
Let's find out.
Sir, we've got a ping off
Ms. Lance's cell phone.
She must still
have it on her.
Where?
A machine shop
at Gail Street and Simone.
Should we rally up there?
Negative.
Hold your location.
Yes, sir.
Sergeant,
keep this position.
Yes, sir.
Well, this is irony
for you, dad.
Didn't you have
Jimmy d'Agostino's body
buried under
the building next door?
I'm sorry, my girl.
Now you're about to die,
I'm sure you are.
No.
I'm sorry for that little girl
I used to take to ballet class.
Go on ski trips with.
The one I used to help
with her math homework.
Oh, she hated math.
Sorry that I caused her
so much hurt.
'Cause she brought me
so much joy.
Helena!
Don't kill him.
You can never
come back from that.
It's too late.
I'm already gone.
Bye, Dad.
Damn vigilantes!
You went above the law!
Last time this happened,
I threw you out a window.
I was holding back.
I won't do that again.
Hey.
No!
You're not a killer.
You don't know who I am,
Laurel, not really.
Then show me.
No...
It was supposed
to be me.
to me who did it.
All right, Bertinelli,
that's enough.
Go.
How did you
get in here?
My family makes a generous donation
to the policemen's retirement fund.
And every once in a while,
I get to call in a favor.
Hmm. Maybe you could
ask them to send me
to prison
somewhere tropical.
You know, I thought
I'd feel different
now that he's dead,
but I don't.
And you always
told me that...
Killing him wouldn't
change anything.
You were right.
But I was wrong, too.
About what?
I thought I could help you.
Stop you from being a killer,
but...
I was just starting.
And I was a killer, too.
And what
are you now?
I'm trying to be better.
It's so stupid,
but...
I keep thinking,
now that he's dead,
my father and Michael
are together, and...
I'm still here.
Alone.
You're not alone.
What are you doing to me?
In Roman times,
a criminal was branded
to identify his crimes
to the world
and to forever remind
him of what he'd done.
Shado wore this
tattoo on her back.
Now you shall wear
it for the rest of your life,
however short
that may be.
Hello, Sara.
I hope you've made
the right choice.
Yes.
Look, on behalf of
the entire DA's office,
I have to apologize.
Adam Donner's employment
here has been terminated.
Obviously we had no idea
what he was plotting.
I would hope not.
Unfortunately, Adam
was not authorized
to offer you
your job back.
I'm sorry,
but nothing
has changed.
Yes, it has.
Excuse me?
You are going
to rehire me, Kate.
Unless you feel like
explaining to the press
that your own assistant
district attorney
was the brilliant mastermind
behind tonight's hostage crisis.
Welcome back.
I have to say,
I am impressed.
I would have thought blackmail was
a little dark for you.
Someone recently told me,
once you let
the darkness inside,
it never comes out.
Hey.
What are you still
doing up here?
Thinking.
Crying.
Roy and I are...
What happened?
I caught him
with some slut.
Right over
there, actually.
I'm sorry.
He was doing it
to push me away,
which clearly
worked.
I just...
I don't know why.
Why is it so hard
for everyone
just to tell
the truth?
I mean, Roy can't even
tell me the truth
of why he wants to
end things with me.
Mom, she...
She keeps all
of these secrets.
I mean, doesn't it...
Doesn't it feel like she's still keeping
something from us?
I don't know, Thea.
You're the only one
that doesn't lie to me, Ollie.
I know
who doesn't keep
secrets from me.
Just, I got to go.
Let me drive you.
No, I just want to be
alone right now.
Is she ok?
She will be.
Eventually.
You did good
tonight.
That's what heroes do, right?
It's a dangerous city.
You shouldn't be out
in the streets alone.
Mr. Wilson?
Please.
Call me Slade.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man