My name is Oliver Queen.
After five years in hell,
I have come home
with only one goal--
to save my city.
Now others have
joined my crusade.
To them, I am Oliver Queen.
To the rest of Starling City,
I am someone else.
I am something else.
Previously, on "Arrow"...
I want you to take my place.
I want you to become
the next Ra's al Ghul.
Maseo...
My master sees
something in you.
Don't let your recalcitrance
take any more lives.
Oliver...
Oliver, we have
to stop this guy
before he puts arrows
in any more criminals.
Or before he starts
putting them in innocent people.
Captain, I think you're letting
your personal feelings
towards the Arrow
cloud your judgment.
Maybe I'm seeing things more clearly
than I have for the last few years.
Alright, enough, both of you!
I am tired--
This is Captain Lance.
City hall, shots fired.
Suspect on the move,
I need ESU
and an ambulance, now!
Are you ok?!
I'm fine!
♪ Arrow 3x18 ♪
Public Enemy
Original Air Date on April 1, 2015
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
We have
confirmation that Mayor Castle
was pronounced dead
at the scene.
Palmer Technologies CEO
Ray Palmer
was taken to Starling
General Hospital
where he is listed
in critical condition.
I tried to call Felicity earlier,
she's not answering her phone.
SCPD Captain Quentin Lance
was present for the attack,
and had this to say
on the incident--
I just requested a first degree murder
warrant for the Arrow.
And reinstated the anti-vigilante
task force with
shoot to kill orders if necessary.
Excuse me.
Why would the Arrow
suddenly decide to assassinate the mayor?
I don't know. But I should
have trusted my first instinct,
that this man is a killer
and a criminal.
If I had, Mayor Castle
might still be alive.
He could be right.
Oliver, don't even start
to think like that.
We have to deal
with the problem that's at hand.
The murders are being
orchestrated by one of Ra's lieutenants.
Maseo Yamashiro.
Ok, you sound like
you know him.
I thought I did,
a lifetime ago.
The man's a stranger
to me now.
Oliver, the question is,
where do we find
this stranger now?
I know someone
who can help with that.
Who are those men?!
I--I don't know.
Then why are we
running away from them?
Shado?
What?
How did you know
my sister?
Your--um, your sister?
My twin. How do you know Shado?
Oliver...
It's a long story.
My--my friend and I
are in a little bit
of trouble,
and, uh, we were wondering
if you could help us get off the streets.
What's going on?
It's also a long story!
Can you help us?
Ok, listen up.
The suspect is armed and dangerous.
No warning shots!
Whatever happened to innocent
until proven guilty?
He was on that rooftop,
Laurel, I saw it with my own eyes.
He's being framed.
By a "copycat."
Which wouldn't be happening if
he wasn't dressed up
like Robin Hood in
the first place.
That's not fair!
You don't understand
what's happening here
and I need you to trust me.
I used to.
Who is he?
Just tell me his
name, or I'll--
What, Dad?
You'll charge me as an accessory?
I'll do what
needs to be done,
'cause this has to end.
And it has
to end tonight.
I am the biggest idiot
in the world
for breaking up with you.
Remember the last
time we did this?
We were going to
run away together.
Why don't we?
Roy.
Things are just complicated with
Oliver right now.
Ra's al Ghul complicated?
Oh, my God.
In the wake
of the attacks,
Captain Lance has issued
an arrest warrant
for the vigilante
known as the Arrow,
as the largest manhunt
in the city's history is now underway.
Captain Lance confirmed that
arrest warrants have also been issued
for each of the Arrow's
accomplices.
Ray?
Hey.
Hi.
How are you?
Well, you're here,
so I'm great.
Mr. Palmer,
how are you feeling?
You have a not so good
look on your face.
You see his face?
I'm afraid I've got some bad news.
During the surgery
to remove the arrow,
you developed a thrombus.
A blood clot.
If left untreated,
it could cause an ischemic stroke.
Well, then maybe
we should treat it.
It's not that simple.
Your injuries have
left you very weak.
A craniotomy could end up
doing more harm than good.
And by harm,
you mean...
Brain damage, at best.
At worst...
So we are saying
basically that
if we have the surgery
now, I could die,
and...if I wait and the clot moves,
I could die.
What if I told you
that I invented a bunch
of teeny tiny robots
that were capable of
entering my bloodstream,
traveling to the clot,
and shrinking it,
all without
damaging my brain
or any other organ
in my body?
I'd say you need a psych eval.
Ok.
But after,
we go to my lab,
get the nano-tech,
inject it in me,
and publish the results in the
"New England Journal of Medicine."
Ah, I'm sorry, but that's
simply not possible.
Uh, I invented the tech,
it's possible.
Starling General has a very
strict policy against
experimental procedures.
Wait, there is a procedure that
could save his life,
and you're saying
you won't perform it?
I'm saying I can't perform it.
The hospital won't permit
the use of an experimental
or untested technology.
How do you know
your invention won't kill you?
I don't.
It's a risk.
I'm very sorry,
but there's really
nothing I can do.
We'll figure something out.
Ray Palmer.
Even in a hospital bed,
you're the most
handsome man I've ever seen.
Can you give us
a minute?
Hi.
Ohh.
Mom!
I heard what happened,
so I caught the first flight out of Vegas!
So tell me,
what did the doctor say?
Absolutely
nothing good.
Ok, ok.
Hey.
What?
At least you finally
have a boyfriend.
Mom!
How did you know
I was still in Starling?
Laurel.
I need your help,
Nyssa.
Maseo--
is also in Starling.
He's the one behind the murders
the Arrow is suspected of.
Sarab does my father's bidding
in an effort to force you
to do the same and take
his rightful place as his heir.
And do you feel betrayed
by that decision?
Not so much that I'd betray him
in turn by helping you.
People are dying,
Nyssa!
And what makes you think
that's any concern of mine?
Sara.
What would she
want you to do?
I have Maseo's location.
A building called
Magnuson Plaza.
Yeah.
The company that
owns that building
went belly up
a few months back.
Apparently the League
has been using it as a safe house
and staging ground
for its attacks.
How'd you find this out?
I am daughter of the Demon.
Your primary concern
should be the League.
You can place Maseo
in the same cage you put me in,
but my father has
an army at his command.
One step at a time.
Oliver...
We're going to have
to spread out
if we're going to cover
that entire building.
Dig, I want you on over watch.
Copy that.
What about her?
Don't confuse my inclination
to provide you information
with a willingness to take up arms
against the League.
We appreciate
what you've done.
We'll take it from here.
Let's do this.
We scoped out every floor,
nothing.
Same with
the parking garage.
Diggle!
North side is clear.
You think Nyssa played us?
Hang on,
I got movement.
Upper level,
southwest corner.
Clearly I chose well
selecting you as my heir.
Killing me will only win you
the mantle you reject.
It'll stop you.
I have legions who live
only to see my will done.
No, boy.
You have but two choices--
you either ascend
to the calling of Ra's al Ghul
or you will spend the rest
of your days in a cage.
You're not going
to take me prisoner.
No, I'm not.
This is
the Starling City police.
Put your weapons down
and your hands up.
You are all under arrest.
Hold your fire,
hold your fire!
Lock down this entire area,
three block radius.
- Diggle!
- I got eyes on.
The blue is everywhere.
The warehouse is on the west
side of the block.
You get there,
you're in the clear.
Go, move. Four more
headed your way.
You got to move, move,
move, move, move!
Go for the door.
I'll draw their fire.
We're not
separating!
They don't want you,
they want me. Now go.
Cooper, Jones,
box 'em in on 43rd.
I got two masks in a warehouse,
West Side of 43rd.
He's headed toward
the east exit!
This way, take him!
Laurel!
What are you
going to do?
Are you going to shoot
your own daughter?
No. But I'm definitely
thinking about arresting you.
Maybe a night in jail
will bring you to your senses.
Daddy, please.
Please don't do this.
Leave her alone.
Nyssa!
Don't hurt him.
Laurel...what are you doing?
We must go.
I'm sorry.
Sweetie...
Did Arsenal
and Canary get away?
Diggle!
Get back!
Freeze!
Get in!
If we get to the tunnel
on 8th, we're good.
Clear those squad cars.
On it.
Hey.
Oh! Oh, thank God,
I've been so worried.
It's ok. I'm ok.
Where's Roy?
He's still
out there.
It's like the whole city has
lost their minds!
It's not the whole city.
It's just one man.
Yep?
Hello, Captain.
I got three men
in the hospital because of you.
I understand that
you feel betrayed,
but you can't be
so angry as to think
that I'm just running around
taking aim at innocent people.
I don't think
anything, I know.
I know this madness
has to end.
Now, you don't want any
more people getting hurt,
you turn yourself in.
Yeah,
that's what I thought.
I'm sorry.
He's in a lot of pain.
I thought that
if we stopped Maseo,
we'd stop the killings,
but Nyssa was right.
This extends way beyond him.
Oh, Roy!
I'm ok. I got clear
somewhere on Hudson.
I had to shoot
a few officers,
but they're just
flesh wounds.
I've underestimated Ra's,
and now we're all
paying the price.
I'm sorry.
What are you talking about?
Ra's is after us
because of Malcolm.
What don't I know?
You haven't told me
your names. I'm Mei.
I'm Akio,
and this is--
Tommy.
So, Tommy,
who are you and your little
friend running from?
It's...complicated.
But, Mei,
the truth is that
I don't know why this person has
sent men after us,
but she did.
Is that your father?
His name is Yao Fei.
And how do you know
my sister?
Oh, uh, medical school.
She never mentioned
any American friends.
You are American,
aren't you?
I dropped out--
of the medical school,
not of America.
So when was the last time
you saw my sister?
It's been a while.
For me, too.
Shado and my father
disappeared three years ago now.
Police think they were kidnapped,
but no ransom came.
I'm so sorry.
The police told me
they must be dead.
If they were, at least
I'd have some closure.
But each time the phone rings,
someone knocks at the door,
or when I meet someone
who knew them...
I can't imagine.
You must be tired.
Not tired, dirty.
I need a shower.
My bedroom's through that door.
There are fresh towels.
You're sure?
Yeah.
I'll entertain
your friend.
Thank you.
Listen, I'm a cop,
not a psychologist,
but in my experiences,
killers don't discriminate
between guilty and innocent.
They kill because
they view themselves
as being above the law,
and the Arrow
is no different.
He is a criminal.
And I promise you,
we will find him
and hold him accountable.
Ohh.
You ok?
Mm-hmm.
Thanks for getting this.
I ran into
Dr. Lockhart in the cafeteria.
I thought maybe,
I don't know...
I could talk him into giving Ray
those nano-thingies.
Nano-tech.
He wouldn't even look at me.
Have you seen
this dress? Hello!
Mom.
The man's an idiot.
I guess...
You're just going to
have to be the one
to inject those teeny
tiny robot things into Ray yourself.
Great plan,
except I'm not a doctor.
Even Ray said
that they can kill him.
I'm not going to be the one
to risk his life, I'm not.
His life
is already at risk.
What you're saying
is that you don't want to be the one
to take the chance.
If your father
were here...
He would be arrested.
Probably.
But right before that,
he would tell you that sometimes,
we got to take
a chance,
particularly for the people
we care about.
I don't give a damn about budgets.
This is a manhunt!
Now approve the extra personnel
and the overtime,
and you do it now!
I apologize
for the coarse treatment.
I didn't think I'd get you to speak
to me of your own accord.
You're him.
Ra's al Ghul.
It's an honor to meet you.
Sara spoke with such love
about her father.
Don't say
my daughter's name.
If she'd never met you,
she'd still be alive now.
If Sara had not
met my daughter,
she would have
starved to death
on the shores
of Lian Yu.
She was never on Lian Yu.
You suffer
false perception.
One of many,
I'm afraid.
Listen, what do you want?
To help the city
as your daughter did.
You hunt for the man
they call the Arrow.
Yeah.
What, you going
to help me find him?
You'll be able to
find him easily...
Once I tell you
his name.
And why would I believe
just any name that you'd throw at me?
Well, because with
this revelation,
everything
will become clear.
And you will realize
the man you've
been looking for
has been right in front of you
the entire time.
The same man who lied,
telling you he wasn't
with Sara on Lian Yu.
Oliver Queen
is the Arrow.
We need to talk.
Aren't you getting tired
of these little chats?
Because I know am.
Then let's cut through
all the crap.
You don't think the Arrow's
behind these murders.
You're just pissed off because he
kept Sara's death a secret from you.
That is not why.
That is not why!
I mean,
maybe at first.
Yeah. But then
I realized,
he is the reason
Sara got killed.
Dad, that is ridiculous.
No. You, Harper, Sara,
the freak in Central
City, the Huntress;
I got a new guy
flying around the city.
All these masks?
They started with him.
And Sara died only
because she was part of it all, too.
You have no idea
why Sara was killed.
She ended up
in the League of Assassins
'cause she was
marooned on Lian Yu.
'Cause she got
in that boat with Queen.
So what?
Now Oliver's to blame?
Oliver, the Arrow,
either way, same guy.
On some level,
I think I always knew.
When I thought he was doing
good, it didn't matter to me.
You know, when
that boat went down
and we--we thought
Sara was dead,
I blamed Queen.
And it's funny
how things come full circle, right?
Well, I got
things to do.
Calling him?
It's too late; I've got officers
headed to his home,
his sister's club,
everywhere.
Oh, for what it's worth,
I'm thinking of starting
a reality TV show,
so maybe I already
have brain damage.
Don't joke, Mr. Palmer.
The next few hours are critical.
I'm going to want to keep you
under close observation.
Oww!
Mom?
No, no, no,
it's nothing. Ohh!
I think my back
is spasming!
Oh! Oh. Ooh.
Gosh, you're so strong.
Ow! Oh, my God,
I think I--
I think I'm going to faint.
Maybe we should
get you on a gurney.
Yeah! Yeah,
let's get me on a gurney.
Ow.
Oh! I'm sorry. Ow!
Is your mom
going to be ok?
Oh...
I think she'll make
a miraculous recovery
in about five minutes.
Ok.
Just like you.
Is that
my nano-tech?
Assuming the organizational
system in your lab is accurate.
Uh, I--are you sure
you want to do this?
Aren't you?
Yeah. I mean,
my alternatives
are brain damage
or death.
But if the hospital finds out,
you could go to jail.
I'll take my chances.
Ahh.
Ok.
All right.
How do we feel?
Uh, normal?
But I wasn't expecting any side--
Ray? Ray!
Ray, Ray, hey!
Hi.
Ok, well...
Maybe there are
some side effects.
I can't
believe this is happening.
The line forms behind me.
The city-wide
manhunt for the Arrow
continues this evening
as Captain Lance
has made capturing this
dangerous vigilante
the SCPD's top priority.
I'm sure those cops
that were chasing you are fine.
I shot them
with arrows, Thea.
When it was happening,
there was a part of me that...
that felt relieved.
Relieved?
That I'd finally
be going to jail.
And I'd get what I deserved.
Roy, listen to me.
The only thing that you deserve
is to be happy.
Now you've got to find a way
to forgive yourself.
What happened with that cop last year,
it's not your fault.
She's right.
Sorry that you had
to go through this, Roy.
I gave you that mask...
so you could help the police,
not run from them.
Then what's
going to happen?
Oh, no.
Run!
This is the SCPD!
Put your hands in the air.
Freeze!
Thank you for the shower.
You ok?
I saw the tattoo
on your back.
Why have you been
lying to me?
Mei...
I need to know
what happened
to my family.
I don't know.
Another lie.
You knew my sister.
You and her were
more than just friends.
Just believe me when I tell you
that the less you know about me,
the safer you're going to be.
Fine, maybe you'll
be more honest with the police!
I understand you're upset;
Please don't call the police.
I already did.
They'll be here any minute.
Akio, we have to go.
What's wrong?
Get down!
Why are the police shooting?!
Because they're not
the police!
I did it.
Ah! I am so proud of you.
I am so proud--your father
would be proud of you.
You know, he's not exactly
a role model, but...
Oh, Miss Smoak,
just the person I wanted to see.
Do you know
what these are?
They're Mr. Palmer's
latest MRI.
The clot in his
brain is gone.
Really?
Not moved,
not smaller. Gone.
He's going to make
a full recovery.
You wouldn't happen
to know anything
about this unprecedented
medical development,
would you?
Huh?
Are you accusing
my daughter of something?
'Cause I work a table
at Caesar's that's frequented
by no less than 3 lawyers.
Thank you. Thank you, please.
Thank you all for coming.
We've had a breakthrough
in our investigation of the vigilante
known as the Arrow.
The district attorney's office
has just issued an arrest warrant
for the person responsible
for these acts of violence--
Oliver Queen.
I had nowhere else to go.
It's ok.
Lyla took Sara
to her mother's.
Lance knows.
The whole city knows, Oliver.
Mr. Queen should be
considered armed
and highly dangerous.
But make no mistake--
he will be found
and brought to justice.
A stunning development, as Oliver Queen
has been outed as the Arrow.
The accusation comes
as a particular surprise,
considering that Queen
was exonerated of being
the Arrow only 2 years ago.
News lady's right.
You put this genie back in
the bottle before, Oliver.
Last time I had it
all worked out.
Getting arrested
was my plan.
This time it's
Ra's al Ghul's.
How's Ray?
So much better than you right now.
Please tell me you have
a brilliant plan.
I don't even have
a regular plan.
What about Dig going out
as the Arrow?
You said that worked last time.
Yeah, but this time Lance
won't rest until Oliver's in custody.
You have to leave.
You have to get out of town.
My father's posted men at every
bus station, train station, and airport.
Also...he's frozen
Thea's assets.
He's not giving you
anything you can use to run.
I can't believe
this is happening.
Do you think Ra's
planned this the entire time?
He's using this city
as a weapon.
It's my city.
Where you going, Oliver?
Only place I can go.
Akio, you ok?!
I'm ok.
Ok.
What's happening?!
Is the front door
the only way in and out?
Yes.
I want you to get low,
I want you to take Akio to the bedroom.
Mei, they're coming
to kill you, too.
Go, go, come on!
Akio?!
Akio?
We followed them.
They work for Amanda Waller.
Who is she?
How are you
feeling?
For a guy who
just avoided death
and/or brain damage,
pretty good.
Good.
Are you ok?
It's, uh,
it's a long story.
I'm just glad that
you're all right.
Thanks to you.
Oh, I think your nano-tech deserves
some of the credit.
All I did was stick
something in you.
Do you think there will ever
come a time
when everything I say isn't
some weird double entendre?
I hope not. It's one
of your more charming traits.
That, and the fact that you had
the courage to throw caution to the wind
and save my life are just two
of the many reasons that I love you.
Wow.
That's a really
nice thing to hear.
Especially after,
you know, everything
that's been
going on with you
with the blood clot,
nano-tech, and the...
nearly dying.
Yeah.
Speaking of, you must be starving
after all that drama.
I'm going to go find
a hospital nurse
and get you some of that
hospital Jell-o.
Oh, my God,
what just happened?
Nothing.
Felicity...
Uh-uh-uh-uh.
You look the way you did when you
were seven years old
and stole your father's electronics
collection to make a super computer.
Oh, my God.
Did you and Ray
just do it in this hospital?
Did you just have hospital sex?!
No! Oh!
I've always wanted to have
hospital sex!
Way TMI! Gross!
What?
He told me he loved me.
Ohh.
And you didn't
say it back?
What is wrong
with me?
He's brilliant.
He knows the plot
to every "Doctor Who" episode.
All 34 seasons.
He looks like
a Disney prince.
I mean, he's...
practically
the perfect man.
You don't love Ray...
because you're in love
with Oliver.
You don't
even know Oliver.
You met him for
like ten seconds.
I knew it in five.
Honey, you lit up
like Christmas
when he walked in the room.
But he's...
terminally unavailable.
And that was before.
You haven't been
watching the news.
No, no, no, I don't
watch the news, it depresses me.
But here's what doesn't--
my daughter
has two men
who are both amazing,
which just means...
She has to make a choice.
I want pictures of Queen
distributed through every officer, ok?
No, a current one,one with the scruff
he's always wearing.
Captain Lance...
I'm here to turn myself in.
Cuff him.
Ok, I was able to get you
ten minutes with Oliver,
but let's make it five,
all right?
It would not look good
if any of these reporters
caught wind of you
meeting with him.
Him, and the three of you?
Makes sense.
You shouldn't
be here.
Oliver, neither
should you.
What were you thinking?
Were you thinking?!
I was thinking
clearly.
I asked Laurel to make a deal--
I turn myself in
and all of you
receive full immunity.
No, Oliver.
You are out of your mind
if you think we're just
going to stand here
and let you take the fall
for all of us.
I started
all of this.
It's my fault to take,
and this is the best
way to save lives,
including yours.
So stop worrying.
I've been through
far worse than prison.
This is insane.
How could we live with ourselves
if we let you do this?
Roy, I'm just going
to need you to!
The only move that
Ra's has left me
is telling
the truth.
You have no idea
how powerful
the truth can be.
Oliver, this is
the wrong move!
John...
You followed me
this far.
All of you have followed me
this far,
but I need you
to follow me just
a little further.
Until it's over.
Hey.
The bodies are taken care of.
We should go.
Just give us
a minute.
I'm sorry
about this.
They tried to kill us.
They weren't
the cops.
They must have
intercepted the call.
They were after you
and the boy?
You knew my sister;
Is there any chance--
Hey. This...
This had nothing
to do with Shado.
You have no idea
what it's like
to live like this.
Looking for any kind of answer.
You were right that
I knew your sister.
I loved her.
I knew
your father, too.
And your family...
they saved my life
more than once.
I don't understand.
The people that
are after me...
They'll kill anyone who knows
too much about who I am.
But Shado and my father--
They...
They're gone.
I'm so sorry.
Thank you for telling me.
For three years now,
all I've wanted
is to know the truth.
You have no idea how
powerful the truth can be.
We shouldn't stay here.
Thank you.
This isn't fair.
This isn't right.
All Oliver has ever done
was protect people.
Help people.
We can't stay here.
This place
isn't secure anymore.
And then what?
We just bug out
and allow this to happen?
Enjoy our new immunity?
Roy, I don't know!
I have no idea.
If I did, you'd be
listening to it right now.
If any one of us were in there
and Oliver was here,
he would think of something.
And it wouldn't matter
what the consequences were.
Lian Yu.
What about it?
This, uh, Ra's character,
he told me that Sara
made it to
the island with you.
You didn't feel like
sharing that with me? Huh?
I mean, I'm only her father.
Well, I was.
When did you decide that you knew
what was best for my family?
I love your family.
You got the right
to remain silent. Take it!
Just ask me what
you want to know.
What do I want to know?
Well, was it worth it?
All that pain and misery
you brought back from that island?
Merlyn, Slade Wilson?
Wouldn't it be better
if you just died there?
The reason I came back
was to try and save
the people
of this city.
I hate to break it to you,
but saving people isn't your specialty.
Tommy.
Hilton.
Your mother.
My daughter.
And now you're set
on killing Laurel, too.
I didn't want her
to be involved in this.
I didn't want anyone to be
involved in this.
But you involved me.
You spent a year making me
look like a fool.
You spent a year
making me your accomplice.
You have any idea
what you've done, huh?
What you've done to all of us,
to the people you claim
to care so much about?
You've made us criminals!
You've made us
liars and victims.
You, Mr. Queen,
are not a hero.
You're a villain.
But you know that,
don't you?
What the hell
are your people doing?
I told them
to stand down.
Well, I guess your word carries
as much weight with them
as it does with me.
Get down on the ground!
You've got
the wrong guy.
Oliver Queen
isn't the Arrow.
I am.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Greg!
Move you head.