No, no, no.
Come on, man.
I'm just trying to make an honest living.
There's nothing honest
about what you do.
Who supplies you with Vertigo?
Tell me now and you live.
Please! He'll kill me!
Whoever you fear...
...fear me more.
Okay, okay!
They call him The Count.
That's all I know.
I swear to God!
Hey! You get me down from here!
- Find what you're looking for?
- Took down three Vertigo pushers.
The last one finally knew a name.
The Count.
The Count?
That's worse than The Hood.
- You're not going back out there?
- I'm not done for the night.
This Count has a lot of blood
on his hands.
- It is long past time he started paying.
- Slow down.
- I think you're missing the point here.
- What?
- Thea.
- Her hearing's in a few hours.
You think she cares more
about some drug lord...
...or you being by her side
when she needs you the most?
- Hey, we should get going.
- Heh.
Judges don't appreciate the value
of being fashionably late.
- Got any other tips?
- Ahh, let the lawyer do all the talking.
They give you a pad and paper,
but do not play tic-tac-toe.
Judges don't appreciate that either.
Come on, Speedy.
I know. I know.
I keep on trying to get up and go...
...but, heh, I just don't.
I wish Dad were here.
I'm here.
We should leave now, Thea.
Miss Queen. Thea, over here.
Can we get a comment?
Just one comment.
Thea, are you going into rehab?
Are you being expelled from Balliol Prep?
Are you worried about the outcome?
"Docket ending 1-10-5-6,
People v. Thea Dearden Queen.
Possession of a controlled substance.
Driving under the influence."
Counselors, I understand
you've reached a plea agreement?
We have.
Given that my client is a juvenile...
...the people have agreed
to probation.
A juvenile?
Says right here she's 18.
She is 18 now, but at her arrest...
...she was still two days shy
of her 18th birthday.
- Miss Queen has no priors.
- Just because Miss Queen's family...
...sweeps her priors under the rug,
doesn't mean they don't exist.
You get your client off.
You help your boss
avoid dealing with a drug...
...that's sweeping across our city
like a plague.
Everyone wins, except us...
- ...people of Starling City.
- With all due respect...
Miss Queen...
...like it or not, you are now
the poster child for this menace.
Maybe if people see
that the Queen family...
...can't get away with using Vertigo...
...they'll think twice
before using it themselves.
The plea arrangement is denied.
This case will proceed to trial.
They can't do this.
That man cannot send my daughter
to prison.
What are our options?
An interlocutory appeal.
The trial judges have discretion
to reject plea agreements.
You might prepare
for the possibility...
...that this isn't gonna go our way.
I'm sorry, Mrs. Queen.
I'll get to work on the appeal.
Well, so much for the best
criminal defense attorney in the city.
Thea, we will handle this. I promise.
Like you promised Walter
you'd always stay faithful to him?
- I feel better already.
- That's enough.
Don't worry. Sounds like you won't have
to be putting up with me much longer.
What, does she not realize
how serious this is? She took drugs.
She drove.
She could have killed someone.
- Or herself.
- I know.
All that judge is looking for
is someone to make an example of.
Why does it have to be her?
Maybe it doesn't.
Listen, I have to go do something.
Are you gonna be okay?
I'm not the one facing prison.
Working for them now?
Why are you doing this to me?
I thought we were friends...
...or something.
Why'd you bother keeping me safe if
you were gonna hand me over to them?
Just get me out of here, okay?
I can't.
Hey. Don't leave me here.
I came back for you.
Now you hear me.
I came back for you!
Looking for a Detective Hall.
I was told he works in Vice.
Oliver?
McKenna Hall.
Hi, heh.
Here I was, expecting a middle-aged guy
in a bad suit.
And I got McKenna Hall.
- I live to surprise.
- Oh.
- I remember.
- Heh.
What was that club you got us
kicked out of? The Club DeVille?
In my defense there was no sign that
said you had to keep your clothes on.
So a cop. I guess you're not hitting
the party circuit anymore.
I still go to raves.
I just go undercover now.
And I have to dress
slightly more appropriately...
- ...to hide my badge and gun.
- Right.
So, what do you need with a vice cop?
- Vertigo.
- Right. I saw your sister on TV.
- I'm sorry.
- The judge is making an example of her.
So if you could find the person selling
drugs, it might take some heat off Thea.
Easier said than done.
Did some digging
and came up with a name.
Um, The Count?
We've known about The Count
for months.
Oh.
I wish this was thicker,
but we really don't have much on him.
Love to say we're gonna catch him before
your sister's trial but it's unlikely.
Oh, I'm late for my shift.
Well, if you hear of anything
about this guy, just let me know?
Always loved how much you
cared about your sister...
...but leave the policing to the police.
Okay.
What did Queen want?
He's an old friend.
His sister's jammed up.
- Anything else, sergeant?
- No.
- You need a tailor.
- You know about the Hood.
He just cornered me, man.
The Hood guy?
I didn't say anything.
Oh, I know.
You can't divulge secrets
you don't know.
But examples must be made.
Vertigo...
...in its purest form.
When injected into the bloodstream...
...affects the thalamus region
of your brain...
...which is where all of the information
from your pain receptors is collected.
No doubt you're in excruciating pain...
...but actually you're not.
You just think you are.
I've seen it last for days...
...until finally the heart gives out.
One bullet left.
Now, you can use that bullet to shoot me
and take your revenge...
...or you could shoot yourself.
It's your choice.
The Hood...
...coming for me.
Interesting.
I'm learning
you're not a morning snuggler.
I'm learning you don't like to wake up
at any hour that ends in a.m.
That's true. Yeah.
So if you're busy being a lawyer all day
and I'm managing a nightclub all night...
...when exactly do we get
to see each other?
Hmm, I got it. Stay.
- Hey.
Hey, how is Thea holding up?
She's doing okay. Thank you.
Um...
Actually, uh, I came to talk to Laurel.
Yeah.
- Hi.
Thank you for coming to court
yesterday.
Of course. But I don't think the judge
is willing to move off his position.
Taking a hard line against criminals
is a platform for his reelection.
I need you to talk to your father.
He's inside the system...
...and maybe he cashes in a chip
with Judge Brackett...
- ...gets him off throwing book at Thea.
- Oliver, I don't...
Laurel, I am working on something
on my end...
...but if it doesn't work out,
this is my best chance to help my sister.
Please.
I'll see what I can do.
- But no promises.
- Thank you.
Yep.
- Absolutely not.
- Dad, I know how you feel about Oliver.
Then why would you even ask me?
Because Thea,
she's only 18 years old.
Which makes her an adult.
She can take medicine.
It's about time somebody
in the Queen family did.
What about the Lance family?
A young girl acting out,
engaging in reckless behavior.
Does that sound familiar?
Laurel, don't go there.
Thea, she's just like I remember Sara.
That is not how I remember
your sister.
Because you remember her
the way you wish she had been...
...not the way that she actually was.
She's not the saint
you make her out to be.
I know she was arrested for shoplifting
and I know you made it go away.
Well, maybe if I'd let her go to jail...
...Queen wouldn't have had her
on that boat.
Dad, you make it sound
like he kidnapped her.
For so long, you and I have blamed
Oliver for Sara's death.
But Sara's to blame too.
When I look at Thea,
I see Sara's potential in her.
And her flaws too.
Yes, Thea made a mistake...
...but she's been through a lot.
She lost a father and a brother.
She doesn't need prison.
She needs help.
So please...
I'll make some calls.
Seen a fair amount of Cyrillic
back in Afghanistan left over by Soviets.
Is this Russian-owned?
It's the not-so-hidden headquarters
of Starling City chapter of the Bratva.
Diggle.
Whatever I say.
Whatever goes down.
Just go with it.
Good to see you too.
Long time.
Particularly for Bratva captain.
I was trying to figure out
where to put my interests.
I decided on pharmaceuticals.
I don't mean aspirin.
A wise choice.
Mephedrone would be
good investment for you.
It's the newest thing.
I was thinking Vertigo.
Newer thing.
Tough market, Vertigo.
- Only one seller.
- I know.
Hoping you could do me a favor,
arrange a meeting.
He is difficult man...
...and he does not like new friends.
This is everything the police
have on him.
Tell him it's a gift.
I will see what I can do...
...provided you do favor for me.
It is unusual for an American
to hold such a position...
...of esteem in our organization,
Mr. Queen.
Anatoli Knyazev...
- ...he speaks very highly of you.
- He should.
I saved his life.
- What did he do?
- Something I told him not to.
Now, the favor.
Kill this man for me...
...and I will believe your interest
in our organization is genuine.
And then I will arrange
a meeting with The Count.
- Oliver...
- Hey, shut up.
Spasiba.
What are friends for?
I'm out of the gate now.
What's going on?
Are we getting out of here?
Where are you taking me?
Well, I admit that bout
was particularly one-sided.
Would anybody else like
to give it a try?
The point of these little
gladiatorial distractions...
...is to strengthen unit cohesion.
To that end,
I think our newest recruit...
...ought to be afforded
the opportunity to try his hand.
- Come on.
- Hurry up.
- Get it on.
- Get it over with.
I can't believe you just killed that guy.
You really have a low opinion of me.
Whoa, that's a neat trick.
You going to teach me that one day?
- No.
- What are you doing?
You need to arrange a new identity
for this guy. Get him out of the city.
So your Russki pal draws out The Count,
the vigilante takes him down.
No, then the Bratva would know I used
them. That relationship is too valuable.
I do the meet with The Count
as myself...
...let him leave,
then we follow him to his hideout.
- Just that easy, huh?
- I will still need my trusty bodyguard.
Fantastic. Looking forward to my new
and exciting career as a drug dealer.
He is a captain.
And he has money.
- Are you interested?
- Hmm.
Let's say, yes.
My father was able to get Brackett
to back off his hard line stance.
Your father hates me.
- No.
My father hates him.
- Nobody asked you to get involved.
- I did.
The judge has agreed to a sentence...
...of 500 hours of community service...
...and two years of probation.
Provisional on the appointment
of someone to act in loco parentis.
In loco what?
It means the court
will appoint an individual...
...to assume responsibility for you.
Me.
I say thanks, but no thanks.
Thea,
you don't actually have a choice.
Oh, actually, I do.
See, I'm 18 now
and I can make my own decisions.
So I decide not to be
your ex-girlfriend's office monkey.
Well, if you change your mind, then.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
Thea.
You're in real trouble. And rightly so.
Doing drugs and driving,
it is beyond stupid.
That is a good deal that Laurel got you.
Why aren't you jumping at it?
- I already have a mother.
- So...
You're gonna go to jail,
and it will ruin the rest of your life.
No, heh, I want to ruin Mom's life.
She's a liar and a cheat.
I mean, deal with it, Ollie.
You can pretend all you want to
that she's a saint, but I hate her.
- And she betrayed Dad.
- So you're gonna go to jail to spite her?
Thea...
...Mom didn't cheat on Dad.
He cheated on her.
Is that the best you can come up with?
Dad wasn't the man he said he was.
On the Queen's Gambit
right before he died...
...he admitted to me that he failed us.
You, me and Mom.
That he wasn't the man
he said he was...
...and that he just wished...
He wished he had more time
to right his wrongs.
- I don't believe you.
- Yes, you do.
- Speedy...
- Leave me alone.
How dare you.
She was old enough
to know the truth.
Oliver, the Russians called.
The meet is set. It's tonight.
You know why they call him The Count?
When he was developing this drug,
he experimented on the homeless.
Prostitutes, runaways.
The police would find their bodies,
puncture marks on their neck...
...like a vampire.
You should not be in such a hurry
to meet this man.
Thank you for this.
But I'm not overly concerned
about the S.C.P.D.
Now, I understand you gentlemen wish
to participate in the feel-good business.
- Yes.
- And why is that?
I'm opening a nightclub.
I'd like my customers to have a little...
...something extra.
Well, as it happens,
I'm looking to expand my brand.
A good wine's value is measured
by its vintage.
The number of years
it took to ferment.
Vertigo is measured in lives.
Fifty-six people died
to perfect this high.
Believe me when I say
that they did not die for nothing.
Let's get out of here.
Come on, come on, let's go.
- S.C.P.D. Put your weapons down!
- Move, move.
S.C.P.D. Freeze.
Get down!
Oliver!
No witnesses.
Get out of the car.
- You okay?
- Keep it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Got it, got it. Go. Steps, let's go.
Oliver.
Drink.
- You're quick.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- All right.
- Come on.
Morning.
How you feeling?
I feel like I'm getting over
the worst hangover of my life. Argh.
That coming from a guy who spent
most of his 20s in a hangover.
Think you can uncuff me?
I'm not gonna kill you.
Promise.
Ah.
- Oh.
- You're standing. That's pretty impressive.
Count got you with half a dose but you
sweated out a small pool coming down.
Ah, The Count.
Any chance our friends
in S.C.P.D. took him down?
None at all.
But we did manage to get this.
I think we should analyze it.
Listen, maybe you need to give it
a few hours.
A near drug overdose isn't something
you just walk away from.
Neither is Thea.
What's wrong?
ls everything okay with Thea?
This isn't about your sister,
this is about you.
Last night, we got a call from a Cl.
Busted up a drug sale between
a bigtime dealer and Russian mob.
"We"? I thought you worked Vice.
Joint task force.
- Vertigo's got everyone holding hands.
- Like I said...
...last night, drug deal gone south.
An eyewitness puts you at the scene.
Whoever he is, he's mistaken.
- Yeah?
- I saw you, Oliver.
Is this true?
I was checking into The Count.
He's the guy who sold drugs to Thea.
Figured I could find out what he looked
like, give your sketch artist something.
I paid a lowlife with a Russian accent an
obscene amount to arrange a meeting.
And did you get eyes on him?
No.
All right. Are you pressing charges
against my son?
Get involved again,
you'll see the inside of a cell.
Unlike last time, you
will not see the way out.
- Detective.
- Thank you very much.
Thank you for what you did for Thea.
My daughter asked me for a favor
and I did it.
And that's the end of it.
- Hope you don't think I sold you out.
- No.
Just doing your job.
- What were you thinking?
- I was trying to help.
By running around with the Russian mob
and a murderous drug dealer?
- Are you out of your mind?
- Heh, Mom, look...
...the real reason that you're upset is
because I told Thea the truth about Dad.
- She never needed to know that.
- Yes, I did.
I'm old enough to know the truth,
Mom.
Mom...
It wasn't about your age.
It was about preserving your memory
of your father.
He loved you.
No matter his faults, he loved you.
I said that I wished...
...you had died instead of him,
but you still didn't say anything.
Why?
One day...
...I hope you're lucky enough
to have a daughter...
...and you'll know why.
I'm so sorry for what I said.
I know, I know.
- Now what?
- Like you said, we analyze the Vertigo.
It's liquid form, it contains water.
So maybe we can trace back
to where in the city The Count is...
...cooking up this garbage.
Oliver? Oliver.
- Hey, we need to get you to a hospital.
- No.
Oliver, God knows what's in that drug.
It could be causing permanent damage.
Ahem, Felicity.
Hey, they said you'd be up here.
You look like something
the cat dragged in.
Not that there are cats
in this building.
Well, once a cat did get in,
but a guard Tased it.
It smelled like fur and static in here
for, like, a week.
Ahem, you mind stepping away
from the window?
I have a little bit of a hangover.
Sounds like you need a Bloody Mary
and a pretzel...
...not the IT Department.
Actually, my buddy Kevin
is starting an energy drink company.
He says it's fantastic
for curing hangovers...
...but I am very particular
about what it is I put in my body.
I've noticed.
I said, "not noticed," right?
Trying to find a secret recipe.
Could you do a spectro-analysis
of the sample...
...and find out exactly
where in the city it's made?
If it's an energy drink,
why is it in a syringe?
I ran out of sports bottles.
Your BS stories are getting worse.
Well aware.
Looks like Felicity came through.
The solvent used in the Vertigo sample
was runoff water...
...originated within a 10-block radius
of where East Glades meets the bay.
Nothing there except an old detention
center abandoned about three years ago.
Cutbacks.
You can't go out there, Oliver. Still
suffering the aftereffects of Vertigo.
Did you hear The Count?
He's taking this drug citywide.
We don't stop him,
this becomes an epidemic.
I can stop you from leaving.
Try.
Oliver, hit this and you can leave.
I'm glad you came to your senses.
You should remember one thing, Dig.
- What's that?
- I don't need the bow.
- My Cl swears this is the place.
- Bring your men up on the flank.
- Okay, this way.
- Follow me.
- He's here!
- He who?
The Hood!
Looks like we're not the only guests.
You should have stuck
to your depraved elite.
I'm merely providing people
with what they want.
- I'm providing a public service.
- So am I.
Enjoy the fruits of your labor.
Freeze!
Put down the needle
or I will shoot you.
- Put down the syringe.
- He deserves this.
Not according to the law.
People think you're a hero...
...people like my daughter
if they could see you now.
You're no hero.
You're what I always said you were.
A killer.
Get him.
Get me an ambulance. Now.
Juvenile delinquent
reporting for duty.
Heh, since you lost your license,
I'll pick you up at 5.
Six.
We have a lot of work for her to do.
Well, then, let's say 7, just to be safe.
Is it too late to choose jail?
Yes, ha-ha-ha.
I need you to go through these files,
and pull out the documents...
...dated March 2007.
Do you think you could do that?
I think I can, heh.
Look, I know I messed up.
I really appreciate this, Laurel.
We're gonna make an upstanding citizen
out of you yet, Speedy.
Thank you. This will be good for her
having a role model...
- ...somebody better than me.
- Oh, you're not so bad.
And besides, it will be nice
to have her around.
I gotta take this. Excuse me.
- Hello.
- I got the Count.
Bust up his lab, got him on everything
from drug trafficking to homicide.
- He'll be gone for a long while.
- That's great. Thanks.
It was great seeing you, Oliver, heh.
You too.
See you.
He's still critical.
I've never seen anyone OD
on this much Vertigo and live.
There's just no way of knowing
what damage has been done...
...to his brain and nervous system,
or if it's irreparable.
"Survive."
- Hi.
Thanks for meeting me.
I was nervous to come to your house, heh.
Okay, heh.
The thing is, I've been debating whether
or not to share this with you for weeks.
Can I trust you?
I'm not an idiot. You've dropped
some fairly ridiculous lies on me...
...and yet I still feel
like I can trust you, heh.
Why is that?
I have one of those faces.
Sorry.
Yes.
You can trust me.
Then I have something to show you.
Have you ever seen this before?
No.
Where'd you get it?
From your stepfather.
It's from Walter.
Uh...
Where did he get it?
He said he found it in your house...
...that it belongs to your mother.
Walter thought
she was hiding something.
Something more...
...and he wanted me to look into it,
but then he vanished.
I think this list
might have cost Walter his life.