OLIVER:
MY NAME IS OLIVER QUEEN.
AFTER 5 YEARS IN HELL,
I RETURNED HOME
WITH ONLY ONE GOAL:
TO SAVE MY CITY.
TODAY I FIGHT THAT WAR
ON TWO FRONTS:
BY DAY, I LEAD STAR CITY
AS ITS MAYOR,
BUT BY NIGHT,
I AM SOMEONE ELSE.
I AM SOMETHING ELSE.
I AM THE GREEN ARROW.
PREVIOUSLY ON "ARROW..."
WHAT ARE YOU DOING
IN RUSSIA?
I'M HERE TO KILL
KONSTANTIN KOVAR.
ONLY PEOPLE WITH POWER
TO GET PAST HIS ARMY
ARE BRATVA.
WE LOST ONE.
IT'S IN THE AIR.
YOU NEED TO DIVERT
THAT MISSILE.
THAT'S IT.
[EXPLOSION]
MAN: TOBIAS CHURCH.
HE AND HIS CREW TORE UP
HUB CITY AND BLUDHAVEN.
ANYBODY ELSE WANT
TO BE IN CHARGE?
CHURCH JUST BECAME
OUR TOP PRIORITY.
FELICITY THINKS
THAT IT'S TIME
WE PUT TOGETHER
A NEW TEAM.
FELICITY: EVELYN SHARP.
BASICALLY A 16-YEAR-OLD
BADASS IN THE MAKING.
JOHN: UNTIL HER
PARENTS MET
DAMIEN DARHK,
I'M GUESSING.
YOU RECRUIT ME, TOO.
YOU WANT TO HELP?
THIS IS MY CITY, TOO.
I DON'T WANT TO SEE YOU
OUT HERE AGAIN!
AAH!
YOU AGAIN?
HOW'S THE LEG?
YOU CALL YOURSELF
A VIGILANTE?
YOU JUST LET
THE HALCONES'
TOP SELLER GET AWAY.
[MAN YELLS]
NOW, I THOUGHT I SAID
THAT I DIDN'T WANT
TO SEE YOU OUT HERE AGAIN.
YOU DON'T LISTEN VERY WELL.
YOU SOUND LIKE MY EX.
RENE RAMIREZ,
YOU NEED TO DECIDE
IF YOU WANT TO BE
A MAN IN A HOCKEY MASK
OR IF YOU WANT TO BE
SOMEONE ELSE...
SOMETHING ELSE.
CONAHAN WAS STRUCK WITH
AN ARROW AND A SWORD.
LITERALLY OVERKILL.
CURTIS: DEFINITELY
NOT CHURCH'S M.O.
TOTALLY DIFFERENT
THAN THE BERTINELLI
MURDER, TOO.
BALLISTICS SHOW THAT HE
WAS SHOT BY HIS OWN MEN.
WELL, THAT HAD
TO BE CHURCH.
IN HUB CITY, HE KILLED
EVERY CRIME BOSS IN TOWN
SO HE COULD
UNITE EVERYONE
UNDER ONE SUPER-GANG
UNDER HIS CONTROL.
HOW DOES HE DO THIS?
IT'S ALL
IN THE CORE.
[GASPING]
OLIVER: SO, CURTIS...
I'M GUESSING THIS
WASN'T PART
OF YOUR OLYMPIC
TRAINING.
IMPOSSIBLE.
IT'S REALLY HOT...
I MEAN, NOT.
IT'S NOT.
CURTIS, IF YOU THINK
THIS IS HARD,
WAIT UNTIL I ACTUALLY
START TRAINING YOU.
WHAT HAPPENS THEN?
THE LAST GUY GOT
AN ARROW IN THE LEG
BEFORE IT EVEN STARTED.
THAT WAS ROY, RIGHT?
ALSO ROY, BUT I'M TALKING
ABOUT WILD DOG.
AND YOU DID PUT TWO ARROWS
IN BARRY ALLEN'S BACK.
I'M STARTING
TO SENSE A PATTERN.
DON'T WORRY.
HIS BARK'S WAY WORSE
THAN HIS BITE.
AND YOU'RE GOING TO GET
IT WORSE THAN ANYONE.
UH, THANKS?
THE PEOPLE THAT
WE ARE LOOKING AT
HAVE AT LEAST
SOME EXPERIENCE
ON THE STREET.
YOU HAVE THE FARTHEST
WAY TO GO
BEFORE I'M CONVINCED
THAT YOU CAN DO THIS.
-I CAN DO IT, SIR.
-DON'T CALL ME "SIR."
-OK, OLIVER.
-DON'T CALL ME OLIVER,
ESPECIALLY IN FRONT
OF THE RECRUITS.
WE DON'T KNOW THESE PEOPLE,
AND THEY CAN'T KNOW US.
WHOA, WHOA, HOLD UP.
YOU'RE GOING TO BE
WEARING A MASK
WHEN YOU'RE TRAINING
OUR RECRUITS?
YEAH, AND SO ARE YOU.
I ONLY WEAR A MASK
ONCE A YEAR,
AND THAT'S IF MY
HALLOWEEN COSTUME
CALLS FOR IT.
THIS IS NOT NEGOTIABLE,
FELICITY.
I'M LATE
FOR A BUDGET MEETING.
YEAH.
YOU KNOW, I'M SURE
THAT KICKING THINGS OFF
BY LYING TO EVERYONE
IS AN AWESOME IDEA.
WELL, THE ORIGINAL TEAM
STARTED OFF
WITH OLIVER LYING
ABOUT HIS IDENTITY.
AND EVERYONE WHO'S NOT DEAD
OR PRESUMED DEAD QUIT.
YEAH.
WALKER:
THIS TRIGGER WAS TAKEN
FROM ONE OF THE NUKES
THAT FELL ON GENESIS DAY.
OUR INTEL TELLS US THAT
A GROUP OF CHECHEN REBELS
IS CLOSE TO OBTAINING IT.
I DON'T HAVE TO TELL YOU
WHAT KIND OF A NIGHTMARE
SCENARIO WILL ENSUE
IF THAT HAPPENS.
THE MISSION IS STANDARD
RETRIEVAL AND EXTRACTION.
SERGEANT DIGGLE HERE
WILL BE RUNNING THE OP.
WHEELS UP AT 0400.
ALL RIGHT, GENTLEMEN,
GET SOME REST.
YOU'RE GOING TO NEED IT.
JOHN: DISMISSED!
YOU GOOD, SOLDIER?
I GOT THROUGH BASIC
TRAINING NO SWEAT,
BUT THIS IS MY FIRST
DAY IN THE SOUP,
AND I DON'T WANT
TO BE SCARED,
BUT I AM A LITTLE.
FEAR IS PART OF WAR,
THE PART THAT
KEEPS US ALIVE.
SEE THESE STRIPES?
THEY GIVE ME
STRENGTH, CLARITY.
RIGHT OR WRONG,
UP AND DOWN,
THEY TELL ME
WHAT TO DO...
WHICH MEANS THAT FEAR
CAN KISS MY 6.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND,
SOLDIER?
-YES, SIR.
-GOOD.
DISMISSED.
OLIVER: IT USED TO BE
THAT THE GLADES
WERE THE WORST PART
OF THE CITY,
BUT NOW IT SEEMS
LIKE EVERY OTHER PART
IS JUST AS BAD.
WE'VE HAD 3
HOSPITAL CLOSURES
IN THE PAST 18 MONTHS,
BUT WITH A FREE MEDICAL
CLINIC EVENT LIKE THIS,
WE CAN START TO WALK BACK
SOME OF THAT DAMAGE.
IN A...IN A DAY,
WE CAN PROVIDE
MEDICAL CARE
FOR UP TO A THOUSAND
PEOPLE.
PLUS WE ALREADY HAVE
ABOUT 30 DOCTORS AND NURSES
JUST WAITING
TO VOLUNTEER.
WE'RE LOOKING
FOR A COMPANY TO COVER
LOGISTICAL
EXPENSES AND...
I DON'T NEED
TO HEAR ANY MORE.
AMERTEK IS IN,
AND NOT JUST FOR
LOGISTICAL EXPENSES,
FOR THE WHOLE THING.
WELL, THAT'S
AMAZING.
THAT'S...THAT'S
INCREDIBLY GENEROUS.
THANK YOU.
PLEASE. YOU WOULD BE
DOING US THE FAVOR.
AND BY "US," SHE MEANS
OUR STOCK PRICE.
GOOD PR IS
WORTH LITERALLY
ITS WEIGHT IN GOLD.
UH, WELL, WE WILL
MAKE SURE THIS CLINIC
IS A SUCCESS
AND THAT EVERYONE KNOWS
THEY HAVE AMERTEK
TO THANK FOR IT.
WOW.
GOD, I'D ALMOST FEEL BAD
ABOUT BOOSTING
THEIR STOCK PRICES
IF IT WASN'T SO GOOD
FOR YOUR APPROVAL RATINGS,
BUT, ACTUALLY, YOU SHOULD
REALLY HANDLE THE PRESS
ON THIS ONE.
MAYBE YOU CAN...
GOD, OLLIE, I THOUGHT
WE TALKED ABOUT THIS.
I CAN'T KEEP DOING
EVERYTHING ON MY OWN.
I HAVE FAITH THAT YOU CAN,
BUT EITHER WAY, NOW
IS NOT A VERY GOOD TIME.
AND WHY IS THAT?
I'M RECRUITING A NEW TEAM.
OH.
YOU OK WITH THAT?
YEAH, WHY WOULDN'T I BE?
I QUIT.
NO, I KNOW, BUT THERE'S
A DIFFERENCE
BETWEEN LEAVING
AND BEING REPLACED.
OH.
IT'S REALLY CUTE YOU
THINK I CAN BE REPLACED.
THAT'S NOT WHAT I MEANT.
I KNOW,
BUT I ACTUALLY THINK
IT'LL BE REALLY GOOD
FOR YOU TO NOT BE
OUT THERE SOLO ANYMORE.
PLUS IT WOULD MEAN
YOU HAVE MORE TIME
TO ACTUALLY BE HERE.
THAT'S THE IDEA,
BUT IT'S GOING
TO TAKE A MINUTE
TO GET THESE KIDS
UP TO SPEED.
WAIT, MAYBE I SHOULD
HIRE MY OWN TEAM
FOR THE OFFICE, THEN.
THAT'S ALSO A GOOD IDEA.
START LOOKING AT RÉSUMÉS.
HEY, QUENTIN.
HAVE YOU ACTUALLY HEARD
ABOUT THIS FREE
MEDICAL EVENT
OLLIE AND I
ARE PUTTING TOGETHER?
FELICITY:
RENE RAMIREZ?
RENE: YEAH.
FIGURES THERE'D
BE MORE OF YOU.
ROBIN HOOD NEEDS HIS BAND
OF MERRY MEN, RIGHT?
WELL, I AM JUST HERE
FOR MORAL SUPPORT.
SHE MEANS SHE'S HERE
TO MAKE SURE
THAT THE GREEN ARROW'S
TRAINING TECHNIQUE
DOESN'T KILL US.
HE'S NOT GOING
TO KILL YOU.
I'M JUST HERE TO MAKE SURE
THAT THE HORRIBLE MAIMING
STAYS AT A MINIMUM.
I'M CURTIS.
EVELYN SHARP.
SO, WAIT,
THERE'S TRAINING?
I'M OUT.
OLIVER: PRETTY EARLY
TO QUIT, MR. RAMIREZ.
I CAN'T QUIT SOMETHING
I HAVEN'T STARTED.
YOU THINK YOU CAN DO
THIS ON YOUR OWN?
I'VE BEEN DOING THIS
ON MY OWN
FOR 5 MONTHS NOW.
AND IF YOU WERE GETTING
IT DONE ON YOUR OWN,
YOU WOULDN'T
HAVE COME HERE.
PFFFT.
I'M OUT OF HERE.
NO MASK?
NO CHANCE.
ON THE LINE.
WAIT. I THOUGHT THERE
WAS GOING TO BE,
I DON'T KNOW,
LIKE AN ORIENTATION.
IS THAT WHAT
THE BROCHURE PROMISED?
HEH HEH HEH!
THAT'S HILAR...
-THAT'S HILARIOUS.
-ON THE LINE!
THIS IS SIMPLE.
GET PAST ME.
RING THAT BELL.
SO WE'RE PLAYING GAMES NOW?
FINE.
I'LL PLAY.
ON THE LINE.
AT LEAST HE'S NOT
SHOOTING THEM.
ON THE LINE.
THIS IS STUPID.
STILL THINK IT'S A GAME?
I CAME HERE TO WORK
WITH THE GUY
WHO KILLED DAMIEN DARHK,
NOT RING
A FREAKING BELL.
THIS ISN'T A GAME,
AND IF YOU NEED
FURTHER EVIDENCE OF THAT,
THEN YOU WALK DOWN
TO THE PIER
AND YOU LOOK
AT THE STATUE
OF LAUREL LANCE.
NOW GET ON THE LINE!
AAH!
[SPEAKING RUSSIAN]
[MEN YELLING]
I'D LOVE TO,
BUT I CAN'T TONIGHT.
TOO MUCH TO DO
FOR THIS MEDICAL EVENT.
YEAH, IT'S GREAT.
JANET AGREED TO IT.
ALL RIGHT,
SEE YOU SATURDAY?
[SIRENS]
HERE YOU GO, BUD.
AAH!
HOW'S THE VICTIM?
VICTIM IS EVAN WENDER.
HE'S IN THE ICU.
DOCTORS THINK THAT HE WAS
SUFFOCATED BY SOMETHING.
IS THAT LINING UP
WITH ANYTHING YOU FOUND?
YOU'RE ASSUMING I'VE
ACTUALLY FOUND ANYTHING.
WHAT'S YOUR INTEREST
IN THIS, ANYWAY?
AMERTEK IS HELPING US
WITH A CHARITY EVENT,
AND ALL OF A SUDDEN,
ONE OF THEIR VICE PRESIDENTS
IS ATTACKED.
IT CANNOT BE
A COINCIDENCE.
[PHONE VIBRATES]
NOT IN THIS CITY.
I HAVE TO GO.
BYE.
THANKS.
WE'RE VERY SORRY ABOUT WHAT
HAPPENED TO MR. WENDER,
BUT I WOULD LIKE YOU TO KNOW
THAT I'VE ASSIGNED
THE ANTI-CRIME UNIT
TO HIS CASE
AND I'VE ASKED THEM
TO MAKE CATCHING
WHOEVER DID THIS
THEIR TOP PRIORITY.
WELL, I APPRECIATE THAT,
BUT IN THE WAKE
OF THIS RECENT
DEVELOPMENT,
MY BOARD OF DIRECTORS...
TO SAY NOTHING
OF AMERTEK'S ARMY
OF ATTORNEYS...
HAVE ADVISED US
TO PULL OUT
OF TOMORROW'S EVENT.
THEY'RE CONCERNED THAT
THE ATTACK ON MR. WENDER
COULD BE THE START
OF A LARGER PATTERN
OF VIOLENCE,
AND IF SOMETHING
WERE TO HAPPEN
DURING THE CLINIC,
THEN AMERTEK WOULD
BE HELD LIABLE.
WHAT IF...
STAR CITY AGREES
TO INDEMNIFY AMERTEK?
OLLIE, THAT COULD
COST MIL...
AND I WILL TRIPLE
THE POLICE PRESENCE
AT THE EVENT.
THERE WILL BE PLENTY
OF SECURITY?
I WILL SEE TO IT
PERSONALLY.
JANET: WELL...
I'M GOING TO HOLD YOU
TO THAT, MR. MAYOR.
THANK YOU.
SO IS THE PLAN
TO SEE TO IT PERSONALLY
WITH THE NEW TEAM?
NO. THEY'RE NOWHERE
NEAR READY.
THEN WHAT'S THE BACKUP PLAN?
ME.
IT'S ONE OF THE ADVANTAGES
OF HAVING THE MAYOR
MOONLIGHTING AS A VIGILANTE.
OR THE VIGILANTE
MOONLIGHTING AS MAYOR.
NO HOSTILES, SIR.
WE'RE A GO.
EXCELLENT.
INTEL WAS GOOD.
HOSTILES ARE
ON A SHIFT CHANGE.
BRAVO TEAM,
YOU'RE UPSTAIRS,
NORTHWEST CORRIDOR,
SECOND FLOOR.
ALPHA TEAM,
YOU'RE WITH ME.
LOOK SHARP.
ALPHA TEAM IS HERE.
BRAVO TEAM,
WHERE ARE YOU?
WHAT'S YOUR...
[GUNFIRE]
COME ON!
MOVE, MOVE, MOVE!
HOW THE HELL DID THEY
KNOW WE WERE HERE?
UP, UP!
ON THE LINE.
I'M HERE TO LEARN
SOMETHING, MAN,
NOT JUST GET BEAT UP.
I TOLD YOU.
I'M TEACHING YOU.
TEACHING US WHAT,
EXACTLY?
BECAUSE, ACTUALLY,
I FIND MYSELF AGREEING
WITH THE SCARY,
WEIRD GUY.
THE GOAL OF THIS EXERCISE
IS TO FIGURE OUT THE GOAL
OF THIS EXERCISE.
NOW GET ON THE LINE!
FELICITY: ACTUALLY,
GREEN ARROW,
CAN I TALK TO YOU
FOR A SECOND?
NOW.
YOU KNOW,
I THOUGHT MAYBE
WE COULD HOLD OFF
ON THE CRITICISM
FOR A LITTLE BIT.
OH, YEAH, NO PROBLEM,
BECAUSE THERE'S A LOT.
LOOK.
I THOUGHT THERE WASN'T
ANY USABLE FOOTAGE
FROM TRAFFIC CAMERAS.
YEAH, BUT WHO NEEDS
TRAFFIC CAMS
WHEN YOU GOT KH-10
SPY SATELLITES?
COULD BE A META
OR MAGIC OF SOME SORT.
EXACTLY.
SO THEA MAY OR MAY NOT
HAVE TOLD ME
ABOUT YOUR
BRILLIANT PLAN
TO PROTECT
THE FREE CLINIC
ALL BY YOURSELF.
I WON'T BE ALL BY MYSELF.
I'LL HAVE
THE SCPD AND THE ACU.
NO WAY.
THIS IS OUT OF BOTH
OF THEIR LEAGUES.
WHAT?
IT'S OUT OF THEIR
LEAGUE, TOO.
THEY'RE TOO GREEN.
SOME COULD SAY
THE SAME ABOUT YOU.
[LAUGHING] I'VE BEEN
WAITING 5 YEARS
TO MAKE THAT JOKE.
THE CONVENTION CENTER
HAS 20 ENTRANCES.
YOU CAN'T
BE ON THEM ALL.
THROW THEM AROUND
THE PERIMETER
FOR 3 EXTRA PAIRS
OF EYES.
WHAT COULD IT HURT?
OLIVER: OK,
HEADS ON SWIVELS,
BUT DO NOT ENGAGE
UNDER ANY CIRCUMSTANCES.
COPY THAT.
YES, SIR.
I MEAN, OLIV...
I MEAN, GREEN ARROW.
WILD DOG,
DO YOU COPY THAT?
WE GOT TO TALK
ABOUT THIS CODENAME.
OLIVER: NOT NOW.
STAY FOCUSED.
YOU KNOW, IT'D HELP
TO KNOW WHERE YOU ARE.
OLIVER: NO, IT WOULDN'T,
BECAUSE YOU'RE NOT
GOING TO ENGAGE.
COME ON, WHERE'S
THE FUN IN THAT?
EVELYN: MAN, IT WOULD
TAKE ONE MAJOR ASSHAT
TO MAKE A MOVE AGAINST
ALL THESE PEOPLE.
CURTIS: SOMETHING
I'VE LEARNED RECENTLY
IS THE CITY IS
FILLED WITH THEM.
STARTS AT THE TOP,
YOU KNOW?
PRETTY BOY QUEEN HERE
THINKS HE'S ACTUALLY
SAVING THE CITY.
THANK YOU,
OFFICER.
HOW ARE YOU?
HELLO.
HI.
DOCTOR: HI.
WHAT HAVE WE HERE?
HER BROKEN BONE
NEVER SET.
OH, YOU'LL BE FINE.
I HAVE SOME EXPERIENCE
WITH THAT.
EVELYN, CHECK
THE NORTHWEST CORRIDOR.
I DON'T GET A CODENAME?
WE REALLY THANK YOU
FOR STICKING WITH US.
OH, WELL, I'M GLAD THAT
OLIVER CHANGED MY MIND.
IT'S NICE TO FEEL
THAT THIS COMPANY
CAN STILL DO SOME GOOD.
UM, SORRY I'M LATE.
IF YOU'LL EXCUSE ME.
THE EVENT IS ALMOST OVER.
YEAH, I KNOW,
BUT IT'S BEEN TYING UP
TRAFFIC, YOU KNOW?
YEAH, BUT YOU WERE
SUPPOSED TO WATCH
THE 10TH STREET
ENTRANCE.
I JUST SAID,
THE TRAFFIC IS TERRIBLE.
ARE YOU OK?
YEAH. YEAH, YEAH, I'M...
I'M FINE, YOU KNOW.
SORRY, IT WON'T
HAPPEN AGAIN.
YEAH, BUT...
YOU HAVEN'T BEEN
DRINKING AGAIN,
HAVE YOU?
[JANET SCREAMING]
JANET CARROLL,
YOU HAVE BEEN JUDGED
AND FOUND WANTING.
HE'S HERE.
[CROWD SCREAMING]
SON OF A BITCH.
OLIVER: OVERWATCH?
I DON'T SEE HIM ON ANY
OF THE SECURITY CAMERAS.
IT'S LIKE HE JUST...
DISAPPEARED.
I WOULDN'T BELIEVE IT
IF I DIDN'T SEE HIM DO
ALL THAT OTHER STUFF
THAT I DON'T BELIEVE.
CURTIS: I'M ALMOST
AFRAID TO ASK...
ACTUALLY,
I AM AFRAID TO ASK...
YOU KNOW, MAYBE
I'M JUST AFRAID.
IS HE COMING?
HE'S ON HIS WAY.
DID HE SOUND...
UNHAPPY?
WHY DID YOU DO THAT,
ANYWAY?
HE SPECIFICALLY TOLD US
NOT TO ENGAGE!
FIRST, HE'S NOT
THE BOSS OF ME,
NEVER WILL BE.
SECOND, IF HE THINKS I'M
JUST GOING TO STAND BACK
AND WATCH SOME
LITTLE GIRL GET HURT,
THEN HE NEVER SHOULD
HAVE RECRUITED ME
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
I THINK THAT'S
QUICKLY BECOMING
THE MAJORITY OPINION.
THIRD, IF I HADN'T
DONE WHAT I DID,
I WOULDN'T HAVE
GOTTEN THIS.
WAIT, IS THAT
A PIECE...
YEAH, THE RAG MAN.
NOW, I MAY BE NEW
AT THIS AND ALL,
BUT ISN'T THAT WHAT
YOU GUYS CALL "EVIDENCE"?
OLIVER: ON THE LINE.
LISTEN, BEFORE
YOU SAY ANYTHING,
I THINK...
MY INSTRUCTIONS
WERE SPECIFIC.
BY NOT LISTENING,
YOU PUT EVERY ONE
OF OUR LIVES AT RISK.
YOU NEED TO CALM DOWN...
NOW, I KNOW
THAT NONE OF YOU
ARE READY FOR THIS,
BUT NOW I'M NOT SURE IF
YOU'RE EVER GOING TO BE,
BECAUSE YOU
ARE RECKLESS,
YOU'RE USELESS IF YOU'RE
NOT BEHIND A COMPUTER,
AND YOU ARE JUST
A LITTLE GIRL
WHO SHOULD BE DOING
SOMETHING BETTER
WITH HER LIFE!
FELICITY:
OK, THAT'S ENOUGH
PEP TALK FOR ONE DAY.
CAN I TALK TO YOU
FOR A SECOND?
DID YOU LEARN NOTHING
FROM WHAT HAPPENED
TO CURTIS LAST YEAR?
NOW, YOU KNOW I DON'T
HAVE A BEDSIDE MANNER.
THERE'S HAVING
NO BEDSIDE MANNER,
AND THEN THERE IS BEING
PHYSICALLY
AND EMOTIONALLY ABUSIVE.
IT TOOK ME YEARS 5 IN HELL
TO TURN INTO SOMEONE
CAPABLE OF GOING OUT THERE.
YOU KNOW WHO DIDN'T
HAVE 5 YEARS?
LAUREL LANCE.
AND NOW SHE'S DEAD.
OH, WERE THOSE 5 YEARS
JUST FULL OF PAIN
AND SUFFERING,
OR DID YOU HAVE SOMEONE
WHO TAUGHT YOU?
I HAD A FEW PEOPLE
WHO TAUGHT ME,
AND I'M TRYING
TO TEACH THEM.
WHAT, TO TAKE A PUNCH?
AN INSULT?
YOU KEEP EXPECTING THEM
TO DO WHAT YOU'RE
TELLING THEM TO DO,
AND THEN YOU'RE NOT
GIVING THEM ANY REASON.
YOU JUST KEEP JABBING
THEM WITH A CATTLE PROD,
EXPECTING THEM
TO PERFORM,
AND THE GUY THAT YOU
CALLED RECKLESS
GOT US OUR ONLY CLUE
WE HAVE SO FAR.
I NEED YOU TO DO
A FULL WORKUP ON THAT.
YEAH, WELL, I CAN'T.
I MEAN, NOT HERE.
THE GHOSTS DESTROYED
OUR GAS CHROMATOGRAPH,
BUT I HAVE
OTHER METHODS.
GOOD.
I HAVE TO GET TO CITY HALL.
WHAT ABOUT THEM?
THE CITY JUST EXPERIENCED
THE EQUIVALENT
OF A TERRORIST ATTACK.
THOSE 3 CAN WAIT.
JOHN: YOU SHOULD GET
TO THE MEDIC TENT
WHEN WE GET BACK,
BUT THIS SHOULD HOLD YOU
FOR A FEW HOURS.
A FEW HOURS?
WHY, WE'RE NOT BUGGING OUT?
OUR ORDERS ARE
TO GET THAT TRIGGER.
THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT
WE'RE GOING TO DO.
THE MEN ARE ON
THE SECOND FLOOR.
WE HAVE NO IDEA HOW MANY
GUYS ARE UP THERE.
YOU REMEMBER WHAT I
TOLD YOU ABOUT FEAR?
GETS YOU THROUGH.
THAT'S RIGHT.
AND SO DOES
THE CHAIN OF COMMAND.
WE DON'T HAVE TO THINK
ABOUT DO OR DON'T
OR RIGHT OR WRONG.
THERE'S A CLARITY
IN THAT, RIGHT?
A PEACE.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND?
FALL OUT.
SECURE THE SOUTH HALLWAYS.
I'LL TAKE THE NORTH.
MAN: CONTACTS WILL
BE HERE ANY MINUTE,
SO LET'S KEEP OUR HEADS
ON SWIVELS, LADIES.
JOHN: THOUGHT YOU GUYS
WERE EITHER DEAD OR GONE.
COLLINS TOOK
A THROUGH-AND-THROUGH.
HE'LL BE FINE, BUT...
[GUN COCKS]
WHAT THE HELL
IS GOING ON HERE?
I'M REALLY SORRY
ABOUT THIS, SERGEANT.
YOU'RE NOT HERE
TO SECURE THE TRIGGER.
YOU'RE STEALING IT.
CAN'T STEAL ANYTHING
IF NOBODY OWNS IT.
NOW, YOU BE CAREFUL NOW,
SERGEANT.
YOU JUST MIGHT
LIVE THROUGH THIS.
FELICITY: NOT THAT I
WOULD NORMALLY CONDONE
DRINKING THIS
MUCH CAFFEINE,
BUT SINCE YOU ARE
SO BUSY TRYING TO SAVE
THE ENTIRE CITY
AND ALL...
ADD IT TO THE LIST OF VICES
I'VE BEEN MEANING
TO SWEAR OFF.
OH, DO I EVEN
WANT TO KNOW?
JUST AS MUCH
AS I WANT TO KNOW
WHY YOU'RE REALLY HERE.
YOU ALREADY BOUGHT ME
AN AMERICANO THIS MORNING
BEFORE I GOT TO WORK.
AND THAT'S WHY YOU
ARE THE DETECTIVE.
IT'S BEEN A WHILE
SINCE I DATED ANYONE.
IS THIS A THING NOW?
NO, THIS IS NOT A THING.
THIS IS...THIS IS...
A VERY LONG,
FUNNY STORY.
DO YOU...
WANT TO TELL ME
THIS STORY?
YEAH. THAT'S WHY
I'M HERE.
UM, THIS BELONGED
TO MY FRIEND'S MAID...
CLEANING LADY.
YOUR FRIEND'S
CLEANING LADY?
SHE'S GONE MISSING.
AND HE'S VERY WORRIED
ABOUT HER.
YOU WANT ME TO MAKE A REPORT
TO MISSING PERSONS?
NO, NO, NO.
I WAS THINKING THAT...
WELL, SHE LEFT
THIS RAG BEHIND,
SO I WAS THINKING THERE
MIGHT BE SOME EVIDENCE
LEFT BEHIND ON IT
THAT, UM...
COULD HELP MY
FRIEND LOCATE
HER CLEANING LADY.
I THOUGHT YOUR FRIEND
WAS A GUY?
ARE YOU JEALOUS?
ONLY INSOFAR AS I HAVEN'T
ACTUALLY MET
ANY OF YOUR FRIENDS YET.
AND, YES, THAT'S A HINT
OFFICIALLY BEING DROPPED.
HINT NOTED.
SO JUST A QUICK
FORENSIC WORKUP,
LIKE MAYBE JUST
A QUICK PASS
THROUGH THE GAS
CHROMATOGRAPH?
FINE.
IT'S YOUR TAX DOLLARS.
YOU ARE THE BEST.
THEA, MAY I SPEAK...
-HI.
I WAS JUST LEAVING.
IS EVERYTHING OK?
UH, YEAH, YEAH,
EVERYTHING'S FINE.
I WAS JUST
TALKING TO THEA
ABOUT MAYBE COMING ABOARD,
HELPING OUT
WITH SOME STUFF.
YEAH.
YEAH, ANYWAYS.
SO, UM...ANYWAY,
I'LL SEE YOU TOMORROW.
OK.
UH, THANKS.
WHAT WAS THAT ABOUT?
IT...IT'S NOTHING.
LOOK, WE HAVE
WAY BIGGER PROBLEMS
ON OUR PLATE RIGHT NOW.
BECAUSE OF YOU,
WE ARE ON THE HOOK
WITH AMERTEK,
AND THE C.E.O.
IS IN THE HOSPITAL.
ACTUALLY,
SHE WAS JUST RELEASED.
SHE'S FINE.
OK, BUT SHE'S GOING
TO HIT THE CITY
WITH A MULTI-MILLION-
DOLLAR LAWSUIT.
WELL, CAN YOU SPEAK TO HER?
MY HANDS ARE KIND OF
FULL RIGHT NOW.
OK. WHAT ELSE IS NEW?
WHAT IS GOING ON
WITH QUENTIN?
I AM 90% SURE
HE'S DRINKING AGAIN.
I'M 100% SURE.
HE TOLD ME WHEN I SAW
HIM LAST WEEK.
OLLIE, I PUT HIM TO WORK
SECURITY AT THE EVENT.
THE DUDE IN RAGS CAME IN
THROUGH THE DOOR
HE WAS SUPPOSED
TO BE WORKING.
THEA, I'M SORRY.
I HAD NO IDEA THAT YOU WERE
GOING TO REACH OUT TO HIM,
BUT WHY IS HE TALKING
LIKE HE'S GOING
TO BE WORKING WITH US?
"I'LL SEE YOU TOMORROW"?
WHAT IS THAT?
HE'S HURTING, OLLIE.
I DON'T THINK
THAT PUTTING HIM
IN A POSITION
OF RESPONSIBILITY
IS THE BEST IDEA FOR HIM
OR FOR US RIGHT NOW.
OK?
I'LL TALK TO HIM.
[PHONE BEEPS AND VIBRATES]
I HAVE TO GO. THANK YOU.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHERE ARE OTHERS?
SOMEWHERE NOT HERE.
THEY QUIT.
THIS REALLY
SHOULDN'T COME
AS ANY SORT
OF SURPRISE TO YOU.
IT'S NOT SURPRISING.
WE CHOSE
THE WRONG PEOPLE.
INCLUDING ME, RIGHT?
CURTIS.
DO YOU KNOW
WHAT THE PURPOSE
OF THIS EXERCISE IS?
TO FIGURE OUT THE PURPOSE
OF THIS EXERCISE?
NO, IT'S TO WORK TOGETHER,
BECAUSE THAT'S THE ONLY
WAY THAT YOU WIN.
THAT IS WHAT I HAVE BEEN
TRYING TO TEACH ALL OF YOU.
WELL, MAYBE THERE'S
A REASON WHY YOU COULDN'T.
WE DON'T TRUST YOU.
THAT'S ON YOU.
NO, MAN.
BECAUSE YOU DON'T
TRUST US,
BECAUSE YOU DON'T WANT US.
OK, THIS IS A SETBACK,
BUT WE CAN SALVAGE THIS.
THEY'LL LISTEN TO YOU.
CAN YOU JUST TELL THEM
HOW OLIVER USUALLY
APPROACHES THINGS AND...
I TRIED THAT.
I TOLD THEM ALL ABOUT
HOW YOU AND SPEEDY
AND SPARTAN WERE A FAMILY,
AND EVEN THOUGH YOU WERE
TOUGH AND SCARY
AND EVEN A LITTLE ABUSIVE,
THEY CLEARLY TRUSTED YOU
BECAUSE THEY STOOD BY YOU.
BUT THEN IT HIT ME.
NO, THEY DIDN'T.
THEY LEFT,
AND NOW I KNOW WHY.
YOU DON'T RESPECT PEOPLE.
YOU DON'T KNOW
HOW TO HAVE PARTNERS.
YOU DON'T BUILD
PEOPLE UP.
YOU TEAR THEM DOWN.
I THOUGHT I COULD
TRUST YOU...
WE COULD TRUST YOU.
I WAS WRONG.
AND THAT'S WHY
I'M OUT, TOO.
FELICITY: FIGURED
I'D FIND YOU HERE.
YOU WERE RIGHT.
AS MUCH AS I USUALLY
LOVE HEARING
THOSE 3 LITTLE WORDS,
GLOATING RIGHT NOW WOULD
BE LIKE KICKING A PUPPY.
I FAILED THESE RECRUITS
AS A LEADER.
WELL, THAT'S BECAUSE
YOU'RE NOT A LEADER.
WELL, IN YOUR DEFENSE,
YOU NEVER SET OUT TO BE.
YOU NEVER PLANNED ON
DOING THIS WITH PARTNERS.
THOUGH, I DON'T THINK
YOU REALLY EVER HAD A WAY
AROUND THAT ONE.
HOW SO?
WHEN I GOT TO KNOW YOU...
THE REAL YOU...
I WAS IN AWE.
I HAD NEVER MET SOMEBODY
SO PASSIONATE...
SO FOCUSED AND DETERMINED
TO MAKE A REAL DIFFERENCE.
BUT THE RECRUITS
DIDN'T GET TO SEE
THE REAL YOU
BECAUSE ALL YOU SHOWED THEM
WAS THIS ANGRY GUY
IN A MASK,
LIKE SCARY ANGRY.
I JUST THOUGHT THAT IF THEY
DIDN'T KNOW WHO I WAS,
IT WOULD MAKE THINGS EASIER.
HOW WOULD THAT MAKE
THINGS EASIER FOR THEM?
FOR ME.
EASIER FOR ME.
WHEN I WAS
IN THE BRATVA...
YOU NEVER TALK ABOUT
YOUR TIME IN RUSSIA.
NOBODY IN THE BRATVA
USES THEIR REAL NAMES.
NOBODY KNOWS ANYTHING
ABOUT ANYONE'S LIFE
BEFORE THEY WERE BRATVA.
SOUNDS LONELY.
IT'S EFFECTIVE.
THEY TEACH YOU THAT
THE ONLY PERSON
YOU CAN TRUST
IS YOURSELF,
THAT WITHOUT
PERSONAL ATTACHMENT,
THERE CAN BE NO LOSS.
LAUREL, THEA,
DIG, EVEN ROY.
I LET THEM INTO MY CRUSADE.
I LET THEM IN...
THEN THEY LEFT.
I WAS PROTECTING MYSELF.
I JUST THINK YOU'RE
MISSING SOMETHING.
ONLY ONE THING?
THE REASON THE ORIGINAL
TEAM WORKED SO WELL...
WAS BECAUSE OF THE TRUST
AND RESPECT
THAT EVERYONE HAD
FOR OLIVER QUEEN,
NOT THE GREEN ARROW.
OLIVER IS THE ONE
WHO MAKES A GOOD LEADER.
HE'S THE ONE
THAT RUNS A GOOD TEAM.
HE'S THE ONE THAT
I CHOSE TO STAND BY
AND THAT I CONTINUE
TO CHOOSE TO STAND BY.
[PHONE VIBRATES]
I GOT TO TAKE THIS.
[SPEAKING RUSSIAN]
HEY, HEY.
IF WE CAN LURE THEM
TO THE LEFT,
WE MAY HAVE A CHANCE.
NO, WE NEED TO DIVERT
THEIR ATTENTION,
AND THEN ONE OF US
SNEAKS PAST,
AND WE RING THE BELL.
[BELL RINGS]
CONGRATULATIONS, OLIVER.
WELL, IT LOOKS LIKE
WE HAVE OUR WORK
CUT OUT FOR US
GETTING AMERTEK
BACK IN OUR GOOD GRACES.
I COULDN'T EVEN GET PAST
THE RECEPTION DESK.
SO WE NEED TO GET THIS
HANDLED WITH...WHAT?
YOU KNOW,
JUST CALL ME BACK
WHENEVER YOU GET THIS.
JANET:
I'M SORRY I'M LATE.
IT COULDN'T BE HELPED.
HELP IT NEXT TIME.
I DON'T LIKE WAITING.
ARE WE ALL SET
FOR TONIGHT?
JANET: WE ARE
IF YOU HAVE THE MONEY.
$100 MILLION...
FOR EVERYTHING I NEED
TO TAKE OVER THIS CITY.
MR. CHURCH,
I'M SELLING YOU
ENOUGH ORDINANCE
TO TAKE OVER A COUNTRY.
SONS OF BITCHES ARE LATE.
GO TOPSIDE.
SEE IF YOU CAN GET
A VISUAL.
JOHN:
DON'T YOU JUST HATE
WHEN YOUR PLAN
TO STEAL ILLEGAL
NUCLEAR TECHNOLOGY
HITS A SNAG?
SO THAT AMBUSH,
THAT WAS YOU?
YOU HAD YOUR OWN MEN,
SOLDIERS, BROTHERS
WALK INTO A TRAP?
AND I'LL CARRY THAT WITH ME
TILL THE DAY I DIE.
BUT TILL THAT DAY COMES,
I'M GOING TO BE A VERY,
VERY WEALTHY MAN.
YOU SWORE AN OATH, MAN!
THEN GENESIS DAY HAPPENED!
ISIS, TALIBAN, AL QAEDA.
I CAN TAKE THEM ALL ON,
BUT WHAT HOPE
DOES THE WORLD HAVE
AGAINST MEN WITH MAGIC?
OR THOSE METAHUMANS
IN CENTRAL CITY?
HOW LONG BEFORE ONE OF THEM
MANAGES TO TEAR
THE WORLD APART?
SERGEANT,
WHAT'S GOING ON?
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
JOHN: NO!
NO, YOU SON OF A BITCH!
YOU SON OF A BITCH!
WALKER: YOU KNOW,
I'VE BEEN PUZZLING OUT
WHY NONE OF MY CONTACTS
HAVE SHOWED UP
AND FRETTING THAT MAYBE
THIS WHOLE THING
HAS GONE A LITTLE BIT
SIDEWAYS.
I WONDERED
WHAT TO DO ABOUT IT.
THEN YOU SHOWED UP
TO SOLVE MY PROBLEM.
THANKS.
OLIVER: SO ARE YOU SURE
THAT IT WAS THEM?
THEA: YEAH,
THAT SON OF A BITCH
LEAVES A PRETTY
GOOD IMPRESSION.
WELL, IF AMERTEK IS
IN BED WITH CHURCH, THEN...
THEN MAYBE THAT GUY IN RAGS
ISN'T SO BAD
BECAUSE HE'S PROBABLY TRYING
TO TAKE DOWN AMERTEK.
STILL, WHY IS THE C.E.O.
OF A FORTUNE 500 COMPANY
LIKE AMERTEK
WILLING TO DEAL WEAPONS
TO A CRIME LORD?
BECAUSE THEY ARE TRYING
TO AVOID BANKRUPTCY.
I GOT THE FORENSIC
WORKUP BACK
ON THAT PIECE OF CLOTH
FROM RAGMAN.
THEA: PLEASE TELL ME
THAT'S NOT
WHAT WE'RE ACTUALLY
GOING TO CALL HIM.
WHAT'D YOU FIND?
THAT IT IS OVER
2,000 YEARS OLD AND...
RADIOACTIVE.
WHICH MEANS TRACKABLE.
IF THIS WEAPONS BUY
IS GOING DOWN,
THIS GUY IS GOING
TO TRY TO STOP IT.
LEADING US RIGHT TO
JANET CARROLL AND MR. CHURCH.
WAIT. WHAT DID YOU MEAN
WHEN YOU SAID
THAT AMERTEK
IS GOING BANKRUPT?
THE ISOTOPE THAT MADE
THE CLOTH RADIOACTIVE
IS VERY SPECIFIC.
IT CAME FROM ONE
OF THE NUKES
THAT DARHK LAUNCHED
ON GENESIS DAY,
SPECIFICALLY A NUKE
MANUFACTURED BY A COMPANY
CALLED ATOMIC
DEFENSIVE SYSTEMS.
THEY'RE LIKELY
A SUBSIDIARY OF AMERTEK.
AW, AND PEOPLE SAY
HE'S JUST A PRETTY FACE.
THE BOTTOM LINE IS
THE SUBSIDIARY'S CONNECTION
WITH GENESIS DAY
HAS MADE AMERTEK'S
STOCK PRICES GO...
[IMITATES EXPLOSION]
WHICH EXPLAINS WHY
THEY WERE SO EAGER
TO HAVE A BIG
PUBLIC RELATIONS BONANZA.
AND WHY THEY'D
BE WILLING
TO UNLOAD THEIR
EXCESS ORDINANCE
ON TOBIAS CHURCH.
WE NEED TO FIND
OUR FRIEND IN THE RAGS
AND HOPE HE LEADS US
TO THAT WEAPONS SALE.
UH, THEY DID JUST SAY
THAT THERE WAS
ENOUGH WEAPONRY
TO TAKE DOWN
AN ENTIRE COUNTRY,
SO I WOULD THINK THIS
WOULD BE A GOOD TIME
FOR YOU TO TEST OUT
YOUR NEW TEAM.
THERE'S NO TEAM
ANYMORE, THEA.
IF I'M GOING IN,
I'M GOING ALONE.
[MAN YELLS]
THIS IS THE SPOT.
FELICITY: THERE'S A CRAZY
AMOUNT OF HOSTILES INSIDE.
I SAY "CRAZY"
BECAUSE THAT IS WHAT
YOU WOULD HAVE TO BE
TO TAKE THEM ON
ALL ALONE.
JANET: ALL RIGHT.
YOU HAVE YOUR MERCHANDISE.
CHURCH: AND NOW
YOU WANT YOUR MONEY.
WHAT KIND OF DENT
CAN $100 MILLION MAKE
IN YOUR BALANCE SHEET?
THAT'S MY WORRY.
NO...
I THINK THAT'S YOUR
GOLDEN PARACHUTE,
AND I ADMIRE THAT.
[MAN SCREAMS]
HELLO, JANET.
EASY. THAT MAN ABOUT
TO SAVE US $100 MILLION.
RAGMAN: THEY ALL
DIED IN FIRE.
YOUR FIRE.
YOUR WEAPON.
ALL FOR YOUR MONEY.
WHERE YOU AT?
[GUNFIRE]
[MAN SCREAMS]
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
I'M TALKING
ABOUT THE KN-08.
YOUR PRIDE AND JOY.
OVER 15,000 MISSILES
LAUNCHED ON GENESIS DAY.
ONLY ONE FOUND ITS MARK.
YOURS.
NO, NO, WE...WE BUILT
THOSE MISSILES
TO KEEP PEOPLE SAFE.
IT...IT WAS DAMIEN.
IT WAS DAMIEN DARHK.
COULDN'T HAVE DONE
ANYTHING
IF YOU HADN'T
GIVEN HIM THE TOOLS!
YOUR MISSILE KILLED
EVERYONE IN MY HOME.
I AM THE VERY LAST LIVING SOUL
OF HAVENROCK...
AND I CARRY WITH ME
A MESSAGE
FROM ALL THOSE SOULS
YOU KILLED.
NO! NO!
OLIVER: RAGMAN!
THANK YOU.
THANK ME BY NOT
STANDING IN MY WAY.
LET HER GO!
[SIRENS]
IT'S OVER.
THANK YOU FOR COMING.
YOUR OFFER SOUNDED
INTRIGUING.
WHY DID YOU MAKE IT?
WHY'D YOU GIVE UP
YOUR VENGEANCE
TO SAVE MY LIFE?
I DON'T KNOW.
I THINK IT'S WHAT MY FATHER
WOULD HAVE WANTED ME TO DO.
HE SAVED MY LIFE.
ON GENESIS DAY, HE...
WRAPPED ME IN THESE RAGS,
SAID THEY WERE ANCIENT,
FROM THE TIME OF DEVARIM,
THAT THEY WOULD
PROTECT ME FROM THE FIRE.
AND THEY DID.
SO YOU SEE WHY I
HAVE TO AVENGE HIM.
YOUR FATHER DIDN'T
GIVE UP HIS LIFE
SO YOU COULD
BECOME A KILLER.
YOU DON'T KNOW THAT.
MY FATHER GAVE UP
HIS LIFE TO SAVE MINE.
HE MADE ME PROMISE
TO BE BETTER THAN HIM,
TO SAVE THIS CITY
IN A WAY THAT
HE NEVER COULD.
IT'S BEEN NEARLY
10 YEARS SINCE THAT DAY.
SO FAR, I'VE FAILED.
WHY ARE YOU TELLING ME THIS?
BECAUSE I DON'T WANT
TO FAIL ANYMORE.
I CAN'T DO IT ALONE.
I NEED A TEAM.
LET'S HONOR THE LEGACIES
OF OUR FATHERS...
TOGETHER.
WHY, ANATOLY?
WHY KILL THEM?
YOU RANG BELL.
THEY DID NOT.
I ONLY RANG THE BELL
BECAUSE OF THEM.
I COULDN'T HAVE
DONE IT ALONE.
BUT USING TEAM
WAS YOUR IDEA.
YOU USE THEM TO WIN.
INTELLIGENT.
BRATVA WANTS THAT.
BRATVA NEED THAT.
I NEVER WOULD
HAVE DONE IT
IF I HAD KNOWN IT
WAS GOING TO COST
THEM THEIR LIVES.
FIRST PART OF INITIATION:
ONLY PERSON
YOU CAN TRUST...
YOURSELF.
YOU SEEM TO HAVE
REOPENED WOUND, FRIEND.
WHAT THE HELL?
STILL THINK YOU CAN WRITE
WITH YOUR CUFFS ON?
I MEAN, IT WOULDN'T BE MUCH,
JUST A SIGNATURE.
YOU WANT TO READ
YOUR CONFESSION
BEFORE YOU SIGN IT?
SCREW YOU!
NOW, SERGEANT,
I AM OFFERING YOU
AN OPPORTUNITY HERE.
I'M NOT OWNING UP TO THIS.
YOU DID THIS.
YEAH, BUT I USED YOUR GUN
TO SHOOT PRIVATE COLLINS.
APPARENTLY, HE WALKED IN
ON YOUR ATTEMPTED ILLEGAL
APPROPRIATION OF WMD
FOR YOUR OWN PERSONAL GAIN.
I GOT 6 MEN OUT THERE
WHO'LL TESTIFY TO THAT.
NO ONE WILL EVER
BELIEVE YOUR STORY.
I WILL.
GOOD LUCK WITH
YOUR COURT-MARTIAL.
OH, PLEASE COME IN,
SORRY.
SIT DOWN, AND I WILL
BE RIGHT WITH YOU.
OK.
THANK YOU FOR COMING.
UM, YEAH, WELL,
I ALMOST DIDN'T...
BECAUSE, YOU KNOW, I...
I SCREWED UP, DIDN'T I,
AND PEOPLE GOT HURT.
IT SEEMS LIKE YOU
FIGURED IT OUT THAT, UM,
YOU KNOW, I'M DRINKING
AGAIN, AND...
AND, YOU KNOW, I JUST...
I DON'T WANT TO BE
ANY...ANY TROUBLE.
I'M JUST SORRY IT...
SORRY IT DIDN'T
WORK OUT, YOU KNOW.
OK, QUENTIN, THAT'S...
THAT'S NOT GOING
TO WORK FOR ME.
WHAT?
YOU LEAVING AND HITTING
THE BOTTLE AGAIN, OK?
NO, I THINK WE CAN
DO BETTER THAN THAT.
I'VE BEEN TO MEETINGS.
NOT A MEETING.
A JOB.
HOW DOES
DEPUTY MAYOR SOUND?
YOU WANT TO...YOU WANT
TO HIRE A DRUNK
TO BE YOUR
DEPUTY MAYOR, HUH?
WHAT, OLIVER'S APPROVAL
RATINGS ARE NOT LOW ENOUGH?
IF WE WERE HIRING
A DRUNK,
THAT WOULD BE
A VERY GOOD POINT,
BUT THAT IS NOT
WHAT WE ARE DOING.
WE ARE HIRING
THE FORMER CAPTAIN
OF THE SCPD WHO...
WHO JUST LOST
HIS DAUGHTER
AND IS HONORING
HER MEMORY
BY DEDICATING
HIMSELF TO THE CITY
THAT SHE LOVED.
OK, WHAT DO YOU THINK
ABOUT THAT ONE?
I THINK MAYBE THE WRONG
QUEEN RAN FOR MAYOR.
LOOK, OLLIE,
HE TOLD ME YOU SAID
THAT YOU NEEDED A REASON
TO STAY SOBER, SO...
I THOUGHT MAYBE
THIS COULD BE IT.
YEAH, MAYBE IT COULD.
YOU LET CHURCH
ALMOST KILL YOU
SO THAT YOU COULD
RECRUIT RAGMAN?
I WAS BETTING
THAT HIS HEROISM
WOULD TRUMP HIS VENGEANCE.
THAT'S A BIG RISK
TO TAKE ON A STRANGER,
DON'T YOU THINK?
YEAH.
WELL, I'M NOT DONE YET.
HEY.
-YEAH.
-ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
YEAH. FINE.
THANK YOU ALL FOR COMING.
RENE: I ONLY CAME
BECAUSE BLONDIE SAID
THERE'D BE AN APOLOGY.
WELL, BLONDIE
MADE A GOOD POINT.
YOU'RE NOT JUST JOINING
UP WITH THE GREEN ARROW.
YOU'D BE JOINING UP
WITH ME.
THE GREEN ARROW
IS THE MAYOR?
CURTIS: I HAD THE SAME
COGNITIVE DISSONANCE.
RENE: I HOPE YOU DON'T
THINK I'M GOING
TO APOLOGIZE
FOR THE TRASH
I TALKED ABOUT YOU.
NO MORE THAN I'M GOING
TO APOLOGIZE
FOR THE TOUGH TRAINING,
BUT I UNDERSTAND
THAT YOU ALL NEED
TO TRUST ME.
THIS IS AS FAR
AS I KNOW HOW TO GO.
YOU'RE SORT OF ASKING
WITHOUT ASKING
IF WE WANT TO COME
BACK, RIGHT?
THAT'S EXACTLY
WHAT HE'S DOING.
OK. GOOD.
THEN I'M IN.
ME, TOO.
WILD DOG?
I'LL FIGHT ANY WAR
AS LONG AS I TRUST WHO'S
LEADING ME INTO BATTLE...
BUT WE HAVE GOT
TO RETHINK THIS CODENAME.
NO CHANCE.
[DANCE MUSIC PLAYING]
HEH HEH HEH!
AH...
CAN'T STAY AWAY
FROM ME, CAN YOU?
YOU ALMOST KILLED
THE GREEN ARROW
THE OTHER NIGHT.
IF YOU HAD,
YOU'D BE DEAD RIGHT NOW.
WHO THE HELL...
THE GREEN ARROW IS MINE.
YOU KILL HIM, YOU DIE.
WHO ARE YOU?
PROMETHEUS.