Previously on "Arrow"...
I need you to help me
find my son.
The men your son
investigated,
when they discovered
his arrest,
they broke into prison,
take him.
They are called
the Jackals.
You let my boy go.
We need your son.
After all,
he's our boss.
Hello, father.
It's been
a long time.
Kane: You should
have stayed dead.
I heard you were
in trouble, kid.
And so I thought I'd
offer my help.
My old man here
to save me.
Last I saw,
you weren't
all that concerned
with saving anyone.
Apple doesn't fall
that far.
What do you think?
Patricide?
Nylander: He's seen
our operation.
It makes him
a liability.
Yeah, you can have
that choice,
but I'll give you
another one.
Let me join you.
Kane: If I wanted
a family reunion,
I would've sent
an invitation.
Maybe you did,
but you just haven't
realized it yet, kid.
See, I came all this way
to talk with you,
and I will kill anybody
who gets in my way
because I got nothing
left to lose, only you.
So go ahead
and make a decision.
I'd be lying
if I said
I wasn't swayed by
the poetry of it all,
but can I trust you?
Trust is built
upon honesty.
I am sure you have a lot
of questions to ask me,
and I've got a lot of
questions for you, Joe.
That's not
my name anymore.
Your mother named you
something different
to keep us apart.
Ok.
Guess we got some
catching up to do.
[Rifle is put in safe mode]
[Labored breathing]
[Sounds of explosions]
I'm not leaving you.
Joe: Father...
Joe.
How are you feeling?
How did I get here?
Evac found
you washed up
on the Philippine
coast.
They said you were
barely conscious,
just muttering
someone's name--
Oliver.
Who's he?
[Shuddering]
Father.
S--someone that owed me
a debt.
Everyone left you
for dead...
But I knew you'd
come back.
I will never leave you
again, Joe.
I promise.
[Opens comms line]
Wild Dog, Terrific,
you ready to do this?
Rene: Always.
But I got bad news.
These guys
aren't just thieves.
They killed
a security guard.
Make that two.
These guys aren't
playing around.
Neither are we.
[Whistle]
Incoming! Fall back!
Now!
Curtis, you were right.
The thieves were after the components
of a 3-d printer.
Two innocent
people get killed
because some psycho
wants to print plastic toys?
This wasn't a consumer 3-D printer.
This was military grade.
You saying there's a printer that
can print weapons?
Or drones or chemicals.
Dinah: Sorry I missed the fun.
Anyone want to catch me up?
John: Break-in,
Cadmus Tech.
Dinah: You're thinking
Cayden James?
That's what we were
assuming, but this crew
doesn't look like the type
he usually runs with.
That would track with
some new street chatter
SCPD's
been hearing lately.
- What kind of chatter?
- New player.
No idea
what his game is.
All we have is a
street name--Dragon.
Dragon. Heh.
That's colorful.
Tomorrow's problem.
Why don't we all get
some rack time,
hit this fresh
in the morning?
♪ Arrow 6x06 ♪
Promises Kept
Original Air Date on November 16, 2017
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Kane: Excuse the poor
accommodations.
I don't plan on staying
in this stain of
a country too long.
Well, there's a reason
why they say
the money is
in the muck.
I did bring one
luxury, however.
Oh, there's a blast
from the past.
My favorite.
I never realized
you'd acquired
a taste for it, too.
Like you told me, always
drink good booze...
And only look out
for yourself.
Well, the Jackals are
an unruly bunch.
Must have been hard
trying to keep A.S.I.S.
in the dark for so long.
It's amazing what
an agency overlooks
when it's willing
to leave its own men for dead.
[Chuckles,
slides bottle on table]
So what kind of operation
are you planning
on running here?
Drugs? Weapons?
Perhaps a military coup.
Let's call it
a reassignment
of resources.
A lucrative one.
Hey, babe.
Hey.
I didn't want
to wake you.
I'm still on
Vlatava time.
Besides,
I heard a rumor
that the Green Arrow
was going to be here,
and I never miss
a chance to see him.
You know, when you
took this on,
I think I got a pretty
good sense of how you felt
when I took Amanda Waller's
place at Argus.
Not that bad, I hope.
But seeing you like this,
being the Green Arrow...
It suits you.
Let's go to bed.
Hey, hey.
Let me clean up first.
Ok.
Don't be too long.
So you
and your boy,
one big happy
family again, huh?
That's none of
your business,
but he told me
about your new job--
the reassignment
of resources.
Tell me about that.
Well, if the boss didn't
think to tell you,
then that means it's none
of your business, Kamrat.
Meeting hall, 30 minutes.
Oliver: Slade.
What are you doing here?
You should have gone home.
I don't abandon
people,
even when they
leave me drugged.
Now, what is
this reassignment
of resources
that your son and his
men are planning?
You overheard that.
Just like I overheard
you're planning
to join his unit.
Your son
is dangerous, Slade.
He's just a younger
version of me.
No. You were never
a gun for hire.
But I was a killer.
Listen, kid,
you'd better go home
before you find yourself
in trouble
you can't get out of.
I can't walk away
from this.
Can you?
Nylander: Feeling
at home yet, Slade, hmm?
Or should I call you
Deathstroke?
Slight change
in plans, gentlemen.
40% of our Semtex was
compromised during transfer.
Conveniently, however,
the Kasnian army
is doing some
transferring of its own.
I'm gonna take a small team
to intercept.
Does this jeopardize
our timeline?
Not with the infamous
Deathstroke backing me up.
What do you say,
father?
Interested in showing
us how it's done?
As long as your dogs
can keep up.
I'll go pack some gear.
[Indistinct chatter]
[Opens channel]
Hey, kid.
Comms are working.
Kane has me making
a run for Semtex.
That's a high-yield
explosive.
Yeah, with Nylander involved,
I should've expected it.
Well, he'll probably be
handling the detonator.
If you can find
the receiver,
perhaps you
can corrupt it.
It might be
in Nylander's gear.
Yeah, I'm on it.
You good?
Just find the receiver.
Slade:
Keep varying your pace.
My pace is fine, old man.
Aah.
So you say.
Dead. Come on. Get up.
How are you better
with one eye
than I am with two?
You must learn to move
with your mind,
not your eyes.
Come on.
Let's go again.
Hold on a sec.
Here. Happy "One year
back from the dead" day.
Well, don't look
too excited.
I can't believe it's
been so long. Thank you.
You might change your
mind about staying home
after you see this.
New prototype.
Should be ready in a year.
That's got to be
tempting, right?
Not in the slightest.
Enough distractions.
Let's train.
[Joe exhales]
Come on.
[Yells]
Damn it, father!
I'm sorry.
I think we're done
with training today.
Woman: You tried
to forget me.
Shado.
But you can't, my love,
because you made me
a promise.
[Indistinct chatter]
You want more drugs?
You got to talk to the boss.
All right, man. Make
the introduction.
Man: Who the hell is this?
A loyal customer.
Is this the guy you
were telling me about?
Ricardo Diaz.
So you're a bouncer,
something like that, right?
That's right.
You're huge.
Well...
I wouldn't want to mess
with you.
I'm just playing
Till we get
our FDA approval,
we got to be careful
with the rollout.
You understand.
I get it. I'm just trying
to make it through a day.
Aren't we all?
Hook him up.
Sure thing, Mr. Diaz.
I always knew you'd
end up wearing this.
[Tires squeal]
Kill the lights.
[Rifle is armed]
[Tires pop]
[Tires squealing]
[Gunfire]
[Fires pistol]
We don't leave
witnesses.
[Footsteps]
[Thud]
Rene: Hey, anybody
in the mood to stress-eat?
Always.
What you got?
Quadruple cheese.
Must be serious.
What's going on here?
Trying to get a line
on this dragon guy,
find out what he
and his crew are up to.
[Computer buzzing]
Well, at least we
know where they are.
Just got
a security alert--
Palmer Tech,
bio division.
Good. Suit up. Stay sharp.
Remember, these guys aren't
afraid of dropping bodies.
[Alarm]
We got company! Go!
[Gunfire]
John: I've got the SUV.
Cover me!
You ok, Hoss?
I ran facial recognition
over John's body cam
footage.
Meet Ricardo Diaz and his
extensive criminal record.
Does anyone want to guess
what his street name is?
Anyone want to guess?
You guys are no fun.
His street name is dragon.
Dinah: This jerk-wad's
been out of prison less than a month.
He's already racked up
a body count.
Rene: This guy was doing
double jolts of life plus one.
- What's that?
- Life without parole.
What's he doing
walking around?
State supreme court overturned
his convictions due to technicalities.
But before he was
on the inside,
he was running
with a group
called the Scorpions
in the Glades.
John, do you know anything
about the Scorpions?
John?
John! John!
Earth to John Diggle.
The Scorpions?
Yeah. I know them.
But Diaz is on something
different--
new muscle, new crew.
They're way too organized.
Rene: I wonder when he
got himself a new crew
and how he got to be
the boss of it.
And why he needs
a weapons-grade 3-D printer.
I think I have
the answer to that.
Drugs, high-end ones.
I cross-referenced
the two models that were stolen.
What they have in
common is
their capacity to
simultaneously print
inert polypropylenes
and soft material
catalyst composites.
Did anyone understand
a word of that?
You think Diaz
is making reactionware?
Anyone normal.
With this equipment,
Diaz cuts
out the middle man.
He can make designer drugs
more cheaply and efficiently
than anyone else
on the street.
Yeah, well, the hell he is.
Whatever science experiment
he's got going on, we're shutting it down.
Curtis, let's work up
a location for Diaz's operation.
You ok, chief?
Yeah. Been a while
since a perp
got the drop on me,
that's all.
We'll make sure
Diaz pays for that.
So what are you planning
with all these explosives?
I'd like to know.
You missed your kill shot
with the soldier back there.
Well, when I lost
this eye,
I lost my
depth perception.
Most of my men think
you joined me
under false pretenses.
There's nothing false
about trying to find my son.
But if they doubt me...
Then maybe I don't have
your trust.
Of course you do,
which is why I got you
a little gift.
[Footsteps approaching]
You told me not
to worry, brother.
[Knee hits back]
Kane: Nylander found
him with my detonator.
Some might see this
as coincidence,
but I see it as fate.
It's time to collect
on that debt
he owes you, father.
Oliver Queen,
I've waited a very, very
long time for this.
An eye for an eye.
You're lying
to yourself, Slade.
You know he's alive.
You've always known,
[echoes]
but still you do nothing.
You know what he did to me.
You know what he
took from us,
and yet here you are
hiding like a coward.
[Echoes]
Coward.
Getting...
[Echoes]
Weak, pathetic.
Give me what you promised.
Give me what
you promised.
[Echoes]
Promised.
Get out of my head!
Not until Oliver Queen
is dead.
He is dead.
He died on the Amazo.
TV reporter: Oliver Queen
is alive.
The Starling City resident
was found by fishermen
in the North China Sea
5 days ago.
Listen, love, you're the only
one who can avenge me.
[Echoes]
Avenge me.
You're the only one
who can make him suffer.
[Echoes]
Suffer.
You know why?
I keep my promises.
Sir, is everything ok?
[Crack]
Come on!
[Sword slicing]
You're telling me you
became the Green Arrow
after you knew
about the tremor.
I was gonna tell Oliver,
but then he asked me
to take over for him.
I couldn't let him down. I--
I couldn't
let the team down.
But you were physically
compromised.
I came up with
a temporary solution,
an experimental steroid.
Lyla, I wanted
to tell you so bad.
I know it was
the wrong call.
I'm sorry.
I'm just glad you
finally told me.
Well, then now that
I have, I need your help.
Is there anything, anything
that Argus is working on
that can help my condition?
I thought it was just
some kind of steroid.
Yeah, we found out
that the manufacturer
is involved in,
uh...criminal activity.
He and his crew have killed
at least two people.
I don't know. Maybe more.
Right. So your
experimental steroid is
actually
an illegal drug.
Look, if this is what
it's taken for you
to come clean
and get this guy
off of the street,
then I guess
I should be grateful.
What?
[Heavy sigh]
You're still using
the drug.
And I guess that
means
that the drug dealer
is out there, too.
To be Green Arrow means
I have to be physically capable
of protecting the city
no matter what.
Lyla, you make
the same choices at Argus
all the time.
Choices you've condemned
me for making.
I know I'm wrong, but
I couldn't let Oliver down.
So you let yourself
down instead.
I mean, Johnnie,
you--you are
the most moral man
I know.
I can't even begin
to fathom how you could do this.
As soon as Argus has a solution,
I will get my guy off the street.
Until then, how many more people is
this guy going to kill?
Lyla, it's not that simple.
It's not that simple!
No. You're the one
who taught me that it is.
Lyla, just
wait for a sec--
No, I just--I want
to be alone right now.
Years ago, I made
you a promise.
Do you remember?
I promised that you
would suffer
the same way that
I suffered.
What are you doing?
You are not
this person anymore.
What I am is a father...
reunited with my son.
I made him
a promise, too,
and I'm not
going to break it again.
We made each other
a promise, Slade...
To save
our sons--
to save Joe, to save William.
He has a son.
I'll make sure he
suffers, too.
Slade.
Do it.
Slade!
[Bonds straining]
That was a little
too convincing.
We got to go.
Come on.
There's no way out.
We'll make our
own way. Come on!
[Thud]
I'll send out the dogs.
We've got the Op.
That's where they'll be.
[Spits]
You sure?
That my father would
try to stop us?
That's
what fathers do.
And that's why
I'm gonna kill him.
Oliver:
Before they captured me,
I saw what Kane
was going after.
They're attacking
the water supply.
It's a death sentence
for half the country.
If we move now, we'll
be able to stop them.
If that's
what you want.
I spared your life
back there.
I know. But back there
it didn't feel like an act
the same way it did with
Chase back on Lian Yu.
Because when I saw
my son,
I was tempted.
I would've done anything
to keep us together.
But when you mentioned
William,
I realize
that's not my boy.
It's Kane.
But what I fear is
there is
only one way
to stop him.
Slade...
There are other ways
to deal with this
that don't involve
killing your son.
Deep down, he's your boy, so
you have to reason with him,
and I swear he will
listen to you.
But I didn't tell you
what happened
after Lian Yu.
I went home
to my son,
and I promised him
I would stay
and never leave.
And I broke
that promise.
No, you broke the promise
because of the Mirakuru.
The Mirakuru
faded for a while,
but when it came back,
it was like a storm
I could not control.
And that monster is
what my son is
trying to emulate,
but it's not
Mirakuru with Joe.
It's anger
and resentment,
and I don't know how
that can be redeemed.
Well, I didn't think that
you could be redeemed,
but I'm here
miles from home,
miles from my son, trying
to help you save yours.
And I can do that because
I knew the man that you were
before the Mirakuru.
That is who your son
needs to see.
He needs to see his father,
the man you are
right now, tonight.
[Sword slices]
[Thud]
Father?
Drop your weapon.
No, not until you tell
me what you're doing.
They were trying
to stop me.
What the hell are you
talking about?
Stop you from what?
Keeping my promises.
[Groaning]
Stay out of my way.
He doesn't show up on
traffic cams.
He doesn't leave a paper trail.
Ricardo Diaz is good.
How's the research on
his old associates going?
Going lousy.
Everybody mentioned
in his
arrest records is
either missing
or dead.
Dinah: That explains why
no one's willing to talk
to the department
about Dragon.
John: I got something--
Diaz's address,
his base of operations.
How the hell did you
get that?
It's a contact.
That's all I can say.
Felicity: We got it.
Thermal imaging shows
a lot of activity inside.
Curtis: Got to figure
Diaz is in there.
Even if he's not,
we can still disrupt
his drug operation.
Let's take
this guy down.
Suit up.
[Canary cry]
[Glass breaks,
men screaming and groaning]
Green Arrow has found us...
[Gunfire]
And his friends, too.
Clear out our stash!
Nothing gets
confiscated. Go!
Go!
[Canary cry]
Hyah!
Enough!
We got to move!
Arrow, let's go!
Kane: Where are we?
Nylander:
All charges are set.
Feels like it
should be you.
I hired you to pull
the trigger.
Move out.
Get to a safe distance.
Semtex makes for
a pretty big bang.
You're not coming with?
- I want a good view.
- You're crazy. I love it!
Don't forget
what you said
about the Semtex,
huh?
I knew you'd show up.
I think it's time
we had ourselves
an honest talk.
[Gunshots]
[Men groaning]
"Trust begins with honesty."
That's what you said
to me, but you lied!
You know life is not
that simple, Joe.
That's not my name.
And how could you forgive
Oliver Queen
after what he did to you?
Because he forgave me
for far worse--
sins that I have
to carry to the grave,
a curse I didn't want to
pass on to you.
All of this anger
and resentment--
it's time to bring it
to an end, son.
No.
This is just the beginning.
[Clang]
[Gunshot]
Hyah! Hyah! Hyah...
[Crack]
You used to be ruthless.
What happened?
What you saw was
the Mirakuru.
Stop lying!
I saw you kill
before the Mirakuru.
[Kane groaning]
Milford Sound,
that little
father-son trip,
the one
you promised
would be all
about you and me.
I saw what you did
to that Chinese spy.
[Thud]
I was on a mission
for A.S.I.S.
Well, here's something
you don't know--
something mother never
told you--I have a brother.
His name is Grant.
Mother didn't want him
in this world.
But me, I'm my father's son.
I made my first kill
6 months
after our camping trip.
And I slit his throat
just like you did.
I wanted to be
exactly like my father,
like Deathstroke.
I am not
Deathstroke anymore.
Then you're not
my father anymore.
You're just in my way.
[Gunshot, clang]
Oliver: Don't move!
Slade,
you all right?
Oliver,
lower your gun.
I wish that
you'd stayed dead.
He's gone.
Thank you.
I spoke with our
friend, the warden.
The Jackals are
in custody,
and he is
very relieved.
You all right?
My son...
He saw me kill
a man before the Mirakuru,
before Deathstroke.
He followed
in my path, Oliver.
No. Don't blame
yourself, Slade.
It doesn't help.
You know why I do.
"Never give up on family."
That's what you told me.
It's time for you
to go home.
Where will you go?
I'm gonna keep
searching for my son,
both of them.
I can't give up.
You ever need my help again,
you don't hesitate to ask.
You have your own son
to protect.
I'm not gonna put
that at risk again.
You've seen what
can happen.
Thank you, kid.
Hey.
I just saw a news report
of a lab explosion.
Looks like you took
down his operation
with plenty
of collateral damage.
Yeah, well, that part
was all Diaz.
He was willing to blow up
the works,
kill all of his men.
So you didn't mean
to destroy the drugs.
Uh...
I planned to take
as much as I could carry.
When I realized
I was losing the very thing
that would allow me
to put on that hood,
I wanted to run straight
into the explosion.
Johnnie.
I was a hypocrite,
and I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Don't be sorry. Be safe.
Are you ok?
I'm trying.
Hey. Come here, you.
Ohh.
I missed you.
I missed you,
Daddy.
I have, uh, one more
stop tonight.
There are some
other people...
Who deserve an apology
and an explanation.
Ok.
William: I'm gonna win.
Felicity: Nope! Oh,
I almost got you.
Come on! Gah!
- Yes.
- No!
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
- Rematch? Rematch.
- All right.
I got you
on this one.
- Hi.
- Hey.
Hey, buddy,
come here.
Ok, ah, you
weren't gone that long.
I know. I know.
I'm happy to see you.
It's allowed.
So what happened
with your friend?
- He found his son.
- That's good.
So what'd I miss?
Well, Raisa made me
clean my room...
Good.
Felicity and I ate
ice cream for dinner,
and I got an "A" on
my science project.
- You got an "A"?
- Yeah.
That's fantastic. Is it
here? Can I see it?
Yeah, sure.
It's a bottle rocket.
Went 300 feet, the farthest
in the whole school.
- Unbelievable.
- I'll go get it.
All right.
Pretty cool.
I hope you don't mind
that I'm here.
I mean, William said that he was
kind of getting sick of Raisa.
And the ice cream
for dinner?
It was Rocky Road,
so, technically,
the nuts should count
as protein and--
I'm so happy
you're here.
Me, too.
Slade got his
happy ending?
Not...Like that.
Ha ha.
It's a long story.
It's a...
It's a sad
story.
I'm sensing a "but."
- I learned something.
- Hmm?
I made the right
decision
to not
be the Green Arrow
for William
and for me.
Good.
William: If we can
go up to the roof,
I can show you
how it works.
- Yeah. Yes.
- Yes!
[Cell phone ringing
and vibrating]
Felicity: Let's go.
The moment I hesitated,
even as the flames
grew closer...
[Heavy sigh]
That was
my rock bottom.
I should've told you
all about the tremor
from the beginning.
I'm truly sorry
I didn't.
Rene: So you're saying
the tremor started
before Black Siren showed
her face in Star City?
Yes.
And that's why,
Rene, I owe you
the biggest apology
of all.
You should've known
what was going on
before we ever got
to that bridge, man.
My pride almost got
you killed.
I betrayed your
trust,
put your lives
in danger.
All I can ask is
that you forgive me,
but I understand
if you can't.
Well, getting shot
wasn't great,
but if I'm counting the
times you've saved my life
against the times you
almost got me killed,
you're still ahead.
I, for one, am
incredibly offended...
And you have every
right to be, Curtis.
That you didn't come
to me first
for help treating you.
I mean, I--I created
a chip to help
a woman walk, people.
He's got a point, John.
It might be time
to outsource
this little problem.
Yeah. Yeah.
Outstanding.
So have you already had
an electromyogram? Wait.
What am I talking about?
We need to start off with an NCV test first.
Curtis, it's been
a long night.
Is there any way
we can do this in the morning?
Sure thing.
It would be my honor.
It would be
my pleasure.
[Fake coughs]
Kiss ass.
What the--
I'm trying to...
You waiting on
a special apology?
Because you deserve one.
No. I'm just waiting
to make sure you're ok.
- Really?
- Really.
Well, I'm gonna
give you one anyway.
Dinah, I lied to
you, and I'm sorry,
but I'll make you
one more promise--
there'll be no more secrets
between you and me.
No more secrets.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man