My name is Oliver Queen.
After five years in hell,
I have come home
with only one goal--
To save my city.
Now others have
joined my crusade.
To them, I am Oliver Queen.
To the rest
of Starling city,
I am someone else.
I am something else.
Previously, on "arrow"...
Oliver:
I'm going to find
whoever did this.
There's something
about Malcolm that both you
And Oliver need to know.
Malcolm is--
Aah!
I don't want to hurt,
or get hurt,
And you seem like someone
who could teach me how not to.
You are my family.
I need you.
Looks like
you're going home.
Did Thea seem...
Different to you?
Where is she?
Where is Sara?
She came here
for the league
two weeks ago.
We've not heard
from her since.
There's something
I have to tell you.
Sara's dead?
I'm so sorry.
It was an arrow, wasn't it?
How do you know that?
Where's her body?
Nyssa...
We buried her
in her grave from
seven years ago.
[sighs]
She knows something.
I want you to follow her,
but be careful.
I have to meet Thea.
Hi.
Sorry I'm late.
Late is your
"on time," Ollie.
So much for my promise
that things would be
different, right?
Relax, it's fine.
Dinner is on me.
With what money?
Aren't you broke?
Um...Aren't you?
Not so much,
actually.
When I decided
to come back,
I had no idea
what I wanted to do,
And realized I kind
of missed the club.
And turns out,
a lot of other
people do, too.
I have investors.
And they're going
to help me buy
back the foundry
From Queen
consolidated.
I'm thrilled for you,
that's fantastic.
You seem changed.
Stronger.
After last year,
I...
Don't see any other
way it could have
turned out.
And that's it?
You're not...
Seeing someone,
Hoping Roy
didn't put you up
to asking that.
No. I'm just trying
to figure out why
you're so different.
How about just being
my big brother
instead?
Ok.
[indistinct chatter]
[cell phone beeps]
Target's on the move.
He's headed north.
He's stopped.
Maseo:
What's he doing?
He's buying ice cream.
He doesn't look like
a terrorist.
The best ones
never do.
Why does Waller want me
to take this guy out?
You ask too many
questions.
Follow orders
and eliminate
the target.
Or is this one
your best friend, too?
Oh, so I'm just a gun
that she can point at things
She doesn't like?
That's exactly
what you are.
He's moving.
Best not to waste
time, then.
Nyssa.
[speaking Arabic]
You have
my condolences.
And that
of my father,
Ra's al Ghul.
I don't want
your condolences.
And I definitely
don't want your father's.
She died with arrows
in her chest.
Do you think that
would have happened
If she hadn't
met you?
You were the one
that showed her
the darkness inside.
You,
And your father.
I know you grieve.
But so do I.
I didn't show Sara
the darkness, Laurel.
It was already inside
of her when we met.
When I found her, alone,
Starving and terrified,
I protected her.
I took Sara into my heart
And I loved her
with all of my soul.
And that jacket...
I gave it to Sara as a gift.
You are not fit to wear it.
Roy: She's moving.
She went to visit
Sara's grave
And now she's on
the top floor of some
dump on Amsterdam.
Could be where
she's crashing.
League of assassins
safe house or something.
Text me the address.
[Nyssa sniffs]
Are you ready to talk?
We have nothing
to discuss.
[sheaths blade]
The trail for Sara's killer
has gone cold.
And I could use your help.
Whereas I don't
need yours.
We've gathered evidence,
we're working leads.
You're visiting cemeteries
And hiding
in league safe houses.
I am not hiding.
And this is not
my safe house.
It was Sara's while
she was in Starling.
[beep]
These were
her favorites.
[sets can on table]
Ok.
You said Sara
was in Starling
for the league.
That suggests
her target
is also her killer.
Agreed.
Except it wasn't her target.
Sara came to Starling
to confirm rumors--
Whispers, really--
that an enemy
of the league was here.
Who?
Malcolm Merlyn.
He's alive.
Merlyn was a member
of the league of assassins.
My father released him
from his obligation to us
With the understanding
he would abide by
its code of conduct.
You guys are
professional
killers.
That is
a pretty low bar.
Merlyn's
undertaking
Violated
the league's
principles.
When you killed him,
we considered
the matter settled.
From a reliable
source that Merlyn
faked his demise.
What source?
Oliver's mother.
Yeah, well, Oliver's mom
wasn't exactly known
for her honesty.
I just can't believe
that a guy everyone
thinks was dead
Suddenly...Isn't.
Neither did I.
Then we found these.
[beep]
Sara took them
two weeks ago.
Didn't the police,
you know, find his body?
Merlyn had resources
all over Starling.
I'm willing to bet
one of them was in
the coroner's office.
Since learning
Merlyn was alive,
The league has hunted
him all over the globe.
Running down
every rumor,
Following every whisper.
And one of those whispers
put Merlyn back in Starling.
She tracked him here.
We are going
to retrace her steps.
You said you found
evidence on her person?
We found a blank piece
of paper in Sara's boot,
But why would she
be carrying a blank
piece of paper?
Do you have a flame?
Unbelievable.
My father had a notebook
with hidden writing
just like this.
The notebook
he received from
Merlyn, I imagine.
One of the means
the league employs
for concealing secrets.
It's Sara's handwriting.
Notes from her surveilLance
of Merlyn.
Oliver, there's not much
to go on here.
There's a couple
of things.
Jansen,
question mark.
Dad help,
Question mark.
Sara reached out
to Lance.
If Lance knew Merlyn was
alive, don't you think
he would have told you?
Only if she told him.
What matters
is what he told her.
And how do we find that out?
[siren]
so, gentlemen,
Word of advice--
next time
you arrest a bookie,
Please make sure
the chief is not
one of his clients.
Now, that's what the chief
told me to tell you, ok,
But as far
as I'm concerned,
You just keep
doing your jobs.
First round tonight's
on me. Please,
get out of here.
Buying rounds?
The fastest way
to a cop's heart is
through his liver.
How you feeling?
I'm fine.
Do you have a minute?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I have
to talk to you.
It's about Sara.
She, um...
She called me.
She said that she was
looking into something.
Something
called Jansen?
Um...
Ahem.
Uh, yeah, someone.
Ken Zhi Jansen.
I hooked her up with his
last known address.
Sara was here.
She asked me not
to say anything to you,
And I should have.
Maybe I should have,
I'm sorry.
It's ok. She was--
She's in
a mysterious
line of work.
Oh, yeah. One I hope
you're not getting
mixed up with.
No. I'm just doing
Sara a favor.
And her?
I'll be right back.
What are you doing here?
Oliver told me
of his plan
to involve you
In the hunt for
Sara's killer.
I have a handle on it.
Your father doesn't
know, does he?
No. He doesn't.
And he can't.
He has a heart condition.
He has the right
to avenge his daughter.
That is none
of your business.
Sara was everything
I hold dear
in this life,
Which is every bit
of my business.
And what would she say
if she was here now?
Hey. I almost
didn't recognize you
Without
your Halloween costume.
Is Sara back in town, too?
No, she is not.
But she told me
to tell you
That she misses you
very much.
The address I gave
your sister for Jansen.
Now she promised me
there wouldn't be any,
you know, assassinating.
Is that still the case?
I assure you,
Mr. Lance,
The only
objective here
Is justice.
This was the next lead
Sara was going to follow?
Jansen's
a buddhist monk.
He was facing
deportation
in china.
Merlyn bankrolled
his defense.
And Jansen returns the favor
by giving Merlyn asylum
In his garden.
Monastery.
We should divide
our forces, take our
flanking positions.
I agree,
but not--
Never understood what
Sara saw in her
in the first place.
Split up,
But be careful.
Got it.
John: Oliver,
we found Jansen.
Negative.
I have eyes on him.
Whoever's up there
is not Jansen.
Jansen sensei,
I am Nyssa, daughter
Of Ra's al Ghul.
Heir to the demon.
You will tell me where I can
find Malcolm Merlyn
Or I will kill you
where you sit.
Hello, Nyssa.
Where is he?!
What's going on?
Did you find
Sara's killer?
We have a suspect.
Malcolm Merlyn's alive.
Sara was here
looking for him.
We think
he found her first.
And where is he now?
We're working on that.
He got away from us
earlier tonight.
But not before
I hit him with an arrow
Laced with particulate
nanotechnology.
Felicity wrote
a program that tracks
the nanites using gps.
The tracer arrow.
Yeah.
You had a shot at Merlyn
and you didn't kill him?
I tagged him.
With a flesh wound!
There's nowhere in
the world he can go
where I can't find him.
And when you do?
I'm not a killer
anymore, Laurel.
Merlyn is.
He killed Tommy
And 502 other innocent people.
How many more people
are going to have to die
before you put him down?
Do you think that's
what your sister
would want?
Yes. I do.
Merlyn may try
to contact Thea.
I'm on it.
The tracer arrow
program...
You have Felicity monitoring
remote from central city?
No, she told me
an idiot could run it.
I will try very hard not
to take that personally.
I'll be on the streets.
Talk me in when
you have his location.
Copy that.
[beep]
It's done.
Nyssa: Laurel.
I just found out
that Malcolm Merlyn
isn't only alive,
But that he killed my sister.
I'm sure you can understand
Why I don't want
to talk right now.
I understand.
I loved her, too.
Sorry for your loss.
I promise Sara,
And I promise you--
We will find
Malcolm Merlyn.
Apparently you already did.
And Oliver should have
killed him.
Yes.
If Oliver catches up
with Merlyn,
He's going to let him live
or let him go.
You can't let that happen.
You need to get Merlyn.
You have to do
whatever it takes.
Hey.
Grand reopening's not
for another three weeks.
Well, looks like
you've still got
a lot more work to do.
Need some help?
But don't really think
that's a good idea.
Just as friends.
And former
co-workers.
[exhales]
Bonsai green,
October mist,
Or avocado?
John: Merlyn stopped.
I've got his position.
Go.
Air conditioner factory.
You want me to share
this with Nyssa?
No. She's liable to
put an arrow in him
Before I get
any answers.
Agreed.
[exhales]
This place is empty.
He's not here, Diggle.
Malcolm:
Hello, Oliver.
I'm not at the--
what is it, the air
conditioning factory?
It's a very neat trick
you have, but I'm sorry
it didn't work out.
When I find you...
You absolutely will.
We need to talk.
But I prefer a venue
less conducive
to conflict.
Nelson plaza
at coldwater and fifth,
Bottom of the stairs.
It's a very public place;
You'll want to leave
your mask behind.
I think this should remain
between the two of us,
So if I even see
one of your associates,
I promise you,
you will not see me.
Malcolm: Hello, Oliver!
How are you?
You've accomplished
a lot with this city, I see.
I'm not here
to discuss Starling.
You think I killed Sara Lance.
How else would
you know she's dead?
These streets were mine long
before you laid claim to them.
This is still my city.
I chose this place
because of the crowds.
Besides, I understand
you're not killing
people these days.
Seriously considering
making an exception.
Ra's al Ghul has placed
a blood bounty on my head.
Why would I try to get it
lifted by killing the love
of his daughter's life?
It's illogical!
Sara comes back
to Starling.
You come back
I came back for the simplest
and most noble of reasons--
Thea.
Six months ago,
during the siege,
She was almost killed
by one of Slade Wilson's
Mirakuru soldiers.
I protected her!
You're lying.
Thea made it out
before the attack.
Unfortunately,
she didn't make it out.
But you wouldn't know that,
because you were out being--
What are you calling yourself
these days? "the arrow."
That was the night I realized
that Thea needs me!
Stay away from her.
Don't worry.
I've kept my distance.
[exhales]
But the world
is a dangerous place.
And you're too distracted
to protect her.
You're a killer.
Yes, I am.
But I swear.
I swear to you
on Thea's life...
I am not Sara Lance's killer.
From the look on your
face, you need something
stronger than coffee.
You ok?
Yeah, are you?
[sighs] back
in Corto Maltese,
I promised you there
would be no more secrets.
No more lies.
And I'm trying to honor that.
Ok...
I learned something last night
That's going to be
difficult for you to hear.
I think that it's what
mom was trying to tell us
The night she died,
right before...
The night of the siege,
you were at the train station.
Yeah. I...
It wasn't fun.
I got attacked
by one of those
crazy masked things
And he tried
to strangle me.
But he got shot
by a cop, I think.
Did you see him?
No.
Why are you asking?
It wasn't a cop, Thea.
It was Malcolm Merlyn.
He's dead.
How do you
know this?
One of Sara's friends saw him.
She's sure.
If he was going to try
to contact you, he would
have done it by now.
Ok?
Thank you.
For telling me.
[cell phone beeps]
It's, uh, one
of my investors. I--
Are you ok?
Yeah. I'm--
I'm fine. I--
It's like you said;
if he was going
to contact me,
He probably would
have done it by now.
Where's Oliver?
Out, taking care
of some family business.
As if there weren't more
pressing matters at hand.
He's not doing
nothing. He tracked
down Merlyn last night.
Did he kill him?
No.
He swore to me
he didn't kill Sara.
And you know all
of his words are lies.
I believe him.
Because he swore to me
On his daughter's life.
We had heard rumors
Merlyn fathered
another child.
We couldn't
confirm them.
You know who it is.
I do.
If you put me
through the effort
Of finding out
on my own...
I might have
to exact a price
From whoever it is
you're protecting.
My sister
is Merlyn's daughter.
And that is the reason
he came back to Starling city.
Because she did.
He's protecting her.
And that is why you
spared Merlyn. Twice!
It had nothing
to do with that.
He explained to me--
in his own twisted way--
That he loves her.
And then he swore
to me on her life.
And I swore
an oath of my own
That I would see
Sara's killer
brought to justice.
Nyssa...Nyssa!
Oliver, wait.
We need to stop her!
Do we?
Listen, I understand why
you can't kill Merlyn,
All of the reasons.
Maybe he killed Sara,
maybe he didn't.
He didn't.
Either way!
The world is
a better place
Without
Malcolm Merlyn
in it.
You made a vow
not to kill.
Nyssa didn't.
Where's your wife?
Tatsu. She needed to be
someplace else.
Ah. She doesn't like me.
You're wrong.
She hates you.
She's not happy
that I'm here.
Neither am I.
I killed a man today.
I don't even know the reason.
Sometimes it's
better that way.
What, blindly
following orders is better?
I'm not blind, Oliver.
I'm focused--
On what's most
important.
You should do the same.
It's not our place
or our burden
To know why
we carry out
our missions.
I didn't realize
having a conscience
was a burden.
[keys jingle]
What are you playing?
A reading game.
Oh, yeah? Do you mind if I try?
I want to work
on my cantonese.
My dad said I shouldn't
let you use my computer.
Ok.
Why don't we make
a deal, then?
You don't have anything.
You're a bum.
Well, this bum has something
that you don't have.
Height.
That your parents
keep in the cupboard
above the fridge?
I'll swipe you two pieces.
Five.
Three.
Fine, five.
Give me the computer.
I need a meet
with Waller.
How did you--akio!
It's not his fault.
I need a meet.
Make it happen.
Waller's going
to want a reason.
Ferris air
flight 637.
She'll know
what I mean.
Thanks for your help.
I mean, you really
didn't have to do all that.
I like painting.
It actually helps me
turn my brain off.
You know, I actually wish
you were still trying
to get into my pants,
Because this whole
zen helpful Roy thing
Is really freaking me out.
Get away from him.
I'm not here
for him.
Roy: Thea...
Thea?
Thea, are you here?
[sighs]
So Malcolm Merlyn is alive,
and Thea's father.
Anything else
you haven't told me?
What did you get
at the precinct?
But I did get this
off a traffic camera.
It was recorded
10 minutes ago.
After I struck out
on anything related
to Nyssa or Thea,
I just looked for strange.
Well, that
definitely counts.
Sara.
She never said much
about the leak.
But she did say that
their communication system
Was a little outdated.
Smoke signal.
Nyssa's sending
Malcolm a message.
I don't know
about the cipher,
but I'm willing
To bet my wallet that means
"we got your daughter."
Doesn't matter.
Video gives me
her location.
You mean "us"
on location, right?
No. I need you
to secure
the perimeter.
Can't risk Thea
seeing you.
She already knows
I know about
the arrow.
Not with a dose
of league tranquilizer
in your system.
Oliver.
This is my fault.
I told Nyssa
to go after Merlyn.
I told her to do
whatever it takes.
It's ok.
I know you're not a killer.
But he is.
Whatever else he means
to you or to Thea...
Know that.
I'm going to get free
of this, and when I do,
I'm going to kill you!
Nyssa: I apologize
for involving you in this.
My quarrel
is with your father.
My father's been
dead for years,
you crazy psycho bitch.
Not robert Queen.
Your true father--
Al sa-her. "the magician."
Known to the uninitiated
as Malcolm Merlyn.
Then you know what
he's going to do to
you when he gets here.
I know he'll die.
My father taught me ways
To cut a man to make
his death last for days.
Sounds like
father of the year.
My father may be the demon...
But yours is the devil.
Run!
Apparently we both
handle grief differently.
Malcolm: There's
a misunderstanding
The three of us
need to clear up.
A conversation I am
eager to have...
Over your rotting corpse.
Nyssa: Do it, Oliver.
He killed Sara.
Tommy.
He will corrupt
your sister.
[grunts]
There is blood
on my hands.
Almost too much
to contemplate.
But none
of it is Sara's.
Kill him!
I did not kill
your beloved!
Your father doubted
Sara's loyalties
The moment
you brought her home.
You know your father.
What he is capable of.
He will kill
without hesitation.
Do you really
need me to tell you
what he would do
To the degenerate
who would steal
his daughter's heart?
[groans]
Nyssa doesn't
believe me, Oliver.
If you don't
believe me...
Listen to her.
Kill me.
You may not have
killed Sara...
But you're still a murderer.
What are you
going to do?
Arrest me?
I could have scpd here
In three minutes.
And in half that time,
I will escape
From whatever prison
they put me in.
You know that,
so does she.
We were trained
by the league;
no prison can hold us!
Not even your one
on Lian Yu.
Which leaves you
with only
One option.
To break your vows...
And kill me.
Kill your sister's
father.
[Nyssa groaning
and gasping]
Is Thea ok?
I just spoke to her.
She's fine.
Doesn't know
who took her or why.
I may have
deserved that.
You deserve worse.
Um, what's going on?
Merlyn didn't
kill Sara.
Which means
whoever did
is still out there.
You're a fool
Who insults the memory
of a woman he once loved.
I will honor Sara's
memory by finding
and punishing
The person
who did this.
The real person.
Nyssa.
So as long
as Malcolm Merlyn
is in my city,
The league will make
no move on him.
He's under
my protection.
You would incur the wrath
of the league of assassins?
I would do...
What I have to
In order to buy
the time necessary
To find out
what really
happened with Sara.
You have made
an enemy tonight.
One with a long memory.
Oliver.
Are you sure?
If I wasn't sure,
I never would
have let him go.
I promise.
What did I miss?
Amanda: I hate Hong Kong.
And I hate
transpacific flights.
And do not even get me
started on the topic
Of being summoned
by one of my operatives.
Ferris air
flight 637.
Paris to Hong Kong
nonstop.
You prevented that flight
from being shot over Lian Yu.
Were you watching me?!
Via keyhole hexagon satellite.
How else was I supposed
to know you possess
The capabilities I require?
That business
with the freighter last year...
Impressive.
Are we done?
Just getting started,
actually.
Adam Castwidth
The man
you had me murder.
He was Edward Fyers'
handler.
And he worked for you.
You're out of your depth,
Mr. Queen!
I don't think I am.
I think Mr. Castwidth
Had a usb drive on him
detailing everything.
I think he knew that
you told fyers to
shoot the plane down.
And I think that
you wanted him silenced!
And the world
thinks you dead,
Mr. Queen.
The convenient thing
about dead men
Is that no one tends
to believe them.
Yeah, well, what
about dead men who
make arrangements
To get
the information
on that usb drive
In the hands of every
blogger and journalist
in this hemisphere.
If anything happens
to Maseo's family,
Then you're going
to spend a long time
Testifying in front
of the senate
sub-committee.
The world's a much more
complicated place
Than you realize.
Edward Fyers thought
he was to shoot down that plane
To destabilize
the Chinese economy.
In truth, I wanted
to take out a single target.
So you blow up a plane
full of innocent people
To take out one man.
No.
To take out one woman.
Chien na Wei.
Two years ago,
we had our only chance at her.
And you saved her life.
And now she's in Hong Kong.
I need to know why.
[grunting]
Laurel: I thought you were
going back to your father.
I thought
I owed you
a good-bye.
I intend to make
good on my promise
to Sara.
And to you.
[exhales]
It kills me that
he's still out there.
Merlyn.
Someone.
It kills me.
It pains me
as well.
I see you've
been training...
And wearing
the jacket.
If you're going
to stand there
and tell me
I'm not strong enough
or tough enough, please...
Don't.
Back at the cemetery,
I would have.
But since,
you've reminded me
That the strongest
metal is forged
in the hottest fire.
And what's that
supposed to mean?
Don't forget
to turn your hips.
It's where the power
comes from.
[siren]
Sara, on voice mail:
It's Sara. Leave a message.
Sara. Sweetie,
it's, uh, it's me.
Look, I know you said
only call this number
in an emergency.
And it's not. It's not.
Everything's fine.
But I--I just...
[sighs] I just want
to hear your voice.
Look, I know wherever you are,
you're looking after yourself.
But, you know,
that doesn't mean
I don't worry.
So, you know,
you don't have to
call me back or anything,
Just, I just
want you to remember--
That I love you.
Are you ok?
It's not my first time
being kidnapped.
That's not what
I meant.
I never imagined
you and scrubbing.
Unless
a spa treatment
was involved.
I spoke
to detective Lance.
He doesn't think
that woman's going
to bother you again.
Why did she come after me
in the first place?
Maybe she thought
the Queens
still had money.
I wish.
But thank you
for checking in on me.
I'm always going
to watch out for you.
Always.
Sorry, guys, I didn't
mean to interrupt.
I was just leaving.
Take care
of yourself.
I thought you had
guys for that.
It's kind of zen.
But you've got that same
worried look on your face
My brother had.
And really, I'm fine.
Good.
I just wanted
to make sure
you're ok.
And I wanted
to apologize.
I'm sorry
I couldn't stop her.
You tried.
Those were some
nice moves back there.
Whatever you're doing
with the arrow
Is clearly paying off.
You know, maybe I should
apply for a job here
As one of your bouncers.
I think I got
that covered.
But I could use
an assistant
manager.
For real?
I need somebody
who knows the place
as well as I do.
Absolutely.
Purely platonic.
Understood.
[cell phone vibrates]
Oh, it's
my designer kurt.
I should probably
take this.
Hi.
Malcolm: Are you safe?
I am now.
Is that woman gone?
For now.
And your brother?
He's completely in the dark.
He doesn't know a thing.
But thank you, dad.
For what?
For taking care of me.
I promised you, Thea.
I will never
let anyone hurt you.
The rumors were true.
Malcolm Merlyn
is in Starling city.
Man: There is a sadness
in your voice.
Ta-er al-Sahfer.
She has fallen.
Sara Lance is dead.
Yes.
Struck through the heart
with an arrow.
At Merlyn's hand?
It appears.
I have vowed a blood
oath to avenge her.
Al sa-her will face
the league's justice.
But for his crimes
against our code.
But Sara--
Was never truly
one of us.
And what of Queen?
He has sworn to protect
Merlyn at any cost.
If that is true,
Then Oliver Queen
courts war with us.