My name is Oliver Queen.
For five years,
I was stranded on an island...
survive.
Oliver Queen is alive.
Now I will fulfill
my father's dying wish.
You can survive this.
To use the list of names he left me
and bring down those...
...who are poisoning my city.
To do this,
I must become someone else.
I must become something else.
Previously on Arrow:
- Sarah!
- How am I supposed to stay...
...away if you won't stay away from me?
John Diggle.
He'll be accompanying you from now on.
I'm just beginning to understand
the kind of man you are.
Hey-
Oliver?
You're that vigilante.
Take it easy, Dig. You were poisoned.
Son of a bitch!
I could've taken you anywhere.
Could've taken you home.
I brought you here.
You did lose your mind
on that island.
- Found a couple of things.
- What, archery classes?
Clarity.
Starling City is dying.
It is being poisoned
by a criminal elite...
...who don't care who they hurt...
...as long as they maintain
wealth and power.
And what are you gonna do,
take them all down by your lonesome?
No.
No, I want you to join me.
Special Forces out of Kandahar.
It's perfect.
You're a fellow soldier.
Oliver, you're not a soldier.
You're a criminal.
And a murderer.
Where were you?
What are you doing here?
I heard about the shooting and
wanted to make sure you were okay.
- You did?
- Yeah.
I knocked on the door
and I found a family terrified for you.
- They had no idea where you were.
- Oh.
Are you so self-centered that you don't
think that people who care about you...
...will wonder where you are
after you got shot at?
You're right.
I made peace with your selfishness
a long time ago...
...but Moira, Thea and Walter,
they don't deserve that.
They deserve better...
...someone who doesn't care
only about himself.
Laurel.
Thank you for coming.
I care about the lives of other people,
Oliver.
Maybe you should try it sometime.
Oh, man.
That was harsh.
- You okay?
-Sure.
Second time tonight
that a friend of mine...
...has taken me to the woodshed.
- Kind of tires you out.
- Yeah.
- Good night.
- Night.
What am I supposed to do with that?
Does that mean "bird"?
I don't speak Chinese!
I'm sorry, Laurel. I'm so sorry.
There were no signs
of forced entry or any evidence of a struggle...
...but hours later, the police found
the blood-stained kitchen knife...
-...in the trunk of Peter Declan's car.
- Couldn't sleep either?
No. What are you watching?
Peter Declan.
Hmm?
Oh, a guy who killed his wife.
Right. This guy killed his wife
in their baby's room.
- Psycho.
- Camille was everything to me.
I couldn't kill her any more
than I could kill myself.
So why can't you sleep?
- Bad dreams.
- About?
Laurel.
So why don't you make a play?
I mean, she did come over here
just to make sure you didn't get shot.
- There are reasons.
- What are they?
Besides you sleeping with her sister
and her sister dying...
...and her father hating your guts
and you being a jerk...
...to everybody
since you've been back.
Those are the top ones.
I know that it might not seem like it
sometimes...
...but I'm not the same person
I used to be.
So show her. Be yourself.
I mean, your new self.
- How did you sleep?
- Just fine, thank you.
Mm.
- We have a visitor.
- Mm. Mr. Diggle's replacement.
- Replacement?
- Yes.
He tendered his resignation
this morning.
Did he say why?
He said he didn't approve of the way
you spend your evenings...
...particularly given that they always
begin with you ditching him.
- Hi.
- Mr. Queen.
Rob Scott.
I'll be your new body man.
Firm grip you got there, Rob.
That's five years SWAT
with Monument Point MCU.
I feel safer already.
Thank God we don't have to hear
about this awful man anymore.
Declan's execution is set for midnight
two days from now.
Camille Declan's former employer,
Jason Brodeur...
...released a statement saying, quote:
"I hope this gives Camille
the peace she deserves."
Jason Brodeur.
- Thank you, Jessica.
- What?
The dead wife
worked for Jason Brodeur.
Apparently so. What? Why?
No reason.
I wanna go into town.
Could you please get the car for me?
No offense, but I have been filled in
on your tendency to slip the leash.
If it's all the same to you, I'd prefer
keeping you in my sights at all times.
We're 20 miles from the city.
If you don't drive me,
how else am I gonna get there?
Right.
I like him.
Hey!
They say Peter Declan murdered
his wife in cold blood.
He had no alibi.
And all the evidence
pointed toward it.
He was tried, convicted,
sentenced to death.
An open-and-shut case...
...except for one thing.
Declan's wife, Camille,
worked for Jason Brodeur.
And Jason Brodeur is on the list.
- Mr. Brodeur.
- Admiring your handiwork, Ankov?
- You should've let me kill both of them.
- Peter Declan is worth more alive.
"Husband Kills Wife"
is a much better headline...
...than "Whistle-blower Uncovers
Toxic Dumping," don't you think?
Either way, 48 hours,
all this will be over.
The odds are good Brodeur is involved
in this woman's murder, which means...
...an innocent man is facing execution.
He'll need a good attorney.
So I take it there's absolutely no point
in asking if you'd like to grab a drink.
I can't. I have to go over transcripts
for the Fernands case.
If you go somewhere
that's not work or your home...
...your odds of meeting someone
increase by a gazillion percent.
That's not true. I could still
get mugged on the way home.
In that case,
I hope he's cute and single.
Good night, Joanna.
Hello, Laurel.
Don't move.
- I'm not gonna hurt you.
- Stay back.
My father is a cop.
You are making a huge mistake.
I'm not the person you think I am,
and I need your help.
Peter Declan is gonna be
executed in 48 hours.
I think he's innocent.
Declan's wife was gonna blow the whistle
on Brodeur. Brodeur had her murdered.
There are a thousand lawyers
in Starling City.
Why me?
We're both trying to help.
What makes you so sure
I'm gonna help you?
Because I know you'd do anything
to save the life of an innocent man.
Ajury has found you guilty, Mr. Declan.
The evidence was stacked against me,
but I didn't kill my wife.
I didn't take my daughter's mother
from her.
The murder weapon was a knife
from your kitchen...
...with your prints on it.
It was found,
along with Camille's blood...
...in the trunk of your car.
Your neighbors said...
...they heard an argument that night.
We had a knockdown fight
over Jason Brodeur.
Camille worked for him...
...and his company had been
dumping toxic waste into the Glades.
Camille told me she'd gone
and told a supervisor about it.
I was afraid for my family's safety.
And we argued...
...very loudly, Yes-
Izzy started crying, so Camille went
and stayed in her room.
In the morning,
I went to apologize...
...and that's when I found her.
So I just grabbed Izzy
and I ran outside and I called 911.
I'm innocent, Ms. Lance.
Well, it looks like someone forgot
a lunch date with his wife.
What do you mean?
Lunch isn't for another...
Forty-five minutes ago. I'm so sorry.
It's all right.
The restaurant is holding our table.
Is there something wrong?
Compliance department tagged
$2.6 million withdrawal...
...from one of our Vancouver
subsidiaries.
Are you saying that someone embezzled
$2.6 million from the company?
It's probably a bookkeeping error, but
Compliance is worried about an IRS audit.
Mm.
But don't worry.
I'm sure it's nothing.
Come on. We're gonna be late.
I mean later.
Well, I wasn't the lead on this,
but from what I recall...
...we had fingerprints, we had blood,
we got motive, everything.
Brodeur seems like the type of guy
with resources needed to frame someone.
Laurel, in 24 hours, Peter Declan is
lying down with a needle in his arm.
If I thought we didn't have the right guy
you think I'd be doing anything now...
...except get at what really happened?
Declan said his wife
went to her supervisor...
...with allegations that Brodeur
was dumping toxic waste.
Yeah, but that supervisor,
he said that never happened.
Let me see. What was his name?
Here you go. lstook, Matt lstook.
He said he didn't even see
Camille that day.
- Happy now?
- Yes.
I thought it'd be cold day in hell...
-...before you started defending criminals.
- I'm not sure Declan is a criminal.
Like you said, he's on a clock.
Can't leave any stone unturned.
Oh, yeah.
- So when are you gonna tell me?
- Hmm.
- About what happened to your arm.
- Oh, it's my shoulder, and it's fine.
I knew that Queen guy was trouble.
Hey, I never said this happened
protecting Queen.
Oh, yeah?
Then what's he doing here?
- Area secure, sir.
- Thank you very much, Rob.
Hello, Diggle's sister-in-law Carly.
I'm Oliver Queen.
- I know who you are.
- No, you really don't.
Hello.
I couldn't help but notice
a distinct lack of police cars...
...when I got home. I knew
you wouldn't drop a dime on me.
- So have you considered my offer?
- Offer? Heh.
- That's one hell of a way to put it.
- It is an offer.
It's a chance to do the kind of good
that compelled you to join the military.
Please. You were born with a platinum
spoon in your mouth, Queen.
What, you spent five years
on an island with no room service...
...and suddenly you found religion?
This was my father's.
I found it when I buried him.
You said your father died
when the boat went down.
We both made it to a life raft.
There wasn't enough food...
...and water for both of us,
so he shot himself in the head.
As much as he was doing it
to give me a chance to survive...
...I believe that he was also atoning
for his sins.
I need to right the wrongs
done by my family...
...and I'm offering you the chance...
-...to right the wrongs done to yours.
- Oliver, what are you talking about?
Police never caught your brother's shooter.
- You leave Andy out of this.
- The bullets were laced with curare.
That's Floyd Lawton's M.O.
He is the sniper...
...that I stopped.
Are you trying to tell me
that you took down Andy's killer?
I'm giving you the chance...
...a chance to help
other people's families.
Do you remember when the people
in this city helped each other?
They can't do that anymore,
because a group of people...
...people like my father...
...they see nothing wrong
with raising themselves up...
...by stepping
on other people's throats.
It does need to stop,
and if it's not gonna be the courts...
...and it's not gonna be the cops...
...then it's gonna be me.
And, I hope, you.
I'm gonna go to the washroom, Rob.
Oh, that boy is long gone now.
- You still following the money trail?
- Mm-hm.
Don't we have accountants
for that sort of thing?
They're being singularly ineffective
in this instance.
Well, then it's fortunate
that I've solved the mystery.
I think I'm the culprit.
Two-point-six million
is a rather specific figure.
That's the exact amount
the company invested...
...in a friend's start-up venture
three years ago.
I will call Accounting. They'll clean it up,
then there's nothing to worry about.
Okay.
You really are putting a lot of hours...
...into this Declan thing.
- You actually think he's innocent?
- Someone does.
So you said,
but you didn't say was who.
A guardian angel.
The guy in the hood?
Wha--? You're kidding.
He tracked me down,
asked me to look into the case.
But you've met him?
But he goes against everything
that I was ever taught to believe in.
He breaks the law
and God knows what else.
How are you not afraid he won't do
"God knows what" to you?
He won't.
I don't know, I can feel it.
When I told you to meet someone,
this is far, far away from what I meant.
I got your message.
Is there a reason
we can't do this face to face?
You've met with Peter Declan.
You were right.
He might be innocent.
Declan said his wife blew whistle
on Brodeur the day she was murdered.
Then we need to get whoever
she told about Brodeur to testify.
He already has.
Matt lstook, Camille's supervisor.
Only he says that she didn't say
a word to him.
- He could be lying.
- Well, if he is, then he's very convincing.
He had the jury
and police believing him.
He hasn't been questioned by me.
I didn't become a lawyer
to break the law or hurt anybody.
I do what's necessary,
what people like Peter Declan need.
If what you're doing isn't wrong...
...then why are you hiding your face
with a hood?
To protect the ones I care about.
- That sounds lonely.
- It can be.
But not today.
I've got one question.
Why am I being fired?
- Ms. Smoak, isn't it?
- Yes.
And I am, without a doubt,
the single most valuable member...
...of your technical division. That's
including my so called "supervisor."
Letting me go would be
a major error for this company.
I agree,
which is why you're not being fired.
I assumed when you brought me
up here it was because...
It's because I wanted you to look
into something for me.
A variance of $2.6 million
on a failed investment...
...from three years ago.
It was authorized by my wife.
I was hoping you could find out
some of the details...
-...of the transaction for me.
- Find out?
Dig up. Discreetly.
I'm your girl.
I mean, I'm not your girl.
I wasn't making a pass at you.
Thank you for not firing me.
What the--?
Matt lstook.
You're him.
That hood guy
who's been terrorizing the city.
Peter Declan. Your lies
helped put him on death row.
Now, either it's time to tell me the truth,
or it's time for the 10:15 to Bltidhaven.
Ah. Okay. Okay. Brodeur paid me
to say that Camille never spoke to me.
But I didn't have anything to do
with her death.
Oh, God. Please let me go.
I'll do anything.
- You can have the file.
- What file?
Camille gave me a file of evidence
against Jason Brodeur.
- Where is it?
- Let me go, and I'll tell you.
Wait! Wait! Wait! Don't go!
Wait! Wait! Wait!
Don't go! Uh, it's in my desk!
The file, it's in my desk at the office!
You can have it! Get me out of here!
What is that? I'm so hungry.
It smells really good.
Hey, fine, don't share.
Hey-
I'm not gonna kill the bird.
Compliments of Matt lstook.
- What's in here?
- Leverage on Jason Brodeur.
Enough to help save
Peter Declan's life.
As an attorney,
I never would've gotten a file like this.
I always thought the law was sacred.
It fixed everything.
And now, Laurel?
Now what do you think?
I think there's too many people in this
city who only care about themselves.
People who are selfish.
I think they need someone who cares
about the lives of other people.
Someone like you.
Oh, my God.
- What's wrong with your face?
- What do you mean?
There's something really weird on it,
like this thing with your mouth.
- It looks like it's in the shape of a smile.
- Yes. That's cute.
- So why are you grinning?
- I took your advice with Laurel...
-...to be myself.
- And?
-It's helping.
- I got mad relationship skills, bro.
Let me know
if you need trendy places to propose.
I think you're getting
a little bit ahead of yourself. Little bit.
Rob. You gotta keep up.
Hey, you look busy.
Is that the Declan case?
There was a funny development on that.
Matt lstook, he, uh, filed a police report.
He said the Hood harassed him
last night.
And that's funny, because I gave
my daughter lstook's name.
- Dad, I--
- He's a vigilante.
He's a damn criminal,
and you working with him.
- That makes you an accessory.
- I'm trying to save an innocent man's life.
No, you're breaking the law.
I wouldn't have to if the police
had done their job right in the first place.
I asked you how you got this case.
You lied to me straight to my face. Eh?
I thought you and I didn't do that.
Guess I was wrong.
Your Honor,
the mere existence of the file proves...
...that Mr. lstook perjured himself
for Jason Brodeur's benefit.
That's slander.
Jared Swanstrom, Your Honor.
I represent Jason Brodeur
and Brodeur Chemical.
The interests of justice requires you
to stay the defendant's execution...
...pending exploration
of the newly discovered evidence.
Ours isn't a court ofjustice,
Ms. Lance.
It's a court of law.
And under the law,
your evidence is sufficient...
...to warrant a stay of execution.
Your motion for habeas corpus
is denied.
This isn't over. I've got the loose end now.
And no matter what happens, I'll pull
on it until your whole world unravels.
STOCK".
Declan's lawyer is pulling me into this.
I'm gonna go to prison, if not for
murder, then this dumping thing!
That won't happen.
There are steps we can take.
You saw her. She's going after me!
She'll wanna meet with her client
after what happened in court today.
We have friends up in Iron Heights.
Prison can be a dangerous place.
We're not done yet.
I'm an attorney. Trust me, we're done.
What do you need to free
Peter Declan?
At this point...
...nothing short of a signed
confession from Brodeur.
- Where are you going?
- To get a confession.
The company Mrs. Queen-- Steele.
Mrs. Queen-Steele. Is she hyphenate?
She seems like a woman
who would hyphenate.
Right. The company she invested in
doesn't exist.
- I don't understand.
- There was no investment.
The money was used to set up
an offshore LLC called Tempest.
Don't recall the name being under
Queen Consolidated.
It's not. There's nothing registered
with the secretary of state.
No federal tax records,
no patent applications filed.
But in 2009 Tempest purchased
a warehouse in Starling City.
- Enough moping.
- Mm.
You quit. It's done.
My advice would be to move on.
Ah. If it were only that easy.
Except it is.
Personal security is dangerous.
Your nephew already lost his father.
He can't lose his uncle too.
Does it ever bother you they never
caught the guy who killed Andy?
You know, when I was in Afghanistan,
I had a job and I did it.
When I could, I'd help out
the people there so that...
...in some small way, when I left,
I could believe I left it a better place.
But ever since I've been home,
all I do is protect punks...
...and spoiled one-percenters.
I miss feeling like I'm making a difference.
Then get out of personal security
and go do something you believe in.
- Yeah, what if it's wrong?
- John, if you believe in something...
...how can it be wrong?
Jason Brodeur.
- What do you want?
- You'll confess...
...you arranged to have
Peter Declan's wife murdered.
What, so I can take his place
in prison?
So you can avoid the death penalty.
Except if I'm dead, well, then you got
no one to pin Camille's murder on.
You need me
to exonerate Peter Declan.
Maybe you could try to force me
to sign a confession or something-- Ahh!
That might be difficult.
My hand!
Just answer it.
- What?
- It's Ankov.
It's going down. One hour.
What's going down in an hour?
What?
Let's just say Peter Declan's
execution is getting moved up.
Okay, you have to listen to me.
We still have a shot.
You remember the friend I mentioned?
The one who believes in you?
He's working on something.
I told you, Jason Brodeur is powerful.
Time to unlock the cages.
I've been here before.
These lawyers holding out
these little nuggets of hope.
What?
What the--?
Secure all corners in cell block C.
The warden is setting up
a secure perimeter in C block.
- Stay here, Ms. Lance.
- Wait!
Let's go.
GO, go!
Stop!
- Open up the generator area!
- Laurel.
Ms. Lance, stay back. Area secured.
Laurel.
Sweetie.
- What are you...?
- I'm all right.
- You sure?
- I'm sorry about what I said to you.
You were right.
Brodeur's bodyguard confessed...
...to Camille Declan's murder.
We got the wrong guy.
But listen to me.
I'm right too, about him.
He's dangerous. He's outside the law.
I know.
He's a killer.
He would have killed that man.
I looked in his eyes.
It's like he had no remorse.
Hey-
Please.
I'm starving.
I never killed anything before.
I'm sorry.
Let's get you home, sweetie.
How did he get
into that prison anyway, huh?
A grown man in an outfit and a hood...
...that kind of stands out a little,
doesn't it?
He actually wasn't wearing
the outfit this time.
He was in a prison guard uniform
and a ski mask.
- What?
- Nothing.
I just had an idea.
Get in the car.
Okay, here's the security footage
from the Exchange Building shooting.
- I've already scrubbed through all of it.
- Yeah, well, we're gonna do it again.
When you went through
the security tapes...
...you were looking for a guy
in a green hood?
And what do you want me to look for,
a man in a wig and a tutu?
I want you to look for anything that's
out of the ordinary, okay? Just look.
Hey, whoa, whoa. Wait. Wait.
Go back 10 seconds. What is that?
I'll be damned.
Play that again.
Thank you, Laurel.
Don't thank me.
Thank Brodeur's bodyguard Ankov
for flipping him.
I think there's someone that wants
to see you.
Izzy.
At least five federal, state,
and local agencies...
...are seeking millions of dollars in fines
and environmental cleanup costs...
...from Brodeur Chemical.
New facts have come to light
that Brodeur Chemical employee...
...Camille Declan had discovered
Brodeur was illegally disposing waste...
...and had collected a file of evidence
against her employer...
...before her murder in 2007.
Peter Decian, who was convicted
of killing his wife...
...has been released
and the case has been reopened.
Yeah. Bird. I know.
Shengcun not mean "bird."
Shengcun mean "survive."
You speak English?
You want survive this place,
bird not last thing you kill.
And forget her.
You look at that all day,
you not survive this place.
You wanted to see me?
You look nervous, Moira.
Do I have a reason to be?
We all do.
A modern-day Robin Hood.
What? Are you worried that
your net worth makes you a target?
Jason Brodeur.
Adam Hunt.
Warren Patel.
Tell me you see a connection, Moira.
- He's not targeting the rich.
- No, he's not.
He's targeting the list.
You here for the bodyguard position?
Because the new guy just quit.
No, I'm not.
I'm here about the other position.
Just to be clear,
I'm not signing on to be a sidekick.
But you're right.
Fighting for this city needs to be done...
...and you'll do this with
or without me.
- Yeah.
- But with me...
...there'll be fewer casualties,
including you.
Diggle, I'm not looking for
anybody to save me.
Maybe not, but you need someone
just the same.
You are fighting a war, Queen...
...except you have no idea
what war does to you.
How it scrapes off
little pieces of your soul.
And you need someone
to remind you...
...of who you are,
not this thing you're becoming.
- Oliver Queen.
- What is this?
- You can't barge in here.
- I got a badge and a gun that say different.
- What the hell is going on?
- Oliver, what's happening?
You're under arrest for obstruction
ofjustice, aggravated assault...
- Walter, stop them.
-...trespassing, acting as a vigilante...
- Are you out of your mind?
-...and murder.
You have the right to remain silent.
If you give up that right...