[CHAINS CLANGING]
OLIVER:
My name is Oliver Queen.
To my family,
I am the brother and son...
...who just returned home
after being lost at sea five years ago.
They don't know I came back with
a mission to bring justice to our city...
...and they never can.
The men and women
I've targeted are dangerous, corrupt...
...a virulent cancer.
Cancers like James Holder,
whose corporation...
...put defective smoke detectors
in low-income housing in the Glades.
There have been many fires
and too many funerals.
But cancers can be fought
and conquered.
All it takes is a surgeon...
...and the right instrument.
[CHUCKLES]
Other than the bill I got handed
by my legal team...
...I'm feeling pretty good.
Now that this lawsuit's been settled...
...we can focus our attention
on Unidac Industries.
[CHUCKLES]
Okay. I'll see you in the office
first thing.
[SCREAMS]
I have armed security inside.
All I have to do is call out.
Go ahead. They can't hear you.
-What the hell do you want?
-How many people died in those fires?
How many?
The courts say you don't owe
your victims anything. I disagree.
James Holder, you...
[GUNSHOT THEN HOLDER GRUNTS]
[GRUNTING]
OLIVER: It's no surprise a man as corrupt as
James Holder has more than one enemy.
[GRUNTS]
The bullet. Poison.
[GROANS]
OLIVER:
Who are you?
Why did you shoot me?
[YAO FEI IN CHINESE]
[GRUNTS]
[SCREAMING]
[COMPUTER BEEPING]
Damn it.
[CHATTERING]
What happened? Thea okay?
Cops brought her home.
She and some of her friends broke into
a store tried on some dresses last night.
Lit up the breathalyzer
like a Christmas tree.
So how was your evening, sir?
After I said I had to go bathroom
at dinner and never came back?
I guess from now on
I'll be watching you pee.
Thank you, officers.
My wife and I appreciate it.
-I'll see you out.
-Thank you.
Last time it was public intoxication.
This time breaking and entering.
My, how we are moving up
in the criminal world.
When you pay off the store owner
you should check out the merchandise.
-They got some pretty killer outfits.
-Thea, go get ready for school.
Uh, you know, I was thinking
of taking a sick day.
Fine, then get some sleep.
You look like crap.
You're letting her play hooky?
When your sister gets like this,
it's best to give her space.
She's testing you.
Yes. Who'd she learn that from?
Mom.
When I was her age, you let me
get away with murder. Looking back...
...I could have used less space
and more parenting.
It doesn't make sense.
Holder fits the profile. Wealthy dirtbag.
Red meat for the hood.
We recovered one arrow.
This time cause of death
is a double tap through the heart...
...and our perp doesn't use firearms.
He's figured out there's easier ways
to kill people than with a bow and arrow.
And it's like you said,
the guy's a whack job.
OLIVER:
The bullets were laced with curare.
A rare and deadly poison.
The killer's unique MO.
He's killed all over the world.
Chicago, Markovia, Corto Maltese.
Interpol even has a codename for him.
Deadshot.
I was prepared to give James Holder
a chance to right his wrongs...
...but this Deadshot has no morality...
...no honor, no code.
He doesn't kill for justice, which makes
him as dangerous as anyone on my list.
In fact, it puts him right at the top.
OLIVER:
What do you think?
-Great spot for a nightclub or what?
-Sweet.
If you're thinking calling it Queens,
I don't think you're gonna get...
...the clientele you were hoping for.
Private office?
For the private one-on-one meetings,
I would imagine.
Hopefully the occasional
two-on-one meeting.
[TOMMY LAUGHS]
Man, are you sure you wanna do this?
It's not like you really have
any experience in running a...
Well, running anything.
How about tomorrow night, the two of us
go and scope out the competition.
There's a new club opening downtown.
It's called Poison. Max Fuller owns it.
-Max Fuller.
TOMMY: Mm-hm.
-I slept with his fiancée.
-Yeah, before the wedding.
It was at rehearsal dinner.
The rehearsal dinner
is technically before the wedding. Ha, ha.
-Right?
-Ha, ha.
And besides,
who stays mad at a castaway?
Aw, damn it, I gotta roll. Anyway,
I'll see you later, man. Good place.
See you.
So...
...what do you think?
I'm here to provide security,
not a commentary.
Oh, come on, Dig, do me a favor.
Speak freely, please.
Well, this is the Glades, right?
Your rich friends wouldn't
come to this neighborhood.
I am Oliver Queen, right?
People would stand in line
for three hours if I opened a club.
No one who lives in the Glades
would see a penny of those charges.
We make it a successful business,
we gentrify the neighborhood.
I was wondering
when we would get to that.
The white knight swooping in
to save the disenfranchised.
And all by his lonesome
with no help from anybody.
Wow.
You don't think very much of me,
do you?
No, actually, sir, I have a very
high regard for how perceptive you are.
Sir.
OLIVER: The nightclub will conceal
my base underneath...
...and provide an alibi for where
Oliver Queen spends his nights.
Hey, do you have the depos
on the Jergens case?
Yeah, they're around here somewhere.
-I was just surfing the net.
-Really?
Joanna, I'm over him.
And you don't believe me.
I would have if I wouldn't have just
caught you trolling for articles on him.
I wasn't trolling.
I don't wanna be the one to remind you
that he cheated on you, Laurel.
With your sister.
I appreciate your self-control.
You're stuck. The reason I know this
is the fact that only relationship...
...you've had since Oliver
is with his best friend.
It is time to move on. It is past time.
-I've been busy. I work a lot.
-Okay.
That's gotta stop.
So we are going out tonight.
And we are gonna have some shots
and we are gonna dance with men...
...that we don't know
and we are gonna stay out way too late.
Oh. Heh.
Jergens depos.
I really don't think
I can go out tonight.
It is adorable that you actually think
I'm giving you a choice.
I want you to come home
right after school.
Uh, can't. Margot and I
are gonna go to the mall.
What, more shopping?
Tell Margot you'll have to cancel.
You're grounded for two weeks.
Grounded? I've never been grounded.
Well, you've never committed
larceny before.
-Since when do you care?
-I've always cared. I'm your mother.
Look, we've had a good thing
going on the last five years.
Why mess with that now?
No, we are paying off store owners
to keep your record clean.
-So clearly, it hasn't been working.
-And you're gonna teach me.
It's Oliver, isn't it?
His judgmental hypocrisy
is rubbing off on you.
No, I don't need Oliver to teach me
how to parent you.
-You'll be home by 4.
-Or what?
You're gonna call the cops on me? Heh.
Tell them I say hi.
[CHATTERING]
Got ballistics back
on the Holder murder.
They pulled two 7.62 millimeter
bullets out of him.
According to stippling and size
of the entry wound...
...they estimate shots were fired
from 100 yards away.
A hundred yards? So the hood
shoots him from another building...
...goes over to his place, he takes out
his security, then fires a few arrows?
And according to his tox screen,
his blood contained strychnos toxifera.
-What?
-Curare. It's a kind of poison.
Oh. Okay, so now we switch from arrows
to sniper bullets and poison.
-I'm not buying it.
-We still found arrows on the scene.
Solid evidence the hood was there.
-Where are you going?
-I'm going to get my own evidence.
OLIVER:
Seven-point-62 millimeter rounds.
The money trail
leads back to the Bratva.
The Russian mob.
Finally, some good luck.
[MAN SPEAKING IN RUSSIAN]
[OLIVER IN RUSSIAN]
[IN RUSSIAN]
[SCREAMS]
Pleased to meet you.
I apologize.
We meant no disrespect to a captain.
Particularly an American one.
So how can I be of assistance?
I'm in the market for a hired gun.
Someone the organization's
used before.
His calling card is a 7.62
millimeter round laced with curare.
-I know no man who uses such tools.
-But you can find out who does.
First, we will drink
to each other's health...
...then I will look into the identity
of this man you seek.
I will also confirm
that you are really Bratva captain.
Should this not be the case,
I will send my mechanic here...
...to find you and kill you
and your family.
MAN [ON TV]: Carl Rasmussen was found
shot to death in his home earlier this evening.
The police will not comment if there's a
connection between Rasmussen's death...
...and the murder of James Holder.
Mr. Rasmussen leaves behind
a wife and three children.
It's a great loss. Carl was a titan.
A titan who was looking to buy out
a company called Unidac Industries?
Well, industries are something
of a misnomer.
UI's recent activity was actually
looking into alternative energy.
The point my partner is trying to make is
that Rasmussen was the second bidder...
-...to lose his life.
-Are you implying something, detective?
Only that your husband's looking
into buying Unidac...
...and the competition
seems to be dropping like flies.
And I'm sure your veiled accusation...
...has nothing to do
with how you feel about my family.
Unidac's in receivership, detective.
Ownership is subject
to a liquidation auction...
...so that means
there are many prospective buyers.
And the auction's tomorrow...
...so if I was taking out
the competition...
...I have a lot of killing to do
in a very short amount of time.
We're just making rounds
with interested buyers.
-Let them know to be careful.
-Oh, yes.
And I'm overwhelmed...
...that Detective Lance
is concerned for our safety.
Well, thank you for your concern,
gentlemen.
Our security consultant, Mr. Diggle...
...is taking
all the necessary precautions.
Yeah. Right.
Well, if you need us...
...we're just a 911 call away.
[DANCE MUSIC PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
Ha, ha. Oh, my, this is gonna be killer.
If Max Fuller sees me here, I agree.
Aw, if you wanna run a business,
you gotta take a few risks.
-I don't see your name on the list.
-Mr. Queen.
Oh.
I have never seen this guy before
in my life. Ever.
TOMMY:
Oh, wow.
Doesn't you going out and having fun
violate some kind of law...
...like the ones
that are carved on a stone tablet.
-That's cute, Tommy.
TOMMY: Thanks.
I can see you two
are up to your old hunting patterns.
Just seeing what passes for fun
in Starling City after five years.
Ah. I'm sure you'll find that it hasn't been
same without you.
Big brother.
Oh, I am so wasted right now.
There is...
There is two of you.
I thought you were grounded.
I am. And thank you.
Thank you for that, by the way.
You're done for the night.
Oh, what are you gonna do?
-Tell mom?
OLIVER: Thea.
You are hanging
with the wrong people.
You're one to talk.
How much do you know about your
own so-called friends over here?
Thea, maybe you shouldn't...
Tommy, I think your BFF
has a right to know.
-Thea, let's go.
-Well, I guess they never told you...
...that they've been screwing
while you were gone.
-Look, man, I...
-Tommy.
It's okay.
You and me,
we're done for the night.
Take your hands off of me.
You're not my father.
And you're barely my brother.
MAX:
Well, well, look at this.
Oliver Queen.
Max Fuller.
How you been?
Happy you drowned.
-Hey, Max...
-Ugh!
MAX:
Get him up!
Hey, let him go, let him go.
Hey, I said let him go.
Told you he was gonna be pissed.
Back off, Merlyn.
This isn't your problem.
You wanna get to him?
You've gotta go through me.
Wow, they are probably gonna go
through me.
[ALL GRUNTING]
LAUREL:
So is this over, Max?
Or are you gonna have your boys
pound on me next?
You three consider yourselves
banned for life.
Get the hell out of my place.
Your club sucks anyway.
-You guys okay?
-Where'd you learn to do that?
Cop dad, remember? He made me
take self-defense classes.
OLIVER:
Laurel.
What Thea said...
Oliver, Tommy and I
don't need your blessing.
And I don't need your forgiveness.
[PANTING]
[COUGHING]
[BRANCHES CREAKING]
[POP MUSIC PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
Why don't you guys, uh, take a seat
and I will grab a couple of burgers...
...and some ice for those faces.
-Cute.
-That's my sister-in-law.
Who I will never speak to or look at.
Ever. Gonna grab a booth.
She's not wearing a wedding ring.
Brother out of the picture?
Yeah, you could say that.
Hey, you.
So sweet of you
to adopt two white boys.
They need a good role model.
That's my client Oliver Queen.
Looks like you're doing
a bang up job protecting him.
Look, man...
...about Laurel.
I was gonna tell you.
I was just trying
to figure out the right way.
To tell somebody
that you slept with their girlfriend...
...after they went missing
and were then presumed dead.
What, there's no greeting card
for that?
[CHUCKLES]
Look, it was wrong.
-And I'm sorry.
-Tommy.
I was dead.
No, man, you were with Laurel.
And whether you were dead,
or as it turns out, alive...
...on a deserted island,
you are my friend.
And me being with Laurel
violated that friendship...
-...in about 50 different ways.
-Thank you.
But it's okay.
How dangerous is this gig, anyway?
It's a cakewalk, Carla, don't worry.
Too late.
Or have you forgotten
this job got your brother killed?
Because, Dig, I haven't. I can't.
You are being
really chill about this. I...
[PHONE RINGING]
Hello?
[OLIVER SPEAKING IN RUSSIAN]
It's a Russian model calling me.
Can we...
Can I have a minute, please?
I can see now
why you were able to be so chill.
Enjoy.
So I checked out?
MAN [OVER PHONE]:
You did. His name is Floyd Lawton.
I have address, where he stayed
last time he was in Starling City.
[OVER PHONE]
But that is all.
Let's hope he's a creature of habit. Go.
MAN:
1700 Broadway, Pape Motel, Room 52.
You'll leave us out of this, yes?
[OVER PHONE] Assuming Mr. Lawton
doesn't kill you first.
[BONES CRACKING]
[CLEARS THROAT]
OLIVER:
Felicity Smoak?
Hi. I'm Oliver Queen.
Of course.
I know who you are, you're Mr. Queen.
No, Mr. Queen was my father.
Right, but he's dead.
I mean, he drowned.
You didn't, which means you could
come down to the IT Department...
...and listen to me babble.
Which will end.
In three, two, one.
Having trouble with my computer...
...and they told me that
you were the person to come and see.
I was at my coffee shop surfing the web
and I spilt a latte on it.
-Really?
-Yeah.
Because these look
like bullet holes.
My coffee shop
is in a bad neighborhood.
If there is anything
that you can salvage from it...
...I would really appreciate it.
Mm-hm.
Wow. Well, good, you're here.
I'm under house arrest, remember.
Do you wanna wear
the Calvin Klein or the Zac Posen?
To dinner?
-I was just gonna wear pajamas.
-To Walter's stock auction.
-I think I rather be grounded.
-No, it's important that you come.
Important to whom?
To me.
All right, listen to me.
When you were 4 years old,
you came home one day with a cat.
It was a stray, it was filthy
and it was mean.
But you stood there and you declared
that it was coming to live with us.
Your father came home
from the office...
...and he saw what was going on...
...and he sat you down
and he explained to you...
...that the cat was in fact a tiger
and that we needed to get it home.
And somehow...
...you understood.
Robert was always so good
at getting through to you.
I was always so jealous of that. I...
You never talk about him.
Dad.
That's the first time
you talked about him in years.
Well, I think you and I
have gotten into some bad habits.
There's been a lot
that has changed recently, Thea...
...and I think
that maybe this can change too.
FELICITY: It looks like blueprints.
-Do you know what of?
-The Exchange Building.
-Never heard of it.
It's where the Unidac Industries
auction is scheduled to take place.
-I thought you said that was your laptop.
-Yes.
Look, I don't wanna get
in the middle...
...of some Shakespearean
family drama thing.
-What?
-Mr. Steele marrying your mom.
Claudius, Gertrude, Hamlet.
I didn't study Shakespeare at any of
the four schools that I dropped out of.
Mr. Steele is trying to buy
Unidac Industries.
And you've got a company laptop...
...associated with one of guys
he's competing against.
-Floyd Lawton.
-No.
Warren Patel.
Who's Floyd Lawton?
He is an employee of Mr. Patel,
evidently.
OLIVER: The Exchange Building is surrounded
by three towers...
...with eye lines into the building.
Lawton can get his kill shot off
from virtually anywhere.
But I can't cover the area.
I can't protect
all of Deadshot's targets.
I can't do this alone.
-You son of a bitch!
-Detective, quiet!
You've got a pair on you, pulling this.
Floyd Lawton's the one targeting
the buyers interested in Unidac.
Interpol calls him Deadshot
because he never misses.
You can look this up after I go.
Yeah, and stop chasing you,
I suppose?
Warren Patel hired Lawton.
I can't be sure who they're targeting,
might be the buyers...
...and I can't protect them
in a space that big.
-I need your help.
-Heh. Yeah? Professional help?
Lawton laces his bullets with curare.
-Tell your men to wear Kevlar.
-I'll them to shoot you...
[SOFT JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING OVER
SPEAKERS AND PEOPLE CHATTERING]
Well, it's quite a turnout.
Well, it's quite an opportunity,
actually.
But regardless of the outcome
of the auction...
...I'm already a winner because I have
two beautiful women...
-...at my side tonight.
MOIRA: Two?
WALTER:
Thanks for coming, Thea.
It means a lot to your mother.
And me.
Mr. Steele, the auction
will be opening in five minutes.
-Please make sure your bid is ready.
-Thank you, Gina.
-Shall we?
MOIRA: Mm-hm.
I got him.
Warren Patel.
I need you to come with me, sir.
Unit one, all clear.
Unit two, you copy.
HILTON [OVER RADIO]: We have Patel
in custody. Still no sign of Lawton.
-Unit three?
WOMAN: I'm at the northwest perimeter.
-All clear.
-Unit four?
MAN 1:
Parking structure is secure.
-Unit five, what's your status?
MAN 2: This is unit five.
All clear.
TOMMY:
Oh, what a shock.
Heh. It is Friday night.
What are you doing here?
Well, I am an attorney
and this is a courthouse...
...so I think the better question is
what are you doing here?
I wanted to talk to you
about last night.
You mean how I saved your asses?
You're welcome.
Okay, first of all, we shall never,
ever speak of that ever again.
Secondly, I think you know
that I meant the other thing.
-I don't care to talk about that.
-I spoke to Oliver.
He was surprisingly cool.
That's because he knew.
Did you see his face
when Thea told him?
Tommy, he didn't even blink.
Trust me, he knew.
-Then why didn't he say anything?
-I don't know.
Maybe because he knows
he doesn't have any right to judge me.
You got a silver lining, though.
Now that the whole truth,
and nothing but, is out...
...is there a chance now
for you and me?
You said you didn't think
that I was a one girl type of guy.
I'm gonna prove you wrong.
-By dating me.
-By being better.
By being someone that you deserve
and that you want to be with.
Well, that's certainly a guy
I'd be interested in meeting.
Good.
Now how about we start, ahem,
by getting you the heck out of here.
Come on, it is Friday night.
Come on.
-Fine.
-Good.
[PEOPLE CHATTERING]
-Don't you scrub up nice?
-Here to support my family.
Yeah, me too, God help me.
Thank you.
[SCOFFS]
Dig. Got your eyes open?
That's what I'm here for.
And answering patronizing questions.
This guy's out of time.
If he's gonna do something,
it's gonna happen before the auction.
Sir?
I heard the story on the radio.
WALTER:
Oliver.
So pleased you were able to attend. Heh.
OLIVER [OVER RADIO]: Walter, the police said
that some of the Unidac bidders were murdered.
I think that we should be
a little bit more careful.
My mother's already lost a husband.
If Moira shared your concern,
she wouldn't have come.
And she definitely
wouldn't have brought your sister.
Hi.
Oliver, what a wonderful surprise.
I need you to get them out of here
right now.
[ALL SCREAMING]
MAN 1: Down.
MAN 2: Get down.
Are you okay? Are you hurt?
No, I'm fine. Where is Walter?
-Go, go, go!
-Walter's fine.
-I have to get you out of here.
-No, them! Them.
Go, I'll find him, I'll find him.
[ALL SCREAMING]
[GRUNTING]
Drop your guns.
I admire your work.
Guess you won't be extending me
any professional courtesy.
We're not in the same line of work.
Your profession is murder.
You've taken lives.
For the good of others.
You're out for yourself.
[CHUCKLES]
[DIGGLE GROANING]
[GASPS]
[IN CHINESE]
[OLIVER GRUNTS]
[BRANCH BREAKS]
[COUGHING]
[GROANS]
Hey.