My name is Oliver Queen.
After five years in hell,
I returned home with only one goal,
to save my city.
But my old approach wasn't enough.
I had to become someone else.
I had to become something else.
I had to become the Green Arrow.
Previously on Arrow...
Those little yellow pills you swallowed,
they do a few interesting things,
including making you cooperative.
Thanks to the algae we engineered
from Star City bay,
the air down here
is now perfectly breathable.
Genesis is almost ready.
We're much too close to play games.
- Do you remember what I promised you?
- A new beginning.
And you will have it.
Once we've brought this world to its end.
Andy's working with Darhk
and has been the entire time.
Andy!
Your brother's way beyond reach,
Mr. Diggle.
If I'd listened to you
instead of trusting my brother,
Laurel would be alive right now.
If Darhk wins, Laurel died for nothing.
He feels unstoppable.
- Because of his magic.
- It's too strong.
You always find a way,
and you have to find a way now.
Now is not the time for panic.
We let him rot in prison.
Clearly, you overestimate
Damien Darhk's capacity for forgiveness,
which is to say that he has any.
Should Damien prove to be unreasonable,
I have implemented contingencies.
My buddies.
Long time, no see.
I brought my posse. Hope you don't mind.
What happened to Ian and Judy?
They come down with that nasty, little flu
that's been going around?
Some were wary of this meeting
given that...
You all abandoned me to my imprisonment?
I visited.
Someone should teach
this evil organization
a lesson in helping their fellow man.
I'm sure it's all
just a simple misunderstanding.
After all, why would I rely solely
on the word of Malcolm Merlyn?
- He can be so underhanded.
- Cute.
And our illustrious council
has worked together
for such a very long time.
I'm glad that we still have your trust.
Of course. I had a lot of time
to reflect while I was in prison,
mostly about religion and bundt cake.
But after much thought, I realized that...
Oh! Almost forgot.
Did my little incarceration
delay Genesis at all?
Of course not.
Genesis is much bigger
than just one person.
Gold star for you.
Where was I? Oh, that's right.
My jailhouse epiphany.
If I could escape prison
without your help,
what do I need any of you for?
Milo, you really have not been
paying attention, have you?
Anyone else care to do something stupid?
No takers?
Pity.
Ladies and gentlemen
and recently deceased,
it is time to begin
the final phase of Genesis.
Milo Armitage.
SCPD found him
in an alley outside Ellendale,
and across town,
Phaedra Nixon.
- Okay. So what am I missing?
- They were both HIVE.
You probably don't recognize
Phaedra and Milo
now that they're dead, or maybe you were
too busy running for your life, but...
They were with Darhk
when he held us hostage.
And now they're dead.
What, so you think
crazy-pants Lonnie Machin's back in town?
No. His grudge is against Darhk, not HIVE.
You think Darhk is cleaning house?
Well, HIVE didn't lift a finger
to break him out of Iron Heights.
That was all Andy and Merlyn.
Okay, well, if Darhk is settling scores,
then now might be the time to hit him.
We have seen how powerful he is.
I can't risk losing anyone else.
We can't just sit on our hands, Oliver.
We're not just sitting on our hands,
but before we do anything,
we need to know
that we can counteract his magic.
Well, is that even possible?
I think it might be.
I was finally able to
get in touch with Constantine
and he put me onto someone
who he thinks may be able to teach me
how to defend against Darhk's magic.
Okay. Well, I'm not just saying this
because I love Harry Potter,
but why are we not all
taking those lessons?
Well, it is easier said than done,
and apparently, quite dangerous.
So, I have to go to Hub City
for a day or two.
Okay. In that case,
can I take the weekend with Alex?
Kind of wants to go away, clear our heads.
That sounds like a good idea.
I think that...
Actually, I think everyone should
take a little time.
Lay low, but stay available, and
we will deal with Darhk when I get back.
Okay.
Let him in.
Mind stepping out?
"HEY. you. How you holding up?"
You've, um, looked better.
Considering I've spent two weeks
in a bomb-proof tungsten-encased bunker,
I think I look pretty good.
You hungry?
Mmm. How long have those been there?
That was lunch.
It might have even been today's.
Yeah, I think I'll pass.
Oliver is leaving tonight
on some Magical Mystery Tour.
He wants me to stay put and do nothing
until he comes back.
Magical Mystery Tour?
Yeah, it's a long story.
But the point of it is that he thinks
it's too dangerous for any of us
to go after Darhk or Andy
until he gets the right magical know-how.
- I can see you're thrilled about that.
- Mmm.
If you think you have it bad,
try remembering you're not the one
being held prisoner in a metal box.
Look, sweetheart.
We've talked about this.
Andy has been inside of A.R.G.U.S.
He's been inside of our home.
It's too dangerous for you
to be either place right now.
I don't want you in either place, either.
Oh, I got you. I got you.
- Let my agents see what they can find.
- Yeah.
And, as much as you don't wanna hear it,
- Oliver has a point.
- Mmm.
HIVE is too dangerous for you
to go off half-cocked, John.
Well, it's always serious
when you call me "John."
Well, John, why don't you
make yourself useful
by grabbing some diapers while you're out.
We're running low,
and I hate asking my people to get them.
- You got it.
- Mmm-hmm.
- Back in an hour?
- Or less.
Good-bye, Daddy. Honey, say bye.
- You've been living down here?
- Seemed to make the most sense.
Where's all your stuff?
It's just in storage.
You know me, I don't need much.
Maybe like a plant?
Like a fern or something.
They thrive in places like this.
How could I forget? Come to see me off?
You were pretty stingy on the details
about this "magic tutor"
Constantine referred you to.
That is, sort of, my MO.
Don't talk to me like I'm other people.
What has you so worried?
Darhk's idol,
the type of magic that he's using,
I've seen it take good people
and turn them dark, soulless,
and almost inhuman.
And you're afraid
that's gonna happen to you?
There's an argument to be made
that I'm already there.
- That's not funny.
- I am not joking.
There is no length that I will not go to,
to avenge Laurel.
To stop Darhk
from hurting anyone ever again.
And I honestly don't know
where that path will lead.
I'm coming with you.
Felicity.
Just because we're not together
doesn't mean you have to do this alone.
And, I've already chartered
the company jet. Mr. Dennis was furious.
And I've booked us a room, rooms.
With points.
Should I even try
and talk you out of this?
No. You've met my mother.
Same DNA.
Did you see anyone else here?
Which way? Get out of here, now.
What the hell?
Sorry, man.
But I'm not playing anymore! Whoo!
You still got those quick reflexes, John.
Too bad they couldn't save your partner.
Don't you dare say anything about her!
Well, you got a gun. Make me!
Hey, honey, it's a little tough for me
to talk right now.
You'll wanna hear this,
satellite track just picked up Andy.
Let me guess, he's somewhere south of Main
between Grammercy and Addison, right?
How do you know that?
Because I'm trading shots with him
right now.
- Johnny.
- Yell at me later. Just send backup.
He's at the Grammercy Power Plant.
How soon can your men get here?
Five minutes, ten tops.
That's too long.
Johnny, you need to wait.
You have no tactical advantage in there.
Well, I can't wait. If I do, he gets away.
I can't let that happen. Not again.
Your judgment is compromised.
Maybe it is.
But it doesn't mean I'm wrong. Get here!
Johnny! Johnny!
So, what exactly are we looking for?
High roller room.
When you said that you had found someone
to teach you magic, I was thinking, like,
a mountain top or a hidden temple,
not Hub City's
premiere underground casino.
Well, with Constantine, I have learned
to expect the unexpected.
I'm betting on Fortuna.
Now, he was a little bit vague
with the specifics. He just said,
"Pitch game, first base, mate,
see if you're worthy."
Wow.
Okay, pitch game, blackjack,
uh, dealer using up to two decks.
"First base,"
first seat on the dealer's left.
I think we're in the right place.
I'm not so sure that finding this guy
depends on gambling.
It's not gambling when I play.
Alex?
Hello? Alex?
Hey, morning. And here I thought
you were gonna sleep past breakfast.
I almost did. I'm so foggy.
Yeah, you were exhausted. You passed out
five minutes after we left the city.
Oh.
Guess I was really tired.
See, it just proves how badly
you needed this trip. We both did.
Now, you ready for some
famous eggs Benedict?
You poached eggs?
Hey, I'm not just a cutthroat
political operative. I contain multitudes.
Mmm-hmm.
And you also wear a very mean apron.
Well, you should see
what I have on underneath.
Mmm.
I forgot how good you were at this.
Ah, like riding a bike.
Rough beat.
Indeed. I should probably head home soon
before they take my shoes.
Well, you never know
when your luck's gonna change. Trust me.
That's so kind. Muchas gracias.
De nada.
Oh, boom!
Come to mama. I mean. What?
I'm starting to think
that this guy's gonna be a no-show.
Right.
It's because he's not a guy, amor.
Esrin Fortuna.
Tell John Constantine
he still owes me money.
Stay right where you are,
you son of a bitch!
It's funny.
I was gonna tell you the same thing.
Bravo, John.
You played the script out perfectly.
What the hell are you talking about?
Oh, don't worry about it.
I'll explain everything.
After you wake up.
Sorry, this place isn't as fancy
as the cage you kept me in
for three months.
Where the hell am I?
You've got bigger worries.
Mr. Darhk is on his way.
To do what?
Well, he's not coming here
to play gin rummy.
I'm supposed to prep you.
Glad to see you're picking up
your psycho boss's old habits.
I'm sorry, but is the man
that locked me up in a cage
and beat me half to death
questioning my savior's orders?
Damien Darhk is no one's savior!
He's a liar and a monster.
The Romans said the same thing
about Jesus.
Just do whatever you gotta do, man! Do it!
Wow.
There's that temper I remember.
You know, it's a good thing
that Sara's not gonna have to grow up
with it like I did.
You keep my daughter's name
out of your mouth!
How could you do this to everyone again
for a second time?
Oh. Oh, I know what you're doing.
You're referring
to my former wife and son.
I left that life a long time ago, John.
You can't even say their names.
Carly. Andy, Jr.
They were your family. They still are!
My family is HIVE.
Okay. So since Oliver
doesn't seem to wanna ask it, um...
Why is an immortal shaman
playing blackjack
in Hub City's premiere underground casino?
Excuse me. Immortal?
- You see any wrinkles on my face?
- And shaman?
A shaman is someone who has influence
in the world of good and evil spirits.
Blackjack is just a hobby. This way.
You're planning on teaching me magic
in the back room of a casino?
You want to learn the dark arts,
Mr. Queen? We cannot do that here.
This is, by far, the coolest high roller
room I've ever seen.
We've left the casino behind, amor.
And that plane of existence.
I've been in a chamber like this before
on an island named Lian Yu.
Yes, Lian Yu is a place of nexus.
Just like your home.
Star City?
There's a nexus chamber there as well.
Wait, you didn't think
it was a coincidence
that Damien Darhk chose that city?
You know Darhk?
I wouldn't be much of a shaman
if I didn't.
A special brand of
nasty loco that one is.
So, if you know Darhk,
why haven't you tried to end him?
That's not the way of things. We immortals
tend to stay out of the affairs of men.
Unless someone owes you money.
Recognize this handsome gent?
Darhk has a similar idol.
- It gives him his power.
- Mmm-mmm.
It only channels it.
Darhk's power comes from...
Death. The more people he kills,
the more powerful he becomes.
Not just a pretty face, this guy.
Yeah, except Oliver's not gonna go
kill a bunch of people
just to be on the same
level playing field as Darhk.
All things have their opposite.
Darhk draws his power from fear and death.
Its opposite is light and hope.
La luz del alma. "Light of the soul."
If you can channel La luz del alma,
you will be able to repel Darhk's magic.
Then that is what I'm here to learn.
I wish it were just that easy.
If the darkness inside you
outweighs the light,
instead of repelling Darhk's magic,
you'll end up fueling it.
You will only make him more powerful.
Are you getting a signal?
Nope. It's one of the benefits
of being on vacation.
Just wanted to call my brother.
You okay?
Seem to be having trouble relaxing.
Yeah, no, I'm...
You're probably gonna think
it's stupid.
Mmm, I can pretty much guarantee
that I won't.
It's this place. it seems too perfect.
Well, it sounds like it's been
way too long since you've left the city.
Yeah, maybe.
Do you hear that?
Yeah, I think people call that "nature."
No. That's...
That's not it.
I don't know,
maybe I'm just tired, but it...
It sounds like
everything is on a loop right now.
Does that sound crazy? That...
That's crazy.
Only a little, yeah.
Like, I think this is just
the last bit of you
trying to fight this vacation.
Yeah.
Hey, let all that go.
- Just be nappy. okay?
- Okay.
I sure am.
- All right.
It's time.
I know this feels personal, John.
But it isn't.
What's happening
is just what has to happen.
Ah!
Do it. Do it for Laurel.
She'd be so disappointed in you.
The only reason why you're still breathing
is because one of us is still human.
I'll hit you with a low dose
of Darhk's magic,
and then we'll take it up from there.
Don't I need an idol or a totem?
The tattoo Constantine gave you
does many things. Are you ready?
Yeah.
Um, I'm sorry. I just thought that these
magic lessons would have, you know, more
lessons.
Magic is a manipulation
of primordial energies.
Primordial as in pre-linguistic.
You'll probably want to
take a few steps back, amor.
Hmm? Mmm.
Two sides of you. Darkness. Light.
Focus on the light.
Good. But that might be,
as they call, "beginner's luck."
So, let's kick it up a notch or two, hmm?
The darkness and light are within you.
In truth, you're only fighting yourself.
The friends you've failed.
The people you've killed.
They have no place in this.
Don't give in. Cast aside your doubt.
Resist your darkness.
- What happened?
- He's not ready.
I'll get it. I'll get it.
Now, let's go again.
I could give you
an infinite number of tries.
It wouldn't change a thing.
What? No, I can do this.
I told you, if the darkness within you
is greater than the light,
you will only make your enemy stronger.
You've seen what's inside of you.
Now, tell me,
what could I possibly "teach" you
that would change what you saw?
Wait, so that's it? It's over?
There's nothing I can do for him.
It's not even getting dark out.
What's that?
It's 8:00 and it's raining outside,
but it's still light out.
Yeah, we're up north and...
Seriously. What's gotten into you?
You never even told me
where we were going.
And, how can you not hear that?
Thea, come on. We've been over this.
Seriously, listen, there's three chirps,
then a bark, then four chirps, and then
it just keeps repeating itself twice.
Okay, I think what's happening here
is you're beyond stressed...
No, okay. Alex, I am not stressed out.
Just listen.
There's gonna be a bark right now.
Since when did you start taking vitamins?
Now you're worried about my vitamins?
Where did you get those?
Ruvé. She said I needed to stay healthy.
Alex.
Where are we?
Is the reason that I don't
remember anything because you...
Did you drug me?
Thea, now you're talking crazy, okay?
No, I can't...
Where are you going? Thea?
What the hell, Johnny?
I told you to stand down!
I know. I know. But I couldn't...
You could've been killed!
I couldn't stand down,
not after what he did.
Then you are going to make
an orphan of your daughter,
because you are not seeing straight.
That's why tonight went south.
- It's okay.
- Lyla, listen, I know, I...
- I know I messed up.
- I know my head isn't on right,
but he's my brother.
And Laurel, she was like a sister.
I know. And it's horrible.
But, right now, Johnny,
you are not acting like the man I married.
You're the man I divorced.
Lyla, l...
I just wanted to help him...
To bring my brother back.
Then bring him to justice.
But do it the right way
I will. I will.
We'll find someone else
to teach you magic.
Someone with more patience
and less smelly incense.
She was right, you know?
It's not about the magic. It's about me.
If she didn't see anything
worthy inside you,
she never would have dealt with us.
She didn't deal with us.
She dealt with you.
She didn't reveal herself
until you offered her your chips.
That has always been the way
with us, Felicity.
You are the one who brings the light.
You know? I told you that I've seen magic
that's turned good people dark.
But all Fortuna did was
show me who I really am.
Don't do this.
Every time you face a setback,
you throw yourself a pity party.
This is not a "pity party."
It's acceptance.
You said it yourself. No matter what I do,
I'm always gonna revert back to the person
I became on the island.
You know, when I said that I was hurt.
I was going through one of the most
painful experiences of my life.
Oliver, you are not perfect.
None of us are.
Good news is,
is that all of us can change.
DARHKI Hmm.
Poor widdle Andy Diggle.
Did your big brother knock your noggin?
Bravo. Your performance was pitch perfect.
Thank you, sir.
I assume the tracker's in place?
We've already locked in on his location.
Well, then I believe it's time
for one last family reunion.
Oh, come on.
You're a bigger baby than Sara.
Ouch.
Is there anything else you can tell me
about their lockup?
Yeah, the place could've really used
some central heating.
Well, it was strange.
Torture just didn't seem
like the right play.
Why not just kill me?
What's that?
Proximity alarm.
Sweetheart, make sure
Sara's strapped in really tight.
- How's Sara?
- She's okay.
It's Director Michaels.
We have a code black.
We have two more bogies.
How the hell did they find us?
It's me. Andy let me go.
He probably tagged me with a tracker.
You can blame yourself
after we get out of this.
You mean, if we get out of this.
Where's your backup?
HIVE has them engaged elsewhere.
A.R.G.U.S. headquarters.
Where's your team?
They're not answering.
So much for "stay available."
We're on our own.
This rig was designed
to withstand just about anything.
Does that include magic?
It's me he's after. I'll draw him out.
No. If you were Darhk's objective,
he already had you.
He wanted you to lead him to me.
- What are you talking about?
- You need to get out of here now.
- Lyla, I'm not leaving you.
- Johnny.
I am not Amanda Waller.
If they use you against me,
I will give them whatever they want.
I need you both safe.
Oh, that was a fun bit of business.
Get him.
Ah!
You are a feisty one, Ms. Michaels.
You had your fun.
It's time for me to have mine.
Oh, it's been a while
since I've hit anybody with this thing.
I didn't think you got my message.
Sorry we're late.
Oliver's on Lyla and Darhk.
- Baby Sara.
- Oh. Hi. Hi, little one.
- Yeah. You got her?
- Yeah, yeah.
_OkaY-_OkaY-
All right.
Okay.
It's a small world, isn't it?
Your brother-in-law
being my loyal servant.
Thanksgiving at your home
is gonna be so interesting this year.
You seem like a likable guy, Oliver.
I bet you've got a lot of friends.
I'm going to enjoy
killing every last one of them.
No. Never again.
I bet you regret not pulling that trigger
the first time around.
What are you gonna do, John?
After Laurel, I left you alone to grieve.
I was being nice.
You have no idea
how much I hate being nice.
It isn't over.
You haven't been paying attention, Andy.
Darhk got out. I got out.
I'll get out again.
That mobile safe-house you've got
looked really homey.
Bet it gets cramped once Sara gets older.
Shut up.
She's gotta go to school eventually.
And Lyla, well, you can't watch her 24/7.
I said, "Shut your mouth," Andy.
Shut your damn mouth!
You're the one who's obviously
not payin' attention. Because this is war.
And women, children,
they're expendable in your war?
Genesis is coming, John.
Lyla and Sara won't be
the only women and children who die.
Tell me, how does it feel knowing that
you had no problem pulling the trigger
to protect a bunch of Afghanis
that you never knew,
but you don't have the guts
to do what's necessary,
to protect your own wife and child?
How's Lyla?
Um...
She's fine.
She's... Uh...
She unconscious, but she's fine.
Felicity's taking her and Sara back.
Darhk is... Darhk's in the wind.
John, what happened?
He was never gonna back off, Oliver.
My family,
they were never gonna be safe.
- Hey.
- Hi.
- Did you get in touch with Thea?
- Not yet.
You Okay?
Earlier, with Darhk, it worked.
He tried to use his magic on me,
and I was able to repel it.
That's incredible.
How'd you do it?
I heard your voice in my head.
You were reminding me
of all the good things
that I have in my life.
I heard Thea, I heard John.
I heard Laurel.
Just telling me to keep fighting,
to never give up.
Just telling me to have hope.
Hey-
- Sara? Where's Sara?
- No, no, no. She's fine. She's fine.
Felicity took her to Donna. She's okay.
But something's wrong.
I, um...
I had to put him down, Lyla.
(And)'-
I had to kill my baby brother.
He wasn't a brother to you, Johnny.
Not in the ways that really matter.
What happened?
He reached for my gun.
I didn't have a choice.
- Oh, no. No, no, no.
- What? What?
It's gone. Darhk took it.
Took what?
Rubicon.
I thought Rubicon was being stored
at A.R.G.U.S.
It was,
until Shadowspire tried to steal it.
After Waller's death, I had it moved
for security reasons.
To where?
It was under your skin?
A subdermal implant. Darhk ripped it out.
Lyla, you need to tell us what Rubicon is.
A ballistic launch override protocol,
designed to prevent any country,
even our own,
from firing a nuclear missile.
Something tells me
Darhk's plans aren't so benign.
With some work
and the right expertise,
Rubicon could be corrupted.
Instead of controlling nukes
to prevent them from being launched...
Oh, my God.
Darhk would control
the world's nuclear stockpile.
To what end? I don't mean to apply logic
to a bad guy's plot here,
but Darhk destroys the world, then what?
He'd be ruler of nothing.
Unless he wants to rebuild.
Andy told me that "Genesis" was coming.
I don't think so. Phil Collins said
they'd never tour again.
The Old Testament. The book of Genesis.
God wanted to give the world a do-over
so he destroyed it.
He destroyed it with a flood.
Rubicon is Darhk's flood.
So, nuclear annihilation
is Darhk's flood,
what's he planning on building as his ark?
English - SDH