My name is oliver queen.
After five years in hell,
I have come home
with only one goal--
To save my city.
Now others have
joined my crusade.
To them, I am oliver queen.
To the rest
of starling city,
I am someone else.
I am something else.
Previously, on "arrow"...
My sister. She was murdered,
and I can't tell anyone.
See, before, laurel, you were swinging
at your sister's killer.
Don't train for that. All right,
train for yourself.
Oliver: The serum that
you were exposed to,
It changes your body
but it also warps your mind.
You're not moving
very quickly this morning.
I just didn't sleep
much last night.
What are you doing here?
Oliver: Roy!
Where'd you go?
Sorry.
Get your head
in the game.
So is the culebra cartel and their
gajillion pounds of heroin.
They all showed up
about 30 minutes ago
And they haven't moved
from your location.
Oliver:
Copy that.
No sentries
outside.
If we're going to do this,
we need to do it now.
I've got north entrance,
dig's got south.
Roy...
East.
The roof.
You're on
over watch.
The culebras get their weapons
from the bratva.
All military grade.
I've got your backs.
Let's do this.
South is clear.
Nobody's home.
Roof's clear.
North is empty, too.
That doesn't make sense.
They all showed up
Half an hour ago
and never left.
They are in there somewhere.
[beep]
Looks like somebody
beat us here.
There's at least a few million
dollars worth of heroin.
[speaking spanish]
He took paco.
Whoever did this
ignored the drugs,
Took a gang member.
This was personal.
Yeah, more than that.
Whoever did this was
trying to send a message.
I think I know
what it is.
Guilty. Well, yeah.
The culebras are the bloodiest
gang in starling.
Who's the second bloodiest?
Culebras have a long standing rivalry
with the los halcones.
Thought you said this was
personal, not business.
There are only 86,000
pacos in starling,
Give or take 5,000
for a few nicknames.
Something tells me
that the culebra's
Long standing rivals will
narrow that down for us.
You know, when we find paco, he'll be
too dead to say anything.
I'm not looking for him. I'm looking
for whoever did this.
I will handle this.
Take the rest of the night.
I'll back you up.
Not dead on your feet,
you won't.
I'm sorry. I know I've been a
little out of it recently.
Don't be sorry.
Be rested.
If I let you get killed because
your reaction time is slow, ok?
There are a lot of halcones
members in starling city.
How about I take the ones north
of tenth street.
Oliver: You know, we've been
waiting here an hour.
After walking around
the block five times.
We need to work
on your patience.
Where is this guy?
And more importantly,
How is he going to help us
find out what this...
China white person is--
Chien na wei.
Whatever!
How is he going to help us find out what
she's doing in hong kong?
Waller hasn't been able
to locate chien na wei
Because she avoids using any
traceable forms of communication.
So he's the target now?
He's her delivery guy.
Her courier. But
he's not a target.
Waller doesn't want
you to kill him.
That's refreshing.
They'll use
a dead drop.
Leave behind information
for chien's network.
Information
waller intercepts.
I see him.
Stay on bluetooth.
I'll be right
behind you.
Ahh!
What was that?
Did he make you?
Yeah, I think he did.
He's gone.
Where is it?
Where's what?
The envelope.
The message.
We need it!
He must have stashed it somewhere
while you were chasing him.
I didn't see him
stash anything!
Yes, you did. You just don't
know it yet.
That's not bad.
Yeah. It's better
than I thought.
What the hell
was that?!
Today's lesson.
Fighting's about
Being surprised and not getting rattled.
You look rattled.
Try angry.
Another lesson, then.
It's not about you getting
knocked to the mat.
It's if you get up.
Okay, fine.
Then let's go again.
Not tonight.
All right?
I got to
close up shop.
And you need to
get some rest.
Let those
muscles recover.
Make sure you get some protein
within the hour, all right?
Yeah, egg whites.
They're my new bff.
Oh, that's disgusting.
No, no, no,
two blocks from here--
Korean tacos.
Korean tacos?
Trust me.
They're heaven.
Come on, I'm buying.
Hey, can I ask
you a question?
You just did.
Kidding. What?
You know how to do
a blood test, right?
I know just enough
to make me dangerous.
And, well, me holding a syringe,
Well, that makes me
more dangerous.
Why?
I need you
to test my blood.
For what?
And don't say stds,
Because that would
be crossing a line.
For mirakuru.
I don't need to check you for
traces of mirakuru.
You were cured.
I know, I--
If this is about
your sleep problems,
Mirakuru makes people
crazy strong
And crazy crazy. It doesn't make it
hard for them to get 8 hours.
Could you just...
Are you ok?
I mean, besides the whole
not sleeping thing.
Totally.
I'm fine.
I'm just looking for reasons
to help me sleep, you know?
Ok.
I'm looking for a crew member
named paco.
Emilio?
Paco!
That's what
they call him, ese!
Paco's his street name!
Who?!
Emilio.
Emilio ortega.
Thank you.
Felicity, I have a name.
Emilio ortega.
Pinging his cell's gps.
He's in the glades.
Ninth and hasen.
Why'd you kill
all those men?
What the hell are
you talking about?
What are you doing?!
Get out of here.
Oh, my god.
Now, laurel!
No!
Ted didn't do this.
Ted's been with me
For the past two hours.
He trained with me,
And then we went for dinner.
And that...
He wasn't here when we left.
Ok, that is ten minutes of my life
I am never getting back.
I'm clean?
Your cholesterol is a little high
for someone of your age,
But absolutely zero
mirakuru serum.
Congratulations.
Ahh, thank god.
Ok, you're acting like
I just told you
That the biopsy
came back negative.
What is going on?
It's--it's stupid.
You just had me
test your blood
For a serum you were
cured of six months ago.
I already knew it was stupid.
The reason I haven't
been sleeping
Is 'cause I've been
having dreams,
And not normal ones.
It was like I was remembering
the time I was out,
You know?
When slade oded me
on the mirakuru.
What do you remember?
Nothing much.
Just a feeling.
A feeling
of being...
Not me.
And being strong
and out of control,
But here's the thing--
In those dreams...
I killed sara.
This really had you worried?
Because the dreams, they didn't feel
like dreams, felicity.
They felt like memories.
I actually remembered throwing
arrows into her.
Crazy, right?
[chuckles]
Yeah.
Crazy.
Quentin:
So that's it?
I was with him
the whole time.
You can put me on the box
if you'd like.
If I wanted to give my
daughter a polygraph,
I'd have done it back when
you discovered beer.
So listen,
what's the story
With you and this guy,
anyway?
He's just my trainer.
Who you went to dinner with?
As friends.
But I know him, and he would
never do something like this.
Well, we've got
to hold him here
Till the coroner's official
findings come back,
And then if they're consistent
with his story,
We'll cut him loose.
Well...
It's like I said.
He didn't do it.
Why would a mass murderer
String up a body in his gym?
Ted caters to a pretty
rough clientele.
A lot of career
criminals,
Gangbangers.
He runs afoul of one
every now and again.
He thinks someone was trying
to send him a message.
Who? He says he doesn't know.
I want to talk to him.
Two weeks ago, I said
I wouldn't train you to fight.
Now you have a trainer.
Who's training me to box,
to let off some steam.
I think I have a pretty good
reason to have some.
Keep your eyes open
with this guy.
He didn't do this.
Just the same.
Why are you sitting like that?
I'm concentrating.
Because I need to remember something.
Why?
Try this.
Pay attention.
Remember where
the matching one is?
See, your memory's fine.
Maseo: He needs your help.
You need my help.
You know I don't
like your friend.
This gaijin,
he is trouble.
Well, I need him
to remember what he saw.
When we capture chien na wei,
my debt is paid.
All I care about
Is us getting home.
Then help me.
I love you.
You know that, right?
Oh, come on,
you must be cheating.
I'm just better
at this than you.
Akio.
[speaking japanese]
We were just
playing a game.
I will house you, feed you,
and clothe you.
But my son
is off limits.
Fine.
Stay!
What are you doing?
I'm helping you.
Now...
Do exactly
as I say.
You ever heard
of this ted grant?
Yeah, I saw his title fight a
few years back on pay per view.
They call him wild cat.
He's the real deal.
Body in his gym
was strung up the same way
That the bodies
in the warehouse were.
Like punching bags.
What if laurel
vouches for him?
I don't think that laurel
is seeing clearly on this one.
If grant's our doer,
he's more than boxer.
I hacked csu's files on the
warehouse murders.
The culebras were
armed to the teeth,
But the killer, the psycho
mass murder guy,
Never fired a shot.
They were beaten to death by
brass knuckles.
It's a pretty specific m.O.
It matches one murder
from six years ago.
Same as tonight,
culebra drug dealer.
Blunt force trauma, consistent
with brass knuckles
Worn by a left-handed
assailant.
Let me guess-- ted "wild cat"
grant's a lefty.
They called him
the starling southpaw.
Well, SCPD never
put that together,
Because ted
was never arrested.
[beep]
he's moving.
You dinged him
with a tracer?
Just because laurel trusts
him doesn't mean I have to.
Talk me in.
[both grunting]
Second time I've found you
with a body!
I've never killed anybody.
I'm being set up.
Why should
I believe you?!
Because I used to be
a vigilante.
I used to be you.
This city's been hurting
long before you showed up.
I've never heard of another
vigilante in starling.
It was six years ago.
I wasn't news--
I stuck to the glades.
And these are supposed
to convince me?
Masks are also useful for
serial killers.
Says a guy currently
wearing one.
Who's that?
I don't know. I've never seen
him before in my life.
But this was hung
around the body
That was found in my gym.
The key is
to the storage locker.
He's leaving me
a trail to follow.
Who is?
Whoever's setting me up.
Look, I've never
killed anyone.
Except for that drug dealer that
you beat to death six years ago.
That was a mistake.
I may have avoided jail,
but I have lived
With the guilt
of that man's death
Every single day
of my life.
I gave it all up
after that.
I locked this place up and I swore
I'd never open it again.
Who else knows
about the locker?
No one.
This is where
I kept my supplies.
A safe place separate
from my day job.
I'm sure you've got
one just like it.
Mine's bigger.
Look, we're both
trying to find out
Who the hell's
doing this.
We could help
each other.
Laurel: His name
is albert mancini.
No criminal record, aside from
a few unpaid parking tickets.
Grant says he doesn't
know who this guy is.
Oh, and now you believe him?
I haven't decided yet!
Do you know that you're training
with a vigilante?
Former, apparently.
And no, I didn't.
I didn't!
So you also didn't know
That six years ago, he beat
someone to death?
How many more reasons
Am I going to have
to give you
Before you stay away
from this guy?
Ok, you know what, are you guys
just about finished
With your little
private chat?
The guy from your storage unit,
He has no criminal record.
He was a magician.
Magician's assistant,
More accurately.
He worked with a local act
Before getting cut loose.
Mancini hasn't worked since.
Culebra cartel,
magician's assistant.
What's the connection?
Their act was
at the sansa bar.
The sansa bar's where's the drug
dealer was murdered.
You mean the person
you beat to death?
Whoever's doing this is leaving me
a trail to follow.
Then we follow it.
We need another minute.
How do you two
know each other?
We used to date.
You cannot be serious.
I am not on
your team.
I don't work for you.
Exactly. You're untrained.
Oh, who's fault is that?
[exhales]
Does he know?
What's driving you?
I told him...
That sara's gone.
But does he know
That you want to follow
in her footsteps?
You're playing a very
dangerous game, laurel.
I can handle it.
No, you can't.
Because you haven't realized
That it's not actually a game.
Let's go.
What about laurel?
She's not coming.
Oliver has a 20
on our killer.
I thought oliver
was tracking grant.
Looks like things
have changed.
Suit up, he wants us
to provide back-up.
Roy can't go.
What?
I need to talk to you about
something important.
It can wait.
No, it can't. John?
I'll take care
of it.
What the hell is that about?
We need to talk.
Yeah, you made that
pretty clear.
Before we buried sara,
I scanned her body
Using portable magnetic
resonance imaging.
Felicity, you're really
starting to freak me out.
I basically created
a virtual autopsy.
It's not as good as
a regular autopsy,
But like when I can use it to
determine things an autopsy would,
Like angle of tack,
trajectory,
And the force
of the arrows.
Felicity, what are you saying?
There were certain things about
the forensics
That I couldn't
reconcile with,
Specifically,
the angle
And the velocity of the arrows
were not consistent
With a normal bow
or archer
But if the arrows were thrown
with mirakuru force...
What if there was some residual
mirakuru in your system?
It would explain
the forensics.
The angle and the force
of the arrows.
But you said that I tested
negative for mirakuru.
There isn't any in
your blood today,
But if one last
mirakuru episode
Burned down any remnants
in your system...
"episode?"
You mean...
Me killing sara.
I'm onsite.
Copy. Keep watching
the perimeter.
How many partners
do you have, anyway?
The culebras.
The body in your gym,
The body in your storage locker.
Someone's gone
to a lot of trouble
To frame you for murders
and bring you here.
Why? What does all this
have to do with one killing
Six years ago?
Hello, ted.
I see you got my messages.
Arrows.
I never knew why we couldn't just
use a gun the way they did.
Because we're better
than they are.
At least we're
supposed to be.
That's almost ironic,
coming from you.
I trusted you!
[siren]
scpd!
Ted grant,
you are under arrest
For multiple counts
of homicide.
Officer: Don't move!
What are you
talkin' about?
I didn't do this.
Yeah?
Tell that to the stiff we found
in your locker.
Let's go.
Sorry he got past me. He knew
an exit out of the building
That wasn't on any
of the blueprints
That felicity
hooked me up with.
You had ted grant
arrested?
Your father's men
found him at a crime scene.
Another body was found at a
storage locker that he owns,
Along with evidence
of past vigilantism.
No. He's innocent.
I know.
I saw the person
who's doing this.
Who is it?
[exhales]
He was wearing ted's old gear.
Full face mask.
Let's go.
Clearly grant knows
who's behind the mask.
Oliver.
Laurel.
What's up?
I have to--
Roy, don't. Let's just--
I need to tell you
something.
Ok?
I...
I killed sara.
That doesn't...
You're not making any sense.
Why would you kill sara?
It was the mirakuru.
Roy had no memory
of the attack.
No real memory, at least.
But he's been recalling
Fragments of his mirakuru
exposure last year.
That, and suppressed
memories
Often resurface in dreams.
This is insane.
Laurel, I am so
sorry. I'm really--
Don't!
Wait, roy, where do you think
you're going?
Let him go.
I thought he was cured.
What we know about mirakuru
is vastly outweighed
By the things
we don't know.
What does that even mean?
That roy killed my sister
and it's not his fault?
The arrows that killed sara,
We pulled dna off of them,
didn't we?
I tested it against the sample
of roy's blood.
It was the first
thing I did.
And?
The results
were inconclusive.
I can't process
this right now.
[sighs]
Hey.
Look at me.
Focus on what you can process.
Ted knows
who we're coming after.
I need you
to find out who it is.
I can't. I can't. If roy
killed sara, then--
If roy killed sara, then...
We will deal with it.
For right now, I need you
To deal with ted.
Ok?
Ok.
How sure are you?
There's other
forensic evidence.
A virtual autopsy, in light of
what roy's described,
It sounds
incriminating.
That, and his trouble sleeping
started right when sara was killed.
My husband says you
are having problems
Remembering what you saw
earlier today.
That's the problem.
I didn't see anything.
You see and hear far
more than you think.
Hidden truths,
Very deep in
your sub-conscious.
You saw something, but your head
is too busy.
You need
to quiet it.
Close your eyes.
Take a deep breath.
In through your nose,
out through your mouth.
In...
And out.
And again.
You're floating,
in nothingness.
All that exists
is your breath.
Any thoughts you
have are clouds.
They just
drift away.
I remember.
16 murders.
17, counting the one
from six years ago.
That's more than the son of sam,
less than bundy.
Probably worth a mini-series,
huh? Maybe a book?
You became
a defense attorney?
Can I talk to him
for a minute?
[exhales]
You sure can
pick 'em.
You ok?
I'm not the one facing
a lifetime in prison.
Who framed you?
I don't know.
I can't help you if you're going
to keep lying to me.
The arrow saw you with him.
He knows you know who it is.
If the d.A.'s office refuses
to seek an indictment,
The police have
to release you.
But first...
I'm going to need you to be
straight with me.
Who was the man
behind the mask?
His name's isaac stanzler.
Six years ago, the culebras
ran the glades.
I thought it would be a good idea
for families to be able to live there
Without worrying about their kids
getting shot.
So I decided to do
something about it.
You became
a vigilante.
Just like your friend
in the green hood--
Without the green hood.
And what about
stanzler?
You know the guy
the arrow's been
Running around with lately?
The one in red?
Stanzler was my guy in red.
I guess you can call him
my apprentice.
And one night,
we decided to go after
This drug dealer that was
pushing crank near the school.
We tracked him all the way
to this nightclub.
And what happened?
That drug dealer...
Isaac got to him first.
That murder from
six years ago...
That wasn't you,
that was him.
[sighs] I hung it up after that.
What about stanzler?
What happened
to isaac stanzler?
I told him to get
the hell out of starling.
That I never wanted
to see his face ever again.
I cut him loose.
That's why I've been lying to you
this whole time, laurel.
Everything that's happening
is my fault.
No word from laurel?
Not yet.
But according to SCPD
email traffic,
Which I may or may not
have hacked into,
They are dropping the charges
against ted grant.
Oliver, let me go after roy.
If he's experiencing
mirakuru side effects,
We can't leave him
running around.
So you bring him in.
Then what?
Oliver,
this crusade of ours,
It's supposed to be about
justice, right?
So if that's supposed
to mean something,
We can have two sets of rules--
One for the bad guys
and one for us.
I'm the one who brought roy
into this crusade.
And maybe it's time
for you to cut him loose.
Are you telling me
to abandon him?
Yes, oliver.
If that's what it takes
to find justice for sara.
So what do you think
stanzler's next move is?
Well, framing me
didn't work.
I'm almost afraid to think of
what he might try to do next.
What I should have
done from the start.
After you abandoned me,
the culebra family,
They wanted payback
for the man they lost.
They tortured me for months
before I escaped.
Isaac, I'm so sorry.
I didn't know.
You have every
right to hate me.
But come on,
let's talk about this.
Oh, don't worry,
we will.
There's so much I have to say
before I kill you.
Where are we going?
Just drive!
Hey, your beef is with me.
Ok, you got me. Let her go.
Taking innocent people hostage?
Man, I taught you better
than that.
They're not people,
they're criminals.
Albert mancini wasn't.
You still strung him up
In that nightclub.
You taught me that
There are no innocents when you
abandoned me to the culebras.
You gave me
direction, purpose.
And then when things got tough,
when I really needed you,
You weren't there.
[cell phone vibrating]
it's laurel.
Put her on speaker.
Isaac: I hated you
so much for that.
That voice,
that's him.
I was just a kid. You were
supposed to know better.
Call's coming
from laurel's cell.
Moving fast, 45 miles an hour.
They're in her car.
They're headed north
on route 17.
Keep that line open.
Isaac, I'm sorry.
I had no idea!
Eyes on the road!
Don't stop!
[tires squealing]
Who was that, huh?
Who was that?!
I don't know.
The only friend
I ever had was you.
Hey!
[tires squealing]
Another vigilante.
Looks like
we started a movement.
Go, go, go!
[laurel grunting]
[tires squealing]
Get grant!
Don't you get it?
He's using you!
You're not
a human being, man.
You were just another weapon
in his arsenal.
And the second you do
something wrong,
He'll turn
his back on you.
He will abandon you!
I'm not you.
Don't abandon me.
Never.
You planning on hiding
in the shadows all night?
That's a good trick. Used it once
or twice myself back in the day.
Thank you.
You can thank me by doing
something for me.
Name it.
Stay away
from laurel lance.
She's in
a vulnerable place
And I don't want her
getting hurt.
Hmm. Did you bother
asking what she wants?
'cause that's her choice.
If she stops coming,
that's fine.
She'll stop coming.
You know, you did me a solid,
So let me repay you
with a little hard won advice.
Learn from my mistake--
What I did, what you do...
This playing judge and jury,
It messed with isaac's. I just waited
till it was too late to cut him loose.
Don't make the same mistake
With the kid you're running
around with.
Ted, your mistake wasn't
cutting him loose...
It was losing faith
in him.
[knock on door]
Oliver: Hi.
Hi.
How are you
feeling?
The worst part about sobriety
Is having to pass
on the pain meds.
I thought maybe you could use
a ride home.
And an "I told you so?"
I don't think that I owe you
one of those.
When I said I wouldn't
train you,
I was trying
to protect you.
But a homicidal former vigilante
apprentice
Was not what
I had in mind.
I know you're trying
to protect me, ollie,
But I'm not helpless.
I've never
seen you that way.
But laurel, I'm always going
to watch out for you.
It's not because
I think you're helpless.
It's because
I care about you.
And what about roy?
Do you trust me?
I'm going to miss this.
I feel like I was just starting
to get good at it.
You are getting
good at it.
That guy?
He said I was just another weapon
in your arsenal.
Well, maybe that's what we should
call you, then.
Arsenal.
I don't know why you would ever
let me suit up after what I did.
Doesn't matter
anyway, because...
I'm going to be
turning myself in.
[sighs]
Ok.
There's something you need
to know, roy.
Something that your mind has
been trying to tell you.
And I think it best
If you help me let it.
With a candle?
With meditation.
Clear your thoughts.
Find hidden truths.
This is weird.
You're hurting.
But it's not for the reasons
that you think.
And I've been afraid
That if I just
came out and told you,
It would only make
the hurt worse.
Do you trust me?
Always.
Good.
Close your eyes.
Now focus
on your breathing.
In through
your nose,
Out through
your mouth.
[exhales]
In...
Out.
Floating along,
weightless.
And the only thing
that exists
Is your breath.
Now your thoughts
are like clouds.
They just drift away.
No!
Let go.
[gasps]
I killed him.
The police officer.
Why didn't you tell me?
Because you were
overdosed on mirakuru,
You didn't remember, and I was
hoping that you never would.
But then felicity told
me you had the dream
That you killed sara,
and I realized...
It was a memory.
I think because of the way sara
was murdered,
The fact
they used arrows...
Brought it
to the surface.
So I didn't kill sara.
No.
But I am a murderer.
No, I just need to be
alone for a while.
This is it.
This is
the dead drop.
What kind of a message
is this?
Have you ever heard
of steganography?
Is that the dinosaur
with the plates on its back?
It's the art
of concealing a message
Within another message.
In this case,
Within an image.
[beep]
Li kuan hui.
Who's that?
I do not know.
But if chien na wei's
interested in him,
So are we.
Hey.
It worked.
Thank you.
I don't want your gratitude.
There's only one thing
I want from you.
Name it.
Get out of our lives
as soon as possible.
Sign says "closed."
learn to read.
Laurel: I thought
you might make an exception.
Yeah? And why
would I do that?
Because I just made sure
your past vigilantism
Fell under the statute
of limitations.
No new charges will be filed.
Much obliged.
But you still
shouldn't be here.
No, this is exactly
where I should be.
Last night when isaac
had me at gunpoint
And when he was shooting
at my friends,
I should have
been so scared.
Rattled.
But I wasn't.
I saw what needed
to be done, and I did it.
I've just been teaching you how
to throw a proper jab.
And your pal robin hood doesn't
want me even doing that.
I want you
to give me the tools
To avenge my sister's death.
I want you to teach me to get
justice outside of a courtroom.
I took on an apprentice once.
That didn't
work out so good.
Well, it's like you said--
It's not about how you get
knocked down to the mat.
It's about whether you get up.
Who the hell are you?
I'm cupid, stupid.
[Sync: Xibirikinho]