MY NAME IS OLIVER QUEEN.
AFTER 5 YEARS IN HELL,
I RETURNED HOME
WITH ONLY ONE GOAL...
TO SAVE MY CITY.
TODAY, I FIGHT THAT WAR
ON TWO FRONTS.
BY DAY, I LEAD STAR CITY
AS ITS MAYOR,
BUT BY NIGHT,
I AM SOMEONE ELSE.
I AM...
SOMETHING ELSE.
I AM THE GREEN ARROW.
PREVIOUSLY ON "ARROW"...
ZOE'S IN A FOSTER HOME,
A GOOD ONE
IT LOOKS LIKE.
SHE SHOULDN'T BE
ANYWHERE NEAR ME.
I DON'T AGREE WITH THAT,
AND I HAVE A LAWYER FRIEND
WHO DOESN'T EITHER.
I'M WORRIED ABOUT
YOU BECAUSE YOU'RE
INTO SOMETHING,
AND YOU DON'T WANT
TO TELL ANYONE ABOUT IT.
YOU JUST HAVE
TO TRUST ME ON THIS ONE.
IF WE CAN PRODUCE VIDEO
THAT CHASE IS PROMETHEUS,
THAT'S GAME OVER FOR HIM.
OLIVER: THAT IS
WHAT WE NEEDED!
DINAH: PLEASE LET ME
BE THE ONE TO WALK THIS
INTO SCPD.
I'M GONNA THROW IT
UP ON YOUTUBE.
THERE WON'T BE ANYWHERE
THAT SON OF A BITCH CAN RUN.
[CELL PHONE VIBRATING]
[SIRENS]
DELTA TEAM IN POSITION.
SEEMS OUR FRIENDS
ARE HERE, TOO.
OLIVER: WE'RE ON SITE.
AN ARGUS DRONE CONFIRMS
ADRIAN CHASE WALKED
INTO THE ARCADE AT 0900.
OLIVER:16 HOURS AGO.
THAT'S A LIFETIME FOR CHASE.
YEAH, BUT NO ONE
HAS ENTERED OR
EXITED SINCE.
WE GOT THE BASTARD.
WE HAVE TO MOVE
RIGHT NOW.
-SEE SOMETHING?
-YES.
THIS IS
MAXIMUM FORCE.
IT'S VINTAGE.
WE CANNOT LET ANYTHING
HAPPEN TO THIS.
I'M MORE WORRIED
ABOUT SOMETHING
HAPPENING TO ME!
DINAH: WILL YOU TWO FOCUS?
[VIDEO GAME SOUND EFFECTS,
MUSIC PLAYING]
INCOMING!
DINAH: IS EVERYBODY OK?
IT WAS VINTAGE.
[VIDEO GAME SOUND EFFECTS,
MUSIC PLAYING]
LOOKS LIKE WE FOUND
OUR GUY.
CHASE ESCAPED THE ARCADE
BY USING A SECRET TUNNEL
THAT LED
TO PORT NEWARK.
HOMELAND SECURITY'S
PLACED HIM ON A NO-FLY LIST.
NO. HE'S NOT GONNA
LEAVE THE COUNTRY.
HE ISN'T DONE YET.
HOW DO YOU KNOW?
-CALL IT A HUNCH.
-A HUNCH?
MAYOR QUEEN, THIS CITY
DESERVES BETTER
THAN A HUNCH.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
EXCUSE
THE INTERRUPTION.
I CAN'T HOLD THEM
OFF ANY LONGER.
REPORTER: MAYOR QUEEN,
IS ADRIAN CHASE GOING
TO STRIKE AGAIN?
AHEM. ALL RIGHT.
I CAN TAKE
A FEW QUESTIONS.
-YES?
-YOU WORKED SIDE BY SIDE
WITH ADRIAN CHASE
FOR MONTHS.
HOW COULD YOU NOT KNOW
THAT YOU HAD
A SERIAL KILLER
IN YOUR ADMINISTRATION?
WELL, MR. CHASE'S
SECRET LIFE
CAME AS A SURPRISE
TO US ALL.
I CAN SAY THAT WE
ARE CURRENTLY
FOLLOWING UP
SOME VERY
PROMISING LEADS.
ARE YOU SAYING YOU HAVE
NO IDEA WHERE HE IS?
NO. I'M SAYING THAT
THE DETAILS
OF AN ONGOING
INVESTIGATION
ARE CONFIDENTIAL.
YES?
MAN: I SPENT
THE AFTERNOON SPEAKING
WITH GAY EKED'S FATHER.
WHAT DO YOU HAVE TO
SAY TO HIM
AND THE FAMILIES OF ALL
OF PROMETHEUS' VICTIMS?
WELL, I WOULD SAY
TO THEM WHAT I AM
SAYING TO YOU.
WE ARE DOING
EVERYTHING THAT
WE POSSIBLY CAN
TO BRING MR. CHASE
TO JUSTICE.
DO YOU HAVE ANYTHING
FOR US OTHER THAN
CANNED PLATITUDES?
BETTER QUESTION IS
DO WE HAVE ANYTHING?
MANHUNTS AREN'T EXACTLY
IN HELIX'S WHEELHOUSE,
FELICITY.
HEY, YOU HELPED ME
UNMASK CHASE.
NOW I NEED YOUR HELP
TRYING TO FIND THE BASTARD.
FROM WHAT YOU'VE
TOLD ME, THEY'VE GOT
HOMELAND SECURITY,
THE FBI, AND ARGUS
WORKING ON THIS.
YEAH, AND LAST NIGHT,
CHASE PLAYED THEM
LIKE MAXIMUM FORCE.
-I USED TO LOVE THAT GAME.
-I KNOW. I DID, TOO.
APPARENTLY, IT'S SEEN
BETTER DAYS.
-HMM?
-POINT BEING, I WAS EXPECTING
YOU AND HELIX TO COME UP
WITH A FRESH PERSPECTIVE,
YOU KNOW, MAYBE PULL
OUT SOME NEW TRICKS,
SOMETHING CHASE
ISN'T GONNA ANTICIPATE.
WELL, IT WOULD HELP
NOT HAVING TO WASTE TIME
REINVENTING THE WHEEL.
YOU WANT TO KNOW WHAT
INTEL THEY'RE WORKING WITH?
GETTING INTO
HOMELAND SECURITY
AND THE FBI IS EASY.
THEIR CYBER SEC IS
A BAD JOKE,
BUT BREAKING
INTO ARGUS' NETWORK?
ALLOW ME.
THE INTEL OF CHASE
BEING IN NEW JERSEY CAME
FROM AN ARGUS DRONE.
-OK. SO?
-SO THE INFORMATION
WAS THEN SENT
TO AN UNSECURED PHONE.
SEEMS LIKE A BIG-TIME BREACH
IN OPERATIONAL SECURITY.
-WAIT.
-WAIT WHAT?
WHAT IF CHASE HAS
A BUDDY INSIDE ARGUS,
SOMEONE WHO TIPPED HIM OFF,
WHO PINGED
THE UNSECURED CELL PHONE?
[TYPING]
YEAH.
[CRASHING]
[DING]
-MR. MAYOR.
-HI.
COULD YOU GIVE US
SOME SPACE?
CHASE PROBABLY KNEW
AGENT PIERCE WAS PART
OF OUR OPERATION
IN JERSEY.
THIS COULD BE PAYBACK.
OK, LYLA. WHAT KILLED HIM?
CAUSE OF DEATH LOOKS
LIKE BLUNT FORCE TRAUMA.
FELICITY, CURTIS,
WE HAVE A CAMERA.
ROGER, ROGER. WE HAVE
CLEARANCE, CLARENCE.
WHAT IS OUR VECTOR,
VICTOR?
GUYS, FOCUS, PLEASE.
THAT'S EVIDENCE.
ARGUS EVIDENCE.
ALL RIGHT.
I GOT THE VIDEOS.
STREAMING BACK
TO YOUR PHONE NOW.
-HERE WE GO.
-ARE YOU GUYS SEEING THIS?
WELL, WE'RE SEEING IT,
BUT IT LOOKS LIKE A META.
AN INVISIBLE META?
FELICITY: OR PSYCHOKINESIS,
THOUGH SOME PREFER TELEKINESIS.
I...I DON'T THINK SO.
CHECK OUT WHAT
THE ELEVATOR'S DOING.
FELICITY: YEAH, GUYS.
CURTIS IS RIGHT.
ACCORDING TO THE ELEVATOR
ACTIVITY LOGS,
THE CAR ACCELERATED UPWARDS
AT...OH, MY GOD...9 GS,
AND THEN IT JUST DROPPED
INTO A FREEFALL
FOR 40 STORIES.
-DEATH BY ELEVATOR.
-THIS DOESN'T FEEL LIKE CHASE.
FELICITY: NO. AT FIRST,
I THOUGHT MAYBE CHASE WAS
TRYING TO TIE UP LOOSE ENDS,
BUT I COULDN'T FIND ANY
CONNECTIONS BETWEEN THEM.
HE HAD HIS ARGUS
SECURITY KEY STILL ON HIM.
WHY ENTER THE ELEVATOR
IF NOT TO TAKE IT?
MAYBE TO CONFIRM THE KILL.
GUYS, HOW DO WE MANIPULATE
AN ELEVATOR LIKE THAT?
REMOTELY. EVERYTHING'S
COMPUTER-CONTROLLED.
ALL RIGHT. HOWEVER
THIS HAPPENED,
LET'S JUST FIND
WHOEVER DID IT.
WE ARE ON IT.
HUH. LOOKS LIKE
THE ELEVATOR WAS HACKED
IN REAL TIME.
PULLING UP
THE ROOTKIT NOW.
OH, MY GOD.
"OH...OH...OH,
MY GOD" WHAT?
NOTHING. THERE'S JUST
A LINE OF CODE HERE
I'M NOT QUITE GETTING,
BUT I THINK I KNOW
SOMEONE AT HELIX
WHO CAN HELP.
UH, HEY. DON'T YOU NEED
TO SHOW THEM THE CODE?
YEAH. THAT'S
A GOOD IDEA. YES.
THANK YOU.
VERY HELPFUL, CURTIS.
I'M SORRY, MR. EKED,
BUT THE SPECIFICS
OF THE INVESTIGATION
INTO ADRIAN CHASE,
THEY'RE JUST NOT OPEN
TO THE PUBLIC.
THE MOTHER OF MY
CHILDREN IS DEAD,
AND YOU CAN'T
TELL ME ANYTHING.
I CAN ASSURE YOU THAT
THE SCPD
AND THE MAYOR'S OFFICE
ARE DOING EVERYTHING
IN THEIR POWER TO
APPREHEND HIM.
WE'RE GONNA CATCH
THAT SCUM BAG.
OH. INSTEAD OF
WORKING SHOULDER TO
SHOULDER WITH HIM?
HUH?
[SIGHS]
SORRY. IT'S JUST...
THINGS MAY NOT
HAVE WORKED OUT
BETWEEN GAY AND ME,
BUT SHE WAS ALWAYS
THERE FOR THE KIDS.
SHE LOVED THEM,
AND THEY LOVED HER,
AND NOW SHE'S GONE.
[SIGHS]
[SNIFFLES]
PLEASE FIND HIM.
GAY DIDN'T DESERVE
DYING LIKE THAT,
AND NO OTHER FAMILY
DESERVES THIS PAIN.
WE WILL FIND HIM,
AND HE'LL KNOW
THE TRUE MEANING
OF JUSTICE.
THANK YOU.
HOW MANY OTHER VICTIMS'
RELATIVES DO WE
HAVE TODAY?
HE WAS THE LAST.
GOD, I DON'T THINK
I COULD HANDLE ANOTHER.
THESE PEOPLE
ARE GRIEVING, RENE.
I'M NOT SAYING THEY'RE
NOT ENTITLED TO THEIR
GRIEF, HOSS.
I'M SAYING HEARING
ABOUT IT ALL DAY LONG
IS A REAL BUZZ KILL.
YOU KNOW, I'D HAVE
THOUGHT SOMEONE
IN YOUR SITUATION
WOULD HAVE BEEN
A LITTLE MORE, UH,
SYMPATHETIC.
MY SITUATION?
YEAH. CURTIS MIGHT HAVE
TOLD ME ABOUT YOUR WIFE
AND YOUR DAUGHTER.
CURTIS TALKS TOO MUCH.
I DON'T DISAGREE...
BUT WHILE HE WAS TALKING,
HE ALSO MENTIONED
THAT HE OFFERED TO SET
YOU UP WITH A LAWYER
TO HELP GET
YOUR DAUGHTER BACK,
AND THAT WAS
OVER TWO MONTHS AGO.
I'M JUST NOT
READY, HOSS.
FELICITY: A POLYMORPHOUS WORM
CONCEALED BY A KERNEL ROOTKIT.
YOU TRYING TO TALK
TO DIRTY TO ME, OR...
I SAW THE CODE, ALENA.
I KNOW YOUR WORK.
YOU HACKED
THAT ELEVATOR.
-YOU KILLED THAT ARGUS AGENT!
-JUST SLOW DOWN.
-YES OR NO?
-KIND OF.
-KIND OF?
-I DIDN'T MEAN TO KILL HIM,
I SWEAR.
I'D NEVER KNOCKED
ANYONE OUT WITH
AN ELEVATOR BEFORE,
AND APPARENTLY,
THERE'S A LEARNING CURVE.
-ALENA.
-I NEED YOU TO HEAR ME OUT
FOR ONE SECOND.
-YOU MURDERED SOMEONE.
-ACCIDENTALLY
AND FOR A GOOD CAUSE.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
I'M HEARING THIS.
CAYDEN JAMES.
HE'S THE MOST
SKILLED HACKER
THE WORLD
HAS EVER KNOWN.
IF HE WAS, I WOULD
HAVE HEARD OF HIM.
NO, YOU WOULDN'T HAVE
BECAUSE HE'S JUST THAT GOOD.
HE'S A GHOST.
HE'S ALSO THE PERSON
THAT FORMED HELIX.
-WHAT DOES THAT HAVE TO DO...
-8 MONTHS AGO,
HE WAS SCOOPED UP
BY ARGUS.
NOT ARRESTED,
NOT CHARGED,
JUST TAKEN,
AND NOW HE'S BEING
HELD WITHOUT CAUSE,
BEING TORTURED,
WHO KNOWS WHAT ELSE,
AND I HAD TO TAKE THIS
OFF THAT ARGUS AGENT
SO WE CAN FREE HIM.
ALENA, YOU KILLED
SOMEONE.
BEFORE YOU GET
TOO JUDGMENTAL,
KNOW THAT YOU'RE GONNA
HELP ME FREE CAYDEN
FROM WHEREVER ARGUS
IS HOLDING HIM.
-WHY WOULD I DO THAT?
-BECAUSE BEFORE HE WAS TAKEN,
CAYDEN WAS WORKING
ON A BIOMETRIC TRACKER
THAT COULD RECOGNIZE
A HEARTBEAT,
POWERFUL ENOUGH TO SCAN
ANYWHERE IN THE WORLD.
ANYWHERE
ADRIAN CHASE IS.
LYLA: WE HAVE A PROBLEM.
JOHN: WHAT IS THAT?
THE PROBLEM.
AFTER DAMIEN DARHK
TOOK MY SECURITY
IMPLANT LAST YEAR,
I INSTITUTED
NEW PROTOCOLS
TO PREVENT ANY
SENSITIVE ARGUS
INFORMATION
OR LOCATION
FROM BEING ACCESSED
BY A SINGLE PERSON.
ACCESS NOW REQUIRES
TWO OF THESE
SECURITY KEYS.
BUT AGENT PIERCE'S
KEY WASN'T TAKEN.
YOU FOUND IT ON HIM.
I FOUND A VERY
SOPHISTICATED COPY.
-SMART.
-EXTREMELY.
I ALMOST DIDN'T
CATCH IT.
IF THOSE KEYS HAVE
BEEN COMPROMISED,
THEN THEY HAVE TO BE
REPROGRAMMED.
THE WHOLE POINT
OF HAVING THE KEYS
IS FOR THEM TO BE
UNHACKABLE.
REPROGRAMMING TAKES
ABOUT 24 HOURS.
OLIVER: LYLA, CLEARLY ARGUS
SECURITY IS UNDER ATTACK,
BUT THIS DOESN'T
FEEL LIKE CHASE,
AND QUITE FRANKLY,
THAT IS WHERE WE HAVE
TO KEEP OUR FOCUS.
AND I SYMPATHIZE,
BUT I'VE GOT
ALMOST ALL PERSONNEL
WITH KEYS IN
LOCKDOWN AT ARGUS.
-ALMOST?
-AGENT DITKOFF IS 20 MILES OUT
NEAR PORT TALBERT.
I WAS HOPING YOUR
TEAM COULD ESCORT
HER BACK TO ARGUS.
OLIVER, I KNOW YOU
WANT TO GET CHASE.
SO DO I, BUT ARGUS HAS
ALWAYS HAD OUR BACKS.
YES, THEY HAVE.
LET'S CALL CURTIS
AND DINAH.
PLEASE LET FELICITY
KNOW WHERE WE'RE GOING.
COPY THAT.
JUST LET ME TALK
TO MY FRIENDS AT ARGUS.
MAYBE WE CAN NEGOTIATE
FOR CAYDEN'S RELEASE.
SORRY. IT'S JUST
FUNNY, YOU KNOW?
NEGOTIATE WITH ARGUS.
SERIOUSLY, I REALLY
THINK THEY WILL.
JUST HOLD OFF
ON TAKING
THE SECOND KEY.
ARGUS WON'T EVEN
ADMIT THEY HAVE CAYDEN.
BESIDES, THE PLAN'S
ALREADY IN MOTION.
WHAT DID YOU DO?
DON'T WORRY. I HIRED
PROFESSIONALS THIS TIME.
-PROFESSIONALS?
-ONE CASUALTY WAS ENOUGH
FOR THIS GIRL'S
CONSCIENCE.
LIKE MERCENARIES?
YOU REALLY CAN BUY
ANYTHING ON THE INTERNET.
WELL, ARE YOUR
INTERNET THUGS HEADED
TO PORT TALBERT?
BECAUSE THEY'RE ABOUT
TO HAVE SOME COMPANY.
CURTIS: OVER TERRIFIC HERE...
OR MR. WATCH...
OR WATCH TERRIFIC...
ANYWAY, IT WILL COME TO ME.
WE'RE ON OUR WAY.
RIGHT. 700 FEET AHEAD,
3 BOGEYS, PLEASE HURRY.
[TIRES SQUEAL]
OLIVER: DINAH AND I ARE
A FEW BLOCKS AWAY.
[TIRES SQUEAL]
[CANARY CRY]
HEY, JOHN. I KNOW YOU
HAVE TO PROTECT THAT AGENT.
WE'RE ON OUR WAY.
I KNOW YOU HAVE TO
PROTECT HER,
BUT I NEED YOU TO LET
THOSE GUYS GET AWAY
WITH HER SECURITY KEY.
WAIT. WHAT? WHAT?!
HEY! DON'T MOVE!
OLIVER, WE HAVE
A SITUATION.
I NEED YOU TO LET
TANGO GET AWAY
WITH THAT SECURITY KEY.
-WHY?
-FELICITY HAS INFORMATION
THAT WE DON'T HAVE.
OLIVER, I NEED YOU
TO STAND DOWN.
WHAT THE HELL WAS THAT?
-FELICITY SAID WE HAD TO.
-WHY?
TO CATCH PROMETHEUS.
IT'S THE ONLY WAY
TO CATCH CHASE.
NO, IT'S NOT,
BUT EVEN IF IT WERE,
AT WHAT COST?
AGENT DITKOFF
COULD HAVE BEEN KILLED.
NO. THE TEAM WAS
THERE TO MAKE SURE.
SHE COULD HAVE
BEEN KILLED
JUST LIKE
AGENT PIERCE.
I TOLD YOU THAT
WAS AN ACCIDENT.
AND NOW...NOW TWO KEYS
ARE IN THE WIND,
AND ARGUS
IS VULNERABLE.
WHAT THE HELL WERE
YOU THINKING?
THAT WE NEED TO CATCH
THIS SON OF A BITCH
NO MATTER WHAT.
GUYS, A LITTLE
SUPPORT HERE.
MIGHT BE CROSSING
A LINE, FELICITY.
WELL, YOU'RE THE LAST
PERSON ON EARTH THAT GETS
TO GIVE THAT LECTURE, OLIVER.
OR SECOND TO LAST,
AND DON'T TELL ME
THAT YOU DON'T MAKE
MORALLY QUESTIONABLE CHOICES
SO THAT I DON'T HAVE TO.
I HAVE TO!
NO, YOU DON'T, FELICITY.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO.
LYLA'S RIGHT. THERE ARE
BETTER WAYS FOR US
TO FIND CHASE.
CHASE HAS BEEN IN THE WIND
FOR A WEEK.
HE WAS TRAINED
BY TALIA AL GHUL.
HE KNOWS HOW TO
STAY IN THE WIND.
WHAT OTHER LEADS
DO WE HAVE?
HOW ELSE ARE WE GONNA
BRING ADRIAN CHASE
TO JUSTICE
UNLESS ARGUS
LETS GO OF CAYDEN JAMES.
-NOT A CHANCE.
-WELL, THEN MY ONLY CHOICE
IS TO HELP HELIX.
JOHN:
YOUR ONLY CHOICE?
FELICITY,
I THOUGHT WE WERE
ON THE SAME SIDE.
NO, JOHN. I'M ON THE SIDE
THAT'S GONNA PUT CHASE AWAY
SO THAT HE CAN'T HURT
ANYONE EVER AGAIN.
OLIVER: HEY, FELICITY.
LET HER GO, MAN.
NOW'S NOT THE TIME.
YOU WANTED TO
SEE ME, HOSS?
YEAH. F-FIRST, CLOSE
THE DOOR.
SECOND, WHAT HAVE
I TOLD YOU ABOUT
CALLING ME "HOSS"?
-DON'T.
-RIGHT.
YEAH.
OH, JUST SIT DOWN.
ARE YOU FIRING ME?
OH, RENE, THERE
WAS A TIME WHEN
I WOULD HAVE LOVED
TO HEAR YOU
ASK ME THAT,
BUT, NO, I AM NOT
FIRING YOU.
I WANT TO TALK
TO YOU ABOUT...ZOE.
YEAH, YOUR DAUGHTER.
YEAH. I KNOW
HER NAME, HOSS.
I THOUGHT I TOLD YOU
I DON'T WANT TO
TALK ABUT HER.
WELL, THAT'S TOO BAD
BECAUSE YOU HAPPEN TO
BE WORKING FOR A GUY
WHO WOULD GIVE
ANYTHING TO BE
WITH HIS DAUGHTER AGAIN.
WHAT DO YOU WANT
FROM ME, MAN?
AN EXPLANATION.
I LOOKED INTO YOUR CASE,
AND YOU HAVE
FULL VISITATION RIGHTS
AS LONG AS YOU'RE
ACCOMPANIED
BY A COURT-APPOINTED
GUARDIAN,
AND THERE'S NO RECORD
OF YOU EVER VISITING.
PLEASE. JUST LEAVE
THIS ALONE, MAN.
I THINK WE BOTH KNOW
I'M NOT GONNA,
SO WHY DON'T WE JUST
SKIP TO THE PART
WHERE YOU TELL ME
WHY YOU DO NOT WANT TO
SEE YOUR DAUGHTER?
OK.
WHEN CURTIS TOLD ME
ABOUT HIS LAWYER FRIEND,
I GOT EXCITED, OK?
YEAH, YEAH. ALL RIGHT,
AND THEN WHAT HAPPENED?
I REMEMBERED WHY
THEY TOOK ZOE AWAY
FROM ME IN THE FIRST PLACE.
YEAH, SURE.
I...I COULD VISIT HER
WITH A COURT-APPOINTED
GUARDIAN LIKE YOU SAID.
WANT TO KNOW WHY THAT IS?
BECAUSE I'M BAD NEWS.
YEAH, YOU'RE
AN ACQUIRED TASTE
FOR SURE...
I HURT HER!
WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
YOU HURT HER?
I...I WAS REHEATING
SOME SOUP FOR HER.
IT WAS JUST ABOUT
ALL I COULD MAKE HER...
AND IT WAS ON THE STOVE,
AND I PASS OUT DRUNK.
POOR ZOE, SHE'S TRYING TO
GRAB IT AND PULLS IT DOWN,
AND IT BURNS HER HAND
REAL BAD...
AND IT WAS HER CRYING
THAT WOKE ME UP.
ZOE DESERVES BETTER
THAN ME.
END OF STORY.
RENE. RENE,
COME BACK...WHA...
[DOOR SLAMS]
[SIGHS]
LYLA: MEET PRISONER 38085,
AKA CAYDEN JAMES.
WHAT ARE YOU
HOLDING HIM ON?
HE'S A PERSON OF INTEREST.
SO NO CRIME.
I'M GUESSING
NO TRIAL EITHER.
DO YOU HAVE SOMETHING YOU
WANT TO SAY TO ME, JOHNNY?
NOT RIGHT NOW, LYLA.
OLIVER: THERE'S SOMETHING
WE'RE NOT CONSIDERING.
WHAT IF FELICITY
IS RIGHT?
SHE MIGHT BE RIGHT.
WE GIVE JAMES A TERMINAL,
WE MAKE HIM FIND CHASE,
AND THEN WE HAND HIM
BACK TO HELIX.
I KNOW YOU WANT CHASE
OFF THE BOARD, OLIVER,
BUT CAYDEN JAMES IS
AS DANGEROUS AS A LOOSE NUKE.
I CAN'T PUT HIM
BACK IN PLAY.
HELIX HAS COMPROMISED
YOUR SECURITY,
AND NOW THEY HAVE HIRED
MERCENARIES
THAT ARE GONNA GO
AFTER ARGUS TO GET JAMES OUT.
WHICH MEANS WE GO
AFTER THEM FIRST.
CURTIS HAS INTEL
AS TO WHERE THEIR
BASE OF
OPERATIONS IS.
AND WE'D BE GOING IN
COMPLETELY BLIND.
WE HAVE A GREATER CHANCE
OF SUCCESS
IF WE LET HELIX
COME TO US.
WAIT, LYLA.
YOU WANT TO SET
A TRAP FOR HELIX
AND USE JAMES
AS THE BAIT?
I DON'T THINK I NEED TO
TELL EITHER OF YOU
HOW DANGEROUS HELIX IS.
THIS IS OUR CHANCE
TO TAKE THEM DOWN.
THIS IS HAPPENING
WITH OR WITHOUT YOUR HELP.
I'LL LET YOU BOYS WRAP
YOUR HEAD AROUND THAT.
WE HAVE TO GET FELICITY
OUT OF HELIX.
WE CAN'T LET HER GET
INVOLVED IN THIS.
YOU MEAN ANY MORE
INVOLVED.
WE KNEW SHE WAS
INTO SOMETHING,
WE KNEW IT WAS BAD.
WE JUST LET HER GET
IN DEEPER.
OLIVER, GRIEF CAN MAKE
PEOPLE DO CRAZY THINGS.
NO ONE KNOWS THAT
BETTER THAN YOU AND ME,
BUT I'M NOT THE ONE
SHE WAS GONNA MARRY.
WHAT'S YOUR POINT?
MY POINT IS...
OLIVER, LOOK, MAYBE
WE SHOULD HAVE TALKED
HER OUT OF HELIX,
MAYBE NOT, I DON'T KNOW,
BUT THE POINT IS
WE'RE HERE NOW,
AND YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE
SHE WILL LISTEN TO.
I'M NOT...SURE
HOW MUCH CREDIBILITY
I HAVE WITH HER.
YOU BOTH WANT TO
CATCH CHASE, RIGHT?
YOU HAVE THAT
IN COMMON,
WHICH TELLS ME YOU ARE
THE ONLY ONE WHO CAN
PULL HER BACK
FROM THE BRINK.
OH!
-HI.
-HEY.
NICE OF YOU TO USE
THE FRONT DOOR FOR ONCE.
MAY I COME IN, PLEASE?
UH, ACTUALLY,
I WAS JUST LEAVING.
I CAN SEE THAT.
SURE.
LOOKS LIKE YOU'RE NOT
SITTING BEHIND A KEYBOARD
FOR THIS ONE.
-CAN YOU BLAME ME?
-NO.
I...MORE THAN
PROBABLY ANYONE ELSE...
UNDERSTAND WHAT IT'S
LIKE TO BE WILLING TO DO
WHATEVER IT TAKES
TO STOP CHASE.
THEN LET ME DO IT.
LET ME JUST TELL YOU
HOW I'M SEEING THINGS.
YOU'RE WILLING TO DO
WHATEVER IT TAKES
TO STOP CHASE
BECAUSE I WAS WILLING
TO DO WHATEVER IT TAKES
TO SAVE THIS CITY,
AND THAT CREATED HIM.
OK. SO IT'S IRONIC.
THAT'S WHAT IT IS.
IT DOESN'T HAVE TO BE.
YOU SEE, WE...WE CAN
THINK OF ANOTHER WAY
TO FIND HIM,
AND THEN WE CAN FIND
ANOTHER WAY TO STOP HIM.
OK. HOW?
THE SCPD TIP LINE?
NO. THAT'S NOT GONNA WORK
THIS TIME, OLIVER.
WE BOTH KNOW THAT.
LOOK. THIS IS
OUR ONLY CHANCE.
AND THIS IS ME ASKING
YOU...
DON'T DO THIS.
FOR THE PAST 4 YEARS,
I HAVE WATCHED YOU DO
WHATEVER YOU HAD TO,
WHATEVER IT TOOK
TO STOP THE PEOPLE
THREATENING THIS CITY.
HOW CAN YOU STAND THERE
AND NOT ASK ME
TO DO THE SAME THING?
BECAUSE OVER THE PAST
4 YEARS, YOU, MORE
THAN ANYONE ELSE,
HAS SEEN THE TOLL THAT
IT HAS TAKEN ON ME.
-AND I TOLD YOU...
-AND I UNDER...I UNDERSTAND.
I AGREE THAT I SHOULD
NOT SHELTER YOU
FROM MAKING
HARD DECISIONS,
BUT YOU WANT TO TALK
IRONY? FINE.
YOU ARE WILLING TO
SELL YOUR SOUL
TO DESTROY A THREAT
THAT I CREATED...
AND...
I...
ONE OF THE REASONS I FELL
IN LOVE WITH YOU
IS BECAUSE YOU WERE
ALWAYS WILLING
TO DO WHAT WAS RIGHT,
NO MATTER WHAT THE COST,
EVEN IF IT'S
UNBEARABLY HARD.
IT'S WHAT MAKES YOU YOU.
SO HOW CAN I BE
ANY DIFFERENT?
YOU'VE SACRIFICED
YOUR SOUL FOR THE TEAM
AND FOR THE CITY
AND FOR ME.
YOU DON'T...
HAVE TO CARRY
THAT BURDEN ANY LONGER.
LET ME DO IT.
FELICITY, I...
I CAN'T.
THEN YOU'LL HAVE
TO STOP ME.
THIS FACILITY HAS
8 INGRESS POINTS.
I'VE GOT 6-MAN TEAMS
STATIONED AT EACH,
PERIMETER SQUADS
KEEPING WATCH,
AND DRONES FLYING
SURVEILLANCE.
HELIX HAS TO BE READY
FOR ALL OF THAT.
THAT'S WHY
WE'RE HERE.
ADDED SUPPORT
AND THE ELEMENT
OF SURPRISE.
YOU THINK FELICITY
WILL BE SURPRISED THAT
WE'RE TRYING TO
STOP HER? HEH.
ACTUALLY, I AM KIND OF
SURPRISED.
I MEAN, YOU AND HER
HAVE A HISTORY.
JUST KIND OF LIKE,
"OH, WE'RE AGAINST
EACH OTHER."
LET'S HAVE YOU
AND DINAH PATROL
THE SOUTHWEST.
STAY ON COMMS, OK?
-UH, QUICK QUESTION.
-MM-HMM.
WHAT DO WE DO
IF SHE SHOWS UP TONIGHT?
WE STOP HER.
LOGISTICS CALCULATES
A 46% LIKELIHOOD
THEY'LL TRY TO BREACH
THROUGH HERE.
OK. THEN WE'LL BE
READY FOR THEM.
WE'RE NOT EXPECTING
HELIX FOR ANOTHER
7 MINUTES,
SO WOULD YOU LIKE TO
USE THAT TIME TO TELL
ME WHAT I'VE DONE
THAT'S GOT YOU
SO PISSED OFF?
[SIGHS]
LYLA, I'M NOT PISSED OFF.
I AM CONCERNED.
WHAT DID FELICITY MEAN
WHEN SHE MADE
THAT CRACK ABOUT YOU
CROSSING A LINE?
I CAN'T EVEN BEGIN
TO FATHOM THE AMOUNT
OF CRAP THAT HELIX HAS
PUT INTO FELICITY'S
HEAD, JOHNNY.
BUT, LYLA, HOLDING
CAYDEN JAMES WITHOUT
DUE PROCESS,
THAT'S NOT
A BUNCH OF CRAP.
CAYDEN JAMES IS
20 TIMES MORE DANGEROUS
THAN SNOWDEN.
WE CAUGHT HIM TRYING
TO HACK AN ARGUS
TRANSPONDER.
IF HE GOT IN, EVERY
NOC AGENT WE HAVE
COULD BE AT RISK.
THAT SOUNDS A WHOLE LOT
LIKE AMANDA WALLER.
WALLER'S DECISIONS SEEM
A LOT LESS WRONG
FROM THIS SIDE
OF THE DESK, JOHNNY.
YOU CAN'T JUDGE ME
FOR THAT.
I'M NOT JUDGING.
I'M JUST WORRIED.
FELICITY SMOAK IS ONE
OF THE BEST PEOPLE
I'VE EVER KNOWN,
AND SHE'S GONE
OVER TO THE DARK SIDE.
I DON'T WANT THAT
TO HAPPEN TO MY WIFE.
ALENA: I'VE DONE A LOT
OF ILLEGAL THINGS,
BUT NONE OF THEM HAVE
REQUIRED HEAVY WEAPONRY
OR ANY WEAPONRY.
YOU KNOW, I FOUND
THE TRANSITION
BETWEEN HACKER
TO VIGILANTE TO BE
SURPRISINGLY
STRAIGHTFORWARD.
YOU'RE GONNA DO GREAT.
BESIDES, YOU HAVE
ENOUGH FIREPOWER HERE
TO INVADE RUSSIA.
WELL, HOPEFULLY,
WE WON'T HAVE TO.
THINK WE MIGHT.
THEY KNOW WE'RE COMING.
I'M NOT WORRIED.
IN CASE YOU NEED THEM.
NO.
I MEAN, EVEN IF WE DO,
I'M NOT USING THAT.
ARGUS WILL HAVE GUNS.
I THOUGHT YOU SAID NO ONE
WAS GONNA GET HURT.
IF WE DO THIS RIGHT,
NO ONE WILL.
WAIT FOR MY SIGNAL.
[DOOR OPENS,
QUENTIN WHISPERS INDISTINCTLY]
RENE: WHAT'S
SO IMPORTANT, HOSS?
I WAS GONNA CALL
IT A NIGHT.
DADDY!
SWEETHEART.
I TOLD YOU.
HEY. YOU'RE NOT
THE ONLY ONE AROUND HERE
THAT DOESN'T LISTEN
TO ORDERS.
WHO'S HE?
UH, THAT'S, UM,
QUENTIN, QUENTIN LANCE,
DADDY'S FRIEND,
BUT I CALL HIM HOSS.
HE ARRANGED
THIS LITTLE VISIT.
THANK YOU, HOSS.
-I MISSED YOU.
-OH, I MISSED YOU SO MUCH.
OH, I MISSED YOU MORE.
DANG, GIRL. YOU'RE
GETTING SO BIG.
LOOK AT YOU. I...
PRETTY SOON,
YOU'RE GONNA BE DRIVING
POPS TO THE GAMES.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT?
TELL YOUR DADDY WHAT YOU'RE
DOING AT SCHOOL NOW, ZOE.
I MADE
THE HOCKEY TEAM!
WHAT?! NO WAY.
WHAT POSITION
YOU PLAYING?
-GOALIE.
-THAT'S MY GIRL.
JUST LIKE YOUR POPS.
AW. THAT'S SO GOOD.
I'M PROUD OF YOU.
CAN WE GO HOME NOW?
I'M SORRY, SWEETHEART,
BUT NOT TODAY.
WHY?
SWEETHEART, THE LAST TIME
YOU WERE WITH ME,
YOU GOT HURT, BABY.
IT WAS AN ACCIDENT.
WHEN CAN I GO HOME
TO DADDY?
I DON'T KNOW,
SWEETHEART.
SOON, PEANUT.
THERE'S A LAWYER FRIEND
DADDY'S FRIEND KNOWS,
AND DADDY'S DECIDED
HE'S GONNA TALK TO HIM
AND YOU'RE GONNA
COME HOME WITH ME.
I PROMISE.
OK? I PROMISE.
THOUGHT YOU WERE STANDING
POST WITH LYLA.
SEEMED LIKE A GOOD IDEA
TO PUT SOME SPACE
BETWEEN US.
FELICITY ISN'T
THE ONLY LADY WHO THINKS
THE ENDS JUSTIFIES
THE MEANS.
WHEN LYLA
AND FELICITY SMOAK ARE
WILLING TO CROSS THE LINE...
MAKES YOU WONDER
IF THERE EVEN IS
ONE, RIGHT?
LYLA ON COMMS:
WE GOT INCOMING.
TANGOS IN THE FIELD.
COPY THAT.
WHAT'S THAT?
THINK OF IT
AS A WEAPONIZED TABLET
PRELOADED WITH
ADDRESS RESOLUTION
PROTOCOL SPOOFING.
THE ARGUS SITE
IS PROTECTED
BY MICROCHIPPED
GUN TURRETS.
RIGHT. THIS WILL
SHUT THEM DOWN?
HOO.
YOU SURE YOU'RE
READY FOR THIS?
LET'S DO THIS.
BOGEYS ON SITE.
WANT US TO INTERCEPT?
NEGATIVE.
DRAW THEM IN CLOSER.
[METAL DETECTOR BEEPING]
IDENTIFICATION,
PLEASE.
IT'S NOT THEM.
LYLA, SITREP.
THE VAN CHECKED OUT.
IT WASN'T HELIX.
WE HAVE A PROBLEM.
WAIT.
THIS ISN'T ARGUS.
NO, IT IS,
JUST NOT THE SITE
ARGUS EXPECTED
US TO HIT.
OLIVER: WHAT PROBLEM?
HELIX IS ABOUT TO EXTRACT
CAYDEN JAMES.
HOW?
THEY'RE NOT HERE.
NEITHER IS CAYDEN JAMES.
AND YOU
DIDN'T TELL US?
I DIDN'T THINK IT WAS
NECESSARY.
WHERE IS HE?
AT AN OFF-BOOKS BLACK SITE
12 MILES AWAY.
DAMN IT, LYLA.
YOU SHOULD HAVE LET
US IN ON THE PLAN.
HELIX WASN'T SUPPOSED TO
KNOW ABOUT THE BLACK SITE.
NO ONE WAS.
THAT'S BECAUSE
IT'S ILLEGAL.
I'M NOT DISCUSSING
THIS, JOHNNY.
GET YOUR HEAD
IN THE GAME.
YOU'RE TWO MINUTES OUT.
FELICITY: WHERE HAS THIS
TABLET BEEN ALL MY LIFE?
ALENA: I MADE IT
SPECIAL FOR YOU.
SO MUCH BETTER THAN
A FRIENDSHIP BRACELET.
FELICITY: OHH! HOW ARE WE
GONNA FIND CAYDEN JAMES?
I KNOW HE'S INSIDE ONE
OF THESE CONTAINERS,
BUT I DON'T KNOW
EXACTLY WHICH ONE.
CAN YOU CHECK TO SEE
IF THERE'S A SITE MAP?
MM-HMM.
OK.
WHATEVER ARGUS IS
KEEPING IN THERE
THEY WANT
TO KEEP SECURE.
OR WHOEVER.
TWO AIR-GAPPED
UNHACKABLE KEYS.
IT'S BEAUTIFUL
TECH, REALLY.
FREE CAYDEN JAMES NOW,
ADMIRE ARGUS TECH LATER.
RIGHT.
-ONE...
-TWO...
THREE.
ALENA: CAYDEN?
CAYDEN? HEY.
IT'S OK.
THIS IS A RESCUE.
WE GOT TO MOVE.
TEAM ARROW WILL BE
HERE ANY MINUTE.
I DOUBT THAT VERY MUCH.
THEY HAVE NO CLUE
WE'RE HERE.
[GUNFIRE]
DO NOT SAY
"I TOLD YOU SO."
MEET US OUT BACK IN 5.
WHERE ARE WE GOING?
WE'RE GONNA GO SAY HI
TO YOUR FRIENDS.
[CANARY CRY]
[GRUNTING]
HYAH!
UNH!
DON'T GRAB A WOMAN UNLESS YOU
HAVE PERMISSION, DUMBASS.
FREEZE!
I'VE GOT
FELICITY'S FRIEND.
I HAVE A NAME,
YOU KNOW?
TURN AROUND,
PUT YOUR HANDS
ON YOUR HEAD.
-DO IT!
-OK. TURNING.
[GUNFIRE]
YOU WANT TO SEE
WHAT ELSE THEY CAN DO?
[GUNSHOT]
NEXT ONE GOES
IN HIS HEAD.
THEN IT WILL HAVE TO
GO THROUGH ME. GO!
GET OUT OF THE WAY!
YOU KNOW I CAN'T
DO THAT.
I WAS REALLY HOPING
YOU WOULDN'T!
OLIVER, DON'T MOVE.
THAT IS A 30-KILOWATT
SPECTRAL BEAM LASER.
IT WILL CUT YOU
TO THE BONE.
CURTIS WILL LET YOU OUT.
I'M SORRY.
I AM. I'M REALLY HOPING
THAT YOU'RE GONNA
UNDERSTAND
AFTER WE GET CHASE.
DON'T COUNT ON IT.
CURTIS:
ON THE BRIGHT SIDE,
WE WERE SUITED UP.
I MEAN, I'M GLAD
CAYDEN JAMES DOESN'T
KNOW THAT, YOU KNOW,
WE WERE TRYING TO
KEEP HIM IN PRISON
BECAUSE IF HE DID
I WOULD BE SCARED
OF MY REFRIGERATOR,
MY CAR, MY ALARM CLOCK,
AND CAN WE TALK
ABOUT ELEVATORS
FOR A SECOND?
BECAUSE I THINK
I'M GONNA BE TAKING
THE STAIRS FOR A WHILE,
WHICH IS BETTER
FOR YOUR...YOUR HEALTH.
ALSO, ON THE BRIGHT SIDE,
YOU KNOW,
SO JUST THINK
ABOUT THAT.
JOHN: THIS WASN'T
A PRISON, CURTIS.
THIS WAS AN ILLEGAL
BLACK SITE ON AMERICAN SOIL
LED BY MY WIFE.
ALSO NO ARGUS
CASUALTI...NO ARGUS
CASUALTIES, YOU KNOW?
THE MERCS USED
RUBBER BULLETS,
SO THAT WAS...
WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO
ABOUT FELICITY?
THERE IS NOTHING
TO DO.
SHE PUT HERSELF
IN FRONT OF A BULLET
IN ORDER TO TAKE
DOWN CHASE.
TILL THAT HAPPENS,
I DON'T KNOW WHAT
TO SAY TO HER.
IN THE MEANTIME,
WE DRINK TO HER
SPEEDY SUCCESS.
I MEAN...
IN THE MEANTIME,
I THINK WE GO HOME.
WHY? THERE'S
MORE GLASSES
IN THE BUNK...
OH, YOU WANT TO
DRINK BY YOUR...
OK. YEAH. RIGHT.
THAT MAKE...YEAH.
THANK YOU BOTH
VERY MUCH FOR TONIGHT.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
HEY. YEP.
YOU'RE WORKING LATE.
WELL, I THOUGHT
I'D STICK AROUND
FOR MY THANK-YOU.
YOU HAD THAT COMING
FOR SURE
ALONG WITH AN APOLOGY.
THERE I WAS THINKING
YOU DIDN'T KNOW
WHAT AN APOLOGY WAS.
I GUESS YOU CAN TEACH
A DOG SOME NEW TRICKS,
EVEN WILD ONES.
I, UH...I SPOKE
TO CURTIS' LAWYER FRIEND.
I PUT THINGS
IN MOTION.
GOOD FOR YOU.
YOU KNOW, THAT ZOE,
SHE'S A HELL
OF A LITTLE GIRL,
AND...YOU KNOW, SHE
DESERVES HER DAD.
YOU KNOW,
FATHER TO FATHER,
I GOT TO TELL YOU
HER DAD DESERVES
TO BE WITH HER.
THANK YOU.
THAT'S WHAT I WAS
WAITING FOR.
ALL RIGHT. HOW ABOUT
A CELEBRATORY
CLUB SODA?
I'M BUYING.
OH. WAIT. HOLD ON
A SECOND, HOSS.
HOW ABOUT
SOMETHING STRONGER?
IF YOU KEEP
CALLING ME HOSS,
I'LL SHOW YOU
SOMETHING STRONGER.
FELICITY: HELLO?
ALENA:
HEY, FELICITY.
HEY. WHERE ARE YOU?
ARE YOU OK?
WE'RE SAFE.
THANK YOU FOR ALL
OF YOUR HELP,
BUT HERE'S
THE THING.
YOUR CONNECTION
TO THE GREEN ARROW
AND HIS TEAM,
IT'S A LIABILITY.
YEAH. WELL, ONCE
WE GET CHASE,
HE'LL SEE ALL THE GOOD
HELIX CAN DO.
I'M SORRY,
BUT WE JUST
CAN'T RISK IT,
ESPECIALLY NOT
WITH CAYDEN BACK
IN THE FOLD
AND ARGUS LOOKING
FOR HIM.
I LOVED GETTING
TO WORK WITH YOU.
MEETING YOUR HEROES,
IT TURNS OUT
IT'S NOT SO BAD
AFTER ALL,
BUT WE LEFT
SOMETHING FOR YOU.
LOOK DOWN.
UP A LITTLE BIT.
LITTLE BIT
TO THE RIGHT.
OH. THIS?
WHAT IS IT?
SOME ON-THE-FLY CODING
FROM MR. JAMES.
TOLD YOU HE WAS THE BEST
THERE EVER WAS.
TAKE CARE, FELICITY.
YEAH. YOU, TOO.
JOHNNY.
WE NEED TO TALK
ABOUT THIS.
I DON'T THINK THAT'S
A GOOD IDEA, LYLA.
I COULD SAY SOMETHING
I MIGHT REGRET.
JOHN.
WHEN YOU SAID THAT YOU
WERE TAKING OVER FOR WALLER,
YOU SAID YOU WOULDN'T
BECOME HER.
I TOLD YOU
IT'S MORE COMPLICATED
WHEN YOU'RE SITTING
ON THE OTHER SIDE
OF THE...
WHAT THE HELL
IS MORE COMPLICATED?
YOU'RE HOLDING SOMEONE
WITH NO LAWYER,
NO TRIAL, NO JUSTICE.
AND THE WORLD
IS SAFER FOR IT.
IT COULD BE SAFER...
BUT IT'S NOT BETTER.
THE WOMAN I LOVE
COULD NEVER DO THIS.
LYLA, THIS JOB
HAS CHANGED YOU.
MAYBE,
BUT MAYBE
THE WORLD'S CHANGED.
IT'S GOTTEN
EVEN WORSE, JOHNNY.
IT'S GOTTEN WORSE
AND UGLIER,
AND WE DO WHAT WE CAN
TO PROTECT THE PEOPLE
WE LOVE.
I AM NOT ASHAMED
OF WHAT I DID...
OF WHAT I'M
STILL GOING TO DO.
WE'VE BEEN DOWN
THIS ROAD BEFORE,
HAVEN'T WE?
WE KNOW WHERE THIS FIGHT
TAKES US.
SO LET'S STOP IT...
MOVE FORWARD.
I DON'T KNOW
IF I CAN.
[COMPUTER BEEPING]
-IS THAT IT?
-YEP.
JAMES' MAGIC TRACKER
TO FIND CHASE?
BIOMETRIC TRACKER,
YES.
NOBODY FROM ARGUS WAS
SERIOUSLY INJURED
IN CASE YOU
WERE WONDERING.
HELIX FROZE ME OUT.
-IT'S OVER.
-SORRY.
THOUGHT YOU WERE NEVER
GOING TO LIE TO ME AGAIN.
I'M NOT LYING.
I'M SORRY.
I KNOW THAT THEY
GAVE YOU
A SENSE OF BELONGING
THAT I HAVEN'T...
NO.
YOU DIDN'T BACK
MY PLAY.
I...I WAS WORRIED.
YOU DON'T TRUST ME.
AFTER ALL THESE YEARS,
ALL OF THE TIMES
THAT I SUPPORTED YOU,
EVEN WHEN I DIDN'T
AGREE,
YOU COULDN'T DO
THE SAME FOR ME.
MMM...
WHAT'S THAT?
[COMPUTER BEEPING]
TRACKER'S HOMING IN
ON CHASE'S LOCATION.
WHERE IS HE?
CHASE...HE'S HERE.
[BEEP BEEP BEEP BEEP]
MAN: GREG, MOVE YOUR HEAD!