CUPID: (SINGING)
Let me call you sweetheart
It's okay. It's okay.
-I'm in love with you
-(SOBS)
(CUPID HUMMING)
CUPID: (SINGING)
That you love me too
(CUPID HUMMING)
Whatever you're thinking of doing,
you don't have to.
-Please. Just let us go.
-In your eyes
-We won't tell anyone...
-No. No one. Absolutely not.
-Right?
-CUPID: Wonderful!
Agreement.
The mortar that holds together
the bricks of love. (CHUCKLES)
So how much do you love each other?
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
With everything that I have.
Oh...
And the missus?
How much does she love her mister?
More than anything in the world.
How sweet.
And pathetic.
Wha... What?
"Love is a bullet to the brain."
(CLINKS)
(GRUNTS AND THUDS)
Or an arrow to the heart.
(CHUCKLES)
JUDGE SAKOW: Please be seated.
First, I'll hear the parties
on the question of bail.
FITZMARTIN:
Your Honor, the defendant wishes
to waive bail so that the court can focus
its attention on our motion to dismiss...
Your Honor, the defendant was apprehended
at the site of a child abduction...
Because he was being held captive himself.
Your Honor.
These documents will confirm
my client's identity as Kenneth Bender,
citizen of Markovia.
LAUREL: Your Honor, this is ridiculous.
The defendant's name is Damien Darhk...
FITZMARTIN: According to whom? You?
Oliver Queen? The media?
(SCOFFS)
Your Honor, there's absolutely
no evidence whatsoever
to suggest that my client
is this Damien Darhk,
much less prove beyond a reasonable doubt
that he committed these acts
that Damien Darhk is even accused of.
Your Honor, we have evidence
and we will present it at trial.
During which time, what,
my client just rots in jail?
I mean, fortunately,
he's no longer in Markovia, right?
Because, you know, in America we...
We have preliminary hearings to determine
whether the State can meet
its burden of proof.
Your Honor...
You say you have evidence, Ms. Lance?
Get ready to present it.
Mr. Darhk...
or Mr. Bender or whatever
he's calling himself...
is hereby remanded to the custody
of the Department of Corrections,
to be held
until disposition of defendant's motion
to dismiss.
(BANGS GAVEL)
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
I worked out a system to maximize
the efficiency of the moving process.
The densest, heaviest boxes
are put into the moving truck first,
creating a solid foundation
for the rest of the boxes,
and providing maximum recovery time
during the most physical moments
of moving.
There's, um, less chance for injury too.
I hired a mover.
(CHUCKLES) And I would never wanna step
on the toes of professionals,
but proper distribution of the mass
and density of the boxes
inside the moving truck could have
cost saving effects for the moving company
in the form of improved gas mileage.
Okay. Great.
So you're doing great.
The...
It's just amazing how much progress
you've made in such little time.
Paul must be just
a physical therapy genius.
Yes, like a symphony of the talents.
You know, with Curtis and Paul.
They're kind of the perfect team.
You know, marrying tech...
Poor choice of words! My bad!
My specialty.
It's okay. That's fine.
I... You know, it's not like, um...
I don't know what it's like.
We were engaged.
And now we're not even together.
That's what it's like.
Could you cancel the venue, please?
Uh, yes. I will get around
to canceling the venue.
Great. Thank you.
(CHUCKLES) And I will
uninvite the guests.
Okay.
The movers'll will swing by
whenever you want.
Just give them a call.
I'll see you when I see you.
Well, tonight...
Tonight?
Yeah. Didn't, I... I, uh...
I mean, I guess we didn't talk about it,
but I was a part of the team
before we were together,
I just assumed...
Oh, tonight, like...
(STUTTERING)
Like every night. Um...
Of course.
You're a part of the team
forever and always.
Keep moving.
BARON : Stop here.
This is it.
OLIVER: Okay, well...
Now that you've found what you're
looking for, you don't need us,
-so we can just...
-No.
This isn't the end, Mr. Queen.
It's the beginning...
Of what?
BARON: I grew up
in a small village in Africa.
A country whose name has changed
a dozen of times over the years.
One day, bandits came to my village.
They wanted water and gold and women.
Once they left with them,
the only thing remaining
of my village was ash.
My home and everyone I loved
was wiped from the earth.
And I was helpless to stop it.
And I swore I would never feel
helpless again.
So killing all the people
you're holding hostage
is gonna help you not feel helpless?
How does that make you
any different than the people
who destroyed your village?
Oh, it makes me very different.
Let me show you.
-(GUNSHOT)
-(GROANS)
How'd it go out there tonight?
It was quiet.
Yeah, this city hasn't had a quiet night
in four years.
DIGGLE: Yeah. I can't believe
HIVE is silent just because
Damien Darhk is in jail.
Not for long...
What are you talking about?
The law's pesky need for evidence.
The Ghosts who took William also took
their cyanide escape plans.
There's no one to testify against Darhk.
-What about my brother?
-LAUREL: You mean the one
that was declared legally dead
five years ago?
No.
It should be walking him into court...
-What about us?
-Yeah.
Damien kidnapped us over the holiday.
We're all witnesses.
Actually, that's good.
The fiancée to the city's
beloved mayoral candidate...
It makes for a compelling story.
What's wrong?
Oliver and I aren't engaged anymore.
Um, or living together.
Or together, together...
-Felicity...
-It's fine.
FELICITY: Which is the universal code for
"I don't wanna talk about it."
DIGGLE: Pieces of Darhk's idol, huh?
-Yeah.
-How're you holding up?
Felicity tell you guys?
How're you holding up?
Was this about your son?
The fact that I lied to her about him?
Yeah.
Yeah, well, you got a kid, man,
that's a whole lot to handle.
But don't worry. She'll come around.
Give her time.
I mean, she wants to stay on the team...
That's a good sign.
-(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
-I think.
THEA: Hey.
Lance just called. It's trouble.
HIVE?
He said it was an old friend.
-(INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER)
-(SIRENS WAILING)
All right, you guys take five.
Hey. You okay?
You do look a little more grim than usual.
Just let me know who did this.
(SIGHS) Look familiar?
Cupid.
She's supposed
to be in custody at A.R.G.U.S.
Yeah?
Tell that to them.
What was there?
She left a note for us.
"Love is dead."
So, is nobody else going to say it?
"It's Cupid, stupid."
Well, she's changed up her M.O. a little.
"Love is dead."
Oh, maybe she's not so insane after all.
I thought Cupid was locked away in some
A.R.G.U.S. sub-basement?
Yeah, not anymore. Just talked to Lyla,
turns out Waller was serious
about prisoners
like Cupid working their way off
of Task Force X.
She's out.
Then we start with her victims.
Did CSU ID them?
-They're running prints.
-THEA: Like, seriously?
None of your crime tech guys
read gossip websites?
(CHUCKLES) Uh, let's assume they don't.
This is Blaine and this is Shannon.
Okay?
Really, guys?
Come on, it's the...
Wedding of the decade.
FELICITY: Why did Cupid wanna ice
Star City's most high profile couple?
Well, we figure that out, we figure out
who her next targets might be.
How do we know there's gonna be
a next target?
I don't think that Carrie Cutter
has changed that much.
We got to get to court.
I'm gonna stay here, work up
some leads on Cupid.
DIGGLE: It was Oliver Queen
Campaign holiday party.
There was gunfire.
The security that we had on site
was killed.
And then, he walked in.
Let the record reflect that the witness
is pointing to the defendant.
And why did the defendant walk in to
Oliver Queen's campaign office?
He was the leader of the gunmen.
He took myself, Thea Queen
and Felicity Smoak hostage.
LAUREL: And while you were held hostage...
DIGGLE: Damien Darhk...
or whatever he calls himself
was there,
calling the shots, the entire time.
Pass the witness.
(CLEARS THROAT)
FITZMARTIN: This, uh, holiday party.
Were you, uh...
Were you there as a guest?
No, sir.
I work security,
personal security for Mr. Oliver Queen.
I have been for the past three-plus years.
Even after Mr. Queen lost his job
as CEO of Queen Consolidated?
I mean... (SCOFFS)
How much does he pay you?
Ten cents an hour?
LAUREL: Objection.
Relevance.
Sustained. Move faster, Mr. Fitzmartin.
FITZMARTIN: Of course, Your Honor.
All right, well, let's, uh, talk about
your alleged co-captive,
Thea Queen.
Isn't it true that five months ago,
you helped her buy $74,000
worth of cocaine?
(PEOPLE MURMURING)
And before you answer that,
you should know that I have
a signed affidavit
from Ms. Queen's dealer, right here.
Which means nothing
because it is irrelevant.
Well, it goes to credibility, Your Honor.
FITZMARTIN: Oliver Queen
publicly slandered my client
by accusing him of ordering
a terrorist drone strike.
Now, if Mr. Diggle can work
for Mr. Queen for free,
to help Ms. Queen buy illegal drugs,
I mean, is it really
that much of a stretch to believe
that he'd also perjure himself in support
of Mr. Queen's campaign
of character assassination?
You watched me swear an oath!
(SIGHS) And then saw you break it.
No further questions, Your Honor.
I don't have a law degree,
but I don't think that went well.
It could've been worse.
If Fitzmartin kept pulling
on those threads,
then everything that we've done
for the city could've been exposed.
Worth it to put Darhk away.
Except it wouldn't put him away.
Because vigilantes
don't make good witnesses?
No, but they make excellent inmates.
Yeah.
(EXHALES)
Okay, so where does this leave us?
We can't just let Darhk walk.
Well, unless I come up with a witness
who Fitzmartin can't tear apart,
then that's what's gonna happen.
Then put me on the stand.
QUENTIN: I don't have a secret identity.
And I can testify about Darhk
and his connection to HIVE.
And spend the rest of your life in jail.
If it's in a cell next to Darhk
it'd be worth it.
-(CELL PHONE BUZZING)
-No.
-We'll find another way.
-It's Felicity.
Huh.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Put it on speaker.
Felicity, we have the whole team here.
What's up?
Good news is, I got Cupid's location.
-DIGGLE: Good. Where is she?
-That's the bad news.
Looks like she's kidnapped
another celebrity couple.
Allison Lee and Robert Joyce.
(SIGHS) Allibert.
Track the GPS on their phones.
When I said I had their location,
how did you think that I got it?
Okay, Felicity, what's next?
Where are we going?
They're on the move
headed towards Pennytown.
Got it.
I'd suit up with you but...
No, what you're doing here
is more important.
Get Darhk.
Get Cupid.
(EMPTY BOTTLES CLANKING)
"'Till death do us part."
(CHUCKLES)
Don't worry.
You won't have to wait that long.
CUPID: Wedding crashers.
Hold on tight.
(TIRES SCREECHING)
SPARTAN: Speedy, look out!
(GRUNTS)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
She's in the center.
(GRUNTS) I'm okay.
Stay with Speedy.
Let them help you.
ARROW: I'll get Cupid.
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
I'd say enjoy the afterlife,
but we both know that's just
eternal nothingness.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(PANTING)
I was in love with the Arrow
but you're not him.
Although I do like the sleeveless.
I got her.
(COMPUTER WHIRRS AND BEEPS)
(CLANKS)
(SIGHS)
(METAL CLANKS)
(ROPE WHIRRS)
(GRUNTS)
I guess you didn't have her.
Really brings a whole new meaning
to crazy ex-girlfriend,
and you didn't even get to enjoy
the fun parts.
Sorry.
Well, Cutter fell
for Floyd Lawton last year.
Lucky guy.
She was heartbroken when he was blown up.
No, Thea's right, though,
Cutter is pathological.
OLIVER: I mean, targeting happy couples?
-Come on!
-Well, it makes sense
if you look at it from her perspective.
Love betrayed her
and now she wants to go to war against it.
And, then that's making sense?
It makes sense to her.
Okay.
She's not just targeting regular couples.
She's targeting celebrity couples.
Probably to bring attention
to her anti-love crusade.
Lance is getting the word out.
He assigned a protective detail.
I'm gonna run forensics on this.
We're gonna hit the streets,
see if we can get a line on Cutter.
Okay.
You wanna talk about
the other obvious problem?
Yeah, the, uh, elephant in the room?
Felicity and I are fine.
(SCOFFS) If you've been listening
to her little asides,
you would know that was not true.
(SCOFFS) John, you were the one
who told me to just give her time.
Okay.
Do you want to get back together with her?
-I do.
-Then tell her that.
DIGGLE: Even if you fall on your face,
Oliver, she needs to know where you stand.
She needs to know that you're willing
to say the words.
-I am willing to say the words.
-DIGGLE: That's good.
So what's stopping you?
(GASPING)
TAIANA: Why did you do that?
-BARON: Don't!
-(MAN GASPS)
Let him die.
What? You're insane!
The difference between insanity and belief
lies only in the number of believers.
This is the power of a single life.
Above us, I have dozens under my control.
MERC: The prisoners are gathered topside.
The men are in position.
Tell them to shoot.
(GRUNTING)
Come on! Come on!
Go, go, go, go!
Oh, hey.
(DOOR CLOSES)
So how'd the rest of the day in court go?
If it went well,
I wouldn't be here still doing this.
(SIGHS)
Listen, I was thinkin', what about
all the rest of the people
at the holiday party, all right?
'Cause they all saw Darhk.
Yeah. It's probably why
they're all too frightened to testify.
We could subpoena 'em.
I did that this afternoon.
One lied,
one in jail because they refused
to testify and one actually tried
pleading the Fifth.
Well, I told you, there's one guy
willing to take a stand.
Dad, I went to my boss and I asked him
to give you immunity from prosecution.
He said he'd prefer to be re-elected.
I don't care about immunity.
But I do.
Dad, I'm not gonna let you
incriminate yourself.
You wouldn't be doing anything.
And it'd be me. And it'd be right.
I'm the one who got in to bed with Darhk
but I made those decisions.
And I should pay the consequences
to 'em, honey.
And, listen, it's the only way
to bring him down.
(SIGHS)
(SOFTLY) Okay.
Okay.
If we do this,
you will also testify
that you acted under duress.
That Damien threatened my life.
Yeah.
'Cause that way I get to say on record
how much I love my baby girl.
Okay.
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
-Felicity Scissorhands.
-Ha-ha.
Struck out trying to find
a line on Cutter.
What's this?
I couldn't exactly fit the entire sleeve
into the gas chromatograph.
(COMPUTER WHIRRS AND BEEPS)
FELICITY: Speak of the devil.
The sleeve contains fibers from at least
60 different types of white silk lace.
White lace. Like in wedding dresses?
That would be ironic.
And also traces
-of acid-free polypropylene.
-(TYPING ON KEYBOARD)
What do they use that for?
-Long term storage of fabrics.
-Well, maybe Cutter's holed up
in a spot where they sell wedding dresses.
FELICITY: Colao Wedding Dress Services
it's the only long-term storage facility
in the city that uses polypropylene.
Twenty-eighth and Hamilton.
That is two blocks from where
she posed the first two victims.
(SIGHS)
The only movement I'm tracking
in that building is you guys.
Stay alert.
SPARTAN: Got something.
Whoa.
ARROW: She does love
her shrines, doesn't she?
SPARTAN: Now we know
how she's picking her targets.
The first two couples,
they were both recently gotten married.
ARROW: Cutter abducted the second couple
after their wedding.
SPEEDY: Yeah.
But Blaine and Shannon, "Blannon",
had a secret wedding 48 hours
before they were killed.
SPARTAN: Now we have to figure out
what celebrity couple
in the city's getting married next.
I think I found one we can rule out.
So by calling off the engagement,
we took ourselves
out of Cupid's crosshairs.
I knew there had to be at least
one silver lining.
Well, she keeps on targeting
high-profile weddings,
so we just got to stake out
whatever the next one is.
That's a big risk to run
with an innocent couple.
We're not gonna take that risk
Hey.
We need to get married.
How romantic...
It's, uh, Felicity...
This is the worst idea you've ever had!
Actually it's not the worst.
Et tu, John?
We lost our lead on Cutter, Felicity.
And this might draw her out.
Oh, so she can kill me?
(GRUNTS) Pass. No, thank you.
Okay.
No, John and I will have your back.
I guess it's too bad I already sent out
all those "un-invitations."
Clearly, none of you guys spend any time
on gossip sites.
THEA: (CHUCKLES)
Okay, look, these bloggers love
nothing more than a private,
secret wedding.
I'll leak the news, saying
you guys wanted to keep it under radar...
It becomes the top story on the website.
It's catnip for Cupid.
Okay, look, we
have to do this quickly, okay?
So Cupid doesn't change her M.O.,
and start killing more innocent couples.
-Can we do this tomorrow?
-Tomorrow will work.
The venue still has our deposit, though.
We'll be able to move up the date.
I thought you said you were
gonna cancel that?
I did say that I was gonna cancel
and I am gonna cancel,
but I haven't canceled yet.
Because when I picked up the ph...
When I pick up the phone to do that,
it means, it's over.
It is over.
Hey. Taiana, wait. Whoa, whoa...
Well, I think we lost them.
Look. Look.
Reiter is not gonna issue a kill order
if he doesn't have
that thing nearby.
You grabbing it, you saved us.
If that's true, then we should destroy
the damn thing.
-No, wait!
-(GRUNTS)
REITER: (OVER RADIO)
Ah, Mr. Queen.
You took his radio?
I know you're still down here, Mr. Queen.
You should have studied
those maps more closely.
The only way out of these tunnels
is back the way you came.
Which means going through me.
You can either return of your own accord,
or you can force me to come and find you.
But don't bother trying
to fight your way out of this.
After all, I'm the only one of us
who has men and guns.
Last August, Darhk asked me
for the vacation plans for the Chief
of the Fire Department.
Objection.
Darhk. Bender.
Whatever he wants to call himself.
I told him where Chief Reynolds
was staying.
The next day, the place blows up.
Objection. Conjecture.
Something you're free to challenge
on cross examination.
Continue, Ms. Lance.
(EXHALES) What else did you do
for the defendant?
QUENTIN: He wanted me to give him
access to the SCPD computer network.
I did it.
He wanted me to give him
the departmental patrol schedules.
I did that.
He wanted me to break
into a federal server farm
to install a computer virus
and I did that.
He wanted me to give him information
on the city's leadership and I...
I did that.
And three days later,
the city leadership were all dead.
You did all of these things
for the defendant?
The defendant and the organization
he works for. He called it HIVE.
Objection. Your Honor, it's hearsay.
Statement against interests, Your Honor.
Overruled.
Captain Lance,
why would you do these things?
At first, I didn't know his intentions.
Like with the Fire Chief.
But when I confronted Darhk about it,
he told me that if I didn't do
everything he asked,
everything he told me to do,
he'd have you killed.
(PEOPLE MURMURING)
No more questions, Your Honor.
Mr. Fitzmartin, your witness.
Captain Lance, have you ever
personally witnessed my client commit
any illegal act?
Well, I'm pretty sure that threatening
the daughter of a police captain
-isn't legal, counselor.
-FITZMARTIN: Objection.
-Overruled.
-You know, the fact of the matter is,
I've seen your client
in his little hidey hole,
with his little men.
Ghosts, he calls 'em.
And I've heard him say repeatedly
how he wants to destroy this city.
And that if I didn't help him do it, then,
he'd kill my daughter.
(PEOPLE MURMURING)
By saying all these things,
I'm setting a match to my career.
Maybe my life.
So why would I be doin' that
if everything I'm saying isn't true?
(SIGHS)
(BEEPS)
In position.
There's no psychopaths here
other than paparazzi.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
I'm tapped into the security cameras.
All clear.
-(DOOR OPENS)
-(FELICITY SIGHS)
Everything okay?
Yes. Yeah.
You look perfect.
Thanks.
I'd like to assure you, I won't breathe
a word of what goes on here to the press.
I'm just thrilled to be part of your day.
-Thank you.
-Can we get this over with?
(OLIVER CLEARS THROAT)
(CHUCKLES)
Can't wait to be married to this guy!
Well...
In that case,
I know you've written your own vows.
Felicity...
The vows?
(SOFTLY) Yeah.
Okay. Um.
(CHUCKLES)
Oliver, you have many qualities.
Many astonishing qualities.
And I, for one, cannot wait to move on
to the next chapter.
All right.
Oliver?
Felicity...
Before I met you, I had a plan.
I had a way that I was gonna be.
But then you walked
into my life, all right.
I showed up in your cubicle...
and you changed everything.
I was in darkness.
But with your kindness,
your generosity, your compassion,
your intelligence, your wit
and your trust,
you brought me into the light.
You let me know that I deserved it.
You were that light.
And I don't know
if I still deserve that trust.
If I deserve you.
I probably don't.
But whatever's happened,
whatever will happen,
the way that you make me feel,
is the best part of my life.
You can ask me to say
that I don't love you.
And I will never
lie to you again.
You are my always.
And I just want the chance to be yours.
Oliver...
(GASPS)
Hello, lovers.
Run!
Copy that. I'm here.
Yeah, we got that. Hold tight.
Your little speech
was only off by a little.
You see, she isn't
the best thing in your life
because that means you love her.
And love means you're soft.
And soft, means death.
Here, let me show you.
(GRUNTS)
(GASPS) Oh, sorry,
I didn't check your gift registry.
Was an explosion
that would bring down
this whole building on your list?
-(BOMB BEEPING)
-(CHUCKLING)
(BOMB BEEPING)
Your engagement, that horrible shooting,
(CHUCKLES) your miracle recovery,
that was all just a fairy tale.
Camelot in Star City.
Thank you.
But once Camelot dies,
everyone will know my truth...
That love is a bullet to the brain.
(OLIVER GROANS) No. No, it's not.
(PANTS)
Kevlar under the tux.
My bodyguard insisted.
-(RINGS)
-What was his plan for C-4?
That's a damn good question.
You know, you don't have to do this.
I do.
(CHUCKLES)
The two words that start every marriage.
"I do." True love.
People need to see,
they need to know what a joke that is.
It's not.
I have loved two men in my life...
...with all my soul.
They're both dead now.
No matter what, love always ends in death.
That's why it's in the vows.
I'm just cutting out the middle man.
Love is death.
FELICITY: It's not.
You saw all those people outside, right?
They're out there because love is real,
because love is life itself.
And if I die tonight,
it'll be okay,
because I was one of those people
lucky enough to have experienced it.
From the moment he walked into my life,
everything changed.
I became a person that I didn't even know
I was capable of becoming.
I became the very best version of myself
that would have never have been possible
without our love.
Our love gives my life meaning,
it gives my life a purpose,
and it brings us more joy
than you can ever take away from us.
And it's worth living for.
All of it.
You really know how to make a girl
believe in love again.
(GUNSHOT)
(CUPID GASPS)
(GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
-(GUNSHOT)
-(GRUNTS)
Are you all right?
Yeah.
-(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
-(CAMERA SHUTTERS CLICKING)
You two give the rest of us hope.
-You okay?
-Uh, yeah.
About what you said in there to Cutter...
Maybe we could meet up and talk about it.
Tonight or...
No. Not tonight.
I think we're both exhausted
from whatever that was.
Tomorrow?
THEA: Hey, guys. Laurel just texted.
I guess Judge Sakow's holding court late,
and she's making her decision.
(SIGHS) I should probably change.
(CHUCKLES)
This outfit is a bit of a focus-puller.
Mmm-hmm.
Not for nothing, Oliver, but I heard
what, uh, Felicity said in there.
Nobody likes an "I told you so", John.
I'm just saying, she needs some time.
Watch it. Could be a trap.
They just left it behind?
Why would they do that?
(GRUNTING)
Drop the weapon.
(GRUNTS)
Maybe you should radio Reiter.
Why?
Now we have guns, too.
The standard of proof
for a preliminary hearing
is much less severe
than one for a trial. Even so,
the evidence against the defendant
is exceedingly thin.
There is no forensic
or circumstantial evidence
that points to the defendant's guilt.
But I found Quentin Lance's testimony
to be particularly compelling.
His credibility is bolstered
by his status as a police captain,
but the fact that he was willing
to incriminate himself
to see justice done makes his testimony
especially believable.
On the strength of it,
I am denying
the defense's motion to dismiss
and binding the defendant over for trial.
Mr. Darhk will be held without bail
-or possibility of release.
-(BANGS GAVEL)
BALIFF: Defendant will rise.
(PEOPLE MURMURING)
Officers, please escort the defendant
from the courtroom.
All right, next step.
Convicting the son of a bitch.
The next step, right. Are we okay?
I wasn't exactly
pulling punches on the stand.
Oh, I'm glad you didn't. 'Cause of that
Darhk's defense is blown to shreds.
He's gonna spend the rest of his life
behind bars.
Hey, Quentin. You have a minute?
Yeah.
Lieutenant Pike,
if I could just talk to you before...
It's all right, sweetheart.
We both knew this was coming. Frank.
You're being suspended
pending an I.A.B. investigation.
I'll need your badge and your weapon.
Yeah.
I'm sorry about this, Quentin.
I'm sure your union rep
will make it clear to I.A.B.
that you were acting under duress.
Yeah, I'm good either way, Frank.
Truly.
It's a temporary setback.
I'll represent you in front of I.A.B...
You just focus on nailing Darhk
to a cross, all right?
I'm proud of you, baby.
(SIGHS)
MALE REPORTER: We have the results
of the high profile preliminary hearing
-against reported Markovia citizen,
-Hi.
Kenneth Bender, also known
as Damien Darhk...
Hi.
Darhk had previously been
implicated in...
-Thought you'd be asleep by now.
-Oh, I can't sleep.
What are you doing here?
I just came to pick up
a few things, you know.
...favorite couple Oliver Queen and
Felicity Smoak in an unexpected...
It's not exactly
how I pictured our wedding day.
I don't know.
Being kidnapped by psychotic criminals
has sort of been the theme
of our relationship.
...at the Hodgeman Hotel...
I, I want you to know that,
what I said today during the ceremony...
Oh, and I meant every single word of it.
I love you.
With everything in me.
But what I said doesn't apply to us.
I can't be with you.
I can't marry you.
Yes, you can.
Yes, you can
because that's what both of us want.
You know, things can be different.
I could be different.
And I'm promising you,
I'm swearing to you,
there will be no more lies.
You know, no matter how much you love me,
there's always gonna be a part of you
that defaults to the man
who was on the island...
...alone.
Who came back to save the city...
And sooner than we both think,
you're going to be stuck in a situation
where you have to make a decision
that requires you
to hide things from me again.
-See, you can't know that...
-I do know that.
And you know that.
That's this life.
I...
-(SIGHS)
-I'm sorry.
(INHALES SHARPLY)
You know, five months ago,
I convinced you that we could have it all.
We could come here to this job
and have each other,
I was wrong.
And then I thought we could just go back
to the way things were,
before we left for Ivy Town.
But God, that was as crazy as Cupid is.
(SNIFFLES)
So what does that mean?
It means that it is, um...
(BEEPING)
-too hard to be here with you
-(WHIRRS)
every night and not be with you.
That's not fair to either of us.
You told me how you worked
some tech magic to return all the money
that Adam Hunt swindled out of people.
You, you don't need me. You'll be fine.
You don't give up.
You know, that's what makes you a hero.
But there's no fixing this.
We have to let each other go.
I want you to keep it
for good this time, please.
I don't wanna let you go.
But I'm already gone.
(PRISON DOOR OPENS)