MY NAME IS OLIVER QUEEN.
AFTER 6 MONTHS IN HELL,
I HAVE BEEN RELEASED
FROM PRISON
AND RETURNED HOME
WITH ONLY ONE GOAL...
TO SAVE MY CITY,
BUT THINGS HAVE CHANGED.
INSTEAD OF OPERATING
OUTSIDE THE LAW,
I AM NOW WORKING
ALONGSIDE THE POLICE.
I AM NO LONGER INMATE 4587.
I AM ONCE MORE
THE GREEN ARROW.
PREVIOUSLY ON "ARROW"...
WORKING WITH THE SCPD...
THAT'S WHAT'S BEST
FOR THIS CITY.
THE WHOLE CITY WILL BE
WATCHING YOU,
HOLDING YOU TO
THE HIGHEST STANDARD.
DAD, PLEASE.
DON'T LEAVE.
EMIKO: DANTE TOOK
ME UNDER HIS WING,
AND HE TRAINED ME.
I KEPT HOLDING OUT,
THINKING
ONE DAY YOU'D BECOME
THE FATHER I DESERVED.
IT'S NEVER GONNA
HAPPEN, IS IT?
ROBERT: IS THERE
SOMETHING ELSE YOU'D
LIKE TO TALK TO ME ABOUT?
NO. HAVE
A GOOD TRIP.
WHEN EMIKO REALIZES
THAT DANTE HAS BEEN
MANIPULATING HER,
IT WILL DRIVE
A WEDGE BETWEEN HER
AND THE NINTH CIRCLE.
ROT IN HELL.
THE NINTH CIRCLE
GOT AWAY
WITH
A VERY DANGEROUS
BIOLOGICAL WEAPON...
THE CYGNUS X-1.
REPORTER: I HAVE JUST RECEIVED
CONFIRMATION
OF TWO FATALITIES HERE AT THE
HUDOLIN MCGUIRE METRO STATION.
SCPD HAVE CORDONED OFF THE AREA,
BUT THE COMMUNITY IS
VERY CONCERNED.
RUMORS ARE ALREADY FLYING AS
TO WHO MIGHT BE RESPONSIBLE.
REPORTER: CAPTAIN DRAKE.
DINAH: HOW'S IT LOOK?
YOU NEED TO SEE
THIS FOR YOURSELF.
HEY, KEEP THOSE DAMN
REPORTERS BACK.
[SIREN]
THIS IS WHERE
WE FOUND THEM.
OH, MY GOD.
WE'LL HAVE TO WAIT
FOR THE OFFICIAL
M.E. REPORT,
BUT IT SEEMS
OBVIOUS...
BLUNT FORCE TRAUMA.
LOOKS LIKE THEY GOT OFF
A FEW ROUNDS
BEFORE THEY WENT DOWN.
DID THEY HIT ANYTHING?
NOTHING ALIVE.
WHERE ARE THE SUSPECTS?
WE'VE GOT TWO DEAD GUARDS
AND ONE HELL OF A MESS.
YOUR TEAM WAS ON-SITE.
I THINK YOU BETTER
START TALKING.
THIS IS...THIS
WHOLE THING
IS RIDICULOUS.
THE REAL DANGER
IS STILL
OUT THERE.
I DON'T THINK YOU GET TO
DECIDE THE REAL DANGER,
MR. QUEEN.
WE WENT TO THE
SUBWAY PLATFORM
TO STOP
A TERRORIST
ATTACK,
WHICH WE DID,
BUT THE PEOPLE
THAT WE WERE
AFTER
ARE STILL ON
THE LOOSE.
WELL, LUCKILY WE HAVE
HALF THE DEPARTMENT
OUT THERE RIGHT NOW
FOLLOWING THE SAME LEAD.
DO YOU THINK THAT THESE ARE
AVERAGE STREET THUGS,
DINAH?
THESE ARE TERRORISTS
THAT TRIED TO RELEASE
A BIOLOGICAL AGENT
IN STAR CITY.
THOUSANDS OF PEOPLE
COULD HAVE DIED.
TWO PEOPLE DID DIE.
WE FOUND TWO EMERALD ARROWS
AT THE SCENE.
THE NEW GREEN ARROW.
WHY DON'T YOU TELL ME
ABOUT HER INVOLVEMENT
AT THE SUBWAY TONIGHT?
[EXHALES]
SHE WAS THERE.
SHE? HOW DO YOU KNOW THAT?
I THINK IT'S TIME WE
TELL PEOPLE THE TRUTH.
THE NEW GREEN ARROW
IS MY HALF-SISTER.
HER NAME IS
EMIKO ADACHI.
DINAH: SHE BELONGS TO
A TERRORIST ORGANIZATION
CALLED THE NINTH CIRCLE.
THE VIGILANTES HAVE BEEN
TRACKING HER
FOR A FEW WEEKS NOW.
WHY DIDN'T YOU INFORM
THE SCPD?
BECAUSE THE NINTH CIRCLE
IS JUST A LITTLE BIT
BEYOND THE SCPD,
OFFICER.
THE SCPD-VIGILANTE
PARTNERSHIP WORKS BEST
WHEN WE OPERATE AS
A COVERT UNIT.
DOESN'T SEEM SO
IN THIS CASE.
WELL, I'M USUALLY KEPT
AWARE OF WHAT'S GOING ON,
BUT I DID NOT
KNOW ABOUT THIS.
CARE TO EXPLAIN WHY?
THINGS STARTED MOVING
PRETTY QUICKLY
AFTER YOU TOLD US
ABOUT DANTE.
FELICITY: OH, THANK GOD.
PLEASE TELL ME THE NEWS
THAT YOU ARE BRINGING
IS ABOUT EMIKO AND HER
NINTH CIRCLE BUDDIES
BECAUSE I HAVE HAD
NO LUCK
WITH MY TYPITY-TYPE
FINDING ANYTHING THING.
OH, WELL, YOU'RE
IN LUCK NOW.
DANTE, NOT SO MUCH.
A COUPLE SCPD BEAT COPS
FOUND HIS BODY THIS MORNING.
LET ME GUESS, AND NOT
FROM NATURAL CAUSES.
NOT UNLESS YOU CALL
3 ARROWS
AND A KNIFE
TO THE CHEST NATURAL.
JOHN: THIS WAS AFTER
YOU TOLD EMIKO
THAT DANTE KILLED
HER MOTHER.
CAN'T BE A COINCIDENCE.
NO. SHE WENT AHEAD
AND KILLED
THE ONLY
FATHER FIGURE
SHE HAD LEFT.
FELICITY: RIGHT.
SO THAT'S A "NO"
ON THE EVIL SISTER
REDEEMING HERSELF
THEN.
JOHN: OK, SO WE HAVE
TO STOP EMIKO FROM USING
THIS BIO-WEAPON THAT SHE
STOLE FROM THE D.I.A.
RENE: THE TERRIFYING
BACTERIA THAT EATS
THROUGH EVERYTHING?
YEAH, LET'S KEEP
THAT CONTAINED.
OK, SO THE BAD
NEWS IS THAT
I HAVEN'T
BEEN ABLE TO FIND
THE BIO-WEAPON,
BUT THE GOOD NEWS IS
THAT THE NINTH CIRCLE
WON'T BE ABLE TO EITHER
UNLESS THEY GET
A DISSEMINATION DEVICE,
A.K.A. A THERMAL FOGGER.
AND, YES, I CHECKED.
THE ONLY PLACE
TO GET ONE
IS AERODYNE INITIATIVES.
DIGG, LET'S GET THERE
-AND HELP THEM PROTECT IT.
-OK.
DINAH: I'LL FOLLOW UP
WITH THE DETECTIVE,
SEE IF I CAN GET SOME MORE
CLUES OFF DANTE'S BODY.
OK.
AND I'LL HANG BACK
WITH FELICITY
AND HELP HER WITH
THE TYPEY-TYPE.
-THAT'S OK.
-MORAL SUPPORT.
OK.
MAN: MR. QUEEN,
MR. DIGGLE,
IT'S A PLEASURE
TO FINALLY MEET
THE FAMOUS GREEN ARROW
AND SPARTAN.
I ALWAYS BELIEVED IN
VIGILANTES IN THE CITY.
WELL, LOVE
TO HEAR IT.
WISH WE WERE
MEETING UNDER BETTER
CIRCUMSTANCES.
JOHN: WE HAVE REASON
TO BELIEVE
THAT AN ASSET OF YOURS
HAS BEEN TARGETED
BY AN INTERNATIONAL
TERRORIST THREAT.
WELL, THAT'S QUITE
AN ACCUSATION,
BUT I CAN ASSURE YOU
OUR SECURITY'S
TOP OF THE LINE.
OLIVER: WITH
ALL DUE RESPECT,
THIS ORGANIZATION IS
FAR MORE POWERFUL
THAN ANY
PRIVATE COMPANY
COULD POSSIBLY
CONTEND WITH.
AND WITH ALL DUE
RESPECT TO YOU,
WE HIRED OVER A DOZEN
OF THE WORLD'S BEST
HACKERS AND THIEVES
TO TRY TO BREAK INTO
OUR FACILITY.
NONE MADE IT PAST
THE FRONT ENTRANCE.
UH, MR. TOTH,
WE'RE SIMPLY OFFERING
TO HELP YOU.
WHAT POSSIBLE REASON
COULD YOU HAVE
FOR TURNING US DOWN?
WELL, I APPRECIATE
YOUR CONCERN,
BUT WE'VE GOT THIS COVERED.
DINAH: IT SEEMS ODD THAT
HE TURNED YOU DOWN.
WE AGREED,
SO WE HAD FELICITY
DO A DEEP DIVE
INTO TOTH'S
FINANCIAL RECORDS.
TURNS OUT HE WAS
GETTING
SOME VERY LARGE
DEPOSITS.
SO HE WAS
ON THE TAKE...
-FROM THE NINTH CIRCLE.
-MM-HMM.
AND WHY THE HELL
DIDN'T YOU TELL ME?
BECAUSE WE COULDN'T
CONFIRM IT
UNTIL LATER, DINAH.
WELL, I WANT TO BELIEVE
YOU, OLIVER,
BUT YOU'VE GOT TO ADMIT,
THIS LOOKS REALLY BAD.
I MEAN, WE GOT ARROWS
AT THE CRIME SCENE.
WE'VE GOT A VERY
INCRIMINATING DISTRESS CALL
FROM ONE OF THE VICTIMS,
AND YOU WERE THERE.
NOT TO MENTION
THE MISSING
SECURITY FOOTAGE.
OK. DINAH,
YOU KNOW ME, ALL RIGHT?
YOU KNOW THAT I DIDN'T
KILL THOSE PEOPLE.
YOU'VE KILLED
BEFORE...
HUH...
MANY TIMES.
FIVE MONTHS AGO,
YOU WERE SITTING
IN A CELL
IN SLABSIDE.
YOU'RE NOT
EXACTLY INNOCENT.
ENJOYING YOURSELF?
YOU HAVING A GOOD TIME?
YOU HAVE HAD IT
OUT FOR ME
SINCE THE MOMENT THAT
I WAS DEPUTIZED BY THE SCPD.
DINAH: YOU KNOW,
THOSE GUARDS WERE NOT
JUST KILLED, OLIVER.
THEY WERE SAVAGELY
BEATEN TO DEATH.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND
HOW BAD THIS LOOKS
FOR THE DEPARTMENT?
YES, I DO,
BUT I DIDN'T DO IT.
-THEN WHO DID?
-I DON'T KNOW.
SO IT
COULD HAVE BEEN
ONE OF THE MEMBERS
OF YOUR TEAM.
MY TEAM...
STOPPED
A TERRORIST ATTACK.
DINAH: EXCEPT IT
WASN'T JUST YOUR TEAM
WHO WAS THERE, WAS IT?
THERE WAS
SOMEBODY ELSE THERE,
SOMEBODY BESIDES
MR. DIGGLE
AND MS. SMOAK
AND MR. RAMIREZ.
YES, THERE WAS.
OLIVER: WE THOUGHT
THE NINTH CIRCLE
WAS GONNA WIPE OUT
STAR CITY.
SO I MADE A CALL.
YOU DO UNDERSTAND WHAT
ACCOMPLICE TO
MURDER MEANS, RIGHT?
YOU CAN'T BE SERIOUS.
TONIGHT'S SECURITY FOOTAGE
FROM HUDOLIN MCGUIRE
SUBWAY STATION
MYSTERIOUSLY DISAPPEARED.
YOU WOULDN'T HAPPEN
TO KNOW ANYTHING ABOUT
THAT, WOULD YOU?
NOPE. NOTHING, ZILCH, NADA.
SHE'S COVERING FOR
HER HUSBAND.
-OH, COME...
-THAT CERTAINLY IS CONVENIENT.
AND WHEN EXACTLY
WERE YOU
PLANNING
ON TELLING ME
ABOUT ROY HARPER'S
INVOLVEMENT?
HONESTLY?
AFTER WE SAVED STAR CITY FROM
THE NINTH CIRCLE'S ATTACK.
WE KNOW HOW YOU GUYS FEEL
ABOUT "THE UNSANCTIONED."
LET'S GET REAL.
EMIKO AND THE NINTH CIRCLE
KNOW OUR FACES.
ROY WAS OUR ACE IN THE HOLE.
SO YOU RISKED YOUR
NEW RELATIONSHIP
WITH THE SCPD
BY TEAMING UP WITH
A CRIMINAL.
FORMER CRIMINAL.
ROY LEFT THE CITY
4 YEARS AGO,
AND HE'S BEEN
ON THE STRAIGHT
AND NARROW EVER SINCE.
ARE YOU SURE
ABOUT THAT?
YES, I'M SURE ABOUT THAT.
BECAUSE WE TRACED
HARPER'S WHEREABOUTS
AFTER HE FAKED HIS
DEATH IN PRISON
TO GET OLIVER QUEEN
OFF THE HOOK,
AND HIS TRAIL
WENT COLD IN MARCH
OF LAST YEAR.
OH. YOU MEAN WHEN
RICARDO DIAZ KIDNAPPED ROY
TO TURN HIM AGAINST OLIVER?
YOU MIGHT HAVE FORGOTTEN
ABOUT THAT SINCE YOU
WEREN'T EXACTLY ON
SPEAKING TERMS WITH
OLIVER AND I AT THE TIME.
IT STILL DOESN'T EXPLAIN
WHERE HE WENT AFTER
GETTING FREED FROM DIAZ.
I'M SURE THE KIDNAPPING
WAS EXTREMELY TRAUMATIC.
HE PROBABLY JUST WENT
TO GO GET SOME R&amp;R...
SOME ROY RELAXATION.
NOT FUNNY. I SEE THAT NOW.
OH. SO THIS IS WHAT
LEGIT LOOKS LIKE.
JOHN: THAT'S RIGHT.
A BADGE AND A BUNKER.
NEVER THOUGHT I'D
SEE THE DAY.
JOHN: GOOD SEEING YOU.
I'M GLAD YOU'RE FINALLY
SEEING IT IN PERSON AGAIN.
-OOH!
-OH!
OH, I MISSED YOU
SO MUCH.
SORRY. I'M JUST A LITTLE
OVERLY EMOTIONAL THESE DAYS.
I MEAN, NOT OVERLY
EMOTIONAL,
NOT, LIKE, HEIGHTENED
OR ANYTHING.
BECAUSE WHY WOULD THAT BE?
MY HORMONES
ARE TOTALLY IN CHECK,
LIKE THEY ALWAYS HAVE BEEN.
NERVES OF STEEL.
YOU KNOW ME. I'M COOL.
OK.
THE ARSENAL. NICE
TO FINALLY MEET YOU.
YOU, TOO. THANKS
FOR KEEPING WATCH.
THE GLADES CAN USE
AS MANY HEROES
AS IT CAN GET.
WELCOME BACK.
ALL RIGHT.
HOW'S THEA?
SHE'S GOOD.
YEAH, I THINK SHE'S
FINALLY FOUND HER PASSION.
YOU'D BE REALLY
PROUD OF HER.
LAST I SPOKE WITH HER,
SHE SAYS
YOU WERE ZEROING IN ON
THE REMAINING LAZARUS PITS.
YEAH, WE FOUND TWO
ALREADY,
-WHICH WE DESTROYED.
-MM-HMM.
WE WERE CHECKING
THE REST WHEN WE
GOT YOUR CALL.
SPEAKING OF WHICH,
WHY'D YOU ASK ME
TO COME HERE
INSTEAD OF THEA?
STAR CITY'S NEW TERRORIST
IS OLIVER'S NEW SISTER.
WHAT?
YEAH.
DON'T YOU THINK THEA
WOULD WANT TO KNOW THAT?
-YEAH.
-YES.
AND I HAVE EVERY INTENTION
OF TELLING HER.
I JUST...THIS WOMAN'S
NAME IS EMIKO,
AND WE WANTED TO GET
HER INTO CUSTODY
BEFORE WE TOLD HER.
I FEEL LIKE SHE'S
FINALLY FREE OF HER
LIFE IN STAR CITY,
AND I...I DON'T WANT
TO HURT HER AGAIN
WITH A WOUND INFLICTED
ON OUR FAMILY
BY OUR FATHER.
FELICITY, VOICE-OVER:
ROY HAD BEEN TRAVELING THE WORLD
DOING SOME EXTREMELY NORMAL
SIGHTSEEING.
APPARENTLY HE WAS TOO BUSY
TO EVEN SEND A POSTCARD.
THEN WHY DID YOU
CALL HIM IN?
BECAUSE OF
THE THERMAL FOGGER.
THE WHAT?
THE SCARY BIO-WEAPON THAT
THE BAD GUYS NEEDED
TO SPREAD THE BACTERIA
THROUGH THE SUBWAY'S
HVAC SYSTEM.
THE DEVICE FOUND
ON THE SCENE.
AT THE SCENE, YES.
LOOK,
WE THOUGHT IT WAS
WEIRD THAT
THE CEO OF AERODYNE
WASN'T GOING TO LET
US PROTECT IT FROM
THE NINTH CIRCLE,
SO WE DID
SOME DIGGING.
AND FOUND THAT JASON TOTH
WAS DIRTY. OLIVER TOLD US.
WE KNEW GOOD OLD JASON
WOULD BE LOOKING FOR
MEMBERS OF THE TGA,
AND WE NEEDED SOMEONE
WITH A VIGILANTE-LIKE
SET OF SKILLS.
VOILA. ROY HARPER.
THE FACILITIES AT
AERODYNE ARE NO JOKE,
AND ROY IS INCREDIBLE
AT PARKOUR.
I'M IN.
OLIVER: REMEMBER, ROY,
THE FLOOR IS ARMED.
FELICITY: IF YOU TOUCH
ANYTHING...
AND I MEAN ANYTHING...
IT IS PARTY TIME
AT AERODYNE,
AND NOT IN A GOOD WAY.
ROY: IS THERE ANYTHING
I CAN TOUCH?
WALLS AND CEILINGS
ARE FAIR GAME.
ANYTHING
THAT'S NOT THE FLOOR.
SO FAR, SO GOOD.
RENE: THE CONTROL PANEL'S ON
THE OTHER SIDE OF THE FAN.
I GOT TO GET HIGHER.
I SEE IT.
YOU HIT METAL,
IT'S OVER. SHOT
HAS TO BE PERFECT.
MARGIN OF ERROR...0.08,
BUT WHO'S COUNTING?
YOUR TARGET IS
THE RED BUTTON...
SECOND FROM THE LEFT.
ROY:
I DON'T HAVE A SHOT...
BUT I WILL.
[CIRCUIT BREAKER WHISTLING]
FELICITY, VOICE-OVER:
JUST LIKE THAT, PIECE OF CAKE.
OH, WHICH ACTUALLY SOUNDS
SO GOOD RIGHT NOW.
DO YOU GUYS HAVE
ANY CAKE OR CUPCAKES
OR ANYTHING WITH, LIKE,
A CAKE-LIKE...
FELICITY, TELL US
WHAT HAPPENED, PLEASE.
ROY SQUEEZED HIS WAY
THROUGH THE BLADES,
AND THEN AFTER THAT,
IT WAS EASY
TO MAKE HIS WAY INTO
THE R&amp;D VAULT. BOOM.
HEADS UP. WE'RE
LATE TO THE PARTY.
OLIVER: THAT WAS OUR
ONLY WAY IN.
NOT THE ONLY WAY.
PLEASURE DOING BUSINESS
WITH YOU, MR. TOTH.
OH, YOUR NEW SISTER...
NOT A FAN.
[CLANG]
TAKE CARE OF HIM.
MOVE! MOVE!
WHO THE HELL ARE YOU?
YOUR NEW WORST NIGHTMARE.
HMM.
SEE YOUSE LADS.
[ROY BREATHING HEAVILY]
ROY?
WE LOST THE BIO-WEAPON.
SO LET ME
GET THIS STRAIGHT.
IF YOUR PLAN HAD WORKED,
ROY WOULD HAVE
SUCCESSFULLY STOLEN
A VERY DANGEROUS
PIECE OF TECH.
IN OTHER WORDS, COMMITTED
A FELONY.
WELL, TECHNICALLY,
ROY WAS THERE TO STOP
THE NINTH CIRCLE FROM
DOING WHAT THEY DID,
WHICH WAS STEAL THE DEVICE,
SO TECHNICALLY, ROY
DIDN'T DO ANYTHING.
NO HARM, NO FOUL.
COULD I MAYBE GET A PIZZA?
JUST A PERSONAL SIZE
IS FINE.
NO. I THINK YOU'VE ABUSED
YOUR FOOD PRIVILEGES
ENOUGH FOR TODAY.
-OK.
-TELL ME WHAT HAPPENED.
WE STOPPED THE NINTH CIRCLE
FROM TERRORIZING THE CITY.
END-STOP.
AND THE TWO
FATALITIES.
THAT WASN'T OUR FAULT.
DINAH:
THEN TELL ME WHAT YOU KNOW.
WE KNEW THAT
THE NINTH CIRCLE
WANTED TO MAXIMIZE
THE BIO-WEAPON'S IMPACT.
THERE WERE TWO POSSIBLE
LOCATIONS TO DO THAT...
THE VENTILATION ROOM
AND THE VENTILATION SHAFT.
OLIVER WENT TO ONE, JOHN
AND RENE WENT TO THE OTHER.
ROY AND I WENT
TO THE SWITCH ROOM.
FELICITY: OH, WOW!
THIS THING IS A FOSSIL,
AND NOT IN
A FUN ICE AGE WAY.
CAN YOU SHUT IT DOWN?
WELL, ONCE I SHUT DOWN
THE VENTILATION PATH,
WE SHOULD BE ABLE
TO MINIMIZE THE DAMAGE.
DINAH, VOICE-OVER: DID
YOU HAVE ANY INDICATION
THOSE GUARDS
WERE STILL ON-SITE?
NO. I DIDN'T SEE THOSE
GUARDS OR ANY GUARDS.
[LOUD THUD]
SOUNDS LIKE WE'RE
NOT ALONE. YOU GOT EYES?
ALL I GOT IS
TWO TRANSIT GUARDS
IN THE CORRIDOR.
IF THEY'RE NINTH CIRCLE,
YOU CAN'T LET THEM
IN HERE.
WELL, I CAN'T JUST
LEAVE YOU HERE.
I'LL BE FINE.
I'LL BE FINE. GO.
I STAYED IN THAT ROOM
UNTIL OLIVER GAVE ME
THE GO-AHEAD.
AND WHAT ABOUT ROY?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
CAN YOU ACCOUNT FOR
HIS WHEREABOUTS
BETWEEN THE TIME
HE LEFT YOU
AND THE TIME THOSE
GUARDS WERE KILLED?
GUYS, THE VENTS ARE
SHUT DOWN.
PLEASE TELL ME THAT
YOU HAVE THE DEVICE.
[GUNSHOTS]
HE WAS KEEPING ME SAFE.
THAT WASN'T
THE QUESTION.
FELICITY, DO YOU KNOW
WHERE ROY WAS
WHEN THOSE GUARDS
WERE KILLED?
NO, I DON'T.
ROY HARPER, YOU ARE
A HARD MAN TO TRACK DOWN.
I'VE BEEN
TRAVELING.
SO WE'VE HEARD.
WHEREABOUTS EXACTLY?
THE WORLD.
DON'T MAKE THIS HARDER
THAN IT NEEDS TO BE.
YOU'VE GOT QUITE
THE RAP SHEET, MR. HARPER.
B&amp;E, GRAND THEFT AUTO...
AGGRAVATED ASSAULT.
SO IS THAT WHY YOU CAME
BACK TO STAR CITY, ROY,
TO STEAL A DEVICE
FROM AERODYNE?
I CAME BACK TO HELP
PREVENT EMIKO
FROM STEALING IT.
SHE'S THE ONE
YOU GUYS SHOULD BE
GOING AFTER.
WE WILL.
BUT FIRST, WHY DON'T YOU
TELL US WHAT HAPPENED
AFTER YOU FAILED
TO STOP HER?
I WENT BACK TO THE BUNKER
TO FIGURE OUT A NEW PLAN.
ACCORDING TO FELICITY,
ALL EMIKO HAD TO DO WAS
FILL THAT DEVICE
WITH SOME SORT OF
KILLER BACTERIA
AND STAR CITY WOULD'VE
TURNED INTO A REAL-LIFE
HORROR MOVIE.
CYGNUS X-1.
YEAH. SO SHE RAN SOME
SORT OF ALGORITHM
AND CAME UP WITH A FEW
POSSIBLE PLACES.
BINGSLEY: AND THAT
EVENTUALLY LED YOU
TO THE SUBWAY.
CUT TO THE CHASE.
WHAT HAPPENED WHEN
YOU GOT THERE?
SPECIFICALLY, WHAT
HAPPENED AFTER YOU
LEFT FELICITY?
I DIDN'T WANT TO LEAVE HER,
BUT SHE INSISTED.
WE THOUGHT THE NINTH CIRCLE
MIGHT HAVE SHOWED UP.
ROY, VOICE-OVER:
TURNS OUT WE WERE RIGHT.
THOSE GUYS IN THE HOODS
JUMPED ME.
AFTER I TOOK OUT
THE FIRST ONE, THEY JUST...
JUST KEPT COMING.
I TRIED TO FIGHT BACK, BUT THERE
WERE JUST TOO MANY OF THEM.
THE LAST THING
I REMEMBER IS
I WAS TAKING A MACE
TO THE FACE
BEFORE EVERYTHING
WENT BLACK.
AND WHEN I CAME TO,
YOU ALL WERE
ON THE SCENE,
AND THE GUARDS, THEY
WERE ALREADY DEAD.
SO YOU HAVE
ABSOLUTELY NO IDEA
WHO MAY HAVE KILLED THEM.
IT'S RATHER CONVENIENT,
DON'T YOU THINK?
YOU BEING UNCONSCIOUS AT
THE SAME TIME
TWO MEN ARE
BRUTALLY MURDERED?
YOU THINK I DID IT?
WHOSE SIDE
ARE YOU ON?
I AM ON THE ONLY SIDE
THAT MATTERS...THE TRUTH.
NOW, WHY DON'T YOU
STOP WASTING MY TIME
AND TELL ME
WHAT REALLY HAPPENED?
JOHN: I TOLD YOU,
ROY WAS UNCONSCIOUS
WHEN I FOUND HIM,
AND THAT WAS BEFORE
THE GUARDS FIRED
THEIR SIDEARMS.
SO YOU DON'T THINK
HE KILLED THEM.
I JUST DON'T SEE
HOW HE COULD HAVE.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO
PROTECT HIM, JOHN.
DINAH, I'M NOT.
RIGHT, RIGHT.
BUT THAT IS WHAT
YOU DO, ISN'T IT?
YOU ALWAYS PUT
OTHER PEOPLE'S LIVES
BEFORE YOUR OWN.
AT SOME POINT YOU
MIGHT DISCOVER
NOT EVERYBODY'S
WORTH IT.
LOOK, YOU DON'T KNOW
ROY HARPER THE WAY I DO.
HE'S HAD HIS TROUBLES.
BUT DEEP INSIDE, HE'S
A VERY GOOD MAN.
WELL, YOU'RE VERY QUICK
TO DEFEND ROY.
WHAT ABOUT YOURSELF?
WHY? ARE YOU ASKING ME
IF I KILLED THOSE GUARDS?
IT CERTAINLY
DOESN'T HELP
THAT YOU HAVE BLOOD
ON YOUR SLEEVE.
WALK US THROUGH
WHAT HAPPENED
AFTER YOU ARRIVED.
WELL, THERE WERE TWO
POSSIBLE DISBURSEMENT SITES.
OLIVER HEADED FOR
THE VENTILATION ROOM.
AND RENE AND I HEADED
FOR THE VENTILATION SHAFT.
AND THAT'S WHEN WE
RAN INTO TROUBLE.
ACCESS SHOULD BE HERE,
AHEAD ON THE RIGHT.
[FOOTSTEPS]
EMIKO.
-I'VE GOT HER.
-RENE!
SHE'S MINE.
GO SECURE THE DEVICE.
SO THAT'S WHEN YOU
AND RENE SPLIT UP.
RENE WAS RIGHT.
THE DEVICE WAS THE PRIORITY.
I WAS HEADED FOR
THE VENTILATION SHAFT,
AND THAT'S WHEN I FOUND
ROY UNCONSCIOUS.
AND THIS WAS BEFORE
THE GUNSHOTS.
THAT'S CORRECT.
[GUNSHOTS]
JOHN, VOICE-OVER:
I RAN TOWARD THE SOURCE
AS FAST AS I COULD,
BUT I WAS TOO LATE.
I CHECKED THEIR PULSE,
BUT THEY WERE
ALREADY DEAD.
THAT'S HOW I GOT BLOOD
ON MY SLEEVE.
WHAT ABOUT
MR. RAMIREZ?
WHERE WAS HE DURING
ALL OF THIS?
[SIGHS]
JOHN?
JOHN, TELL US
WHAT YOU SAW.
WHEN I GOT TO THE BODIES...
THAT'S WHEN I FOUND RENE.
RENE?
WHAT HAPPENED
TO YOUR HAND, RENE?
I CUT IT.
WELL,
THAT'S OBVIOUS.
WAS IT AROUND THE SAME TIME
YOU LOST YOUR GLOVE?
WHAT ARE YOU
GETTING AT, D.?
YOU KNOW, I'VE SEEN
PLENTY OF PERPS
CHANGE THEIR TUNE
THE LONGER THEY
SIT IN HERE.
THE TRUTH HAS A WAY
OF COMING OUT.
THIS ISN'T MY FIRST TIME
BEING FALSELY ACCUSED
OF A CRIME...
SIR.
TWO MEN ARE DEAD, RENE.
NOW, WE KNOW TEAM ARROW
WAS ON-SITE
AS WELL AS EMIKO, WHICH
MEANS OUR TWO MAIN SUSPECTS
ARE EITHER HER OR...
ME?
I DIDN'T SAY THAT.
WELL, THAT'S WHAT YOU
WERE THINKING,
'CAUSE YOU'VE BEEN
LOOKING FOR ANY EXCUSE
NOT TO TRUST ME
THIS WHOLE YEAR.
THAT'S BECAUSE
YOU HAVE GIVEN ME
EVERY REASON NOT TO.
HOW MANY TIMES HAVE I
WARNED YOU ABOUT EMIKO?
I TOLD YOU SHE WASN'T
TRUSTWORTHY.
YOU REFUSED TO LISTEN.
WELL, NOW SHE ENDS UP
ON THE SCENE
OF AN ATTEMPTED
TERRORIST ATTACK
AND A DOUBLE HOMICIDE,
AND YOU WERE THERE, TOO.
AND YOU WHAT? YOU
THINK I HELPED HER?
I JUST WANT THE TRUTH, RENE.
TELL ME WHAT YOU WERE DOING
BEFORE THAT MISSION TONIGHT.
RENE: WE MANAGED
TO GET THE INFO
ON THE NINTH CIRCLE'S
TARGET
THANKS TO FELICITY'S
ALGORITHM.
SHE TRACED
THE CHEMICAL SIGNATURE
OF THE BIO-WEAPON
TO THE SUBWAY STATION.
AND THAT'S WHEN YOU
HEADED OFF.
YEAH. STRAIGHT AWAY.
YOU GOOD WITH ALL THIS?
I'LL BE BETTER
ONCE WE GET TO
THE SUBWAY AND STOP HER.
I KNOW THAT IT'S
GOING TO BE TOUGH
GOING UP AGAINST EMIKO.
YOU GUYS GOT
REALLY CLOSE, RENE.
IF YOU'RE GONNA TRY
AND GIVE ME A PEP TALK,
SAVE IT. I'M GOOD.
I DON'T WANT TO GIVE YOU
A PEP TALK.
I WANT TO MAKE
SURE THAT
IF YOU'RE GOING
OUT ON A MISSION,
YOU'RE DOING IT
WITH A CLEAR HEAD.
WHEN I FIRST MET EMIKO,
AVENGING
HER MOTHER'S DEATH
AND HELPING THE GLADES
WERE THE ONLY THINGS
THAT MATTERED TO HER.
RIGHT, EXCEPT SHE
WAS LYING.
THEN WHY DID SHE KILL
DANTE?
WHY'D SHE DO IT?
I MEAN, SHE TURNED ON
A MEMBER OF THE NINTH CIRCLE
FOR HER MOTHER.
THAT TELLS ME THAT
FAMILY
MEANS MORE TO HER.
FINE. IT DOESN'T CHANGE
THE FACT THAT SHE
COULD POTENTIALLY
KILL THOUSANDS...
THOUSANDS OF PEOPLE.
I KNOW, I KNOW, BUT SHE'S
STILL YOUR SISTER, MAN.
DOESN'T ANY PART OF YOU
THINK THAT MAYBE SHE'S
DOING ALL OF THIS
BECAUSE OF WHAT YOUR
FATHER DID TO HER,
THAT IF NOT
FOR HER UPBRINGING,
SHE'D BE FIGHTING WITH US
INSTEAD OF AGAINST US?
A BIG PART OF ME
THINKS ABOUT THAT...
ALL THE TIME.
AT A CERTAIN POINT,
RENE,
PEOPLE NEED TO TAKE
RESPONSIBILITY
FOR THEIR ACTIONS.
EMIKO MADE HER CHOICE.
I'VE MADE MINE.
YOU NEED TO MAKE YOURS.
THERE'S SOMETHING
I'M NOT LIKING ABOUT
YOUR STORY, RENE.
THE PART WHERE WE
SAVE THE CITY?
THE PART YOU'RE NOT
TELLING US.
EVERYTHING I TOLD YOU
TONIGHT IS THE TRUTH.
THEN WHY DID WE FIND
YOUR FINGERPRINTS
ON THE MURDER WEAPON.
WHAT WERE YOU
DOING WITH THAT
PIPE, RENE?
I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING.
THAT'S GETTING
HARDER AND HARDER
TO BELIEVE.
JOHN AND I SPLIT UP.
HE WENT AFTER THE BOMB.
I WENT AFTER EMIKO.
AND DID YOU
CATCH UP TO HER?
NO.
EMIKO, IT'S NOT
TOO LATE.
LET ME HELP YOU.
I DON'T NEED YOUR HELP.
I SPARED YOU ONCE.
THIS TIME, I WON'T
BE SO GENEROUS.
WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS?!
BECAUSE THE QUEENS TOOK
EVERYTHING FROM ME.
NOW IT'S MY TURN TO
TAKE EVERYTHING FROM THEM.
THIS ISN'T YOU.
YOU CARE ABOUT
THE GLADES.
YOU'RE DRESSED AS
THE NEW GREEN ARROW,
AND YOU KILLED
DANTE.
AND THAT PROVES WHAT
EXACTLY?
THAT FINDING YOUR
MOTHER'S KILLER MEANS
MORE TO YOU
THAN THE NINTH CIRCLE.
WHY ELSE WOULD YOU
RISK MURDERING
THEIR LEADER?
YOU REALLY DON'T GET IT.
DANTE WASN'T THEIR LEADER.
I AM.
YOUR MOTHER WOULD HATE
WHAT YOU'VE BECOME.
AGH!
RENE, VOICE-OVER: I WAS STILL
SEARCHING FOR EMIKO
WHEN I HEARD
THE GUNSHOTS.
[GUNSHOTS]
BINGSLEY: WHERE WERE
YOU EXACTLY?
SOME RANDOM CORRIDOR.
THE GUNSHOTS WERE CLOSE.
I FOLLOWED THE SOUND, WHICH
LED ME TO THE PLATFORM.
YOU KNOW WE
HAVE A WITNESS
WHO PINS YOU AS
THE FIRST PERSON
ON THE SCENE.
YEAH. JOHN. HE SHOWED UP...
HE SHOWED UP SECONDS
AFTER I DID.
WHAT ARE YOU NOT
TELLING US, RENE?
SOMEONE ELSE GOT TO
THE PLATFORM BEFORE I DID.
DINAH: AND WHO WAS IT?
IT WAS OLIVER.
BRING BACK MR. QUEEN.
YOU DIDN'T TELL US
THE TRUTH.
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
YOUR FRIEND RAMIREZ SAYS HE
FOUND YOU NEAR THE BODIES.
OLIVER: I HAVE NO MORE
WAYS TO TELL YOU
I DIDN'T KILL
THOSE GUARDS.
BINGSLEY: LET ME TELL YOU
WHAT I THINK.
I THINK YOU AND YOUR TEAM
WERE THERE
TO STOP
THE TERRORIST ATTACK.
I EVEN THINK YOU DID.
BUT ONE OF THE BAD GUYS
GOT AWAY;
YOU WENT AFTER THEM;
AND TRANSIT GUARDS
ROSENBERG AND KIM
GOT IN YOUR WAY.
I DIDN'T KILL
THOSE GUARDS.
OK, THEN WHO DID, OLIVER?
BECAUSE I REALLY
WANT TO HELP YOU,
BUT I CAN'T DO THAT UNLESS
YOU'RE HONEST WITH US.
SO LET'S TRY THIS AGAIN.
TELL ME WHAT WENT ON IN
THAT SUBWAY,
AND I WANT THE TRUTH
THIS TIME.
OLIVER, VOICE-OVER:
AFTER WE SEPARATED,
I WENT TO
THE VENTILATION ROOM.
VIRGIL: COME ON, COME ON,
COME ON, COME ON.
WHOA, WHOA.
CAREFUL, CAREFUL.
ONE WRONG MOVE,
AND WE'LL ALL BE
IN A LOAD OF TROUBLE.
[BEEPS]
AAH!
YOU'RE A REAL PAIN IN
THE ARSE, YOU KNOW THAT?
[MEN GRUNTING]
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLING]
DINAH: THAT'S NOT THE PART
WE'RE INTERESTED IN.
WE APPRECIATE YOU
DISARMING THE DEVICE,
BUT THAT'S NOT
WHY YOU'RE HERE.
OLIVER: THE DEVICE
IS A WEAPON
THAT WAS GONNA KILL
THOUSANDS OF PEOPLE,
AND NOW IT'S IN
SCPD CUSTODY,
THANKS TO US.
WHAT HAPPENED NEXT?
[EXHALES]
I WAS STILL IN
THE VENTILATION ROOM
WHEN I HEARD
THE GUNSHOTS.
[GUNSHOTS]
OLIVER, VOICE-OVER:
THE GUARDS MUST HAVE
GOTTEN OFF A FEW SHOTS.
OH, NO.
BUT WHEN I
GOT THERE...
THE KILLER WAS
STANDING OVER THEM.
THEY WERE GONE.
BLOOD EVERYWHERE.
AND YOU GOT A GOOD LOOK
AT WHO DID IT.
YEAH.
THEN WHO WAS IT?
OLIVER, THEN WHO WAS IT?
IT WAS MY SISTER.
EMIKO KILLED
THOSE GUARDS.
I CAN'T BELIEVE WE'RE
LETTING HIM GO.
OLIVER QUEEN IS
PROTECTING HIS SISTER.
IT MAKES SENSE.
I DON'T KNOW. SOMETHING
DOESN'T FEEL RIGHT.
WE DON'T HAVE
ENOUGH EVIDENCE
TO KEEP THEM HERE.
THEIR STORIES LINE UP.
MAYOR POLLARD AGREES.
SO HOW'S IT LOOK?
POLLARD BOUGHT IT.
YEAH, AS FAR AS THE
SCPD IS CONCERNED,
EMIKO WAS
THE ONE WHO KILLED
THOSE GUARDS.
YOU ALL ARE VERY,
VERY GOOD LIARS.
SO ARE YOU, D.
WE KNOW THAT THIS
WASN'T EASY FOR YOU.
DINAH:
NO, IT WASN'T.
IF ANYBODY
FINDS OUT ABOUT
WHAT WE DID,
OUR PARTNERSHIP
WITH THE SCPD
IS OVER.
AND THE SAME
GOES FOR MY JOB.
WE JUST RISKED
EVERYTHING.
THAT'S WHY WE ALL
HAD TO AGREE.
THIS WAS THE ONLY WAY.
[FOOTSTEPS]
[CLANG]
-I'VE GOT HER.
-RENE.
SHE'S MINE.
SECURE THE DEVICE.
I'LL BE FINE. GO.
[BEEPS]
AAH!
HEY! WHAT THE HELL'S
GOING ON DOWN HERE?
GUARD: VIGILANTE
ATTACK IN PROGRESS,
HUDOLIN MCGUIRE METRO STATION.
[GUNSHOTS]
[THUD]
ROY!
ROY, STOP IT!
LOOK AT ME!
ROY, STOP!
[PIPE ROLLS]
RENE! RENE, DON'T
TOUCH THAT.
[PIPE CLANGS]
THEY'RE DEAD.
WHAT THE HELL HAPPENED HERE?
WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO?
WE HAVE TO PROTECT HIM.
TWO INNOCENT PEOPLE
ARE DEAD,
AND WE'RE COVERING
IT UP.
OLIVER: DINAH, IF SOMEONE
ON THIS TEAM GOES DOWN,
THIS ENTIRE TEAM GOES DOWN.
JOHN: HE'S
ABSOLUTELY RIGHT.
AND IF POLLARD
KNEW THE TRUTH,
WE WOULD BE
SITTING IN LOCKUP
WHILE THE CITY
REHASHES
WHETHER VIGILANTES
ARE A THREAT OR NOT.
FELICITY: WHICH
WOULD FREE EMIKO UP
FOR EVIL PLAN B.
BUT ROY IS NOT
A PART OF THIS TEAM.
HE'S BEEN GONE FOR MONTHS
DOING WHO KNOWS WHAT.
WITH DUE RESPECT, YOU DON'T
KNOW WHAT HE'S BEEN THROUGH.
ROY IS AND ALWAYS WILL BE
AS MUCH A PART OF THIS TEAM
AS THE REST OF US.
DINAH: EXCEPT THE REST
OF US DON'T GO AROUND
KILLING INNOCENT PEOPLE.
JOHN: DINAH, AS HORRIBLE
AS THAT WAS,
LET'S NOT LOSE SIGHT
THAT WE STOPPED
AN ATTACK TONIGHT.
AND WE FRAMED EMIKO
FOR MURDER.
OLIVER: EMIKO'S A MURDERER,
A MURDERER WHO'S THE LEADER
OF THE NINTH CIRCLE.
AND AS LONG AS SHE IS
OUT THERE,
THIS CITY WILL REMAIN
UNDER THREAT.
JOHN: I HOPE WE CAN
ALL AGREE ON THAT.
YES.
MY SEARCH ALGORITHMS
ARE UP AND RUNNING.
IT MIGHT ACTUALLY
BE A GOOD TIME
TO GO ASK ROY
WHAT HAPPENED.
I'M PRETTY SURE
I ALREADY KNOW.
THAT WASN'T MIRAKURU.
NO.
HOW DID IT HAPPEN?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
HOW DID YOU DIE?
HOW DID YOU KNOW?
YOU, THEA, AND NYSSA
LEFT HERE OVER A YEAR AGO
IN SEARCH OF LAZARUS PITS,
AND I HAVE NOT SEEN
BLOODLUST LIKE THAT
SINCE THEA
WAS RESURRECTED BY ONE.
DAMN IT.
TO HELP, I NEED TO
KNOW WHAT HAPPENED.
[SIGHS]
THE THANATOS GUILD
HAD US SURROUNDED.
I TRIED TO GET THEA
TO SAFETY,
BUT I WAS HIT WITH
AN ARROW,
WHICH...WHICH IS IRONIC.
I DON'T REALLY REMEMBER
A LOT AFTER,
EXCEPT FOR...EXCEPT FOR
SEEING NYSSA AND THEA
DESTROY THE PIT.
THE ONE THEY USED
TO BRING YOU BACK.
YEAH.
NYSSA HAD THE LOTUS ELIXIR.
SHE AND THEA THOUGHT
THAT WE COULD CONTROL
THE BLOODLUST, AND WE DID.
UNTIL YOU DIDN'T.
I KEEP TRYING
TO FIGURE OUT WHY.
AND ALL I CAN THINK OF
IS THAT MAYBE
THE MIRAKURU
CHANGED SOMETHING.
YOU KNOW, I NEVER
WOULD'VE COME BACK HERE
IF I WOULD'VE KNOWN WHAT
WAS GONNA HAPPEN.
I NEVER MEANT
TO HURT ANYONE.
I KNOW...
BUT KEEPING THIS
INFORMATION FROM US,
IT JEOPARDIZED
ALL THE THINGS THAT
WE HAVE BEEN WORKING
FOR THIS YEAR.
I NEVER ASKED YOU
TO COVER FOR ME.
I DIDN'T WANT YOU TO.
YOU NEVER HAVE
TO ASK ME.
EVER.
FELICITY: GUYS?
FELICITY
HAS SOMETHING.
I EXPANDED MY SEARCH
PARAMETERS, AND PRESTO.
FACIAL RECOGNITION
PUTS EMIKO
IN AN ABANDONED BUILDING
A FEW MILES OUTSIDE
OF STAR CITY.
ANY BACKGROUND ON
THE BUILDING?
I MEAN, YOU NAME IT,
IT'S BEEN IT.
HOSPITAL,
SHIPPING WAREHOUSE,
MANUFACTURING PLANT.
I MEAN,
IT'S HAD MORE OWNERS
THAN
A "FORTUNE" 500 COMPANY.
WHICH MEANS IT COULD BE
A COVER FOR SOMETHING.
YEAH, SOMETHING
BEING
THE NINTH
CIRCLE'S
HEADQUARTERS
HERE
IN STAR CITY.
EMIKO'S THERE, WHICH IS
ALL THAT MATTERS TO US.
WE'RE GOING AFTER HER
AS A TEAM.
ARE YOU SURE?
RENE: WE GOT
YOUR BACK.
OH, HEY, DINAH! THANK
YOU FOR WIPING THAT
SECURITY CAMERA FOOTAGE.
I COULD NOT GET THERE
BEFORE THE COPS DID.
I THOUGHT THAT WAS YOU.
NO.
LET'S GO WIDE.
ARSENAL, ON MY 6.
OVERWATCH,
ANY HEAT SIGNATURES?
FELICITY:
NO. NOT EVEN YOURS.
THERMAL IMAGING
CAN'T PENETRATE
THROUGH THOSE WALLS.
[OPENS COMMS]
I HAVE EYES ON HER.
JOHN:
MOVING TO INTERCEPT.
JOHN: OLIVER, CONFIRM
YOUR LOCATION.
THIS IS OVER.
IS IT?
RIGHT NOW,
SERGEANT BINGSLEY
IS RECEIVING
AN ANONYMOUS GIFT
DELIVERED TO HIS OFFICE:
THE MISSING
SECURITY FOOTAGE
FROM THE METRO STATION.
YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO MADE IT DISAPPEAR?
YOU SET US UP.
WHAT DO YOU WANT?!
FOR YOU TO SUFFER
THE WAY I SUFFERED.
YOU AND YOUR TEAM ARE
GONNA DIE IN THERE.
AND I WILL BE OUT THERE
DESTROYING YOUR LEGACY.
YOU'LL DIE A VILLAIN
JUST LIKE
OUR FATHER DID,
AND I WILL BE THE CAUSE
OF BOTH OF YOUR DEATHS.
AND JUSTICE WILL FINALLY
BE SERVED.
WHAT DID YOU SAY?
I HAD THE CHANCE
TO WARN OUR FATHER
ABOUT THE "GAMBIT."
IT WAS RIGGED
TO EXPLODE,
AND I KNEW
ABOUT IT.
I LET OUR FATHER
DIE BECAUSE HE
DIDN'T DESERVE
TO LIVE.
AND NEITHER DO YOU.
BYE, BROTHER.
FELICITY: OLIVER,
DO YOU READ ME?
DOES ANYBODY COPY?
OLIVER, COME IN.
JOHN?
JOHN, COME IN!
OLIVER?
COME IN, PLEASE!
COME IN!
MAN: GREG, MOVE YOUR HEAD.