My name is Oliver Queen.
After five years in hell,
I returned home with only
one goal, to save my city.
But my old approach wasn't enough.
I had to become someone else.
I had to become something else.
I had to become the Green Arrow.
Previously on Arrow...
So, when 're you gonna pop the question?
O LIVE RI Tonight.
This is a map of Lian Yu.
And I think that it leads to
whatever Reiter is looking for.
To get there I'll need your help.
The restoration of Starling Bay.
Leave the Bay as it is.
What if I refuse?
The fight to save Star City isn't
gonna be fought in the shadows.
It's gonna be fought in the light of day.
And I promise you,
that I will never stop fighting
to save this city.
There was a time
I would've thought this was my fault.
It's not my fault. It's my responsibility.
Ollie?
Hey. How we doing?
It's actually a pretty great turnout.
Who knew people would
rather pick up garbage
than celebrate the holidays, huh?
Not bad for a hippie-crunchy
campaign proposal, huh?
Nobody likes an "I told you so."
Except apparently Star City.
Your approval rating is up 10 points.
- I have an approval rating.
- Yes. Yes, you do.
Welcome to politics, Mr. Queen.
- Mr. Queen.
- Yes! Excuse Me.
How do you feel about inspiring
so many people to come out here today?
Oh... I didn't inspire anyone.
This is the city that I know,
it's the city I remembered,
- and it's the city that we can be again.
- Nice. Thank you for your time.
- Thank you.
- Nice line.
Did you give him that one?
I might've given a note or two.
Well,
you have people picking up garbage
when they should be picking up presents.
- You missed your calling.
- How are you doing?
I have my brother home with me
for the holidays, Oliver.
He's in a cage...
But he's here.
We're gonna get Andy out
from under Darhk's influence, John.
That is a promise.
If we can reduce just 40%
of the toxicity that's produced
by the bacterial microorganisms
that have just sprung up here...
We can swim in just 12 more days
- if the restitution rate stays consistent.
- Yes.
- She's like a mini-you. That's so cute.
- That's awesome.
Everybody get down!
Go! Go! Go! Go! Take cover!
Let's go! Let's go! Get down!
I think I can power
the drones down remotely!
I think now would be a good time for that.
GO! Go!
Hurry!
Hurry up! Everybody get down!
You all right?
A day of hope for a better tomorrow
has turned into another day of despair
for Star City.
A terrorist attack has left
dozens in critical condition
after people showed up
to help Oliver Queen
and his campaign staff
clean up the Star City Bay.
In the meantime, SCPD
and national authorities
are searching for
the individuals responsible,
but so far, there are no suspects.
Any news on the victims?
Some are being released.
Some are still in surgery.
- It's a miracle that no one died.
- Despite Darhk's best efforts.
Are we sure that this was HIVE?
Yeah, that's what I thought.
- Are you okay?
- There were kids there.
It's Alex.
He's saying that every
news network in the country
- is looking for a comment from you.
- No comment.
- Ollie, we have to give them something.
- What do you want me to say?
I asked people to come and help,
they almost died because of it.
It's when we have a plan to get Darhk,
then I will talk to the press.
I know HIVE wants this city to die
but going after a volunteer event,
ltjust seems a little overkill.
Two weeks ago, Darhk told me
to back off my plan to clean up the Bay.
Today, he went after civilians.
This is important to him for some reason.
We need to understand what it is.
Last time I tried to talk to my brother
it didn't go too well.
Try to talk to him again.
A couple of weeks in a cage
will change your perspective. Trust me.
All right. Almost there.
Maybe two more miles.
Since when does two more miles
mean almost there?
- Taiana, we need to push forward.
- No.
That's what you want.
My brother's dead and
you have me marching to the sea.
I thought you wanted to
get back at Reiter.
I want to kill the bastards
who killed my brother.
Conklin is just an extension of Reiter.
You want to hurt them,
you keep them from getting what they want.
Your idea of revenge
is a bit more indirect than mine.
You're right. I'm using you.
You said you were a dive instructor.
I need those skills.
But I'm promising you,
if I get what I want,
Reiter and Conklin will suffer.
What would Vlad want you to do?
My friends seem to think
you're ready to talk,
but I know better.
You were always
one stubborn son of a bitch.
Pictures of Carly and Andy Junior.
A real man would've asked for them by now.
You know Carly cried for months
because she thought you were killed?
Andy Junior grew up without a father.
- And you let them.
- It wasn't me, it was HIVE.
They fake our deaths so we're untraceable.
Floyd Lawton shot me
with ammo supplied by HIVE.
He didn't even know.
You destroyed your family, Andy!
And you never reached out to them.
Not even once.
How could you do that?
I get it.
You didn't care then, you don't care now.
Just so you know,
your good friend, Damien Darhk,
attacked the Star City Bay this morning.
Hurt a whole lot of people.
And the neuro-blockers he was using on you
were no longer in your system.
So, chemically speaking, Andy,
you're no longer his bitch.
I'm not anyone's bitch. And I'm not yours.
What happened to you, Andy?
If Damien Darhk brainwashed you,
I could get it.
But according to Darhk...
Were you running drugs
and weapons in the 'Stan?
I had to do what I had to do.
I'm giving you a chance here, man.
A chance, Andy, to redeem yourself
for all that you've done.
'Cause I have to believe that
someplace deep inside of you,
you want to make the right choice.
So I'm asking whatever's left
of the brother I loved,
the one I still love, Andy,
one last time, man.
What does Darhk want with the Bay?
I don't know.
Hey, Mom.
- Thank God you're okay, baby.
- Yeah, I'm okay. I'm fine.
Oh...
It's so awful. It's just, like...
Who shoots up a bunch of people
during the holidays?
That's what makes it awful?
Why does it look like
Santa Claus threw up in here?
It's for Oliver's campaign holiday party.
I wanted to make sure your
Jewish heritage was represented.
Yeah, I'm not so sure
that's still gonna be happening.
What? Humbug. No, no, no.
That's ridiculous, sweetie. No.
You can't let the terrorists win.
- I'm gonna take a shower.
- Okay.
Mom? Mom? Are you okay?
Are you okay? Are you okay?
- In the Christmas lights...
- Uh-huh.
In a ring box I found...
I found this.
Three carats. Princess cut.
No cloudiness at all.
I knew Oliver loved you,
but not this much.
He's gonna propose.
He's gonna propose. Oh, my gosh!
Honey, I don't know who's more excited,
you or me.
I think it's me.
Thanks for coming.
I'm trying to figure out
how to deal with them.
I sort of think our best bet
is telling the truth.
It's the only play we got, man.
The HIVE has us outnumbered.
If we have any chance of stopping Darhk,
we need to ask the city for help.
If we do this, it is gonna
paint a target on all of our backs.
- We can take care of ourselves
- Let's light 'em up.
Thank you for coming, everyone. Thank you.
As today's tragedy has reminded us,
we are at war.
For six months, we have been besieged
by a nameless, and a faceless organization
that seems hell-bent
on destroying our city.
You know them as the Ghosts.
And while they may be anonymous,
their leader is not.
He has a face. He has a name,
and I think that it is high time
the people of Star City
know the truth about who he is.
His name is Damien Darhk.
He controls the Ghosts on behalf
of an organization known as HIVE.
HIVE wants this city to die.
Now I will be distributing this,
the only known photograph of Mr. Darhk,
to every news outlet and
social media feed in the country.
For months, this man
has made us afraid to walk the streets.
I suggest that we return the favor.
We will also be setting up a hotline.
Now, individually,
Mr. Darhk may be able to defeat us.
But united...
He doesn't stand a chance.
Congratulations, Damien. You're famous.
Well, that should get
his attention at the very least.
- You good with the hotline?
- I'm on it.
- Happy hunting.
- That is a whole lot of Hanukkah.
Yeah. For your campaign holiday party.
You better believe that my faith is
going to be well-represented.
Felicity, we just waved
a red flag in front of a bull.
That doesn't mean the bull
is gonna charge right away.
And it doesn't mean we can put
our entire lives on hold in the meantime.
- But... Help me out here, man.
- No can do.
- Can't throw a grenade then go to ground.
- John is right.
As much as your speech
was about outing Darhk,
it was also about sending the message
that you're not afraid anymore.
- And canceling your Christmas party...
- Holiday. Holiday.
Your holiday party
is sending the opposite message.
Okay. Talk to Lance,
see if he can get some extra security
- for this holiday party.
- Yes.
Could I ask you a question?
Now? Here? I mean...
What's the question?
Did we do the right thing?
You mean with Darhk?
Yeah. Well, he's gonna retaliate.
Somewhere. Some place and...
When he does, we'll be ready.
I think the drugs Reiter has
you and the other captives growing
is just funding his bigger plan,
searching for some sort of
mystical artifact.
- He likes his prayers and trinkets.
- And maps.
But I cannot make that one without
detailed survey maps of the island.
- Reiter doesn't have them?
- Not that I've seen.
But Reiter is not the first person to come
to this island while I've been here.
If you're here to give me
a Christmas present
you can keep whatever knife
or torture device you plan on giving me.
No presents.
Nothing gift-wrapped, at any rate.
I just wanted to check
and see how you're feeling.
I'm great.
Haven't wanted to snap anybody's neck
who's given me the wrong look
since Damien Darhk whammied me.
I think I might be cured, Dad.
So, you can keep whatever file
you have on a pedophile,
or meter maid, or politician,
whoever it is
that you think I'm gonna kill.
Since you told me about
your encounter with Damien Darhk,
- I had my minions looking into it.
- You love having minions.
Darhk's effect on you
had nothing to do with his exposure
to waters from the Lazarus Pit.
Then why do you think
he's affecting my bloodlust?
I don't know. There are very few things
in this world that scare me, Thea.
But I'm beginning to suspect
we're dealing with something
- that might fall into that category.
- Just cheer up, Dad.
Okay? It's Christmas.
We are dealing with universal forces
that I don't understand yet.
Please, promise me
that you will be careful.
I pinky promise.
You look good.
You were not kidding
about the extra security.
- Where did you find all these guys?
- Well, a friend of mine is a SEAL.
He knows someone, who knew someone,
who knew someone.
Really big somebodies.
These guys are like three of me.
Yeah. Where's Laurel?
Probably fielding
a million calls on the hotline.
She must love you right now.
Is it just me or did you hire
the U.S. Army as your caterers?
Actually, they're marines.
I am John Diggle.
I work security for Mr. Queen.
Curtis Holt,
I work for Mr. Queen's girlfriend.
- This is my husband, Paul.
- A hottie. Nice work, Curtis.
- What? Was? Wait, was that weird?
- A little.
Don't worry. You're handsome,
duh, but you bat for the other team.
And I'm practically engaged.
And, by practically engaged,
I mean not engaged at all. Right?
I mean anything could happen eventually
in, like, years. In another galaxy.
Excuse me. Can I steal you for a second?
The fire department chief's here.
- Very nice to meet you.
- You too.
- Curtis.
- Oliver.
- How long have you two been married?
- Five years, right about now.
Oh, winter wedding.
That must've been beautiful.
It was the summer, actually.
We got married on a scuba-diving boat
- near the Great Barrier Reef.
- Whoa...
I hid the ring in a seashell
at the bottom of the reef.
And you are lucky I found it.
Well, you never would've found it
if I'd put it in a dessert
like straight people do.
Have you seen him eat a piece of cake?
He doesn't chew, he inhales.
Soufflé.
- Felicity? Are you okay?
- Yeah. Just got to find my mom.
Oh, my gosh! No, it was awesome.
- Mom?
- Oh.
Uh... Hmm.
I am never gonna be able to un-see this.
Sorry, honey. Um...
Sweetie, I would like you
to meet my boyfriend, Quentin.
- She is your mother?
- He's your boyfriend?
What?
- Did you say boyfriend?
- I'm sorry. Do you...
- Do you guys know each other?
- I thought it was just, like, a date or...
Can I talk to my mom for a second?
Oh, yeah, listen... Um...
- Laurel doesn't know.
- Yeah.
I'm gonna hit myself over the head
with something very heavy
so that I don't know either.
- All right. Yeah. Okay. Bye, honey.
- Bye, honey.
Isn't Quentin amazing? Oh, my gosh.
Oliver was gonna propose to me
three months ago.
- What?
- Three months ago.
- How do you know?
- It's a long story.
But he was gonna propose
and then we moved back here.
So why didn't he just pop the question
once you settled back in?
- Yes.
- No.
Excuse me.
Hey, hey. hey, hey. What's going on?
- I don't know.
- Is it Darhk?
Inasmuch as that he's the reason that
Laurel and Thea showed up on our doorstep
three months ago.
Right before you were going to propose.
And before you say anything,
you should know that my morn found the ring
- in the decorations box.
- It's not what you think.
Well, that depends on whether or not
you think that I think that
you were gonna propose
- and then that you changed your mind.
- I didn't change my mind.
- Well, something changed.
- Everything changed.
Where we live. What we do. Who we are.
- I was gonna propose.
- Hmm.
But then we came back to Star City.
And then I just needed
some time to rethink things.
Because you thought
I wasn't gonna say yes?
No. Because what we're doing is dangerous.
And I...
But I chose this life. And I chose you.
And I don't understand
why we can't have both.
What do we have here?
Mmm, mmm, mmm.
Malbec. Nice.
How did you know that was my favorite red?
So full-bodied, so full of life,
unlike your security outside.
Oh... And in my defense, they fired first.
I guess my invitation
was lost in the mail?
I'm only kidding,
it's not my kind of scene anyway.
Hmm.
I'm only here to have a word
with the man of the hour.
What do you want?
Well, something I can't have, apparently.
Your loyalty, your allegiance.
I told you there'd be
a price to pay if you refused.
I made that decision, not these people.
- Let them go.
- Ooh.
I wish I could do that, I really do.
But sometimes the best way
to teach someone a lesson
isn't to punish them.
It's to punish the ones
he cares about the most.
Bye-bye.
Take them.
- Oliver? Oliver, they took her.
- What?
They took my baby girl.
It's okay. It's okay. I'll get her back.
- They took Thea, too.
- She's gonna be okay.
- What happened?
- It was all over before it started.
John and Thea, they didn't stand a chance,
and I couldn't make a move,
because then Darhk would know
that I was playing for your side.
And I'm not sure that was the right call.
You made the right call.
But we need to track Darhk.
You need to dig up everything
that you can find, okay?
- Yeah. I'm on it.
- Alex?
The police are gonna wanna
ask you about what happened.
Take care of these people.
Get them home if they need it,
get them medical attention
if they need it,
- and pay for it out of the campaign fund.
- Of course. What about the police...
Stall the police.
Tell me where to find Damien Darhk.
Oliver, we'll find them.
Not even the Ghosts know where they are.
Did you learn anything from the hotline?
Only how many
crazy/bored people are in this city.
- Don't go there.
- Where?
Your go-to place.
Where you sit there
and you say that it's all your fault.
Well, it is my fault.
I'm the one who outed Darhk.
I know. I seem to remember us
all being there when you did.
I ran for mayor
because I can protect myself,
- and I thought that all of you could, too.
- And you were right. We can.
I know. But you didn't sign up for this.
Oliver, we can take care of ourselves.
And that's including Felicity.
You inspired a lot of people.
Well, Thea and John and Felicity,
inspiration is not what they need tonight.
Hmm.
But somewhere, someplace,
there is a Ghost that's gonna talk to me.
And what if there isn't?
Then I'm gonna take great pleasure
in trying to make them.
Are you ready?
I hope so.
I don't see how you can free-dive
after only an hour's instruction.
Well, since coming to this island,
I've learned I could do a lot of things
I didn't think I could.
Plus, you're a good teacher.
- I could go with you.
- I know the ship.
I'll be back in a few minutes.
I want every uniform canvassing leads.
I want every detective
talking to every Cl we got.
You get it?
Hey, baby. What's, what's going on?
Something happen?
Got a message from the office.
A tip came through the hotline.
- Yeah. Something we can move on?
- About you.
Come here. Come here.
Are you working for Damien Darhk?
- It's not what you think.
- You don't know what I think.
Darhk threatened you, okay?
I did what I had to do
to keep you safe, honey.
Oh, really? And what's that, Dad?
How many people died?
How many fathers' daughters?
None. I hope. None, I...
I just been eyes and ears, all right?
First for Darhk and then,
for the past month or so, Oliver.
- Oliver knew about this?
- Yeah. He found out.
Didn't take it too well at first,
but then, I think he understood.
Understood what?
That there is nothing I wouldn't do
to protect my baby girl.
Oliver?
- You got something?
- Just a lot of suicidal Ghosts.
- Yeah, and where's that leave us?
- Nowhere.
Honestly, Oliver, this place is even
easier to break into than your last lair.
What the hell is going...
- Dad!
- Malcolm!
We're pressed for time.
Suffice it to say, I'm a little less dead
than most people think.
- What are you doing here?
- My daughter's in danger.
Shouldn't your first question be,
"What took you so long?"
What is this?
HIVE used polyphasic-encrypted
satellite phones to communicate.
- That is one of them.
- And where'd you get it?
I'm Ra's al Ghul.
Maybe we can use the phone to track Darhk.
If Felicity were here, maybe.
But, as it is, our only play
is trading me for them.
Okay, listen, I'm not going to pretend
to understand what is going on here.
But the idea of you
turning yourself over to Darhk,
that's the worst idea
I've heard in a while.
Maybe, but it's our only play.
I brought all this on. I have to end it.
Well, I hope you're all enjoying the city.
You know, we have a lovely symphony
and the best coffee
on the western seaboard.
Wonderful. Ms. Fayad said
you liked to play games, Damien.
- Games?
- Yes, games.
Now you're just wasting our time.
We came here to check
on your progress with Genesis,
not to watch you exercise
a personal vendetta.
Oh. You're talking about
Oliver Queen's friends.
We have greater concerns
than some mayoral campaign.
That campaign's involvement in the
Star City Bay turned out to be a concern.
Well, folks.
Turns out things are
gonna get real interesting.
Real fast.
"DARHK". I was surprised to get your call.
And on one of our secure phones, no less.
You are more than you seem, Oliver.
Oh, you really better hope
that isn't true.
What's the word for a man
who threatens the man
who's holding his
nearest and dearest captive?
I don't know, "idiot"?
You didn't kill my friends.
You took them to make a point.
- You've made it.
- No.
Not yet I haven't.
I'm here. Let my friends go.
I'm sorry, did you think this was
quid pro quo, Mr. Queen?
We had a deal. Now, let my friends go.
Pafience.
Do you know who perfected the gas chamber?
The Nazis.
For years, I wondered why the world would
allow those monsters to exist,
let alone thrive.
And then I realized,
the world needed them to.
As horrible as it sounds,
every now and then humanity needs a reset.
A do-over.
That time has come.
- What is this?
- A demonstration...
Of the project
that you're gonna help us with,
once we install you as mayor.
Think of it as your friends
and family's life insurance policy.
Oh...
Thank you for your service,
your mind and your belief in me.
You will forever be part of our HIVE.
"DARHK". The bloom is active.
Good.
Oh, and by the way, thank you for
doing the legwork on skimming the bay.
My people were using the harbor
to create a certain type of algae.
One that would allow us
to do this undetected.
Hmm? Aw, bummer.
Well, at least he lasted longer
than the previous one.
I guess that's something.
All right, let's continue to adjust
the ratio of the bloom.
If you told me I'd ever get used to
seeing you dressed up like that, I'd...
Excellent, you've got your
bondage outfit on.
No mask for you?
Not my thing.
If we're going after Oliver,
wouldn't it make sense for you
to bring along a few of
your little ninja friends?
I can't afford to pit
the League against HIVE.
Do you have Oliver's location?
An abandoned industrial complex
outside Pennytown.
You'd think Darhk would've checked to see
if he was tagged with a tracker.
Well, I'm sure he did.
Damien's very thorough.
But Oliver had me tag him with
the same particulate nanotechnology
- he used on me last year.
- What about me?
- No. You'll blow your cover with Darhk.
- It's pretty much already blown.
- Can you give us the room?
- Happily.
I have enough father and daughter drama
in my life as it is.
- Good luck.
- Thank you.
Remember, we're on a clock.
Okay. if this is about you not trusting me
anymore after working with Darhk...
No. It's just the opposite.
You've done things.
Things that you'll
never forgive yourself for,
because you were protecting me.
But I'm the one who gets to decide
whether I need anyone's protection.
That's not how
parenting works, sweetheart.
I think that you and I can both agree that
our relationship
is a little unconventional.
I guess the mask
should've been the first clue.
Listen, sweetheart.
You just be careful out there, all right?
'Cause I don't know what I'd do
if anything were to happen to you.
In fact, that's not true,
I know exactly what I would do.
And it'd be ugly.
These people. They're volunteers?
True believers. Every last one.
Oliver!
DARHK'. AW...
Well, I'll give you guys some privacy
to say your farewells.
- Are John and Thea all right?
- Yeah. I think so.
Please, don't tell me that
you traded your life for ours
because that would be
extremely Old Oliver.
I had to turn myself in.
It was the only way to know
where you were being held.
One little problem,
two if you think that Darhk is gonna
keep up his end of the bargain.
But what happens when the cavalry shows up
and the Green Arrow's not present?
Darhk is evil, not stupid.
I have that handled, Felicity.
It had to be this way.
Why? Because you think that we're in
this situation because of your decisions?
Look, I really hate to be the one
to break this to you, Oliver,
but you are not the boss of me.
And I am the one who decides
whether I need anyone's protection.
I know.
Back at the Christmas party from hell,
you said you were gonna propose
and you didn't because you weren't sure
our relationship
could survive this kind of life.
It was a holiday party.
And I had more to say,
but we were attacked.
And here we are, fighting...
Fighting our way through the danger
instead of running away from it.
Isn't that the whole point of marriage?
To get through the hard times because
we're together, not in spite of it?
Um...
Just so you know, if you had asked me...
I would've said yes.
- Ah... Thank you for coming.
- Oh, my God.
What's going on?
The deal is that I bring myself here
and you let my friends go.
Hey!
- Let me go!
- I am so sorry about this.
We had a deal!
Well, I think if you replay
our conversation in your mind,
our bargain was only, at best, implied.
Even so... Bad guy, remember?
- You let them go.
- I will. Existentially speaking.
You do this and you lose any leverage
that you have over me.
Wrong. As long as they're alive
you have something to fight for.
That is what I'm taking away from you,
but don't worry.
It's painless.
Well, mostly.
Look for seams, this place
may not be 100% sealed.
Oh, Oliver, don't worry.
There are plenty of fish.
If it's blondes you like, I can have one
at your house in 20 minutes.
One that I won't kill.
Hey! Come on. Let's go.
- Hey. I thought I'd lost you.
- I'm here. I'm here.
Is this guy my father?
Really? And here I was ready
to just call it even for the night.
You may go.
As the kids say, "I got this."
You really haven't learned anything,
have you?
Oh... I might've learned a little.
Where's Malcolm?
There you go.
I am dying to see
what's beneath that mask.
Seems like you're dying a bit, too.
We shouldn't leave all these guys here.
If they're anything like Darhk's guy
in the gas chamber, we probably should.
Okay, they're definitely like
Darhk's guy in the gas chamber.
Is that the best you've got?
There's four of you and a lot more of us.
Yeah, well, now there's five.
I guess you decided
you didn't need anyone's protection.
I brought the cavalry.
Hope you don't mind.
Let's go!
Good news.
I'm gonna let you live long enough
to watch me kill your little green buddy.
Get clear!
Are you sure that Darhk
didn't make it out of the explosion?
Have you seen any horror movies?
These guys don't stay dead.
Especially if you can't find a body.
Whoa! Glass half-empty much?
Good news is,
whatever Darhk had going on there,
- we lit it up pretty good.
- Where is Merlyn?
Said he had to attend to League business.
Can't believe I'm gonna say this,
but I owe him one.
- I helped out a little bit, too.
- Yes, you did.
Wait. Aren't we supposed to
go to that thingy?
What thingy?
It's a surprise. You're not the only one
who can keep a secret.
- What happened?
- Shark!
Guess I don't taste very good.
On!
That is gonna leave a scar.
Ahhh...
What?
Well, hey, Taiana.
You're a little less dead
than you're supposed to be.
And you, you may not be a spy
but you're definitely a liar.
Which means you're probably
lying about being a spy.
I'm gonna enjoy taking pieces out of you.
- What do you want?
- To talk.
- Thought you gave up on that.
- I did.
Until I met your cult leader,
Damien Darhk.
It's not a cult.
The man has people, regular people,
honest people, I'm thinking,
so brainwashed.
They're willing to die for him. Cult.
You know what?
Think what you wanna think.
It's a free country. For now.
This isn't you, Andy.
The man I knew...
Pulled me out of dark waters...
Convinced me to keep going
when I didn't see the point.
No. What you didn't see,
what you failed to see
is the man I really am.
Right in front of you. The whole time.
So my brother's a Ghost.
Fine. We'll treat you like a Ghost.
Your vigilante problem's getting worse.
Oh, relax, Ms. Nixon.
Focus on the here and now.
There's concerns that
you're leading us off the rails.
No. I'm leading us
exactly where we need to be.
Beautiful, isn't it?
And I don't even like corn.
Go ahead. Breathe. Drink it in.
Tell me what it reminds you of.
- It seems so real.
- Ah. I liken it to the air on Everest.
A little thin, maybe but just enough
to keep things interesting.
I thought the tests had failed.
Not the last one.
Thanks to the algae
we engineered from Star City Bay,
the air down here
is now perfectly breathable.
We are right on schedule.
- Phase four begins now.
- And what of Oliver Queen?
This was all Alex's idea.
Here to show the people
that you're not backing down.
All you got to do is flick a switch
and give a speech.
That's it?
We'll be here waiting for you
when you're done.
- You're coming with me.
- No.
Oh... Please. Hey.
Oh, thank you.
Thank you everyone.
This week,
an event just like this was
interrupted by terrorists.
But all of us are here tonight
to send those people
a very simple message.
We're not gonna let the darkness win.
So all of us are here
to light a candle together.
United.
This right there is possible
because of all of you.
And I am grateful for each one of you.
There is one person in particular
that I am grateful for.
You.
Someone that has stood beside me
when times were darkest.
She's the one who lights my way.
Felicity Smoak...
Would you make me...
The happiest man on the face of the Earth?
- Yes?
- Yes.
It looks even bigger in here.
Ooh...
You know what? To tell you the truth,
I don't even care about the bling.
All I care about is you.
What's going on?
Felicity!
English - SDH