Previously on Arrow...
So I think I finally
figured out a plan b
to keep us hidden from Archer
while we try to destroy it.
We'd have to steal it
from Keven Dale's computer
in his office at Galaxy One.
Something's come up which
requires my immediate attention.
We should get out of here.
Keven: Seize them.
- Where is William?
- Mom, what's wrong?
Frak!
Zeta: By the authority
of Galaxy One,
you are under arrest.
Emiko!
Rene: She has
the weapon.
Roy: And we have no idea
where she's gonna use it.
We'll find her.
Man on P.A.: This is SCPD
aerial support.
Hold your positions.
Stop right there!
We are not the enemy,
lieutenant.
The enemy is still
out there,
and we should be working together,
not wasting time.
Six Arrows and six
dead cops say otherwise.
Talk to
sergeant Bingsley.
He'll tell you we
didn't do this.
Sergeant Bingsley is
unconscious
in the back of
an ambulance right now.
Lieutenant.
Lieutenant: Turn around.
Put your hands behind
your head!
All of you, do it now!
[Sirens]
[Gunshots]
What do you think
is worse,
Emiko being in possession
of a bioweapon
or the team being Star
City's most wanted?
Rene: Can I choose both?
I'm going to go with the
warrants out for our arrest.
The real us, not
the vigilante us,
which means our lives in
this city are over.
Roy:
Been there before.
Oliver: Guys, this team always finds
a way to come through.
John: Yeah, but this
feels different.
Emiko has a personal vendetta
against you and your whole family.
She has a bigger ax to grind
than Adrian Chase or Slade.
Fine. But there has to be
a way to get through to her.
Roy: And she knows
we're alive now.
That'll make her even more
determined to destroy the city.
Rene: Which means we need to
figure out where in the city
she's planning on
deploying the Cygnus.
Felicity: Yeah. Well,
easier said than done,
because Emiko must've found out
that I was tracking the Cygnus
by using its
chemical signature
because she's figured out
a way to block me,
which brings us back
to square one.
Curtis: Sounds like
you all could use some help.
It's a good thing you
called for backup.
In accordance with Star
City penal code 10101971,
you are all under arrest.
Turn around and put your
hands behind your head.
Ohh. Smoak Tech
flex-restraints.
Nice to see another
one of my creations
being used against me.
And what if we don't
want to go quietly?
Failure to comply will result
in summary execution.
Wrong answer. Hyah!
[Circuits crackling]
- Alena!
- Uh!
They know what we're gonna do...
Even before we do it.
Archer's
predictive algorithm!
Hyah!
Hey, troublemaker.
I had him.
You're welcome.
We have to find William.
Not from here.
This place is burned.
I know somewhere
that isn't.
What are they
gonna do with us?
You mean before they
torture us to find out
what you stole off Keven
Dale's computer or after?
I'm gonna stop asking
questions now.
Look, I'm sorry
I blew your cover.
It's not your fault.
Dale's been
suspicious ever since
I questioned what
they did to Felicity.
On the bright side,
I did manage to steal
Galaxy One's secret evil
plans for Star City.
They plan to use the
ZETAs to establish
martial law
and remake Star City in The Glades'
image.
Which means they're gonna hunt
down everyone with a record
no matter how minor
and kill them on the spot.
Which is basically everyone
on that side of the wall.
It will be
a bloodbath.
[Elevator chimes]
Duck.
[Sighs]
Dad, I was so worried.
We're OK, peanut.
We need to get out of here.
You're back just in time
for the fun stuff.
Curtis: I'm so happy
Roy's back.
I love a good reunion.
You seem awfully
positive
about the stuff
with your sister.
I know how to break my
family's cycle of violence.
Ooh, I hope it goes
something along the lines of
stopping Emiko from destroying
the city and killing us all.
That's part one,
but it needs to be
more than that.
Felicity, i...
I want to help her redeem herself.
If I don't break
this cycle of violence,
I just don't ever see us
being able to provide
a secure future
for our family.
John: Hey. We just got
some strange chatter
over the SCPD scanner.
Someone called in
a bomb threat
at a shopping complex
downtown.
Somebody using a signal-bounced
untraceable number.
Suspicious.
Why would Emiko give an advance
warning on her own attack?
It doesn't make sense.
Roy: So that the whole complex will
evacuate into the Plaza outside,
where she'll deploy
the Cygnus.
Rene: Maximizing
the casualty count.
Dinah: Well, we can't
let that happen.
We won't.
Let's move out.
[Excited chatter, sirens]
This place
is jammed.
Cops, too.
This could get messy.
That's exactly
what Emiko wants.
Overwatch,
do you have eyes on?
OK. Still no sign of Emiko,
but we are tracking
what is most likely
a detonation signal
to a package on the norTheast
corner of the Plaza.
It's got to be
the Cygnus X-1.
All right. We need to get
these people clear
and find that device now.
John: Copy that.
We're focused on
the weapon.
Let's get all these
people out of here.
Rene: Listen up!
Everybody move now!
We have
to go!
Dinah: Move. Hey! If we don't
evacuate this building right now,
all these people
are gonna die.
You're
the vigilantes
who killed those
transit workers.
You're under arrest.
[Gunshot]
All right. Enough.
We don't have time for this.
Stand down.
You should still be in jail...
all of you.
We're not gonna
stand for this...
he's trying to save you,
dumbass.
Questions later.
How can I help?
Clear a path.
[Crowd murmuring]
[Beeping]
[People screaming]
[Screams]
Overwatch, what
happens to the Cygnus
if I shoot it down?
An accelerant will
augment the effects.
You need to freeze them.
It worked!
The Cygnus didn't spread.
You got all of them.
You contained it.
Not fast enough.
Star City is reeling tonight
following a horrific
terrorist attack
perpetrated by its own heroes,
which injured hundreds.
The vigilantes' motives
are still in question.
Dinah: I cannot believe they
still think we're behind this
after everything
we've done for this city.
Well, not everyone.
I'm out on parole thanks to you guys.
Oliver: Look, I know tonight
didn't go as planned.
Rene: That's
an understatement.
That doesn't mean
it's over.
John:
You can't possibly think
Emiko could have
a change of heart.
Laurel: Oliver's right.
What? I'm happy that you two
are on the same side finally.
But how can you be
siding with the woman
who tried to destroy
your life?
She actually did me a favor.
If I hadn't had toyed around
with being Black Siren again,
then I never would
have realized
that that's not the life
that I want to live.
Maybe Emiko will have
the same realization.
If people were correct
in their thinking
that Laurel and I
couldn't change,
well, we wouldn't be
here helping you.
Curtis: I hope you
guys are right
because Emiko only used
a fraction of the Cygnus.
She has a lot of scary
nightmare bacteria left.
Any idea where she may
be targeting next?
At the moment, everywhere.
Felicity: The detonation signal's
been purposely scrambled,
which means the target
keeps moving.
Yeah. It's like
a whack-a-Cygnus.
[Laughs] Ohh,
I missed you.
Our descrambling
algorithm is working,
but it's going to be
slower than normal.
Roy: Even if you find
the targets,
we still need to find a way to
contain the drones at each site.
Are you all familiar
with the term
"optimized
cryogenic chambers"?
Oh, no, they aren't.
Yeah. It's just us? OK.
Basically I was able
to modify
an old portable
freezing device
so that it can contain
the Cygnus on the drones.
Good thing you guys didn't toss
all of my old tech equipment
when you did the new
bunker upgrades,
which, by the way,
are very cool, so...
- Felicity: Right?
- Rene: OK, look...
Uh, it's not that I don't
have faith in this team,
but if this scary bacteria
gets all over the city,
I got to get Zoe
somewhere safe.
John: OK. Well, Lyla took J.J.
to a secure A.R.G.U.S. location.
She can pick up Zoe
as well.
You have a son,
right? Connor?
- Yeah.
- We'll bring him as well.
Thank you.
Jackpot. I got two
detonation sites.
Oliver: OK, digg, Turner, and I will
go to the water treatment plant.
Roy, Dinah, Laurel,
you go to the convention center.
All right. And I will
stay here with Felicity.
All right. No one die.
- Felicity: "No"... wow. What?
- Curtis: Uh, I'm rusty. Sorry.
Felicity: Well,
I'm glad everyone is safe
to say the least.
Does anyone need anything?
Do we need any water?
It's very important
to hydrate.
No. And we don't need
any snacks either.
Dinah: According to
the information
William got on Dale's
computer, the ZETAs
are marching into
Star City tonight.
We have to disable Archer before
they start their mass execution.
Rene: That won't be easy.
Archer doesn't have
a server room.
Its server is
the actual wall
outside of The Glades.
Wait.
The ZETAs use Archer to track our DNA.
They'll know
the second
we get anywhere
close to that wall.
- Mom...
- Hmm?
Why are you making
that face?
I am not
making a face.
This is my face.
I might have put a
backdoor into Archer
that utilizes
Queen/Smoak DNA
so that you wouldn't
be in the system.
So you basically just
erased me.
I...
you know, just add that
to the list of lies.
I was
protecting you.
William: Wait. Hold on.
Yes, what she did may be
overprotective
- and overbearing...
- Yeah.
But it could be the break
that we've been waiting for.
I mean, if Archer
doesn't recognize Mia's DNA,
she could be the key
to shutting it down.
You're right. If Archer
inputs your DNA,
it theoretically
creates an opening
for a virus to be
uploaded.
I mean, I don't know
if it would work.
Alena: Well, even if it did,
Archer only inputs data
to its main server
at one location...
the checkpoint between
Star City and The Glades.
That's where Dale plans
to march the ZETAs
into Star City.
So we go there,
we scan Mia's DNA,
we upload the virus.
Even with the Archer
blindspots put in place,
we're way too publicly
recognizable
to get anywhere near
that checkpoint.
William: I mean,
you can't, but we can.
- No.
- Uh, the... the public
doesn't even know
who we are.
No. It is much
too dangerous.
Mom, you've trained me
my whole life for this.
Trust me.
Got to hand it to you,
Curtis.
Your containment chamber
worked like a charm.
Nice to know you still
think I'm terrific. Heh!
Heard it. That was bad.
Any luck unscrambling
the detonation signal?
Felicity: Dinah started transmission
at the convention center.
Her data plus your data
should do the trick
and help us identify
the targets.
OK, perfect. If we can neutralize
the rest of the Cygnus,
then we can turn our focus
back to Emiko.
Uh-oh.
[Computer buzzing]
What's happening?
Felicity: OK, so we have
a good news/ bad news situation
going on here, guys,
the bad news being we
just got 15 new targets.
We don't have time to
neutralize that many.
We might not have to.
All the Cygnus devices are
linked up to the same detonator.
- That was the good news, right?
- Uh-huh.
OK, well, if we destroy
the detonator,
we can neutralize
the rest of the targets.
I'm working on
a location for you now.
Oh, double frak.
It's at Palmer Tech.
Formerly Queen consolidated,
our father's company.
She wants to tear
down our family's legacy.
This is her target.
Call the team.
Two of the Cygnus
dispersement sites
have been compromised.
The Circle,
they're concerned.
Look, they want
to detonate
the remaining
devices now.
That isn't the plan.
The plan was
only to profit
on the destruction
of Star City.
I mean, this extra
chaos is unnecessary,
especially now with
the D.I.A. Closing in.
Chaos is the point.
Without terror,
there is no profit.
The Circle respectfully
disagrees,
and they worry that your
focus on your brother
has led to our exposure.
Your personal vendetta is only
drawing more attention to us.
I think you...
And the Circle
have forgotten
who their leader is.
My brother deserves
to suffer
just like I have suffered
all of these years.
And when he sees
his city burn
with his family to blame,
he will.
Overwatch,
we're on-site.
We're in
the telecom suite.
B.C., Laurel, and Wild Dog
are still en route.
I'm picking up over a
hundred heat signatures
in the building, including the penthouse
that is still under construction.
One guess as to where
your sister is.
Roy: She really
knows how to maximize
collateral damage,
doesn't she?
If we try to evacuate the civilians,
we'll blow our cover.
We need to find
that relay trigger
before The Ninth Circle
knows we're here.
Actually, just the device
relaying the signal.
There's a power surge coming
from the room you're in,
so the relay must be
somewhere nearby.
We shut down Emiko's
ability to detonate,
we save the city.
Find
the relay device
and then evacuate
the building.
You going after
Emiko?
John:
I've got your back.
Got to go
alone.
Communication is
mission critical.
The last thing we need
are comms failing
while we're out there.
While we're
out there?
Sounds like you still
haven't budged
on Mia and William
taking the reins.
We are about to
stop a small army
from infiltrating
Star City.
I can't be the only one
worried about the kids.
Of course
I'm worried,
but I taught Zoe
everything she knows
about being
a hero.
Almost everything.
And now my little girl's
a grown-ass woman
and one of
the canaries.
I know she can
handle herself.
And your kids,
they're no slouches either, Felicity.
They're like their parents.
This is not
the life
that Oliver and I
wanted for them.
They're supposed
to be living
happy, normal
lives right now.
That was the only thing
that Oliver asked me to do.
It was the only
thing that I
promised him
I would do.
And I failed.
Some mother I
turned out to be.
It's time.
Be safe.
I love you.
I love you, too, dad.
I'm going to be watching
over both of you.
We'll need you.
Roy: Mia...
Thought you might
need these.
[Gunshot]
[Yelling]
[Siren scream]
What happened to us being
public enemy number one?
Bingsley: I told
Pollard the truth
about what really
went down.
You guys are heroes.
Is the relay down,
overwatch?
Oh, so down,
it's in Australia.
Emiko can't trigger
the devices now.
Every remote device.
There's still an active
one in the building.
Enough to take
this place down?
And then some.
We need to evacuate
this building now.
You heard
the captain. Move!
John: Oliver,
the relay's deactivated,
but the building is still
armed. Do you have Emiko?
I do now.
I have been waiting
for you.
Emiko, it's over.
This was his view,
wasn't it?
Your father.
His perch above the
city, above everyone.
I'm glad you'll get to
see it all fall.
Not tonight.
What did you do?
I'm giving you
a second chance...
Before it's too late
for both of us.
I don't need bombs
to kill you.
Archer:
Welcome to Galaxy One.
Proceed to checkpoint.
This couldn't be
creepier.
Just keep
your heads down.
Once the scan starts,
it'll only take
a few seconds to upload
the virus.
Archer: Proceed.
Prepare
for identification.
[Circuits crackling]
Done. Let's
get out of here.
Mr. Clayton.
What a surprise.
I thought you'd be
smarter than this.
Turns out you're just
like your father.
Looks like you're having
technical difficulties.
No, no, no.
Don't tell me you actually
liked that creep.
No, it didn't work.
The virus didn't
destroy Archer.
It's rebooting itself.
We failed.
You have every right
to be angry.
I was angry, too,
because you let
our father die.
And that led to a ripple
effect in my life of loss.
I lost Tommy, my mother,
Laurel, Quentin.
And I wanted to kill you
for all of it.
Hyah! Hyah...
I know his death
affected you, too.
Instead of finding
the hero
that I really believe
is inside of you,
you went down
a dark path.
And it killed
your mother.
Dante killed my mother.
No, he didn't, Emiko.
Your allegiance to The Ninth
Circle killed your mother.
Your hatred of our father
killed your mother.
His worst impulses
drove you away,
and it led to every terrible
moment in both of our lives.
I think that together,
we can be better.
So if you're gonna
kill me, do it.
Virgil: Well, if you're
not gonna kill him,
we'll gladly oblige.
Felicity: Galaxy One must have
found a weak spot
and modified
the system.
OK. How long until the
ZETAs are back online?
Uh, best-case scenario,
5 minutes?
Dad, you said
the brain of Archer is in the wall,
so if we destroy
the wall?
When we built
the wall,
we installed
explosives
inside of each
control tower.
They're linked together
electronically,
but they can only be detonated
from inside one of the towers.
Yeah, but there's no way
anyone can make it up there
in 4 minutes.
An Archer could.
Felicity:
No way, Mia. Look.
Even if you got up there, you wouldn't
be able to make it back down in time.
You'll die.
Once I'm inside the tower,
can you talk me through it?
You know it's the only way.
If you can get inside,
I can access the system remotely.
- Mia, listen to me!
- Sorry, mom. I have to do this.
Emiko: Beatrice, you don't
have the authority to be here.
The council was promised
the total destruction
of Star City,
not a sibling spat.
And for the first
time in history,
the world knows
of our existence.
The Ninth Circle
answers to me.
Not anymore.
Finish them.
Almost in position.
Ready when you are.
[High-pitched tone]
[Screaming]
You're still here.
Yeah. I don't leave
my family.
Detonate the building.
[Grunts]
[Explosions]
[Zeta screams]
OK. The device is installed.
Now all I have to do is bypass
the encryption protocols,
reconfigure
the detonation commands,
and voila.
[Computer beeping]
Ready when you are.
Take care of mom.
She's already lost so much.
Here goes nothing.
I just started getting
used to having a sister.
I'm not
losing you now.
You have 60 seconds until
that wall goes boom.
Get out of there.
I'm sorry.
I know. It's OK.
You need to hide.
[Breathing heavily]
Your family's gonna die.
I made sure of it.
You need to hide
Felicity and the baby.
[Straining]
Emiko.
I... i...
I wanted to be a Queen.
[Explosions]
[Screams]
Uh-oh. The ZETAs are
back online.
You think?
William:
You have 20 seconds.
[Screaming]
So this is what it feels
like to save a city,
minus Palmer Tech
becoming a crater.
No civilian casualties.
That's a win.
Oliver: We really couldn't have
done this without your help.
Thank you.
Laurel, thank you.
Felicity: That
last-minute SCPD assist
really helped
turn the tide.
Oh, well, I'm just
relieved the department's
back on our side
and we can show our faces
- in the city again.
- Yeah.
Turner: Because you proved
this is a team of heroes.
I'm sorry about Emiko.
Thank you. I... I know
I tried to save her.
Oliver, I know this
wasn't how you wanted
her story to end.
Curtis: Hey. I'm sorry.
I hate to save and run.
- Ohh.
- But I have to go back to D.C.
The jeweler called.
The ring I picked out
for Nick is ready.
Oh, my god. Oh, my god.
You're popping the question?
Yeah. The Holt-anastases are
gonna make it official,
assuming he says yes.
Of course he'll say yes!
He'd be a fool not to. Oh!
Congratulations.
Any thoughts about what
you're gonna do next?
A man with your
set of skills,
a lot of people
will be looking.
Lyla... well, she's
always looking.
I just want to spend
time with my son,
who I need to get back to.
- Copy that.
- All right.
And then there were six.
Actually, five.
I can't stay.
You're gonna catch
up with Thea?
There's a lot I still
have to figure out.
I killed two
innocent people.
I have to find a way
to atone for that.
Felicity: Well,
since we're on the subject of good-byes,
we have
an announcement, too.
Hmm?
We're stepping back.
We're leaving Star City.
Not forever,
but, uh, for now.
Rene: You just saved
the city.
You don't want to take
a victory lap?
I didn't do anything.
Our team did.
Felicity: The fact that
the city is safe is
the reason why we can leave.
I've spent a long
time thinking about
my legacy as
the Green Arrow.
I always hoped it would
be saving the city.
But now I know that
my greatest legacy...
Is this team.
I started this
mission alone.
I was certain that
I would end it alone,
but the truth of
the matter is that
every bit of success that
I've had along the way
is because
of all of you.
The city is safe because
of your courage,
your compassion,
your selflessness,
and your loyalty.
Courage, compassion,
selflessness, loyalty.
Oliver, that sounds like
the 4 pillars of heroism to me.
Dinah: We should find a way
to remember them
to symbolize we will all be
there for each other always
no matter what.
Felicity: Ooh, like
a signal, you know.
One of us is in trouble,
we'll all come running,
including you, Roy.
We should just call it
the mark of four, right?
Felicity: That's brilliant.
Oliver: Man, I really hope
this isn't the last time
we're all in this bunker
together.
Hear, hear.
But it does feel like
the end of an era.
Felicity: OK, well, let's just
try to think of it
as the beginning of a new one.
Star City is a wall-free
zone once again.
Restoring The Glades
won't be easy.
The Glades hasn't been open
to outsiders in years.
Plenty of people will be
trying to take advantage.
Seems like the city's
gonna need heroes.
We were thinking
the same thing.
The four of you are the
heroes that the city needs.
What are you
talking about?
Dinah: Passing the torch.
Zoe, you are a born leader.
And I think you are
more than ready
to rebuild and take control
of the canaries.
I don't understand.
Someone's gonna get blamed
for what happened.
It should be us.
You'll be
fugitives.
We've spent the last two
decades living in hiding.
Going off-grid
won't be new for us.
Wait. I just got you back.
I'm so sorry,
but the four of you
having a future,
that's worth any sacrifice.
Thank you,
both of you.
I should be thanking you.
You got me off that island.
You never really told me
how you got on that island.
It's a long story. Look,
we should really get going.
Um, I'll catch up
with the two of you.
There's something I have to
do before we say good-bye...
something to honor
your father.
You having second thoughts?
[Sighs]
No.
Right. Yeah. Me neither.
It's the right thing to do
for our family.
I do wish we could tell
the team about the...
Yeah.
Baby, but I
understand it just
puts them in The Ninth
Circle's crosshairs.
When that threat is over.
Until then, it's
the best thing for them...
And us.
You know, the spirit
of this place
will live on long
after we're gone.
You've inspired so
many people, Oliver.
They will carry
on your legacy.
Sounds like
a cycle for good.
Far better
than that.
A cycle of
heroes...
Who will fight to
defend this city
with every fiber
of their being.
Anyone ever told you you always
know exactly what to say?
I have been told.
[Both laugh]
Mm.
Let's get you two
to your new home.
Good-bye, old friend.
Well, it's not Ivy town,
but it'll work.
Well,
it's temporary.
John: Well, basically,
this whole neighborhood is
ex-C.I.A.., ex D.I.A.,
and ex-A.R.G.U.S.
This is one big safe house.
You two will be fine here.
Please thank
Lyla for us.
Of course.
Well, I guess
this is home now.
At least until the threat
against our baby girl
is taken care of.
Your baby girl?
You're having a girl.
Mia.
Mia. That's
beautiful.
It's beautiful.
Well,
I guess since the city's in good hands now,
you two can focus
on your family,
which is exactly
what you should do.
Well, you are part
of that family, John.
Maybe it's the pregnancy
making me overly emotional,
but, oh, I'm gonna
miss you so much.
We love you.
I love you.
And you.
Yeah.
I'll reach out
to you two later.
Hey. You maintain
my bunker.
No food
by the monitors.
There's nothing worse than
crumbs in a keyboard.
[Sighs]
What now?
Well, this isn't
a tropical paradise,
but we never did
take our honeymoon.
[Music playing on soundtrack]
Oh. Yes.
Mom juice. Mm.
Ahh. You know,
as much as I miss
the team
and the action of taking
down the bad guys,
- this has been so nice.
- Yeah.
I wish William
were here.
Me, too.
You know, if this is
gonna be the new normal,
we should talk
with his grandparents
about getting
shared custody.
Yeah. I would
love that.
Mia's gonna need
her older brother.
[Wood creaks]
Now?
I thought
I had more time.
The universe is a complex
piece of machinery,
and balance must be
maintained.
One change requires another.
How would you propose
I keep the balance?
Will you help me save
Barry and Kara or not?
No. But I will give you
the means to save them.
Tell me what you
need in exchange.
Whatever
the multiverse requires
to survive the crisis
that is looming.
When it is time.
[Thunder]
It's OK.
So what bargain
have I made?
What does
the multiverse require?
You assist me
as we seek
to prevent
the inevitable.
But that sounds impossible.
The multiverse is more complex
than you could fathom.
What are you not
telling me?
I've seen your
future, Oliver,
inexorable
and unavoidable.
I have watched you die.
During this crisis?
I am truly sorry.
No. You are not taking him.
Felicity.
Oliver.
I am not here to bring harm
to you or your daughter.
Trust me, the world
needs her.
You think that I'm just
going to let you leave here
with my husband's life?
This is bigger
than us...
Than all of us.
Why does it always
have to be you?
Monitor: I cannot
prevent his passing,
but he can prevent
the deaths
of countless more,
including you
and your daughter.
But he needs to come
with me tonight.
Mom?
- Hi.
- Are you OK?
Yeah.
[Sighs]
I wanted to say good-bye
to both of you.
- Here?
- Yeah.
I just wanted us to be all
together one last time.
What do you mean,
one last time?
Just because you're
a fugitive,
it doesn't mean we
can't still communicate.
Well, things are gonna
be different this time.
You two don't need
my protection anymore.
You're our mom.
We still want you
in our lives.
I promised your father
that I would protect both of
you until you didn't need me.
He would be so proud...
So proud of you two.
I miss him so much.
I know.
I wish I got to know him.
I know, but he lives on
in the two of you.
[Inhales and exhales]
It's time for me to go
on a journey of my own.
I love you both so much.
So you promise me...
That the two of you are gonna
take care of each other, OK?
OK?
Ruelle:
I don't wanna know
Who we are
Without each other...
[Chuckling]
Hey.
It's just too hard...
I don't wanna leave
Here without you
This is why we can't
have a normal life.
This is why our children
will never have
normal lives.
I had to make the deal.
Oh, there's always
gonna be some danger
or some threat...
the league of assassins
or hive or The Ninth Circle
or...
The end of the friggin'
universe.
I need you to make me
a promise.
Yeah, OK.
No matter what
happens to me...
no matter what...
you need to do everything
in your power...
[Voice cracking]
You...
You need to keep
William and Mia safe.
I will keep them safe.
But wherever you go...
Whatever happens to you...
You'll never leave me.
On our wedding day,
you told me that I was the best part of you,
but the truth is...
We are the best parts
of each other.
And that is so much bigger
than the friggin' universe.
When I came back
to Star City
to start my mission,
I didn't think that I was
capable or deserving of love.
But you opened up
my heart
in ways that I never th...
thought were possible.
[Sniffles]
My only regret is not telling
you I loved you sooner.
No regrets.
Would you tell Mia that
I love her every day?
And I know that she
will grow up to be
as smart
and as beautiful
as her mom.
I will find you... Again.
I promise.
I love you.
I love you so much.
I don't wanna know
What it's like
to live without you
Don't wanna know
The other side
Of a world without you
I don't wanna know
I don't wanna know...
I'm ready.
Where I'm taking you,
there is no return.
I have waited a very
long time to see him.
I'm ready.
Ruelle:
In broken dreams
I don't wanna know
What it's like
to live without you
Don't wanna know
the other side
Of a world without you...
Man: Greg, move your head.