MY NAME IS OLIVER QUEEN.
AFTER 5 YEARS IN HELL,
I RETURNED HOME
WITH ONLY ONE GOAL...
TO SAVE MY CITY.
TODAY, I FIGHT THAT WAR
ON TWO FRONTS.
BY DAY, I LEAD STAR CITY
AS ITS MAYOR,
BUT BY NIGHT,
I AM SOMEONE ELSE.
I AM...
SOMETHING ELSE.
I AM THE GREEN ARROW.
PREVIOUSLY ON "ARROW"...
BEFORE HE WAS TAKEN,
CAYDEN WAS WORKING
ON A BIOMETRIC TRACKER
THAT COULD RECOGNIZE
A HEARTBEAT ANYWHERE
IN THE WORLD.
ANYWHERE
ADRIAN CHASE IS.
YOU'RE GONNA HELP ME
FREE CAYDEN FROM WHEREVER
ARGUS IS HOLDING HIM.
WE CAN THINK
OF ANOTHER WAY
TO FIND HIM.
THIS IS OUR ONLY CHANCE.
DON'T DO THIS.
HELIX IS ABOUT TO
EXTRACT CAYDEN JAMES.
JOHN: YOU'RE HOLDING
SOMEONE WITH NO LAWYER,
NO TRIAL.
THE WOMAN I LOVE
COULD NEVER DO THIS.
LYLA, THIS JOB
HAS CHANGED YOU.
YOU DIDN'T BACK
MY PLAY.
ALL OF THE TIMES THAT
I SUPPORTED YOU,
YOU COULDN'T DO
THE SAME FOR ME.
WHAT'S THAT?
THE TRACKER'S HOMING
IN ON CHASE'S LOCATION.
WHERE IS HE?
HE'S HERE.
[BEEPING]
[MUFFLED EXPLOSION]
[EARS RINGING]
FELICITY?! FELICITY?
FELICITY! HEY!
CHASE...HE'S HERE.
DON'T MOVE.
THAT'S NOT GONNA
BE A PROBLEM.
ALL RIGHT.
IF CHASE IS HERE,
HE'S NOT ON THIS LEVEL.
THAT...IT FELT
LIKE AN EXPLOSION,
BUT THERE'S
MINIMAL DAMAGE.
IT WAS AN EMP.
A BURST OF ELECTROMAGNETIC
RADIATION.
EVERYTHING IN THE BUNKER
WITH AN ELECTRIC CIRCUIT
HAS BEEN FRIED.
HOW DO YOU KNOW?
BECAUSE THE SPINAL IMPLANT
THAT HELPS ME WALK
ISN'T WORKING.
I CAN'T FEEL MY LEGS.
YOU KNOW, UNDER
DIFFERENT CIRCUMSTANCES,
THESE CHEMLIGHTS
MIGHT SEEM FESTIVE.
NO SIGN OF CHASE.
IT LOOKS LIKE THE EMP
WAS HIS PLAY.
ELEVATOR
AND SECURITY DOORS OFFLINE.
DID YOU CHECK
THE EMERGENCY EXIT DOOR?
I DID.
IT'S WELDED SHUT.
IF CHASE WASN'T SO EVIL,
I MIGHT ACTUALLY
BE IMPRESSED.
THE AIR VENTS ARE
GONNA BE DOWN, TOO.
THE AIR VENTS WILL LAST
A LITTLE WHILE LONGER,
BUT...YEAH, WE HAVE
TO GET A MESSAGE OUT.
OTHER THAN STANDING
AT THE DOOR AND YELLING
REALLY LOUDLY,
I DON'T REALLY KNOW
WHAT OUR OPTIONS ARE.
WE'RE TRAPPED.
FELICITY, VOICE-OVER:
DO YOU EVER FEEL LIKE
WE'RE TRAPPED?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
LIKE WE'RE TRAPPED
IN THIS VICIOUS CYCLE.
I MEAN, YOU PUT AN ARROW
IN ONE CRIME LORD,
AND ANOTHER JUST,
LIKE, POPS UP.
WELL, A LOT OF PEOPLE
ARE TRYING TO FILL
THE VACUUM LEFT
BY DAMIEN DARHK.
YEAH, AND THIS WEEK'S
WINNER IS WERNER ZYTLE.
UGH. DO YOU HAVE
A LOCATION ON HIM?
NOT YET, BUT CURTIS
IS WORKING ON FIXING
A TWENTY.
SOUNDS LIKE YOU DON'T
EVEN NEED ME.
HAVE YOU SEEN CURTIS
TRY TO THROW A PUNCH?
I MEAN, WE DON'T NEED YOU.
WE NEED 10 OF YOU.
NICE TRY.
IF WE HAD MORE BOOTS
ON THE GROUND
OR MASKS ON FACES
OR WHATEVER,
WE MIGHT ACTUALLY HAVE
A REAL POSSIBILITY
AT CATCHING ONE
OF THESE GUYS THAT IS
AUDITIONING TO BE
THE NEW DAMIEN DARHK.
I DON'T HAVE
THE BANDWIDTH
OR, MORE IMPORTANTLY,
THE TEMPERAMENT
TO TRAIN A NEW TEAM.
BESIDES, YOU'RE TRYING
TO FIX SOMETHING
THAT'S WORKING.
WE ARE A GOOD TEAM.
YEAH, WE ARE,
AND WE ALWAYS HAVE BEEN.
YEAH.
OH, MY GOD.
THAT'S A NASTY CUT.
OHH. WELL, IT'S
NOT GONNA SCAR, BUT I
WAS THINKING MAYBE...
MAYBE GETTING
SOME KEVLAR SLEEVES.
YOU KNOW ME TOO WELL.
CURTIS: AHEM.
HEY, GUYS.
-HEY.
-HI, CURTIS.
PALMER TECH HAS BEEN
WORKING ON AN ADVANCED
THERMAL IMAGING
PROTOTYPE,
WHICH I BORROWED,
TWEAKED, AND DEVELOPED
TO FIND...
BOOM!
BAD GUY ON A YACHT.
DANG.
THANK YOU FOR THE ASSIST.
SEE? HELP IS GOOD.
I WILL CONTACT YOU
WHEN I'M ON SITE.
CALL ME BACK, WILL YOU?
BETTER YET, JUST SHOW UP.
THINGS ARE GOING TO ALL
KINDS OF HELL AROUND HERE.
RENE: STILL NO LUCK?
NO.
[TELEPHONES RINGING]
IT'S LIKE OLIVER'S
DROPPED OFF THE FACE
OF THE EARTH AGAIN.
HOW'S IT GOING
OVER HERE?
WELL, EVERY DEFENSE ATTORNEY
IN TOWN JUST FOUND OUT
THAT THE D.A.
IS A SERIAL KILLER,
SO NOT GOOD.
YOU THINK THE COURT'S
GONNA OVERTURN
CHASE'S CONVICTIONS?
IF I DIDN'T, I WOULDN'T
HAVE CONVENED THIS WAR ROOM.
IT'D SURE BE NICE
TO HAVE A MAYOR
HEADING IT UP, THOUGH.
YOU HEARD
FROM FELICITY?
RADIO SILENCE,
BUT I GOT CURTIS.
-AND?
-HE'S GONNA CHECK AND SEE
IF OLIVER'S
AT THE BUNKER.
GET ON IT.
RENE ON PHONE:
YOU FIND OLIVER YET?
HEY, RENE.
YOU DO REALIZE
THAT YOU CALLED ME
LITERALLY 15 MINUTES
AGO, RIGHT?
BLAME IT ON LANCE.
GUY GETS FREAKY
WHEN HE'S WORRIED.
YEAH. WELL, LUCKY
FOR YOU, I CAN RUN FAST.
-WEIRD.
-WHAT'S WEIRD?
NO POWER.
WHOLE PLACE.
WHAT ARE THE CHANCES
THAT OLIVER FORGOT TO
PAY HIS ELECTRIC BILL?
INFINITESIMAL
CONSIDERING
I RIGGED THE PLACE
SO THAT IT'D BE
OFF THE GRID AND...
[EXPLOSION]
AND A BOMB
JUST WENT OFF.
-NOT FUNNY.
-I...I'M NOT KIDDING.
I HEARD SOME KIND
OF EXPLOSION.
FELICITY:
HOW MANY IS THAT?
11. HASN'T MADE
A DENT YET.
WHAT'S THAT THING
MADE OF ANYWAY?
KELTIUM. IT'S
A PROPRIETARY ALLOY
DEVELOPED
BY THE U.S. GOVERNMENT
TO REPEL NUCLEAR BLASTS.
SO YOU'RE SAYING EVEN
IF WE HAD A NUKE DOWN HERE,
IT WOULDN'T WORK?
SEEMS LIKE CISCO
DID SUCH A GOOD JOB
OF TURNING THIS PLACE INTO
AN IMPENETRABLE FORTRESS,
HE TURNED IT INTO AN
IMPENETRABLE DEATH TRAP.
CHASE DOESN'T
WANT TO KILL ME,
REMEMBER?
YEAH. HE JUST LOCKED
YOU DOWN HERE
FOR THE FUN OF IT.
HE LOCKED US DOWN HERE
BECAUSE HE IS
UP TO SOMETHING
UP THERE,
AND I CAN'T DO
ANYTHING ABOUT IT.
WELL, THE GOOD NEWS IS
THERE'S NOT MUCH LEFT
FOR HIM TO DO.
I MEAN, HE'S ALREADY
GONE AFTER CURTIS,
LANCE, EVELYN,
EVEN SUSAN,
AND THEA'S AWAY,
AND LYLA AND J.J.
HAVE ARGUS PROTECTION.
I MEAN, WHO'S LEFT?
WILLIAM.
WILLIAM'S
IN A DIFFERENT TOWN
WITH A DIFFERENT NAME
AND A DIFFERENT ADDRESS.
I'D BE SURPRISED
IF CHASE EVEN KNOWS
ABOUT WILLIAM.
WHEN HE WAS HOLDING
ME CAPTIVE,
HE...SHOWED ME
A PICTURE OF HIM.
WHAT? DOES HE...
HE DOESN'T KNOW
WHERE HE IS...YET.
WE HAVE TO GET OUT
OF HERE.
CISCO'S ORIGINAL BLUEPRINTS
ARE IN THAT CABINET.
IF YOU'RE JUST GONNA
STAND THERE,
YOU MIGHT AS WELL
SAY SOMETHING.
I THOUGHT YOU
WERE SLEEPING.
I COULDN'T SLEEP.
I KNOW YOU'RE UPSET.
I KNOW YOU THINK
THAT I'VE VIOLATED
SOME KIND OF TRUST
BETWEEN US, BUT...
LYLA.
WHEN YOU SAID THAT
YOU WOULDN'T BECOME
LIKE AMANDA WALLER,
I WAS WORRIED ABOUT YOU.
I'M FINE.
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO
SEEMS TO HAVE A PROBLEM
WITH THE WAY THAT
I'VE BEEN RUNNING ARGUS,
WHICH IS PARTICULARLY
INTERESTING TO ME
SINCE NEITHER ONE OF US
HAS A JOB THAT FITS
THE CONVENTIONAL
DEFINITION OF MORALITY.
WELL, WHAT'S THAT
SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
YOU'RE UPSET BECAUSE
ARGUS IS LOCKING PEOPLE UP
WITHOUT DUE PROCESS
WHEN YOU AND OLIVER
AND YOUR TEAM
OF MASKED RECRUITS
HAS BEEN PLAYING
JUDGE AND JURY
FOR YEARS NOW.
LYLA, I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU'D ACTUALLY COMPARE
TEAM ARROW
TO THIS...THIS...
THIS CLANDESTINE
GOVERNMENT SUPERAGENCY!
WELL, I JUST DID!
HEH.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
CURTIS: HELLO?
DIGGLE FAMILY?
ANYBODY HOME?
I DEFINITELY HEARD
LYLA YELLING.
KNOCK...KNOCK AGAIN.
LYLA: DIDN'T KNOW
WE WERE HAVING A PARTY.
RENE: I'M SENSING A LOT
OF MARITAL TENSION.
WHAT DO YOU GUYS
WANT?
DINAH: SO SORRY TO
INTERRUPT.
THERE'S A PROBLEM
AT THE BUNKER.
OLIVER: I CAN GET US
OUT OF HERE BY CLIMBING
UP THE ELEVATOR SHAFT.
IF YOU CAN THINK
ABOUT GOING
UP THE ELEVATOR,
CHASE HAS ALREADY
THOUGHT OF A WAY
TO STOP YOU.
SO YOU'RE SAYING
IT'S BOOBY-TRAPPED?
I'D BET MY COPIOUS
PALMER TECH SEVERANCE
PAY ON IT.
-I'M SAYING I CAN HANDLE IT.
-OR WE FIGURE OUT A NEW PLAN,
LIKE GETTING A SIGNAL
OUT TO THE TEAM.
YOU JUST SAID THAT
EVERYTHING WITH
AN ELECTRICAL CIRCUIT
DOWN HERE
HAS BEEN FRIED.
ONLY BECAUSE I HAVEN'T
FIGURED OUT HOW TO
GET POWER YET.
SO FIGURE OUT
HOW TO GET POWER,
AND I WILL GO
UP THE ELEVATOR SHAFT.
SERIOUSLY, ARE YOU STILL
NOT LISTENING TO ME?
DID THE EMP GIVE YOU
SHORT-TERM AMNESIA
ABOUT WHAT WE WERE
ARGUING ABOUT
DOWN HERE
IN THE FIRST PLACE?
THIS FEELS LIKE
THE BEST CHOICE RIGHT NOW.
BESIDES THE ONE
I JUST GAVE YOU.
[GRUNTS]
[CLICK]
UNH!
[GROANING]
FELICITY: I TOLD YOU SO,
I TOLD YOU SO, I TOLD YOU SO.
HOW MANY TIMES DO YOU
THINK THAT IS?
I WAS NOT KEEPING COUNT.
HMM. 11, I THINK,
BUT NOT NEARLY ENOUGH.
YOU READY?
BECAUSE YOUR
OPERATING THEATER
IS NOW LIT,
AND OF ALL THE THINGS
THAT WE NEED TO DO
TO GET OURSELVES OUT
OF THIS HERMETICALLY
SEALED BUNKER,
STITCHING UP A WOUND
FROM A FALL
THAT I TOTALLY PREDICTED
ISN'T ONE OF THEM.
I THINK THAT COUNTS
AS 12.
I...OK. I'M READY. UNH!
OHH!
-THAT HURT?
-YES. YES, IT DID.
I WON'T SAY "GOOD,"
BUT LET THE RECORD SHOW
I WAS TEMPTED.
DO YOU REMEMBER WHAT
WE WERE DISCUSSING
BEFORE WE GOT
EMP-BLASTED?
MM-HMM.
THE FACT THAT I BACK
YOUR PLAY
EVEN WHEN I DON'T AGREE,
BUT YOU DON'T HAVE THE SAME
CONSIDERATION FOR ME.
YOU DIDN'T LISTEN TO ME
WHEN I WANTED TO JOIN HELIX.
WITH GOOD REASON.
I COULD SAY THE SAME
THING ABOUT YOU
A MILLION TIMES OVER,
BUT I SUPPORT YOU
BECAUSE I TRUST YOU.
FELICITY, I TRUST YOU.
REALLY? BECAUSE
THE HOLE IN YOU BACK
SAYS OTHERWISE.
FAIR ENOUGH.
THAT THE PAINKILLERS
TALKING?
IF YOU HAVE A PLAN
THAT WILL GET US
OUT HERE, FANTASTIC.
LET'S FINISH THIS UP,
AND LET'S TRY IT.
OK.
RENE: WHAT'S AN EDM?
SOMETHING YOU MIGHT HEAR
AT A NIGHTCLUB?
THIS WAS AN EMP.
ACTUALLY, FUN FACT,
THE PREVIOUS LAIR USED TO
BE UNDERNEATH A NIGHTCLUB.
-CURTIS.
-RIGHT. SORRY.
LYLA: AND YOU
SAID FELICITY'S
DOWN THERE, TOO?
ACCORDING TO THE LAST
POSITION LOGGED
BY HER TRACKING NANITES.
WHAT DO WE NEED
TO GET THEM OUT?
RAPPELLING GEAR,
ACETYLENE TORCHES,
WIDEBAND
ACTIVE FIELD PROBES,
TUNGSTEN CARBIDE
DRILL BITS.
I CAN COBBLE TOGETHER
MOST OF THOSE THINGS, BUT...
LYLA: TEXT ME A LIST
OF WHATEVER YOU NEED.
ARGUS IS
AT YOUR DISPOSAL.
-GREAT.
-IF THAT'S OK WITH YOU.
DINAH: I HATE
TO ASK THIS,
BUT HOW MUCH AIR
DO THEY HAVE LEFT
DOWN THERE?
WELL, IF THEY DON'T
EXERT THEMSELVES,
5, MAYBE 6 HOURS.
OK. WE'RE HERE.
NOW WHAT?
THE MAINFRAME HAS
A BUILT-IN CELLULAR CHIP,
BUT OUR REWIRE DIDN'T
GENERATE ENOUGH KILOWATTS
TO JUMP-START IT.
RIGHT BECAUSE EVERYTHING
WITH AN ELECTRONIC
CIRCUIT IS FRIED.
EVERYTHING
WITH AN ELECTRONIC CIRCUIT.
MY OLD BIKE.
FELICITY: SHE'S A BEAUT,
GOOD OLD-FASHIONED
COMBUSTION ENGINE.
SO WE CAN GENERATE
ELECTRICITY
WITHOUT AN ELECTRONIC
STARTER.
-OH, YEAH.
-THAT IS SMART.
SCPD IS HAPPY TO HAVE
ZYTLE OFF THE STREETS
OR, MORE APPROPRIATELY,
OFF THE DOCKS.
-GREAT. SO MISSION ACCOMPLISHED.
-YEAH.
WHAT'S NEXT FOR MY
FAVORITE POWER COUPLE?
-POWER COUPLE?
-YEAH.
I THOUGHT THAT YOU
AND OLIVER...
YOU GUYS AREN'T
HOOKING UP AGAIN?
-OH, NO. NO. GOD, NO.
-OH!
WHY WOULD YOU EVEN
THINK THAT?
WELL, BECAUSE EVERY TIME
I COME BY,
YOU GUYS ARE IN THE MIDDLE
OF EXCHANGING
LONGING LOOKS
FOR EACH OTHER.
-NO, WE'RE NOT.
-OH, FELICITY.
-WE LOOK NOTHING LIKE THAT.
-"I MISS OLIVER.
WISH I DIDN'T
BREAK UP WITH HIM. OHH."
WHAT? WHAT?!
"YOU KNOW, WE WERE
SO HAPPY TOGETHER."
-WERE.
-YEAH.
-PAST TENSE. YES.
-LOOK. I KNOW THAT HE HURT YOU
BY NOT TELLING YOU
ABOUT HIS SON, BUT...
LOOK. IT'S NOT
ABOUT WILLIAM.
IT'S ABOUT WHAT WILLIAM
REPRESENTS.
OLIVER HAVING SEX
WITH ANOTHER WOMAN.
NO, BUT THANK YOU
FOR THAT VISUAL.
WILLIAM IS SYMPTOMATIC
OF A LARGER PROBLEM
BETWEEN OLIVER AND I.
THAT BEING?
OLIVER DOESN'T
TRUST ME.
RIGHT. THE MAN WHO HAS
PUT HIS LIFE IN YOUR HANDS
A COUPLE THOUSAND TIMES.
TRUSTING ME AS OVERWATCH
IS ONE THING,
BUT WE'RE TALKING
ABOUT HIS SON.
CURTIS, HIS CHILD.
IF OLIVER DOESN'T
TRUST ME ENOUGH TO SHARE
IMPORTANT INFORMATION
AND CRUCIAL INFORMATION
WITH ME,
WHAT'S THE POINT OF BEING
IN A RELATIONSHIP AT ALL?
I'M NOT GONNA SAY
THAT OLIVER QUEEN PLAYS
GREAT WITH OTHERS.
-BUT?
-BUT HE CAN STILL CHANGE
THAT ABOUT HIMSELF.
-TCH.
-YOU KNOW WHAT HE CAN'T CHANGE?
WHAT?
THAT WAY HE LOOKS
AT YOU.
YOU BOTH OWE IT
TO EACH OTHER TO SEE,
FELICITY, TONIGHT.
TONIGHT? NO.
WHY TONIGHT?
-WELL...
-DON'T.
OLIVER: CURTIS, NEXT TIME...
PICK UP YOUR OWN
CHINESE FOOD.
CURTIS: UM, YOU KNOW,
I JUST THOUGHT WE'D
ALL BE HUNGRY
FROM THE CRIMEFIGHTING.
HEH HEH. YEAH. OH!
OH, MAN. I...YOU KNOW,
I JUST REMEMBERED
I HAVE A DATE NIGHT
WITH PAUL, MY HUSBAND.
I HAVE A DATE
WITH MY HUSBAND,
SO I...I HAVE TO GO
TO THAT.
YOU GUYS ENJOY
THAT, THOUGH.
YOU ENJOY THAT.
ALSO, THERE IS WINE
IN THE GARAGE,
SO...BYE.
WHAT?
I'LL GO GET THE WINE.
OK, GENTLEMEN.
EYES ARE UP.
RENE: GOT TO SAY
THIS TEAM IS NEVER BORING.
DIDN'T THINK I'D BE
DOING THIS WHEN I
WOKE UP THIS MORNING.
OLIVER AND FELICITY
MIGHT SUFFOCATE.
HOW CAN YOU BE SO GLIB?
YOU'VE MET ME, RIGHT,
AND HOW COME
YOUR TOY BALLS CAN'T
FLOAT DOWN THERE
AND DO THIS FOR US?
FOR THE THOUSANDTH
TIME, RENE, THEY'RE
CALLED T-SPHERES,
BUT IF YOU WANT,
CALL THEM BY THEIR
PROPER NAME.
YOU NAMED THEM?
KODO AND PODO. HEH.
YOU KNOW, DAR'S
THIEVING LITTLE FERRETS
ON "THE BEASTMASTER."
LET'S JUST SAY
A YOUNG MARC SINGER
WAS QUITE HELPFUL
IN ME DISCOVERING
MY HOMOSEXUALITY.
DINAH:
AND MY HETEROSEXUALITY.
YOU'RE ON AN OPEN CHANNEL
BY THE WAY.
OPEN LINE.
CURTIS: LOOK. I CAN'T GET
MY T-SPHERES BECAUSE
THEY ARE IN THE BUNKER
AND THEREFORE FRIED.
SO WHATEVER.
I SWEAR THOSE TWO
ARE GOING TO MAKE
THE CUTEST COUPLE
ONE DAY.
JOHN? JOHN?
YEAH.
ANYTHING IN PARTICULAR
YOU'RE LOOKING FOR
WITH THAT
THOUSAND-YARD STARE?
IT'S THAT OBVIOUS, HUH?
RENE WASN'T THE ONLY ONE
WHO COULD CLOCK TENSION
BETWEEN YOU
AND THE MISSUS,
IF THAT'S WHAT YOU MEAN.
RIGHT.
LET ME GUESS.
YOU CONFRONTED LYLA
ABOUT THE ARGUS
BLACK SITE,
AND IT DIDN'T GO
TOO GOOD.
SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
YOU WANT TO TALK
ABOUT IT?
NOT REALLY.
OK.
WELL, IF YOU DID,
I'D TELL YOU
ABOUT VINNIE AND ME.
VINNIE?
MY UNDERCOVER PARTNER
ON AND OFF THE JOB.
WORKING UC, WE HAD TO
KEEP CERTAIN THINGS
FROM EACH OTHER,
AND WE DIDN'T DO IT
BECAUSE WE WANTED TO.
WE DID IT BECAUSE
WE HAD TO.
[DOOR OPENS]
OK. IT TOOK SOME
HORSE TRADING,
BUT I GOT EVERYTHING
CURTIS ASKED FOR.
-OH, GREAT.
-WHAT'S THE STATUS HERE?
HE AND RENE ARE
GETTING THE LAY
OF THE LAND.
KODO AND PODO,
ANY UPDATES?
CURTIS: NO GOOD ONES.
THE EMP FRIED
THE HYDRAULICS SYSTEM.
WE HAVE TO CUT
THROUGH THE MAGNETIC SEAL
IN ORDER TO REACH
THE MANUAL OVERRIDE.
WE'RE GONNA NEED
THE ACETYLENE TORCH.
AND THE WIDEBAND
ACTIVE FIELD PROBE.
WITHOUT MY T-SPHERES,
THERE'S NO TELLING
WHAT'S ON THE OTHER SIDE
OF THIS THING AFTER
THE EMP BLAST.
[ENGINE REVS, RUNNING]
-IS IT WORKING?
-GIVE IT A SECOND.
THANKS AGAIN FOR TRYING
THINGS MY WAY.
FIRST TIME
FOR EVERYTHING.
REGARDING HELIX,
YOU KNOW WHY I DIDN'T
BACK YOUR PLAY,
AND YOU KNOW...
OR YOU SHOULD...
THAT IT HAD NOTHING
TO DO WITH A LACK
OF TRUST.
IF YOU'RE GOING TO START
SAYING YET AGAIN
THAT IT'S BECAUSE YOU DON'T
WANT ME TO BE LIKE YOU,
YOU CAN HOLD YOUR BREATH,
PARTICULARLY SINCE WE
ARE RUNNING OUT OF OXYGEN.
CAYDEN JAMES IS
A CRIMINAL...
CAYDEN JAMES IS A HACKER,
AS IN SO MUCH LESS WORSE
THAN THE BRATVA.
I MADE THE EXACT SAME
TRADEOFF YOU DID
TO GET CHASE.
I PICKED THE LESSER
OF TWO EVILS.
THE FACT THAT I DIDN'T
WANT YOU TO DO THAT
DOESN'T MAKE ME
A HYPOCRITE.
-WHAT DOES IT MAKE YOU, THEN?
-IT MAKES ME SOMEONE
WHO DOESN'T WANT YOU
TO...BE LIKE ME.
YEAH.
[MAINFRAME POWERING UP]
BAM! THAT'S WHAT
I'M TALKING ABOUT!
[ENGINE SPUTTERING]
[HISSING]
-ARE YOU OK?
-YEAH, DEPENDING ON WHAT
THAT SOUND IS.
THAT'S NOT GOOD.
ONE OF THE PIPES IS DAMAGED.
I JUST HOPE IT'S NOT
THE HIGHLY TOXIC
AND FLAMMABLE GAS PIPE.
SO MUCH FOR DOING
THINGS MY WAY.
FELICITY: CAREFUL.
DON'T BREATHE!
WELL, BREATHE,
BUT DON'T INHALE.
[COUGHING]
-DONE.
-YOU OK?
YEAH, YEAH, I'M FINE.
I'M A LITTLE, UH...
A LITTLE LIGHTHEADED.
FELICITY: OK.
OLIVER.
HOW MUCH MORE
DUCT TAPE DO WE HAVE?
[SIGHS]
THAT WAS THE LAST
OF IT.
UM, WE HAVE
THE EPOXY SPRAY
THAT CISCO GAVE US
TO FIX OUR SUITS.
IT'S UPSTAIRS,
AND THAT'S DEFINITELY
FLOODED BY NOW.
HOW MUCH TIME
DO WE HAVE?
20 MINUTES MAX
BEFORE WE ASPHYXIATE.
GOOD TIMES, RIGHT?
OLIVER, WE'VE ALREADY
GONE OVER THAT.
IT'S JUST FULL
OF DEAD ENDS,
WHICH IS AN UNFORTUNATE
BUT ACCURATE CHOICE
OF WORDS.
-WAIT A SECOND.
-YEAH, WE CAN WAIT.
WE ONLY HAVE 20 MINUTES,
BUT WE CAN WAIT.
THERE'S A STEAM TUNNEL
UNDERNEATH THIS PART
OF THE BUNKER.
DO WE HAVE ANYTHING
TO PRY THIS OPEN?
I DON'T KNOW. IT DOESN'T
LOOK PRYABLE.
FELICITY, THIS IS IT.
OK. THIS COULD BE
THE FUMES TALKING,
BUT I THINK I HAVE
A SLIGHTLY INSANE IDEA.
HOW INSANE
IS "SLIGHTLY INSANE"?
WELL, THAT DEPENDS
ON HOW YOU FEEL
ABOUT SETTING OFF
AN EXPLOSIVE ARROW
IN A ROOM FULL
OF FLAMMABLE GAS.
CAREFUL, RENE.
THAT SEAL IS
PURE TITANIUM.
IT HAS A MELTING POINT
OF BETWEEN 1,600
AND 1,700 DEGREES CELSIUS.
JUST LET ME DO
MY THING, HOSS.
[DEVICE BEEPING]
[LOUD BEEP]
THAT'S WEIRD.
THAT WOULD MEAN...
NO, NO, NO! RENE, STOP!
AGH!
[BOTH PANTING]
OW, OW, OW,
OW, OW! OW! OW!
I'M GONNA NEED YOU TO
STOP MAKING THAT NOISE.
I'M SORRY MY AGONIZING PAIN
IS BOTHERING YOU.
I MEAN, THANK YOU VERY MUCH
FOR HELPING ME WITH THIS.
THESE ARE JUST
SECOND-DEGREE
BURNS, CURTIS.
YOU SHOULD BE
JUST FINE
IN A COUPLE
OF WEEKS.
DO WE KNOW WHAT
CAUSED THE EXPLOSION?
HIGH LEVELS OF METHANE.
AM I THE ONLY ONE
THAT THINKS THIS
IS PROMETHEUS?
NO, BUT WE NEED TO
FIND A WAY OF SAVING
OUR FRIENDS
WITHOUT BLOWING
THEM UP.
-WHAT ABOUT ACID?
-NO.
NO. I DON'T THINK
THAT WILL WORK.
WAIT, WAIT.
YOU SAID THE HATCH
WAS TITANIUM, RIGHT?
YEAH.
HYDROCHLORIC ACID
WILL TURN IT
INTO SWISS CHEESE.
I USED TO WORK
UNDERCOVER WITH A GANG
OF SAFE CRACKERS.
JOHN: THAT'S GOOD.
LET'S GET COOKING.
[GAS HISSING]
CAREFUL!
IF THE POWDER IS
ONE GRAM UNDER,
THE GRATING WON'T BLOW.
WHAT IF IT'S
ONE GRAM OVER?
WELL, IT WILL INCREASE
THE BREACHING RADIUS,
IGNITING THE GAS,
FILLING THIS ENTIRE
PLACE WITH FIRE, AND...
IT WILL KILL US BOTH
WAS WHAT YOU WERE
GONNA SAY, RIGHT?
YEAH.
-NO PRESSURE. CAREFUL.
-MM-HMM. YEP.
-WAIT.
-WHAT?
MY MATH IS
PROBABLY RIGHT,
BUT WHAT IF IT'S WRONG?
ARE YOU STILL
FELICITY SMOAK?
-YEAH.
-YOUR MATH IS ALWAYS RIGHT.
RIGHT.
OK. UM, THE ARROW
NEEDS TO GO IN
AT EXACTLY
A 45-DEGREE ANGLE.
OK. AHEM. BY EXACTLY,
DO YOU MEAN EXACTLY?
WELL, ONE
CENTIMETER OFF,
AND THE BLAST
WILL FORCE
THE GRATE OFF,
IGNITING THE GAS, AND...
PLEASE DON'T MISS.
YOU DIDN'T MISS.
LOOKS LIKE ABOUT
A TWO-STORY DROP.
DROP?
I'LL GET
THE CLIMBING GEAR.
FELICITY: REMIND ME
AGAIN WHY I THOUGHT
THIS WAS GONNA BE
A FUN IDEA.
I DON'T KNOW.
HOP DOWN, HOP DOWN,
HOP DOWN.
-OHH!
-EXCUSE ME.
OW!
RIGHT. OK. SO...
THIS IS JUST
A CHIN-UP.
-OK.
-EVERYBODY KNOWS A CHIN-UP.
-WELL...
-ALL RIGHT. IT'S A CHIN-UP
WITH A FLOURISH
AT THE END.
YEAH. I CAN'T DO
A CHIN-UP.
-COME HERE.
-OK.
UM...
-I DON'T FLOURISH WELL.
-I BELIEVE IN YOU.
-OH.
-READY?
WHOA! OH, MY GOD!
OHH! HEY.
I'M CHINNING AND UPPING.
-KIND OF.
-OOH!
-OK.
-OH, OW. YEAH.
-ALL RIGHT.
-OK.
-YOU READY?
-MM-HMM.
1, 2, 3, GO!
NOPE, NOPE, NOPE.
HELP, HELP, HELP.
-THAT'S TOO HIGH.
-HANG ON. I GOT YOU.
OH, GOD. THAT'S HIGHER
THAN IT WAS BEFORE.
I GOT YOU.
UH, YEAH. I KIND OF
DID IT, I THINK.
-SURE.
-THERE WAS THE CHIN-UP PART
I THINK WE COULD
WORK ON.
-YOU DID A HALF OF ONE.
-HALF. I'LL TAKE THE HALF.
SORRY. I DON'T THINK
THAT'S REALLY MY THING.
IN FAIRNESS, YOU'VE
HAD A LITTLE BIT TO DRINK.
-AHEM.
-I'VE HAD A LOT TO DRINK.
OK.
ACTUALLY, COULD YOU
JUST...THANK YOU.
JOHN: WHAT HAPPENED?
DID THE ACID WORK?
YEAH. IT'S JUST
IT'S GONNA TAKE
10 SEASONS
OF "THE BACHELOR"
BEFORE IT MELTS
THOSE HINGES DOWN.
WHAT? I DON'T JUDGE
YOUR DVR.
OK. HOW MUCH TIME
DO THEY HAVE LEFT?
RENE: 10 MINUTES,
GIVE OR TAKE.
YEAH. SOMEBODY BETTER
ORDER UP A MIRACLE.
LYLA: I DON'T KNOW
IF THIS COUNTS,
BUT IT COULD HELP.
WHERE THE HELL
DID YOU GET THIS?
ARGUS LIKES TO KEEP
TABS ON INTERESTING TECH.
YOU COPIED MY T-SPHERE?
NO. WE IMPROVED THEM.
JOHN: NO. YOU'RE
BOTH WRONG.
LYLA, IF YOU
STOLE THIS,
WHAT OTHER SURPRISES
CAN I BE EXPECTING
FROM YOU?
-WHOA!
-OHH!
THAT'S OK. JUST
HANG...HANG ON
TIGHT.
NOT THAT TIGHT.
THAT'S OK.
-ALMOST THERE.
-OK.
OK. I GOT YOU,
I GOT YOU, I GOT
YOU, I GOT YOU.
OK.
-ALL RIGHT.
-WE'RE HERE.
-YEAH, I KNOW.
-THANKS. OK.
ARE YOU OK?
HEY!
-YEAH. I'M FINE.
-WE MADE IT, WE MADE IT.
-WE MADE IT.
-YEP.
PLEASE.
[SIGHS]
IT'S ANOTHER
DEAD END.
OK. PLEASE STOP
USING THAT TERM.
WE BOUGHT OURSELVES
SOME TIME AWAY
FROM THE GAS AT LEAST.
HEY. OLIVER.
OLIVER!
OLIVER! OLIVER!
HEY, HEY, HEY.
YOU GOT TO STAY
AWAKE, OK?
I THINK I'M LOSING
A LOT OF BLOOD.
TELL ME SOMETHING
I DON'T KNOW.
I'M SO SORRY.
NORMALLY, I WOULD RELISH
AN OLIVER QUEEN APOLOGY,
BUT THIS SUDDEN ADMISSION
IS MAKING ME NERVOUS.
YOU WERE RIGHT.
I DIDN'T HAVE YOUR BACK,
BUT IT WASN'T BECAUSE I
DIDN'T WANT YOU
TO END UP LIKE ME,
FELICITY.
-IT WAS MUCH MORE THAN THAT.
-OK. LOTS OF BLOOD LOSS
WITH EXPOSURE
TO TOXIC GAS MAKES
YOU GO CRAZY.
NOW WE KNOW THAT.
-I NEED YOU TO HEAR THIS.
-I WILL LATER, RIGHT?
-I MIGHT NOT HAVE A LATER.
-DO NOT TALK LIKE THAT.
I NEED YOU TO KNOW
THE TRUTH.
ABOUT WHAT?
I DIDN'T HAVE YOUR BACK.
IT WAS NOT
BECAUSE OF YOU
OR LACK OF TRUST.
IT WAS BECAUSE OF ME.
I'M NOT THE MAN
YOU THINK I AM.
I'M NOT THE MAN YOU
FELL IN LOVE WITH.
I PUT THE HOOD ON
TO RIGHT MY
FATHER'S WRONGS,
BUT THE BASIS OF IT,
THE...THE FOUNDATION
OF IT
AND WHAT YOU DID
AND WHAT DIG DID
AND WHAT THE TEAM DID
IN MY NAME,
IT WAS ALL BASED
ON A LIE.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
CHASE...HE SHOWED ME
WHEN HELD ME HOSTAGE
THAT I DIDN'T DO
WHAT I DID TO BE A HERO.
I DID WHAT I DID...
BECAUSE THERE WAS
A PART OF ME...
A BIGGER PART THAN
I WOULD LIKE TO ADMIT...
I ENJOYED IT.
I ENJOYED KILLING.
IT'S NOT ABOUT
NOT TRUSTING YOU.
I WILL ALWAYS TRUST YOU.
I DON'T TRUST MYSELF.
OLIVER, OLIVER, DON'T.
OLIVER, OLIVER.
HEY! HEY!
OLIVER, COME BACK!
COME BACK! OLIVER!
COME BACK.
PROMISE ME YOU'RE NOT
GONNA TELL ANYONE
THAT WE HAD BUNKER SEX,
AND BY ANYONE,
I MEAN CURTIS
BECAUSE HE'D NEVER
LOOK AT ME THE SAME.
ARE YOU SURE?
BECAUSE HE HAD ME
PICK UP CHINESE FOOD,
AND THEN HE
SUGGESTED WINE.
I'M PRETTY SURE THAT
HE WAS ROOTING
FOR EXACTLY THIS,
SO...
MAYBE HE SAW SOMETHING
THAT WE DIDN'T SEE.
I THINK CURTIS WATCHES
TOO MANY ROMCOMS WITH PAUL.
YOU OK?
YEAH, I'M FINE.
IT'S JUST...
TALK TO ME.
WHAT'S GOING ON.
THIS WAS NICE, YOU KNOW.
IT WAS REALLY NICE.
IT JUST...
IT DOESN'T CHANGE
THINGS BETWEEN US.
WE STILL HAVE
OUR PROBLEMS.
BECAUSE WE NEVER TALKED
ABOUT OUR PROBLEMS.
WE NEVER TALKED
ABOUT WILLIAM.
EVEN IF THERE WAS
NO WILLIAM,
THERE STILL
WOULDN'T BE AN US...
BECAUSE YOU DON'T
TRUST ME.
I WAS HOPING THAT
YOU'D CHANGE...
BUT YOU DON'T
TRUST ANYONE,
AND I DON'T KNOW WHY.
YOU KNOW, MAYBE
IF I KNEW WHY,
THINGS WOULD BE
DIFFERENT.
I DON'T EVEN THINK
YOU KNOW WHY.
I LOVE YOU...
BUT THAT IS WHY I CAN'T
SETTLE FOR ANYTHING LESS
THAN YOUR FULL TRUST.
I KNOW I SHOULD
BE MAD THAT YOU
STOLE MY TECH,
BUT THE MODIFICATION
DESIGNS YOU GUYS
PUT ON HERE
ARE RIDONCULOUS.
HEY. HOW ABOUT
LESS GEEKING OUT
AND MORE FIGURING OUT
HOW TO USE THAT THING
TO GET TO FELICITY
AND OLIVER?
THEY RAN OUT OF TIME
10 MINUTES AGO.
WHAT IS THIS?
IT'S AN AUDIT
OF EVERY BLACK OP
I'VE SIGNED OFF ON
AS DIRECTOR
OF ARGUS.
WHY ARE YOU
GIVING ME THIS?
I DON'T WANT THERE
TO BE ANY MORE SECRETS
BETWEEN US, JOHN,
BUT THERE IS ONE THING
I NEED TO KNOW FROM YOU.
NAME IT.
NO MATTER WHAT
OLIVER QUEEN DOES,
NO MATTER HOW
MORALLY COMPROMISING,
YOU STAND BEHIND HIM.
-LYLA.
-NO MATTER WHAT.
WHY CAN'T YOU DO
THAT FOR ME?
[SCOFFS]
[SIGHS]
LYLA, I GUESS I NEVER
REALLY THOUGHT OF IT
LIKE THAT.
WELL, MAYBE YOU
SHOULD START
BECAUSE I'M NOT OLIVER,
JOHNNIE.
I'M YOUR WIFE,
AND EVEN THOUGH
I DISAGREED
WITH MANY
OF YOUR CHOICES,
I TRUSTED THOSE CHOICES.
I TRUSTED YOU.
I THINK I DESERVE
THE SAME CONSIDERATION.
CURTIS:
I FIGURED IT OUT!
OH. SORRY. WERE YOU
GUYS IN THE MIDDLE
OF SOMETHING?
IT LOOKS LIKE YOU
WERE PROBABLY IN THE
MIDDLE OF SOMETHING,
BUT I DID FIGURE IT
OUT, SO LET'S...
CHOP, CHOP, CHOP.
IT'S OK, CURTIS.
WE'RE FINE.
LET'S GO GET OLIVER
AND FELICITY OUT OF THERE.
OLIVER? OLIVER!
OH, DAMN IT.
WAKE UP.
HEY. AGH! OHH.
ARE YOU OK?
OH, MY GOD.
YOU'RE OK.
I THINK THE WOUND
RECLOTTED. UGH.
CAREFUL. HEY.
FELICITY, I DON'T...
I DON'T KNOW THAT
I CAN GET US
OUT OF HERE.
WELL, IT WILL
GIVE US SOME TIME
TO TALK ABOUT SOMETHING,
LIKE THIS CRAZY IDEA
THAT YOU ENJOY KILLING.
[SIGHS]
[COUGHS]
THAT'S WHY YOU DISBANDED
THE TEAM, ISN'T IT?
YEAH.
OLIVER, YOU SAID THAT
I DON'T KNOW
THE KIND OF MAN
THAT YOU ARE.
I WOULDN'T HAVE FALLEN
IN LOVE WITH YOU
OR WANTED TO MARRY YOU
IF I DIDN'T KNOW
EXACTLY THE KIND
OF MAN THAT YOU ARE.
CHASE TORTURED YOU
FOR A WEEK.
YOU'RE THE TOUGHEST
PERSON I KNOW,
BUT ANYONE...ANYONE
WOULD HAVE ADMITTED
TO BEING A TAP-DANCING
FLAMINGO
AFTER WHAT HE PUT
YOU THROUGH.
ADRIAN CHASE DIDN'T
MAKE ME A KILLER.
NO. 5 YEARS IN HELL
DID THAT,
5 YEARS DEALING
WITH THE CITY'S
WORST DID THAT.
YOU HAVE SPENT
A DECADE DEALING
WITH HORRORS
THAT MOST PEOPLE DON'T
EVEN REALIZE EXIST,
AND THE FACT THAT
THAT DIDN'T TURN YOU
INTO A MONSTER
PROVES EXACTLY THE KIND
OF PERSON THAT YOU ARE.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT KIND
OF PERSON I AM.
HEY.
CURTIS?
LYLA: NOT JUST CURTIS.
ARE YOU GUYS OK?
OLIVER IS A LITTLE HURT.
WE COULD USE YOUR HELP.
RENE: ABOUT THAT.
WE GOT A NEW PROBLEM.
THE BUNKER'S GENERATORS
HAVE A DOOMSDAY
SCENARIO FAILSAFE.
ASSUMING
A CATASTROPHIC ATTACK,
THEY'RE TAMPER-PROOF,
SO NO ONE CAN STOP THEM
FROM TURNING BACK ON.
OLIVER:WAIT. WHY WOULD
YOU WANT TO STOP THEM?
THE METHANE. THE POWER
COMING BACK ON
WILL SPARK IT.
IF WE DON'T GET
THE AIR VENTS
BACK ONLINE
FIRST SOMEHOW.
YOU GUYS ARE SITTING
UNDERNEATH A...
4-STORY BOMB.
[DEVICE BEEPING]
HOW LONG DO WE HAVE
BEFORE THE GENERATOR
KICKS BACK ON?
CURTIS:AND BLOW YOU UP?
12 MINUTES,
BUT DON'T WORRY.
-TOO LATE.
-WE HAVE A PLAN.
JOHN: CAREFUL.
WE GOT TO BE
GETTING CLOSE.
[GASPS]
THINK WE'RE THERE, D.
LYLA:TALK TO ME, CURTIS.
I'M TRYING TO HACK
THE CITY GRID
TO REROUTE POWER
TO THE VENTILATION SYSTEM.
CAN YOU BLOW THE GAS
BEFORE THE GENERATORS
COME BACK ONLINE?
WELL, WE'LL KNOW IF WE
HEAR AN EARTH-SHATTERING
KABOOM BENEATH OUR FEET.
SLOW DOWN, SLOW DOWN.
WE DON'T HAVE TIME
TO SLOW DOWN.
YEAH? WELL, WE DON'T HAVE
TIME FOR YOU TO BLEED
TO DEATH EITHER.
-OK?
-THAT'S A GOOD POINT.
-THAT'S GOOD.
-OLIVER. OLLIE!
OLIVER. AGH.
OLIVER, OLIVER.
CURTIS, OLIVER'S DOWN.
WE NEED YOUR HELP!
HANG ON.
COMING TO YOU.
THIS LOOKS LIKE
THE DEATH STAR
INTERROGATION DROID.
I LOADED IT
WITH 20 CCS
OF ADRENALINE.
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE
TO INJECT THAT
INTO OLIVER...
[GASPS]
WHOA!
OHH, OHH, OHH!
-I'M OK!
-NOWHERE CLOSE,
BUT WE GAVE YOU
ENOUGH ADRENALINE TO
GET US OUT OF HERE.
OHH!
-GOOD. OK. ALL RIGHT.
-OK. YUP!
DINAH: ARE YOU REALLY
GONNA CLIMB DOWN THERE?
SOMEBODY HAS TO MEET
THEM HALFWAY.
NICE JUMP, DIG.
JOHN!
ARE YOU OK?!
I'M GOOD.
LYLA: WE ARE RUNNING
OUT OF TIME.
I'VE ALMOST GOT
THE VENTILATION
SYSTEMS BACK UP.
OLIVER! OLIVER!
-YEAH!
-HEY!
HEY. YOU GUYS
ALL RIGHT?
NO, NOT REALLY.
OHH!
JOHN!
AGH!
YOU OK?
STAY THERE,
AND WE'LL FIGURE
SOMETHING OUT.
JOHN, WE DON'T
HAVE TIME!
LOOK. DO YOU HAVE ENOUGH
CABLE TO MEET US HALFWAY?
YES!
THAT'S OPTIMISTIC.
WE ONLY HAVE 30 FEET.
THAT'S NOT HELPING.
THROW HIM THE LINE.
THIS IS CRAZY.
DON'T HEAR ME
ARGUING, DO YOU?
-ALL RIGHT. HANG ON TIGHT.
-YEAH.
I'VE ALWAYS APPRECIATED
YOU DOING THE SALMON LADDER
BUT NEVER AS MUCH
AS IN THIS MOMENT.
OH! UH!
[INDISTINCT MUTTERING]
JOHN: I GOT ABOUT
5 FEET OF SLACK.
I CAN MAKE IT.
OLIVER,
IF YOU DON'T...
I WILL.
[BEEPING]
[GRUNTING]
FELICITY: OHH!
OH, MY GOD.
YOU HAVE TO LET ME GO.
YOU HAVE TO GO!
JOHN: CURTIS,
CUT THE VENTS.
-NOW HE TELLS ME?
-DO IT!
I'M SORRY, FELICITY.
[GROANING]
OHH!
I KNOW YOU HATE IT
WHEN I DON'T LISTEN TO YOU.
RENE, PULL US UP.
[MOTOR RUNNING]
HEY, LYLA.
THANKS FOR LETTING US
COME HERE.
SEE? ARGUS ISN'T ALWAYS
USED FOR EVIL.
I KNOW. YOU WERE RIGHT.
I SHOULD HAVE
TRUSTED YOU.
I...I DO TRUST YOU.
WE JUST WORK IN MORALLY
GRAY AREAS, LYLA,
AND I...I LET THAT CLOUD
MY PERSPECTIVE A BIT.
-OR A LOT.
I'M SORRY...
BUT I PROMISE WE WILL
GET THROUGH THIS.
OK.
HEY. ANY WORD
ON OLIVER?
LYLA'S CHECKING NOW.
GOT TO SAY IT'S
GOOD TO SEE YOU UP
AND WALKING AGAIN.
FELICITY: YEAH.
THANK CURTIS.
HE'S THE MIRACLE WORKER.
IT'S JUST
A TEMPORARY FIX.
I'LL HAVE TO RUN
MORE COMPREHENSIVE
DIAGNOSTICS.
YOU GUYS ARE
GONNA HAVE TO
EXPLAIN TO ME
HOW ALL THIS WORKS
ONE DAY.
YOU REALLY DON'T WANT
THEM TO DO THAT.
NERDAPALOOZA.
LYLA: OLIVER JUST GOT
OUT OF SURGERY.
HE'S GOING TO BE FINE.
-CAN WE SEE HIM.
-ACTUALLY, HE ASKED TO SEE YOU.
OOH! HEY. HEH.
WE WERE ALL
THINKING THAT.
WOULD IT HELP IF I DIDN'T
ASK FOR LESSONS
ON A PARTICULAR PIECE
OF EQUIPMENT?
LOOK. I KNOW YOU'RE
PROBABLY A LITTLE UPSET
ABOUT WHAT I SAID
LAST NIGHT STILL.
I'M NOT MAD.
-YOU WERE RIGHT.
-SO WERE YOU.
YOU KNOW, WE NEVER
REALLY DID TALK
ABOUT ANYTHING, AND...
I WALKED.
THAT WAS WRONG.
I'M SORRY.
THANK YOU.
I'M NOT SAYING NEVER
ABOUT THE TALK.
I JUST...
MAYBE NOT QUITE YET.
I'M NOT READY YET.
I'M NOT GOING
ANYWHERE.
OK.
[HEART MONITOR BEEPING]
HEY.
YOU'RE WALKING.
I AM.
MORE IMPORTANTLY,
YOU'RE LIVING.
YOU REALLY GAVE US
A SCARE BACK THERE.
OH, I FIGURED YOU'D
BE USED TO SEEING ME
CLOSE TO DEATH BY NOW.
HEH HEH HEH.
NEVER GONNA GET
USED TO IT EVER.
BUT SPEAKING
OF BEING CLOSE TO DEATH,
UH...
I SAID A FEW THINGS
BACK THERE.
I REALLY, REALLY
APPRECIATE WHAT YOU SAID.
ANY OF IT STICK?
HOPEFULLY.
-I'M SORRY.
-FOR WHAT.
FOR BEING
A HYPOCRITE.
YOU WERE RIGHT.
I WAS STARTING TO
BECOME LIKE YOU
AND NOT IN THE HEROIC,
HONORABLE, MUSCULAR WAY.
IT WAS JUST
AFTER I LOST BILLY,
I WAS WILLING TO DO
WHATEVER TO GET CHASE.
IT DROVE ME TO WORK
WITH HELIX,
AND I WAS WILLING
TO BREAK ANY RULE
OR DO ANYTHING
TO GET PAYBACK,
AND, YOU KNOW, WHAT
I'M TRYING TO SAY IS
I THINK I GOT
THE TINIEST TASTE
OF WHAT YOU'VE
BEEN THROUGH,
THE TINIEST.
HMM. I GET IT NOW.
I UNDERSTAND...
WHY YOU LIED TO ME
ABOUT WILLIAM,
WHY YOU HAD TO.
I GET IT,
AND FOR THE EXTENT
THAT I JUDGED YOU...
AND I DID JUDGE YOU...
I'M SORRY.
YOU KNOW, YOU SAID
YOU DIDN'T KNOW WHAT
KIND OF PERSON YOU ARE.
I THINK YOU SHOULD
FIGURE THAT OUT.
WILLIAM.
MY NAME IS MATTHEW.
BUT IT USED TO BE
WILLIAM, RIGHT,
BEFORE YOU AND YOUR MOM
LEFT CENTRAL CITY?
YOU KNOW MY MOM?
ACTUALLY, I KNEW
YOUR FATHER,
AND HE KNEW MINE.
MAN: GREG, MOVE YOUR HEAD!