My name is Oliver Queen.
After 5 years in Hell,
I returned home
with only one goal--
to save my city.
But I couldn't honor that
commitment
and honor the promise I made
to the mother of my son,
so I asked the best man I know
to help.
His name is John Diggle,
and he is the Green Arrow.
Previously on "Arrow"...
Our old friend
Alex Faust.
Ok, clearly he was at SCPD
when the explosion went off.
So he's
either died or escaped.
He escaped.
Special Agent
Samanda Watson.
Can we help
you with something?
I'm here
as a courtesy
to inform you
of the investigation
I'll be conducting
in your city.
- Investigation into what?
- You.
Ok. Present us is
only worried
about you quitting your
nobody-told-about job.
When are you gonna
let that go?
When you go
into business with me.
Wait. I'm sorry.
Go into what with you?
Think about all
the good we could do.
Yes.
On Lian Yu, Felicity and I
got caught in one of the explosions.
I thought you guys
were fine.
I have nerve damage.
That's why you haven't
been pulling your gun.
It's just a tremor.
I can manage it.
You nearly got killed
last night
because you couldn't
rely on me.
But what are you
gonna do about it?
Tell Oliver.
Eyes on Faust?
Shoot her!
I got him. He's in
the structure next door.
- Everyone get into position.
- Copy that.
- On it, Hoss.
- You got it.
Hurry!
Get him!
Uh!
Ooh.
Down for the count.
No more bombs
for you, bitch.
Go, Green Arrow.
Or should I call
you the Green Arrow?
It feels kind of weird.
It's weird,
but at some point, we all
have get to used to it.
♪ Arrow 6x03 ♪
Next of Kin
Original Air Date on October 26, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
It seemed to go well
out there tonight.
Yeah, we make a good team.
And yet you still have
worried face.
It's because sooner
or later,
someone's going
to find out
that the Green Arrow
isn't shooting
any arrows.
Yeah, well, Curtis
and I are working on that.
We're gonna
figure something out.
Good. Thank you.
Ok. I am going to go home.
I'm going to sleep,
and maybe I'll even get
4 hours.
Maybe in another week,
I'll get used to that
judgmental stare
you keep giving me.
This isn't judgment.
It's amusement.
Hmm.
"Sooner or later,
someone's gonna find out
the Green Arrow isn't
shooting any arrows."
Dinah, I'm not an Archer.
No, it's not about
the arrows, John.
It's about the injury.
I thought you were
gonna talk to Oliver.
I was...
Until he asked me
to put this on.
Which he never would have
done if he knew the truth.
Dinah, what do you
want from me?
The man's under
the FBI microscope.
He's worried about
his son.
Imagine how worried
he'd be if he knew
you were out there
compromised.
Did you see me tonight?
Did I look compromised?
Dinah, I have this
handled.
The tremor's gone.
Well, I guess I worried
for nothing, then.
Good morning.
You like your eggs
scrambled, right?
Yes, I do.
Good. That's what
I made you.
This is for real-for real,
isn't it?
Me being around more?
And not the other guy?
It is for real-for real,
if that's cool with you.
Yeah.
Good.
What you got there?
Math. Big test later
this week.
Yeah, I know what it's
like switching schools,
but don't worry
about it.
You'll get there.
Not by the end of
this week.
I'll be lucky to get a C.
Nothing wrong with
getting a C every once in a while.
I used to get Ds.
I would've been psyched for a C.
You don't get it.
I am kidding. Just, I
think that if you relax
a little bit more,
it'll come easier.
I got to study.
Can I be excused?
Yeah.
- Thanks.
- Yup.
- Hey.
You all right?
Ye--no. William's
stressing over a test.
I tried to be supportive,
and I feel like I just--
I'm--I'm making it worse.
I feel your pain. That
was Dinah's department.
I don't know what
I'd have done parenting alone.
Uh, uh, I mean, you'll
figure it out, though.
Thank you.
Agent Watson,
I do not believe you
are on my schedule.
I think you'll come to find
I really don't give a damn.
Ok.
Your office issued
a statement
on last night's
apprehension of Alex Faust.
We did. He was apprehended
by the Green Arrow.
And I'm sure you have
an airtight alibi
for last night.
Rockets game with
my kid.
We were on
the Jumbotron.
And only an idiot
of the highest order would be fooled
by someone else running
around in that hood.
Whoever your understudy is,
he might want to brush up
on his archery.
Or did you think we
didn't notice
that no arrows were used
in taking down Faust?
Are you done?
- I'm not.
- Ok.
Whether I can prove
you're the Green Arrow,
there's no question you
support him as mayor.
You're known to protect
and communicate with him and his team.
Is that a crime?
No. But you're
sending a message
to the police of this city
that they can't do their job
without vigilante help.
I'm glad I don't work
for you.
She's not wrong.
Uh, about the "Glad you
don't work for me" part
or the "Nobody's buying
John under the hood" part?
The undercutting
the cops part.
I know they're not enough
for this city,
but they never will be
if we keep saying it.
That's a catch-22,
Quentin.
I mean...
Can you try to find
a solution?
Yeah. I'll try.
Thank you.
It'd be nice to have
something
before John and the team have to get
back in the field.
Hey, I'll be back in 5.
Uh, guys?
Yeah, we heard you.
You'll be--
what the...?
Officer Lopez...
I hope you don't own
any Kord Industries stock.
My pension fund does,
though it seems a little crass to worry
about that now.
What do we got?
The vics all died of broken vertebrae
or blunt force trauma.
- Forensics?
- Not even a fingerprint.
And speaking of,
the unsub used
one of the vic's palm
prints to gain access
into Kord's
internal server.
To get what?
The company doesn't
know yet.
I'm gonna need a chat
with the CEO.
In the meantime, I'm gonna
take a look around here.
- You get all that?
- Yeah, and a bag of chips.
Sorry. I didn't get a chance to eat
breakfast this morning.
I'm feeling
a little peckish.
Ten will get you 20 that Kord's CEO
won't tell you anything.
Can you
access the server?
Already here. Now what?
Ok, you're looking
for a master port.
It's female with
a yellow border.
Got it.
Ok, insert our toy
and let us do
our thang.
You keep saying
"thing" wrong.
All right. We're in.
Curtis has got it from here.
You going somewhere?
Yeah, I got startup
work to do.
Yeah, we're still trying
to decide on our name.
Hey, so I think
I have a solution
to our cop's catch-22.
That was fast.
I was chatting with
councilwoman Pollard.
She's in the early
stages of drafting
some anti-vigilante
legislation.
No.
Hear me out.
If you were to join
it, sponsor it...
Still, no.
You could tailor the bill to however
you want it, all right?
You could take
the teeth out of it
so it can't
bite the team too hard.
Ok, first, Pollard
is not a pushover,
so we know this isn't true.
Second, I am not going
to put John in the hood
and then actively support
legislation
that further brands him
a criminal.
Find another way, please.
- Hi.
- Hey.
Um, city hall is
6 blocks that way.
I thought maybe you
could use
a late afternoon
snack.
Who are you, my mother?
I mean, that's not
even accurate.
My mother rarely remembered
to pick me up from school,
let alone make me a snack.
May I come in?
Yeah. Yeah.
I, uh, love what you've
done with the place.
Yeah, well, you know,
it's near impossible
to find affordable office space
in the city.
Someone should talk to
the mayor about that.
Oh, speaking of,
how do you feel
about the name
"Bit By Bit"?
Sounds like a sitcom
from the eighties.
Great. That's, like,
really not what we're going for.
Well, who knew that
when you
stopped balancing
being vigilante
with everything else
that you would have time
to drop off snacks?
Speaking off, how is
William now that you're
done pulling double
vigilante/daddy duty?
It's a two steps
forward,
one step backwards
sort of thing.
I was just thinking,
I'd really love to lean
on Thea, but, um,
I mean, she
just has a knack
for this sort of thing.
Yeah, she'd be the most
bad-ass aunt ever.
Would she ever.
Well, I know I'm not Thea,
but I am so down to help
in any way that you need.
Well, truth be told,
aside from snacks,
I do sort of need
your help.
Ah.
William has a math test
later this week
that he's really
stressing out over,
and, um, every time
I open my mouth,
I am making it worse.
So the man who took down
Damien Darhk is bested
by arithmetic.
It wasn't my strongest
subject in school.
No? What was, truancy?
Charm.
Yeah, no doubt.
Let me guess, you told him
something along the lines of,
"Just relax. I would've
been psyched to get a C.
All I got was Fs."
Ds. I most--
How did
you know that?
Because I know you,
and I know that if you
even cared about school,
you would've been good
at it.
Thank you.
Nothing would grind my gears
more when I was his age
when my mom was just telling
me to stop worrying
when I was freaking out
about a project.
Why?
I didn't need
to learn how to relax.
I needed to figure out
how to do the work.
So what do I do?
What d--
Well, ask him--ask him
what he needs,
and then put him
in the driver's seat,
and he'll show you
how to help him.
You make things
so simple.
You always have.
Huh.
Curtis?
No wonder Kord doesn't like
to share their secrets.
They invent a lot of
really nasty stuff,
including this new
military grade nerve gas ZX.
What does that have
to do with our mystery killer woman?
She downloaded
the transport schedule for said nerve gas.
Now, do you find that
alarming, or is it just me?
No. I definitely find that alarming.
When is it moving?
One hour.
Ok. I'm on my way.
Alert the Green Arrow.
Well, I mean Diggle.
I mean John.
I mean, it's just good OPSEC to use
code names in the field.
I agree. Go.
You know, if you're not
going to say anything,
you can at least turn on
the damn radio.
With your presets?
I'd prefer the silence.
Just turn it on.
♪ children of Aquarius ♪
♪ your world is
my world ♪
It's not safe on the road.
That's what he's for.
My team's more equipped.
♪ children of Aquarius ♪
♪ your dream is my dream ♪
You have horrible taste
in music.
Why are we slowing down?
I don't know.
Stay here.
Overwatch.
Any bogies on thermal?
Just you guys.
And I'm guessing
you're not bogies.
What's going on, guys?
Why aren't you moving?
I'm trying to find
that out right now.
Perfect.
Ignition blocker.
Surprise, bitch.
Careful. Bullets
and bioweapons don't mix.
Your friend's right.
Hyah!
Leader's in the cab, Hoss.
Go after her or the gas?
Or both?
They're getting away, Hoss.
Make a decision!
Screw this.
Couldn't get to it.
Couldn't stop her.
It wasn't
your fault.
What the hell happened
out there?
Ask him.
Dude just froze.
Casualties?
No. Everyone got out.
A dozen people were sent
to the hospital
for smoke inhalation,
and two are
in critical condition.
What the hell, Hoss?
There were two targets
and two of us.
What was
so freakin' complicated?
I don't know. That's
never happened to me
in the field before,
not in the army
and not with this team.
The fog of war.
Things don't always
go perfect out there,
so we close ranks
and we move on.
Thanks.
It won't happen again.
Ok. Good,
'cause it looks like
you guys got another shot
at these guys.
Facial recog came back
with a match.
Onyx Adams, leader of
a CIA black Ops squad
working undercover in Syria.
They disappeared in 2015
with $100 million
in Syrian government gold.
And what have they
been doing since?
My guess is preparing
for the ZX gas heist.
And finding the tech
they need to do it.
Why weren't they blinded by
the flashbangs like we were?
Also, if these guys got away
with 100 million in gold,
why would they risk it by
trying to steal nerve gas?
Fine. See if you can pick up any chatter
on the dark web--
encrypted message
boards, whatever.
I'll check with Lyla,
see if any Intel
has changed.
Also, I'm sorry
about tonight.
That wasn't me.
Hey. When I said move on,
I meant you, too.
Fortunately, the two victims
in critical condition
are expected to recover.
Multiple witnesses spotted
Green Arrow and his team
of vigilantes at the scene.
Becky, can you get
the fire chief's latest
report, please?
And could--would you mind
putting in an order
for some coffee?
One of the big boxes
of coffee, please.
Thank you.
So I guess being
the Green Arrow involves
something of
a learning curve.
We don't know the circumstances
surrounding last night.
Yeah, but we know how
it's gonna play out.
What do you mean?
Heh! Wow.
Speak of the devil.
Got to admire
her sense of timing.
- Who?
- Pollard.
She's seizing
the moment.
She's using last
night's disaster
as a pretext to
introduce
her anti-vigilante
legislation to the council.
- Does she have the votes?
- I don't know.
Can you make sure
she doesn't?
Hey.
Can we talk for a second?
I just wanted to say
thank you
for having my back
with the team.
Now, truth be told,
I, um...
I was a bit surprised
considering you--
Well, don't be
surprised.
And don't think I said
what I said for you.
I said it because this
team needs a leader.
Without
a chain of command,
we're easy pickings
out there.
Ok. I guess
that's why you decided
not to tell anyone
about my injury, right?
It is.
But, honestly,
as worried as I am
about your hand,
after last night,
I'm a little more
worried about your head.
I know.
Hey, Dinah, I know.
Look...
Every time I've had
to give orders
in the army,
on this team,
there was always
someone there
backing my plays.
I'm not used to making
the hard calls alone.
No one is more
disappointed in me
than me.
Well, next time,
get it right.
Our lives depend on it.
She shoots, she scores!
What do we have?
Ok, these are our
new friends back in 2015.
But last night, you said
there were only 5.
You think when that
leader went rogue,
not everyone went
with her.
Woof. Wild Dog for the win.
Three of
her original members
defected back to the CIA
for a little while at least.
What do you mean,
for a little while?
Ok, 'cause this guy and
this guy were both killed
in separate poison gas
attacks last year,
one in Mosul,
one in Tripoli.
The video footage is...
it's--it's really gruesome.
Well, poison gas
can't be a coincidence.
No. I mean, ISIS is
linked to both of them,
but I'm pretty sure this is how Onyx likes
to solve her problems.
So she staged two terrorist attacks
just to settle a grudge?
No, not just a grudge.
These are the only two
that can pin her to the stolen gold.
Bingo.
All right. So she's
wiping out defectors.
Got one left--rob Reynolds,
whereabouts unknown.
Yeah, but you got to figure Star City
or somewhere close by.
Well, I'm
guessing we should worry
what this gas could do
to a populated area.
Oh, yeah. Look.
Hey, buddy.
Hi.
How's it going?
Fine.
You still worried
about the test?
Yeah.
Anything that I
can do to help?
Uh, do you know
quadratic equations?
Wow! Um, those sound
vaguely familiar,
but then again, I wasn't
the most enthusiastic
math student, so...
I really shouldn't be
talking
to anyone who can't
help me right now.
Ok.
Got a minute, Hoss?
Sure.
This about Pollard's bill?
No. Uh, sorry. I...
I've been out of
the office.
No, this is
about John.
What about him?
It's not working out.
You talking
about last night?
I'm talking about
something--
something a hell of
a lot worse
than what happened
last night.
That poison gas
could kill thousands.
John can handle it.
That's why I'm here,
Hoss.
He can't. He's in
over his head.
We're lucky nobody
died last night,
but luck runs out.
We need you
to come back.
I'm still working on
a 20 with Reynolds.
It's gonna take a while.
These black Op guys are
really hard to find.
Hey.
Hey. Wow.
I'm just surprised
to see you here,
and I'm also surprised
that you remembered the access code.
It's been, like, a week.
- Yeah. It was--it was a joke.
- Ok.
I'm guessing
you're here for--
Well, yeah, and the guy
that you're searching
for, this Reynolds.
- Yeah.
- Can Curtis handle it?
Yeah. I'm sure he can.
Why? What do you need?
Well, I asked William
what he needs,
and he needs a tutor.
Aw. Lucky for you
and for him,
you are looking
at Nevada's
3-time state
mathletics champion.
Only 3 times?
Yeah, they wouldn't let
freshmen enter.
It was an ordeal.
I got over it,
but it still kind of hurts.
This can't interfere
with an operation.
No. We're in
a holding pattern.
I'm sure Curtis
can come and cover me.
I might have
to leave abruptly,
but other than that, yeah.
No, it's not a problem.
Well, I'll probably see you back there.
I'm gonna...
Ok. Yeah. Ok, yeah.
Yeah, I'll call Curtis.
He'll be here soon.
Ok. Ok, bye. Bye.
This is weird.
Being back down here?
How many times have
you come down here
to find me brooding?
Well, I'm not brooding,
Oliver. I'm thinking.
Yeah.
Ok, maybe I'm brooding
a little bit.
Well, if you haven't
figured it out already,
that expression is
as much a part of the uniform
as the green hood.
Every time you were down
here brooding,
it was because you made
some kind of mistake.
I think you made
another one, man.
No. Not even close.
Who came to you? Rene?
I needed to come and
ask Felicity a favor.
And then, of course,
I saw
that very familiar
expression.
It makes me wonder
if maybe I asked too much of you.
What do you mean?
I gave up being
the Green Arrow for William,
but you have J.J.,
you have Lyla.
It doesn't exactly
seem fair.
That's not the issue
at all, Oliver.
I made my peace with this
whole life a long time ago.
So what's the problem?
I don't know how you did it.
You never hesitated
to make the call.
You were always sure.
I'm not.
I was never sure,
not one time.
I'm very flattered that
it--it looked that way on the outside,
but on the inside,
it was...
It was instinct.
It was instinct,
and it was fear.
Yeah, but you worked
past it.
Well, you'll work
past it, too.
Now, I'm not gonna
sit here and say
that you
won't make mistakes,
that you won't lose
people along the way.
You know, most--most
will be strangers,
but some...
well, some won't be.
Because, John, you're
one of the main reasons
that the Green Arrow
even exists.
What are you talking about?
The Restons.
- The bank robbers?
- The bank robbers, yeah.
You were the first
person who convinced me
to look past
just the names on
my father's list.
You helped me discover
that the hood--
that persona--he wasn't
a hero.
You--you helped me
find one.
All of this--
the Green Arrow,
the idea of it--
it exists
because you had faith
in me.
Now you got to have
the same kind of faith
in yourself.
Because if you do...
You can be
a better leader.
a better hero
than I ever was.
- Sitrep.
- Good to go.
Any doubts?
You ask that
each time?
Because we are going
after our brothers in arms,
comrades.
I need your resolve.
You got it. And tonight
Reynolds gets his.
Roger that.
What about
the Green Arrow?
What about him?
You've seen him
in the field.
Being highly trained
operators,
would you consider him
a threat?
- Hell no.
- There's your answer. Move out.
Ok, and after you
divide by x...
Uh, solve for x.
Yes, but first...
Is it factor
the binomials?
Yeah, right. Cool.
But why can't I just
solve for x?
Oh, you will,
I mean, eventually,
probably in high school,
but first you have
to master the binomials.
Oh, I'm gonna bomb this.
I know it sucks because
you're new
and probably
a little behind,
but the fact that you're
frustrated means
that you can see how useful
math could be,
which means, unfortunately,
you're really good at it.
Oliver said school doesn't matter
in the real world.
Hmm, well, Oliver didn't
grow up in the real world.
School changed my life.
I used to love school.
Yeah. You will again,
promise.
How's it going in here?
Good.
Yeah, I'd say we're
making progress.
Good.
Could you tutor me some
more before the test?
Um, yeah. I mean, if it's
cool with your dad,
it's cool with me.
If it's cool with you,
it's totally cool with me.
Special delivery.
Hey, that's not
grilled cheese.
No, it's not
Those are Monte Cristos.
What's a Monte Cristo?
What? You've never had--
this is the best nighttime
snack you can ever have,
and you used waffles.
Well, that is how we do it
in the not real world.
Curtis got a location
on Reynolds. We gotta--
Well, I gotta--ha ha!--Go.
This is--without you,
it's weird.
Best of luck out there.
Oh, I'll be in
the bunker for this.
William, you're awesome.
- Thank you.
- See you soon.
She's pretty cool.
Yeah, she is.
Traffic cams picked up
Reynolds
heading north
on Hillcrest.
The only things
out there are
souvenirs
and the Haselby Grand.
A hotel's a great
place for an ex-spook
to stash a go-bag
and try to slip out
with the tourist
crowd.
Huh. It makes you wonder if
his old crew tipped him off
or he's just the luckiest
target in the world.
Either way, there are
hundreds of people in that hotel,
so if they disperse
the gas--
They won't.
Let's move out.
Did he forget
to say "suit up,"
or was "let's move,"
like, his version of "suit up."
Because, personally,
I like "let's suit up,"
'cause then it just lets
you know that you...
Go suit up, Curtis.
Yeah, I have
to go suit up. Ahem.
Hey, hey.
Can you handle this?
I asked Oliver to come back.
Well, the fact that he
didn't should tell you something, right?
Maybe.
Look, all I know for sure,
if John doesn't straighten
himself out,
it's gonna be
another rough night.
I got eyes on the tango.
Roger that
Package is deployed.
What do we know, Overwatch?
Lots. Thermal reads
a potential 166
casualties inside,
and Onyx's team cut
the CCTV.
So we're going in blind.
Literally if we get hit
with those flashbangs of hers again.
Your dorky-ass glasses
better work.
Got visuals thanks to
Mr. Terrific's T-spheres.
Go now.
We need locations on
Reynolds and the gas.
I have him,
upper lobby,
but I got no way of
detecting the gas.
Canary, terrific, see if
you can locate the gas.
Dog, you're
with me on evac
after we clear
Reynolds.
Oh, I really hope he's not
making decisions
based on animal code names.
Incoming!
All right, Hoss,
let's check these out.
Guys, you got
two hostiles in the lobby.
- Hyah! Hyah!
- Hyah!
Hyah! Hyah!
Guess your old tricks
don't work.
I don't need tricks,
just collateral.
Ohh.
Onyx just released
the gas. What should we do?
The gas is spreading.
Do you copy?
Arrow, Arrow do you copy?
Handle the gas.
We've got Reynolds. Move.
The gas is coming
from the trash can.
Everybody get
behind me now!
Get behind me now!
I'm going after
Reynolds.
Night-night.
Overwatch, we need a way
to neutralize the nerve gas.
You could burn it,
but I don't suggest it
since you're still inside
the building.
We won't be for long,
I hope.
The breaches are too small
to evacuate
all these people.
Which is why we're
gonna make them bigger.
Going somewhere?
I wasn't gonna tell
anyone about the gold.
You know, it turns out
money can buy happiness.
It just can't buy
peace of mind.
Uh! Uh!
Hyah! Hyah...
You all right?
Who the hell are you?
I'm the Green Arrow.
I got one of Onyx's
flashbangs.
It should be enough
to ignite the gas.
Ok, everyone,
when I count to 3,
that wall is going bye-bye,
so I need you all
to haul ass.
There is nerve gas followed
by a huge explosion.
I don't think they need
the motivation.
Good point.
1, 2...
3!
Gas dispersed.
All civilians accounted for.
Good work.
The other four are down.
- Onyx is in the limo.
- What about this guy?
He helped steal
millions in foreign gold
and turned a blind eye
when his comrades
were being killed off
in fake terrorist attacks.
That's good work
back there.
Just following your
lead, Hoss.
Can we do this
after every win?
Oh, a new tradition for
a new era. I like that.
To go with our new
team arrow victory dance.
I didn't know
we had an old one.
We don't. Never will.
Things won't be changing
around here that much.
Look...
There's something
you should know.
- You went to Oliver.
- You told him.
She didn't have to.
I know you,
Rene.
I know all of you.
It's a leader's job to.
Gift time.
Oh, yes. So...
Curtis and I have been
working on
a little something
in our spare time.
Very limited spare time,
may I add?
We call it
the Green Monster.
Or something cooler
than that.
Like, pretty much whatever
you want to call it.
The important part is
it shoots arrows
instead of crossbow bolts.
260-pound draw weight.
The arrows exit the gate at 400 fps.
That's feet per second.
Integrated recoil energy
dissipation system.
Adjustable
mount scope,
quick detach quivers,
pistol grip,
finger guards,
non-slip rubber insert.
You two want
a moment alone?
You want to take
it for a spin?
Damn, Hoss.
Did you guys put stabilizers
on that crossbow?
Nope.
That aim there is
pure John Diggle.
Not a bad idea, though,
for the next upgrade.
Nice going.
Steady.
See? Told you.
The tremor's gone.
Well, I'm convinced.
You were wrong about
one thing, though.
What's that?
You can make the hard
calls on your own just fine.
Thank you.
Hey.
So, uh, your friends
did good last night.
I had a feeling John
would get it together.
How did you manage?
Well, too many councilmen
owe Pollard too many favors.
It's--it's gonna pass,
Oliver.
Well, I'll veto it.
You've got enough
PR problems as it is, don't you think?
Besides, they've got enough
votes for an override.
There has to be
something that we can do.
Matter of fact...
Let the record show
there are no nays
on the anti-vigilante
measure.
Those in favor?
Point of order.
Does it address the matter
at hand, Mr. Mayor?
It does,
madame parliamentarian.
Thank you.
And good morning.
As you know,
I have been accused
of a great many things
recently,
including but not limited
to supporting vigilantes
at the expense of our men
and women in uniform.
This was never my intention.
In the wake of
the attacks on the SCPD,
putting this police force
back on its feet is
my number one priority
as mayor.
We need the women and men
of the SCPD on our streets
protecting us,
but they can't do that
if they are busy
hunting vigilantes.
That is why I oppose
this bill,
and that is why I am
invoking chapter 9
of the city charter.
And you are aware that
will convert
councilwoman
Pollard's bill
to a citywide
referendum?
I certainly am.
Because last night, a group
of vigilantes saved
hundreds of lives.
So if we are going to decide
on diverting
police resources
towards stopping them,
we are not going to do that
until the people of
Star City have spoken.
What the hell
was that?
Stay of execution.
The mayor's procedural maneuver
took both the council
and the public by surprise.
How the public will decide
on the issue of vigilantism
is anyone's guess.
According
to multiple reports,
the city council was set
to pass strict measures
against the Green Arrow
and his team.
This anti-vigilante
legislation was introduced...
Who are you protecting?
Oliver...
with a gift.
You busy?
No. Um...No. I--come in.
I was just working on
a name for the startup,
which would be a lot easier
if Curtis and I
actually knew
what we were trying
to start up. Heh!
You know, that's
tomorrow's problem.
Is it my birthday?
William got an "A"
on his test.
Oh, he did? Oh,
that's awesome.
I mean,
I knew he would.
He's super smart.
His understanding
of math is at prodigy levels,
much like me
at his age.
Ha ha! Can you believe
he's your son?
I didn't mean it--
that's not what I meant.
I mean,
math isn't everything.
I mean, you have--
you have so many
redeeming qualities.
You know, you have
amazing abs and...
I'm just gonna
open this.
- Please.
- If that's ok.
Hmm.
It's a key to my apartment.
Ok.
Um...
Won't that be confusing
for William?
I mean, it sure as hell
is confusing for me.
I know that when I took
William in,
we agreed that we would
keep our distance because...
He was gonna have a lot
to process.
He's still got
a lot to process.
Yes, he does. Every day,
there's a new challenge.
I sense a "but" coming.
There's a "but" coming,
right?
But then I saw you
with him.
And I became 100% sure
that if you want...
his life will be better
with you in it...
just like mine.
Are you sure that's
what you want?
I'm sure.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Greg!
Move your head.