The day I went missing...
...was the day I died.
Five years in hell
forged me into a weapon...
...which I use to honor a vow
I made to my father...
...who sacrificed his life for mine.
In his final moments,
he told me the truth...
...that our family's wealth had been
built on the suffering of others.
That he failed our city...
...and that it was up to me
to save it and right his wrongs.
But to do that without endangering
the people closest to me...
...I have to be someone else.
I have to be something else.
Who's that? Where'd he come from?
What's going on here?
Get the chopper back, now.
Who is this guy?
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Please, wait, wait.
No, please.
Marcus Redmond, you've failed this city.
Please, don't. Please. Don't.
Cell phone, inside pocket,
call your partner.
Tell him to give those pensioners
back their money.
- Please, don't.
- Do it now.
Over the past 15 years,
Mr. Redmond has withdrawn...
...more than 3O million dollars
from the plan's account.
Mr. Redmond claims refunding the Halcyon
pension plan has always been his intent.
But sources say Redmond
was coerced by the vigilante.
This guy gets more airtime
than the Kardashians, right?
Five years on an island and
you still know who they are.
Been catching up. It's nice to see
our culture has improved while I was away.
The city used to be different.
People used to feel safe.
Oh. What's the matter, Morn?
Afraid we're gonna be next?
Do you have any questions, Oliver?
It's a simple proof of life declaration.
Read out a brief statement to the judge...
...and your death in absentia
judgment will be voided.
It's fine.
I've been in a courtroom before.
Four times by my estimate.
There's the DUI.
The assault on that paparazzi
douche bag.
Stealing that taxi, which was awesome,
by the way.
And who could forget peeing on the cop?
- I wish everyone would.
- I'd hang, but we're headed to court.
It's why I'm here. My best friend
is getting resurrected?
- I wouldn't miss this for the world.
- What about you?
I think the first four times of you
in court was enough for me.
Fair enough.
Mrs. Queen, car's ready.
Walter.
Mr. Queen. Mr. Queen.
How does it feel to return to civilization
after five years?
What happened on that island,
Mr. Queen?
- Tell us about the accident.
Oliver--
There was a storm.
The boat went down.
I was the only survivor.
- She's not there.
- Sara.
My father didn't make it.
No.
I almost died. I--
I thought that I had because I spent...
...so many days on that life raft
before I saw the island.
When I reached it, I knew...
...I knew that I was gonna have to
live for both of us.
And in those five years,
it was that one thought...
...that kept me going.
Your Honor, we move to
vitiate the death-in-absentia...
...filed after Oliver's disappearance at sea
aboard the Queen's Gambit five years ago.
Unfortunately, we will not be requesting
that the declaration of death filed...
...for the petitioner's father,
Robert Queen, be rescinded.
The Queen family is only entitled
to one miracle, I'm afraid.
Now on to the offices.
Everyone is waiting to meet you there.
Morn, that was, uh...
A little bit heavier
than I was expecting it to be.
Could we do that tomorrow? Please?
- Of course.
- Thank you.
Last week you couldn't wait
to get to the company.
Tommy, I spent five years
away from civilization.
I wasn't exactly thinking straight.
- Hi.
What are you doing here?
Oh, they were bringing me back
from the dead. Legally speaking.
- What are you doing here?
- My job.
- Right.
- More like the DA's.
- Hi. Oliver Queen.
- Emily Nocenti.
Oliverjust got back from five years
on an island.
Before that,
he was cheating on me with my sister.
He was with her when she died. Last week,
he told me to stay away from him.
It was really good advice. Excuse me.
- It was nice to meet you.
- Yeah, let's go.
Come on, buddy.
Shake it off. Let's go.
Mr. Somers. One question, sir.
I don't know what I've done to earn this
witch hunt from Ms. Lance...
...and her bosses at the CNRI, but I can
tell you this. I am an honest businessman...
...and I will fight this slander
to my last dime and breath.
That's all I have to say. Thank you.
- Oh, there's Mr. Queen.
- Do you want to follow up?
Tell us what happened inside,
Mr. Queen.
Step back everybody, please.
Can you give us a couple comments?
- Before you go, sir.
- Comments about the island?
- What happened?
- Step back.
Hey man, I'll make you
swallow that Nikon. Back.
This happens to you a lot, doesn't it?
How much is a life worth?
A life of a man, a good man.
A stevedore on the docks of the city
in which we live.
A father.
A man with a daughter. The plaintiff will
prove by a preponderance of evidence...
...that Victor Nocenti learned that his boss,
that man, sitting there, Martin Somers...
...was taking bribes from the Chinese
triads to smuggle drugs into our city.
When Victor
threatened to tell the police...
...Martin Somers had him killed.
Mr. Somers is very well-connected...
...and has friends
in the District Attorney's office.
Which is why if Emily Nocenti
is to get justice for her father's death...
...if Somers is to get justice
for his crimes...
...then someone is gonna have to do it
for them.
Martin Somers.
LaureVs targeted
the worst of Starling City...
...so it's no surprise his name
is on my father's list.
The city's police and DA
can't stop him or won't.
Laurel thinks she's the only one
willing to bring him to justice.
She's wrong.
You, listen up.
The longer this goes on, the more
the media is gonna crucify me.
You shut this trial down,
understand me?
- Yes, sir.
- What the hell?
Martin Somers--
Who the hell are you?
- You've failed this city.
- No, no, no.
You're going to testify in that trial.
You're gonna confess
to having Victor Nocenti killed.
There won't be a second warning.
I hired you to protect my son.
I'm not a bodyguard,
but it seems to me the first requirement...
...would be staying next
to the man you're hired to protect.
I've never had a client
who didn't want my protection.
I hired you.
That makes me the client.
Now, where do you think my son is going
on these chaperone-less excursions?
- Ma'am, I truly do not know.
- And he truly doesn't.
Then perhaps you'd like to share with me,
you know, where it is you run off to?
I've been alone for five years.
- I know that, Oliver--
- Mom.
Alone.
I see.
I promise to introduce her if it ever gets
to the exchanging first names stage.
I'd rather you promise to take Mr. Diggle
with you on your next rendezvous.
It's not safe.
You've already been abducted once.
There is a maniac out
there hunting the wealthy.
- That maniac saved my life.
- This isn't a game.
I lost you once.
And I am not going through that again.
Okay-
Dig's my guy.
Thank you.
Sorry to give you so much grief.
I served three tours in Afghanistan,
Mr. Queen.
You don't even come close
to my definition of grief.
I tell you what...
...you ditch me one more time
and no one will have to fire me.
- Where are you going?
- Somewhere loud and smoky.
Don't bother trying
to pickpocket my stash...
...because I'm gonna go
get drunk instead.
Thea.
Do you think this is what Dad
would want for you?
Dead people don't want anything.
- It's one of the benefits of being dead.
- I was dead.
- And I wanted a lot.
- Except for your family.
You've been home a week.
And all you do is avoid Mom...
...ignore Walter and judge me.
Don't wait up.
Well, I owe you an apology, Mr. Somers.
We come all the way down to your docks...
...and turns out
you don't need the police.
Which is exactly what I've been saying.
So I guess that 911 call we got last night
from your stevedores saying...
...you were attacked by a guy
in a hood and a bow and arrow.
Iguessthatn.
Hm...
Was that a practical joke?
- These guys like to fool around.
- Yeah.
You know, I'd be very
inclined to believe an honest...
...upstanding businessman like
yourself except...
Well, one of my men...
...found this at your docks.
You see, there's this vigilante
running around.
He thinks he's some kind of Robin Hood.
Robbing the rich.
Trying to teach them a lesson, I guess...
...I don't know.
But the point is, the man is a killer.
And nothing and no one is gonna
stop me from bringing him clown.
But like you said...
Huh.
...clearly nothing happened
here last night.
Isn't this a conflict of interest, Detective?
After all, your daughter is suing me.
- I'm good at keeping my emotions in check.
- I'm not.
You and your daughter don't wanna find out
what I'm capable of when I get emotional.
As you can see, Oliver,
we've modernized quite a bit.
Hi.
- Ha, ha, are you enjoying yourself?
- Yes, I am.
I remember your father used to
bring you here when you were a boy.
You always were so excited.
- Dad let me drink soda in the office.
- So that's why you enjoyed coming.
Queen Consolidated's success of late
is a result of its targeted diversification.
We have been making impressive inroads
in cutting-edge fields like...
...biotech and clean energy--
- That's neat. Excuse me.
Can I get a sparkling water
or something cold, please?
Sweetheart, Oliver, Walter
and I have something to discuss with you.
Come, please, sit.
Morn, it makes me nervous
when you ask me to sit down.
The company is about to break ground
on a site for the Applied Sciences division.
And we would like to honor your father
by dedicating the building in his name.
Nice.
And we'd like to make
an announcement at the dedication.
That you will be taking a
leadership position in the company.
- No.
- No. Your, your company.
No. I don't wanna lead anything.
Besides, Walter's doing
a very good job here.
You said that you wanted
to be a different person.
And you are Robert Queen's son.
- I don't need to be reminded of that.
- Obviously, you do.
Everyone here understands that
this transition is really difficult for you.
Thank you, Walter.
Which part though?
Everyone fantasizing that I got my MBA
while I was on the island?
Or the fact that my father's CFO
now sleeps down the hall from me?
You know, five years ago, your
irresponsibility was somewhat charming.
It is a lot less so now.
There he is.
The driver will be here in a minute.
Okay-
I spent the first 27 years
of my life in Starling City...
...and the next five in Afghanistan.
You want to know what I learned?
There's no place like home?
No, just the opposite.
Home is a battlefield.
Back home, they're all trying to get you.
Get you to open up, be somebody
you're not sure you are anymore.
Or I could be wrong. Maybe after
five years alone, you're not as messed up...
...in the head as you have
every right to be.
Hey. Hey, get away.
HEN-
Dad?
Hey. Hey, stay away from him.
Well, we anticipate
that Somers' attorney will...
...try and paint you as blinded by grief
or looking to make a buck.
But this isn't about the money.
I just want justice for my father.
Emily, there are a lot of people
who don't want this trial to proceed.
- Dangerous people.
- My mother died...
...when I was a baby. My father
is the only family I've ever known.
And they slit his throat.
They are going to have to kill me
if they want me to give this up.
- Well, let's hope it doesn't come to that.
- And it won't.
- What's going on?
- You three are getting police protection.
Get used to their faces,
they're going with you everywhere.
- No arguments.
- I'm a lawyer. I live to argue.
I'm your father.
I live to keep you safe.
- Emily, let's go grab a cup of coffee?
- Yes, why not do that? Thank you.
Please, go with them. Stay there.
Protective custody? I seem to recall you
trying that once I discovered boys.
- It didn't work then, either.
- This isn't a joke, Laurel.
Martin Somers got attacked last night.
- What?
- Yeah.
- By who?
- Doesn't matter.
You have whipped up a storm
with these guys...
...and until the dust settles,
you will be protected.
End of discussion.
That might've worked when I was 8...
- ...but it's not gonna work anymore.
- End of discussion.
Doing your job? Great.
This is me doing mine. Okay?
Not just as a father, but as a cop.
These people are more dangerous
than you are willing to admit.
And you've made them angry.
- Thank you for coming.
- Anything for a friend.
We're not friends. You smuggle drugs.
I let you use my port.
For which you are paid a lot of money.
I don't get paid enough
to have arrows shot at me.
You need to take this guy seriously.
He's a bigger threat
than Nocenti ever was.
Now it's Nocenti's daughter
who's the problem.
Unlike your friend with the hood,
we know where to find her.
Don't be an idiot. Take out Emily Nocenti
and Lance will never let this go.
She won't stop until she burns you,
me and the entire triad to the ground.
Then we kill Ms. Lance.
Attorney for shipping
magnate Martin Somers confirmed his client...
...has no intention of testifying, maintaining
innocence in the death of Victor Nocenti.
Nocentfs body was found
four weeks ago.
We'll keep you updated
as information becomes available.
- Wait, how did you get those?
- Don't you knock?
No, wait... Morn said
that there were scars...
I'm... Oliver,
what happened to you out there?
I don't wanna talk about it.
Of course you don't.
You never want to talk to me
about anything except for my social life.
Wait. Where are you going?
Why should I tell you?
I'm sorry, Thea.
I need to get better at talking
about what happened to me there.
But I'm not ready yet. Okay?
- Do you have a second?
- Yeah.
Good. I wanna show you
something out back.
Sometimes when I felt... whatever.
I'd come here.
About a month after the funerals,
Morn stopped going out.
Pretty soon
she stopped talking altogether.
The house got so quiet.
So I'd come here.
To talk to you.
Stupid stuff.
Like what I was doing that day...
...what boy I had a crush on.
And then sometimes, I'd ask you, beg you,
to find your way home to me.
Now here you are.
And the truth is, I felt closer to you
when you were dead.
Look, I know it was hell where you were.
But it was hell here too.
You gotta let me in, Ollie.
You gotta let someone in.
Hi. Are you okay?
There are two cop cars outside.
How am I supposed to stay away from you
if you won't stay away from me?
What are you doing here, Ollie?
My sister took, what...
She pointed out that
I have been distant since I got back...
...and that it would probably be a good idea
if I let somebody in.
So you thought you'd start
with the first person you pushed away?
I did that to protect you.
And then I saw you yesterday
and I realized that I hurt you.
Thank you.
Wow.
This place hasn't changed in five years.
I haven't really had time to redecorate.
I'm a jerk.
Before the island, I was a jerk,
and now I'm just a...
- I'm a damaged jerk.
- What's in the bag?
I thought about many things
on the island...
...but there was one thing
I thought about every day.
I actually dreamed about it,
and I promised myself...
...that if I ever got a chance to do it again,
I'd do it with you.
Eat ice cream.
This is as good as I remember.
My mother wants me
to join the company.
Yeah. Take my rightful place.
I can't exactly picture you
as the master of the universe.
You know, after five years, I have plans.
I have things that I have to do.
I can't do that if I'm...
I don't know. Attending board meetings
and stockholder briefings.
Oliver. You're an adult.
- You can say no.
- Oh, I tried.
Didn't take.
Well, then don't tell her, show her.
Be the person that
you want her to see you as.
Trust me.
I have plenty of experience
with disapproving parents.
I have been on the receiving end
of your father's disapproval.
He blames himself
more than he blames you.
He thinks that, you know, maybe if
he and Sara were closer...
...she would have told him
about the boat trip.
And he could have stopped her
from going with you.
- I am sorry.
- You apologized already.
It'll never be enough.
- Did you hear that?
- What?
There's someone on the fire escape.
- Hey, come on. Come on.
Huh.
U m“!
- Are you hurt?
- No.
- Are you hurt, Mr. Queen?
- No. No.
This is why it's a good idea
to have a bodyguard.
Hey, you okay?
- Daddy.
- Thank God.
- Thank God. Are you all right?
- I'm okay.
- Yeah.
- Those cops that you put on me.
- They--
- I went to ask for a light...
...and they were both dead
in the squad car.
It's all right, honey. It's okay.
Mr. Diggle, thank you.
You feel free to run as many red lights
as you want.
- I was doing my job, sir.
- No, your job is protecting him.
It seems like whenever you're
with one of my daughters, people die.
You stay away from Laurel, or...
...the next time you disappear,
it'll be permanent.
- Dad.
- No, Laurel--
It's okay. I understand.
Yeah.
Laurel.
I'd say thank you
but I don't think that'd cover it.
Like I told your cop friend,
I was just doing my job.
Besides, I think it should be you
that I'm thanking.
- What for?
- The knife.
The knife.
- I got lucky.
- That was a kitchen knife.
It wasn't weighted properly.
You threw it for accuracy
across a ten-foot room.
Exactly. I got lucky.
I'm not the man you want
to take for a fool.
- You understand me?
- Yes.
I think I'm just beginning to
understand the kind of man you are.
Shouldn't take you very long.
I'm shallow.
And very tired. 80...
Good night.
Good night, sir.
I wanted to give
Martin Somers the chance to confess...
...and face a court,
but he chose to go after someone...
...I care about instead.
He's still going to face justice.
It'll just be a different kind.
That triad bitch screwed up
the hit on Lance.
Now the triad is gonna erase
every ounce of evidence...
...of their smuggling operation.
Including me.
Except that's not gonna happen.
Tell Wallace to get the boat ready.
I'm leaving tonight.
Wallace? Wallace, you copy?
Wallace?
Wallace isn't here.
But I am.
We need to move. Now.
- Move.
- Sir, we got six men out there.
That's not enough. Move it..
You're going into that court room
to recuse yourself.
Or drop it, but either way you are done.
If you think I'm gonna abandon
Emily...
...you don't know me that well.
You don't know me well, young lady.
I will lock you in a cell.
Well, I guess
that's what it's gonna take then.
Damn it, Laurel. I thought after
what happened with Sara...
...that you'd stop being just so reckless.
It's not about being reckless,
it's just the opposite.
I'm trying to make this city safer.
Just like you.
Sweetie, you're my only daughter, Laurel.
- You're all I have left to live for.
- But what you want for me isn't living.
Having cops around,
not being able to do my job.
Your job is not going after people
like the triad or Somers.
My job is to use the law to fight
for what is right.
- Just like you taught me.
- Well, that's dirty. Using me against me.
You can't do that.
Well...
...maybe I picked that up
along the way too.
- Lance.
MAN". Sir, we got a report from the wharf site.
- Somer's imports.
- I'll be right there.
I've gotta go.
There's something going on at the docks.
Somers.
Oh, God, no, no, no.
He can't help you.
I want the truth about Victor Nocenti.
- I can't. The triad will kill me.
- The triad's not your concern right now.
All right. All right, all right.
It wasn't me that killed him.
- It was the triad.
- Acting on whose instructions?
- Whose?
- All right, all right. It was mine.
It was mine, all right?
Nocenti said
he was gonna testify against me.
It's the police.
Drop your weapons.
You're surrounded.
Come out with your hands on your head.
Freeze.
You twitch and you're dead.
Bow down, hands up.
It was mine. It was mine, all right?
Nocenti said
he was gonna testify against me.
Son of a bitch.
Laurel was right.
I can't be the Oliver
my mother wants me to be...
...and still keep the promise
I made to my father.
I have to be the person
I need them to see me as.
Okay, this is a surprise.
- Did you show up here by mistake?
- By invitation.
- Oh...
- Oliver invited me last night.
- Last night?
- Is that surprise orjealousy I'm hearing?
Look, I just don't want him
to find out anything, okay?
- Oliver has been through a lot.
- Tommy, we've all been through a lot.
Good afternoon
and thank you all for coming.
Welcome to the future site of the Robert
Queen Memorial Applied Sciences Center.
Now this is a building that will stand
as a monument...
...to the man whose company
and vision are his greatest legacies.
Whoa! Whoa.
Mm.
What about me? Right? I'm a legacy.
Hey, thanks for warming them up, Walt.
All right. Fine, fine. Shovel. I got it.
Whoa! Oh.
I'm kidding. I'm kidding.
I got it. I got it.
Some of you may not know me.
My name is Oliver Queen.
Watch some television, read a newspaper,
I'm kind of famous right now.
Mostly, though, I'm famous
because I'm Robert Queen's son.
Uh, but as Walter, who's my new dad...
Huh? Who is... Sorry.
As Walter was saying,
I'm not much of a legacy, per se, and--
- Oliver, you don't have to do this--
- No, sit. Sit. Gosh.
See, I was supposed to come here today...
...and I'm supposed to take
my rightful place at the company.
Prodigal son returns home
and becomes the heir apparent.
But I'm not my father.
I'm not the man he was.
I'm not half the man he was.
I never will be.
So, please, stop asking me to be.
Martin Somers, CEO of Starling Port...
...arrested for the murder of Victor Nocenti.
He is also being accused of accepting cash,
including over ten million in bribes.
We can pursue the civil suit if you want,
but the DA now has no choice...
...with Mr. Somers' confession,
to prosecute him.
He's going to jail, Emily.
For the rest of his life.
Thank you so much for fighting for us.
Well, thank you for being brave enough
to let me.
HEN-
I thought I didn't need
police protection anymore.
I thought I didn't need a reason
to see my daughter.
You don't.
Hm. You look tired.
I was filling out reports
on the shoot-out at the port...
...and getting grilled about
how I let that archer get away.
I have to admit, I'm kind of glad he did.
He brought down Martin Somers.
He hurt a bunch of people doing it.
He is no hero. He's an anarchist.
Yeah, well, whoever he is,
it seems like he's trying to help.
The city doesn't need that help.
I always told you...
...you don't go outside the law
to find justice.
No, I believe that, all right?
And I promise you, when I catch this guy...
...he's gonna believe it too.
Well, you saw for yourself.
My son knows nothing.
Robert didn't tell him anything
that could hurt us.
He has no idea
that the yacht was sabotaged.
All that time on the island,
plotting my return...
...I didn't realize
how hard it would be...
...to reconnect with Morn, Thea...
...Laurel. Okay, I didn't...
I didn't know how painful it would be
to keep my secrets.
You asked me to save the city.
To right your wrongs.
I will.
I swear.
But to do that, I can't be the Oliver
that everyone wants me to be...
...which means that sometimes...
...to honor your wishes...
...I need to dishonor your memory.
I'm sorry.
Take it down.
Will you be going out tonight, sir?
Definitely.