My name is Oliver Queen.
After five years in hell,
I returned home with only one goal,
to save my city.
But my old approach wasn't enough.
I had to become someone else.
I had to become something else.
I had to become the Green Arrow.
Previously on Arrow...
Someone else is
throwing their hat in the ring.
- Who?
- Ruvé Adams.
I'm Oliver.
He can't know that you're
his father. And nobody else can.
I know who Oliver Queen cares about
more than anyone.
Who?
His son. William.
Merritt Davis will be
moderating the debate.
There 'II be a podium there,
another one there.
And according to tradition,
the selection's made
by some coin-toss thingy.
Mr. Queen.
At last, we meet.
Ms. Adams.
I'm just curious,
is Adams your maiden name?
Oh, I'm not married, actually.
- Really?
- Mmm.
Well, I'm sure you just haven't
met the right person yet.
Well, it is lovely to finally meet you.
An unconventional candidate,
to say the least.
Bit of a dark horse yourself.
Just meaning that your candidacy
seems to have come out of nowhere.
Well, generally, I prefer to keep
my philanthropic works quiet,
but the city is in simply too much trouble
for me to remain in the shadows.
Yes, it is.
The people destroying our homes
need to be fought in the light of day.
Well, I hope that we have
a productive debate, Mr. Queen.
I look forward to it.
Ms. Adams.
More like Mrs. Deceitful Darhk.
I feel like "Adams" probably polls better.
You know, it's not like we can prove
that Adams isn't her real last name.
How is our opposition research coming?
Nothing yet.
She's apparently clean.
But the more we do digging
into her and her background,
the more likely
she is gonna dig into ours.
I think that's our cue.
Hey, wait, I really need you to take a
look at these engagement-party invites.
My mom's been hounding me.
The envelope is very pink.
I know. Wait, don't...
Open it.
You should've totally
seen that one coming.
I'm so sorry.
- What do you think?
- Maybe less glitter.
You look good in glitter.
Yeah, let's move out.
The valet's bringing up her car.
All right, Laurel's got the eyeball.
You should move.
Are you gonna be all right in here?
Oh, yeah. Great Wi-Fi.
Overwatch on.
I've got her approaching 7th.
You think she's headed to her house again?
Like she did the last six times
we trailed her, you mean?
She has to be coordinating
with Darhk somehow.
We keep this up, we learn how,
we find out where he is.
I've run out of roof.
I'm On it.
If she turns left on Wilson,
she'll be headed home.
She's not. Right turn.
Could be our lucky night.
Speedy, you're it.
Got her.
Green Arrow,
are you ready for the handoff?
Already there.
I've got eyes on.
- I lost her.
- What do you mean?
That pursuit was textbook.
You had an appointment
with my husband the other week.
He does not take kindly to being stood up.
And he has a little something to say
about you stalking his wife as well.
FELICITYI Are you all right?
She got away again.
Okay. So clearly, we're not gonna
find Darhk by tailing his wife.
Yeah, well, it's not like we have
a lot of moves left to make.
Darhk has gone, well, dark,
ever since Machin attacked his family.
Darhk is not afraid of Machin.
He's just...
His plan's gone to a new phase.
But how do you know that?
Because HIVE spent months
trying to cripple this city's leadership.
They discouraged people
from running for mayor.
They even tried to co-opt my candidacy.
Yeah, then Mrs. Evil
threw her hat in the ring.
There has to be a reason.
Darhk did not try and destroy Star City
so that his wife could be mayor.
There's something that we're not seeing.
Oh, I can see it.
Clear as day.
You on the podium, Thursday night,
vexing Oliver Queen
with your political legerdemain.
Until we take him out
of the game completely, you mean.
Oh, you're not reconsidering the plan?
Malcolm Merlyn reached out,
gave me an early birthday present.
It would be a shame not to make use of it.
Ah! My buddies.
Let's get the rest of
the organization on the line.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I am giddy to report that
Phase 4 is proceeding on schedule.
There's still some concern
about the Star City operation.
Enlighten me.
Phase 5 requires control over City Hall.
Yet, somehow, we've found ourselves
mired in a petty political race
to see that happen.
We didn't exactly plan
on Oliver Queen, did we?
No one ever does.
I think what Mr. Armitage
is too polite to say
is that Phase 5 now rests
on your wife's questionable
political acumen.
Tomas, how is Madrid this time of year?
I remember taking a siesta
in your office, once.
I can practically picture
the room right now.
As if I'm actually in it.
Okay, then. Anything else to cover?
Well, there is the matter
of Quentin Lance.
He's clearly been aiding the vigilantes.
I can confirm as much.
Don't worry.
That loose end is about to be well tied.
Hi.
Hey, time for my 8:00 feed already?
Funny. I thought you could use
a little pick-me-up.
I think you used that excuse last week
to check up on me.
DA's office never worked
with my department so much.
I'm just... I'm worried about you.
No kidding.
No, Dad, seriously.
Darhk has to know that you're the one that
gave up the Ghost base of operations.
And I go to work every day
surrounded by men and women with guns.
It is all right, sweetheart.
It's all right.
Hello. Lance. Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, all right.
I'll be there in 10.
I've got a possible 602.
Isn't that a little below your pay grade?
Uh, yeah, that's how shorthanded we are.
Good, I'll come with you.
I'll wait in the car,
and then we can go for dinner.
I got plans with Donna.
That's even better.
I've been wanting to spend some time with
the woman that won over my father's heart.
Oh, wow.
Oh, I knew we should've had Slade Wilson
do the party planning.
Hey, guys. lam...
You know, I don't know how I'm gonna
get everything done in time.
- Maybe we should cancel.
- What?
I think what Felicity is trying to say
is that we just don't...
We don't want you working too hard.
I don't consider this work.
I think of it as a dry run
for your wedding.
- Mmm-hmm.
- So listen,
we are gonna have
party favors over in that corner,
we're gonna have a champagne tower
right here, mmm-hmm,
and we're gonna play games
over by the fireplace.
Oh, oh, oh, I brought my favorite,
Pin The Junk On The Hunk.
FELICITYI Oh, my God.
Sorry. Is this bad timing?
For who?
- Is everything okay?
- Yeah. We got to, uh...
- Yeah.
- Uh, where are you going?
Duty calls. Sorry. Sorry, sorry.
Is everything okay?
So, Alex got a phone call from one of the
lawyers doing research on the opposition,
and it looks like
they might've found something.
On Ruvé?
On you, actually.
In 2013, Homeland Security
did a tax audit after the Undertaking,
and looks like Mom wrote
a million-dollar check
to some woman named Samantha Clayton.
I mean, Alex flagged it as something
potentially weird for us.
By weird, he means...
Well, the check was never cashed.
So, why would Mom write a check
for a million dollars
to a woman young enough
to be her daughter,
and why would that woman
not cash the check?
I don't know.
Should I look into this Samantha person?
I don't really see the point.
I mean, whatever was going on
with this Samantha person,
clearly, she wanted
nothing to do with Morn.
And either way, I don't... It's just...
I don't see how something like this
would blow back on me.
Thank you.
Okay.
Everything has unfolded
according to providence.
What do you think is under there, anyway?
Power, Mr. Queen.
I'm glad you have recuperated.
We have much to accomplish together.
Reiter's pet.
You don't know what you're talking about.
I know you killed Vlad.
I watched. We all did.
What are you going to do?
Kill him right in front of Reiter's men?
They don't care what we do to him.
They remember what he did to Conklin.
Maybe you men need to go
for a drink or something.
A 602 is breaking and entering.
Why would they need backup
in the form of a police captain?
I told you, we're shorthanded.
Don't worry.
It's not a job for Black Canary.
SCPD! Anyone here?
Yeah, this is Lance. Get me dispatch.
- (Dad!
- {GROANS)
Come on.
Thought I told you to stay in the car.
Yeah, you're welcome.
Go, go, go!
Laurel! Laurel! Go! Go, get out!
Get out! Come on!
Go, go, go!
Are you okay?
What the hell was that?
I don't know. It's like the building
attacked me or something.
But that's not possible.
Is it?
Captain, you move again
and it's gonna leave an even bigger scar.
What happened?
Your guess is as good as mine.
It's like the Big Bad Wolf
huffed or puffed or something.
This wolf being Darhk.
Why do you think they
went through so much trouble
to make it look like an accident?
Maybe they didn't want to take the heat
of killing a police captain.
Thanks for the needlepoint.
Where are you going?
Yeah, if Damien Darhk
has you in his gun sights,
it might not be a good idea
to show yourself in the open.
Uh, I'm meeting with Donna.
Oh, she's fine.
She's probably just playing
Pin The Junk On The Hunk or something.
- What?
- Do not ask. Do not ask.
Stay here for a minute
and let us do what we do.
Look, I'm gonna check with Andy.
See if he's ever seen HIVE
use these tactics before.
Besides, I'm on Daddy duty.
Now that Lyla's the head of A.R.G.U.S.
I'm gonna try and backtrace the call
that supposedly came from dispatch.
I am...
Going to go work on your debate prep?
Yeah.
Debate prep, just took the words
right out of my mouth.
Yep.
This man deserves to die. He tortured us!
And he saved me.
At great risk to himself,
he kept me alive.
I have more reason than anyone
to hate this man.
But he's our best chance of going home.
He killed your brother.
Yes, he did.
Tell them why.
The guard, Conklin, he put Vlad up to it.
I was defending myself. He attacked me.
Now, I...
I know that you have no reason
to trust me,
but I am not your enemy.
All I want to do is stop Reiter,
and get all of you out of this place.
So prove it.
How?
Kill Conklin.
Aside from my brother,
have you killed before?
Yeah.
There was a man in Hong Kong.
And I did terrible things to him.
And that made me a monster.
And you're afraid killing Conklin
will make you into this monster again?
Good.
It takes a monster to fight monsters.
I like this midday summons.
It's very mysterious.
Very sexy-
Pooh Bear, what happened to you?
It's nothing. Listen...
No, baby, it doesn't look like nothing.
Oh, my gosh. Come sit down.
Aw, my big, tough police-captain baby.
- Can I make it all okay...
- No. No, no. Listen to me.
We can't see each other for a while.
What?
Yeah, it's a thing I got into.
I owe some guys some money.
You gamble? Mr. Straight and Narrow?
Yeah, it helped me cope
after I quit drinking.
And I've pissed off
some pretty tough customers and...
Wait a minute, wait, honey,
please, please, I'm a Vegas girl, okay?
Whomever you owe money to
is gonna have to get up pretty early
in the morning to take me on.
So, don't worry.
Sweetheart, it's a little more
complicated than that.
Just for a few weeks. That's all.
That's it.
You know, how about we make it longer?
- What?
- My ex-husband was a lying son of a bitch.
Only two good things
came out of that marriage,
my daughter and my BS detector,
which is flawless.
And right now, yeah, it's redlining.
Donna, you, don't... Please...
Don't... Oh, my God. Don't "Donna" me.
You know what?
This is actually very simple.
You either respect me enough
to tell me the truth, or you don't.
Clearly, you don't.
Donna, please...
- Hey, Mom.
- Hey, honey.
I'm fine.
What did you do?
Why you think it's me
that did something?
Because you're a man.
I'm trying to put some distance between us
in case Darhk is after me,
because I can't stand the idea
of anything happening to her, Felicity.
Yeah, but she looked pretty upset.
Yeah.
Oliver's not here.
I was looking for you.
I found something.
The 602 didn't come from
SCPD dispatch at all.
Someone just made it look like it did.
That someone being HIVE, you're thinking.
There's an encryption on it
that uses the same cipher of a HIVE
sat phone that Merlyn gave us.
- One more time.
- They lured you to the hotel.
Do we know where the call came from?
Price and 14th.
Bunch of other calls
came from there as well.
I'm guessing
it's their base of operations.
Okay. Contact the team,
and have them meet me there.
Yep.
Split up.
Job seems easy enough.
Don't get cocky.
Darhk won't tolerate another screw-up.
Where's Jack?
"HARDHAT". Patrolling.
Why?
Ahh!
Blow it! Let's move!
Go, go, 90!
They're demoing the factory,
just like they did the hotel.
You guys go get Spartan, okay?
I'm gonna get the laptop.
Speedy“ 'N0.go!
Hey, can you walk?
I don't have much of a choice.
- Where's Speedy?
- Right behind us.
Please tell me that the nails
are the clue,
and not what's on the laptop's hard drive
because there are three nails running
straight through this thing.
Yeah, the bad guys went a little crazy
with that nail gun.
Yeah, according to Andy,
they're called the Demolition Team.
Former GRU, IRA, and Mossad.
They're experts in precision demolition.
Now they work for HIVE.
I got a look at the laptop
before it got shot up,
and there were blueprints on the screen.
So they are gonna take down
another building.
Felicity?
I know. The first time we met,
the first thing you asked me to do
is pull data off a damaged laptop.
It's kind of romantic.
In case the laptop is a dead end,
lam going to work up
a list of potential targets.
Yeah, Andy is supposed to
get some more intel.
I'll see if he's made any progress.
Huh. Mom.
Wonder what took her so long.
What was that about?
Donna called it quits.
Oh. I'm sorry to hear that.
Yeah, yeah, me too.
You're lucky you're with someone
you don't need to keep secrets from.
Are these really necessary?
Can't risk you jeopardizing
your life again.
You're much too important.
You know, you keep saying that to me,
but I have no idea what you mean.
Do you believe in destiny, Mr. Queen?
I prefer the idea of free will.
This map conceals deeper truths.
Secrets I couldn't uncover
without more information,
until you brought these to me.
Except, I didn't bring them to you.
Conklin took them.
Destiny, Mr. Queen.
With the survey maps' details,
I was able to decipher
the inscriptions on this,
which you also provided me.
Are you beginning to see it now,
the pattern?
The trend of providence?
Legend tells of a hidden place,
within which lies
a device of untold power.
The quest to find it requires one
who has been granted passage by the gods.
I believe that person is you.
Hey, you're needed upstairs.
Keep Mr. Queen company till I return.
We still have much to discuss.
All this magic mumbo jumbo.
The way it saved your neck with Reiter,
maybe I ought to start
believing in it, myself.
Ain't easy
when it looks like toilet paper.
Boy, you got some balls.
I'm gonna enjoy watching you die.
I am... I...
Ugh. I didn't want to bother you
when you walked in on us
at Oliver's campaign office, but I'm...
It's okay.
No, honey, no. No, it's not.
- It's actually not okay.
- It's okay.
After your father, after all these years,
I thought I finally found the one man
who wouldn't lie to me, okay?
Maybe he's got a good reason.
Yeah. Right.
Honey, I want you to know
that I'm really sorry
that I've been going all Momzilla
for this engagement party...
Momzilla.
Do you want to know why
I pushed the tiaras and...
The ten-tiered cake?
Well, that's because you've loved
princesses since before you could walk.
Yes, that, and, um...
I've been living vicariously
through you.
You and Oliver are one of those couples
that everyone believes in.
You don't lie to each other.
Even
And he's gonna be the best daddy
in the whole world
- when that time comes.
- Ah.
You know that, don't you?
In my bones.
And when I see something that beautiful
and that rare and that romantic,
it also reminds me that,
you know, I'm never gonna
find a love like that.
Yes, you will.
You have it now with Captain Lance.
No, honey, no.
Not if he's hiding something from me.
Maybe he's doing it to protect you.
Because he loves you.
And you need to return that love
with a little bit of trust.
- I love you.
- I love you, too.
Crime, health care, taxes,
business incentives,
you've actually
pretty much nailed them all.
Stop sounding so surprised, please.
Well, I mean, you did spend
your education nailing chicks,
not doing social studies.
Okay. I'm sort of wiped.
- Can we wrap this up, maybe?
- Um...
Yeah, I did just have
one more question for you.
Okay.
Why didn't you tell me you went to college
with Samantha Clayton?
I was with Samantha Clayton
while I was dating Laurel.
And I'm not proud of that, so...
So why did Mom pay her a million dollars?
Thea, I told you, Mom is...
Ollie, I, um... I looked her up.
Right after you guys broke up,
she moved to Central City.
She's got a son
named William.
- Who's about as old as that check is...
- Okay, Thea.
When we were in Central City,
I knew something was bothering you,
and I knew it just wasn't Vandal Savage.
I mean, now it makes sense.
William's your son, isn't he?
Yes, he is.
Why haven't you told anyone?
Because Samantha said that
the only way that I could see him
is if I promised to not tell him,
or anyone else, that I'm his father.
God, that's...
That is brutal. Are you okay?
I thought I was doing okay.
I spent a lot of time
convincing myself that I was...
That I was trying to do
the right thing, but then,
you know, you brought this,
the thing with the check, and I'm not...
It's not your fault, but it's...
You bring it up right when we're trying
to plan an engagement party.
So, I'm left to think,
"How can I marry Felicity"
"if there is this lie between us?"
It's not a lie.
Okay? It's a promise that you are keeping
to the mother of your child...
Doesn't make it right, Thea.
Look at it from Samantha's perspective.
As far as she knows,
- you are a rich playboy...
- Right.
Who slept with a bunch of women,
and got her pregnant.
I'm not that person anymore.
Now you're the Green Arrow.
Anyone who comes into your life
is automatically a target.
What Samantha is asking for you to do...
As hard as it may be,
it is the right thing to do.
I know you want to tell Felicity...
And trust me, I would love to be an aunt.
But you have got to do the right thing
for your son here.
As hard as this may be for you, Ollie,
keeping William a secret
is keeping him safe.
Yes, John.
Andy did a little digging on the dark web.
Found out the Demolition Team
uses a specialized acid
that can weaken building structures.
Only one warehouse in the city stocks it.
- Text me the address, I'll be right there.
- I'm coming with you.
No, no, no. Just...
It's a long shot, at best.
- Thea.
- Yeah?
- Thank you.
- For what?
Just saying what I needed to hear.
I'll clear the area.
Too late. They cleaned this place out.
Yeah, took 100 gallons
of that acid with them.
Whatever they plan on taking down...
ls massive.
Hey! Uh, hope I'm not bothering you. I...
Uh, Curtis, why is my face
your screen saver?
At the risk of early termination,
uh, none of your business.
- Curtis!
- Please don't ask.
I'm, like, super bad with secrets.
Okay. It's an early wedding gift,
but it's really bad luck if you see it,
so, please stop trying to see it.
Okay, I think you're getting
your wedding traditions confused,
but fine, I will let it go.
Lucky for you,
I have more important concerns.
I maxed out the computer power
in the lair, again,
and I was hoping maybe your mainframe
might have better luck.
- I'll do my best.
- Thank you.
Really, me on a screen saver, hmm?
Whatever the surprise is,
it better be good.
Oh, it will be.
Well, that's not
your typical nighttime suit.
You're the reason I'm wearing it.
Inspiring me to save this city
in the light of day.
Fine inspiration I turned out to be,
hiding down here in the dark.
For your protection.
You haven't told Donna, have you?
No.
How you kept this up
for four years, huh?
This double life,
these secrets, lying, I mean...
I'm trying not to live that way anymore.
Trying.
You know in AA,
we say you're only as sick
as the secrets you keep.
You're looking pretty healthy these days.
And I just hope I can get back
to that place with Donna.
For what it's worth,
you're in a tough spot,
and you're trying to keep her safe.
You know, sometimes, a lie isn't wrong
when it's for the good
of someone that you love.
Just so you know, after I'm done with you,
I'ma gut that slave girl, just for kicks.
All the rest of 'em, too.
You're never hurting them ever again.
There he is. There's the killer.
You stupid son of a bitch.
Reiter's gonna kill everyone
no matter what you do.
So, Ruvé's probably gonna question you
on your party-boy past,
but if she does we just gotta...
If she does, just steer the conversation
back towards the issues.
- I've got it.
- Yep.
Alex's mom kind of picked the wrong week
to go in for surgery, don't you think?
I couldn't agree more.
We got about 20 minutes until we're live,
so, how're you feeling?
Are you nervous at all or...
You know, I don't think that "nervous"
is in Oliver's vocabulary.
Yes, but "translucent matte powder"
should be.
You don't want to shine under
those big bright lights.
Hey, why do we... No.
Why do we even need makeup?
We're not even gonna be onstage.
Reaction shots, sweetie.
Plus, I just... I love makeup.
- Mom, Mom, Mom!
- What?
- I gotta take this.
- Oh, okay.
You know what? I'm gonna be right back.
I hate this. It's a horrible powder puff.
It's just... It's awful.
That was fast.
You sound surprised. I don't know
whether to be flattered or insulted.
- Okay, Curtis. What did you get?
- Not much. Just a set of blueprints.
Pretty underwhelming, considering.
I'm uploading it to you now.
Curtis, I gotta call you back.
Oliver, I need you.
What's wrong?
I know what building
HIVE is planning on taking down.
It's this one.
Okay,
I have a million questions.
But first, why would HIVE
try to attack the debate?
To take me out and discourage
anyone else from running.
Okay. But Darhk's wife is here
at ground zero.
So it doesn't really make sense to...
Unless Darhk's demolition team is
gonna wipe everyone out except for Ruvé.
Leaving Mrs. Darhk a sympathetic survivor
instead of the pot of evil stew
that she actually is.
Can you identify the likely areas
the bombs would be in?
Yeah, according to the schematics,
it's these three points.
But this building, it's huge.
We need to split up and cover more ground.
Okay, good thing
we brought a change of clothes.
Call Laurel and Diggle.
Can you hack the fire alarm?
We need to evacuate the building.
It's an old system.
It might take me a minute.
Yeah, I learned that in high school.
So, we could...
Listen to me very carefully.
Change of plans.
Do not let Oliver Queen
leave this building alive.
Copy that.
Hey, I finally found it.
Where's Oliver and Thea?
Oh, they're probably just inside
making sure everyone gets out okay.
You left them inside? Honey, come on,
we need to go help them. Let's go.
- Excuse me. Outta the way.
- Excuse us.
Captain Lance,
you're supposed to be... Not here.
What kind of cop sits on the sidelines
when people's lives are at risk?
You stay here.
I count three charges, but no Demo Team.
What do you see?
Same here. No hostiles.
"SPEEDY". Lots of ticky-tocky bombs.
More charges down here.
I see the countdown.
13:25 until detonation.
That's two minutes
after the debate starts.
We need to disarm these things.
Disarming one now.
I hope this neutralizing agent works.
Ahh!
- You okay?
- Yeah.
The place is booby-trapped.
Be careful up there.
Or don't. It's not polite to touch things
that ain't yours.
Yeah, you're not the only one with tricks.
Watch out!
Speedy!
We're clear.
It's clear down here, too.
Top is clear. Thanks.
Sure you should be out in the open?
Don't you have somewhere to be
right about now?
I checked the cafeteria,
the green room, everywhere.
Everywhere except
for the bathroom, apparently.
Sorry. Nervous bladder, I think.
Oh, that was something
I never needed to hear, ever.
- Um, are you ready to go?
- More than.
All right, come on, buddy.
Come on.
Captain Lance never lets his man get away.
You shouldn't either.
Nice applause.
It's enough to bring the house down.
Almost.
Good luck.
Despite a bomb threat, tonight's
mayoral debate then went on as scheduled
with Mr. Queen being declared,
by most pundits, the clear winner.
Oh! Of course he's the clear winner.
He's marrying my daughter.
Well, I think you're a little biased.
Did Alex call with the new poll numbers?
Well, if Bethany Snow is right,
he doesn't have to.
Experts are saying that you already won.
- Experts aren't the voters.
- Okay.
Well, you at least have one voter
in your camp.
- Me!
- Only one that matters.
Mmm.
Conklin may have had his difficulties,
but he was a good man.
Yeah. He was a good man who attacked me.
- Self-defense.
- As it was with her brother?
I'm not saying it lacks irony.
I need you alive, Mr. Queen.
But there are different forms of alive.
Don't test me again.
You did it.
- What was that for?
- Thank you.
I don't need thanks, Taiana.
Before he died, Conklin told me
that Reiter was gonna kill everybody here.
We don't have much time.
Thank you.
Uh, John, can I introduce you
to Laura Hoffman?
- Laura.
- Oh, don't mind if I do. John, hi.
Laura was our neighbor in Ivy Town.
She drove all day to get here.
Please. The drive was nothing.
I've been waiting five months
for this moment to finally arrive.
Oh, hey, have you started
your wedding registry yet?
Because I may very well have
the perfect gift idea for you.
Oh, let me guess. Slow cooker?
HOW did she...
- How did you know that?
- I'm telepathic.
Excuse me, sorry to interrupt,
but I need you both.
Photographer is here.
- Did you invite him?
- Who? Me? Uh...
- Sorry, could I talk to you for a minute?
- Yes, absolutely.
- Felicity...
- What?
The photographer's right over there.
We will make it there just fine
by ourselves.
- Captain.
- Nice to see you.
Please.
Thanks. It's quite the party
you've got going on here.
What? What?
What do you want to talk about?
Well, I came here to apologize
because you were right. l...
I lied to you.
Because I was afraid
of how you would react to the truth.
That thing that I was worried about?
- It wasn't a gambling problem.
- It was HIVE.
The same people that...
- The same people that hurt my baby?
- Mmm.
Why wouldn't you tell me that?
'Cause I'm not in their gun sights
'cause I'm police.
I'm in their gun sights
'cause I stopped working for them.
You were working with Damien Darhk?
He threatened Laurel.
And the truth is,
I'm glad Darhk came after me and not her,
because if he'd done that, I...
You were protecting her.
Just like you were protecting me.
Well, I'll be...
- I'm so sorry.
- No.
Ah...
Is it possible to go blind
from too many flashes?
Take a little bit of a break.
Just for a moment.
I literally can't see a thing right now.
I think the cure for that is champagne.
Ah! Dr. Queen, I do believe you are right.
Curtis! Paul!
So glad you guys made it.
Quick. Grab a glass of this champagne.
Careful, he might drink the entire bottle.
- I like my bubbly, what can I say?
- Mmm-hmm.
Uh-uh-uh.
Mixing a downer with all the coffee
you've had in the last 72 hours?
Your head might explode.
Yeah, I have been pulling
a lot of crazy hours.
After my surprise was blown on my gift,
I wanted to finish it as soon as possible.
Thanks. We forgot to register
for microchips.
Actually, it's neither micro nor chip.
It's an implantable bio-stimulant.
And why would I need
an implantable bio-stimulant?
For walking.
Curtis...
In the perfect world, it'll work in time
for you to walk down the aisle.
I mean, but it's pretty cutting-edge,
and so I can't promise anything.
You're telling me that this little piece
of technology is gonna help me walk again?
After it's implanted in your spine, yes.
He's been trying
to crack it for a while,
but he needed a power source,
something that would last a lifetime.
- Palmer Technologies' power cell.
- Exactly.
Once I solved that,
I knew this might actually work.
Oh, my God.
I don't know what to say.
I do.
Curtis, you're terrific. Thank you.
No. Well, don't thank me yet.
It still has to work.
It'll work. I know it will.
You, come with me.
We're about to make my mother very happy.
- Hi, Daddy.
- Hi, sweetie.
Nora, honey,
there's someone I'd like you to meet.
Nora, this is William.
William's mother asked us
to look after him.
He'll be staying with us for a while.
Nice to meet you, William.
- You want to play?
- Sure.
English - SDH