My name is Oliver Queen.
After five years in hell,
I returned home with only one goal,
to save my city.
But my old approach wasn't enough.
I had to become someone else.
I had to become something else.
I had to become the Green Arrow.
Previously on Arrow...
I'm not gonna kill you.
But you need to trust me,
or we're both dead.
What this city needs is someone willing to
stand up in the light of day,
not a guy lurking around in the shadows.
I'm going to run for mayor.
What a pleasant surprise.
I want you to bring my sister
back to life.
Even if Sara went into the Pit,
even if it worked,
what came out of the Pit
would not be Sara.
"MALCOLM". We are in uncharted waters here.
I suggest you prepare yourself
for the worst.
Leave a couple of those
on the table, Junie.
Thought you said
we're delivering 40 kilos.
So they'll get 38.
Dumbasses can't count, anyways.
- Get out! Now! Now! Now!
- S.C.P.D.! On the ground!
Clear!
- MALE SWAT 11 Clear!
- All clear!
We're good to go here.
S.C.P.D., hands in the air!
Relax. We got this.
What're you guys doing here?
We didn't hear a call for ESU go out.
You guys
aren't supposed to be here, either.
Well, we got a tip from one of our Cls.
Sons of bitches.
Let's go.
Well, this is horrible.
What type of secret lair has windows?
Well, you know, Oliver said
he wanted to do things differently.
I think I just saw a cockroach.
Listen, about Oliver...
Oh, no. Look, it's fine, he
still thinks
we spent the weekend at a spa.
But why can't we tell him about Sara?
Sara, she needs more time.
And I don't need Oliver's judgment.
Just a couple more days,
and she'll be back to herself.
I promise.
Guessing he didn't tell you
what we're doing here, either.
No. He just had a perma-grin on his face
the whole way here.
Okay, now I'm worried.
He said he has some big announcement
to make.
Oh, my God, wait.
Where is it? Why aren't you wearing it?
Wearing what?
Uh...
What is it that you wanted to tell us?
And why are you telling us here?
- Remember this office?
- Yes.
This was
Sebastian Blood's campaign office.
And now it's mine.
Anyone who's qualified is afraid to run,
for good reason.
But I can protect myself.
So, I'm running for mayor.
Uh, don't everyone
congratulate me at once.
- Oh, you're serious?
- Yes.
The other week, Lance was saying
that this
city needs someone to stand up,
who isn't hiding behind a mask.
- It needs a leader.
- But why does that person have to be you?
I mean, don't get me wrong,
but you're not a politician.
Well, maybe that's the best reason
for me to be elected.
What are you going to do for a staff,
or campaign manager, money?
The money part's taken care of.
Palmer Tech has funded enough
to kick-start the campaign.
The decision I'm sure
my Board of Directors
are gonna be thrilled with.
What platform are you gonna run on?
- I'll figure it out.
- What qualifies you to be mayor?
I care about this city.
But you can't say that you're gonna run
because being the Green Arrow
isn't enough.
I'm working on that.
We need to brush up on those answers
before the first press conference.
Obviously.
Kind of thought everyone would
be a little bit more supportive.
It's not that
we're not supportive, Oliver.
- It's just...
- We just want to make sure
- that you're not in over your head.
- Yeah.
Maybe the other announcement
will go over better.
Okay.
For real?
There's a reason we had Felicity
buy Blood's campaign office.
Blood also needed his own lair.
But don't worry,
I burned a lot of incense.
- Oliver, how did you...
- How did you do this all by yourself?
- Well, I had help.
- He had a lot of help.
Cisco and S.T.A.R. Labs.
Four polycarbonate cases,
each keyed to your individual biometrics.
God, I didn't even think
you could pronounce biometrics.
I had some design input.
Wow!
Oliver, this is amazing.
Well, when I set up shop in the foundry,
it was just me.
That's not the case anymore, so I thought
we could use a little more space.
What was that? Did it break?
- Oh.
- You okay?
Yeah, I'm just not used to this chair yet.
I'm feeding police emergency services and
Homeland Security radio transmissions
through a processing algorithm, 24/7.
This way, if anything happens in the city,
we will know about it.
Two police detectives found shot to death
responding to a code three.
Um, there's no record of them
calling dispatch for backup.
Which means either their comms failed,
or they were ambushed
the moment they arrived on the scene.
Thea and I will do recon.
See if there's anything
the CSI missed at the crime scene.
Right. I'll talk to Lance.
Maybe skip the part
about running for mayor
because I'm pretty sure
you're not gonna have his vote.
That'll have to change.
Can't run the city
without the help of the S.C.P.D.
- Okay.
- Hmm.
What did Thea think that you were wearing?
Noidea.
Fast track ballistics and have
CSI dust every shell casing for latents.
Hey, Forensics recovered this. SIM card.
Probably belongs to one of the doers,
but CSU says they need 48 hours
to get a full work-up.
What? How is evidence from a crime scene
where two detectives were killed
not a top priority?
We don't have the manpower.
You spend more time here now
than when you were getting collared
- for hitting paparazzi.
- You have a moment for me?
Yeah.
So these visits,
are they gonna be a weekly thing?
Well, I was just trying to help with...
- What's that?
- I wouldn't know.
City Hall has cut my budget so tight,
I can't get evidence turned around
before I'm 80.
I'm hoping that's something
I might be able to help with eventually.
- Yeah?
- I've decided to run for mayor.
- Really?
- And I know it's a long-shot,
but it would mean a lot
if you would endorse my candidacy.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, sure.
After what happened
to the last few mayors,
I'm hoping you win in a landslide.
Till then,
I'm trying to catch a cop killer
and I don't have time to wait
for my under-staffed crime lab.
I want you to wait until nightfall
to light a fire.
Okay? Otherwise,
you're gonna draw attention. All right.
There's fresh water coming off a stream
at the base of the hill.
There's edible plants, maybe 50 feet
to the north.
Just... Hey. Do not eat the red berries.
And do not let anyone see you.
Why are you doing this?
Risking your life, to save mine.
It's complicated.
They may think I'm dead, but
they're going to come looking for you...
They're not gonna come looking for me.
I'm going back to camp.
I've watched those men.
They are like brothers to each other.
They have a history. A bond.
You are not one of them.
That's why you're gonna have to
do something for me.
And you're not gonna like it.
All right, so I figured it out.
It's Neal Adams in data processing.
He won the archery medal
three years running at a summer camp,
he has a problem with his temper,
and he likes the color green.
Right. You think that Neal Adams
is the Green Arrow?
- He's 5'2".
- Lifts?
I am not telling you who he is.
Oh, and B-T-dubb, next time you want to
prank your boss, worst career move,
but whatevs,
you might wanna try a little harder.
And you lost me.
- I've been receiving these all week.
- Okay, well, I didn't send this.
And trust me, if I were gonna prank you,
I'd be a lot more creative.
This code is from 2013.
But the IP address
is coming from Palmer Tech,
from a terminal here, in your workspace.
I believe the term is,
"You are so busted."
I'm not busted. I can't be busted.
I didn't send you two-year-old code.
Though it is elegant.
And familiar.
I was going through some of Mr. Palmer's
old prototypes, and I found this.
Yeah, that was Ray's.
I mean, Mr. Palmer's.
I mean, this has code that's, like,
identical to what you have on the phone.
I mean, the question is,
why is Mr. Palmer's prototype OS
sending you texts in your phone?
Ray must have connected
the prototype's computer
to the company's Local Area Network.
He did. it uploaded a crash log.
I mean, the equipment's programed
to record the user's voice
right before a fatal malfunction.
Sorry.
Poor choice of words.
The... The point is, is that
Mr. Palmer's last recorded statement
could shed some light on how he died.
Except that it's password protected.
I already know how he died.
I don't need to relive it.
- Bub-
- But“
Ray and I were close.
We were, um, friends.
He died six months ago, I don't
really want to open that particular wound.
- It did it again?
- No. Different mystery.
Lance gave us a SIM card
recovered from the crime scene.
Where's Laurel?
Said she had something
she needed to deal with.
Ah, it's a good thing you guys
aren't short-handed these days.
This SIM card isn't from a cell phone.
Looks like some kind of walkie with GPS.
GPS as in we can track it?
As in, I can figure out
all the places it's been
and triangulate from there
to determine, hmm, where it came from.
Gear up.
- Fifth floor is clear.
- Yeah, this place is completely empty.
I think I found something. Third floor.
Headed your way.
Every door here is open or unlocked.
Except for this one.
- Clear.
- It's not empty.
M-Fours, there's Kevlar,
Flashbang grenades...
Some of this stuff is military grade.
What, do you think
we found the Ghost armory?
No.
- Wait...
- Star City Police Department.
The people who killed those detectives
were police officers.
All right. All right, I'll bite.
- What are we doing down in your basement?
- It's better if I just show you.
After what happened between us last year,
I swore that I would never keep secrets
from you again.
Especially when it has to do
with our family.
Family? Oh, my...
Baby?
How's...
How is this even possible?
"LAUREL". The League of Assassins.
They have something called
the Lazarus Pit.
- It can bring someone back from the dead.
- Back, from what? From the...
This isn't back, Laurel. Look at her.
- Look at my baby. I don't...
- Dad, she's alive.
Your daughter is alive.
This isn't my daughter.
Daddy, it is, she's just been gone
for a really long time.
It's okay.
She'll remember who she is.
We just have to be patient,
and we'll help her find her way, right?
Do you remember me?
I'm Laurel. Your sister?
Look. There's me.
Then, this is you. Do you see that?
Yeah? And who's that?
Is that Daddy?
We're your family. We love you.
Who am I?
She's speaking because she's remembering.
Let me go. Let me go!
Laurel!
- You all right?
- I'm fine.
She just... She needs more time.
I think you better add
"Get an entirely new police force"
- to your campaign platform.
- It's not the entire force.
But, yeah,
we don't know who's compromised.
Well, except for Captain Lance.
Yeah, well,
Captain Lance is MIA right now.
I think it's safe to assume that
whatever help we're going to get
- is right here, in this room.
- I'm working on something.
Oh, Cisco said we were still working out
some of the kinks.
In the last two months, there's been
a huge spike on gangs stealing
- drug shipments from other gangs.
- Yeah, but it's not these gangs.
It was these bad cops.
Who steal the drugs to sell them back
to the gangbangers they stole them from.
So these corrupt cops are taking down
- big drug scores.
- Mmm-hmm.
- Let's give them one.
- How?
That depends on how close you are
with your former drug dealer.
Depends which one.
- We're going to need some money.
- Don't you mean more money?
Mmm-hmm.
Queenie.
I haven't seen you in forever.
This your boyfriend?
Bodyguard.
Didn't realize the Queens could afford
that kind of help these days.
Well, I recently came into my inheritance,
and was hoping to throw a party with it.
- So you can help me out?
- To the tune of...
Eighty keys. You know how I like to party.
I might have a hook-up.
But he doesn't take credit cards.
Let me make a call.
I've been trying to get in touch with you.
Uh, yeah, phone's been off. What is it?
You're gonna tell me
you're running for president now?
Your detectives aren't dead
because of gang violence.
- They were killed by cops.
- What are you talking about?
The SIM card that you gave us,
it led to the killer's armory,
and all the equipment, the weapons,
it was all S.C.P.D. issue.
- Who is it?
- It could be anyone in the department.
These guys have been taking down
drug busts.
So I've had Thea procure
a couple kilos of cocaine.
Your mayoral campaign
is off to a fantastic start then.
We're keeping the drugs
in a warehouse on Meldrum.
I need you to subtly get the word out.
All right.
Listen... Wait, wait, wait.
- I wanna be there when they show.
- I'm not sure that's a good idea.
Yeah, well, I'm not sure
I really give a damn.
Because, if I got bent cops
in my precinct,
I'm gonna be there to bust 'em.
- The hell happened to you?
- The woman tried to escape.
We chased her,
but she went through a mine field.
- Thought I heard an explosion earlier.
- That one got Richards.
- Son of a bitch.
- I caught her.
Eventually.
Made it memorable.
- What? I'm supposed to kill her, right?
- Her, yeah. Richards, not so much.
- I didn't kill Richards. I told you...
- Yeah, landmine. I know.
You know what's funny?
We've been here months without a problem.
And here you come, and two guys
get wasted by landmines.
What's that supposed to mean?
It means I want to see her.
The woman. I want to see the body.
Okay.
I know this is a trap and all,
but something about the drugs, the club...
It makes me feel like
I'm back in high school again.
What?
Just thinking about how much I hate
raising a daughter in this city.
Heads up. I'm reading a truck
closing in on your position.
The make matches the profile
for an ESU strike vehicle.
- Copy. We're ready.
- Two minutes out.
Captain Lance.
What, I don't get a code name
like the rest of you?
Detective. Get ready.
Targets on site. Let's go.
We've got multiple tangos! Move!
Move out!
You Okay?
The training, the equipment,
those were cops.
And no, I'm not okay.
You have got to be kidding me.
Uh, no, um...
Not to complain, but you do know
that you just brought a police captain
into our secret lair?
Don't worry.
I got enough to put you away for 25 years.
Kidding.
Captain Lance isn't the police
we should be worried about.
Wow! No wonder
there's corruption on the force.
Everyone else has got better resources.
I don't know.
Those ESU
had some pretty fancy toys tonight,
that definitely weren't
standard police issue.
Well, they were police issue, all right.
But just not standard.
Those were specialized anti-vigilante
task force gear.
I thought the task force was disbanded.
Yeah. I might've reinstated that, uh,
last year.
- How many officers are there?
- Forty or so.
Well, that definitely narrows things down
a bit.
We should check their conduct records.
Maybe that will narrow it down
a little bit more.
Yeah, that's gonna take
a little bit longer than usual.
Well, I can give you unrestricted access
to the department's computer network.
Might speed things up a little.
I'll see what I can dig up
at the precinct.
Looks like eighty keys here.
Idiots baited the mouse trap
with real cheese.
Because they knew
we'd sniff them out otherwise.
Well, it's a good thing we decided
to pack the special gear.
We weren't the only ones showing up
with a little surprise tonight.
- Captain Lance?
- There's no way he didn't peg us as cops.
- We got to take him out.
- We don't kill cops.
Tell that to the two gold shields
we wasted last night.
They were in the wrong place
at the wrong time.
I'm not killing fellow officers
in cold blood.
Our advantage was
the force thought we were gangbangers.
We should put this to a vote.
My vote's nine-millimeters
and the only one that counts.
We are not criminals.
Let's all just try to remember that.
We went this route
because this city is dying,
and we need to be able to provide
for our families.
It still doesn't change the fact
that Lance is a problem.
No. He's not.
He's a solution.
Curtis.
There you are.
Why haven't you been answering my texts?
Your texts were "9-1-1 OMG ASAP"
and five exclamation points.
I do not have time to respond to something
that doesn't contain
at least one actual word.
I need your help
with Mr. Palmer's crash log.
I thought I told you to let that go.
Look, I've tried brute-forcing
the password, but nothing works.
But there is a sub-kernel
that contains a programmer note.
Oh, my God, this must be
what talking to me is like.
And that programing note suggests that
you know the password.
I mean, which makes sense, right,
you and Mr. Palmer were friends.
- Yeah. I know the password.
- You do?
- So tell it to me so we can just...
- No, I...
I do not want to listen to a recording
of my ex-boyfriend's
final moment before he died.
You and Mr. Palmer were together?
Now, do you understand why
I don't want to hear his voice?
No.
My brother died six years ago.
Pancreatic cancer.
To be able to hear something from him
I'd never heard before?
God, I'd give anything.
Captain Lance. What a pleasure it was
to receive your message.
And for you to initiate contact, well,
it made me feel like our relationship
took an important step forward.
- I need your help.
- I'm sorry. Say that again?
It's for my daughter.
And not the one
that you're holding over me as leverage.
Sara, the one you lost last year.
Yeah, she's back.
This thing called the Lazarus Pit.
Sure you've heard of it.
What, you did your homework on me,
you don't think I did a little
digging around on you?
You used to be a member
of The League of Assassins.
What is it you want, Mr. Lance?
She's my daughter.
She's not right.
She's come back, and she's different.
- She's crazy.
- It's a miracle she came back at all.
It doesn't feel like a miracle, all right?
Now, you know about this stuff.
Is there anything I can do?
- Is there anything that you can do?
- I can give advice.
Father to father.
I can tell you that
if it were my daughter, I'd put her down.
- She's my baby girl.
- No, she isn't.
She may look like your daughter,
but she doesn't possess her soul.
The most loving act you can commit
is to return Sara to her final rest.
I'm sorry.
Oh!
Oh, I'm so glad we came back.
- You all right?
- Hmm?
You're doing that, um...
Crinkly thing, with your eyebrows.
Just...
No, just something at work.
It's no big deal. Um, this work, big deal.
Liza Warner.
I pulled her S.C.P.D. personnel file
using my computer at Palmer Tech
since ours is fritzing.
One of the original recruits
to the anti-vigilante task force
- over three years ago.
- Hand-picked by then-Detective Lance.
Do you think she's a suspect?
I think that Sergeant Warner has deposited
over a quarter of a million dollars
into offshore bank accounts
for the last three months.
- Where can we find her?
- I am working on that.
I used the network access
that Captain Lance gave us,
and I turned on every
uniform and squad car camera
on the force during the last 12 hours.
I'm running facial recognition
looking for Warner.
- Do you see something?
- No. Someone.
Pause.
Zoom in.
The man that Lance is talking to...
It's Damien Darhk.
You know I got a heart condition, right?
For years, you've looked at me
with such contempt...
Utter disdain.
So I'm wondering...
Do I have that same look on my face now?
- What the hell are you talking about?
- I'm talking about you.
And Damien Darhk.
Okay, it's, it's...
I didn't know if you knew who he was,
or what he's been doing to this city.
But now, I see this look on your face...
You know.
- It's complicated.
- No, it's not.
Do you have any idea
how many people he's killed?
Yeah, I've got more of an idea than you.
And listen, you of all people,
you don't get to come into my house
and pass judgment on me! All right?
You always held yourself out
as better than me!
More righteous.
And you were.
Until tonight.
Actually, it's been
a little more than two months now.
Me working with Darhk.
It started out benign.
He said he had resources,
he had people, money.
He held himself out as just another guy
who wanted to help this city.
And we needed the help.
You weren't here.
By the time I figured out who he was,
what he was...
- That's when he threatened Laurel.
- Laurel can take care of herself.
You see what she does out there.
- That's what I thought about Sara, too...
- Stop it! Stop it!
Stop hiding behind your daughters!
They would be ashamed
of what you're doing right now.
- You don't know what I'm going through...
- And you know the funny thing?
You were the main reason
behind me running for mayor.
A part of me has always wanted you to see
what kind of man I really am.
I didn't expect to wind up finding out
what kind of man you really are.
What're you gonna do?
I don't know.
So how'd you do it? Kill the woman.
How'd you do it?
I strangled her.
Thought you said you made it,
what was that word, memorable?
She won't forget it.
What? You gonna propose?
You don't sound like a guy
who just committed his first murder.
And I'm guessing
you didn't have too many opportunities
at whatever posh boarding school
you grew up in.
You think I'm lying?
I think if you're not,
then you're a stone cold killer.
Even if you didn't off her,
even if you're messing with me,
which I do not recommend...
I see it in your eyes.
Reiter saw it, too.
It's probably why he recruited you.
Saw what?
You are one dark bastard.
Something very cold inside of you.
And you're terrified of it.
Okay, Conklin, tell me something.
If I'm this dark person,
shouldn't you be afraid of me?
No.
I'm the exact same way.
If you're lying to me,
you're gonna find that out.
- Nice sign.
- Yeah. Arrived this morning.
Are you all right?
Just thinking.
About?
Going to Sentinel games as kids.
- Do you remember Papp Stadium?
- Oh, yeah.
I loved the popcorn.
Every time a Sentinels player
hit a homer,
every single person in that stadium
stood and cheered.
Every single one.
United.
And I wanted to run for mayor, because
I wanted to be the leader of that city.
Wanted?
Thea, I don't know
if that city exists anymore.
I think that it might be beyond saving.
So what are you saying?
That I don't have to run for mayor.
I'm sorry, baby, but you're not her.
You're not her.
Dad.
- Dad, what the hell are you doing?
- I'm doing what I got to do.
You got no idea the terrible things
I would do for both of you.
No. No, you're not gonna kill
your own daughter...
She's not my daughter!
It's Sara.
It's okay.
Oh, God.
What am I doing?
- What am I doing? What am I doing?
- It's okay. Look at me. It's okay.
You're okay. It's okay.
I'm sorry, baby, I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Captain Lance?
- Liza. What are you doing here?
- Heard you were looking for me.
- Thought I'd make it easier for you.
- The hell are you talking about?
What...
Dad!
Ever been here before?
It's the S.C.P.D.'s contraband
disposal facility.
Thousands of pounds of
Slam, Vertigo, heroin, all incinerated.
- That's just literally burning money.
- Yep.
And the site requires
a precinct Captain to gain access.
- And that's not happening.
- What was your plan, Quentin?
You have to know this city's dying.
You were just gonna stay at your
desk until there was no city left?
Tell you what I wasn't gonna do,
I wasn't gonna dishonor
the badge, like you have.
I'm no saint,
but at least I'm not a criminal.
Neither am l.
I'm just a desperate cop
who got backed into too tight a corner.
What do we know?
Liza Warner and her posse took Lance
outside of Laurel's apartment.
- We need to find my father.
- I'm working on it.
Just a little hampered.
I think I got something
before the latest glitch.
Captain Lance's ID was just used to access
the S.C.P.D. Contraband Disposal Facility,
three minutes ago.
Thank you, Quentin.
Sorry about all the paperwork you'll have
to fill out when they find you here.
Word of advice?
Put a bullet in my head now,
'cause I am coming after you
with everything.
By the time they find you,
we'll be long gone.
We're leaving this city
like everybody else.
New frequency. Same cry.
Let's get out of here.
Sergeant Warner,
you have failed this city.
Is that all you got?
Nope.
Get out of here.
All I got to do is push
and I'll sever your spinal cord.
But you're not gonna do it, Liza.
You said you're not a criminal.
You kill that man, you are.
I told you I wasn't a criminal.
But I also told you I was desperate.
We all are.
Living in this city,
dealing with what we're dealing with
right now, we're all desperate.
We've all been made to do
desperate things.
Terrible things.
But I've got to believe
that we are not beyond redemption.
I got to believe that
this city can still be saved.
'Cause once we stop believing,
that's when this city really dies
and us, us right along with it.
But, maybe...
Just maybe, we start saving our home
by saving ourselves first.
And that means facing up to our mistakes.
That means facing justice.
You put on that uniform
'cause you believe in justice.
Ask yourself, Warner.
Is that still the case?
Do what you got to do.
I guess you know your Miranda rights.
- You got your own key or something?
- What you said to Warner saved my life.
I didn't know you had such a way
with words.
Well I don't do encores.
You believe what you said?
Yeah. Every word.
Especially the part about facing justice.
When One Police Plaza opens this morning,
I will be there, turning myself in.
Can't have you do that.
We haven't been able
to get close to Darhk.
You have.
I'd like you to stick around.
Stay on the inside.
Well...
Well, that's only a smart plan
if you can trust me.
I trust the man who said
we can't stop believing
we can save this city.
- Like I said, stone cold killer.
- You satisfied?
Get rid of the body.
This cave might be useful for something.
It's okay. You're okay.
How did you...
Where did you learn to do that?
I learned it here.
I haven't always been alone
on this island.
Son of a bitch.
Oh, my God, he's here.
Hi.
How you doing, man?
Oliver Queen. Oh!
Hi, there.
It's, uh, absolutely wonderful
that, that all of you are here.
Just, just wonderful, and surprising.
So? What do you think?
Um, hey, did you, did you hire
all of these people?
No. That's what makes them interns, Ollie.
Where did we get all of these interns?
Easiest way to get a lot of followers
on social media
is to own a very successful club.
All I had to do was tell them
what I've already known for three years.
Oliver Queen is gonna save the city.
- What's this?
- This is your speech.
You're announcing your candidacy
this afternoon.
So you better get your suit out
of mothballs.
Did you write this?
I wrote it down.
I just went with what you told me.
About this city being united.
United.
That's what this city used to be.
It's what it can be,
it's what it must be, again.
Now I know that
I'm not the obvious choice for mayor.
I'm not a politician.
I signed away my family's company.
I didn't even graduate from college,
although in my defense,
I did go to four of them.
I certainly don't have
a traditional background for leadership,
but I can tell you this.
After five years in hell,
I returned home with only one goal.
I wanted to save my city.
And with your help, I can.
With your help, we will restore our home
to the shining beacon we know it can be.
Now how we're gonna get there
isn't a mystery.
We will overcome our challenges
with help from our friends...
Our family.
Our loved ones.
I'm sorry, Felicity. This is my fault.
Those we trust and those we will need to
trust again in order to prevail.
Because the only way that
we are gonna return our home to greatness
is to do so together.
United.
English - SDH