Previously on "Arrow"...
The prosecution's
smoking gun--
it's a witness who
is willing to testify
that you are
the Green Arrow.
It's someone
on the team.
Dinah isn't
the witness, Oliver. It's me.
You're off the team.
It's been real, y'all.
I'm out, too.
I'm done.
So we've got them
fighting with each other
instead of fighting us.
This is only
the beginning.
Mr. Bertinelli, I think you're going
to like these numbers.
We need a name for the Panam-X
that's coming in.
Christening ships does make it seem
more legit if the IRS checks it.
Well, how about
The Huntress
after my cousin?
- Very good.
- Thank you, sir.
Who the hell
are you?
Someone...Important.
Real important.
You don't look it.
How'd you get
past my men?
I blew them a kiss.
Jerry Bertinelli
of the eponymous crime family
and the last
of his kind.
The rest of your
family is either...
dead
or incarcerated.
You writing a book?
I have heard
that sometimes
ships appear on your
docking manifest
but never
actually arrive.
Sometimes, ships arrive
and never end up
on the docking manifest.
That's, uh--that's
very profound.
If the price is right,
maybe--maybe
we can facilitate
a few things.
No. I'm afraid you
misunderstand.
We want to buy
you out.
I got a feeling
you're not hearing me.
Port's not for sale.
Take a walk.
Oh, it sounds to me like
you want a kiss, too.
You have 48 hours
to consider our proposal.
Don't you have a daughter attending
Columbia University?
I've always wanted
to visit New York.
♪ Arrow 6x10 ♪
Divided
Original Air Date on January 18, 2018
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Hey, you.
Looks like you need this.
Oh, John Diggle,
savior of souls
and bringer of java.
- Hmm.
- Oh, thank you.
I have been called.
I guess I have to
find ways to be useful.
You're working overtime
trying to find Cayden James,
and I'm still
on the disabled list.
Well, not for long.
Curtis is on his way over,
and we will fix you.
We have
the technology.
Ha. I'm not
the six million dollar man.
Not yet you're not,
and more like
2.24 million dollar man
because Curtis and I
are stretching pennies
with Helix Dynamics
as it is.
Oh, speak of the devil,
that little psychic.
Oh. He's early.
He'll be here soon.
- Who's early?
- Curtis.
Shouldn't you
be getting home?
Raisa must be making
quadruple overtime by now.
Raisa's doing
just fine.
I mean, William
loves her, so--
William doesn't know
you're here.
I know,
and I don't like it,
but...we need to
find Cayden James.
Are we making any
progress on that front?
Despite my 21st
consecutive all-nighter, no.
He's either the first
bad guy to ghost us,
or he's just
biding time.
- Black Siren?
- Another strikeout.
I can't track her cry,
and Cayden must have
inserted some sort of
Trojan into the software.
It's confusing our facial
recognition algorithms.
I cannot find her.
All right. We will
continue with the low-tech option,
and I will go out
there again tonight.
Yeah,
and every time you do,
you are playing
Russian roulette,
considering you're being
followed and all.
- And the anti-vigilante law.
- I'm not worried.
You should not
be either.
The three of us,
we will solve
this problem together.
Like your haircut.
It's nice.
I didn't get a haircut.
Curtis, it's fine.
I'm really appreciative
that you're helping John.
No hard feelings?
No.
That wasn't
superawkward. Heh.
Ooh. Let's get to work.
Yep.
- Hi.
- Heh heh heh. Look who it is.
Ahh. To what do I owe the pleasure?
Sit down.
Uh, well, I heard you
needed a new assistant.
Yeah. Developed
some trust issues with the last one.
Yeah. Ollie told me
you fired him.
Yeah. About that.
He also mentioned that
you wanted to, what,
err on the side
of forgiveness.
Yeah. I mean, look.
You know, everyone makes mistakes,
and I--I totally get
why you did what you did,
but I just feel like
it might come across bad for optics.
It--it might look like
you're retaliating
against a whistleblower.
Yeah. I hear what
you're saying,
but, Thea--ahem...
Oliver shouldn't have to
work shoulder to shoulder
with a guy who's
testifying against him.
Doesn't mean you're not
still down an assistant.
Yeah. Well, actually,
I hired a replacement this morning.
Oh.
What I could really use
is a Chief of Staff.
Almost there.
Just slipping past
the radial carpal.
Yeah.
Boom! Chip implanted.
That's it?
That seemed simple.
Yeah, for you.
I mean, making the chip,
that was the hard--
What was that?
Some kind of electromagnetic
frequency interference.
- From the chip?
- No. I doubt it, but--
It's probably nothing.
All right.
Moment of truth.
Can you make a fist
without the tremor?
Round two, El busto.
You need to just stop pouring money
into this, into me.
You let us worry
about the money, ok?
We're gonna do this.
I can tinker with
the design some more when I get home.
Or you could do it here.
Heh. Hard pass.
After this morning's awkwardness,
I am good.
- See you guys.
- See you.
Please tell me you can get Halo
on that thing.
If I have to go
one more week
without shooting a bad guy,
I'm gonna bust.
Funny. I always pictured you
like more a Call of Duty k--
What?
Dig.
Anastas,
who collared this guy?
We've had a warrant
on him for weeks.
Nobody. He just up
and turned himself in 5 minutes ago.
- Turned himself in?
- It's crazy.
Fifth one this week.
Like all of a sudden,
these bad guys
grew a conscience.
Did you like
my presents?
What are you
doing here?
Seeing you.
You know, anybody
in this office could arrest you.
Hell, I could
arrest you.
For what?
I'm a Central City
police officer.
The only rap on me
is that I am presumed dead.
Then again,
I was an undercover,
so that death is
probably bogus.
The vigilante put
the fear of God in these guys.
At least the vigilante
isn't killing them.
Most guys just send
flowers.
How about a stroll
by the pier instead?
Tomorrow after your
shift ends?
Sure.
Ok.
Clear.
What's going on?
We've been
compromised.
Into the bunker
for John's implant.
We got massive signal
interference. We got lucky.
3 months ago, when Laurel
infiltrated the bunker.
She stole one
of Curtis' T-spheres
James had it on him back
at Starling Stadium.
We were so focused
on what she could have taken,
we never thought
about what she could have left behind.
- Like a bug?
- Exactly.
Then he's been watching
us for months!
I got it on loop, ok?
Audio and visual
of the bunker.
He doesn't know
that we know.
- All right.
- I spoke with Lyla.
She said we can use
A.R.G.U.S. for the time being.
That's smart.
No. Smart is
Cayden James
being one step ahead
of us from the very jump, Oliver.
I hate to belabor
the depressingly obvious,
but secret identities...
No longer secret.
The block between
74th and Jansen just lost
their security
signal uplink.
That doesn't just
happen on its own.
- Cayden James.
- I'm on it.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Can you stand down?
I just needed to
get your attention.
You're a hard man
to find.
You ever consider
a web site,
maybe a spotlight
in the sky,
you know, a big
silhouette of an arrow?
What do you want?
You, uh, you know
who I am?
Jerry Bertinelli.
You're in the Bertinelli
Syndicate.
I am the Bertinelli
Syndicate,
at least what's
left of it,
and I can't go down
without a fight.
In 5 seconds, you're
gonna be in a fight.
Just hear me out.
Look. I--I never actually wanted to
get in this life,
you know, but we do
certain things for family,
am I right?
Now the ports,
these docks,
it's all we got left,
and last night,
these people came over
and threatened to take it from me,
you know, some dweeb
in glasses,
a thug, a woman
with superpowers.
I mean,
you know them?
- Maybe.
- Yeah. No. I figured you might.
They're looking
to control the docks.
So talk to your cousin.
She's been underground,
so I'm asking you.
You really think
that I'm gonna help you win a turf war?
No. I think you're
the enemy of my enemy,
which makes us allies.
We need to know
what's on this.
"Hi, Felicity.
How are you?
"Are you busy with anything?
Can you help me with something?
You look tired."
- Hi.
Jerry Bertinelli
gave that to me.
The port is the only
thing the Bertinelli family has left.
Cayden James and Black Siren
are trying
to take it
from them.
So we're getting in bed
with the Bertinellis now?
I remember last time
you got in bed with one of the Bertinellis.
It did not work out well.
I have a long memory
for these sort of things.
Call me crazy.
Two nights ago,
they paid him a visit.
This is the security
footage.
They made a threat
against his daughter.
Well, what's on here
might help us locate them.
That's the plan.
Well, what about
a license plate?
Old school. I like it.
Little bit of old school
combined with some new school,
and I'm about to find us
this Cayden James needle
in the Star City
haystack.
Do it.
Then I was thinking
after school,
we could hit up the zoo.
They have this new
reptile room
with a komodo dragon.
Thing's so big,
it could eat a cow.
- That's dope, right?
- I guess so.
What's up, sweets?
I thought you were all
about this animal stuff.
I am, but why
aren't you going to work today?
I's going through a little
transitional period.
- Will I have to leave again?
- Hey.
No one will ever take
you away from me ever again.
- What's up, dawg?
- What's up, dawg?!
I brought crogurts.
- Crogurts?
- I didn't name them.
I just eat them.
Hey, Zoe.
- Hi, Curtis.
- Hey. Go get your bag.
We're about to leave.
Must be great having
her back, huh?
Best feeling
in the world.
You don't look like
you're feeling
the best feeling
in the world, though.
I can't shake how
everything went down with Oliver.
In order to do right
for me,
I--I had to
betray him.
You had to put
your daughter first.
She's family.
Is that why you
called me over?
Actually,
I was thinking,
all the evidence Agent Watson says
she has against me
has to be digitized,
right?
Yeah.
So what if that
evidence suddenly vanished?
Then I'll be able to--
what do you call it--
um, recant.
You put your family
first, Rene.
That's nothing to be
ashamed about.
I mean, now, accessing
might files might be a little easier
now that the case has
been moved back
to the Star City D.A., but--
So that's a yes?
No. That's a "let me
think about it."
Fine. Yeah. I'll do it.
We all know I'll do it.
Aw. That's what I'm
talking about, Hoss.
Oh! That was--
that was the worst stakeout of my life.
Do you remember--ok.
It was, like, what, minus one?
It was freezing.
I was freezing my ass off,
and the car's heater
broke down.
I warned you about that.
Yeah, you did, and I
didn't listen.
I think there's
a life lesson in there somewhere.
Oh. Ha ha. I think
I drank a gallon
of coffee that night
to stay warm.
I had to pee
so bad--I've never
had to pee
so bad in my life,
and I had to go back
behind the car,
so, you know--
I mean, I wasn't gonna ask the scum bag
if I could use
his bathroom.
Oh, God, and the second
I go back there,
he decides to make
a run for it, that son of a bitch.
I go chasing after him,
fall face-first into the snow bank,
and knock--knock myself
out on the curb.
Ohh.
This is complicated.
I know.
I'm used to complicated.
Vince, this is a whole new level.
It doesn't have to be.
I stopped being the Black Canary
5 weeks ago.
I really want to uncomplicate
my life right now.
Just so long you
don't forget to live it.
I'm sorry.
Text from an informant.
My next target's
on the move.
Don't worry.
I'm not gonna kill him.
Well, just make sure
you bring him in when I'm off duty, ok,
because all this intake
is giving me carpal tunnel.
Pen?
I can always
count on you.
So Quentin told me
the good news.
You're back with us.
Yes, I am.
And you're happy
about that?
Oh, I'm just sorry
that I can't be of more help to you
and the team or
lack thereof.
That's fine.
I just know you need
the manpower right now,
and I'm--I'm just
not there.
Thea...
You will always
be my Speedy
whether you're using
a bow and arrow or not.
Ahem.
Yeah?
- Found him!
- Where?
His vehicle's parked
outside a warehouse in Adams Heights.
Looks like he's alone.
And he doesn't know
that we know. Ok. Talk me in.
Oliver, if you do that,
you'll be going in solo.
Let us stake the place out,
do some recon.
We have the chance to
take him by surprise.
We can't pass it up.
- Ollie!
- Yeah?
Go get him.
Overwatch, I'm
in the east sector. Where to?
Ok. You're coming up
on the main floor.
Same 3 heat sigs have
been there for a while now.
Good odds
that's our target.
I'm sensing
some impatience, Ms. Lance.
Would you care to
elucidate?
I'm not impatient.
I'm annoyed.
We have the numbers.
Why not just take the pier from the Bertinellis?
Oh, no.
Not impatient at all.
Mr. Sheck...
No need to
stir the pot.
I think you'll find
that brute force,
while it's easy, it's
exceedingly messy.
I prefer precision.
Design over chaos.
Unh!
You taught yourself
some new tricks.
No more games.
Overwatch, I have the target.
That's a whole lot
of bad news.
Arrow, you're about
to get some company.
- Oliver!
- Overwatch, do you copy?
I'm afraid Ms. Smoak
can't hear you.
You see, I also have
some tricks, Mr. Queen, and I have friends.
Hello, kapiushon.
How were your holidays?
Funny you
should mention that.
Looks like we're
getting a late Christmas present.
I thought you only
targeted criminals.
Thought you'd know
vigilantes are criminals, Mr. Mayor.
You'll find that
I don't play games, Mr. Queen,
but I do win.
It's enough.
I am so sick of everyone
not killing him
when we get
the chance.
Let him go.
You know,
for a smart guy,
that was a dumb move.
There's a time and a place for
Oliver Queen's demise.
Now is not it.
So Cayden James not
only has Laurel,
but he's backed by two
different criminal organizations?
And a deranged killer
that we haven't been able
to put down
for two years.
Oliver, if Cayden James
has his own posse, man,
maybe we need to
think about evening the playing field.
We are not folding Curtis,
Rene, and Dinah back in.
I don't trust they
won't compromise us.
Cayden James told you that
he wants to watch this city burn.
This is no time
for ego, man.
This is not ego.
John, you more than
anyone know
you don't go
into the field
with people you
can't rely on.
Ok. Well,
then how about not going into the field?
They need to know
what's going on.
Dinah deserves to
know the truth about her ex.
I agree,
so we share Intel,
but that's it.
Is that a bottle?
Worse maybe.
Oh.
A photo album.
Ok. You've definitely
just hit bottom, Quentin.
I think we need to call
your sponsor.
Yeah. Maybe he can
talk some sense into me.
Ok. Well, I've been
in a coma for 6 months,
so why don't you
fill me in a little?
Um, you know--you know
last month when I was held hostage,
you know, and she--
she let me go?
What I saw in her
is what I see here.
Look. I mean, everyone--
even Ra's Al Ghul--
has had moments
of kindness.
Yeah.
Look. I'm not saying
that this Laurel is that bad, but--
I just can't stop
thinking that if I abandon her,
if I write her off
as some kind of psycho
and--I know this--
sounds crazy,
but if there is
just some way to
get through to her
and I don't take it,
it's gonna be like
watching her die
all over again.
You're like a father
to me, you know that?
Ohh...
If you go down
this road, Quentin,
you could end up
getting killed.
Even if you don't care
what happens to you,
don't forget to think
about your other daughter.
- Hey.
Thanks for agreeing
to meet with us.
Yeah. I'm not really
sure I see the point.
We're out of the game.
I don't exactly
see Cayden James
respecting those type
of boundaries.
Cayden had Laurel plant
a camera at the bunker.
We're all compromised.
How long have you all
know about this?
24 hours.
You've known we were
exposed like this
for a whole day,
you're just telling us now?
Look. We thought our
Intel was rock solid,
and then we found out
that Laurel wasn't
the only one
that he's in league with.
He's working with the Bratva
and Ricardo Diaz.
Just what
the city needs.
She's not the only member
of his group.
Dinah...
Vincent's working with them, too.
No, no. That's--that's--
that's insane, that's insane.
Vince hunts criminals.
He doesn't throw down with them.
Oliver saw him with James
and the rest.
Well, excuse me if I don't just take
Oliver's word for it.
I mean, keeping us
under surveillance.
It sounds like he
and Cayden James have a lot in common.
Rene, we did that
for the good of the team.
Oh.
Is that how you
sleep at night, John?
We are facing
an actual breach in security.
You guys gave up
on Oliver.
You don't get to stay
mad at daddy because he read your diary
and you get to just
skip out on curfew.
That's not the way
it works.
I'm getting sick and tired
of you talking to me
like I did what I did
on a whim.
I did it for my daughter.
And your choice put the whole team
in jeopardy, Rene.
We think that showed us
where you stand.
- Dinah.
- Where you going, Dinah?
Out. I'm not gonna sit here
and watch you two
point fingers at everybody
but yourselves.
Move or get moved, hoodie.
Hey. Stand down.
He's a--
he's a friend of mine.
Well, he's
an acquaintance.
Business associate?
What do you need?
You going somewhere?
I got a, uh, text
sent to me tonight from inside
my daughter's
dorm room.
Now, Cayden James,
he can--he can have the port.
You're running scared.
I'm gonna run anywhere
for my baby girl, all right?
As long as James
and his crew are out there,
she will never be safe.
Neither will you.
But?
But I can stop him
with your help.
If you listen to me,
you do what I say,
we can end Cayden James.
I'm so glad you wanted
to meet again.
Unh!
Cayden James.
You don't understand.
You lying
son of a bitch.
You were just getting
close to me for him.
Dinah, hey, can we talk
about this somewhere else?
That's a great
idea, Vince.
The precinct has
a really nice room for you,
really nice
interrogation room.
I can't let you
do this.
I should have taken
you in the second
you came back
into my life.
I'm sorry.
- Charges are in place.
- So are mine.
Oliver, you sure
about this, man?
You don't sound like
you are.
If we do this,
Cayden James will bring
his whole group here.
- And?
- And Cayden will bring
everyone, Oliver.
I'm no place close
to 100%,
but, look--
the rest of the team.
- There is no rest of the team.
- Oliver, we can use their help.
- All you have to do is ask.
- We would have to trust them,
and we can't.
We can't. John,
we've been over this.
I know, but we've also
been over other things
like you and
the League of Assassins,
me with my secret.
Oliver, the best partnerships are built
on forgiveness, man.
No one knows that more
than you and me.
I got arrested
in front of my son,
got dragged away in
handcuffs because
of something that
Rene did.
I don't know how
to forgive it.
I tried. John,
more importantly,
what's Cayden James
up to?
We don't know.
He has known
our identities for months.
He hasn't
outed us. Why?
This started with you, with me,
and with Felicity.
Whatever comes our
way, we can handle it.
I believe that.
Are you actually eating
the old crogurt?
Shut up. Your old
is my delicious.
- How's Zoe?
- I don't know. I just...
Need her to feel like
everything's going back to normal.
I hope it is. It'd help
if you could delete whatever the D.A.'s got.
We just found out
that Cayden James had the bunker bugged
for a couple of months,
so maybe we should just take a little break
on saying incriminating
things like that out loud!
All right, all right.
I'm sorry.
I'm just anxious is all.
I know,
but, unfortunately,
they have a backup
of all these files,
and even worse, the records are saying
that they have hard copies.
- Damn.
- Yeah, I know,
but I'm inside
the system.
I'm just trying
to find--whoa!
- Whoa what?
- I think I just found something.
Yeah. There's a record on how
Watson found out you were Wild Dog.
- There's an audio recording.
- You thinking what I'm thinking?
Well, that depends on
if you're thinking that Cayden James leaked
an audio file of you
from the bunker to the FBI.
Is that what you're thinking?
That's what you're thinking, right?
- Yeah.
- Good. We're on the same page.
Don't you knock?
Don't you lock
your doors?
You look like you were
just in a fight.
- You were just in a fight.
- With who?
Vince.
I confronted him.
- He did this and ran.
- I'm so sorry, Dinah.
It was my fault for believing in him
in the first damn place
and for confronting him,
exposing the fact that
we know about him
and Cayden James.
That's my fault, too.
Sorry.
Curtis and I were just
talking about James
and the bunker
being compromised.
Yeah, and how that
might have led to Rene being compromised.
You think Cayden provided
Samanda Watson with her case?
- That's the theory.
- A good one, though.
Yeah, but if Cayden
had audio and video
on all of us,
especially Oliver,
why would he just
tee up, Rene?
It figures he'd go
after the most handsome and charming.
Well, maybe when Oliver
finally takes down Cayden James,
we'll figure out all the details
of his master plan.
Why assume we're gonna
wait for Oliver?
What are we gonna do here?
We're gonna sit around
and wait to see how
this all plays out?
Hope it plays out,
you mean?
Are you guys serious
about this,
about taking on Cayden James
and his superposse?
I let Vince walk once.
I'm not gonna make that mistake again.
And I owe that
son of a bitch some serious payback.
If I'm reading
the room correctly,
we're gonna form
our own team, right?
Right.
- What's going on?
- Signal chatter
from the Bertinellis' laptop.
They're bringing in
the Red Lions.
Ah. The Red Lions.
Chechnyan death squad.
Bertinelli's not
gonna let the port go without a fight.
Well, I'm thinking
the enemy of Cayden James is
my favorite death squad.
The Red Lions liberated a town
in Kizlyar last year.
Turned it
into a wasteland.
We can't let James' group
go up against these guys.
The collateral damage
will destroy the port.
Where are Bertinelli
and the Red Lions holed up?
Storage facility
on Fifth and Brockton.
We can take the port
without Bertinelli's say,
but there are a lot
of players in this city.
I think you should set
a precedent
for when you're
in charge.
I'm already in charge,
Ms. Lance.
Even more reason to use
his corpse as a message.
I concur.
Mr. Bertinelli has
his army.
He should meet ours.
- Think Bertinelli's gonna show?
- He better.
He will.
Well, let's get
this over with.
If keyhole satellite
imagery is anything to go off of,
it looks like Cayden James
took the bait.
Funny thing!
You guys don't look like
a Chechnyan death squad.
We have Ricardo Diaz
in the house
but no Cayden James.
I'll take it.
Oh, no. We have
a very large problem.
Oliver, get out
of there!
Send in the cavalry.
So how does this
compare to Halo?
So...Much...Better.
Stand down, Oliver.
You are vastly outnumbered.
Ugh!
Damn it!
Let's get the hell out
of this freak show.
Hey.
All right, all right.
Don't leave early.
The best parts are
always at the end.
I'm disappointed,
Mr. Bertinelli.
I truly am
but not unreasonable.
This can go one of two ways
for you and your men.
The choice is yours.
Forgive me, kid.
- Mr. Bertinelli--
- Fine. Relax, all right?
All right. Just take the--
take the freakin' port.
Oh, thank you.
Although you elected to betray
me this evening,
you ultimately made
the right choice.
Which is why I won't
have your daughter killed.
I expect you can find
the most effective use for this corpse to--
how did you put it--
send a message.
So are you happy to be back
in your newly debugged,
crime-fighting lair?
Cayden James
got away.
Everybody got
away. Ahem.
Have you seen that movie
"Bull Durham"?
- Hmm.
- My mom made me watch
that movie all the time.
I mean, it is the best
baseball movie ever,
but she used to say
that Susan Sarandon
was her fictional
life coach.
Anyway, there's a line
in this movie
where she says,
"Sometimes, you win.
"Sometimes,
you lose.
- Sometimes, it rains."
- "Sometimes it rains."
You can't
control the weather.
You couldn't control
Bertinelli betraying you.
You know what else
I can't control?
Their numbers
advantage.
I can't be out there
solo against that group.
It's--it's not
the smart move.
I won't make
that mistake again.
I just want to say
that I, for one,
think it's great that we're all back in
the same room together.
Trust and forgiveness.
For the past few weeks,
I have been
really struggling to
square that circle.
I think--I think
all of us have.
Rene, as a father, I understand
why you did what you did.
I also recognize
that you might be taking
me away from my son.
I reacted to that,
and I got angry.
The three of us decided
to put the three of you under surveillance.
I take responsibility
for that.
It was without question--
it was a breach of trust.
So was lying to the team
about Vince,
and I'm not trying to
point fingers, Dinah.
I am simply trying to
illustrate that there is--
there is blame
on all sides here,
but we don't have time
for grudges or recriminations.
We don't, not with what
this city is up against.
So what do you guys
think?
Clean slate?
Things just go back
to the way they were before?
Yeah.
I don't think
I can do that.
Not after what
the three of you did.
This city needs us,
and we know that, and we're not
shirking that responsibility.
We decided to go
our own way.
- Wait a minute.
- No, no. Let's--
No, no, no!
This is what
Cayden James wants.
Cayden didn't do this,
Felicity.
He didn't create
an environment of distrust,
a team where some members
of that team
were treated differently
than others.
Cayden James didn't
demand allegiance
and then play by his own
set of rules.
I came because I want
to be a part of a real team.
Point taken.
I'd like to wish
the three of you good luck,
and I mean that sincerely--
with Cayden, with Anatoly,
Diaz, Black Siren, vigilante.
These people are dangerous,
so whatever you
have planned,
whatever your move is...
Good luck.
Let's go, guys.
I may have solved
the glitch in my chip.
I hope it helps.
I, um, really do.
What the...?
Hope you don't mind.
Found these in my
personal collection
and thought that we could
add them to your album.
Oh, thank you
very much.
- It's my apology.
- For what?
You were right.
Look. Malcolm was
every bit as bad
as this Laurel is
right now,
and...then in the end,
he--he wasn't.
He changed,
and Laurel can, too.
I had no right to tell
you that she couldn't.
Right.
How the hell am I
gonna do that?
Well, I can help,
and I don't know.
Maybe together,
we can find a way
to break through
to her.
Yeah.
When you said you
had something to show us,
didn't you think lights
would be useful?
One second, guys.
It is all
about the reveal.
What does it
look like?
Some...Place.
No. It's--it's
our new lair. Heh.
Helix used to
operate out of here,
but it's not like they're
using it anymore, so--
Curtis, it's genius.
Seriously, nice work.
I'm glad you guys
like it.
Now, I don't suggest
we make this a regular thing,
seeing as how
I'm a lightweight and all,
but this event
warrants a celebration.
Well, I am just glad
that I found partners who I can trust.
That's what I'm
talking about.
Salud.
I'm concerned...
And the feeling doesn't
suit me well.
You got the port
like you wanted.
Sorry if I was unclear.
My concern relates to you.
Your continued association
with Ms. Drake
wouldn't worry me
if this surveillance
didn't suggest
that she knows
about our association.
Don't worry.
I can handle Dinah.
There's not a button
she has that I don't know how to push.
All right.
New chip is in.
Just one second.
All right.
Doesn't feel
any different.
Well, it takes
a minute.
Or not!
It worked?
Looks like we're not
as undermanned as we thought.
Yes!
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man