Previously, on "Arrow"...
These waters' powers,
they have permitted me
to live way beyond my time.
I want you to take my place.
I want you to become
the next Ra's al Ghul.
If you insist on pursuing this
path of resistance,
there will be consequences.
Is that a threat?
I am the Demon's Head.
And very soon,
your brother.
He will never
take your place.
He will.
Thea?
Thea?!
Oh, my God,
Thea! Hey!
I...couldn't...stop him.
I need an ambulance
to 455 Merced, Unit 10.
Please hurry.
Ok, you're
going to be ok.
You're going to be ok.
No, Thea, stay
awake! Come on! Up!
Hang on, we're almost there.
How long was she like this?
Uh, 20 minutes, 40,
I don't know, I just found her.
- You need to stay here.
- I'm not going to leave her!
You need
to let us work.
Get me a set
of vitals. Lift.
Charge up to 200 joules.
Charging.
Clear.
No response.
Draw up one milligram EPI,
charge to 200.
Charging.
Ready.
Clear.
Start CPR.
Come on.
Come on, stay with us.
♪ Arrow 3x20 ♪
The Fallen
Original Air Date on April 22, 2015
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
We did the best we could
under the circumstances,
but her injuries
were extensive.
Even if she were
to regain consciousness,
we can prolong her life
for as long as you wish.
But...it might be best
to consider other options.
I am truly sorry,
Mr. Queen.
May I see her?
Sorry.
Oliver...
Thea.
What are they doing?
They're
unloading the truck,
and, um,
having dinner.
General Shrieve is there.
The Alpha,
the Omega,
he's combining them.
The bio weapon is armed.
What happens now?
Now he'll take it somewhere
to be released.
Somewhere densely populated
where it will have the most impact.
We need to stop
that truck.
Where's Oliver?
Come on!
You stole a car?
I borrowed it.
Come on.
Oh, my God.
Oliver!
Oliver, we came
as soon as we could.
What happened?
Oliver.
They just
left her there.
To die.
Oliver, is--is she?
It's bad.
What is it?
Smoke.
The League?
Screw 'em. At least
until we get our bearings, Oliver.
Come up with a plan.
He's won.
There is no plan.
Stay here with Thea.
Did you do this?
Did you do this?!
You could still
save her, Oliver.
I don't understand.
Take your rightful place
as heir to the Demon...
And Ra's al Ghul
will bring your sister back.
Oliver, what's going on?
Oliver, where are you going?
Away.
You can't just
leave like this.
You have to tell us
what's happening.
There's a way
for me to save her.
Thea?
Come on, Oliver,
that's not possible.
Yes, it is.
There are waters
in Nanda Parbat.
They've permitted Ra's
to live for over a hundred years.
And in rare instances,
told in legend, those waters
have been used to restore
the dead to life.
He offered to use the Lazarus pit
on Thea, didn't he?
Lazarus, as in
from the bible, Lazarus?
The pit's real.
I've seen it.
It can save Thea.
Right.
But only if you become
the new Ra's.
Ok. Well, even
if a magic hot tub
were not crazy talk,
we're not going to let you go and join
the League of psychotic murderers,
even if it is to save Thea.
Which this wouldn't.
The waters change a person.
In the soul.
Even if they work,
the Thea you get back
will not be
the one you lost.
The one we lost
because of you.
Oliver...
I'd prefer that we didn't do our usual
"please don't go" dance.
We're not going to.
Because I'm coming with you.
Assuming that this works,
someone's going to need
to bring Thea back home.
We need a way to get
to Nanda Parbat.
Sorry to interrupt.
Everything all right?
'Cause you got that crease
between your eyebrows
that tells me things
most definitely are not.
Something awful
has happened.
And I--
I need a favor.
A really big favor.
Last time you asked me
for a big favor,
I had to loan you
my helicopter.
Don't need
your helicopter.
I need your jet.
Well, Oliver does,
but both of us.
It's not
what you think.
Well, if you're going
to fly away with him,
then...it's exactly
what I think.
Ray...
Last night was a bit
of an eye-opener.
Insofar as
realizing something
I should have realized
a long time ago...
Can be considered
eye-opening.
Last night, when you were
saying good-bye to Roy,
you and Oliver...
You still have
feelings for him.
When I...told you
that I loved you at the hospital,
you responded with Jell-O.
Seeing you two together
last night,
I realized...
You don't love me
because you're in love with him.
I'm sorry.
You're the last
person I ever meant to hurt.
Take the jet.
I hope the something awful
stops being awful.
What did Felicity
say to Dr. Vaca?
She thinks Thea's
being moved to Central City.
You know, they do amazing
things at S.T.A.R. Labs.
We might think about
paying them a visit
before putting Thea
on a long flight to Nanda Parbat.
S.T.A.R. Labs
can't save her.
Only
the Lazarus pit can.
Oliver!
Look, I know
what I have done
doesn't seem like the actions
of a loving father,
but I do love her.
She's the only child
I have left.
Having said that,
I would rather
lose her forever
than--than subject
her to the pit.
Get on the plane, Malcolm.
You look chilly.
Yeah.
Thanks for letting me
be here for you.
You're welcome.
I didn't have much of a choice,
though, did I?
No.
I wanted to make you think
you had grown
a little as a person.
I know that I've only
told you a little
about the five years
that I was away.
Well, if by "little,"
you mean hardly anything.
I came back
to Starling City
before they found me
on the island.
I don't understand.
It was complicated.
I saw Thea.
She didn't see me.
She had a drug problem.
So I..confronted
her dealer.
And I broke his neck.
And I did it because
I was angry, sure.
But I also did it because I felt like
I was protecting her.
All I've ever wanted to do
was protect her.
Malcolm told me.
He warned me what
Ra's might do.
But I never thought...
I failed.
Incoming!
Maseo, take the wheel.
You look like
you can use a hand.
It's not in here.
What is that?
It's the League.
Welcome home,
Al Sah-him.
I must prepare
for the ritual.
I will treat her
as my own family.
I hope you find
the accommodations acceptable.
Such luxury is a small
glimpse of the life that awaits Oliver.
You trying to reassure me
or yourself?
I don't know
what you mean.
You're Oliver's friend.
Maseo, right?
I am Sarab.
Call yourself
whatever you want.
If you gave
a damn about Oliver,
you wouldn't be working for the man
who practically killed his sister.
Oliver will be
spared grief
in a manner that
was denied to me,
and he'll
receive an honor
greater than
you can imagine.
League of Assassins.
You're feared for your bravery
and power.
Well, all I see are
a bunch of weak men
running from their lives,
trying to escape.
That's not powerful, Maseo.
Or brave. That's cowardly.
Do not presume
to know me
until you've held
your dying child in your arms.
Until you've told him
everything would be ok
so that the last
words he ever hears
are a lie.
You know nothing.
I'm sorry.
What was your child's name?
Akio.
You think Akio would be
proud of his father right now?
_
Thea!
I've fulfilled my end
of our arrangement.
I suggest you begin
to make peace with yours.
Hey. Hey. It's ok.
You're ok.
I don't know you.
Thea, it's--it's me.
It's Ollie.
Ollie's dead.
Dad?
I'm here, Thea.
It--it's me.
What's going on?
Where am I?
Some place safe.
You are safe.
Where's mom?
Your mother's not here.
Look--
just lie back, close your eyes
and get some rest, ok?
I love you, Dad.
Ra's told me that
the confusion would pass.
You have no idea
what you've done.
What I've done?
She's alive,
Malcolm.
What I did
saved her life.
She thinks Moira's still alive.
She'll be fine.
- You don't know that.
- Yes, I do.
Because you,
Diggle and Felicity
are going to take
her home and she will recover.
And what is that worth?
Felicity...
No, this is wrong!
It is just wrong!
I need to talk to you.
What is happening here is perverse!
What you are doing to Oliver.
What you are making him do;
I am not going to let it happen.
You can leave us.
You have a great
fire within you.
I can see now why
Oliver loves you.
If you knew the first thing
about love,
you would not be ripping
Oliver away from his family.
I am merely helping him
fulfill his Destiny.
Yeah, I know all about
the "survive my sword" prophecy,
and I am here to tell you
that I could really give a crap.
Me and John and, God
help me, Malcolm,
are not going to let this
happen, and we have friends,
and we have resources and
we will go to war to get Oliver back.
You know,
many lifetimes ago,
I loved a woman
immeasurably.
And she loved me.
And we had a son
and then a daughter,
and for many years,
I felt I was the most
fortunate man in the world.
My life was bliss.
And one night,
a man came to my door
and he gave me
a horrible choice--
to leave without saying
a word to them,
or to stand and watch them
tortured and then killed.
And I left
without a farewell.
And to spare them pain,
I endured an agony
worse than death.
Sounds like you gave up
too easily.
If there's one immutable
truth about life...
It's often more cruel
than it is fair,
and rarely provides
an opportunity for any of us
to find closure.
And all
your posturing
and all
your threats of war
will merely delay
the inevitable,
causing you
to forfeit
the opportunity
you have.
This was denied me.
You need to tell
Oliver good-bye.
Tell him how much
you love him.
Tell him whatever it is your heart
needs to express.
And do it now.
Before he is lost
to you forever.
Yeah?
Hi.
Hey.
You ok?
I'm sorry, that's
a stupid question. You...
You just saw your sister
come back from being mostly dead
and you are about to give up
everything you know and love,
so you're probably not.
I remember the first
time that I thought
I'd never
see Thea again.
When my father's
boat went down.
But you did see her again.
And you'll see her again...
Again.
This is different.
I've just been
thinking about
the...person I was.
The brother
that I was.
And how he probably
died when that boat went down.
All this time, I've been struggling
with who I am...
And you think who you're
supposed to be is...
The next
Ra's al Ghul?
Honestly?
I don't know.
The only thing that
I can know for sure
is that everything
that I've done;
every--everything
that happened,
it lead me right here,
to this moment.
And Felicity,
if that's true,
then...I don't know
what it was all for.
I do.
I wish that I could change
your mind about staying here,
but I know I can't.
Just like I know how leaving you
here is going to destroy me.
I don't regret
a single moment.
And you shouldn't,
either.
You have done so much.
You have saved so
many people's lives.
And you have changed so many
for the better.
Including mine.
Knowing you has
changed my life.
You...opened up my heart
in a way I didn't even
know was possible.
I love you.
We searched the whole truck.
There's nothing in there.
Where is the bio weapon?
Don't make me ask again.
Food cart. It's
in the food cart.
Where is the food cart?
We should split up
to cover more ground.
What's wrong?
I know you don't
think we should be doing this.
You decided we should
set an example for our son.
And for ourselves.
We can't just
let people die.
If we do, we are
just a shell.
Not really alive at all.
So...that happened.
I'm glad it did.
Me, too.
What's this?
If there's
any kind of God,
something...
Alcoholic.
There's not much
to toast to up here,
is there?
Well...
There's us.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
Hmm?
Look, I know there's no way
of avoiding this,
of--of getting
out of here,
going some place
where Ra's can't find us, but I...
Felicity...
Felicity.
What did you--
I can't lose you.
I won't.
I stole some of that powder that
that creepy priest lady used on Thea.
Wasn't sure exactly what I was going
to do with it when I got it, but I...
Yeah, how did you know you were
going to completely lose your mind?
Or commit suicide.
Was your plan to
sneak Ra's prize out
unconscious
without getting us all killed?
I couldn't leave him.
We have to get him
out of here.
Felicity, this place
is like a fortress.
There's no way we're getting
Oliver out of here without Ra's knowing.
We can't. You can.
If we get caught,
he'll kill all of us.
Then we can't get caught.
I have seen
enough movies to know
that the scary fortress
always has a secret exit.
You were Ra's right hand
stooge for years.
If there is anyone that knows
the way out of this hellhole,
it's you, so don't even
try to play games with me.
The catacombs.
It's rough terrain.
It is not going to be easy.
How do we get there?
Through the temple.
Go get Thea and meet us
back here in five minutes.
Go!
Which way?
Temple's this way,
come on!
There's not much time. Hurry.
Why are you
helping us?
Because if I don't,
then I am just a shell.
You reminded me of that.
30 meters down.
The path forks.
Take the left passage.
Come on.
These tunnels are centuries old.
Stay close.
Need to stop and rest
for a minute?
No, no, no.
Maseo says stay left.
Thea?
No. No. No...
We have to move, now!
Too late.
Believe me, we do not
want to be taken alive.
Hold!
I am Al Sah-him.
Wahreeth Al Ghul.
Heir to the Demon.
And you will obey.
Put your weapons down.
Now!
Tell Ra's I will
return shortly.
Oliver, please!
Thank you for trying.
I love you all
the more for it.
But this only ends one way.
This is as far as I go.
Oliver, the jet's less
than a mile away.
Where are we going to fly to?
Ollie,
I don't understand.
Malcolm is going
to take you home.
Aren't you coming with?
Not now.
You go on, I'll catch up.
I love you, Thea.
Don't ever
forget that, ok?
Oliver...
Oliver, I don't know
what to say.
I do.
John, you're the best man
I've ever known.
And whatever happens,
you're my brother.
I am afraid I will never forgive myself
for leaving you here.
You told me once that...
life is precious.
And that you wanted more
from it than I could offer you.
Don't give up on that.
The only way that
I'm going to survive this...
is if I know that
you're out there
living your life, happy.
We're always saying good-bye
to each other.
You'd think I'd be
good at it by now.
Well, let's not
say good-bye this time.
What's--
what's going on?
Everything's fine,
Thea, you're--you're ok.
If you're here,
then I'm not.
Well, at least
you're feeling a little
more like yourself again.
What do you want?
Where's Ollie?
Thea, do you remember
anything about
the past few days?
I...
I was here.
And--and Ra's, he--
he attacked me.
No, Thea.
He nearly killed you.
Where is my brother?
That is--that is what
I'm trying to explain.
To save you, Oliver
had to join the League.
He--he traded
his life for yours.
No. No.
I am sorry.
I know you hate me,
and you have every right,
but I am going to make up
for that, for everything.
That is not possible!
Yes, it is!
The League isn't after us
anymore; I am free!
I could go anywhere
in there world,
but...this is where
I want to be. Here.
With my daughter.
You took care of me when I was injured.
Now, please, Thea,
please. Let me
take care of you.
Sorry to interrupt.
Is everything
all right?
No.
It's not.
Felicity...
Oliver's...
He's gone.
What are you
talking about?
He joined the League.
No.
He's not coming back.
Shh.
Blood has been shed.
League blood.
And that is a transgression
punishable by death.
And yet you allowed
your friends safe passage home.
You tell me why I should not
hunt these people down
and stain my blade
with their blood.
Because I stayed.
I'm honoring
our agreement.
Now no one close
to me will ever be harmed again.
And your allies
would not have been able
to escape through the catacombs
without assistance,
so you tell me who aided you,
who this traitor is.
I don't know.
Me.
I struck down
three of our number.
For my betrayal...
I offer you my life.
You did not betray me
tonight, Sarab.
Maseo Yamashiro did.
For a moment,
your old life took hold.
But by coming here
and kneeling before me,
you have proven your loyalty,
and I will not spill
Sarab's blood
for Maseo's actions.
Stand up.
Your service will be vital
in the coming weeks.
Oliver will need you for his
transformation.
And like Sarab...
vestiges of your old
identity still remain.
Oliver Queen must be
extinguished from memory.
Stop!
No!
Give me the vial.
The word "assassin"
has fallen victim
to many abuses of language.
Its real meaning
hidden beneath the sediment
of lies and falsehoods.
In truth,
"assassin" comes
from hashishiyya,
which means, "those who stand
apart from society."
Now, every man
and woman in here
have renounced
their past life
and forfeited their identity
in the name of something new.
And it is a cleansing
only achieved by fire.
Embrace the pain,
for it is your soul
finally being unburdened.
Oliver Queen is dead.
Eventually to be reborn
as Ra's al Ghul.
But for now,
only the Arrow,
Al Sah-him,
shall remain.
Al Sah-him.
Heir to the Demon.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Greg!
Move your head.