PREVIOUSLY ON "ARROW"...
WILLIAM: WE DID IT.
THE BOMBS ARE
DEACTIVATED.
KEVEN: THE ATTACK
BY THE VIGILANTES HAS
PROVIDED US
AN OPPORTUNITY.
RENE: WHAT IS THAT?
KEVEN: THE TOOL THAT WILL
ALLOW US TO ELIMINATE
ALL VIGILANTES FOR GOOD.
DINAH: GUSTAVO HERNANDEZ
WAS FOUND DEAD.
YOU THINK I DID THIS.
I'M NOT EXACTLY
HEARING A DENIAL.
I HAVE BUSTED MY ASS,
BUT NO MATTER
WHAT I DO,
YOU ALWAYS JUST SEE ME
AS THE BLACK SIREN.
BETHANY SNOW ON COMPUTER:
DISTRICT ATTORNEY LAUREL LANCE.
NEW PHOTOS SHOW HER
WITH RICARDO DIAZ.
COULD THE CITY'S
HIGHEST PROSECUTOR
ACTUALLY BE
A WANTED CRIMINAL HERSELF?
EMIKO: LOOKS LIKE
YOU'VE GOT A PROBLEM.
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
MAN: YOU LOST?
I'M HERE TO SEE
SHADOW THIEF.
[MEN LAUGHING]
SHE'S BUSY,
BUT YOU CAN STAY
HERE WITH US.
-HYAH!
-UNH!
I'LL PASS.
[BONES CRACK]
[SIREN SCREAM]
WHERE THE HELL
IS SHADOW THIEF?
UH! WHO ARE YOU?
I'M BLACK SIREN.
STILL KICKING ASS, I SEE.
I HEARD YOU WERE
BACK IN TOWN.
AND I HEARD YOU TRADED
IN YOUR LEATHER
FOR A POWER SUIT.
WELL, THAT SUIT
DIDN'T REALLY FIT.
SEEMS THE ENTIRE CITY
HAS TURNED AGAINST YOU.
JUST REMINDED ME
THAT THERE'S ONLY
ONE PERSON I CAN TRUST...
MYSELF.
IT'S TOO BAD
ABOUT DIAZ.
WHAT, THAT HE DIDN'T
DIE SOONER?
I COULDN'T AGREE MORE,
BUT AT LEAST HE INTRODUCED
US BEFORE HE DID.
AS MUCH AS I'M ENJOYING
THIS LITTLE REUNION,
WHY DON'T YOU TELL ME
WHY YOU'RE HERE?
I'M LOOKING
FOR A PARTNER.
YOU GOT A JOB?
MULTIPLE...
AND I NEED SOMEONE
WITH YOUR PARTICULAR
SET OF SKILLS.
[CELL PHONE RINGING
AND VIBRATING]
UGH.
WHO WAS THAT?
NO ONE.
YOU STILL GOOD
WITH LOCKS?
HEY, LAUREL.
IT'S ME AGAIN.
I JUST HAD A CRAVING
FOR FRENCH FRIES,
MILK SHAKES,
AND REALLY COLD FRUIT.
ARE YOU IN?
LOOK. I KNOW THIS IS
PROBABLY GONNA GET BURIED
BETWEEN THE MANY, MANY,
MANY, MANY MESSAGES
I HAVE ALREADY LEFT YOU,
BUT I'M JUST TRYING TO
MAKE SURE YOU ARE OK,
SO IF YOU COULD CALL
ME BACK, PLEASE.
[BEEP]
STILL TRYING TO
GET IN TOUCH WITH LAUREL?
YEAH. IT'S TAKING
AN ALARMING "SWINGERS"
AMOUNT OF TIME.
NOT PROUD,
AND MY GO-TO WAY
TO FIND HER
WOULD BE ARCHER,
BUT THAT IS TAKING
AN ANNOYINGLY
LONG TIME TO GET
BACK ONLINE, SO...
SHE DOESN'T WANT
TO BE FOUND, FELICITY.
HER WHOLE LIFE
HAS BEEN FLIPPED
UPSIDE DOWN.
I KNOW WHAT THAT'S
LIKE. JUST...
SPEAKING OF, ARE YOU
SURE THAT YOU ARE OK
NOW THAT YOU KNOW THAT
YOUR SISTER'S EVIL
AND TRIED TO KILL YOU?
TOO SOON?
NEED TO FOCUS ON
FINDING HER
AND THE NINTH CIRCLE
AND STOPPING WHATEVER
THEY HAVE PLANNED.
WELL, LUCKY FOR YOU,
YOUR WIFE IS
INCREDIBLY RESOURCEFUL.
SO I MADE A CHEAT
SHEET ON YOUR NEW LEAD.
EMIKO'S BULLET LED ME
TO ANDREW THORNTON'S
RIFLE,
WHICH LED ME TO
12 DIFFERENT
SHELL COMPANIES,
WHICH LED ME
TO THE BUYER.
AND IT'S NOT WEIRD
THAT SHE HASN'T FOUND
THE BUYER HERSELF
WITH THE RESOURCES
OF THE NINTH CIRCLE
AT HER DISPOSAL?
OK. WELL, NOT TO
TOOT MY OWN HORN,
BUT EMIKO IS MORE
OF THE "KARATE KID,"
HILARY SWANK VERSION,
AND I AM MORE
OF THE "MR. ROBOT"
VERSION BUT PRETTIER.
HAVE YOU CONSIDERED
THAT EMIKO PROBABLY
MADE UP
THE WHOLE "FINDING
MY MOTHER'S KILLER"
THING?
I KNOW THAT SHE'S LIED
ABOUT BASICALLY
EVERYTHING ELSE,
BUT I...I JUST HAVE
A SIXTH SENSE
THAT SHE'S NOT
LYING ABOUT THIS ONE,
SO IF JOHN AND I CAN FIND
THE KILLER FIRST,
THEN WE CAN LEVERAGE
THAT AGAINST EMIKO
AND THE NINTH CIRCLE
AND STOP WHATEVER
THEY HAVE PLANNED.
WELL, I HAVE A SENSE
THAT A ROAD TRIP
WITH JOHN IS EXACTLY
WHAT THE DOCTOR ORDERED.
BRING RENE WITH YOU
FOR BACKUP.
RENE...AHEM...HAS
A SCHOOL THING WITH ZOE.
SPEAKING OF WHICH,
WILL YOU JUST...
WILL YOU TAKE IT EASY
FOR ME, PLEASE?
OH, WHO? ME?
UM, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I REALLY WISH I COULD,
BUT I HAVE
A REALLY INTENSE
NETFLIX BINGE
THAT I HAVE
SCHEDULED WAY BACK,
AND I ALSO AM GOING
TO EAT EVERYTHING
IN THE FRIDGE,
SO IT'S GONNA GET
PRETTY CRAZY IN HERE.
-PRECIOUS CARGO.
-I KNOW.
COMPUTER: DISARMED.
[DOOR SHUTS]
ZOE: IS HE STILL
FOLLOWING US?
I DON'T SEE HIM.
I THINK WE FINALLY
LOST THE SON OF A...
OH! UH!
MIA: SPOKE TOO SOON.
ZOE: OVER HERE. HURRY.
DINAH ON COMMS:
ZOE, MIA, COME IN.
WHAT'S YOUR ETA?
TRYING TO SHAKE
A BOGEY.
WHAT'S THE STATUS
ON NEST TWO?
DINAH: GONE. GALAXY ONE
HAS RAIDED
ALL OF OUR SAFE HOUSES.
ALPHA BASE IS OUR
LAST SECURE LOCATION.
ALL SURVIVING CANARIES
NEED TO RENDEZVOUS
HERE IMMEDIATELY.
BE CAREFUL.
WE NEED TO TAKE
THIS GUY OUT.
DINAH GAVE US
AN ORDER.
I DON'T WORK
FOR DINAH.
[CLANG]
WE'RE CLEAR.
LET'S GO.
WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU DOING?
FINISHING THIS.
YOU'LL GET US
BOTH KILLED.
[BEEPING]
SNOW ON TV: FORMER
DISTRICT ATTORNEY LAUREL LANCE
IS FACING ALLEGATIONS
OF MURDER
FOLLOWING THE DEATH
OF HALCONE GANG MEMBER
GUSTAVO HERNANDEZ LAST WEEK.
THE SCPD HAS ISSUED
A WARRANT FOR HER ARREST,
SPARKING A CITY-WIDE MANHUNT.
ANYONE WITH INFORMATION
ON HER WHEREABOUTS...
A MANHUNT? DON'T
YOU THINK THAT'S
A LITTLE HARSH?
-LAUREL KILLED SOMEONE.
-ALLEGEDLY.
HER DNA AND FINGERPRINTS
WERE FOUND
ALL OVER THE SCENE.
LAUREL IS SMART.
YOU REALLY THINK THAT
SHE'D LEAVE EVIDENCE
BEHIND
IF SHE REALLY DID
KILL THE GUY?
SHE HAD A PRETTY
STRONG MOTIVE.
HERNANDEZ'S DEATH
WAS IMPERATIVE
IN HER WINNING
HER CASE.
SHE HASN'T KILLED ANYONE
SINCE SHE'S BEEN THE D.A.
WHY WOULD SHE START NOW?
YOU'VE SEEN HOW HARD
SHE'S WORKED,
HOW MUCH SHE'S CHANGED.
EXCEPT SHE OBVIOUSLY
HASN'T.
LOOK. I KNOW SHE'S
YOUR FRIEND,
AND FOR A WHILE,
I ACTUALLY THOUGHT
THE TWO OF US WERE DOING
GOOD WORK TOGETHER, TOO,
BUT THE TRUTH IS
LAUREL IS BLACK SIREN.
SHE IS A RUTHLESS MURDERER,
AND WE ARE ALL FOOLING
OURSELVES THINKING SHE IS
ANYTHING LIKE THE REAL
LAUREL LANCE.
WE SHOULD BE HELPING
HER, NOT HUNTING HER.
LAUREL IS A CRIMINAL,
AND WE ARE GOING TO
BRING HER TO JUSTICE,
SOMETHING WE SHOULD HAVE
DONE A LONG TIME AGO.
[ADDING MACHINE CLICKING]
PINKY SANTORINI.
IT'S QUITE THE OPERATION
YOU'VE GOT HERE.
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
I OWN A DRY-CLEANING
BUSINESS.
PLEASE. I HAVEN'T HAD
A PROBLEM IN 22 YEARS.
WELL, IT LOOKS LIKE
YOU HAVE A PROBLEM NOW.
THANKS FOR PLAYING.
[BEEPING]
TIME FOR OUR PAYDAY.
FEELS GOOD
TO BE BACK.
HEY. ARE YOU OK?
YOUR MESSAGE MADE IT
SOUND LIKE THE BUNKER
WAS ON FIRE.
LAUREL DIDN'T KILL
GUSTAVO HERNANDEZ.
-EMIKO DID.
-WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
THIS IS HIS
TOXICOLOGY REPORT.
THERE WERE TRACES
OF HYDROGEN CYANIDE FOUND
IN HIS BLOOD, WHICH IS
THE GO-TO POISON
OF THE NINTH CIRCLE.
THE SCPD HAD NO REASON
TO TRACE IT BACK TO THEM.
EMIKO FRAMED LAUREL
BECAUSE LAUREL TOLD
OLIVER HER SECRET. BOOM.
WELL, IT STILL DOESN'T
CHANGE ANYTHING.
OF COURSE IT DOES.
DID YOU HEAR
WHAT I JUST SAID?
EVEN IF LAUREL DIDN'T
KILL HERNANDEZ,
SHE'S BACK TO BEING
BLACK SIREN.
THERE WAS JUST A ROBBERY
AT PINKY'S DRY CLEANER.
WHAT'D THEY STEAL,
BUBBLES?
PINKY'S IS RUN
BY WALTER SANTORINI.
HE'S A MONEY LAUNDERER
FOR THE MOB.
THEY TOOK
OVER 100 GRAND.
-WHOA.
-YEAH.
MAYBE SHE NEEDS THE
MONEY BECAUSE
SHE'S PLANNING
ON LEAVING TOWN AGAIN.
SHE ALSO NOW
HAS A PARTNER.
WELL, THERE HAS TO BE
AN EXPLANATION.
SANTORINI'S ACTUALLY
PART OF A CASE
LAUREL AND I HAD
BEEN WORKING
FOR THE LAST
FEW MONTHS,
A CASE WHICH IS NOW
NONEXISTENT THANKS
TO THIS LAST
LITTLE STUNT.
SO SHE'S USING HER
D.A. RESOURCES
TO IDENTIFY TARGETS.
THAT'S CLEVER.
BAD. VERY BAD.
OK. THIS IS THE DATABASE
OF ALL THE CASES
CURRENTLY BEING
INVESTIGATED BY THE
DISTRICT ATTORNEY'S OFFICE.
PLEASE HOLD.
YEAH. LOOKS LIKE LAUREL'S
BEEN ACCESSING IT
THROUGH A SERIES
OF REROUTED IP ADDRESSES.
DOES THAT MEAN
WE CAN TRACK HER?
I MEAN, IT MEANS I COULD
PROBABLY TALK TO HER,
AND THEN I CAN CONVINCE HER
NOT TO DO THIS WHOLE
BLACK SIREN BACKSLIDE
OR WHATEVER THIS IS.
WELL, EVEN IF
YOU COULD,
DAMAGE IS
ALREADY DONE.
IT WAS A GOOD CHAT.
I REALLY LOVE OUR CHATS.
FELICITY TELL YOU
HOW SHE TRACKED
THE RIFLE
TO THIS APARTMENT?
JUST CALL HER A GENIUS
AND LEAVE IT AT THAT.
-GONNA CHECK UPSTAIRS.
-COPY THAT.
-OLIVER, I FOUND SOME...
-NOTHING!
YOU.
NEW OUTFIT.
[ARROW FLIES]
YOU THINK AN ARROW
IS GONNA STOP ME?
I THINK A TRANQ
ARROW WILL.
DO YOU KNOW HIM?
HE'S ONE OF
THE LONGBOW HUNTERS.
WHAT ARE THEY DOING
MIXED UP IN EMIKO'S
MOTHER'S MURDER?
THAT'S A GOOD QUESTION.
[CELL PHONE RINGING
AND VIBRATING]
[SIGHS]
DON'T HANG UP,
AND I MEAN THAT.
LITERALLY, YOU WILL
NOT BE ABLE TO EXIT
MY WINDOW.
YOU REALLY CAN'T
TAKE A HINT, CAN YOU?
LOOK. I KNOW
THAT EMIKO KILLED
GUSTAVO HERNANDEZ.
OOH! CONGRATULATIONS,
DETECTIVE FELICITY.
IT'S ONLY A MATTER
OF TIME UNTIL
OLIVER STOPS HER,
SO WHATEVER BAD
AND EVIL PLAN THAT
YOU HAVE BREWING,
IT'S NOT TOO LATE
FOR YOU TO NOT GO
OVER TO THE DARK SIDE.
OLIVER'S SISTER DID
ME A FAVOR
BECAUSE I WAS REALLY
SICK AND TIRED
OF PRETENDING TO BE
SOMEBODY I'M NOT.
PLUS, NO ONE BELIEVED
IT ANYWAY.
I DID. LOOK.
WHAT HAPPENED
TO YOU WASN'T FAIR.
YOU WERE
ACCUSED OF MURDER,
YOU LOST YOUR JOB,
DINAH DIDN'T HAVE
YOUR BACK.
I GET IT. YOU GOT
A BUCKET LOAD
OF BAD NEWS,
BUT YOU ARE NOT
BLACK SIREN,
NOT ANYMORE.
IT'S FUNNY. I USED TO
BELIEVE THAT, TOO.
THINK OF ALL
THE GOOD YOU'VE
DONE, LAUREL.
THINK ABOUT HONORING
QUENTIN.
QUENTIN IS DEAD.
NOBODY CARES ABOUT QUENTIN.
HE ONLY WANTED
HIS DAUGHTER BACK.
THAT IS NOT TRUE.
YOU'VE DONE A LOT
OF GOOD AS THE D.A.,
NOT TO MENTION YOU
WERE THERE FOR ME
WHEN I NEEDED A FRIEND.
I'M NOT WILLING TO
LET YOU JUST THROW
THAT ALL AWAY
AND FORGET ABOUT IT.
LOOK. I'M REALLY SORRY
IF YOU THOUGHT
WE HAD A REAL FRIENDSHIP,
BUT IT WAS ALL
JUST AN ACT,
AND DON'T YOU DARE
TRY AND STOP ME.
STOPPING THOSE BOMBS
PROMPTED GALAXY ONE
TO PUT THEIR
MASTER PLAN IN MOTION,
EXPANDING ARCHER'S
INFLUENCE INTO STAR CITY
AND MAKING SURE THEY
TAKE OUT ANY AND ALL
OPPOSITION.
STARTING
WITH THE CANARIES.
[SNIFFLES]
HOW MANY HAVE WE
LOST?
I'M WAITING
ON A BODY COUNT
FROM ROY, WILLIAM,
AND CONNOR,
BUT THEY'VE ALREADY
CONFIRMED 10 DEAD
AND 5 MISSING.
[INHALES AND EXHALES]
IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT.
BUT IT'S MY
RESPONSIBILITY.
[DOOR OPENS]
OH, THANK GOODNESS
YOU TWO ARE SAFE.
YEAH. UM, COULD HAVE
TAKEN CREEPY MASK GUY
OFF THE BOARD
EXCEPT SOMEONE GOT
IN MY WAY.
ZOE MADE THE RIGHT CALL.
WE'VE LOST ENOUGH BLOOD
ALREADY AS IT IS.
AND UNTIL WE KNOW WHAT
THE HELL IS GOING ON,
WE NEED TO LAY LOW.
AND DO WHAT,
NOTHING?
WHAT WE DO IS
MOURN OUR DEAD.
THEN WE FIGURE OUT
A PLAN THAT WON'T COST
US ANY MORE LIVES.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
GALAXY ONE HAS US
OUTMANNED AND OUTGUNNED.
WE NEED TO FIND
ANOTHER WAY TO
EVEN THE ODDS.
GALAXY ONE JUST
DECIMATED THE ENTIRE
CANARY NETWORK.
YOU WANT TO EVEN
THE ODDS, YOU GET
OUT THERE
AND YOU FIGHT
THE HELL BACK.
IF YOU DON'T,
WE'RE ALL DEAD.
SHADOW THIEF: PSST.
UNH!
I REALLY MISSED
OUR GIRLS' NIGHTS OUT.
-ME, TOO.
-LIKE TAKING CANDY.
FROM A FILTHY RICH BABY.
[CHIRP]
[BEEP]
THAT'S GOT TO BE
$10 MILLION WORTH
OF DIAMONDS.
DINAH: IT'S TOO BAD
IT DOESN'T BELONG TO YOU.
AND WHAT?
ARE YOU GONNA
STOP US?
DON'T DO THIS, LAUREL.
OH, I THOUGHT
YOU'D BE HAPPY.
YOU WERE RIGHT
ABOUT ME ALL ALONG.
OH, AND IT'S TOO BAD
THAT YOU DON'T HAVE
YOUR CRY ANYMORE.
[CANARY CRY]
BUT I STILL HAVE MINE.
PHEW. WHAT AN ENTRANCE.
OH, AND FEEL FREE
TO TELL LAUREL'S NEW FRIEND
THAT IT'S A BAD IDEA
TO LEAVE VAULT SCHEMATICS
JUST HANGING
AROUND HER LAIR.
WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE?
LAUREL: YEAH.
SAME QUESTION.
AREN'T YOU SUPPOSED
TO BE ON YOUR LITTLE
SPACESHIP OR SOMETHING?
I TOOK A BREAK
TO CLEAN UP YOUR MESS.
WHAT IS THIS, SOME
KIND OF INTERVENTION.
I KNOW YOU'RE NOT
MY SISTER,
BUT IN ANOTHER WORLD
OR ANOTHER LIFE,
YOU COULD HAVE BEEN,
AND MY FATHER
BELIEVED IN YOU.
WELL, HE WAS WRONG,
BUT YOU'RE RIGHT
ABOUT ONE THING.
YOU'RE NOT MY SISTER.
[SIREN SCREAM]
STAY THE HELL
AWAY FROM ME.
YOU DIDN'T GO BACK
TO THE BUNKER.
WE ALWAYS GO
BACK TO THE BUNKER.
I HAD WORK TO DO.
I KNOW I SHOULD HAVE
TOLD YOU ABOUT SARA.
IT WOULD HAVE
BEEN NICE.
AND WHAT WAS THAT DEVICE?
I MODIFIED O.G.
LAUREL'S OLD COLLAR.
-SAME TECH, NEW LOOK.
-IT WAS IMPRESSIVE.
FELICITY, WE ARE
THE ONLY TEAM SANCTIONED
TO WORK WITH SCPD.
PLEASE REMEMBER IT
DOESN'T MEAN ANY VIGILANTE
GETS A FREE PASS.
IN MY DEFENSE,
IF ANYONE'S GONNA GET
THROUGH TO LAUREL,
IT'S HER SISTER...
WELL, NOT HER REAL SISTER,
BUT THE FACE
OF HER SISTER...
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
YOU CANNOT SERIOUSLY
THINK SHE'S STILL
CAPABLE OF REDEMPTION
AFTER WHAT WE JUST SAW.
THAT IS HARSH,
ESPECIALLY COMING
FROM THE PERSON
WHO WRONGLY ACCUSED
HER OF MURDER.
SO YOU'RE SAYING
WHAT LAUREL'S DOING
IS MY FAULT?
OUR FAULT. MAYBE
IF WE HAD BEEN
A BETTER SUPPORT
SYSTEM TO HER.
LAUREL DID NOT BECOME
BLACK SIREN BECAUSE
WE WERE BAD FRIENDS,
FELICITY.
THAT IS A CHOICE SHE MADE
ON HER OWN.
IT IS NOT SOME
INEVITABLE CONSEQUENCE
OF SOMETHING WE DID.
EVERYTHING THAT HAS
HAPPENED SINCE SHE
HAS BEEN FIRED
IS ON HER!
I THINK YOU'RE BEING
HARD ON HER
BECAUSE YOU FEEL GUILTY.
AND I THINK YOU NEED
TO DROP THE BLINDERS.
THIS IS LAUREL'S
NEW GAL PAL...
AVIVA METULA,
FORMER MOSSAD AGENT
TURNED MASTER THIEF.
SHE NOW GOES BY
THE NAME SHADOW THIEF.
DINAH: VERY ON THE NOSE.
SHE USED TO WORK
WITH DIAZ,
WHICH MEANS SHE PROBABLY
USED TO WORK WITH LAUREL.
IT LOOKS LIKE
SHADOW THIEF HAS
REALLY LEVELED UP
HER BAD GUY GAME
SINCE HER DIAZ DAYS.
THERE'S NO MORE
PETTY HEISTS.
IT'S ONLY A MATTER
OF TIME BEFORE SHE
GETS LAUREL
MIXED UP IN WHATEVER
SHE CAME TO TOWN FOR.
-THEN WE BETTER FIND THEM FAST.
-OK.
FELICITY MUST
HAVE FIGURED OUT
I WAS USING
THE D.A. DATABASE
TO FIND OUR TARGETS.
WHICH ONE WAS FELICITY?
THE CHATTY ONE.
HERE. YOU NEED THIS.
DON'T WORRY. THERE ARE
PLENTY OF JOBS.
NOT IF SHE KNOWS HOW
I'M FINDING THEM.
MAYBE IT'S A GOOD THING.
NO OFFENSE,
BUT YOUR JOBS ARE
SMALL POTATOES.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
LET'S JUST SAY THAT
SINCE OUR DIAZ DAYS
I'VE MET SOME
NEW FRIENDS,
SOME VERY POWERFUL
FRIENDS
WHO PAY VERY WELL
FOR MY DESTRUCTIVE
SERVICES.
SO YOU'RE
A TERRORIST FOR HIRE?
HEH HEH. I PREFER
MERCENARY WITH PERKS,
AND I COULD USE
SOMEONE LIKE YOU.
I JUST WANT TO MAKE SURE
THAT YOU'RE
THE SAME RUTHLESS
BLACK SIREN I ONCE KNEW.
I WOULDN'T BE HERE
IF I WASN'T.
GOOD BECAUSE IF THOSE
WOMEN CONTINUE
TO BE A PROBLEM
FOR US...
YOU DON'T HAVE TO
WORRY.
[SETS GLASS ON DESK]
THEY GET IN OUR WAY
AGAIN, I'LL KILL
THEM MYSELF.
WHO HIRED YOU TO
KILL KAZUMI ADACHI?
KAZUMI WHO?
WRONG ANSWER.
JOHN:
DOESN'T MATTER TO US.
HOW DO YOU WANT
THIS TO GO?
YOU GUYS CAN CHOP OFF
ALL 10 OF MY FINGERS,
AND IT WON'T MATTER.
I HAVE NO IDEA
WHO HIRED ME.
THEY NEVER CONTACTED
ME DIRECTLY.
THEY HOW'D THEY
OFFER YOU THE JOB?
THEY DIRECTED ME
TO A DROP-OFF LOCATION.
ONCE I GOT THERE,
FOUND A COIN.
WAS IT
AN ITALIAN FLORIN?
NO IDEA.
ALL I KNOW IS
THAT IT WAS OLD.
THERE WAS A MICROCHIP
INSIDE,
INSTRUCTIONS TO GET
MY WEAPON, THE TARGET.
ONCE THE JOB WAS COMPLETED,
THEY WIRED MY PAYMENT
FROM A BANK ACCOUNT
IN SWITZERLAND.
A FLORIN,
SWISS BANK ACCOUNT.
JOHN, THIS IS DANTE.
SO WHAT NOW?
YOU GUYS KILL ME?
LET'S GO. WE GOT
WHAT WE CAME FOR.
[GROWLS]
FELICITY: WELL,
I'M HAVING DEJA VU
IN THE BEST WAY
POSSIBLE.
SARA: DID DINAH READ YOU
THE RIOT ACT?
NOTHING
I CAN'T HANDLE.
YOU'VE COME A LONG WAY
FROM THE I.T. GIRL
SECRETLY CRUSHING
ON OLIVER QUEEN.
APPARENTLY, IT WASN'T
MUCH OF A SECRET.
EVERYBODY KNEW.
ZERO POKER FACE,
AND I ALWAYS
WONDERED, YOU KNOW,
WERE YOU
FLIRTING WITH ME
ALL THOSE TIMES
YOU SAID I WAS CUTE?
WHY? WERE YOU INTO IT?
OF COURSE. IT'S YOU.
-OH, I MISSED YOU.
-I MISSED YOU, TOO.
-THANK YOU FOR COMING.
-OF COURSE.
I JUST WISH IT
HAD GONE BETTER.
LOOK. LAUREL
WILL COME AROUND.
ALL WE HAVE TO DO
IS GET HER AWAY
FROM HER NEW BFF
LONG ENOUGH
TO KNOCK
SOME SENSE INTO HER.
I MEAN, THAT IS
IF YOU DON'T HAVE
TO GO BACK
FOR ANY TIMEY-WIMEY
SHENANIGANS.
WELL, EVERY TIME
I LEAVE THE SHIP,
IT BASICALLY MEANS
THE INMATES TAKE OVER
THE ASYLUM,
BUT IT'S FINE.
WANT TO MAKE SURE
THAT MY REAL SISTER'S NAME
DOESN'T GET DRAGGED
THROUGH THE MUD,
AND, BY THE WAY,
WHY ARE YOU SO CONCERNED
WITH SAVING THIS LAUREL?
I MEAN, SHE'S MORE
LIKE OUR LAUREL
THAN YOU REALIZE.
SHE HELPED OLIVER
GET OUT OF PRISON
THE LEGAL WAY,
AND SHE STOPPED ME
FROM KILLING
RICARDO DIAZ.
FELICITY SMOAK IS
KILLING PEOPLE NOW?
I REALLY HAVE
MISSED A LOT.
THE POINT IS,
IS THAT I DIDN'T
KILL ANYONE
BECAUSE LAUREL PULLED
ME BACK FROM THE EDGE.
THAT'S WHAT I WANT TO
DO FOR HER NOW,
YOU KNOW, SEND HER
OUT A LIFELINE.
EVEN IF THERE WAS
A WAY BACK FOR LAUREL,
SHE HAS TO WANT IT.
YOU CAN'T FORCE
REDEMPTION ON PEOPLE.
OH, THAT I KNOW.
WELL, IT'S ALL
THEORETICAL ANYWAY
SINCE I HAVE NO IDEA
WHERE SHADOW THIEF
OR LAUREL ARE
OPERATING OUT OF.
HOLD THAT THOUGHT.
DINAH JUST GOT
A LOCATION
ON SHADOW THIEF'S
SECRET HIDEOUT.
TURNS OUT...OF
COURSE, OF COURSE...
IT'S AT A SHADY WAREHOUSE
IN A SHADY PART OF TOWN.
IS THAT WHERE LAUREL'S
BEEN HOLING UP?
THAT'S WHAT DINAH THINKS.
MAN, IT IS COMPLETELY
OFF THE GRID.
[CELL PHONE CHIMES]
DINAH WANTS ME TO GO
WITH HER SO SHE
DOESN'T GO IN BLIND.
SO WE DON'T GO
IN BLIND.
UM, NO. MMM. THIS IS
MORE OF A TWO-WOMAN JOB.
DINAH WANTS TO KEEP IT
ABOVE BOARD.
NO. GOT IT.
NOT INVITED.
-OK.
CALL ME.
FELICITY: NOT TO BELABOR
THE POINT OR ANYTHING,
BUT IT WOULD HAVE BEEN
REALLY NICE TO HAVE
WHITE CANARY HERE WITH US...
THE FLIGHT. HEH!
YOU KNOW, SINCE
YOU'RE BOTH CANARIES
AND EVERYTHING.
-CAN WE TALK ABOUT THIS LATER?
-MM-HMM.
WHO'S HERE
BESIDES US?
THERE'S ONLY TWO
HEAT SIGNATURES
IN THE ENTIRE BUILDING
BESIDES US, AND...
THEY'RE RIGHT
BEHIND THIS DOOR.
IT'S GOT TO BE
SHADOW THIEF
AND LAUREL.
-YOU READY?
-MM-HMM.
WHERE ARE THEY?
-THEY PLAYED US.
-FAKE HEAT SIGNATURES?
THAT IS DEVIOUS
AND IMPRESSIVE.
[BEEPING]
GET DOWN!
ARE YOU OK?
LAUREL TRIED
TO KILL US.
IT TURNS OUT WE
COULD HAVE USED SOME
WHITE CANARY BACKUP
AFTER ALL.
-WELL, YOU GOT IT NOW.
-SORRY.
NO WORRIES.
FIND ANYTHING
AT THE LAIR?
NO, NOT YET.
THEY WERE
SLOPPY, THOUGH.
PROBABLY TOO FIXATED
ON KILLING US.
THE TECH THAT SHADOW THIEF
LEFT BEHIND
WILL PROBABLY
GIVE US SOME INSIGHT
ON HOW SHE OPERATES.
WITH ANY LUCK, THAT'S
HOW WE'LL FIND HER.
I'M SO SORRY.
I REALLY THOUGHT
LAUREL HAD CHANGED.
WELL, THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
WE'RE JUST LUCKY
SHE'S RUSTY
AND MESSED UP.
-YEAH.
-OR MAYBE IT'S NOT LUCK AT ALL.
I MEAN, BLACK SIREN'S
A LETHAL, UNFORGIVING KILLER.
IT'S RARE SHE FAILS,
EVEN RARER SHE DOESN'T
DO THE JOB HERSELF.
I'M GONNA GET SOME AIR.
LET ME KNOW IF YOU GUYS
FIND ANYTHING.
YOU KNOW, MAYBE
IF I COULD HAVE
HELPED MORE OR...
FELICITY, YOU HAVE TO
STOP BLAMING YOURSELF.
LAUREL HAD EVERY
OPPORTUNITY TO MAKE
THE RIGHT DECISION,
AND SHE DIDN'T.
LAUREL HAS NOT CHANGED.
SHE IS THE SAME MONSTER
WHO KILLED VINNIE.
WHAT LAUREL DID
IS UNFORGIVEABLE,
BUT SHE'S JUST
ON THIS PATH,
AND SHE DOESN'T KNOW
HOW TO GET OFF OF IT.
DO YOU KNOW HOW MANY
TIMES IN MY LIFE
I COULD HAVE GONE
DOWN THE SAME PATH,
INCLUDING KILLING LAUREL
LAST YEAR, AND I DIDN'T?
YEAH, YOU DIDN'T
BECAUSE YOU HAD US.
I MEAN, WHEN
OLIVER BROUGHT YOU
ON THE TEAM,
YOU WEREN'T
EXACTLY A SAINT.
I WAS PROTECTING WOMEN
WHO COULDN'T PROTECT
THEMSELVES.
YES, BUT EVEN IN YOUR
DARKEST OF TIMES,
EVEN WHEN YOU
WERE HELL-BENT
ON KILLING LAUREL,
WE STILL HAD
YOUR BACK.
I MEAN, WE GAVE YOU
A SECOND CHANCE,
AND LOOK WHERE YOU
ARE NOW.
YOU'RE...YOU'RE CAPTAIN
OF THE SCPD,
YOU'RE A DEPUTIZED
VIGILANTE.
I MEAN, YOU COULDN'T
POSSIBLY HAVE IMAGINED
THAT THIS IS WHERE
YOU WOULD HAVE ENDED UP.
NO, THAT'S TRUE, BUT I...
I'M GRATEFUL FOR OLIVER
AND FOR THE WHOLE TEAM,
BUT I DON'T THINK
IT MATTERS WITH LAUREL.
I DON'T THINK SHE EVER
EVEN WANTED THAT KIND
OF SUPPORT.
OR MAYBE SHE WANTED
IT MORE THAN ANY OF US
AND DIDN'T REALIZE IT
UNTIL IT WAS GONE.
I APPRECIATE YOU
WANTING PAYBACK
FOR WHAT HAPPENED
TO THE CANARIES,
BUT NOT LIKE THIS.
MIA, IF YOU GO
OUT THERE ON YOUR OWN,
CHANCES ARE YOU WILL NOT
MAKE IT BACK ALIVE.
GALAXY ONE FOUND ALL OF
YOUR SAFE HOUSES, DINAH.
THEY'LL FIND
THIS ONE, TOO.
I'M NOT GONNA SIT
AROUND AND WAIT
FOR THEM
TO MASSACRE
THE REST OF US.
BELIEVE ME, THERE IS
NOTHING I WOULD
LOVE MORE THAN TO SEE
THOSE SONS OF BITCHES
PAY FOR WHAT THEY DID
TO MY GIRLS.
SO WHY DON'T YOU?
BECAUSE I KNOW I
CAN'T DO IT ALONE,
AND NEITHER CAN YOU.
THEN COME WITH ME.
INSTEAD OF HIDING
IN THE SHADOWS,
LET'S TAKE THIS FIGHT
TO GALAXY ONE,
MAKE THEM PAY
FOR BLOOD WITH BLOOD.
SOMETIMES, I DON'T
KNOW WHO YOU SOUND
MORE LIKE...
YOUR MOTHER
OR YOUR FATHER.
DO YOU KNOW WHY
I STARTED THE CANARIES,
WHAT IT REPRESENTS?
THIS IS MORE THAN JUST
SOME REBELLION GROUP.
IT'S A SUPPORT SYSTEM.
THIS IS A WAY FOR WOMEN
TO KNOW WE ALWAYS HAVE
EACH OTHER'S BACKS
NO MATTER WHAT HAPPENS,
WHENEVER WE NEED IT MOST,
SOMETHING I FAILED TO DO
FOR A FRIEND ONCE,
BUT EVER SINCE
THAT HAPPENED WITH HER,
I MADE A PROMISE
TO MYSELF THAT I
WOULD NEVER MAKE
THAT MISTAKE AGAIN.
THAT'S WHY WE WEAR THESE.
TO HONOR THAT PROMISE
AND THE BRAVERY
AND THE SACRIFICE
SHARED WITH THESE
AMAZING WOMEN,
WHO SOMEHOW...NO MATTER
HOW MANY TIMES THEY
GET KNOCKED DOWN...
THEY ALWAYS FIND
THE STRENGTH
TO GET BACK UP
AND FIGHT AGAIN...
AND THAT IS EXACTLY
WHAT THE SURVIVING
CANARIES ARE GOING TO DO
TOGETHER BUT WHEN
THE TIME IS RIGHT.
IT'S TOO BAD
I'M NOT A CANARY.
DANTE HAS BEEN
PULLING THE STRINGS
THIS ENTIRE TIME.
HE ORCHESTRATES
HER MOTHER'S MURDER,
AND HE SENDS HER
DOWN THIS PATH.
SOUNDS LIKE YOU'RE
SOFTENING UP ON YOUR
SISTER AGAIN.
I JUST HAVE A BETTER
UNDERSTANDING OF WHY SHE'S
DONE WHAT SHE'S DONE.
WHEN EMIKO REALIZES
THAT DANTE HAS BEEN
MANIPULATING HER,
IT WILL DRIVE
A WEDGE BETWEEN HER
AND THE NINTH CIRCLE.
THAT'S HOW WE
STOP THEM.
SARA: THOUGHT I MIGHT
FIND YOU HERE.
IT'S PRETTY BRAVE
OF YOU,
SNEAKING UP ON ME
FROM BEHIND.
IF YOU WANTED
TO KILL PEOPLE,
YOU WOULDN'T HAVE GAVE
THEM THAT WARNING TIME
BEFORE THE BOMB
WENT OFF.
I REALLY MISS HIM.
IT LOOKS LIKE
YOU DO, TOO.
IS THIS YOU TRYING
TO CONVINCE ME
THAT I'VE CHANGED,
THAT I'M MORE LIKE
YOUR LAUREL?
NO. NOBODY'S AS GOOD
AS THE ORIGINAL
LAUREL LANCE,
NOT EVEN ME.
LOOK. I DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU'VE HEARD
ABOUT ME,
BUT BASICALLY,
I HAD AN AFFAIR
WITH MY SISTER'S
BOYFRIEND,
I ALLOWED MY ENTIRE
FAMILY TO THINK
THAT I WAS DEAD,
AND THEN I BECAME
A LEAGUE-TRAINED
ASSASSIN.
WOW. THAT'S IMPRESSIVE.
MY POINT IS EVEN
SOMEONE WITH A PAST
AS CHECKERED AS MINE
CAN STILL TURN
THEIR LIFE AROUND,
CAN BE A HERO.
I WAS BEING A HERO.
I WAS THE D.A.,
I GOT OLIVER
OUT OF PRISON,
AND I WAS THE ONLY
ONE WHO FIGURED OUT
THAT HIS LITTLE SISTER
WAS BASICALLY THE DEVIL,
AND THEY STILL
TURNED ON ME.
SO, WHAT, YOU THINK
YOU DESERVE A MEDAL
FOR TRYING TO BE
GOOD FOR 5 SECONDS?
REDEMPTION ISN'T
A DESTINATION.
IT'S A JOURNEY.
I WASTED YEARS
RUNNING AWAY
FROM ALL THE BAD THINGS
THAT I HAD DONE
BECAUSE I DIDN'T WANT
TO FACE THE PAIN THAT
I HAD CAUSED
BECAUSE I DIDN'T WANT
TO BE THAT PERSON,
AND THEN I REALIZED
THE ONLY WAY TO STOP
BEING THAT PERSON
WAS TO COME HOME
AND OWN UP
TO THE THINGS
THAT I HAD DONE,
AND, YEAH, IT WAS
PAINFUL,
AND IT TOOK
A REALLY LONG TIME,
BUT IT WAS THE ONLY WAY
TO BECOME SOMEONE ELSE,
SOMEONE BETTER
THAN WHO I WAS.
WELL, THAT'S GREAT
FOR YOU,
BUT EVEN IF I WANTED
TO CHANGE,
IT'S A LITTLE BIT
TOO LATE
BECAUSE THIS IS
WHO I AM.
HEH. I WAS STARTING
TO THINK YOU MIGHT
NOT SHOW.
I HAD SOME BUSINESS
TO TAKE CARE OF.
SO WHAT'S THIS WEAPON
THAT WE'RE STEALING?
WHO CARES? ALL THAT
MATTERS IS THAT
WE'RE GETTING PAID.
YOU READY?
ABSOLUTELY.
LAUREL: MANPOWER
SEEMS THIN.
I THOUGHT WE'D RUN
INTO SOME GUARDS.
WHY, DO YOU THINK
WE'RE HITTING IT NOW?
I'M GONNA CHECK OUT
THE SOUTH WING.
-YOU.
-DON'T LOOK SURPRISED.
YOUR FRIEND'S SUIT
IS BASICALLY
A GIANT TRACKER.
DINAH: AND WE HAPPEN
TO KNOW SOMEBODY WHO'S
VERY GOOD WITH A COMPUTER.
YOU BROUGHT YOUR
LITTLE FRIEND WITH YOU.
HOW TYPICAL.
IT'S NOT TOO LATE,
LAUREL.
DON'T DO THIS.
OHH. THAT SONG
OF YOURS IS GETTING
A LITTLE OLD.
[DEVICE BEEPING]
LAUREL!
UGH. GOD. YOU'RE
HERE, TOO?
DO YOU KNOW WHAT
SHADOW THIEF IS PLANNING
TO DO WITH THAT DEVICE?
YES. SELL IT
FOR A LOT OF MONEY
OF WHICH I GET HALF.
WHO DO YOU THINK SHE'S
GONNA SELL IT TO,
THE GIRL SCOUTS?
THAT DEVICE IS GONNA BE
USED TO KILL PEOPLE.
WELL, THAT'S NOT REALLY
MY CONCERN NOW, IS IT?
-MOVE.
-NO.
SERIOUSLY? FELICITY,
DON'T YOU THINK
YOU'RE JUST
A LITTLE BIT OUT
OF YOUR ELEMENT?
THAT IS CORRECT.
I KNOW THAT,
BUT SO ARE YOU.
OH, FOR THE LOVE
OF GOD, WOULD YOU
GIVE IT UP ALREADY?
THIS IS WHO I AM!
DO YOU NOT SEE THAT?
WHO I SEE IS SOMEONE
THAT I BELIEVE IN
AND SOMEONE THAT
I REALLY CARE ABOUT.
DINAH: FELICITY,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
FELICITY: FORGET LIVING
UP TO LAUREL'S LEGACY,
AND FORGET BEING WHO
LANCE WANTED YOU TO BE.
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
I WANT YOU TO GET
OUT OF MY WAY.
I GUESS IF YOU'RE OK
WITH THAT DEVICE
KILLING PEOPLE,
YOU MAY AS WELL
START WITH ME.
-ME, TOO.
-AND ME.
[SIREN SCREAM]
I CHANGED MY MIND.
THE DEAL'S OFF.
I KIND OF EXPECTED.
GOOD THING I HAD
A BACKUP PLAN.
WE HAVE TO GET
OUT OF HERE.
LOOK. IS THE PAYLOAD
DEVICE BIG ENOUGH
TO CLEAR OUT
THE BUILDING?
FELICITY: YES, BUT
THE PROBLEM IS
WE'RE
INSIDE THE BUILDING.
THAT'S EXACTLY
WHY THEY WON'T
BE EXPECTING IT.
HOW LONG DO YOU
NEED TO ARM IT?
90 SECONDS. BUT HOW
ARE WE GONNA GET OUT?
SARA: BIRDS FLY, DON'T THEY?
LET'S BUY HER SOME TIME.
UH...GO. GO.
[GUNFIRE]
[GRUNTING]
LAUREL:
HYAH! HYAH! HYAH...
COME ON, COME ON,
COME ON, COME ON. COME ON.
[BEEP]
-OHH!
-IT'S TIME TO GO.
STAY CLOSE.
[CANARY CRY]
OVERWATCH, NOW!
[BEEP]
FELICITY: CAN WE NEVER
DO THAT AGAIN?
SARA: IS EVERYBODY OK?
LAUREL: YOU CAME BACK FOR ME.
WE'RE ONLY AS STRONG
AS WE ARE TOGETHER,
SOMETHING I DIDN'T
REALIZE TILL JUST NOW.
WE ARE PRETTY
BADASS TOGETHER.
YEAH. LIKE A BIRDS
OF JUSTICE.
SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
[EXPLOSION
IN DISTANCE]
TO LADIES TAKING
DOWN LADIES.
DINAH: HEH.
AND TO LAUREL.
THANK YOU
FOR THE ASSIST,
AND I AM VERY,
VERY SORRY THAT
I DOUBTED YOU.
THAT MEANS A LOT.
I JUST WISH WE GOT
SHADOW THIEF.
WE'LL GET HER
NEXT TIME.
SO DOES THIS MEAN
YOU'RE NOT
GONNA ARREST ME?
I DON'T SEE
WHY I WOULD.
THIS NEW EVIDENCE
PROVES YOU DIDN'T
KILL HERNANDEZ,
AND YOU WENT
UNDERCOVER
TO BRING DOWN
THE SHADOW THIEF,
SO I AM AS SURPRISED
AS ANYONE.
THANK YOU.
NOW THAT LAUREL LANCE,
UPSTANDING CITIZEN,
IS BACK,
EVERYTHING CAN GO
BACK TO NORMAL.
ACTUALLY, IT CAN'T.
SAY WHAT, NOW?
I AM SO TIRED
OF RUNNING.
IT'S TIME FOR ME
TO GO HOME NOW.
HOME? AS
IN EARTH-2 HOME?
YEAH. SOMEONE
IN SIMILAR SHOES TOLD ME
IF I WANTED TO BE
ONE OF THE GOOD GUYS
THAT I NEEDED TO
RIGHT MY WRONGS,
AND THE ONLY WAY
TO DO THAT IS TO GO
BACK TO WHERE
IT ALL STARTED.
YEAH.
DINAH: OH. WELL, UH...
I'LL CHEERS TO THAT.
FELICITY: YEAH.
LAUREL: AH-AH.
HEH. I THINK I DESERVE
TWO OF THESE.
I MEAN, COME ON.
I WORKED REALLY
HARD, SO THERE.
CHEERS TO ME.
[CELL PHONE RINGING
AND VIBRATING]
OH, NO.
IT'S THE SCPD.
OK. APPARENTLY,
CRIMINALS DON'T CARE
HOW BADLY I NEED
A GIRLS' NIGHT.
I HAVE SOMETHING
FOR YOU.
FROM ONE CANARY
TO ANOTHER,
SARA WANTED YOU
TO HAVE THIS.
I CAN ADJUST IT FOR YOU.
PROBABLY GET YOUR CRY
BACK IF YOU WANT IT.
-THANK YOU.
-YEAH.
-YES, YOU ARE WELCOME.
-THANK YOU.
NO SWEAT.
DID IT ALL THE TIME
WHEN MY SISTER
WAS PREGNANT.
OH. WAY TO BURY
THE LEDE.
THAT'S HOW YOU KNEW
I WAS PREGNANT.
MM-HMM.
I HAVE SOMETHING
FOR YOU.
IT'S LAUREL'S
BLACK CANARY COSTUME.
YEAH. YEAH. I THOUGHT
YOU COULD USE IT HERE,
BUT, YOU KNOW,
MAYBE EARTH-2 NEEDS
A BLACK CANARY.
YOU ARE STILL PLANNING
ON BEING GOOD, RIGHT?
I'M PLANNING
TO TRY, YEAH.
GOOD.
I JUST REALLY HOPE
ONE DAY I'M
ACTUALLY WORTHY
OF IT.
ARCHER: WELCOME HOME,
MS. SMOAK.
OH, YOU'RE HOME.
I MISSED YOU.
DID YOU GET WHAT
YOU WERE LOOKING FOR?
YUP. I'M EXHAUSTED.
JUST WANT TO SIT
ON THE COUCH
AND ORDER SOME FOOD,
AND...I DON'T KNOW...
I'LL HAVE WHATEVER
YOU'RE CRAVING, OK?
I ALREADY ATE
AFTER I SAID
GOOD-BYE TO LAUREL.
SO YOU FOUND LAUREL,
BUT YOU SAID GOOD-BYE
TO HER ALREADY?
WELL, YEAH, AFTER WE
STOPPED HER
FROM GOING
ON A KILLING SPREE.
-HMM?
-DINAH AND SARA AND I.
-YEAH. THAT SARA,
AND WE DID IT,
SUPEREASY, YOU KNOW.
IT WAS LIKE
"CHARLIE'S ANGELS"
WITHOUT THE FEATHERED
HAIR AND CASUAL SEXISM.
SO THAT WHOLE
TAKING IT EASY THING?
WELL, YOU KNOW I'M
NOT GOOD AT THAT.
WELL, I'M HERE NOW,
SO I'LL TAKE CARE OF YOU.
WELL, YOU COULD START
WITH A FOOT RUB.
YEAH.
AHH.
[RUSTLING]
WE KEEP THIS UP, PEOPLE
ARE GONNA START ASKING
WHY WE KEEP HANGING OUT
IN CEMETERIES.
I WAS NEVER VERY
GOOD AT GOOD-BYES.
QUENTIN ALWAYS SAW
THE GOOD IN ME
WHEN...WHEN NOBODY
ELSE DID.
I WISH I COULD TELL HIM
HOW MUCH IT MEANT TO ME.
HE KNEW.
HE WAS THE FIRST PERSON
TO MAKE ME FEEL LIKE
I WAS NEVER ALONE.
YOU'RE NOT ALONE,
NOT ANYMORE.
[DEVICE CHIRPS]
SO MUCH
FOR PLAN "A."
[GRUNTING]
UNH.
[SIREN SCREAM]
[RUNNING FOOTSTEPS]
[WHOOSH]
WHOA.
MIA: BUT I'VE SEEN
YOU BEFORE.
THE OLD GREEN ARROW
DOCUMENTARY.
-YOU'RE...
-A FRIEND OF YOUR PARENTS.
YOU'RE LUCKY WE GOT HERE
WHEN WE DID.
DINAH SENT YOU
TO WATCH MY BACK.
IT'S WHAT CANARIES DO.
GIVE THIS TO FELICITY.
YOU LOOK SO MUCH
LIKE HER,
AND YOU MAY NOT BE A CANARY,
AND YOU STILL HAVE
A LONG WAY TO GO
TO PROVE THAT
YOU'RE A HERO.
TAKE IT FROM SOMEONE
WHO KNOWS HOW HARD
IT CAN BE,
AND DON'T SCREW IT UP.
MAN: GREG, MOVE YOUR HEAD.