My name is Oliver queen.
After five years
on a hellish island,
I have come home
with only one goal--
to save my city.
But to do so, I can't be
the killer I once was.
To honor my friend's memory,
I must be someone else.
I must be something else.
Previously on "Arrow"...
Time to choose, Oliver.
Who lives
and who dies.
Because in 30 seconds,
I will shoot them both.
You got what
you came for!
I guess you made
your choice. Time's up.
No!
If you stick that
in me, I'll kill you.
No, brother Roy,
you'll kill for me.
Where'd you get
the Mirakuru?
It was a gift.
A gift I would use
to save this city
from itself.
Whoa, oh, ahh!
Ahh! Oh!
The man in the skull
mask, who is he?!
I--I don't know!
You're the biggest street dealer
in Crescent Circle.
You know everything that
goes on over there.
Who is he?!
I ain't seen the guy before!
A skull mask,
are you freaking kidding me?!
Come on, man,
I'm still on parole!
Not anymore.
A spokesman for the
Central City mayor's office confirmed
the lack of any damage
or radioactive fallout
from the explosion that rocked
S.T.A.R. Labs five weeks ago.
Is Felicity
not back yet?
She said she wanted to spend
a few more days with Barry.
Any improvement
in his condition?
Still comatose.
How'd it go out there tonight?
Same as every other
pointed conversation
I have with these lowlifes
in Crescent Circle.
Nobody...
has seen a man
in a skull mask.
But he's still
out there.
Oliver, for the past
five weeks,
you've pushed yourself
pretty hard looking for this guy.
He has the Mirakuru,
Diggle!
I mean, you saw
what it took to kill one guy
that had been injected.
We practically had to drop
a building on him.
So imagine ten
or a hundred,
imagine a thousand.
You said Roy was injected.
Yeah.
I've just never seen you
spooked like this before.
That should
tell you something.
♪ Arrow 2x10 ♪
Blast Radius
Original Air Date on January 15, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Shado always told me
that I wouldn't die here.
But looking back,
I realized
that she never once
said that about herself.
I just hope she's
with her father now.
Here, kid.
She'd want you
to have that.
You're the one she cared for.
Slade...
Hey, Ollie,
just give him space.
I can't keep lying to him, Sara.
I need to tell him
how Shado really died.
Ivo killed Shado.
He pulled the trigger.
Because I chose to save you.
He needs to know the truth.
Wait, Ollie, he--
Get off me.
He has the Mirakuru
in his system now.
What does that
have to do with anything?
Look, the Japanese,
they experimented
on hundreds of men
working to develop Mirakuru.
And I read
the research.
The people who died?
They were
the lucky ones.
The ones who survived,
they were deformed.
Either their bones
or their minds.
They became
someone else.
You summoned me here
for a drink?
You certainly look
dressed for it.
No, I...
have a date.
What are you working on?
Something to do
with Sebastian Blood.
Aka the next mayor
of Starling City.
Well, maybe
he shouldn't be.
What does that mean?
I've just been doing
some investigating.
Blood had a connection
to the Langford
psychiatric institute.
The one that burnt down
under very
mysterious
circumstances.
Do the police suspect arson?
No.
They're saying that
it's inconclusive.
But Blood also knew
Cyrus Gold--
the man that shot
and killed four police officers.
Laurel, where are you
going with this?
I don't know.
But I do have to go.
I'm going
to be late.
So who's the lucky guy?
Sebastian Blood.
So, please,
join me in our efforts
to send Starling's
favorite son there.
To Sebastian Blood.
Sebastian for Starling.
Thank you, Oliver.
And not just for your support,
but also for your friendship.
And thank all of you
for coming.
You know, when Oliver
calls me a son of Starling City,
it feels like
the literal truth.
I was a street orphan,
and this city raised me
as one of its own.
I am the man that
I am today because
of my Starling City family.
So it's time that
I start to give back.
So thank you all
for your support.
Nice speech, Ollie.
Who knew you cared so much
about politics?
Well, I care about
the city, and...
Sebastian has become
something of a friend.
He's got a way
of doing that, apparently.
That's very cute.
Speaking of which,
how's Ray?
Handsome, brooding, usual.
Why is my boyfriend
such a topic of interest?
Well, Thea, his idol
put an arrow in him, and I just...
Wanted to make sure
there weren't any lingering issues.
Oh, my God.
Now that I think about it,
you know, he did something
completely out of character this morning.
What?
He showed up for work on time.
Thea! Oh, it's--
it's just wonderful.
Proud to my civic duty.
No, I'm the one
who's proud.
You've taken Oliver's...hobby,
and turned it into
a successful
business.
Hobby?
Oh, sweetheart.
Oliver.
Ah.
Thank you so much
for your kind words.
I'm just speaking
the truth.
Oh, forgive me,
a friend just walked in.
Hi.
Glad you could come.
Sebastian invited me.
Yes, I hear the two of you have
been spending a lot of time together.
We're just friends.
Does he know that?
Uh-oh.
What's
holding you back?
Sometimes I feel like
I don't know the real Sebastian.
He reminds me a little
of you that way.
Hmm.
Freedom.
Liberty.
Justice.
Long have the people
of this city suffered
under the shackles
of a corrupt government...
Slaves to self-interested
politicians
and their lobbyist puppeteers.
I declare war
on them all.
Anyone
in the building?
Cleaning crew
and a group of bankers
working out a late night deal.
Can you patch me
into police and fire?
I'm on it.
Diggle...
Hey, man, this is not my thing.
It's too hot.
We're falling back.
You've still got
people on the 5th floor.
It's too hot.
We're pulling back.
Help!
Gary's still back there.
Get to safety.
Give me your hand.
Thank you.
Hey.
You ok?
Where you going?
To the plane,
to get geared up.
For what?
Ivo is still
out there.
I'm going to find him,
and when I do,
I'm going to cut
pieces of him.
You can't. Ivo has a ship
full of men, of killers.
And I don't care
what you did before,
you can't take them all out.
Your only play here is to find
safe ground and wait him out.
Well, of course
you would say that.
You were working
for him.
You're probably
still working for him!
Hey, hey!
She's not.
Get out
of my way, kid.
Look, let's just
take it easy--
I said...
Get out of my way.
You ok?
Long night.
Yeah. News report said the bomber
didn't steal any money.
I think this guy
just wants to make a statement.
That went online an hour ago.
His manifesto. 300 pages
of anti-government hate.
You think this psycho's
any way connected to our
psycho in the skull mask?
This guy has
a completely separate agenda.
He's a lone wolf,
but we need
to find him before he finds
his next target.
I'd start with the bomb.
Everyone's unique.
Maybe we can get some kind
of signature on the guy.
But the bomb residue
is with the SCPD.
Fortunately we have an in
with one of the officers
at the department.
I thought you were staying in
Central City for a few more days.
I got a news alert
about the bombing.
Caught the first train
out this morning.
Good.
We need you here.
How's Barry?
Ah, he's still sleeping.
I prefer sleeping to coma,
'cause coma sounds,
you know, not fun.
I'll reach out
to detective Lance.
Hey.
Did we have a lunch today?
No.
I was just
in the neighborhood.
Thought I'd stop by.
But if this is
a bad time, I mean,
I can always come back.
Oh, no, not at all,
they're still setting up out there.
Wow.
This is pretty impressive
for a street orphan.
Are you suggesting I spread it
on a bit too thick last night?
No.
It's just...
Laurel, if there's
something on your mind,
give it voice.
I don't bite.
I promise.
You know my father's
with the department.
Yes.
He said the suspect
that he was investigating
when he and his partner
were attacked
was a man
named Cyrus Gold.
Cyrus Gold...
was a preacher
at the orphanage
where I was raised.
Cyrus was a very good
friend to me--
like an older brother.
Or even a father figure,
to be honest.
He was the first person
I said a word to,
and this was after a month
of not speaking at all.
You talk a lot about
being an orphan,
but you don't talk
about your parents.
Did you know them?
My father was
a very unhappy man.
One night he came home
soaked in whiskey.
He lost his job again,
so he broke her arm.
I tried to stop him,
but he threw me off.
And the next thing I saw
was my mother holding
my father's gun in her hand.
And I watched her shoot him.
She panicked.
Ran and was gone before
the police even arrived.
It was the last time
I saw my parents.
I'm so sorry.
I don't know...
Why Cyrus' life took
the turn that it did,
I'm sad to say.
All I know...
is that he helped
a very young,
very frightened boy
find his voice again.
Ahem. I'm sorry.
More later?
Didn't hear you come in.
Yeah, sorry, I--
I got here early.
I just want to get these crates
unpacked before lunch.
Are you ok?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Just...I haven't been
sleeping much lately.
I got a lot
on my mind.
You want to talk about it?
Talk about what?
Whatever's been going on
with you the last five weeks.
Look, I'm fine.
Ever since the Arrow
shot you,
you've been acting
really weird, Roy.
With me, with everything.
This isn't
about the Arrow.
Is it me?
Is it us?
Look, I really just want
to get through this, ok?
Ok.
Let me know if there's
anything I can do to help.
Thea.
You do help.
Every day.
And honestly, right now
you're the only thing
that's keeping me
together.
I do what I can.
How did I get
to be so lucky?
You...stole my purse.
Hmm.
Roy?!
Thea, are you ok?
Yeah.
Oh, your arm...
Um, that looks really deep.
It might need stitches.
Um, I'm going to go downstairs
and get the first aid kit, ok?
Ok.
U know, most cops,
they meet their informants
in the backseat of a cruiser
or maybe a coffee shop
or something, but...
What's with the mask?
Gift from a friend.
You got friends?
Did you bring me
what I asked for?
That's a sample of everything
the CSU collected from the blast.
There's melted glass,
multiple explosive fragments,
and trace residue,
and it looks like nitroglycerine.
Which means that we're dealing with
more than just a basement nutjob.
Someone with training.
Thank you,
Detective.
I need a favor, too.
The son of a bitch
who killed my men, my partner...
He's dead.
And whoever tipped him off,
told him we were coming,
he's doing just fine.
What do you need?
Cell phone records
for every cop in my precinct.
You think there's a leak
in the department?
I think those phone records
are the only way
to know for sure,
and your blonde friend,
she's pretty good
with computers.
I'll ask her--
DC-52 to Central,
10-80, downtown!
He's hit again.
Starling City
municipal building.
Give me a location.
I'll give you one better--
I'm checking
the surrounding cell towers.
There was a GSM spike
of 3,800 megahertz
two seconds before the blast.
That frequency's way outside
the approved frequency
for U.S. carriers.
Signal's moving.
I think he's mobile.
Give me an intersection.
Right in front
of you, 400 meters.
I see him.
Turn left on 67th.
Felicity,
I've lost him.
What?
Me, too, hold on.
Got him. Bank left
on Gerrard Street.
You're almost
right on top of him.
It's not him, Felicity.
You picked up the wrong signal.
What? I thought--
he must have scrambled the signal.
It doesn't matter.
He's gone.
What happened?
He's using cellular technology
to detonate his bombs.
Clearly, his expertise extends
to obscuring that signal.
Felicity, your expertise
was supposed to trump his.
Excuse me?
If you have something
to say to me, Oliver, say it.
People are dying. So I would like you
to pull your head
out of Central City
and get back in the game.
Sure, right after you get
yours out of your ass.
Excuse me?
All right.
Maybe we should
just take a breath here.
No, wait, I want to know,
what exactly was that crack
about Central City
meant to imply?
When the first bomb went
off, you weren't here.
And when the second bomb
went off, you sent me the wrong way.
After you didn't catch him
in the first place!
Don't blame me because
you didn't have it tonight.
I need some air.
At the risk of me getting
my head knocked off...
Playing the blame game's
not going to help us
catch this son of a bitch.
Neither is doing
things halfway.
Is that what you think's
going on here, Oliver?
You think
she was distracted?
She wasn't giving it her all?
She almost ran me
into a bus, Diggle.
What do you think?
I think you didn't
have a problem
with Felicity's performance
until she met Barry Allen.
I'm sorry.
You're not
well, Slade.
Hey...
It's the Mirakuru.
It's messing
with your head.
It's going to be dark soon.
We should make camp.
What's going on?
You ok?
Yeah, it's just,
arm still hurts when it's cold
and I lost the pain meds
that the doctor gave me.
How's yours healing up?
Ah, you know,
good days and bad.
I'll see you later.
Hey.
Pretty crazy.
Yeah. You doing all right?
I thought I could use your help,
if you have a second.
You being
at the DA's office now,
it's almost like you joined
the family business. Come on.
I'm trying to find someone
named "Maya Resik."
I searched the Internet,
the DMV records,
social security...Nothing.
Why are you looking
for a ghost?
Sebastian's paying her bills.
A woman who doesn't
seem to exist;
I find that suspicious.
Thinking that
your boyfriend's up to no good,
that's typically
more my thing than yours.
Oh, he's not exactly
my boyfriend.
Well, that makes
digging into his life
a little less fun, then.
Hey, Laurel.
If I bring you
something back,
you know I'm going
to want to know why.
Of course you are.
Over the last few days,
our resolve has been tested.
But all of you continue to prove
that the only way we keep on...
Ah, you're just in time
to see the show.
What's he doing?
Bringing the city together.
And if I'm not mistaken,
campaigning.
Tomorrow night, I am holding Starling's
first ever unity rally at City Plaza.
We are going to show the world
that the people of this great city
will not back down
to terrorists.
He's committing suicide
and he just invited
the entire city
to join him.
Sebastian's
your friend.
Can't you talk him
out of this, Oliver?
Well, that day is now.
Well, he won't
listen to me.
Sebastian Blood...
This rally tomorrow night,
you need to call it off.
The Starling City vigilante paying
a visit to wave me off.
I'm flattered.
This event, Mr. Blood,
you might as well be painting
a giant bulls eye on your chest.
This city needs
to come together.
And I need
to show them how.
You won't be able to show them
anything if you're dead.
Every night,
you risk your life
for the people
of this city.
How can you expect
me to do any less?
And what about the lives of
the people coming to your rally?
This rally is about
Starling City
standing up and declaring
with one voice
that living afraid
isn't living.
I won't send a contrary
message to people
telling them to stay home,
to stay scared.
I've made my decision.
That's the thing, alderman...
whatever happens
tomorrow night,
it's not up to you.
♪ I wake up
and she's not there ♪
Ah, Mrs. Fazekas.
The train set
for your nephew
just came in.
He's going to love it.
Oh. You are a miracle worker,
Mr. Scheffer.
How much do I owe you?
$50 even.
Forget
the sales tax.
Going to the alderman's
unity rally tomorrow night?
I wouldn't
miss it.
Gathered here despite
the rash of bombings
that have plagued the city,
some have called
Sebastian Blood's unity rally
a cynical
and dangerous PR stunt
for his mayoral
campaign.
But the crowd
continues to grow.
Tried to get him
to stand down.
He seems as stubborn as you
when it comes to fighting back.
Or everything.
Hey, is this how
it's going to be
with you two from now on?
Maybe we should just
head down to the rally.
Maybe we won't have to.
I analyzed the bomb
remnants we got from Lance.
The design's identical
to the bombs used by
an anti government
militia group called the Movement.
Lucky for us, they have a very active
and hackable message board.
One of their most prolific fans has
an IP address right here in Starling.
Tell me.
The computer's in a local souvenir shop.
The whackadoo in question goes by
the username Shrapnel.
You want back-up?
No, I need you
at the rally.
Cover our bases.
Is this all for me?
No, for me.
SCPD phone records.
Why are you going through
the department's phone records?
Um, so I checked up
on your not exactly boyfriend.
And? Did you find anything?
Yeah, it turns out
he's a hell of a guy.
Covers the expenses
of his dear aunt...
your Maya Resik.
If Sebastian has other family,
then why was he placed
in an orphanage?
Well, maybe 'cause Aunt Maya
is nuttier than a Snickers bar.
She's a patient
at St. Walker's Hospital.
It's a mental institution,
it's the kind you don't check out of.
Now, listen, you going to tell me
what this is all about?
Something about him
just seems off.
Laurel, there is
nothing sinister
about a guy
who is covering the expenses
of his only
living relative.
The truth is,
it's kind of nice.
Listen, I gotta get
to City Plaza.
Pike wants all hands
at this unity rally.
You're not going,
right?
No, I need to look
into this more.
Laurel, he seems
like a good guy
and you
deserve good.
Ok, so stop
looking for reasons
to talk yourself
out of it.
Please.
Alderman Blood,
is this not dangerous?
I'm afraid so.
Why are you gathering all these
people here to be targets?
Please, I'll get to all
of your questions later.
Boom.
You're dead.
Or will be if you
take one more step
or move
a single muscle.
And then you'll miss
the show.
Candidate Blood's
unity rally.
Already rigged with 50 pounds of
RDX high explosives.
Not unlike what's packed inside the
drywall of my store.
This city thinks Sebastian Blood
can keep them safe.
Tonight, they learn that the only
thing politicians
care about protecting
is their jobs.
Felicity.
Here.
Did you get him?
No. He said he
rigged the Plaza
with an explosive device.
Oliver,
it's crazy-town there.
That bomb could be
anywhere.
I can narrow that down.
Get me Diggle.
Go.
Shrapnel said he ringed
the perimeter with rdx.
I'm on it.
You're heading to
the Plaza, too, right?
Not yet.
I need you to pull me up
anything you can on the store.
Blue prints, permit
schematics, anything.
What's going on?
Shrapnel left behind
a surprise.
Said he packed the drywall
with explosives,
but the trigger
needs to be--
Would need to be hooked up to
some sort of power supply.
That's assuming that
the detonator's connected
to the store's electricity and not
something independent
like a car battery.
I know, not helpful.
You sure you want me
doing this?
My head might not
exactly be in the game.
Felicity!
The building was built
in the seventies.
That's good news.
The wiring in a lot
of construction back then is defective.
So if you sever
one wire,
it will blow fuses in
the entire building
and shot off power
to the bomb.
Hold tight.
I see a fuse box.
Oliver, be careful.
Oliver?
It's all right.
I'm all right.
Get to the rally.
Help Diggle.
I'm on my way.
Thea, I really don't think coming
here was a good idea.
It's gonna be fine.
Let's just go find Roy.
Please, please.
You're the ones who
deserve an ovation.
8 months ago this city
survived a devastating attack...
But we rose up.
You rose up
and banded together,
just like we are tonight.
Dig, I'm on site.
I'm on the east side.
Think I found the trigger.
And prove to the world
that we cannot be broken.
That the people
of this city
are too strong.
And that no bomb
and no earthquake
is strong enough
to tear us apart.
Oliver said that
the whole place
was ringed
with explosives.
It's in the sound
equipment.
And this is
the trigger.
Shrapnel activates it
by cellular transmission.
Listen, we don't
have to disarm it, just disable it.
I can do that.
I think.
I hope.
Listen,
you be careful.
He probably put in
a safeguard.
Tampering with it
will set off a
deadman's switch.
That's a really
depressing term.
And a little bit sexist.
Step away.
Or we all know
how this ends.
Dig!
Mom!
I'm ok.
Drop the bow.
I've got charges
planted all over Starling.
I drop this stick,
they all blow.
Did you just hear
what I said?
Yep.
Hey.
How's your mom?
She's fine.
Just a little shooken up.
You saved her.
I got lucky.
That wasn't luck.
That was impossible.
You know those stories
of mom's lifting cars to save their kids?
Things you can do
when adrenaline hits.
It was...
It was one of those.
Your arm.
There's not even
a mark.
It's...I heal fast.
It's fine.
Right.
I'm kind of tired.
It's been a long night, you know.
I gotta go.
Roy.
With you dropping
fewer bodies,
Starling City should probably
build a bigger jail.
Another night of
skull mask hunting?
Not exactly.
How's your shoulder?
Oh, just a
through-and-through.
Walk in the park.
Still, Diggle, you should
go home and get some rest.
I'm sorry.
Are you apologizing to me
or were you talking
to your quiver?
I didn't snap at my quiver.
You kind of
more than snapped
I know.
And I'm sorry.
I understand that this Mirakuru
thing has you freaked
and I have been
in Central City a lot.
Felicity,
it's not that.
When you are there,
well, it just made me realize
how much I need you here.
In the beg...beginning,
I was just gonna--
I was gonna do all of this by myself.
And now with you and Diggle...
I rely on you.
Does that mean
I have a shot
at employee
of the month?
No.
Because you're not
my employee.
You're my partner.
Barry's gonna wake up.
And when he does,
you will be there.
I finally have a guy who's
interested in me
and he's struck
by lightning,
ends up in a coma.
Typical.
Well, maybe he's
dreaming about you.
You know, actually there's
conflicting cases
about whether coma
patients can in fact dream normally
or they're more like
hallucinating.
Thank you.
Sara.
Sara, I know you're listening.
Answer me.
This is very simple,
Sara.
I know you and your new friends
have the Mirakuru.
You know I will lay
waste to this entire island to get it.
Get Slade.
But it doesn't have to
be that way.
All I want
is the serum.
In exchange, I'll promise you
and your friends
safe passage
off this island, I promise.
Within 10 days,
you and your new friends
could be making port
in Shanghai.
The alternative is
I send my men
into the jungle to take
the serum from you.
They'll be under orders
not to kill any of you.
Instead, you'll remain
alive enough
for me to indulge
my scientific curiosity.
Think about it, Sara.
He's gone.
What?
Slade's gone and he took the
Mirakuru with him.
You can ask all
the questions you want,
but I wouldn't count on
getting anything back.
She probably won't even
know you're there.
I'll be down the hall
if you need anything.
Maya?
I'm here to talk
about your nephew.
Un buen Chico.
Maya, my name's
Laurel Lance.
Maya?
I'm here to talk
about your nephew.
Un buen Chico,
un Chico listo,
un Chico hermoso.
Maya?
Maya, que Chico?
Que Chico? Sebastian?
Sebastian.
Yes, yes.
Sebastian Blood.
There will always be
those who seek to harm us,
but it will not
weaken us.
It will only make us
stronger.
Well done, alderman.
Thanks to you.
Still a very big risk
to take.
Tonight we both
stood up for Starling City.
You and me, we can
save this city,
if we work together.
Maya, can you talk to me
about Sebastian?
It's ok.
You can trust me.
Ok?
Sebastian is my friend.
Sebastian is the devil.
He the one
who put me here.
He made everybody
think I'm insane.
But why would he do that?
He killed his father.
And I was there.
I saw it.
Oh, my God.
Sebastian isn't your nephew,
he's your son.
Don't trust a word
he says.
You can't trust
Sebastian Blood.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man