Previously, on "Arrow"...
Tonight
we rise up as one
and take back
this city.
Slade's got 20 guys
just like him,
and we have
no way to stop him.
Mirakuru. We're going
to use it to make a cure.
Slade promised me city
hall, and he delivered.
I understand he made you
a promise, too.
There is still
one person who has to die.
What's happening
is bigger than you and the city.
There's so many of them!
We can't fight!
We're not going to.
Laurel.
Laurel?
Laurel!
You killed me...
Let me return
the favor.
You can't kill me.
You're not invincible.
Close enough.
Laurel!
Oliver!
Are you ok?
The tunnel collapsed.
I'm trapped.
I just...
It's getting really...
Hard to breathe!
You are going
to be ok.
I need you to tell me
everything that you see.
Rocks, and water, and--
and your bow.
You see my quiver?!
Wait! Yeah, yes,
I have it! I have it.
How many arrows
are in it?
There's a bunch of them.
There should be one
with a metallic head
that's bigger than
the rest of them.
Do you see it?
Why do I need this?
Because it's
an explosive arrow.
And you're going
to fire it.
Do you want to save me
some time and energy?
Then tell me where I can
find Felicity Smoak.
I have been aching
to put a bullet in her
smug little face
ever since the day--
Oh, I really thought
the airbags were going to go off.
Thanks for the help.
Any word from Oliver?
Dig...
What do you think,
hit her again?
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
Get out! Get out!
Get out!
Reports are coming in
from all over the city.
Starling General
is preparing for possible casualties.
Power is out south
of Harbor Boulevard.
Governor. Governor.
Sending in the National
Guard at this point
will only cause
mass hysteria.
Trust me
and my police force.
We have this situation
under control.
Mr. Mayor.
D.A. Spencer.
What is going on?
There are men in masks
tearing through the city.
Yes, I know. And we're doing
everything we can.
The SCPD have
already mobilized.
No, the police
force, they're not
equipped
to handle this.
You don't
understand.
I have never seen anything
like this before.
These--the men
in masks,
it--it's like
they're not human.
Not human?
Kate, do you even hear yourself?
Look, I know you're scared,
but you need to pull
yourself together.
Starling City needs both of us
thinking clearly right now.
How are you so calm?
Because I know we're going
to get through this.
And when we do, Starling City will be
stronger and better for it.
Can I count on you?
I need you with me on this.
Mm-hmm.
Good.
Then let's save
the city together.
Are you far enough away from the debris
to avoid the blast?
I don't know!
What if I can't shoot that far?
The bow's a hybrid
compound, Laurel.
It's going to do
all the work for you.
All I need you to do...
Just aim at the middle
of the debris.
Take a deep breath.
Center your feet.
Left hand on the bow.
Place the arrow
on the drawstring.
Ok, ok, ok, ok, ok.
All right,
I want you to pull back
on the drawstring.
And keep
your left arm straight.
Ok?
You count to three
and then you just
let go.
You can do this.
1, 2...
3!
Nice shot.
Diggle, you there?
Yeah, Oliver, we hear you.
We're coming up.
Sara's gone.
Slade must have taken her.
Chert.
What's that?
It's sonar.
I was monitoring the "Amazo."
She's moving.
We have one torpedo
left, right?
Da.
Could you rig it to fire
in a straight line?
I'm discovering capacity
to do many things
I never thought
I would do.
I need you
to get the sub close enough
to the freighter
so that I can swim over.
Well, then, what do you need
torpedo for?
If Sara and I
aren't back in an hour...
You're going to sink
the "Amazo."
Freeze!
Who are you?
I'm her father.
♪ Arrow 2x22 ♪
Streets of Fire
Original Air Date on May 7, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Dad!
Laurel, thank God.
Are you safe?
I am now.
I'm with the Arrow.
Well, that's--
that's good.
Now listen, something tells me
he's got work to do.
I want you off the streets.
Yeah.
Laurel, please, keep low, keep out
of sight, all right?
Dad, I know, you don't have
to worry...about me.
- You ok?
- Yeah.
You?
Isabel attacked Dig so I hit her
with the van.
Slade's army.
He has at least
50 men out there,
all like him.
They're everywhere.
We need
to stop them.
We might have a way.
S.T.A.R. Labs called.
They have a cure.
There's a courier en route.
Where is it?
Hello?
Hey, it's Felicity Smoak.
Where are you?
Fourth street, I think. I don't
know what happened.
A guy in a hockey mask came out
of nowhere and attacked my truck.
Please help me.
Stay where you are.
I can't move
even if I wanted to.
I think my leg's broken.
You should go.
Laurel, I'm not leaving you out here
in the middle of this.
The precinct,
it's in the other direction.
I'll be fine.
No.
I don't need you right now.
Everyone else does.
So go.
Go save the city.
Hey!
You still there?
Yeah, I'm here.
I pinged your phone.
On our way.
Please hurry.
Find him.
In the last five minutes,
SCPD has had over 200 reports
of masked men
attacking the city.
Should have gone with Laurel
and made sure she got to the precinct.
She'll be with her father,
she'll be fine.
She will, Oliver.
All right.
We are 10 meters away
from the freighter.
But still,
this is sumassed shitty crazy.
Crazy. You cannot
even be certain that Wilson has her.
You're a good man, Anatoly.
If this is good-bye, be safe.
I will see you soon.
You and Sara.
I meant what I said.
If we're not back
in an hour,
you sink the freighter
and get yourself home.
I think maybe
I prefer Bahamas.
Oliver.
I don't know if we will see
each other again.
But know that you have made
friend for life.
If there is anything you need,
it does not matter what...
You have only to ask.
Prochnost,
my friend.
Proch--prochnost.
Prochnost--proch--
I also teach you to speak Russian.
Listen up. We're going
to establish a perimeter
with check-points
at 5th and Adams,
2nd and Kingsley. We got to create
a safe zone, you hear me?
Who the hell
are these guys?
These guys are the enemy.
They're attacking
innocents at random,
creating mayhem
and chaos.
We need
to put them down.
Lieutenant--
now!
Listen to me, these guys,
have you seen them?
Huh? You seen these guys?
They do not go down!
We got to call in
the National Guard.
That's a call
for the mayor.
And he hasn't
made that yet.
And he won't.
Mayor Blood
let this happen.
What?
Trust me.
Blood's behind this.
Look, even
if I believe you...
I don't have
that kind of authority.
Well, in an emergency,
the chief of police does,
so get him on the line.
Chief's dead.
Well, then...
There's only
one more guy we can call.
You're not going
to like it.
The Vigilante.
The Arrow.
Lieutenant,
I know he's
breaking the law.
But what we're up against,
it's not about the law.
It's about survival.
We got masks tearing
our city to pieces,
and we're going to need
a mask to stop 'em.
Make the call.
Ok, let's do it.
One more thing--
you know more about what's going
on over everyone else I got.
I need you making decisions
and leading these men...
Detective.
Follow me. I can
get you to safety.
Sara...
We lost contact
with our reporter on the streets,
but we have over two dozen confirmed
sightings of masked men
attacking numerous
municipal locations.
Officials are asking
that you stay indoors...
Stop!
No, no, no!
Enough!
This isn't part of the plan!
Sebastian?!
I am mayor of Starling City,
and I order you to let her go.
I don't take
orders from you.
No...
Any word
from Thea? Is she safe?
She decided
to leave Starling
before the attacks started.
Just under two miles
to the bridge. And the courier.
It's for you.
What is it, Detective?
How can we help you?
We?
The Starling City
police force
is standing with you
on this one.
We need help
containing the soldiers.
We're working something
and it may stop them
but we need more time.
We can do that. Whatever you're
doing, good luck.
For all our sakes.
This is the only street
that feeds into the bridge.
Floor it!
Hold on!
Dig?
Diggle!
Yeah, yeah.
Is she breathing?
Felicity!
Yeah, yeah.
Then we have
to get out of here.
Yeah, I'm on it.
Thea!
I'm not here to hurt you.
Why should I
believe you?
You're
a murderer!
Terrorist,
and psychopath!
I don't expect you
to understand what I've done.
Not now.
Not without more time
to explain.
How are you
even alive?
Why are here?
I heard what happened
to your mother.
I needed to make sure
you were all right.
I needed to see my daughter.
I am not
your daughter!
You're nothing to me!
And I want nothing
from you.
Do you understand?
Yes. But right now,
you need my help.
My protection.
You have no idea, Thea,
how dangerous it is out there.
The city is falling. At least let me
take you to safety.
They say Nero sang
as he watched
Rome burn.
Now I understand why.
If only Shado were here
to witness this.
Who's Shado?
What the hell is going on?
Once of your juiced-up jack boots
just killed my entire office staff,
and snapped
the district attorney's neck!
And?
And.
And I never agreed to this!
You were supposed
to call off your dogs.
That was your plan,
Mr. Blood, not mine.
We had a deal.
And do you feel that
I've not lived up to my end of it?
Those are innocent people.
Dying out there.
You do not need to kill them.
Yes, I do!
I made a promise
to someone once,
and I will uphold it.
So this really is
all about you
just trying to hurt
Oliver Queen.
I vowed to him
that I would
take away everything
and everyone he loves.
And he loves this city.
But this city...
It's mine, too.
Not anymore.
As of tomorrow night,
it'll be nothing but
rubble, ash, and death.
A land only good
for one thing.
Graves.
Oh, my God.
Sara...
Where have you been?
Doesn't matter.
Why did you come back?
I don't know.
There isn't anything
here for me.
Your family's here.
You don't know,
Laurel, about me.
About who I am
and who I've become.
I know you're a hero.
I'm not a hero...
Laurel.
I am the furthest
thing from it.
I am "Ta-er Sah-fer."
That was my new name.
Because the woman
that I was...
The girl that I was,
was gone.
I'm not going to pretend
that I've been through
anything that you have.
One thing that I've learned
in the past year
is that these things...
They don't break us.
They make us who we are.
And what I am...
is irredeemable.
What was that word
you said before?
Ta-er Sah-fer.
What does that mean?
It means
"The Canary."
If you're so far gone
and so irredeemable...
Then why would they know you
by such a beautiful name?
Ollie! Ollie!
Ollie, Ollie, Ollie!
Thank God!
Ollie, Ollie...
Come with me.
All right,
come with me.
The sub is right
alongside the freighter.
You just need
to swim, ok?
Ok.
Ok, what
are you doing?
I can't leave yet.
Ollie, come on.
The cure.
No!
I can't--I can't
leave Slade behind.
I'm not just going to--
I'm not just going to write him off.
We injected him
with the Mirakuru.
But it was me--
Ollie.
I chose you over Shado.
I--I just--I just
want to go home.
I just want to see
my family, Ollie.
Come on, please!
I need to do this.
I need to save my friend.
I need to at least try.
Get to the sub.
Get safe.
Not without you.
Sara...
Come on.
It's Dad.
Hello?
Laurel, baby,
where are you?
55th and Alfred--
there were a few roadblocks.
But you're ok?
Yeah. Sara's with me.
Right. Ok. Listen,
stay there, both of you.
I'm on my way.
I can walk.
Where is he?
The cell phone GPS says he should
be within a 500-foot radius.
I'll call him.
Hey, where are you?
We're here, where are you?
Honk your horn.
Cool. Hold on.
Wait! I can see your feet.
You're standing
right outside my car.
That's not us.
Oh, no!
It's gone.
The situation has intensified
as officials struggle
to contain this historic assault
gripping our city.
Mr. Wilson. Is this
what you're looking for?
Yes, it is.
I just got off the phone
with Cisco at S.T.A.R. Labs...
The cure they sent us
was all they had.
And they used all the Mirakuru
that we gave them,
so they can't make more.
We can't stop Slade's
men without the cure.
We'll find
another way.
There is no other way!
Diggle, the foundry's
been compromised
and we need to get
Roy out of there.
I'm on it.
I didn't
know, Felicity.
Five years ago, I was
a completely different person.
And I had...
No idea that something like
this was even...
Possible. I couldn't
have imagined.
When you and Diggle
brought me back to Starling City,
I made a vow to myself
that I would never let anything
like the Undertaking
happen again.
What's happening now
is not your fault.
Yes, it is.
I have failed
this city.
Yao Fei.
Shado.
Tommy.
My father,
my mother.
All that I have
ever wanted to do
is honor those people.
You honor the dead by fighting.
And you are not done fighting!
Malcolm Merlyn,
the Count,
the Clock King,
the Triad--everyone who is
trying to hurt this city,
you stopped them.
And you will stop Slade.
I don't know how.
Neither do I.
But I do know
two things.
You are not alone.
And I believe in you.
Where's Dad?
He should be here by now.
You should get
to a better vantage point.
Somebody help!
Please, help!
Please!
Stay here.
Someone help!
Please help!
Please!
My daughter is still inside,
I couldn't get to her!
Don't, it's too dangerous!
Laurel!
Dad!
Are you hurt?
No, I'm fine.
I'm ok.
My daughter's still inside,
I couldn't get to her!
Dad!
Delta Charlie 52
to Central, copy!
Delta Charlie 52 to Central,
please copy me, now!
Delta Charlie 52 to Central--
Dad.
My baby, my baby!
Oh, my baby.
Who was that?
That's the Canary.
Thea, please,
come with me.
I don't want
anything to do with you.
to even see you!
Stay behind me.
You're out of arrows.
You're not!
Oliver...
This is your phone.
What do you want?
Same thing you do, Oliver.
To save this city
before it's too late.
It's already too late.
You were right
about Slade Wilson.
I should have
listened to you.
But I'm here now
and I can help you.
Why should I trust you?
Because, Oliver...
I have
the Mirakuru cure.
How much venom
do we have to keep him under?
Two hours, maybe.
Let's go.
Hey.
I need you
to stay with Roy.
Ok.
Oliver, John--
um, maybe
this is obvious,
but are we sure
this isn't a trap?
No.
I'm just saying, if you guys don't
come back alive,
I'm going to be
really pissed.
As a young boy, I was
plagued by nightmares.
Every night, I would
wake up in a cold sweat,
frightened and alone.
It was my father's face
that haunted me.
And this is how
I saw him.
The embodiment
of desperation and despair.
I made this mask
to conquer my fears.
And remind myself
why I fight,
every day,
to give this city's
most desperate a chance.
All I ever wanted
to do was help people, Oliver.
Then help me
believe.
Where is the cure?
Slade Wilson will not rest
until he honors the promise
that he made you.
I won't be so easy to kill once
we level the playing field.
He's not interested
in killing you.
Not until he's taken away
everything
and everyone you love.
After he murdered
my mother,
he said one more
person had to die.
Whoever you love the most.
I hope you can
beat him with this.
For all our sakes.
And when this is over,
I promise you...
I will do everything
in my power to rebuild
Starling City.
And I won't just
make it what it was.
I will make it better.
Like I always planned.
You really think...
After everything
that's happened,
after what you've done,
that they'll still
let you be mayor?
Why not?
No one knows that
I've done anything
except try
to save this city.
And if you tell anyone
about my mask,
I will tell them about yours.
Do what you have to,
Sebastian.
I got to get back to it.
Hey.
Are you guys ok?
Yeah.
Are you ok?
You wouldn't believe it--
a blonde in a mask
ran out of a burning
building with a kid in her arms.
It was the bravest thing
I've ever seen.
That woman's a hero.
You gave it to him,
didn't you?
I did what I thought
was necessary.
Don't worry,
I'll tell Slade.
Does he still have the cure?
No.
Slade, you betrayed--
Good-bye,
Mr. Blood.
I loved this city.
Why does every secret formula
have to be a color?
Whatever happened to good,
old-fashioned clear?
All right, so if we inject one
of Slade's soldiers with this...
According
to S.T.A.R. Labs,
it will counteract
the effects.
Assuming they got
the recipe right.
We need to test it.
We can't.
Treat Roy like
some kind of lab rat?
Felicity...
What if it doesn't work?
What if it kills him?
What if he wakes up
and kills us?
We need to know.
One way or the other.
Go lock
the other door.
Ok.
Sara, where does Ivo
keep his safe?
It's, uh,
by his books.
Oliver...
What are you
looking for, kid?
This?
A whole area
of the country...
Detective Lance.
Yeah?
What's going on?
What is it?
You're watching live footage
of an army convoy
arriving on the outskirts
of the city to restore order.
Looks like the cavalry's
here, finally.
Maybe.
What do you mean?
Well, they're taking up positions in
the bridges and tunnels.
Well, those are
the only ways into the city.
Yeah,
and the only ways out.
A buddy of mine
in military intelligence
once told me the army
isn't always the army.
But it's clearly
the military.
The trucks,
the uniforms.
Except the nearest army base
is at Monument Point,
which is 300 miles from here.
So how could they mobilize
to Starling City so fast?
Ok. So if that
isn't the army,
who the hell are they?
I'm sorry.
I can't.
It's Lance. Detective.
Are you near him?
Yes.
Are you near a TV?
Turn it on.
You're watching
live footage of an army convoy
arriving on the outskirts
of the city to restore order.
How did you
get this number?
Amanda.
What are you doing?
I'm not sure what you mean.
Amanda, the troops taking up position
at the city's exits--
they're not army,
they're A.R.G.U.S.
Those are your men.
So you tell me what you're up to.
Amanda!
Slade's followers
are a clear
and present danger.
I cannot allow them
to escape the city.
They need to be contained...
By any means necessary.
You can't.
They're a drone
en route
carrying six
GBU/43-B bombs,
enough fire power
to level the city.
There are over half
a million people in this city.
576,000.
None of whom
deserve to die.
But I have to think
about the people in every city.
You once told me that Mirakuru
made a man virtually unstoppable.
What could happen
to this country,
this world,
if I don't end this
here and now?
Listen to me.
I have the cure.
I can stop Slade
and his men.
I can't take the chance
you'll fail, Oliver.
Amanda, I just
need more time.
I'm sorry.
You have until dawn.
And then Starling City
is a crater.
If you're going
to use that,
you'll want to click
the safety off.
I'll shoot you.
I will!
I can see it
in your eyes.
My eyes.
They're just
like mine.
Both of them filled
with pain and anger,
because those we loved were
ripped from us.
I lost my name,
my wife...
Tommy.
Shut up!
You're all I have
left in this world,
and you've lost
everything, too.
Thea.
But you still
have a father.
You still have--
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man