My name is Oliver Queen.
After five years
on a hellish island,
I have come home
with only one goal--
to save my city.
But to do so, I can't be
the killer I once was.
To honor my friend's memory,
I must be someone else.
I must be
something else.
Previously on "Arrow"...
Ivo killed Shado.
Because I chose to save you.
The man who killed Shado
is still out there.
Not for long. Because we're going
to take the freighter.
Merlyn is
Thea's father.
But I thought you deserved
to tell Oliver yourself.
I'm not going
to tell my son anything.
Thea can never
find out about Merlyn.
As of right now,
we have no relationship.
You and I are done.
Sweetheart, you ok?
Every single thing
that's gone wrong
in our lives is your fault.
Now get out.
I'm sorry.
I said, get out!
In six seconds,
lobby security will
undergo a shift change.
When that happens,
make for the elevator bay.
Copy.
Now, remember
what I told you--
timing
is everything.
Maintain a pace
of 1.3 meters
per second.
Six seconds to target.
5, 4...
Now is the time,
gentlemen.
It's a fingerprint reader.
I can't crack it.
I can.
You have 5.3 seconds to get
down the east stairwell.
Stop. Stop!
What the hell are we doing?
We got what we came for.
He said to wait.
Out in the open?
Forget this.
Don't do it.
Don't do it!
Ahh!
Security clocked us!
Ughh!
SCPD? You've got to send
some officers here.
Up there, third floor.
Third floor!
Ta ta ta ta!
They've alerted
the SCPD.
Exit the east lobby
in 22 seconds.
SCPD!
Put your weapons down!
Walczak!
Delta Charlie 52 to search,
I need back-up, downtown!
Power to the people.
♪ Arrow 2x14 ♪
Time of Death
Original Air Date on February 26, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Dig!
Sara, I'm so sorry.
It's ok, I'm fine.
Let me see.
She's bleeding,
but it's not deep.
Good, I can't take
any more scars.
Speaking of...
Mortar round?
Yeah, IED, the Paktika province
in Afghanistan.
Good eye.
I know my wounds.
Grenade. Algiers.
I've never
been hit by a grenade.
All those scars, you've never been
hit by a grenade?
Arrow, knife, knife.
A lot of bullets,
no grenades.
I've got myself
a new bullet.
Nine millimeter,
right there.
.38. I'm mostly swords,
and a spear.
I have a scar.
It's in my mouth.
I had my wisdom teeth
removed when I was 16.
Three stitches.
They were really badly impacted.
You're still cute.
We should get going.
You don't want to be late
for your own
welcome home party.
You didn't have
to throw me a party, Ollie.
Sara, when you come back
from the dead, you get a party.
It's a Queen family tradition.
I don't know how well
that's going to work
with the Lance family
tradition
of holding grudges
forever.
She'll come around.
Maybe.
And maybe we should
keep what's going on
between you and me
between us.
For Laurel's sake.
I get that.
I survived Lian Yu
and Nanda Parbat,
I guess I can handle
a cocktail party.
Don't be so sure.
We're never
going to make it.
Ivo has eight guards
on deck at all times, all armed.
The second they see us,
we're dead.
Assuming we can deal
with Ivo's defenses.
How are we going to get
close enough to board the ship?
Maybe we build
a raft.
It'll take us weeks
to find the timber.
We don't have weeks.
I've been on this island
for 264 days.
All I have is weeks.
Shut up.
You don't have
to stick up for me, Ollie.
What? No, both
of you shut up.
Listen.
Do you hear that?
Hey!
- Hey, down here!
- Help!
You left us sitting in front
of the security camera.
Guards could
have killed us.
Are you listening?
If you had simply waited
for five more seconds, like you were told,
no one would have died.
Sorry. I wasn't going to bet
ten to twenty up in Iron Heights
on your skills
with a stopwatch.
"The strongest of all warriors
are these two--
time and patience."
What?
It's from "War and Peace."
1,440 pages.
It takes a while,
but it's worth a read.
Tolstoy knew that patience
was the epitome of strength.
It takes fortitude
to stand still.
Just as it is a sign
of weakness or cowardice
to move when you should not!
Look.
We did the job.
You owe me.
The dead are owed nothing.
Ah, come in.
Come in, come in.
Welcome home, Sara.
I'm so happy you're here.
Come on.
Oh, Sara, this is Sin.
Wait, do you two
know each other?
Uh, no.
We don't.
Right. Uh...
I love when people
come back from the dead.
You know.
Juices my zombie fetish.
- Hmm.
- Ahh.
Um, Roy.
Sara.
Come on.
Sorry.
Laurel, it's Ollie.
I hope you're coming to the party.
I heard that you maybe were
a little mad at Sara,
and I...she's your sister,
and--and you only get one.
You know?
Bye.
Hey.
Laurel
is not coming.
Well, maybe
she just needs time.
Yeah.
Yeah, I needed
time, too.
When you got back, I...
Well, I was pretty
harsh on you.
Hey, Mr. Lance,
you--you don't have to--
Oh, I do.
When you and Sara
went off on your dad's boat,
you were just a kid,
both of you were.
And whether
she came back, or...
I was out of line.
You're not
a killer, Oliver.
Yeah, come on, yeah.
I'm so happy for you, Dinah.
Those five years
that Oliver was gone,
was...like a piece of me
was missing.
I know just
what you mean.
Oh, excuse me.
Of course.
I didn't think you'd be here.
This is my house.
And if you don't want to pretend
to be mother and son,
then don't throw
parties in my home.
Mom?
Is everything ok
with you and Ollie?
Yes, of course.
Hey.
You know, I still can't
quite believe it.
I never really
thought Sara
would come back
to us, Quentin.
Yeah, I know.
Excuse me. Lance.
I'll be right there.
It's work.
There's a homicide
in the Glades, and I--
I better go.
Mm-hmm.
I'm on my way.
How did
you know I was calling?
Because Detective Lance
just got the same call.
What, you guys just
show up to every crime scene now?
I saw you leave.
CSU just pulled this out of a skel
I know named Eddie Walczak.
I've never seen
a knife life this.
It's not a knife,
it's a minute hand.
Like from a clock.
I popped Walczak for b&e
a few years back.
This morning, he and an
accomplice were involved
in a robbery homicide.
What'd they steal?
Some high-tech gizmo.
Kord rep called it
a, um, skeleton key.
What? You know what it is?
It was intended as a military tool
to aid in code breaking
on foreign
intelligence targets.
Felicity Smoak works
at Queen Consolidated
and she said they were working on
something similar...
But Oliver Queen
shut it down once he realized
what it could be used for.
What?
It could be modified
to open a bank vault.
Any bank vault.
Ok, listen--
Walczak's small-time
on a good day.
I mean, I doubt he'd even know how
to use this thing,
let alone break into
a place like Kord and steal it on his own.
Walczak was
just the muscle.
We need to find
the brain.
Plant your feet.
Strong foundation.
Equals stronger punch.
Nice.
If this is for self defense,
I'd recommend Wing Chun.
It uses your opponent's
strength against him.
So it's ideal
for smaller people...
Like us.
You seem like you can
take care of yourself just fine.
Are you ok?
Where are we
with the skeleton key?
And what...
are you wearing?
I just thought I'd...
I'm cross referencing
Walczak's known associates
with decryption experts
on the NSA watch list,
but it's taking some time.
Which we don't have.
Ok, the key is not
just a code breaker.
In the wrong hands,
it's a weapon.
Whoever killed Walczak,
in addition to finding
creepy uses for clock parts,
is very good
at covering his tracks.
Lucky for us.
Uncovering tracks
is what
you're very good at.
Right.
Of course.
Ohh!
He's barely alive.
Do you have medical supplies
at the fuselage?
We have--we have some.
Just go.
I'll be fine.
Hey.
I'm really starting
to regret giving you a key.
I'm sorry I bailed
on the party.
Ah, I figured you wouldn't
make an appearance.
Finally, someone understands.
Well, I, uh,
I wouldn't go that far.
But I understand how
Sara keeping it a secret
that she was
still alive could hurt.
'Cause it hurt me, too.
I sense a "but"
coming in my future.
But, yes, but I need you
to move past it.
Laurel.
A family dinner.
It's a chance to reconcile.
I don't want
to reconcile with Sara.
I'm not talking
about you and Sara.
I'm talking about...
me and your mom.
What do you mean?
I don't know to
describe it.
It was like there
was, um...signals.
And feelings.
And I'm not exactly sure
what's going on,
but I figured if we were all
together as a family,
maybe it would remind her of
how happy we were.
You know?
I mean, I don't
know, maybe it...
Is it stupid?
No, it--
Go for Delta-Charlie 52.
415 in progress.
Widmeer Bank. Lieutenant
requesting all units.
Delta-Charlie 52
responding.
I got to go.
Tonight.
8:30.
Tell everyone to be here.
What?
Well, your place
is too small,
and, no offense,
it's kind of a mess, so...
Oh, sweetheart.
Ok.
I love you, sweetheart.
Device is hot.
3.2 seconds.
Extract as much money
as you can in 90 seconds.
Stop! Get out of there!
We've still got 20 seconds.
No, you don't.
Come on!
They're
already gone!
I think
I have an idea where.
The skeleton key operates
on an OFDM wireless signal.
I'm picking up
a transmission signal
in the alley next
to the bank.
But you won't be
heading there.
What was that?
He's hacked our
transmission.
My associates may be
headed to the alley,
but the 9:10 bus
from Crescent Circle
is about to collide with
the Starlight Freight Express.
Oh, my God, he's right, the 9:10's
headed for the track at Amherst.
By my calculations,
you can't be in two places at once.
He doesn't know
there's two of us.
Come on!
He's in the transit
department network!
He's--he's hacked
the signaling system.
I--I can't get
the crossing barriers down!
Those
buses have radios.
Can you break in,
wave them off?
No, he's keeping me out.
I guess it's not real until
the media comes up with a nickname.
How can I run a bar
without any bartenders?
For that matter,
how can you quit
without giving me notice?
No, one hour before opening
is not notice, Mandy.
Can I talk to you
for a second?
I'm going to go use
the little blonde's room.
Everything ok?
You tell me.
Other than the party,
I haven't seen you
at home all week.
I've been busy.
Being a CEO doesn't leave me
a lot of free time.
Yeah, looks to me a whole lot like
you're avoiding mom.
I'm not avoiding mom.
You're lucky your life
does not revolve around lying.
Thea.
Everything's fine.
You know, it's secrets that pushed
this family apart in the first place, Ollie.
Speedy, speedy. Really.
Everything's fine.
What do we know?
He hacked
into our frequency,
somehow gained
remote access,
but I upgraded
our firewall.
Now he won't be able to talk into
our comms even if he had a bazooka.
You know...
computer science-wise.
Good.
I think I have something
that might help us track him down.
I can run that
to the lab.
I spent a year on the freighter
studying genetic blood anomalies.
I kind of know my way
around a microscope.
There's some significant
cell damage
and the platelet count
is extremely low.
Felicity, can I use
your computer?
Macgregor's Syndrome.
It's a genetic defect
that creates fluid
build-up in the lungs,
which leads to oxygen deprivation
and multi system organ failure.
It's terminal.
But the syndrome may
give us a way to ID him.
People with Macgregor's
are extremely rare,
and people with Macgregor's
and a degree in computer
science are even more rare.
William Tockman.
Former encryption engineer at,
wait for it--
Kord Enterprises.
What's the point? He'll be dead before
he can spend all the money.
He's not stealing
the money for himself.
He's using it for his
family. His sister, specifically.
She's got cystic fibrosis and needs
a lung transplant.
Give me an address, please.
52 Nelson Way.
This area doesn't look
very residential.
There.
That's
Tockman's ride.
Tockman's not here.
Just some device.
I'm on it.
Whatever's in the truck
is transmitting the same OFDM signal
Tockman used at the bank.
Can you trace it?
As we speak.
It's leading...
back to our network.
Tockman's piggybacking
off my hack. It's a trap.
He--he's trying
to break into our network.
I'm not trying.
I am.
Where are you?
Are you home?
Are you safe?
Somewhere you think
you're safe...
Somewhere without windows
for anyone to creep through?
Underground, perhaps?
You think no one
can get to you?
can touch you
in the safety
of your hidey hole?
Felicity...
But I can.
How bad?
Tockman used
the skeleton key
to penetrate
our firewall.
And recode
our security.
Basically, he told our system
to commit suicide.
And it did.
Bravo, clock king.
Sara stopped Tockman's men
before they could
get away with the cash.
So Tockman is going
to be looking for another score.
Maybe we should
give him one.
Would you call Walter
and have him liquidate
500,000 shares of QC stock?
Put it in cash in my vault
at Starling National,
and ask him
to do it tonight.
If Tockman wants
to make another score...
Who better to rob than
a suddenly cash flush Oliver Queen?
And what if he doesn't
take the bait?
That's a good point.
Make it 800,000 shares.
Ok.
What can I do?
Go to your dinner.
Your family's probably
waiting for you.
Right.
Dinner at Laurel's.
This is more important.
You can't do
anything here, Sara.
Your family's
important, too.
Yeah.
Hey.
You should go.
Will you go with me?
What?
I know I've wanted us
all to get together for a while now.
It's just, now that it's
actually here, I'm nervous.
I mean, last time I saw Laurel,
it...didn't go very well,
and...
It'd be helpful to not
have to go alone.
I should probably
stay here.
What is it exactly you think
you can do here to help?
Call if you need us.
Yep.
You know, it's not
your fault, Felicity.
Really?
Which one of the rest of you
put up the security
safeguards?
Maybe if it been Sara,
we wouldn't be
in this mess.
Now, I know we haven't
talked about this,
but it must be difficult
for you seeing them together.
This isn't about them
being together.
This is about me.
Ok, Sara can analyze blood.
She can kick ass.
She can do anything.
And the one thing
I'm supposed to be good at,
I'm failing at
miserably.
And why do you even
need me now that you have her?
Because you're irreplaceable,
Felicity.
I have a lot
of work to do.
Laurel,
Sara's here.
Oh.
Hey, Mom.
Hi.
Oliver.
Well, thank you,
these are lovely.
Thank you.
Hey.
I don't remember
your last name being Lance.
Well, yeah, I certainly didn't want
to crash your family dinner,
but then...Sara and I
ran into each other,
and she mentioned it.
And I told him how dad
was making his famous
chicken cacciatore.
Actually--excuse me!
We're, uh, we're--Oliver.
Hey, Mr. Lance.
Yeah. Um, we're having
pizza. I'm sorry.
I had a little incident
in the kitchen.
I guess that's what
happens when you haven't
used an oven in six years.
Want to grab a slice?
Yeah, when I was
pitching a tower of caccitore--
a cacciatore tower, yeah.
Are you still teaching,
Mrs. Lance?
Yes, I am. Greek
and Medieval History
at Central City University.
Wow.
You could probably
give them notice.
Why would I do that?
Well, I mean, you're going to come
back to Starling, right?
No.
I'm not moving back
to starling, Quentin.
Well, Sara's back.
I have a new life
in Central City,
and, um, I have
a wonderful job.
Well, there's
jobs here.
More than a job.
Um...I have...
Someone.
Oh.
Congratulations.
You know,
it's great, Mom.
You deserve
to be happy.
- Everybody does.
- Yeah.
Ohh.
You've got to be
kidding me.
What?
You've been back
like, what, a week?
And you're not
even denying it.
It's...It's
complicated.
Of course
it is. It's you.
Laurel, please.
Dad, you are no better
than they are.
I mean, what did you think,
mom was just going
to sit around and wait
for you for six years
to bake her chicken?
Ok, Laurel, enough!
And sweep her
back off her feet?
Enough, ok?
Yeah, you know what, it is enough!
Invite yourselves out
when you're done.
My wallet.
Ok.
She's my daughter.
She's 12.
I need to talk to her.
Your radio's broken.
Her mother died.
Just after she
got out of diapers.
Cancer.
And without me...
She's not going to have anybody
to look after her.
So...
I know I don't know you.
And I know
you don't know me.
But...
Please make sure
my daughter's ok.
Please.
Hey!
You are
unbelievable!
You lecture me on how
I need to repair
my relationship
with Sara
when you're the one
who messed it up in the first place.
By screwing her!
And now you're
doing it again.
You're right.
This is all my fault.
Yeah. Yeah,
yes, it is.
And is you losing your job,
doing drugs
and being a drunk,
is that my fault?
Is that your family's fault,
or are you going
to blame Tommy for dying?
Screw you,
Oliver.
I have stood by you
through everything--
the DUI, losing your job,
and Laurel, I was concerned
about your well-being
when you were trying to get
my mother the death penalty!
Yeah, you've been a real
stand-up kind of guy.
Laurel, do you think you're the only one
that is having a hard time?!
Do you think you're the only one
with family issues?
You have--
you have no idea
what is going on
with my family right now.
But I am still standing here.
And you are still blaming
everybody but yourself.
Are you done?
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm done.
I'm done taking the blame.
And I'm done caring.
Why don't you go have a drink?
Get wasted, go...
Go to Verdant.
I'll pay for it.
I have loved you
for half my life.
But I'm done
running after you.
Have you seen Felicity?
No. Wait, why?
I went to Big Belly to get some take-out.
When I came back, she was gone.
I haven't seen her for hours.
Hey.
Tockman took the bait.
The money you had Walter deposit.
I'm reading his signal
at Starling National.
Wait...How do you
know that?
Because I'm here.
What?!
Aahh!
Ahem.
What are you doing here?
I'm tracking Tockman.
He fried our computers,
so I'm using the bank's
to trace the skeleton key's
signature.
And the jacket?
I was cold.
Hmm.
Diggle, get her out of here.
Tockman disabled
the bank's security system.
I re-abled it.
They're blocking
our way out.
I'll deal with them.
Tockman's
signal's strong.
He's here, he's close.
Find him, Felicity.
No need.
I'll tell you
exactly where I am.
I'm everywhere.
At the moment, I'm particularly focused
on the sub-level.
The gas mains,
specifically.
Oh, my God. He shut down
the gas main release.
And why is that bad?
The build-up could
cause an explosion.
It will. It'll blow up
three square blocks.
No, it won't.
Wait. Tockman
overplayed his hand.
The gas main's in the city's network,
that's where I live.
Am I supposed
to understand that?
Ohh. In trying
to blow us up,
he gave me a way
to track him down.
That I understood.
What's happening?
Look out!
You don't even know
why I'm doing this.
The money's
not for me!
I'm doing this
all for her!
Doesn't make it right.
Tempus fugit.
Time flies.
What the hell was that?
His cell phone.
I uploaded
the same virus
he used on my gear
in the foundry.
I didn't just
kill him, did I?
Just knocked him out.
We did it.
You did it.
Are you sure you don't want
to go to the hospital?
Mm-mm. You guys never
go to the hospital.
Besides, Dig gave me
some of those aspirins.
Are you spinning?
Aspirin?
Oxycodone.
I wouldn't be here
if you hadn't been
so brave. Thank you.
It was nothing.
I've always wanted to say
I've taken a bullet for someone,
and now I can.
So really I should
be thanking you.
All done.
Ohh.
Not bad, but you're still
going to have a scar.
My own scar.
Yay.
You all right?
Diggle had mentioned
that maybe you were
feeling...a little left out.
What? No.
I was just...
use to being
your girl.
I mean, not
your girl-girl.
Your girl.
I know it sounds
like the same word,
but it means something
different in my head.
Mmm.
Hey.
Hmm?
You will always
be my girl, Felicity.
Can I have another
one of those aspirins?
Hi.
Try this.
Good, huh?
It's really good.
Mm-hmm.
And what
are you doing
back here
mixing drinks?
Thea hired me.
I am the new bartender.
Uh-huh.
I bartended in college,
and, uh, well,
it's kind of hard to get a job
when international assassin
is the highlight of your résumé.
You're going
to do great.
I have to go home.
Is everything ok?
I hope so.
You can go.
I'm not here
to kill her or anything.
I remember you used
to bartend
at that skeevy bar
with the...
peanut shells
all over the floor.
Yeah, Oblivion.
Right.
I'm not here
for a drink or anything.
Then why
are you here?
Because I realized that...
that I went on that boat
with you, too.
And...
I've been slowly
drowning for all of these years.
And after every heartbreak
or set-back
or loss...
I sank deeper
into the dark water.
And so when I saw you,
so beautiful,
and so alive,
I realized that
I'm not those things.
Not anymore.
So please...
Please don't hate me, Sara.
Please.
I missed you.
Didn't think anything could
make you cry.
Guess I'm not
as tough as you thought.
So...
Why the running
mascara?
I had--
I just had a moment
with my sister.
It was a good one.
That's good.
Hey, Laurel's my big sister.
I still have room
for a little one.
Good.
I don't know what
I'd do without you.
Well, you won't have
to find out.
I'm going
to go find Roy.
Got it.
It's too late.
He's gone.
We're all going
to die here.
Just like him.
No, we're not.
I think I found our way
on to the freighter.
Parachute.
Thea!
Oliver.
What's wrong?
Is everything
all right?
Thea texted me there was
an emergency at the house.
No emergency.
I'm in the middle of a meeting
and Thea's
not even here.
Well, then why would she...
I can't believe she would do this.
Do what?
She's trying to force us to talk because
she's sensing the tension between us.
And what did you
tell her?
Nothing.
To protect her.
Not you.
Mrs. Queen.
Is everything ok?
Yes, thank you.
Uh, my son just
dropped by.
Oliver, I'd like you
to meet Slade Wilson.
It's a pleasure
to meet you...
Mr. Queen.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man