[Laughter]
[Conversations in Russian]
Taxi.
[Arrow flies]
[Man yelling]
[bolo arrow flies]
Kapiushon?
The rumors are true.
Kapiushon is back.
You cost us
a lot of money
back in Star City.
And you'll more
than make up for it
by taking over
his drug operation.
You've kept your
end of bargain.
Now you keep yours!
By the time you get
back to America,
it will be done.
No. I need
more than your word.
Show him that.
He'll know
it's from me.
Rene: Man, I can't
believe how good
this crappy hallway
looks.
Yeah, and it really
is crappy.
I mean, this paint
looks like it's been here
since the sixties.
It has.
But it must be good
to be home, right?
Yeah, to be home
and to see my baby.
You told Zoe to come straight here
after hockey practice, right?
Actually, she wanted
to skip hockey practice today.
Dinah: Welcome home!
- Baby!
- Welcome home!
Ohh! I missed you
so much.
I missed you,
too, Dad.
I'm so glad
you're back.
[Kiss]
Aw. You guys didn't
have to do all this.
Hey, you've been in
the hospital over a month.
You deserve
a hero's welcome.
We have cake, too.
Your favorite.
[Curtis and Dinah chuckle]
Is that red velvet?
I'll cut you a slice.
I love you so much.
[Chuckling]
So how are you feeling?
Better than ever,
ready to take down
Diaz anytime, anywhere.
We haven't been able
to find him or his lair
using our usual
tracking methods.
That's probably because
Diaz is controlling the entire city,
including police
and cameras.
I just hacked into a new thermal-sensing
program from the NSA,
so maybe that gets us
somewhere.
The point is, now "us"
is back to full strength.
That's right.
John: Ricardo Diaz is working with
SCPD captain Kimberly Hill,
district attorney Armand,
and a former Bratva Pakhan
named Anatoly Knyazev.
But that is just the tip
of the iceberg.
Ricardo Diaz has
members of Star City's
entire governmental
infrastructure
either bought
or compromised.
So how are we supposed
to find him?
24/7 surveillance
on all of Diaz's known locations
and subordinates
until either he or someone he is working
with makes a mistake.
You have your orders.
Everything
all right, sir?
You can drop the "sir."
A.R.G.U.S.
isn't the army.
Just checking to see how
you're acclimating.
I feel like I'm
getting my sea legs.
It might feel that way,
but it doesn't look it.
From where I'm standing,
it looks like
you've been doing this
your whole life.
At least that's what
I told the boss.
You were talking
to Lyla.
Ha ha! Talking might be
a bit of an exaggeration.
Moldavian phone lines
aren't exactly the best.
Copy that.
Got something that might
help with Diaz.
Lydia Cassamento--
gun lobbyist
who took control
of her family business.
Now she runs weapons for
the Quadrant.
The Quadrant?
High-end cartel ruled by
moneyed families
with ties to all things
black market:
Guns, cryptocurrency,
drugs, humans.
KH-11 picked up Cassamento
coming into Star City.
You think Diaz is
looking to restock his firepower.
And if she's making
the trip personally,
that means the deal she's
working on is big.
I got a tac team ready
to take her out.
No. Delay that order.
If she's bringing guns
to Diaz,
she may lead us
right to him.
What kind of wool
is this again?
Rare vicuna.
A suit like this is
worth what, 100 grand?
For a basic cut,
yes.
Hey. I don't want
the basic cut.
Leave a little room
for the guns.
And, don't forget,
the muscles
are getting bigger.
You said she'd
be here by now.
I called her 3 times.
You called me once.
Since when did you let these
guys start lying to you?
Don't tell me that
the Quadrant's money
has made you go soft.
I thought we were supposed
to meet up last night.
Well, I guess your men
are lying to you again.
I told them I would be
down by the docks.
There were some
Halcones that needed disciplining.
Good. There's somebody else
that needs a little
instruction.
The new mayor.
You mean my father?
I thought he
wasn't your father.
You know what I mean.
I need to have
a conversation with him,
lay down some of
the ground rules.
I'll talk to him.
No. I'll talk to him.
You set it up.
You do trust me,
don't you, baby?
Of course I do.
I'll make it happen.
[Conversation in Russian]
[TV shuts off]
[Tap tap tap]
[Object rolling on floor]
If I'm supposed
to be frightened,
you are wasting
your time, kapiushon.
I just want to talk.
We stopped talking
a year ago.
How you find me?
I got a tip from
a friend of yours in Russia.
I have no friends in Russia.
Your doing.
That's fixed.
Also my doing.
This is Pakhan's.
How you come to have it?
You told me that
the Bratva exiled you
because of your
friendship with me.
I owed you a debt,
I owed them a debt.
I paid it.
You can go home now,
Anatoly.
You said you were
an honorable man.
Now, I think you know
deep down
that Diaz isn't.
Help me stop him.
Well, you're right.
I was honorable man.
[Electricity crackling]
♪ Arrow 6x20 ♪
Shifting Allegiances
Original Air Date on April 26, 2018
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
[Grunts]
Handcuffs
would've been fine.
What, so you can dislocate
thumbs and escape?
[Chuckles]
Come on, Oliver.
Most of your tricks
I taught you.
I also taught you not to go into
situation alone, hmm?
I've gone back to basics,
Anatoly.
I'm working alone.
That explains why you
broke into SCPD
wearing
kapiushon outfit.
[Chuckling]
Oh, Diaz and I had
good laugh on that one.
Maybe one day we
will have bigger laugh about this.
So you two are friends now.
I thought you wanted back in
with the Bratva, Anatoly,
so I delivered that
to you.
And I thank you.
But over past year,
I see things
a little more
clearly.
I devote my whole life
to brothers.
I even become
their Pakhan.
And at first setback...
[Snaps fingers]
They cast me out.
Oh, Diaz is gonna do far
worse than cast you out.
If I betray him, yes,
but why would I do that?
[Chuckles]
Diaz...
Is going to make me
a very rich man.
Bratva took
a hundred years
to go from prison
into government.
Diaz did same thing
in months.
I'm still gonna take
him down.
Not alone, you cannot.
My mission was always
supposed to be solitary.
Put me with a team,
fill it with people
that I care about...
It splits my focus.
Is that why you think
Diaz was able to beat you?
He took over the city
while I was distracted.
If you seriously
believe that,
then you are even bigger
fool that I thought.
And that is
saying something.
Damn! It is good to be back.
I guess it's true what
they say,
there's no place
like bunker.
I bet you really missed
Curtis' bad jokes.
You know what?
I did. A little.
But I missed this baby more.
Well, good. 'Cause
you are gonna be wearing it plenty.
We're the only
vigilante team left standing.
What do you mean?
John got into a huge
fight with Oliver and joined A.R.G.U.S.
Then Oliver kicked
Felicity out of the bunker.
So now he's going solo.
Huh. So Oliver finally
drove them all away.
I can't say I'm surprised
or that I care.
Taking down Diaz was always
gonna come down to the 3 of us.
So what's the plan?
Well, we can wait
till my NSA lead pans out.
Till then, we're kind of
dead in the water.
The city's dying. We can't just sit around
here picking our noses.
No. You're
absolutely right.
And we need to go at
this some way
that does not depend
on finding Diaz,
even if that means
grasping at straws.
Look, forget grasping
at straws.
What if we
grasp at his wallet?
[Chuckles]
The best way
to get to Diaz
is to go after
his operation.
What operation?
He was really deep
into pushing Vertigo.
- Was?
- John and Oliver...
Took out his operation
3 weeks ago.
Well, then that means Diaz
has to be in the market
for a new supplier.
Or an old one.
Before Diaz went to prison,
he led the Scorpions.
That is Star City's
biggest supplier.
That feels like a leap.
It may be,
but it's all we got.
And even if it doesn't
lead to Diaz,
we still take down
a drug operation.
That's a win-win.
Dinah: Yeah,
but the problem is
with me boxed out of
the SCPD,
it's gonna be a lot
harder to get Intel on the Scorpions.
Maybe not. Diaz isn't the only person who
grew up in the Glades.
Quentin: Well, I was
pretty surprised to get your invite,
especially to this place.
You remembered what I said
about coming here with my girls, huh?
Ha ha! And the new location
got an upgrade.
Not fancy enough
for the new mayor?
It's perfect.
You ok?
I'm really sorry.
What are you talking about?
Diaz: Mr. Mayor...
I've been meaning
to congratulate you.
I thought I'd come
down here in person.
I mean...
You are the mayor
of my city.
And we have
a lot in common.
What the hell do you want?
Straight to business.
I love it.
Here's
an executive order
for a certain piece of
municipal real estate
to be sold privately.
Now, the good news,
it's a bargain.
Well, I'm not signing this.
I'm not signing
anything for you.
Diaz: I would reconsider
your position.
Really?
I bet...
She'd give you
that same advice.
I'm telling you right now,
if anything happens to her--
why would I want
to hurt Laurel? Hmm?
She's with me now.
And she is such
a smart little thing.
[Kiss]
[Exhales]
She knows how to pick
the winning side.
I hope it runs
in the family.
Let's go, baby.
Come on.
Behind that glass door is
where the Scorpions
do their business.
The problem is
it's soundproof.
Not laser-proof.
- You sure this is gonna work?
- Absolutely.
The CIA would kill to get
a laser microphone
of this capacity.
How long is this
gonna take?
Just trying to find...
A signal.
All right. Well,
let's hurry it up.
I didn't get a severance. Really
shouldn't be gambling.
Got something. Ahem.
Huge deal going
down tonight.
New buyer. He's trying
to get some product
to tide him over
for the short term.
Could be our friend.
They say when
it's going down?
No, no, no, no.
I lost the signal.
The big guy
is blocking my laser.
I'm on it.
Yo, man.
Yo, man, you think
I ain't see that?
You trying to copy
my bets, Hoss?
You trying
to ruin my odds?
What the hell are you
talking about?
Rene: Oh, ho ho!
So we lying now?
That's what we're doing?
Let me see that paper.
You're crazy.
Oh, damn. Uh, you--
you know what?
I'm sorry. I--I was wrong.
Yo, here you go, man.
That's yours.
I just get a little crazy
when I lose.
Everybody chill.
I'm leaving.
You get the location?
Got it.
Let's ruin Diaz's
next party.
Curtis: What if we're wrong
and those crates are filled with something
other than narcotics,
like lollipops or--
I don't know--puppies?
Dinah: I counted a dozen
more guys out front,
strapped up.
I'm guessing
it's not puppies.
Look, we got to get this done
before the group outside
notices we're here
and before
Diaz's crew shows.
Let's do this.
[T-sphere whirs]
[Gunshots]
Still got it.
Still humble, I see.
Curtis: Definitely
not puppies.
Or drugs.
The product the Scorpions
are moving is M4s.
You guys still think
Diaz is the buyer?
Yeah. Definitely. Nobody's
doing anything in this city
without his say-so.
[Gunfire]
Diaz's crew's a little
early. Come on.
We got more company! Who
are the guys in the suits?
[Gunfire continues]
We got to get
out of here.
Back door! Over there!
[Canary cry]
We're trapped.
Blow them all to hell.
[Fires pistol]
Let's go! Now!
The Quadrant.
You know, I heard about these guys
when I was working undercover.
I never could get
anyone to confirm their existence.
Yeah, well, they are real.
Very, very real.
We were tracking
this one, Cassamento,
hoping she would
lead us to Diaz.
Yeah, we were hoping
the Scorpions
would lead us
to Diaz, too.
Got some Intel they were planning
a huge thing tonight.
We just figured
it was drugs.
Turns out it was
an ambush.
The Quadrant wanted
the Scorpions dead.
They wanted
us dead, too.
It's a good thing you guys
showed up when you did.
You probably want a thank-you
or something, huh?
[Scoffs]
What I want
is to apologize, Rene.
My feelings on how you guys conducted
yourselves aside...
[Sighs]
Things got
really out of hand.
And I'm sorry for the part
that I played in it.
Thanks, Hoss.
Let's get back to work.
Everyone who
thinks the Quadrant showing up
when Diaz gets control of the city
is a coincidence,
raise your hands.
The muscle that they
brought in yesterday
were Diaz's guys.
The question is,
what are they doing
working
with the Quadrant?
John: A.R.G.U.S. thinks
Cassamento is planning
to move a huge shipment
of weapons into the city--
Kasnian weapons--
military grade,
much worse than what we
saw tonight.
We think Diaz may be helping
her with that operation.
I wasn't expecting
to see you here.
I wasn't expecting to see you either.
Everything all right?
Not really.
Diaz just paid me a visit.
He wants me to sign over a piece of
city property to him,
a building.
So why are you here instead
of talking to your boy?
Because I couldn't get
in touch with Oliver.
[Exhales]
Quentin: "The Quadrant."
What is that?
Just a super powerful,
monolithic,
secret organization.
No big deal.
Diaz was wearing
that ring.
So Diaz
isn't just working
with Cassamento,
he--
Joined the Quadrant.
The attack
on the Scorpions was
to take out
the competition--his.
And I'm guessing that
that city property
would be a really nice place to store
all that foreign ordnance
that Cassamento is planning
on bringing into the city.
This city building
that Diaz wants,
where is it?
My men have woken up
from tranquilizer darts.
Time to go see Diaz.
Think he'll give you
a reward?
A man can dream,
but I settle for
satisfaction.
Enjoy it while it lasts,
because, Anatoly, when you
are no longer useful,
he'll cut you loose...
Just like Cayden James.
Cayden James
made fatal mistake,
underestimating Diaz.
I do not.
I see him
for who he is.
I understand
his code.
Diaz doesn't have a code.
He doesn't have honor.
But you working
with him,
you are betraying
everything
that you've ever
believed in.
No need to be gentle
with this one.
Uh!
It's pretty quiet
around here.
You've been
quiet, too.
Should I be taking
that personally?
No, Hoss. We're good.
That apology you made--
you got fiber, John.
What's on your mind?
I can't stop
thinking about dying.
Middle of the fight,
I just froze.
PTSD Fritz-out.
I mean,
actually, it wasn't just so much about
dying as it was about--
Leaving Zoe
without a father.
Yeah, you get it.
You got a kid
younger than Zoe.
How do you deal
with it?
I don't, man. Not out here.
When I put this holster on,
I leave daddy home.
I put the walls of
compartmentalizing up hard, Rene.
You been out of the game
for a month, over a month.
It'll come back to you.
Just give it some time.
Yo, take a look at that.
[Vehicle-in-reverse signal]
Rene: If Diaz's plan is
to store the weapons,
why are they bringing
the crates to the truck?
Cassamento's not
looking to move guns into the city.
She and Diaz are using
the city to ship them out,
turning Star City into
a way station.
Curtis and Dinah, we've
seen all we need to see.
Let's regroup at
A.R.G.U.S.
[Knock on door]
You still here, Becky?
Nope.
Sorry. Not Becky.
Or Laurel, at least
not my Laurel.
She wouldn't choose
a guy like...Diaz.
You think he gives
anyone a choice?
Do you?
That's why I'm here--
to tell you that you
don't have a choice.
You have to sign this,
whatever Diaz wants you to sign--
Don't pretend like you give
a crap about me, all right?
Are you proud
of yourself, huh,
turning a father's grief
against him?
As far as I'm concerned,
you're worse than Diaz.
You have no idea
what he's capable of.
I know what you're
capable of.
You can bring walls
smashing down.
You really expect me to
believe that you are scared
of a thug like Diaz?
He is so much more
than just a thug.
And yes.
Yes, I am scared.
And you should be
scared, too.
So just sign
the damn paper.
[Heavy sigh]
Oh, come on.
I made this so easy
for you, didn't I?
I let you into my home,
set you up.
The law books, everything.
I bet you and Diaz, you
must've just loved that.
Hate me all you want.
I'm sure I deserve it.
But I need you to sign this,
or he's gonna kill you.
Now that the daughter act
is shot...
There's no need for you
to be in my home, is there?
All right. So when
I get home tonight,
please--I--I'd like you
to be gone, all right?
Please just be gone.
- Quentin--
- Please get out of here now!
Now!
John: Those Kasnian weapons
Cassamento imported
are shipping out tonight for
the eastern seaboard.
But even with A.R.G.U.S.
backing us up,
there is no way we can
stop all that ordnance.
So what's the play?
The play is we destroy it,
tag the trucks,
and let A.R.G.U.S.
attack them separately.
Curtis: If Diaz is there,
we're taking him out.
That's the plan, right?
That is
still the plan.
I won't let anyone
split us up ever again,
I promise.
Rene.
You good?
I don't think so.
That compartmentalizing
you talked about,
it's not kicking in.
Give it some time, man.
Maybe. I don't know.
But what I do know is
if I go out
there like this,
I'm no good to anyone.
Sorry, but I think
I might have to sit this one out.
Curtis: Wait.
What's happening?
Just a tough re-entry,
that's all.
The 3 of us plus
A.R.G.U.S. we'll be fine.
[Zipper closes]
I'll be gone in a minute.
Just wait.
Listen, back there
at my office, I--
I've never heard you
sound so scared.
It made me realize
you were serious.
Diaz is a monster.
You can't even imagine
what it's been like.
Ok, back on the earth
you're from,
you got a guy named
Damien Darhk,
a real
son of a bitch.
Yeah.
Well, I worked for him.
I did whatever
he wanted
to keep my Laurel safe.
And then
when I betrayed him...
He killed her.
What I'm trying
to say is
I know what
it's like to do
a bad thing
for a good reason.
You signed it.
On one condition.
You let me help you
get away from this guy.
That's not possible.
Come on.
I've known a lot
of bad men.
And they've been
filled with anger
and with hate,
but not Diaz.
He's not filled
with anger inside
because he's not
even human inside.
I watched him
burn a man alive
over a childhood
grudge.
If I cross him, what
is he gonna do to me?
Well, I'm not gonna
let him do anything to you, all right?
Yeah, you're gonna protect me
because  you're the mayor.
You're not the mayor
or anything.
Ok, listen, I'm gonna
protect you
because I refuse to let
what happened to my Laurel
happen a second time.
Ok.
So we protect
each other.
[Speaking Russian]
You say I betray myself
working with Diaz.
I think much on this.
And?
You may be right,
but I realize moment
things went wrong--
last year when I trusted
you to bring me into city.
So if I betray myself,
kapiushon,
it is because you,
you betray me first.
Diaz is here.
If Diaz and
the Quadrant ship
even one of
those crates out--
They'll be arming their
syndicates with weapons and tinder
for high-tech warfare.
Yeah, I got it.
The drone is 3 minutes out.
It won't circle long.
Ok, folks, we have
a window.
Their weapons are equipped
with stealth adaptors,
making them invisible
to ASMs.
You know what to do.
You guys provide me
cover fire,
I'll tag all the trucks
by hand
so the drones
know where to aim.
Maybe we should
paint the targets?
Olympic decathlon medalist
here. I got this.
Copy that.
Let's move out.
Cassamento: Not having
a police presence
to worry about has made
our jobs easier.
First convoy
is ready to move out.
[Whirring]
Not again. This time
take care of them, please.
[T-sphere whirs]
Hyah!
Uh!
Gah!
[Canary cry]
John: Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
[Gunshot]
Drone is en route.
Payload commencing.
5 down, 3 to go!
[Gunshot]
One left.
You guys aren't gonna make it
any easier, huh?
[T-sphere whirs]
Your friends just
blew up $12 million
in next-gen
firepower.
I don't have any friends.
[Spits]
Tickles.
You see this,
man?
Savior of
the city?
It's pathetic.
Ugh!
[Groans and spits]
I feel like you can do
better than that.
Anatoly: Stop it.
This is pointless.
You said you had
plan for him,
that you needed
him alive, no?
In Bratva,
we have ways of dealing
with conflict like this.
We fight with honor.
We don't do this.
You want me
to fight him fairly?
Life ain't fair.
Every drop of blood
you draw from prone man
is sign of weakness,
your weakness.
I'm not weak.
Let's go.
Thank you.
I not do this for you.
Let's make things
interesting.
I put you on the ground,
you leave Star City forever.
You put me on the ground,
I'll do the same.
Is that fair enough for you?
Yeah.
Diaz: Think
you're so tough
'cause you spent
5 years in hell?
I was born in it.
Come on.
Yield!
Yield or I'll break
your neck.
[Groans]
Aah!
[Oliver groaning]
[Gasping]
[Panting]
It's like I said...
[Breathing heavily]
Life ain't fair.
You...You have
failed this city,
and I'm gonna take
it back.
Diaz: Maybe he won't be
so smug when he wakes up.
Thank you.
Bandages, least I could do.
Not for the bandages,
Anatoly.
Thank you for giving me
the chance
to take out Diaz.
What makes you think
that's what I was doing?
Maybe I wanted to see
for myself.
See what?
Which one of you had honor.
Just like you wanted, no?
And you allow yourself
to be captured
so I bring you to Diaz.
You know,
I just thought
that I could count
on you to be
the man I knew.
That man was
my friend.
Hurry up with bandages.
I have plan to get you
out of here.
He wants to see him.
You know, I'd almost
forgotten how awesome it is
being a team,
working together.
It's almost like "Captain Planet"
or the Power Rangers
or whatever reference you guys
understand.
Star City Rockets.
Is that like
a sports team?
John: I got to get going.
I got a debrief
on my schedule.
Having a day job has been
a definite change.
Hey, John, um...
You ever think about
dropping the A.R.G.
And, you know, joining "us"?
Dinah: Oh, wow. I hate puns,
especially bad ones,
but he does have a point,
and we are down
one teammate.
Guys, look, I've
made a decision.
I'm gonna see it
through,
but if we need to,
it doesn't mean
we can't ever help
each other.
John: Oh, and by the way,
even if I do join you guys,
you'll still be
down a teammate.
[Knock on door]
- Yo.
- Hey. What's up?
Is that a cake? Wow.
If Zoe keeps this
up, you guys
are gonna have to open
a bakery or something.
Yeah, this is her
biology homework.
I'm letting her
sleep in.
She crashed hard
after finishing
her leftover
mitochondria.
Gummi worms. Good choice.
What are you doing
here, Hoss?
[Sighs]
I'm just checking up on you.
Seeing if there was anything
I could do to speed up
that compartmentalizing
you were talking about.
It's been
half a day, Hoss.
Ah...
Plus, you guys had
a big win without me yesterday.
It was
a s-small win, really.
Seriously, with Diaz working
with the Quadrant now,
things are only
gonna get worse.
If we're gonna have a chance
in hell of stopping him,
we're gonna need
all the help we can get.
We're gonna need you.
Look, man.
Every time I think
about going out there again,
all I can think of
is Zoe.
What's gonna happen
to her if something happens to me?
I'll be fine, Dad.
- Uh--
- Uncle Curtis and I were just
talking about...
How you both wear masks
and go and fight bad guys?
It's way obvious.
And you and Dinah talk way
louder than you think you do.
Really?! Really? Oh, yeah,
I can actually hear it.
It's pretty loud.
Sweetheart,
come here.
Sit down.
I'm sorry I didn't
tell you sooner.
I don't need to be
Wild Dog anymore.
Dad, this is my home.
And I want you
to fight for it.
You know I've been
hurt in the past year twice already.
I know. And that was scary,
but you taught me
to be brave
and face up to the things
that scare me.
Come here.
I'll be brave just
like my little girl, ok?
Ok?
[Sighs]
Now who are we planning
on whacking?
That's what I've been
thinking on.
Maybe your daddy.
Which is why
I came to see you.
Mazel tov.
This is good.
What do you care
about owning this property legally?
It's not about legality.
It's about this.
I needed to know
if I could trust the new mayor.
And what if he
didn't sign it?
What if?
We had an agreement
if I recall.
I put you
on the floor,
you leave the city.
That assumed a fair fight.
Puh-tay-toh, puh-tah-toh.
But I have a certain
pang of, uh, conscience.
I changed my mind.
You can stay
in the city...
For 25 to life.
Diaz: I'm thinking about
moving up your trial.
[Groaning]
Diaz: How's next week
for you?
[Handcuffs are locked]
Don't even think
about getting bail.
I got a lot
of friends...
At the courthouse.
- Mr. Queen?
- Mr. Queen.
Bethany Snow: A shocking
development today
as Oliver Queen's bail
was revoked.
Speculation that
the former mayor is
secretly the Green Arrow
has multiplied
in recent weeks
after his decision
to terminate two city
officials investigating him
led to his impeachment.
The trial is scheduled
to begin May 3.
Jean Loring will represent
the suspected vigilante,
but she has an uphill battle
ahead of her.
If convicted, Oliver Queen
could face
a life sentence.
His fate now rests
in Star City's justice system.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man