My name is Oliver Queen.
After 5 years in Hell,
I returned home
with only one goal--
to save my city.
Today, I fight that war
on two fronts.
By day, I lead Star City
as its mayor,
but by night,
I am someone else.
I am...Something else.
I am the Green Arrow.
Previously on "Arrow"...
Traitor! I'm taking
you to hell with--
Sorry you didn't
get to know your father.
I guess you're stuck
knowing me.
What I saw in her
is what I see here.
Sounds crazy,
but if there is,
there's--there's some way to get
through to her.
We have a massively
huge problem.
- What is it?
- The nanothermite when combined
with the explosive creates
a thermobaric weapon.
Cayden James
could do it,
and he'd probably
detonate it in a populated area.
Maximize casualties.
Your city's entire
infrastructure
is under my control--
buildings, institutions,
even people
all under my dominion.
These are innocent
people.
And you can save them
by wiring $10 million
into that offshore account
no later than 11:30 tonight
and every night.
Wire the money.
All right.
We're all set here.
Captain Hill, thank you
for stepping up
to lead the department.
I wish it was
under better circumstances.
After tonight,
they will be.
All right. Take me
through the details.
We know Cayden James
is monitoring traffic
in and out of the city--airports,
highways, ports,
but the shoreline
might be the blind spot.
Specifically, right here,
there's no satellite
flyover for about
10 minutes.
- That's our window.
- And SWAT has the perimeter,
so no one's getting
in or out without us knowing it.
Good. When do
we make contact?
Should be any minute.
Mr. Mayor, I'm
Alex Scott, A.R.G.U.S.
- Good to meet you.
- We're good to move?
Yes.
All clear on shore.
Exit, exit.
- Ugh!
- What's wrong?
No. Just some
weird feedback.
Are your comms
line of sight?
No. We're patched in.
You got to get
those things off!
Aah!
Got to get the other
divers out of the water!
♪ Arrow 6x12 ♪
All for Nothing
Original Air Date on February 1, 2018
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
$70 million.
Ahem. At this point,
we've got maybe another day or two.
What about
the federal government?
I mean, don't they have
plans for this kind of stuff?
A.R.G.U.S was
our best shot,
and Cayden James
was ready for it.
I--I think that we
are on our own.
So does that mean
I go forward
with the emergency
bomb shelters?
Yeah. We need
a contingency.
It--it won't save
everyone,
but it's a--
it's a start.
How's William
holding up?
Doing as well
as can be expected.
He's holed up at
an A.R.G.U.S. safe house
with Raisa
and a PlayStation 4.
You look like you could
use some rest.
I'll get some
if you will.
Like brother,
like sister, I guess.
Hey. Don't worry, ok?
Cayden James is not the first guy
to try to take our city hostage.
We will figure it out.
Cayden James' hold on Star City
has reached 8 days
and counting now
with all routes
in and out of the city
under James' control.
Though Mayor Queen
has urged for calm,
tensions are running high
as the threat
of the thermobaric bomb
continues to loom.
With supplies running low
and desperation growing,
many are left wondering,
how long will the city last
before it implodes?
That's a damn good
question.
You're late.
Sorry. SCPD's been dealing
with the fallout
from last night's
debacle.
I didn't know
about the A.R.G.U.S. team
until after Cayden
killed them.
You believe me,
right?
Cayden James likes to play
things close to the vest,
even with the people
he's supposedly in league with.
Which makes finding
the location
of the thermobaric
bomb very difficult.
You believe me, right,
about not knowing about
the A.R.G.U.S. divers?
I already told you
I do.
I guess what I'm
asking is
do you trust me?
Does that answer
your question?
- Sorry I'm late.
- Don't be sorry.
Just don't be late.
Vincent Sobel, meet
Dinah Drake.
Tina Boland is
my cover name.
Tina Boland?
You got quite the rep.
No idea you were a cop.
That's the idea,
isn't it?
Vince has spent
the last 8 months
in Sean Sonus'
operation.
And he is smart.
He makes sure that
no one person ever sees
enough of the whole picture.
Sounds like you could use
an extra set of hands.
And eyes and ears.
I got to tell you,
Sonus isn't just smart.
He's unpredictable.
This could go south fast.
When do we start?
Didn't know we were having
a clubhouse meeting.
Only boys allowed
today or what?
Ms. Lance is
en route.
This is less a meeting
than it is a wake
for Mr. Sheck.
He bought the farm
a week ago.
I didn't think we
were sentimental like that.
It's not
sentimental.
Surprised.
Oliver would not
kill man this way.
None of his team would.
The place wasn't
lacking for cops.
One of them probably
took him out.
What's really behind this
sudden paranoia?
Mr. Queen was obviously
able to get word
outside the cordon
we placed around the city.
To A.R.G.U.S.,
you mean?
- He seems more than capable.
- Agreed,
but it was unexpected,
I don't like surprises,
and I like even less
the feeling
that I can't trust
my comrades.
It sounds like it's
just me you don't trust.
If I didn't, you wouldn't
be drawing breath right now, Mr. Sobel.
Oh. Oh, I love your face,
but that is just not
a good face.
What's up?
Just spent the past
two hours trying
to convince
the city council
that we will get out from underneath
Cayden James' thumb.
I'm not sure even I
believe that at this point.
Hey.
You know what I'm
looking forward to
once we put
Cayden James away?
- What's that?
- Our honeymoon.
Heh.
We are going
on a honeymoon, right?
- Aruba.
- Aruba. Ooh.
Mm-hmm. Any news here?
We split the city in half
with the other team.
Divide and conquer
is not getting us any closer
to finding
Cayden James.
Our sector has been
quiet for a few hours.
"Has been" being
the operative phrase.
Ok. Facial recognition
picked up vigilante.
Despite his mask
having no face,
Cayden James' people
don't ordinarily walk around like that.
We might have
caught a break.
Let's text John
the location.
I'm headed your way.
You going somewhere?
Where's Cayden James?
You're making a mistake.
You've got
3 seconds.
- Oliver, listen.
- 1...
- I'm trying to stop Cayden.
- 2...
- I can't blow my cover.
- 3.
Hold your fire!
Don't shoot, don't shoot!
- He's a friendly!
- What?!
He's here
for a meet with us.
He's undercover
with James' group.
We were gonna tell
you guys...Eventually.
I can't believe
that you had time
to secretly put
all this together
and continue starting
our startup.
Well, being single does wonders for
your time management.
Ok. On your next date,
you are not allowed to lead with that.
How do you know
you can trust him?
He saved
my life last week.
Killed one of James' men
to do it.
And he's in love
with Dinah.
Just stating facts.
Vince is working
on locating the thermobaric bomb.
We take that out
of play,
and we got the situation
handled.
What kind of progress
are you making
locating the bomb?
Not much.
Cayden keeps the bomb
on the move constantly
and has become
especially paranoid
since I killed
one of his men.
Your stunt with A.R.G.U.S. last night
didn't help matters.
So why don't you just take us
to where Cayden and his men are hiding?
Because the second you show up,
he'll detonate the bomb.
With the amplifier
he has,
he'll take out
the city.
He's right,
and until we find out
where that bomb is,
we've got no moves.
Ok. Well, then we just--
we find out where the bomb is.
Last year, we used
a sniffer device
to pull information from Prometheus'
mother's house.
You want to use the same device
for Cayden James?
That's exactly
what I want to do.
We can gather all
his ones and zeroes.
There's got to be a scrap of data left
in there somewhere.
Then we have someone to
plant Felicity's toy for us.
Yeah.
There's just one small problem.
- Just one?
- Well, two, actually.
The sniffer needs to be
manually implanted into Cayden's server.
No. No, no.
There's no way he can do that
without Cayden
noticing, Felicity,
especially now that
he's circling the wagons.
I knew what I
signed up for.
I didn't expect this
to be easy.
- What else?
- Ok. Cayden's server is deep
within the building, so while
our comms will be working,
transmitting a data pull that large,
it requires line of sight.
Which means
you have to install the sniffer,
then wait for it to download the content
of Cayden James' server.
Making sure Cayden
doesn't see you or the sniffer.
- That would be bad, very bad.
- And then get it outside
so you can transmit
the files.
Yeah. That sounds like
more than two problems.
Sounds like a good way
of getting yourself killed.
Then it's a good thing
I heal fast.
Vince...May I speak
with you, please?
Ms. Queen, I'm telling
you there is nothing liquid,
and we have no way
of borrowing capital.
Jay, that's just not
gonna work for us,
so I need you to try
to find more money.
I might be able to pull
a few hundred thousand, but that--
That's not gonna be enough money
for Cayden James,
so I just-- I need you to try
and find some more.
Sorry. Sometimes,
he just needs to be pushed a little bit.
Quentin, what's up?
Uh, she's been
following me.
- Laurel?
- Yeah.
It--it started
a couple of days ago.
Ok. Have you
talked to her?
Not quite.
Every time I turn around,
she disappears.
What do you think
it means?
I think maybe we
made some kind of connection.
She wants to reach out,
but...she's afraid.
Does that sound
crazy?
No. Not after everything
we've seen lately. No.
- So what do we do?
- If it seems like
she's trying to
reach out to you,
then--I don't know--
maybe we just got to find
a way for you
to reach out to her.
What's on your mind?
Dinah, Curtis,
and Rene trust you.
I'm not there yet.
I want you to try
to imagine
how little
I give a damn.
You've taken a shot
at me.
Matter of fact,
you've taken a shot
at nearly everybody
in that room,
so I will be convinced
that you are not
playing us the way
that you claim
to be playing
Cayden James.
I don't have to
convince you
because you're not
stopping me from doing this.
- Are you sure?
- I am,
because you know
saving this city means
doing whatever's
necessary,
and you know that
means using me.
Did Oliver push you
to do this?
He didn't have to, D.
It's the right play.
Hey. It's gonna
be ok.
I'm not so sure. Something just
doesn't feel right,
you know, the same way
it did for you
when everything
went bad with Sonus.
That was my call, D.
Don't you wear
that guilt.
I don't want to
lose you again.
I'm so happy
to hear that,
and you won't.
Aces and queens.
Got me.
And you are
in the black barely.
- Thanks.
- Yeah. This cash inflow
coming from
San Francisco was huge,
but it wasn't
very efficient.
You know, if I knew
more, I might be able
to maximize
the revenue stream.
Sorry. I know I'm
not supposed to ask specifics.
Just we need a little more of it,
that's all I'm saying.
I'll take that
under advisement.
All right.
Well, I'm going to
go home for the night.
Good night, boys.
I'll walk
with you.
Ahem. Can't let a lady
walk home alone, hmm?
That was subtle.
What, you didn't have a neon sign?
It's fine.
No one noticed.
So what'd his
books say?
He's got a boatload
of money floating around
neither of us
have eyes on,
and seriously, Vince,
Sonus should not
see us together.
They all think I'm
just trying to get in your pants.
Hmm. Well, if only
wishing made it so.
Nice. Love what
you guys haven't done with the place. Heh.
Let's get this
over with.
We, uh, turned
your room into a home gym because--
because this extremely
awkward situation
needs to be masked
with humor.
I think what
she means to say is welcome back.
We have the inside man.
You have the tech.
That's the only reason
we're back, Hoss.
- Is Vince on site?
- Should be as of 5 minutes ago.
That is if everything
goes according to plan.
You sound
like it might not.
Vince said he doesn't have
access to the server room,
so if anyone spots him
in there, he's gonna have
a lot of explaining
to do.
We've got eyes.
- Can I talk to him?
- Yeah.
Hey, Vince. You get
any kind of bad feeling here at all,
you abort,
you hear me?
Don't worry.
I'll see you soon.
He's at the server.
The door to
the server room's locked.
You guys have
a solve for this?
Try 06141998.
- Try?
- It's his son's birthday.
If you're wrong,
he's dead.
I'm not gonna be wrong.
Phew.
Ok, Vince.
You're in the red zone.
Just let the sniffer
do its thing.
Whew. 80 terabytes of data.
You guys can get comfortable.
This is gonna take
a minute.
Mr. Sobel?
Frak.
I think we need
to talk.
All of my people
have specific domains.
I don't believe that
I.T. Is one of yours,
which means you
would not have
a proper passcode
to enter.
How much data's
been copied?
20%.
No, but Mr. Sheck did.
He was a little more
loose-lipped than you'd like.
Rest in peace.
Still doesn't explain
what exactly you're doing in here.
We got to pull him out.
- Dinah, not yet.
- Oliver!
Ok, wait.
Vince, if you want to stay alive,
repeat exactly
what I say.
You think just...
Because I can
handle a gun
doesn't mean I know
the difference
between
a trans-polymer hybrid
and a fiber optic cable.
I'm just impressed.
I wanted to know
how you maximized
the data throughput.
Sorry. I should
have asked first.
Perhaps.
I may have
underestimated you.
It seems that you have
more skill than I gave you credit for.
I keep telling people
I'm more than just a pretty face.
Keep him talking.
We're at 80%.
Funny thing is
I underestimated you, too.
- Is that right?
- When you recruited me
to help you take
this city from Oliver Queen,
I didn't think
you'd have the resolve
to do what was necessary to make
him fear you.
- I was wrong.
- Does that mean that you
also fear me,
Mr. Sobel?
I'd be a fool
not to.
Such flattery.
Are we done here?
Yeah. We're good.
Take the sniffer and leave.
After you.
It appears that
Mr. Knyazev has returned from the port.
- Join us in 5.
- Absolutely.
- You were amazing.
- Yeah, we'll engrave
your Oscar when
you're out of the building.
Phew. Heading out now.
- That's our final offer.
- Oh, please.
Your final offer is
never really final, Sean.
You got a vise
under there?
You want me to just
gently put my nuts in it for you?
So we gonna
celebrate or what?
I think she's gonna drop half
the product
and leave us with our asses
hanging out
- like she did last time.
- I'll make good on my end.
You don't need to
worry about me.
I'd take a look
at your own house first.
What the hell
are you talking about?
The Darbinyans rooted
out a mole last month,
an OCB operative.
A few fingernails later,
he got very chatty.
According to him,
you have a cop on your payroll.
Hold up.
Mr. James wants
to see you.
Huh!
Did I teach you
that move?
I taught you
that move.
All right.
Transmitting now.
It's coming through. Man,
this is the mother lode.
We're gonna need Alena
on this to help us process.
Now get your ass
back to Helix.
On my way.
We need to call
Singh,
roll this thing
up right now.
We don't even
have Sonus yet.
We've got enough.
If the Alvarez buy
falls through,
we have got nothing.
Vince, we need
Sonus in the room.
We need money
changing hands.
I know,
but what we don't know
is which one of us
is made.
Oh, baby. If Sonus
knew anything at all,
one of us would
already be dead.
We've been working
at this for months.
We're close. You know,
we're so close.
Can't pull the pin
on this now.
All right.
We'll play it
your way.
Mr. Sobel.
Sorry. I got a text
from my girlfriend.
She's at the hospital.
Thinks it's appendicitis.
Well, I'm sure the doctors are doing
everything they can.
I need you here for a rather
important assignment.
Yeah? What's that?
Rooting out
a traitor.
Cayden sure has a lot
of junk in his server
for someone who's as
type "A" as you say he is.
Well, brilliant people
are often slobs,
or so I tell myself
and my dates.
Show-off. I can't
even get a date.
- Anything yet?
- Well, if by anything, you mean
the location
of the bomb,
no, not yet.
Ok. How much longer is
this gonna take?
Yeah. How much longer
do I got to be here,
because I'm starting
to get PTSD.
- Maybe an hour.
- Hopefully, less.
I'm gonna head
back to Helix.
I should have heard
from Vince by now.
I'll go with you.
Sorry, boys.
Guess I'm just lucky.
More like pretty women
make smart men dumb.
Speak for yourself,
Declan.
Hey, Tina. Can I borrow
you for a sec?
Yeah. What's up?
I got the Alvarez buy
coming up.
I wanted your expertise
on the numbers.
Yeah. Sure. You want me
to dive in now?
Yeah. You can start
on page 12.
I noticed something
a little concerning.
Looks like your
luck is up.
You were always
the enigma, Mr. Sobel,
the vigilante willing
to ally himself
with criminals to take out
other vigilantes.
I must confess I never
totally bought into it.
Given your background
as an undercover operative,
I would have been
a fool to.
I don't strike you
as a fool, do I?
No. You are coming off
a little crazy, though.
I've done good work
for you.
I got no love for Oliver Queen.
You know that.
I don't know anything
for certain.
That's what this is for.
Unh!
I must admit
that is fascinating.
You can torture me
all you want.
You'll keep getting
the same answer.
I didn't do anything.
I admire your
tenacity,
but even a man
who's difficult to kill
cannot withstand
torture, at least not forever.
Hmm. In my country,
we do things a little--
how do you say--
dirtier.
We'll give
the two of you some privacy.
Okey-dokey.
Where shall we begin?
Ok, Thea. I'm inside.
Are you sure she's still following?
She's right
behind you. Keep moving.
All right.
Laurel.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Don't--don't go, please.
- This was a mistake.
- If you really thought that,
you wouldn't have
spent the past few nights following me.
I think you want
to talk.
There's nothing
to talk about.
Then don't. Just--
just--just listen
and watch.
You see her?
This is Laurel.
This is my Laurel.
Oh, she was
incredible.
When I look
into your eyes,
I see the girl
I raised.
I see the same
warmth, kindness,
the love,
and I see a hero.
You just need to
see it, too.
Please.
This isn't me.
This isn't--this isn't me!
- Are you ok?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
You know, I know it
sounds crazy,
but I think I just saw my daughter
in her eyes.
I saw her.
Vince didn't make it
back to Helix.
Did he reach out
to any of you?
No.
Boom goes the dynamite!
- Oh, yeah!
- Maybe not the best choice
of words considering
the circumstances.
Oh. If by circumstances
you mean locating
Cayden's bomb, then,
yes, we just did.
- Where?
- Warehouse district,
10th and Valley.
What exactly are we
walking ourselves into here?
We have no idea.
It's a surveillance dead zone.
- We can't really see a thing.
- No surprise there.
The place is
massive.
Then we need everybody.
Agreed?
- What's that?
- That's Vince.
He just activated
his comms.
The pain stops
once I have my answers.
Vince. Oh, my God.
We need to help him.
Hey. Look.
Like Vince said,
James is constantly
moving the bomb.
This might be
our only chance.
He is being tortured.
And he can handle it.
With his healing abilities,
they can't do anything
to hurt him permanently.
As far as we know,
this could be a trap.
Once the bomb
is rendered safe,
we go back in,
we get Vince.
He has already been made.
By the time we get there,
that bomb is gonna be
long gone!
- You don't know that.
- Yes, I do.
Look. We all got
him into this.
We should all
be getting him out!
- Fine. I'll do it myself.
- Dinah.
Vince would not want
you to do it this way.
Don't you dare!
You know damn well
if it was Felicity out there,
if it was Lyla, this wouldn't even
be up for debate.
Vince is my family,
and I am not letting
him die, not again.
Dinah.
You're not talking me
out of this, Curtis.
We know.
That's why we're
coming with you.
You're our family, too.
We'll save Vince.
You guys save the city.
We're not gonna be able to cover
the bomb's location
with half
the manpower.
Looks like you're gonna have to figure
out a way, Hoss.
Unh! Arr!
Agh!
How much further?
About 100 yards or so,
give or take.
That might as well
be a mile away at this rate.
Not if you draw
their fire.
Follow the T-sphere. Go!
Unh!
Looks like your
little buddy's finally found us.
Took longer
than expected.
Good for us.
Bad for him.
No sign of the bomb. You?
Nothing. This place is
too big to search,
and we are gonna
run out of time.
I've got movement,
east corridor.
Huh!
Hello, kapiushon.
No need for me to
explain choice here, yes?
I thought you were
an honorable man.
I am. Why else
I give you choice?
Find bomb or save--
Go. I'll take care
of them.
Vince?
Oh, thank God.
Smart work activating
your comms.
I didn't.
Hang on.
- Vince.
- I'll get you free.
Oh, I highly
doubt that.
Ugh.
Your ability to withstand
extreme punishment
is impressive.
But we all have
our limits.
Let's find
Mr. Sobel's.
Don't make me doubt
your loyalty, too, Ms. Lance.
No. No, please.
Please. Please.
Don't.
Hey, Tina.
You're not looking
too good,
but I got something here
that might put
a smile on your face.
- Look who we got here.
- Oh, my God.
Vinnie.
I am
begging you.
Please.
No.
Oh, my God.
- Hey!
- Dinah!
Hey!
Baby. Baby.
Baby, wake up.
Oh, babe, please.
Baby, please wake up.
- Wake up.
- He's gone, Dd.
No. Oh, my God.
No, baby, not again.
No. Oh, no.
Baby, no.
She hasn't moved
or said a word in over an hour.
After my wife
was murdered,
it took me days.
What do we do?
Nothing. I'm fine.
You're definitely
not fine.
How can we
help you, Dinah?
You already have...
By having my back.
Did they get the bomb?
Tell me.
Felicity called.
There was nothing
they could do.
Vince died for nothing.
- I'm sorry.
- We needed more numbers.
We didn't have them.
Any word
from the other team?
I wish it was
better news.
Vince?
He didn't
make it.
How is Dinah?
I'm guessing as
good as she can be.
It was a choice
between an entire city
or one man.
You made
the right call.
I know it feels
like this was all for nothing,
but it's not
entirely true.
Alena found
something.
I've been working
on the data haul from Cayden's servers.
Mm-hmm.
What'd you find?
Evidence he received
while in Corto Maltese--
video of his
son's murder.
It's Cayden's son,
Owen Post.
Guess we know why
he hates you so much.
This is fabricated.
It didn't happen.
This could not
have been you.
- You were in Hub City.
- Yeah, but Owen Post
was still murdered
supposedly
by the Green Arrow.
Wouldn't the SCPD be
all over this, the FBI?
Records in the case
were wiped clean.
Right. So Cayden
wanted me all to himself
and didn't want anyone
to get in the way.
How do we prove
that this is fake?
Well, we're working on that,
but there is something
super interesting
about this.
The digital alteration
of this is consistent
with that of the bogus
surveillance photo
of you in
the Green Arrow suit.
We thought Cayden James
leaked that image.
Whoever doctored this
leaked that photo.
To make James think
you killed his son.
Whoever planned this
knew exactly how
Cayden would react.
Which means that person
has to be close to Cayden.
If that's true,
Vince wasn't the only
traitor that Cayden has to worry about.
Hey. You know what?
Laurel--she needs to see this, right,
because the video worked,
it got through to her
a little bit,
but this is gonna--
what is it?
You all right?
I think we might have
been wrong about Laurel.
- What are you talking about?
- Felicity just called.
Uh, D-Dinah's former
partner, her--her boyfriend...
Right.
- He's dead...
- Ohh.
And, um...
Laurel killed him.
I know how badly
you want to believe in this
and believe in her, and--and seriously,
Quentin, I really do, too.
I'm so sorry.
You shouldn't
be here.
Dinah, please give
me a chance to explain.
You lost that right
when you decided
to leave Vince
on his own to die.
I'm truly sorry
about what happened to Vince
because I know what
he meant to you,
but this was his call,
and he knew what
he signed up for.
Wow. You are really
bad at apologies.
I'm not here
to apologize.
Of course you're not.
I'm here
to explain that
this wasn't
all for nothing.
Felicity's been going through the data that
Vince pulled out,
and for the first time,
Dinah, for the first time,
we have some
viable options.
Viable options?
You know, I used
to tell Vince
his way of seeking
justice wasn't viable.
I convinced him
to change
just how you
convinced me,
but you know
what, Oliver?
Vince was right.
The only way to
bring justice to this city
is with a bullet.
No, Dinah. I need you
to listen to me.
I'm going to make
sure Vince didn't die for nothing.
I'm going to kill
every last one
of them...
Starting
with Laurel.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man