Previously on "Arrow"...
This is a plan to
level all of Star City.
Felicity wouldn't do
something like this.
Maybe she had a change of heart,
tried to back out last second.
It'd explain why someone
would want her dead, right?
Last call out was to someone named...
- Blackstar.
- What's this?
Something I lifted off Byrd
before he went into custody.
It's a painting?
Looks like someone doesn't
want us to see this.
Ricardo Diaz is behind bars tonight,
thanks to the unidentified Green Arrow.
Felicity put a gun right to my face.
I don't believe you.
I made a deal with the feds.
Oliver will be a free man again.
After keeping a low profile
since his release last
week, Oliver Queen will make
his first public appearance tonight
at a gala supporting prison reform.
But will Star City welcome
back its former vigilante
with open arms?
Or has public opinion soured
against the Green Arrow
now that we know who's under that hood?
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
Aah!
Hey. It's just me.
Hey. I'm sorry about earlier.
I didn't mean to freak you out.
No. I'm just, um, getting used
to being home.
Mm. I missed that.
Having someone to zip your dress?
Well, that, and you.
And I really miss William.
Yeah. Christmas vacation feels like
it's 20 years from now.
So why aren't you dressed?
I'm gonna sit this one out.
Oh, no, no, no.
I don't think that's how this works,
especially when you're
the one being honored.
Besides, you've been spending more time
in the shadows recently
than when you were the Green Arrow.
The last time I faced
the city, I was in cuffs.
A lot of people are mad at me, Felicity.
I lied to them.
They have a right to be mad at me.
Which is exactly why this event is
so important.
They want to publicly
recognize you as a hero.
And after all the lives
you saved at Slabside,
let them see you for who you really are,
without a mask.
I mean, you're probably right.
Oh, I'm always right.
You will always be the best part of me
for the rest of my life.
You remember.
Of course I remember.
Happy anniversary.
This used to be the nicest club in town
20 years ago.
You can practically smell the money.
Yeah. Definitely not smelling that.
I can't believe Roy's
missing out on all the fun.
If he got recognized here,
we'd have big trouble.
And you're sure Blackstar's here?
The Canary network couldn't find much,
but they did learn Blackstar
likes to frequent this club.
I seriously question this
person's choice of friends.
That's why we need to
keep our heads down.
Blackstar was the last
one to talk to Felicity.
Whoever this is could have
either been helping her or...
Or they're the one who killed her.
And you were worried this
was going to be dangerous.
Hey, we're looking for
someone named Blackstar.
You know who that is?
Yeah. She's right there.
Uh!
Blackstar! Blackstar!
Blackstar! Blackstar...
Well, she seems easy to talk to.
We didn't get this treatment after we
put Diaz behind bars.
Envy is not a good look on you.
Neither is the crab cake
on your face.
This event is messed up.
Rich folk and politicians fronting
like they actually care
about prison reform.
If everybody in here
actually gave a crap,
they'd use that money to help people
in hard-up neighborhoods
who end up in the system
because they don't have anything else.
What?
You ever think about running for office?
Oliver, what's it like
to be out of prison?
How does it feel to be back home
with everyone knowing
you're the Green Arrow?
Are you gonna put on the
hood now that you're back?
My husband is very grateful
to be home with his family. Thank you.
Excuse me. Queen!
Max Fuller.
Hey, man, I know we've
had some bad history.
You, uh, had your bodyguards
kick the crap out of me
and Tommy at your club.
Right. Well, you slept with my wife.
Well, now my ex-wife.
Dude, all that is in the past, okay?
You're the freaking Green Arrow.
Well, I'm Felicity.
I am the wife of the
freaking Green Arrow.
That sounded a little
less strange in my head.
Impressed.
You see, he didn't used
to be the marriage type.
- Ah. Hmm.
- Yeah.
But, hey, people change, right?
Yes, they do.
And we are just gonna
say hi to some friends
if you'll excuse us.
Yeah, please.
Is it just me,
or is that guy the absolute worst?
Uh...
I never got to ask you.
What was your first
meal when you got back?
Double Double at Big Belly Burger.
That's what I'm talking about.
Taking a while to get
those sea legs back, huh?
Speaking of,
you thinking about
getting back out there,
trying that old suit on for size?
Shh, shh. No, no, no.
He's absolutely not
just like we don't do that anymore.
Dinah's right.
I'm very much enjoying
not being in prison.
So what now?
I don't know.
Find a different way to help the city,
way you guys did.
What about you, Felicity?
Well, I'm developing
a new security system.
Well, then I'm sure it's
the best one in town.
We're friends with her now?
It's more like frenemies.
It's a long story.
Relax. I'm just here
keeping up appearances.
D.A., remember?
Actually, we should all
really be thanking Laurel.
I mean, she is the one who did the trade
to get Oliver out of prison.
That's true.
I'm very grateful.
I know that I haven't always given you
the benefit of the doubt, so...
Well, it was really Felicity
who was willing to do
anything to stop Diaz.
She's ruthless.
Welcome.
Thank you all for
attending this evening.
I would like to introduce
this evening's honoree,
Mr. Oliver Queen.
Thank you, Mayor Pollard.
I used to believe that justice was
as simple as putting
criminals behind bars...
but then I spent some time in prison,
and I realized that the truth is
nowhere near that black and white.
The truth is that our institutions have
a long way to go
before they achieve true justice.
The attack perpetrated by
the Green Arrow this evening
is further proof why we, as a city,
cannot trust men that hide behind masks.
There is a reason why the
anti-vigilante law exists.
Thank you.
Look, I know how this looks,
but this wasn't the new Green Arrow.
He hasn't murdered anyone.
That you know of.
Has anyone actually seen
who's behind the mask?
Well, no. But whoever it is
has been helping the city.
And helped us take down Diaz.
This was cold-blooded murder.
Now, I appreciate how
all of you feel as though
the new Green Arrow is an ally,
but I would like to be sure.
And how are you gonna do that
if you're a no-go on the Arrow?
Is there a law against me consulting?
You mean an investigative
consultant, like "The Mentalist"?
I love that show.
I can't think of a
better way to investigate
a copycat Green Arrow
than with the original.
I can. With my help,
because I'm not sitting this one out.
I appreciate it, but there's
nothing left to be done tonight,
so go home.
Let my guys work the scene.
And if I need help,
I'll call you tomorrow.
This is everything Dinah's
compiled on the vigilante...
Every sighting, targets.
It's all there.
It says here the SCPD
nearly arrested him last month.
But he had an accomplice?
Uh, yeah, that... That was me.
I, uh,
I didn't want Dinah to lock him up.
Oh, I bet she really appreciated that.
She threw my ass in jail.
I'm really sad I missed that.
What else do we know?
Uh, he's definitely not
a rookie. I know that.
I mean, the guy's efficient,
disciplined, precise.
I mean, he works the bow and arrow
about as well as you do.
That takes a very
specific type of training.
Hey. Sorry I'm late.
Pollard's on the warpath.
That's okay. Forensics pull
anything from the scene?
Well, nothing we didn't already suspect.
Arrows are consistent
with the vigilante's.
Here. Take a look.
Thank you.
Well, they're both handmade.
The materials in the
arrowhead seem to match.
This would be difficult to replicate.
But not impossible, right?
The security camera footage?
Yeah, but you're not gonna find much.
The killer was off-camera.
His arrows weren't.
If this guy is as precise
with a bow and arrow
as Rene says, then he
would've had a target.
Based on the trajectory, that guy.
Oh, wait a minute. That's...
That's Clayton Ford.
He's a rich dude who
actually helped the Glades.
He funded a clinic.
This makes no sense.
The vigilante's only targeted people
who've hurt the Glades.
Ford helped it.
Then what the hell's the motive?
Sure would help
if we could ask directly.
Wait. Hang on.
You're... you're in contact?
That was one time, all right?
And count me out if we're
gonna roll up and arrest him.
I'm not talking about the SCPD.
Just us. We just need to
talk to the new Green Arrow.
You think he's innocent.
So we'll be fine.
And what if we aren't?
Then we deal with him.
You should make the call.
Hey.
Got to say, I never appreciated
how tightly you run this ship
until you were gone with the brass.
It is so good to see you
behind that desk again, Lyla.
Flatterer.
Shut the door.
What's going on?
I had my contact look into the image
that Curtis decrypted
from the Malcolm Byrd op.
The "Dante" painting.
It's being used as some sort of
highly advanced identification protocol
within terrorist circles.
Kobra, Basilisk,
the Third World Liberation Army...
They're all using the name
Dante like it's a contact.
For what? Or for who?
I don't know, but I might
know how to find out.
When I cross-referenced
the terrorist groups
with the financials that
we obtained in Geneva,
I found a common account.
- Could you trace it?
- No.
Come here. Look at this.
Five transactions in the past 7 months
between Dante and a consulting firm
called Rubrum, Silentium, and Ursa.
That's Latin for "red,"
"silent," and "bear,"
the Longbow Hunters.
Look.
You got to be kidding me.
This is definitely the place.
Then where is he?
Maybe he got held up.
Rene, stop.
What are you talking about?
There are motion detectors.
We've been made.
I said, come alone.
These are my friends.
You already met Captain Drake.
You can trust them.
We only want to talk.
I'll pass.
A piece of advice
from one Green Arrow to another:
cooperate.
Because right now,
most of the people in this city think
you're a killer.
Are you?
- Cut him off!
- On it.
Mr. Queen. Mr. Queen. Mr. Queen.
Do you know who the new Green Arrow is?
Are you helping with this investigation?
I have no comment, guys.
Hey, whoa, whoa, whoa.
What the hell is this?
You all know the precinct is off-limits.
Captain Drake, care to comment?
The SCPD does not comment
on ongoing investigations.
But I do. The vigilante didn't do it.
Okay. Can somebody please
get these guys out of here?
Not helping.
Hey. Why does the mayor
have to have all the fun?
Maybe meeting at the precinct
wasn't the best idea.
Yeah. Well, I thought the jig was up
after you were spotted last night.
Oh, and speaking of last night,
turns out we were right
about your Green Arrow clone.
He is innocent.
How do we know?
Remember our second suspected
target, Clayton Ford?
- Mm-hmm.
- My guys found him dead
across town at the same time
we were chasing the vigilante.
- We're his alibi.
- OK.
What do we know about the Ford murder?
Emerald arrow, center... chest,
same as Hutchinson.
Someone's going through a lot of trouble
to pin this on the new Green Arrow.
We really need to come up
with a better name for him.
He's making everyone,
including Pollard, look away.
The question is from what?
Well, Ford may have known.
He was trying to skip
town when he was killed.
He found him with bags
packed and ready to go,
clothes and cash.
Yeah, he knew he was the target.
What the hell is going on?
Last time I checked,
Mr. Queen and Mr. Ramirez
were not employed by the SCPD.
Well, they're just
here giving statements.
That the vigilante didn't
do it. Yeah, I heard.
You know, it's no big surprise
that the old Green Arrow would
be supporting the new one,
but I expected more
from my police captain.
You telling me how to conduct
my investigation, Ms. Mayor?
Because last I checked,
I was still in control of this precinct.
I hired you to restore the
city's faith in this department.
That means bringing that
vigilante to justice.
And if you can't do that,
I will find someone else who can.
She may be the tiniest,
most unpleasant person I've ever met.
You have to listen to her, but I don't.
What are you thinking?
It says here both victims were
members of the same society at Yale.
I know a guy. Max Fuller,
he was a member, too.
I could go see him, gather some intel.
I'll be in touch if I
learn anything, all right?
Excuse me, Ms., uh, Blackstar?
Can we talk to you?
I'm kind of busy.
Clearly.
We only need 5 minutes.
Not interested.
Like I said,
I'd love to talk.
So this whole fight club thing,
you just beat people up for what? Fun?
Stress relief.
Do you really want to
spend your 5 minutes
talking about my hobbies?
How do you know Felicity Smoak?
I don't.
Well, that's strange, because you were
the last person she called
before she was killed.
Felicity's dead?
Oh, so you do know her.
We worked together sometimes.
What kind of work was that?
The kind that's none of your business.
So, illegal.
Well, you're one to talk, Canary.
You're not as smart
as you think you are.
But you want to come
in here and judge me?
At least I'm not lying to everyone,
pretending to be some kind of hero.
At least I'm not a vigilante.
You don't know what
you're talking about, kid.
You know, you're part of
the reason Star City is
in the shape it's in right now.
Really? 'Cause I could've sworn,
the story goes, it's because of you.
Hey, just tell us why
Felicity called you.
Then we'll leave you alone.
I work as a broker.
I help people find certain items.
Felicity asked me to find her
an electrical firing circuit
and a couple transmitters.
Those are mechanisms
for triggering a bomb.
I don't know why she needed 'em.
I didn't ask.
As long as I get paid, you
can ask for whatever you want.
Sounds like you two had a lot in common.
If that's it, I have
my next fight coming up,
and I really should stretch.
Yeah. I'm done here anyway.
Word of advice.
Asking questions about Felicity Smoak
will not end well for anyone.
Five fully-stocked bars,
3 private lounges,
and the sound system is the best...
outside of Europe.
A.I. adjusts the acoustic environment
based on capacity.
Right this way here.
That's a ton of security
you got down there, Max.
It must be costing you a fortune.
Heh! Not when you pay for them
with crypto you mine yourself.
All it costs me is the little USB drive
I put it on. Scotch?
It's a 25-year.
Why not?
We can toast your new club.
Hey. Toast to your new prison-
and Green Arrow-free life.
It's really got to piss
you off, though, huh?
Seeing some lame copycat screw up
everything you sacrificed for.
I wanted to speak with you about that.
The last two murders weren't
connected to the vigilante.
So the rumors are true.
You are helping the
cops investigate this.
How can I help?
You were a member of the Scroll and Key
back at Yale.
Allegedly.
It is a secret society.
Fair point.
How well did you know Clayton Ford
and Sam Hutchinson?
Clay and Hutch.
Well enough to mourn them.
Mm-hmm.
But we'd sort of fallen out of touch.
Ford looked like he
was trying to skip town
before he died,
like he knew the hit was coming,
but we just... we don't know how.
You're looking for skeletons.
And are we gonna find any?
I know you're not supposed
to talk ill of the dead
or whatever, but, you know,
there were always rumors
that they had shady
business dealings going on
with the Triad, I believe.
So who knows? Maybe they
got in over their heads.
Probably.
I won't take up any more of your time.
Thank you, Max.
Mm-hmm.
You mind if I ask you a question?
They sent you to prison
for helping this city.
Why the hell should you
care about any of this?
Old habits.
I guess some people don't
change that much after all.
Hey.
Sorry I'm late.
That's okay.
I'm still getting used
to you coming home at all.
How did things go with Fuller?
Max Fuller is hiding something.
Do you mind looking into it?
Of course.
Hey, you just came in the front door,
and none of my security
measures triggered.
You sure?
Felicity!
Who are you?
My husband asked you a question.
Where'd you get that?
We'll talk about it later.
Stay down!
Hey, hey.
All right. As soon as
the doc gives the okay,
we'll take him into the
station for questioning.
In the meantime, we'll go through
his effects, see what we can find out.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Oh, hey, and just a bit of advice.
Yeah.
You probably shouldn't be shooting
people your first week out of prison.
- That's a good tip.
- Yeah.
He must've somehow countered my alarm
- by sonically hacking into the sensors.
- Felicity.
That is a design flaw that
could take weeks to fix.
- We need to talk about this.
- No. We need to be safe.
This security system was
supposed to bring peace of mind.
- You mean like owning a gun?
- Yeah.
Where'd you even get a gun?
Your best new friend Laurel?
Of course not.
I got it from your
ex-best friend, Anatoly.
You what?
I've barely been gone 7 months,
and you've aligned yourself
with two of the most
immoral people we know?
Oliver, you don't get to judge me.
You just shot a man in our living room.
Something you've done a million times.
Hey, this isn't you.
You don't obsess over security.
You certainly don't carry a gun.
This is me, Oliver,
not because I was influenced
by Laurel or Anatoly.
This is me because of you.
You were the one that decided
all on your own that you were
going to sacrifice yourself,
leaving your son and your wife
alone at home as sitting ducks for Diaz.
And the best part about
the whole thing is that
you didn't even ask us
about how we felt about it.
I've already apologized for this.
I don't know how many times
you need me to apologize.
What am I supposed to do
with an apology, Oliver?
I'm just supposed to move on?
While you were gone,
I had to figure out how to survive.
And I am glad that I did
because the old me, she was weak.
How could you possibly think that?
The old you was the
person I fell in love with.
Well...
she's gone.
And she's not coming back.
I thought you didn't drink.
Yeah, well, it's been a tough week.
I know the feeling.
You know, Roy told me
this would only bring me pain,
and he was right.
I'm going home.
Just like that, huh,
without any answers?
Felicity is dead.
And before that, she had a
plan to blow up an entire city.
So I'm not sure exactly
why I'm supposed to care
about what happened to her.
I'm just sorry I dragged
you all into this.
You need to see something.
It's called the mark of four.
Your dad came up with it.
I don't remember that.
You were already gone.
It was right before everything.
It symbolizes the 4
pillars of heroism...
Courage, compassion,
selflessness, and loyalty.
We all got them as a reminder that
no matter what happened,
if one of us was in trouble,
the other ones would be there.
That's why Roy came with
you back to Star City.
He saw the symbol written on
the inside of your father's bow.
So that's why you're helping us?
I didn't know what to
make of you at first.
Trust doesn't come so easily to me.
Yeah? So what changed?
I started seeing the best
parts of your dad in you...
The strength that made him a hero.
I am not that.
You sure about that?
'Cause your dad, he had this
way of looking into things,
of seeing beyond the evidence.
So what does your gut
tell you about Blackstar?
That she isn't telling
us the whole story.
Good. Let's find out what she's hiding.
Hey, hey. Who's hungry?
Ohh. You're a life saver.
It's not often I get to buy
the police captain dinner.
Yeah?
Well, you'd better get your fill in now
because I probably won't
have this job much longer.
Why? You don't think this
will blow over with Pollard?
Well...
I don't know.
You know, maybe it shouldn't.
How can I really be effective here
if she's just gonna
undercut me the whole way?
I'd be better off as Black Canary.
Whew. You don't know how long
I've been waiting for you to say that.
But you're the best damn
person for this job, D.
This city needs you here.
Hey. How's it going with the hit man?
Good. He's still recovering,
but we got an ID thanks to A.R.G.U.S.
Frank Cassaday, otherwise
known as "the Mirror."
Specializes in kills via mimicked m.o.
Proof the vigilante didn't do it,
but who ordered the hits?
Where'd you find that?
I found that on Cassaday.
Why? You recognize that?
Fuller. He used those to
pay his muscle in the club.
This was Fuller.
He ordered the hit on Hutchinson
and then Ford and then me
once I got too close.
Why? I mean, he's a rich douche bag,
but I didn't peg him to be a killer.
Felicity ran background on Fuller.
He had secret business dealings
with both Hutchinson and Ford.
If they were gonna cut him out,
this was payback.
All right. Well, the hit on you failed,
so that means Fuller's gonna
know something's up soon
if he doesn't already, right?
I'm gonna send S.W.A.T.
in while we still have
the element of surprise.
It's not that simple.
Fuller's in there right now
with at least 12 hired guns,
and the club is at capacity.
So it could get really messy.
Guys.
It won't get messy
if the Green Arrow
goes in... the O.G. one.
No. I... I can't risk being
separated from my family, Rene.
I can't do it.
I might know a way you can.
Even if you did,
Pollard would never stand for it.
Pollard wanted me to restore
the city's faith in this department,
and that is never gonna happen if we
keep treating our heroes like criminals.
It's time the mayor realizes that.
Dinah, I trust you,
but you have to be sure.
Half this city believes in the vigilante
because they were hoping it was you.
Now they don't have to hope anymore.
Okay.
I need to make a pit stop.
The bunker has seen better days.
Yes, it has.
It didn't seem right coming back here
after the team disbanded.
Thanks for bringing this.
The FBI still has mine.
It's a good thing you made another one.
Yeah.
Does that mean you changed your mind
about breaking the cycle of violence?
No.
I cannot burden William with this.
But it's not just about
breaking the cycle of violence.
It's about accountability.
What does that mean to you?
If Star City wants to
hate the Green Arrow,
that's fine.
They'll have to hate me, too.
You want some backup out there?
Thank you, but this
time, I got to go solo.
Hey.
Yeah.
Don't you need this?
No.
Cassaday, you were
supposed to check in here
when the job was done.
Where the hell are you?
Listen, I want everyone
on high alert, okay?
No one gets in here.
Go!
I'm in.
Copy that. We're ready.
Keep your men in position
and wait for my word.
I don't want to tip our
hand or panic the crowd.
Let's hope you're not rusty.
All units, stand by.
Queen?
Aah! Uh! Uh...
Oliver, do you have Fuller?
I'm about to.
Stay back!
Drop the gun, Max.
- I'll shoot.
- Hiring killers is easy.
Taking the shot yourself isn't.
Oh. You're a vigilante.
You don't have the
authority to arrest me.
She does.
Max Fuller, you are under arrest
for the murder of Clayton Ford
and Sam Hutchinson.
Take Mr. Fuller into booking.
Should I give you two a minute?
We do this together.
Ms. Mayor, to what
do I owe the pleasure?
You've got some nerve.
I want Mr. Queen booked
in violation of the anti-vigilante law.
Hmm. Afraid I can't do that.
Then I want your resignation.
I think that would be a mistake.
Oh, that's rich, coming from the man
who stared this city
in the face and lied.
You made a mockery of city hall.
I'm gonna show you that
no one is above the law.
I could not agree with you more,
which is why, as of today, Mr. Queen
is officially working for the SCPD.
He's no longer a vigilante.
I'll get that tossed
by this time tomorrow.
Well, you can try, but
I have a strong feeling
the district attorney is going
to side with me on this one.
This isn't over,
not even close.
This should be fun.
Got to warn you, this one's a handful.
We know.
You sure you're good with this?
Hiding the truth from
Oliver and Felicity? No.
But this is the
strongest lead we've got.
If we don't exploit it now,
who knows how many
people will be hurt later?
Open it.
We'll take it from here.
Hello, Mr. Diaz. Remember me?
I'm sure you remember my husband.
What do you want?
We need your help.
Man. And I thought I was messy.
How are we supposed to
find anything in this place?
Guys!
These are the bomb schematics we found
in Felicity's hideout.
Blackstar knew about her
plan to blow up Star City.
Maybe she didn't just know about it.
Maybe she was part of it.
Huh. If Felicity got cold feet,
that's one hell of a motive to kill her.
Okay. But why hang on to these?
I mean, why not destroy the evidence?
Because she's still
planning on using them.
Okay, we have got to go to the cops.
The SCPD are a joke.
They'd love to watch
Star City go up in flames.
Well, there is another option.
We go to the Glades.
I thought we weren't welcome there.
Well, we're not, but she is.
No. No way.
Zoe, we don't know when or where
this is going to happen, right?
And by the time we find
out, it could be too late.
I don't love the idea either,
but we need resources.
I guess it's time to pay my dad a visit.
With the successful arrest
of Max Fuller assisted
by Oliver Queen, the Green
Arrow will officially be working
on the side of the law
hand in hand with the SCPD,
marking a new era for Star City.
Well... it looks like
you're famous again.
Could you have imagined 7 years ago
that you'd be working unmasked
and alongside the cops?
A lot has changed.
Yeah.
All those months at Slabside,
there wasn't a day that went by...
There wasn't an hour
that went by I didn't think
about you and William and...
getting our life back.
Me, too.
Okay.
So what's changed?
I think time apart forced us to move
in different directions.
Okay. But how do we...
start pushing in the
same direction again?
I want to.
Mm-hmm.
But you're right.
You know, I've changed...
more than you know.
I almost killed Diaz,
and I would've killed him
if Laurel hadn't stopped me.
And I know that you're gonna want
to talk me down to the old Felicity,
the one that you met
chewing that red pen.
While you were gone,
I had to learn how to protect myself.
I put you in the position
where you had to do that,
and I'm sorry.
No. This isn't on you.
Well... okay.
I love you more than a human being
should love another human being.
I just don't know
if what's best for me right now is
the same thing as what's best for us.
Hey, Dad, turns out
Oliver is more like you
than I thought,
more like me, too.
But I'm not giving up,
not ever.
You failed.
Why are you doing this?
You did this to yourself.
And now all of you will perish.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --