My name is Oliver Queen.
After five years
on a hellish island,
I have come home
with only one goal--
to save my city.
But to do so, I can't be
the killer I once was.
To honor my friend's memory,
I must be someone else.
I must be something else.
Previously on "Arrow"...
We would like to serve
notice to the defense,
pursuant to rule of
criminal procedure 15.
I would like to have
a conversation with you
before you seek
the death penalty.
Moira, what don't I know?
There are some things
that must never
be spoken of.
He's beaten me twice, and I
don't know how to stop him.
Who are you?
Once you know, your life
will never be the same.
Sara?
Yeah, Dad,
college is great.
No, me and my new roommate
totally hit it off.
We're like besties.
Ok. Yeah, dad,
I got to get back to chem lab.
Yes. It looks like
I got a long night ahead of me.
Psst. Get off
the phone!
Love you, Dad. Bye.
Ollie.
You are trouble.
How is
Detective Lance?
Ah, he's clueless,
as usual.
Guess I was thirsty.
Did you hear that?
1, 2, 3...
It's getting closer.
That's not very
scientific.
And what would you know
about science,
Mr. Ivy league drop out?
I happen to know
a lot about science.
I know...
Fermentation.
I know...Biology.
♪ I'm tearing up
this joint, ready or not ♪
♪ in with my crew
and we're turning heads ♪
♪ you play it right,
you can touch my dreads ♪
Mmm. Laurel's
going to kill me.
She's so going to kill me.
Your sister
will never know.
Just come here.
Ok, that one was really close.
Sara.
We're going
to be fine.
Sara?
Sara!
Help! Help!
Oliver!
In sports, the international
basketball league was busy
last night with seven games
on the schedule.
The Cavaliers came up
with a surprise upset...
Can't sleep?
I don't do well
with my eyes closed.
Hey, thanks
for letting me stay here.
I know you got a lot
going on with your mom.
Thea's mostly staying
at her boyfriend's.
So...don't worry about anyone
finding out that you're back.
Thanks for understanding.
I don't understand.
You know, not a day goes by
that your family doesn't miss you.
Yeah? How do you know?
Because I missed you.
I don't think they'll be as happy
to see me as you think.
How can you say that?
I know how hard it is
to come home when you've
been gone for so long.
I'm guessing my father
and Laurel
weren't too happy to see you.
No.
No, not at first.
I wasn't sure if you
and she ever got back together.
We tried.
It's too much.
Yeah some things, you know,
it's better left in the past.
I'm done waiting for Mr. Queen.
Let's get started.
Sorry I'm late.
There's an old friend...
In town.
I just finished explaining
to your mother and sister
that Miss Lance will be
sitting second chair
for the prosecution.
This is a conflict of interest.
Miss Lance practically
grew up in the Queen house.
I think
you're overstating matters.
Oh, we'll see when I move to conflict
Miss Lance off this case.
Maybe there won't be
a case much longer.
I come here not just
with Miss Lance,
but also
with a plea offer.
Life, with
the possibility of parole.
No.
We are not pleading out.
Mrs. Queen is innocent.
She aided
and abetted 503 homicides.
Under duress from a homicidal maniac
named Malcolm Merlyn.
She also withdrew
from the criminal conspiracy
prior to its execution.
Five minutes prior.
With Malcolm Merlyn
dead, a jury's going
to want to have
to blame someone.
If she doesn't
take the deal,
then she's facing
the death penalty.
Sounds a lot
like blackmail.
Try reality.
And here's some more--
we've subpoenaed over a decades'
worth of phone messages,
phone records,
letters and emails.
I'm willing to bet I find something that
crushes your duress defense
to powder.
Mr. Donner...
If you don't mind, I'd like a few days
to consider your offer.
Of course.
Excuse me.
I'll be right back.
Laurel?
I'll meet you
at the car.
You're prosecuting
my mother?
I didn't ask for this case.
I was assigned.
So say no!
It's a new job, Oliver.
I don't have a lot of pull.
And what pull I do have,
I used to get that
plea bargain for your mother.
This was your idea?
Life in prison?
The D.A. is serious
about the death penalty, Ollie.
We both know what it's like
to lose someone.
So think about it
and save your mother's life.
Are you ok?
In case I wasn't clear
last week...
I'm done answering
that question.
Help!
Over here!
Sara?
Sara.
You ok?
How did everything
go with your mother?
I ran into your sister.
She's working on the case.
You didn't tell her...
No.
I know a little something about
keeping secrets
and respecting them,
even though I don't...
totally understand why
you're keeping yours.
Is this--
is it because of what happened
on the island?
No.
After.
There were things
that I did;
things that I had
to do to survive.
Things that there's
no forgiveness for.
Well, that's the thing
about forgiveness--
you can't get it
until you ask for it.
Merlyn?
Who are you?
Just a warrior. Like you.
Why are you dressed
like Malcolm Merlyn?
Huh? Who sent you?!
♪ Arrow 2x05 ♪
League of Assassins
Original Air Date on November 6, 2013
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
I remember the first time
I saw this hood.
Shado was wearing it.
This is quite the set-up
that you got here.
Where you're launching
your one man war for starling.
I'm not one man.
These are my friends.
This is John Diggle
and Felicity Smoak.
Guys. This is Sara.
Welcome home, Sara.
I was happy to hear
you're not dead anymore.
I mean, I didn't know you before
you didn't die the first time.
I'm still glad you're alive.
Thank you.
We just had an uninvited
guest in the Queen mansion.
Trained. Highly skilled.
And he was dressed like Merlyn.
Well, the last I checked
Malcolm Merlyn was dead,
courtesy of an arrow
jammed through his heart.
It wasn't him.
It was a follower, an underling
bent on revenge.
Whoever it was...
He knows who I am.
Gee, I didn't
get you a bag of dirt.
I found it in the house.
Copycat Merlyn tracked it in.
I want you to analyze it.
Hopefully it'll lead me right to him.
Then what?
If this pretender
wants to follow
Malcolm Merlyn so badly,
he can follow him
right into a grave.
Sara? We'll find this guy.
I don't want you to.
What do you mean?
He wasn't after you, Ollie.
He's after me.
Who is he?
He's called Al Owal,
"The First."
And he's a member
of the League of Assassins.
The League
of Assassins?
I thought they were a myth.
What's the League of Assassins?
And please,
don't say it's a league
made up of assassins.
No, it's an urban legend.
I heard about them in Afghanistan
from a tribal leader.
He claimed there was
an ancient sect of assassins,
deadly warriors that killed
and vanished like ghosts.
Thought he was smoking
what he was selling.
I tried to tell you, Ollie,
but you wouldn't listen.
That's where you've been
the past four years.
That's where
you learned to fight.
You're one of them.
After the freighter,
a member of the league
rescued me; Took me in
and brought me
to Nanda Parbatt.
They remade me
into what I am.
And I swore them
my allegiance.
Why are they kicking down doors
trying to find you now?
Because I left.
And there's only way
that you leave the league.
Is that why you didn't want
to see your family?
A year ago,
I was in Guyana.
I was sent there
for a man named Suarez.
He was a local diplomat.
And I slit his throat.
In his bed.
And his kids...
They found his body
in the morning.
I'm a murderer, Ollie.
You think that my family
will be happy to see me?
I have to go
to Iron Heights.
Felicity, I need you
to find this Al Owal.
Thank you,
thank you.
What were you doing out there?
The boat that I was on,
and we got caught
in the storm.
Wait, wait, wait, guys!
Wait! I--Robert Queen.
Robert Queen.
It was his boat,
and--and--
he'll pay whatever
you want, please!
Please, please!
Please, no!
Please, no! No!
You've made a mistake.
Please let me out.
Why won't you let me--
no, please, come back!
Let me out!
You cannot be serious!
What's going on here?
She wants to take the deal!
Whoa! If this is
about the death penalty...
I've been explaining
this to your mother.
Even if we ever get
to sentencing,
you were acting under duress.
I have everything I need
to keep them from
sentencing you to death.
The death penalty
doesn't scare me, Jean.
Then why aren't you
fighting?
I have my reasons.
Name one.
Because I'm tired of fighting.
I am not confident
that I can win
over a jury.
And I'm not altogether certain
that I deserve to.
That was actually three.
Thea...
No, seriously, you're just ready
to give up?!
Just take your medicine and
spend the rest of your life in here.
We still need you.
I still need you.
I--I can't take this.
Growing up...
I didn't think that there were
secrets kept between us.
Last year
I learned different.
And I've gotten
pretty good
at knowing when you're hiding
something from me.
So, Mom...
What are you
hiding now?
Help your sister
come to terms with my choice,
because it's made.
Sorry if I upset you before.
We all join clubs
we wish we hadn't.
It took me a year to get out
of that gym membership.
Thank you.
For what?
Not making me
feel like what I am.
Oliver's lucky to have you
both as friends.
He hasn't always
had the best luck in that area.
How'd it go with your mother?
Not well.
Have you found somebody
for me to hit yet?
Could be. Spectro analysis
of the dirt from your house
had trace amounts
of aldicarb in them.
What?
It's a pesticide.
Starling City used to have
its own aldicarb plant,
but per the EPA,
it was shut down three years ago.
What's it being used for now?
Nothing. It's abandoned.
But my guess is,
it's the homebase
to one League
of Assassins assassin.
He will kill you.
Like you, I am not that
easy to get rid of.
This is my fight.
He made it my fight
when he came
into my house.
And when he threatened
somebody that I care about.
Arrows.
Such an ineffective
projectile.
I find it strange anyone
who still fears them.
I'll show you why--
if you don't leave
Sara Lance alone.
This is your only warning.
And it would be
effective,
were you to pose
a threat to me.
You barely defeated
Malcolm Merlyn
at nearly the cost
of your own life.
What hope would you have
against the man who trained him?
Helps that I didn't
come alone.
The child of Ra's al Ghul
awaits your return.
I'm not going back.
That's not your choice.
I have orders
to return you...
Alive or dead.
You're not going to kill me.
You overestimate
your importance.
Regardless, you're
coming back with us.
Us?
Like you,
I did not come alone.
If you will not return
willingly,
we'll stay to bury your family.
You're not even
flinching when he...
Pain and I came to a little
understanding few years back.
Done.
The League of Assassins.
Why wouldn't she tell me
what happened to her all those years?
Probably the same reason
why you didn't tell us
what happened to you
on the island.
We need to protect the Lances.
I'll take Laurel.
What can I do?
Nothing. You're hurt,
and you need to stay here.
What about
my father?
I'll go talk
to Detective Lance.
Tell him he needs
to get out town for
a couple of days.
Please don't tell
him about me.
I can keep a secret.
Just ask him.
You three are quite the team.
We have our moments.
Get back.
No, no, please!
Please, please, no!
The more you struggle...
The more it'll hurt.
No, no, please!
Please!
Wait.
Let her go.
You don't give me orders.
No, that would be
the Captain.
But he works for me.
Doesn't he?
Help me, please!
Come here.
Laurel, listen,
it's your father--again.
Ok, now listen,
I know you're still mad at me
after what I said when
you got pulled over last week,
but it's not right,
us not talking.
So please, just--
just call me, ok?
Detective Lance!
I knew you'd be
getting home around now
because your shift
has ended.
Which I knew because
I kind of pinged your cell phone.
Miss Smoak.
You have cockroaches
and they mean business.
Since when did you start
making house calls?
Since you're in danger.
I'm not afraid
of cockroaches.
Yes, you're in real danger!
You need to get out of town
for a couple days.
Listen, I'm in danger
every time I put on this uniform,
so you're going
to have to be a little more specific.
There's an organization
called the League of Assassins
and three of its members
are targeting you.
It...sounded a little less
crazy in my head.
I doubt it.
Malcolm Merlyn was apparently a member.
That should give you
some sort of idea
about the type of people
we're dealing with.
Ok, I'll bite.
What did I do
to piss them off?
That...um...
Is a really long story.
You just...
You need to trust me.
You're not safe here
in Starling City.
Smoak,
nobody's safe, ok?
Especially not us cops.
We get shot at
for a living.
And my shift?
It just ended.
Detective Lance!
Good-night.
Wait, you need
to listen to me!
Good night,
Miss Smoak.
So I guess this means
you're not leaving town?
Evening.
I should have
said this earlier,
but it's not appropriate for us
to be discussing your mother's case.
Actually, I was in the neighborhood,
so I thought that I would
swing by and see if I could
give you a ride home
and maybe get a bite to eat.
It's been a long day.
I don't need an even longer night
of you trying to talk me
out of your mother's plea agreement.
Laurel.
I promise, this has nothing
to do with my mother's case.
You've had a rough
couple of weeks.
You really going to tell me
you couldn't use a friend?
Come on.
Hey.
How'd it go?
Badly.
He either didn't believe me
or didn't take me seriously.
In hindsight,
I probably shouldn't have led
with League of Assassins.
What do we do now?
What are you doing?
Oliver told you to stay put.
I thought you didn't want
your father to know you're still alive.
I don't. But it's better
than him not being.
Where do you think you're going?
With you.
I'm not going to let you go out there
without any back-up.
Dig, you may be
a three tour Special Forces veteran,
but I was trained by the people that
make the Special Forces
look like a kindergarten class.
So step aside
or get put down.
It's your funeral, Sara.
It wouldn't be my first.
No, it can't be.
It can't be Sara.
It's me. It's Sara.
Daddy...
It's ok.
Sara?
Sara!
You speak Chinese now?
Picked up a couple things
in the past few years.
Yes.
Why didn't you let us know
that you were alive?
I mean, your mother
and I, we...
We missed you.
And your sister
did, too.
You know that,
right?
I know you got divorced.
Yeah.
But it wasn't
your fault.
That was on me.
Because of me.
I'm sorry.
It's all right.
None of that matters
now. You know why?
'Cause you're home,
sweetie, you're home.
Are you in trouble?
Huh?
No, Dad.
You are.
You sent Felicity Smoak
to warn me to leave town.
You know the Arrow.
You're the girl in the mask.
You've been kicking the crap
out of creeps in the Glades.
You've been home for weeks.
Tell me something--
if these assassins,
if they hadn't shown up,
would you have ever let us know
that you were alive?
No.
Felicity said that these guys were
part of a league of something.
What do they want
with you.
What all assassins want--
to terminate their objective.
Oh, this is crazy.
Dad, we have to go.
No, we are not
going anywhere.
Not until you sit down
and you tell me exactly
what you've gotten
yourself into.
You are an amazing cop
and you are strong
and decent and honest.
But these men, they will cut you
down before you can lift a finger.
Now please.
Come with me.
I'm afraid it's not
much, but, uh...
It's home.
Why did you
lock the door?
No, no, no, no.
It's not because...
It's just a habit. My shipmates aren't
exactly the nicest bunch.
Please, come in.
Have a seat.
My name is Ivo.
Dr. Anthony Ivo.
And you are?
Sara.
Nice to meet you,
Why do you keep those people
down there in those cells?
It's my work.
I need them.
What work?
I am going to save
the human race, Sara.
Maybe you can help me.
I noticed you didn't have
a drink at dinner.
No. I didn't.
So will you now
admit that you and my father
overreacted
last week
when you thought
that I was becoming a drunk?
I am prepared to admit
that I care about you.
Is that why
you insisted
on walking me
to my door?
You know me.
I just wanted
to make sure you were safe.
This is safe.
This...
We shouldn't.
Then why did you come
all the way up here?
I'm really sorry if I was
sending the wrong message.
No! No, no,
I got the message.
I get it loud
and clear every day.
Run.
Run, run away
from Laurel,
run as fast
as you can.
Laurel, come on.
Sara...
She got on
"The Gambit" with you.
My father, he--
he climbed
into a bottle.
My mother, she--she
climbed into her car
and she drove away,
and then Tommy...
What is so wrong with me
that everybody leaves?
I will never leave you.
Until you do.
I thought I locked that.
Stay here.
Ollie?
Anything?
All good.
I have to go.
Listen, I'm sorry
about what I said--
Don't be.
Just stay here.
Felicity, Al Owal
was at Laurel's place.
What? Is she ok?
She's fine. Looks like he moved out
before we got there.
But if Laurel's
not his target...
He's after Lance,
and I need a location now.
Well, I can't believe
I didn't think to look for you up here.
It's a good vantage point.
You can see the whole city.
Like a bird on a wire.
Where I was, they have
you choose a new name.
I chose
ta-er sah-fer.
It's arabic.
For Canary.
I bought you that Canary
when you were ten.
I was as far from home
as you can get,
but I never forgot
where I came from.
You know how they say
the first thing
you forget about somebody when
they're gone is their voice?
You can remember their face,
and the way they move,
but you can't hold on
to the way they sound.
I never forgot
your voice, Dad.
Sweetheart...
We're out of time.
So, this is where you wanted
your father to die.
What the hell, Sara,
who are these guys?
Associates of your daughter,
Officer Lance.
Well, she always did have
the worst taste in friends.
Did you really think
we weren't going
to find you here?
No.
I knew you would.
Go.
You should be mindful
of your surroundings.
Guns are a coward's weapon.
What are you
without your side arm?
A guy with a spare.
You think because
you are the beloved
you will be granted
your freedom?
There's only one freedom.
Let me grant you yours.
You don't have to do this.
It's over!
Not yet.
Sara, baby, don't...
Tell Ra's al Ghul
that my family is off limits.
His quarrel is with me.
I'm sorry you saw that.
I can't imagine what
you must think of me.
I think
you're a survivor.
I think you're one of the
bravest people I've ever known.
You're my daughter.
It's time for you
to come back home.
I can't.
Why not?
They are never going
to stop looking for me.
I'll protect you.
We'll protect you.
Tell her it's safe to stay.
Dad...
If they hurt you
or Laurel or mom,
then I really would die.
But they need to know.
They can't. They can't, Daddy.
Why not?
You know why! I came back
to make sure that my family was safe,
and you are.
But if they knew I was alive,
Laurel and mom,
they would never
stop looking for me,
and that could get them
both killed.
I can't let you go.
I can't let you go!
I have to--Dad,
I have to--I have to go.
I love you.
Keep them safe.
Detective...
She's right.
You have to keep
her secret.
It's already the hardest thing
I've ever had to do.
How do you live like this?
I never mind getting
a visit from my children,
but I know why you're here.
We just have
one more thing to say.
Oliver, we've already
been through this.
I am not going
to change my mind.
This is about me
changing mine.
Because I thought that you
didn't want to go to trial
over...a secret.
Then I caught up
with an old friend,
and I watched as she struggled
to tell her family hers,
because she was afraid...
That they wouldn't love her
if they knew the truth.
Whatever you are
worried about,
it will not make us
love you any less.
You don't know.
Who do you think you raised?
You taught us
to be strong.
That we could overcome
any obstacle that we faced;
to fight.
Do you really think that we
are going to scare that easily?
Whatever comes out...
You won't lose us.
Ever.
Wow.
I'll instruct Jean
to reject Mr. Donner's offer.
Hey.
Dad.
I know I owe you
a phone call.
I have a lot
of work. Can we--
can we do this
another time?
I just had to see you, Laurel.
Did something happen?
Are you ok?
One day, honey,
when you have
a daughter of your own,
you'll understand
that being a parent,
it means you just never
stop worrying about your children.
Dad, I'm--I'm sorry
I didn't call you back.
I've--I've had
a really long week,
and--and I'm tired.
Are you all right?
I don't know.
I wish that
there was--
there was
something, a...
A sign that
it gets better.
It does, honey.
It gets better.
How do you know?
I wish I could tell you,
sweetie.
I wish I could tell you.
Where's Sara?
She left.
You cool with that?
I didn't have
much of a choice.
An old friend
gave this to me.
Said I would know when it
was the right time to drink it.
And now's
the right time?
I'm not sure.
But I need a drink.
Prochnost.
Hmm. That's...
So you were right.
Yeah, I usually am,
Oliver.
About what,
specifically?
No matter how hard I try,
Diggle, my past...
It doesn't want to stay buried.
I don't want to try
so hard anymore.
The five years
that I was gone...
I wasn't always on the island.
Aah!
How are you--
Prisoners do not speak.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man