My name is Oliver Queen.
After five years in hell,
I returned home with only one goal,
to save my city.
Today, I fight that war on two fronts.
By day, I lead Star City as its mayor.
But by night, I'm someone else.
I am something else.
I am the Green Arrow.
Previously, on Arrow...
Follow me or die.
Hello, Mr. Queen. My name is Talia.
I've been looking for you.
As soon as I'm out of here,
Walker will concoct some reason
to put a bullet in my head.
I think I'm gonna have
to prosecute this one myself.
It could take a while.
I haven't kept my promise to Laurel.
You're gonna train a new Black Canary?
I think that somewhere out there, there is
a woman worthy of Laurel's legacy.
Now all we've gotta do
is find her.
Protests continue into the final
countdown for tonight's ignition
of S.T.A.R. Labs'
controversial particle accelerator.
S.T.A.R. Labs founder
and CEO, Harrison Wells,
promises a new era of
scientific advancement is at hand.
Would you look at that?
Future's getting brighter every day.
What do you think, babe?
You a fan of progress?
Why don't you just put a bullet
in my head and be done with it?
Or maybe you don't
have the sack to pull the trigger.
I was gonna play another hand,
let you rest some.
But lay down a challenge like that,
what's a guy gonna do?
I'm gonna get what I need from you,
or maybe one of those molars back there.
Forget her.
Hey, Tina. Not looking too good.
But I got something here
that might put a smile on your face.
Look what we got here.
- Oh, my God. Vinny...
- I'm sorry, Tina.
Aw, so sweet.
I thought you two
were just cop buddies, but...
You can tell me, Vin.
You're tapping that sweet ass, aren't you?
I wasn't sure which one of you to Kill.
Thanks for making up my mind for me.
Get the tarp.
No, please, please, please!
Don't hurt him.
Shut up.
Wait, we are now being
told to evacuate the facility.
The storm may have
caused a malfunction
to the primary cooling system.
Officials are down...
Sean, I am begging you.
Please.
- No.
- What do you mean, "No?"
- Did you even read her resume?
- Yeah, I did.
So, you know she flew
600 sorties over Iraq,
launched a program for inner-city kids
to get into flight school
as a way out of poverty,
plus, she's got skills in krav maga
and a third-degree black belt.
If Top Gun here is a maybe,
how the hell did I even get on the team?
Don't answer that.
Look, finding a new Black Canary
isn't just about reviewing resumes,
it's a feel thing.
Well, I feel like we're busting
our asses to find you candidates,
and you keep shooting 'em down.
I promised Laurel that
I would carry on her legacy,
I just don't won't Black Siren
to be all that's left of her.
Well, what about this woman?
Allison Slater.
Okay, she's a decorated CIA officer
who also happens to be
a world-champion in judo.
Nope. Okay.
What about Tara Michele?
Army special ops, but then
she decided to open a clinic downtown
to offer free healthcare to the homeless.
Okay, well, I will keep digging.
Okay, hold up, what about this one?
This woman got
her engineering PhD at age 20,
won gold in karate at the Olympics,
turned down offers
from the NSA and ARGUS
to join NASA as an astronaut by day,
while at night she secretly protects
the citizens of Houston as, get this,
a ninja vigilante.
Oh, and she works
soup kitchens on Saturdays
and rescues puppies on Sundays.
Astronaut-ninja? You're making that up.
He did.
Karate won't be an
Olympic sport until 2020.
Fine, you got me.
This is just some woman
who teaches preschool in the Glades,
- but my point still stands.
- That point being?
That no matter how amazing they are,
no one's gonna be good enough for you.
Because you keep
comparing them to Laurel,
which is an impossible standard
you might wanna consider loosening.
We just need to keep looking,
to think outside the box.
How far outside the box
are we talking here?
Are we talking way outside the box,
like, urban legends outside?
Because if we are,
I think I might have something.
Wait, what do you mean, "urban legend?"
I mean her.
By her, you mean who?
Well, actually,
I have no idea what her name is,
but according to the chat rooms I visited,
she's a kickass woman
who appears out of nowhere
- and saves crime victims.
- In Star City?
All over America, actually.
And get this, she even has a cry.
Like, a canary cry.
She's a meta,
with the same power as Earth-2 Laurel?
If that isn't bashert,
I don't know what is.
- What?
- Bashert means fate. Destiny.
According to the ARGUS database
I just hacked,
sightings started
three years ago in Central City.
That is right when S.T.A.R. Labs exploded.
And she even has a black
leather jacket and everything.
Only thing that's really
missing is the blonde hair,
and you can fix that with a wig.
I have to handle
something for John.
Let's see if this urban legend
is the real deal,
and call me when you have something.
- Hey.
Just got a text from Adrian,
do you know what it's about?
Maybe to figure out how
Prometheus faked Lyla's voice
to get me out of the bunker and into here.
I'm less concerned
with how you got in here
and more concerned
with getting you out again.
Gentlemen, sorry I'm late.
How you holding up?
Walker's gonna have custody
of me in a week, so...
As soon as Walker gets his hands on John
he's gonna throw him into a hole.
Maybe not.
I've got a buddy
at the National Security Agency.
Turns out they have
General Walker under investigation
and were putting together quite the case.
Wire transfers and some
keyhole satellite images
of his movements with the nuclear trigger.
That's enough to exonerate John.
Except I don't like
the way you just said,
"were building a case" just now.
Walker has friends in high places.
Managed to get
the investigation slow-rolled.
But the file still exists.
I made a FOIA request,
but seeing as all this is classified,
that could take months, maybe even years.
- That's time we don't have.
- I'm sorry I don't have better news.
No, Adrian, you have gone
above and beyond already.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
Well, Felicity is really going
to enjoy hacking the NSA.
You mean after she's brought you
a hundred Black Canary candidates
for you to say no to?
You're not the only one
who visits, Oliver.
John, I understand what I promised Laurel.
Now that we're actively doing it,
trying to replace her?
It just...
It feels wrong.
She didn't want you to
find someone to replace her,
just someone to take on the mantle.
And from where I'm sitting,
that's two very different things.
Sleeping beauty awakes.
- Where am I?
- Some place safe.
I have to get back to the Bratva.
Why, so they can finish killing you?
That was Gregor, I have allies there.
I think you'll come to discover
circumstances within the Bratva
a bit more complex than you thought.
Why did you save me?
Well, from what I could tell,
you needed rescuing.
- Where'd you get that?
- Wasn't hard.
Sneaking past a bunch of oafish Bratva
is hardly a test of my skills.
Why did you do that?
Shipwrecked on Lian Yu, fled to Hong Kong,
the Omega Virus, Shadowspire,
and now, you're mixed up with the Bratva.
But along the way,
you went back home to Starling City,
though you couldn't bear to
reveal yourself to your family.
- How do you know this?
- I did my homework.
What makes me so interesting?
You wear the hood of one of my students.
Yao Fei Gulong?
You get my text about John?
If there is any trace
of the file that Digg needs,
it's gonna be buried
behind some serious firewalls.
Actually, firewalls don't
even begin to explain it,
it's gonna be more like
fire castles, or fire mountains.
How did you know where to start?
All that I told you was that
Chase might have something.
Yeah, and then I hacked his laptop.
Saving Digg is gonna break
at least 12 federal laws.
Hacking your DA is just small ball.
Plus, you are the mayor,
you can pardon me.
Actually, I can't.
It doesn't matter because I am having fun.
I haven't done a good old
grab-government-secrets kind of hack
in a really long time
and it's a great change of pace
and it feels awesome.
And it'll keep me busy while you're gone.
- I'm going somewhere?
- Maybe Hub City.
We're thinking that's where
the new Black Canary is hanging out.
Yeah, let's not call her that just yet,
I'd like to see her
in the field at least first.
Ask and you shall receive.
I was able to track down cell phone
footage of her latest act of heroism.
Heroine-ism? Heroism. Anyway, take a look.
The video isn't clear enough
for facial recog,
but she's real all right.
I've watched it, like, ten times.
The woman can fight.
She can focus the sound
better than Black Siren,
and she is more skilled at hand-to-hand.
This is almost like...
What was that word that you used?
- Bashert.
- Yeah, that.
It almost sounds like
you'd be willing to give her a look.
- Call Rene, we're going to Hub City.
- Mmm.
Stop!
Wow.
Costume Warehouse having
a fire sale I didn't know about?
What do you what?
You're a vigilante and a meta-human.
For the past three years,
you've been working alone.
We have a proposition for you.
Oh, I'm sorry, you were doing fine.
You take it, yeah.
We'd like you to join us.
I can give you a home,
and a team,
and a place to better train
the use of your power.
I can take care of myself.
Oh, and if you get in my way,
I'll send the three of you back
to Star City with your nuts in a sling.
I thought that went pretty good.
Hey, man, what are
we still doing around this dump?
Leather jacket lady made it seem
pretty clear about us screwing off.
When have you ever known me
to give up that easily?
Never. The answer to that is, "Never."
That might have been implied.
We're not gonna find a better candidate.
Any progress on the facial
recognition from the body cams?
Sorry, but the Wi-Fi
in here is incredibly slow.
You take your time,
I got three patties
and three slices of cheddar to go.
That's disgusting.
Okay, actually, got it.
Our screaming sonic lady has a name.
Tina Boland, formerly of the CCPD.
That tracks, she was in Central City
when the particle accelerator exploded.
And after that she went off the grid,
which means that we have
no way of finding her.
Yes, we do.
- Captain Singh.
- I need information.
- Who is this?
- It's the Green Arrow.
Or some nutjob with a voice modulator.
You want help, I'm gonna need proof.
Very clever.
Fine, what do you wanna know?
Tina Boland.
She was CCPD, what happened to her?
Nothing but tragedy there.
She went deep undercover
and her partner got killed in action.
Her partner's name was...
- Vincent Sobel.
- Yeah.
Tina quit the force
the day after his funeral
and we haven't heard from her since.
- Is she in some kind of trouble?
- Not sure yet.
You get anything, give me a call.
I've always had a soft spot for Boland.
- She's a good kid.
- Will do.
Looks like our Tina is trying
to avenge her former partner.
Which means we have a lead.
Trained Yao Fei?
How's that possible?
You're half his age.
Don't you know it's improper
to talk about a woman's age?
Let's just say it's a family secret.
So, you found me because of Yao Fei?
Congratulations.
Yao Fei's gone.
I found you because
the world needs people like you.
The man who survived all this
is destined for so much more
than playing gangster in Russia.
You know, if you knew me so well,
you'd know that I made a promise...
A promise, yes.
To get revenge on Konstantine Kovar.
I have something that will help.
That is Misha Yurievich,
a black-market smuggler with
a particular specialty, young girls.
You might guess his top customer.
Kovar.
We take down Yurievich
and that leaves Kovar
without his key revenue stream.
"We?"
You should be honored
I'm offering my services.
Let me help you dispose of Yurievich,
then you will hear me out
with what I have to say.
At the very least, you'll be dealing
a major blow to your enemy.
Oh, thank God. You are a lifesaver.
Yeah, well, I figure you gotta
get your share of fast food
before they lock you up
in Lompoc for hacking the NSA.
Lompoc doesn't house female inmates,
they'd probably send me to Hazelton,
or they would
if there was anything to hack.
Uh, you lost me.
The file containing all the dirt on
General Walker, it's gone. Scrubbed.
So, what does that mean?
Well, it means that John
is back to being totally screwed.
There's no sign of Boland.
You sure this is
the right spot, Mr. Terrific?
Am I still Mr. Terrific if I'm on comms
and not in uniform?
Anyway, yeah, I cross-referenced
the ATM withdrawals,
and pings from a burner cell phone.
Detective Boland is here, room 511,
should be straight down the hall.
Whoa.
Homegirl clearly never met a trash can.
Even though she's not on the force,
she's still playing detective.
No, she's not playing.
She's out for blood.
That's her dead partner.
Mr. Terrific, are you seeing
these names on the body cams?
Already running them.
- Drop the hammer.
- Get out!
No, don't go, help me, please!
Tina...
Sonic dampener, new and improved.
He's dead.
Hello, team?
Looks like we're gonna have some company.
- Can't let her go!
- Get her, I got this.
We didn't get to finish
our last conversation.
- You're persistent.
- You killed that man.
Before, I thought you were worried
I was the one who was gonna end up dead.
- Make up your mind.
- Detective Boland.
If you know I was police,
then you know that guy back in my place
helped kill my partner.
Your vendetta doesn't end with him.
No, I'm still looking for his boss.
His friends are the ones currently
shooting it out with your friends.
We can help you get him without
anyone else dying in the process,
including and especially, you.
You know, from what I hear,
there are plenty of nutcases
running around Star City
looking to make it a better place.
What makes me so special?
Maybe stay in the same spot
for more than a minute
and I'll get a chance to tell it.
Well, if you're gonna make
a sales pitch, make it good.
You went through something traumatic.
For the past three years
you've been trying to understand it
because you're afraid
of what happened to you,
and of what you've become.
So, you're running from it.
- How would you know?
- Because I've been there.
And I can help you find your way back.
Okay.
What's the range on that...
What did you call it, sonic dampener?
That's what I thought.
Now, that's what I'm talking about.
You know, I would tell you
to chew with your mouth closed,
but I don't even know how
you could do that with this thing.
Five-stack, baby. Nothing better.
Curtis.
Yeah, so I've made some sense
out of Tina's crazy murder-board.
Meet Sean Sonus.
Three years ago, he was a player in
Central City's criminal underworld
and the target of Tina's investigation.
Interestingly, Sonus disappeared
around the same time that Tina did.
That's why she's been
traveling across the country,
she's been following him.
The only thing I don't understand
is why Sonus is in Hub City now.
Tobias Church.
Your belly hurts?
Yeah, that's not surprising.
"Tobias Church."
He had all the gangs
in Hub City under his thumb,
just like he tried to do back home.
I'm thinking with Church's demise,
it left a power vacuum here,
especially in the drug trade.
What's Sonus pushing?
Some drug I've never
heard of before called "Sly-Dee?"
It's pronounced "slide,"
like in playground,
'cause it hooks kids young and
makes them move to the big stuff faster.
If Boland's after this scumbag,
I vote we get out of her way
and let her do her thing.
I can't believe
I'm about to say this,
but I actually agree with Rene.
- I can't believe it, either.
- And then there's this.
The After-Action Report
on her partner's death.
Sonus' men captured her
and tortured her for two weeks.
So even if she didn't drop
out of the police,
she would have been
put on indefinite leave
because of psychological trauma.
All the more reason
not to leave her out there alone.
Look, I didn't know this Laurel chick,
but you're taking on a lot
to keep this promise to her.
I'm thinking this is about
more than just Laurel.
If Sonus is connected to Church's men,
that makes him more dangerous
than we thought.
We need to find Boland
before she gets involved
in something that she can't handle.
What's the plan?
Follow my lead.
Hey, hey, hey.
We're walking into a fortress
and you're gonna use just a bow?
To use a bow and arrow
requires patience and discipline.
That's Yurievich.
I will take on his guards, Yurievich...
Yurievich is mine.
Please tell me you didn't sleep down here.
I didn't sleep.
I thought the NSA was a dead end.
The file was erased.
Yeah, but then I remembered nothing
on the internet is ever erased.
Everything leaves behind a digital shadow
and I've been scouring
the dark web trying to find it.
- What's that?
- A terminal message.
- From who?
- I have absolutely no idea.
And how'd they get into your system?
I have absolutely no idea.
- Who's "Ghost Fox Goddess?"
- It's me.
It was my hacker handle in college.
I made a lot of bad choices in college.
What do you mean, bad choices?
I used to be a hacktivist,
it's a hacker activist.
I left that life way behind,
what with the goth look
that was not good for me.
Goth?
Mmm-hmm. Dark hair, dark Felicity,
taking on corporations and governments.
It was a power trip though,
it wasn't healthy.
What's "IRL?"
In real life.
Yo, you know what you're doing there?
Are you kidding me?
I hacked all the traffic cams
in my hometown on a dare.
So, this is gonna help us
find Ms. Loco Bananas?
Or Sonus. Either way...
Either way, we're gonna
put ourselves in the middle
of a showdown between a nutbar
and a psycho drug dealer.
When Oliver explained
his thinking to us on this,
which he rarely ever does, by the way,
I thought you would be more on board.
How'd the last crazy recruit turn out?
Okay, Evelyn did have her issues,
true, but so did Rory.
And Oliver channeled his vendetta
into something positive.
And as far as nutcases are concerned...
As far as nutcases are concerned, what?
Nothing. I...
That was a... It was a period.
"As far as nutcases are concerned."
Period.
That was just, it wasn't... That's it.
You were thinking of me, weren't you?
I meant it in the nicest way.
I guess you're right.
- I am?
- Yeah.
Maybe this team is all about
finding second chances.
Could you hand me that adapter and tablet?
Yep.
Thanks.
- Got a location.
- Nutbar or psycho drug dealer?
- Psycho drug dealer.
- Great.
Check it out.
Hey, Sean. Been a while.
Detective Boland.
A little outside
your jurisdiction, aren't you?
I'm not a cop tonight.
Get away from her.
Son of a bitch!
What the hell was that?
Sonus...
He's a meta-human, too.
- How is she?
- Still unconscious.
I don't know about you, man,
but my head is still spinning a bit.
It's his meta-power.
I think he can control sonic waves.
It would explain how he disoriented
you guys and counteracted Tina and...
Their powers are related.
- What do you mean?
- I think I have an idea.
I didn't sign up for metas, man.
Enhanced ability or not,
Sonus is running a drug trade
that sells to kids.
If that means we're moving on
from trying to recruit this crazy lady
and focus on taking
down this prig, I'm all in.
Yeah, but we have to find Sonus first.
I know where he's gonna be.
What time is it?
11:40. Where are you going?
Sonus is taking in
a major shipment of Slyde.
And you know where.
And something tells me
you're not gonna tell us.
After three years,
the man who killed my partner
is finally in my sights,
I'm not letting anyone get in my way.
Lady wants to commit suicide,
we should let her.
Free country.
He nearly killed you last time.
Against him, your ability is a liability.
Let us help.
Hey, thanks for the save.
Safe trip back to Star City, boys.
Yurievich is dead.
Good. Now we can talk.
Look sharp.
If this goes south on me,
I want you to take this guy down, hard.
Paranoid much?
You don't know
the dark web like I do, okay?
These guys aren't exactly
known to be friendly.
OMG! OMG.
The Ghost Fox Goddess, here in meatspace.
The real Ghost Fox Goddess!
- You're Kojo Sledgehammer?
- Yeah.
I know it's not nearly as cool
as "Ghost Fox Goddess,"
but then, I can only aspire
to your level of cool.
Which I do. Aspire to, I mean.
Take her down hard, you said, right?
Hey...
It is so great to meet you.
When I saw your traffic on the darknets,
I wasn't even sure it was you.
I mean, you've been a blank
for, well, years.
- I've been busy.
- I know, Palmer Tech.
I just figured
once you got fired, you'd...
- Figured I'd what?
- It's none of my business.
Okay, well,
I became a hacker, a hacktivist,
because of you.
The GFG.
I read about your hack of the
Department of Education, and I was, like,
"I know what I wanna be."
But then you just totally stopped
and became this, like,
information technology
support player and...
Sorry. Never meet your heroes, you know?
No, I haven't just been corporate,
you know, I've been doing work that is...
Important.
If it was, I would've heard about it.
Oh, sorry, there I go again.
I guess I was just excited
when I saw you on the darknets.
It was like...
Like you were returning, you know?
The O.G. GFG was back.
Well, I was looking for an NSA file
to exonerate an innocent man.
- John Diggle.
- Yes.
- My organization does its homework.
- Organization?
A hacktivist group,
we call ourselves Helix.
A month ago, we hacked ECHELON.
- The NSA's information gathering program?
- Mmm-hmm.
We hoovered up eight petabytes of data.
Including everything you need
to help your friend.
We're calling the data cache "Pandora."
With it, you can take down politicians,
bankrupt companies, spark revolutions.
So, you're not just
giving me the file for John?
You inspired me
to make the world a better place.
And now I intend to inspire you
to be the hacktivist you used to be,
the great Ghost Fox Goddess.
Let me guess.
You're trusting me with your mask off
so now I'm supposed to trust you?
No, I just thought that if you weren't
gonna listen to the Green Arrow,
that you might listen to Oliver Queen.
Nice to meet you.
I spent five years in hell.
Not unlike what happened to you
when you were undercover
in Sonus' organization.
Or what he put you through when
he discovered you were a cop.
And, what, you think you see
a little bit of yourself in me?
It's more than that.
There is a man in Star City
who's trying to convince me
that I destroy the lives
of everyone that I touch
because I am beyond redemption.
Yeah, and you think if you can save me
you'll prove him wrong?
- Don't put your issues on me.
- Absolutely right.
But if you think that you can take on
Sonus and his men then you are wrong.
Let us help.
Let us help, and then we're gone.
All right.
I'm reading fifteen shooters
on the roof and a helicopter inbound.
Copy, we're in position.
Shipment's late.
Some screw-up in Bludhaven.
Take a hundred grand off.
- We need to move.
- Patience.
You still have Curtis'
insurance policy with you?
Yeah, but I'm still gonna
get to use my guns, right?
Chopper's about to land, guys.
Move.
Kill 'em all!
Not so fast, dirtbag.
Yes! Yes.
They got air support.
All right, I'll take care of it.
But, Wild Dog...
I got her six.
Guess I should be flattered.
To think you've held out a candle
for me after all these years.
- What are you waiting for?
- Tina...
Don't do it. You're better than this.
You know I'm not.
If we're as alike as you said,
we both know you'd kill him.
You're right.
Maybe it's too late for me,
and maybe I don't get a second chance.
You don't have to go down that road.
Do you know what
would Vince want you to do?
He'd want me to do that.
Hey.
Let her go.
Hey. Oh, man.
I was gonna ask how
it went with the new Canary,
but I can tell by that look on your face.
- Well, I have some good news, though.
- I am in the market.
I've got all we need to exonerate John.
That's incredible. How'd you do that?
Long story.
Is there something you're not telling me?
I know that we are
not used to getting good news,
but this is what it looks like.
I am gonna go leak the file on Walker.
Why don't you go tell John the good news?
- What's going on?
- You tell him.
Tell me what?
Earlier this evening, I received
the NSA's case against Walker
- from an anonymous source.
- Anonymous?
On the strength of it,
I went to the Judge Advocate
ex parte, and got you released on bail.
Wait, what?
I filed a motion to dismiss
which is as close to
a slam dunk as these things get,
given the cards we're holding.
What does this mean?
It means that you can go home,
and hug your wife and son.
You wanted this, baited me with Yurievich.
Yes.
To see for yourself what I've become?
To remind you.
Why go to all the trouble?
Huh? What do you care?
You don't even know me.
I thought I'd proven otherwise.
General Shrieve, Baron Reiter,
Konstantine Kovar.
You keep looking for new fights
when the real fight has been
in front of you all along.
Your father literally wrote it for you,
a list of all the Yurievichs
and Kovars in Starling City.
He told me. He left me a message.
And yet you still don't return home.
Why do you deny
your father's wish for you?
You saw the reason tonight.
I am not the man that my father raised.
Not anymore.
You're afraid of what's happened to you,
of what you've become,
and you're running from it.
- How do you know all this?
- Because I've been there.
And I can help you find your way back.
You think yourself a monster.
No.
I am a monster.
There is a monster inside you,
yes, but it is not you.
I don't see the difference.
No, you need to create one.
You need to give the monster an identity.
It's only when the monster
becomes someone else,
something else,
that you're free to be Oliver Queen.
I don't know if I'm ready.
I will help you become ready.
Mr. Mayor, excuse me,
but there's someone here to see you.
Her name is Tina Boland.
Yeah, send her in, please.
Mayor Queen. It's impressive.
Maybe you should've led with that.
I gotta admit,
I didn't think I'd see you again.
Yeah, neither did I.
I guess I thought
I would feel different...
with Sonus gone.
I thought I would feel...
- Liberated.
- I wish it worked that way.
How do you do it?
How do you keep living with so much pain?
I'm still working on that myself.
But I can tell you
it helps to not be alone.
That's why you're here, right?
That's why I'm here.
Back on the roof, you asked
what Vince would have wanted.
We were more than just partners,
we were lovers.
I hated Sonus for killing Vince.
But I hated myself more
for not being able to stop him.
Rene, the guy in the hockey mask,
told the other guy
that was with us, Curtis,
that this team is all about
finding second chances.
You said maybe
we don't get second chances.
Well, maybe I was wrong.
Maybe you're my second chance.
That's a lot to put on my shoulders.
Well, Tina, there's something
that tells me you can handle it.
So about that name...
"Tina Boland" was my official cover
for undercover work.
It was to protect my family.
My real name is Dinah.
Dinah Drake.
Dinah?
Does that name mean something to you?
I had a friend named Dinah.
She's the reason I sought you out.
What do you think
she'd think about all this?
I think she'd be proud of both of us.
English - SDH