Previously on Arrow:
These waters' powers,
they have permitted me...
...to live way beyond my time.
I want you to take my place.
I want you to become
the next Ra's al Ghul.
If you insist on pursuing
this path of resistance...
...there will be consequences.
Is that a threat?
I'm the Demon's Head.
Very soon...
...your brother...
He will never take your place.
He Will.
Thea?
Thea? Oh, my God.
Thea.
I couldn't stop him.
I need an ambulance
at 455 Merced, Unit 10.
Please hurry.
All right. You're gonna be okay.
You're gonna be okay.
No, Thea, stay awake. Come on.
- Hang on. Almost there.
- How long was she like this?
- I don't know. I just found her.
- You need to stay here.
- I'm not gonna leave her.
- You need to let us work.
Get me a set of vitals.
Lift.
- Charge up to 200 joules.
- Charging.
Transfer lines.
- Clear.
- No response.
Draw up 1 milligram epi.
Charge to 200.
Charging. Ready.
Clear.
Asystole. No pulse.
- Start CPR.
- Yes, doctor.
- Pulse ox at 78.
- Come on.
Come on. Stay with us.
Come on.
Come on, come on.
We did the best we could
under the circumstances...
...but her injuries were extensive.
Even if she were to regain consciousness...
We can prolong her life
for as long as you wish...
...but it might be best
to consider other options.
I am truly sorry, Mr. Queen.
May I see her?
I'm sorry.
Oliver.
Thea.
What are they doing?
They're unloading the truck.
And, uh...
...having dinner.
General Shrieve is there.
The Alpha, the Omega.
He's combining them.
The bioweapon is armed.
- What happens now?
- He'll take it somewhere to be released.
Somewhere densely populated
where it'll have the most impact.
We need to stop that truck.
Where's Oliver?
- Come on.
- You stole a car?
I borrowed it. Come on.
Oh, my God.
Oliver.
Oliver, we came as soon as we could.
What happened?
Oliver?
They just left her there...
...to die.
Oliver, is she...?
It's bad.
What is it?
Smoke.
The League?
Screw them,
at least until we get our bearings, Oliver.
Come up with a plan.
He's won.
There is no plan.
Stay here with Thea.
Did you do this?
You could still save her.
- I don't understand.
- Take your place as Heir to the Demon...
...and Ra's al Ghul
will bring your sister back.
- What's going on?
- Where are you going?
- Away.
- You can't just leave.
- Tell us what's happening.
- There's a way for me to save her.
Thea?
- Oliver, that's not possible.
- Yes, it is.
There are waters in Nanda Parbat.
They've permitted Ra's to live
for over a hundred years.
And in rare instances...
...told in legend, those waters have been
used to restore the dead to life.
He offered to use the Lazarus Pit on Thea,
didn't he?
Lazarus, as in from the Bible, Lazarus?
The pit's real. I've seen it.
It can save Thea.
Right. But only if you become the new Ra's.
Okay, well, even if a magic hot
tub were not crazy talk...
...we're not gonna let you join
the League of Psychotic Murderers...
...even if it is to save Thea.
Which this wouldn't.
The waters change a person.
In the soul.
Even if they work,
the Thea you get back...
...will not be the one you lost.
The one we lost because of you.
- Oliver.
- I'd prefer that we didn't do...
...our usual "please don't go" dance.
We not going to. I'm coming with you.
Assuming that this works...
...someone's going to need to bring Thea
back home.
We need a way to get to Nanda Parbat.
Sorry to interrupt.
Everything all right?
Because you got that crease
between your eyebrows...
...that tells me things most definitely
are not.
Something awful has happened.
And I need a favor.
A really big favor.
Last time you asked for a big favor,
I had to loan you my helicopter.
I don't need your helicopter.
I need your jet.
Well, Oliver does. But both of us.
It's not what you think.
Well, if you're gonna fly away with him...
...then it's exactly what I think.
Ray.
Last night was a bit of an eye-opener.
Insofar as realizing something...
...you should have realized
a long time ago...
...could be considered eye-opening.
Last night,
when you were saying goodbye to Roy...
...you and Oliver...
You still have feelings for him.
When I...
...told you that I loved you
at the hospital...
...you responded with Jell-O.
Seeing you two together last night...
...I realized...
...you don't love me
because you're in love with him.
I'm sorry.
You're the last person
I ever meant to hurt.
Take the jet.
I hope the "something awful"...
...stops being awful.
What did Felicity say to Dr. Vaca?
She thinks Thea's being moved
to Central City.
You know, they do amazing things
at S.T.A.R. Labs.
Think about paying them a visit before
putting Thea on a flight to Nanda Parbat.
S.T.A.R. Labs can't save her.
Only the Lazarus Pit can.
Oliver.
Look, I know what I have done...
...doesn't seem like the actions
of a loving father, but I do love her.
She's the only child I have left.
Having said that...
...I would rather lose her forever
than subject her to the pit.
Get on the plane, Malcolm.
- You look chilly.
- Yeah.
Hm.
Thanks for letting me be here for you.
You're welcome.
- I didn't have much of a choice, did I?
- No.
I wanted to make you think
you had grown a little as a person.
I know that I've only told you a little...
...about the five years that I was away.
Well, if by a little,
you mean hardly anything.
I came back to Starling City...
...before they found me on the island.
I don't understand.
It was complicated.
I saw Thea.
She didn't see me.
She had a drug problem.
Sol...
...confronted her dealer.
And I broke his neck.
And I did it because I was angry. Sure.
But I also did it
because I felt like I was protecting her.
All I've ever wanted to do
was protect her.
Malcolm told me.
He warned me what Ra's might do.
But I never thought...
I failed.
- You got that?
- I got it.
Incoming.
Maseo, take the wheel.
You looked like you could use a hand.
It's not in here.
What is that?
It's the League.
Welcome home, Al Sah-him.
I must prepare her for the ritual.
I'll treat her as my own family.
I hope you find the accommodations
acceptable.
Such luxury is a small glimpse
of the life that awaits Oliver.
Trying to reassure me or yourself?
- I don't know what you mean.
- You're Oliver's friend.
Maseo, right?
I am Sarab.
Call yourself whatever you want.
If you gave a damn, you wouldn't work for
the man who practically killed his sister.
Oliver will be spared grief...
...in a manner that was denied to me.
And he will receive an honor
greater than you can imagine.
League of Assassins.
You're feared for your bravery...
...and power.
But all I see are a bunch of weak men
running from their lives.
Trying to escape.
That's not powerful, Maseo...
...or brave.
It's cowardly.
Do not presume to know me.
Until you've held your dying child
in your arms...
...until you've told him
everything would be okay...
...so that the last words he ever hears...
...are a lie...
...you know nothing.
I'm sorry.
What was your child's name?
Akio.
You think Akio would be proud
of his father right now?
Thea.
I've fulfilled my end
of our arrangement.
I suggest
you begin to make peace with yours.
Hey. Hey. It's okay. You're okay.
I don't know you.
Thea, it's me.
- It's Ollie.
- Ollie's dead.
Dad?
I'm here, Thea. It's me.
What's going on?
Where am I?
Someplace safe.
You are safe.
Where's Mom?
Your mother's not here.
Look...
...just lie back, close your eyes,
and get some rest, okay?
I love you, Dad.
Ra's told me that the confusion would pass.
- You have no idea what you've done.
- What I've done?
She's alive, Malcolm.
What I did saved her life.
She thinks Moira's still alive.
- She'll be fine.
- You don't know that.
Yes, I do. Because you, Diggle
and Felicity are gonna take her home...
...and she will recover.
And what is that worth?
- Felicity...
- No, this is wrong. It is just wrong.
I need to talk to you.
What is happening here is perverse.
What you're doing to Oliver...
...what you're making him do,
I'm not going to let it happen.
You can leave us.
You have a great fire within you.
- I can see now why Oliver loves you.
- If you knew the first thing about love...
...you would not be ripping Oliver
away from his family.
I am merely helping him
fulfill his destiny.
Yeah, I know all about
the "survive my sword" prophecy.
And I'm here to tell you
that I could really give a crap.
Me, and John, and God help me, Malcolm,
are not gonna let this happen.
We have friends and resources
and we will go to war to get Oliver back.
You know, many lifetimes ago...
...I loved a woman immeasurably...
...and she loved me.
We had a son...
...and then a daughter...
...and for many years, I felt
I was the most fortunate man in the world.
My life was bliss.
And then one night a man came to my door
and he gave me a horrible choice.
To leave without saying a word to them...
...or to stand and watch them
tortured and then killed.
And I left without a farewell.
And to spare them pain...
...I endured an agony worse than death.
Sounds like you gave up too easily.
There's one immutable truth about life:
It is often more cruel than it is fair.
It rarely provides an opportunity
for any of us to find closure.
And all your posturing...
...and all your threats of war...
...they merely delay the inevitable...
...causing you to forfeit
the opportunity you have...
...which was denied me.
You need to tell Oliver goodbye.
Tell him how much you love him.
Tell him whatever it is
your heart needs to express.
And do it now...
...before he is lost to you forever.
Yeah?
- Hey.
You okay? I'm sorry,
that was a stupid question, you...
You just saw your sister
come back from being dead...
...and you're about to give up
everything you love...
...so you're probably not.
I remember the first time
that I thought I'd never see Thea again.
When my father's boat went down.
But you did see her again.
And you'll see her again...
...again.
This is different.
Just been thinking about the...
...person I was...
...the brother that I was...
...and how he probably died
when that boat went down.
All this time,
I've been struggling with who I am.
You think who you're supposed to be...
...is the next Ra's al Ghul?
Honestly?
I don't know.
The only thing I can know for sure
is that everything that I've done...
...everything that happened...
...it led me right here to this moment.
And, Felicity, if that's true...
...then I don't know what it was all for.
I do.
I wish that I could change your mind
about staying here...
...but I know I can't.
Just like I know how leaving you here
is going to destroy me.
I don't regret a single moment.
And you shouldn't either.
You have done so much.
You have saved so many people's lives.
And you have changed so many
for the better...
...including mine.
Knowing you has changed my life.
You opened up my heart...
...in a way I didn't
even know was possible.
I love you.
We searched the whole truck.
There's nothing in there.
Where is the bioweapon?
Don't make me ask again.
Food cart. It's in the food cart.
Where is the food cart?
We should split up to cover more ground.
What's wrong?
I know you don't think we should do this.
You decided
we should set an example for our son.
And for ourselves.
We can't just let people die.
If we do, we are just a shell.
Not really alive at all.
So that happened.
- I'm glad it did.
- Me too.
- Heh-heh.
- What's this?
If there's any kind of God...
...something alcoholic.
Not much to toast to up here, is there?
Oh.
There's us.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
I know there's no way of avoiding this,
of getting out of here...
...of going someplace
where Ra's can't find us, but I...
Felicity...
Felicity.
What did you...?
I can't lose you.
I won't.
I stole some of the powder
that priest used on Thea.
I wasn't sure what I was gonna do
when I got it, but...
Yeah, how did you know
you were gonna lose your mind?
Or commit suicide.
Was your plan to sneak Ra's prize out
unconscious without getting us killed?
I know it's an insane idea,
but I couldn't do it.
I couldn't leave him.
- We have to get him out of here.
- Felicity, this place is like a fortress.
There's no way we're getting Oliver out
without Ra's knowing.
We can't. But you can.
- If we get caught, he'll kill all of us.
- Then we can't get caught.
I've seen enough movies to know that the
scary fortress always has a secret exit.
You were Ra's' right-hand stooge for years.
If anyone knows the way out, it's you.
- So don't even try to play games with me.
- The catacombs.
It's rough terrain.
It is not gonna be easy.
- How do we get there?
- Through the temple.
Go get Thea.
Meet us here in five minutes.
Go.
- Which way?
- Temple's this way. Come on.
- There's not much time. Hurry.
- Why are you helping us?
Because if I don't, then I am just a shell.
You reminded me of that.
Thirty meters down, the path forks.
- Take the left passage.
- Come on.
These tunnels are centuries old.
Stay close.
- You need to stop and rest for a minute?
- No.
Maseo said stay left.
- Thea?
- No.
- No, no. No.
- We have to move. Now.
Too late.
Believe me,
we do not want to be taken alive.
Hold.
I am Al Sah-him. Wah-reeth al Ghul...
...Heir to the Demon, and you will obey.
Put your weapons down.
Now.
Tell Ra's I will return shortly.
Oliver, please.
Thank you for trying.
I love you all the more for it.
But this only ends one way.
This is as far as I go.
- The jet's less than a mile away.
- Where are we gonna fly to?
I don't understand.
Malcolm is gonna take you home.
Aren't you coming with?
Not now.
You go on, I'll catch up.
I love you, Thea.
Don't ever forget that, okay?
Oliver...
Oliver, I don't know what to say.
I do.
John, you're the best man I've ever known.
Whatever happens...
...you're my brother.
I'm afraid I will never forgive myself
for leaving you here.
You told me once...
...that life is precious.
And that you wanted more
than I could offer you.
Don't give up on that.
The only way that I'm gonna survive this...
...is if I know that you're out there...
...living your life, happy.
We're always saying goodbye to each other.
You'd think I'd be good at it by now.
Well, let's not say goodbye this time.
What...? What's going on?
Everything's fine, Thea. You're okay.
If you're here, then I'm not.
At least you're feeling
more like yourself again.
What do you want?
Where's Ollie?
Thea, do you remember anything
about the past few days?
I... I was here.
And Ra's, he...
- He attacked me.
- No, Thea. He nearly killed you.
- Where is my brother?
- That is... That is what I'm trying to explain.
To save you, Oliver had to join the League.
- He... He traded his life for yours.
- No.
No.
I am sorry.
I know you hate me,
and you have every right...
...but I'm gonna make up for that,
for everything.
- That's not possible.
- Yes, it is.
The League isn't after us anymore.
I am free.
I could go anywhere in the world,
but this is where I want to be.
Here, with my daughter.
You took care of me when I was injured.
Now, please, Thea, please...
...let me take care of you.
Sorry to interrupt.
- Is everything all right?
- No, it's not.
- Felicity?
- Oliver's...
He's gone.
- What are you talking about?
- He joined the League.
He's not coming back.
Shh.
Blood has been shed. League blood.
And that is a transgression
punishable by death.
And yet you allowed your friends
safe passage home.
Tell me why
I should not hunt these people down...
...and stain my blade with their blood.
Because I stayed.
I'm honoring our agreement.
Now no one close to me
will ever be harmed again.
And your allies would not have been able
to escape through the catacombs...
...without assistance,
so you tell me who aided you...
...who this traitor is.
- I don't know.
- Me.
I struck down three of our number.
For my betrayal...
...I offer you my life.
You did not betray me tonight, Sarab.
Maseo Yamashiro did.
For a moment, your old life took hold...
...but by coming here and kneeling
before me, you have proven your loyalty.
And I will not spill Sarab's blood
for Mase0's actions.
Stand up.
Your service will be vital
in the coming weeks.
Oliver will need you for
his transformation.
And like Sarab...
...vestiges of your old
identity still remain.
Oliver Queen must be extinguished
from memory.
StOp!
Give me the vial.
The word "assassin" has fallen victim
to many abuses of language...
...its real meaning hidden
beneath a sediment...
...of lies and falsehoods.
In truth, "assassin"
comes from hashishiyya...
...which means
"those who stand apart from society."
Now...
...every man and woman in here
have renounced their past life...
...and forfeited their identity
in the name of something new.
And it is a cleansing
only achieved by fire.
Embrace the pain...
...for it is your soul
finally being unburdened.
Oliver Queen is dead...
...eventually to be reborn as Ra's al Ghul.
And for now, only the Arrow...
...Al Sah-him, shall remain.
Al Sah-him...
...Heir to the Demon.