I can do this. I can do this.
I can so totally do this.
Yes, you can.
But either way, we've got you.
There's no pressure here, Ms. Smoak.
Curtis's implant
is the longest of long shots.
I was expecting
a little more encouragement
from the husband of the genius
who invented the thing. (CHUCKLES)
My man works miracles with technology,
but the human body
doesn't play by the same rules.
Well... (BREATHING HEAVILY) Here we go...
Here we go.
Here we go. Here we go.
Here we're going.
-(FELICITY GRUNTS)
-Oh. Okay. It's okay.
Got you. Got you. Got you. Here you go.
(PANTING) Well, that went nowhere.
-PAUL: Curtis ever tell you how we met?
-Mmm-mmm.
He came in with Achilles tendinitis.
He was training
to qualify for the Olympics,
so all he cared about was results.
Mmm.
Took me weeks just to get him focused
on what really mattered.
How handsome his therapist was? (CHUCKLES)
Healing.
You got to be patient with yourself.
These things take time.
(CHUCKLES)
Are you sure what Conklin told you
was the truth?
Conklin was dying.
He had no reason to lie.
Whatever Reiter has planned,
he is gonna kill everyone here.
Mr. Queen. It appears we are
within striking distance of my prize.
I want you both at my side
when I claim it.
I don't give a damn
about your superstitious crusade.
Nevertheless,
you'll both bear witness to its fruition.
You okay?
Me?
I knew you were gonna ask me
so I thought I'd beat you to the punch.
(CHUCKLES) Are you okay?
A guy, a brilliant guy,
says he can put a microchip
in my spine and I will walk again.
I'm enough of a geek
to know science fiction when I see it.
You're still disappointed.
-Yeah. You know. Stupid.
-No.
Talk to me.
I wanted to be able to
walk down the aisle on our wedding day.
(CHUCKLES)
(DARHK CLAPS)
Aw, you two just melt my stone cold heart.
You almost made me believe in love again.
Nice to see you, Mr. Queen.
How was your Christmas?
-You son of a bitch...
-Ooh. Oh. You're so brave
for a political candidate
and reformed party boy.
Oh, sorry about the limo.
Love the wheelchair,
might I suggest motorized.
(GRUNTS AND EXHALES)
We have extremely powerful friends.
You do not know who you're messing with.
If it makes you happy,
the "messing" ends today.
I tried to bring you
into the fold, Mr. Queen.
I tried to kidnap
your nearest and dearest.
I tried to kill you but none of that took.
Like she said,
you don't know who you're messing with.
I suspect that is true.
But as they say, well, or should,
the fourth time is the charm.
(PHONE CHIMES)
Go ahead. Take a look. I'll wait.
William thinks that I'm friends
with his mother. Funny.
Anywho, 6:00 on Friday
you're going to hold a press conference
and drop out of the mayoral race.
Oh, that's 6:00 p.m., by the way.
I'll be at home watching you
from my brand new television.
What did he show you on your phone?
Who's William?
He's my son.
Please say something.
-Look, Felicity, I can explain...
-Stop.
I cannot hear another lie.
You know, it's more complicated than that.
God, Oliver, you are
the only person on the planet
that considers the truth "complicated."
Just to be clear,
I don't care that you have a child.
I can't believe that you have a child
that you didn't tell me about.
What does it say about our relationship
if your first instinct is to
always hide the truth?
William's mother made a condition
that the only way
I would be allowed to meet my son
is if I agree to keep him secret.
Even from you.
Who even makes that kind of ultimatum?
I just don't...
A mother who is trying to protect her son.
And she thought
that the best thing for him
was to keep his world separate from mine.
After everything that's happened,
can you really say that she was wrong?
Well, it didn't work, did it?
Somehow Darhk still found out.
Hey, we got your 911.
FELICITY: Darhk paid us a visit.
He's holding a 10-year-old boy hostage.
Says that he'll release him
if Oliver drops out of the mayoral race.
OLIVER: Just get in touch with Alex.
Have him schedule
a press conference for Friday at 6:00 p.m.
You are not actually
going for this, are ya?
(SIGHS) The boy Darhk has,
William, he's my son.
FELICITY: Yeah, I just found out, too.
Apparently, the only two people that knew
about William were Oliver and Darhk.
Actually, I found out, too. Uh...
Um, what's our next plan?
-William lives in Central City, right?
-Yep.
I will call Barry.
See what the CCPD can do.
Is it okay that I tell Barry
that William is your...
(CHUCKLES) Barry knows, too.
Let's also get in touch with Malcolm.
He has an axe to grind
after what happened with the League
and, uh, Malcolm knows, as well.
Maybe it would be easier to list the
people who don't know about your son.
(PHONE CHIMES)
(CLEARS THROAT) Samantha's here.
-Who's Samantha?
-It's William's mother.
Alex?
She said her name was Samantha Clayton.
The name struck a bell
from the million-dollar check
you told Thea wasn't gonna be a problem.
It's not gonna be a problem.
Okay.
Then why did I just get
a 911 text from Thea
telling me that you're
pulling out of the race?
Have you heard from William?
Do you know where he is?
I don't, but I'm doing everything I can.
(SIGHS) I knew it.
I knew the second I realized he was gone,
I knew that you had to have
some sort of involvement in this.
My God, what was I thinking
letting you get into his life?
Two months later, and he's missing...
Samantha, I need you
to tell me exactly what happened.
No, Oliver. You need to tell me
what the hell is going on
and you need to give me
my son back right now.
I'm trying but you need to tell me
what happened. Please.
(SAMANTHA SOBBING)
I went upstairs to get him for dinner,
and he was gone.
Gone.
No, no note, no sign of struggle.
Just vanished.
I called the CCPD,
and they've been looking everywhere,
but it's already been 48 hours
and still nothing.
But then a crime scene technician
pulled me aside,
and said that I needed to
talk to you about this.
Barry Allen?
Yes, that's the one.
-Oliver, you promised.
-I...
You promised me that you
wouldn't tell anyone about my son...
Barry figured it...
That's not what's important right now.
What's important is that
I am going to do everything,
and I mean absolutely everything,
in my power, and we will get him back.
What can you do, Oliver?
What can you do, that the entire
police force hasn't been able to do?
Samantha...
I'm the Green Arrow.
This doesn't make sense.
Well, like I said,
I'm not the person that I used to be.
Samantha, these are my friends and
they are going to help us find William.
You probably remember...
Laurel Lance?
I'm so sorry that
you're going through this, Samantha.
We will help you get William back.
Look, Laurel, it was one time.
And, I knew that you and Oliver
were together,
but I was young and stupid and selfish.
And I should have been honest with you.
No, Oliver should have been.
Come on.
Does CCPD have anything?
No. It was a clean grab.
(SIGHS) Do we have any other angles
we can work? Other than Malcolm.
Finding William isn't the problem.
Beating Damien Darhk is.
Every time we've faced him,
we have been beaten. Thoroughly.
It's because
we can't go against his magic.
We just need to fight harder,
we need to fight smarter...
No, Oliver.
Insanity is doing the same thing
over and over again
and expecting a different result.
-We need a new strategy.
-What about Constantine?
-He's in hell.
-Really? What's going on?
I mean, he's actually literally in Hell.
Oh.
But I might know someone else.
Her name is Mari McCabe.
She possesses a totem
which is powered by magic.
She calls herself Vixen.
What the hell was that thing?
Cerico doesn't pay us enough to find out.
(GUNSHOTS)
(GROWLING)
(SNARLING)
(GUNSHOTS)
Come on out. Face us like a man.
WOMAN: I've got a better idea...
How about I kick your ass
like a woman instead?
(GROWLS)
(GRUNTS)
-I had that under control.
-I know.
What, not enough in Star City
to keep you busy?
I need your help.
I have got to get me one of these.
-Mari.
-Laurel, hey.
-It's good to see you.
-You, too.
Mari, this is John Diggle
and my sister, Thea.
Pleasure.
It's nice to meet you. Sorry it's under
such horrible circumstances.
You spoke to Felicity on the phone.
-Hey.
-MARI: Hey.
And, this is Samantha. William's mother.
She's a friend.
The hero in Detroit they call "Vixen."
Mari and I had an...
Animated encounter last year
and we've stayed in touch ever since.
How are you going to help me find my son?
With magic.
Magic?
Yeah. It's a long story
but the short version is that
this totem gives me the ability
to channel the ashe
or the spirit of any animal.
Do you have anything
of William's with you?
Yes, I do. Just this. It's his favorite.
Don't you dare tell Barry about this.
He's in the city. I think I can find him.
Okay, good. Dig and I will cover you.
Laurel, get in touch with your father,
we're gonna loop in the SCPD.
Felicity, I need you to...
Would it be all right
if you sat with Samantha?
Working up a search profile. Sure.
Thank you. Thea...
Yeah, Malcolm's coming over.
I'll go talk to him.
We're going to find him.
And he's going to be okay.
Okay.
Can you feel it? The energy. Primordial.
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
What is that?
Destiny, Mr. Queen.
-(EXPLOSION)
-(ALL GRUNTING)
(SPEAKING IN ARAMAIC)
(SIGHS) I know you're here.
There's no need to lurk in the shadows
like the boogey man.
You haven't seen me in a while.
And, I'm not the man I used to be.
Yeah, I know. They told me.
Not pretty, is it?
Mmm. It could have been a lot worse.
-Could've chopped your head off.
-And I would've been better off for it.
He took the League away from me
and gave it to Nyssa al Ghul.
And that was more important
than saving your daughter's life?
Yeah, heard about
that part of the story, too.
Refusing to bargain with
Nyssa to save me...
My intention was to save your life
and to keep my seat of power,
for the betterment of the world.
Did you tell Darhk about Ollie's son?
Do you really think
I would do something like that?
Just answer the question.
No. No, I won't.
Because you should know me better
than to ask me the question.
I know you all too well.
You should know one thing, Thea.
No matter what happens,
I will always love you.
It's what fathers do.
It is a crazy world we live in, huh?
Metahumans. Magic. Oliver Queen, father.
-I'm sorry I didn't tell you.
-No man, I totally get it.
Samantha put you in a tough spot.
That couldn't have been
an easy decision for you,
and I totally get why you made it.
She was right. William was safer
when I didn't know about him.
-So maybe if I never found out I...
-You can't even go there, man.
You'll eat yourself up inside with,
the "what if this" or "maybe that."
It's part of being a parent.
Most important thing now is focusing on
getting your boy back home safe.
John, how do you do it?
I know where Sarah is every night, Oliver.
I know what she's doing, who she is with.
She sees my face every single day.
I'm there for her.
And she knows, and I know,
that I would never let
anything bad happen to her.
I kept her close, man, and that's
how you keep your children safe.
He was wearing a blue hoodie. Plaid shirt.
Gray corduroys. And um, a Diamonds
baseball cap. He's a big fan.
Oliver likes baseball, too.
Here's hoping the innate
fatherly influence stops there.
Um, does he have any
distinguishing features?
Freckles, birthmarks, anything like that?
Oliver told me that
there was someone in his life.
Someone special.
He said her name was Felicity.
He wanted to tell you
and I wouldn't let him.
I didn't know who he was now.
I didn't know what kind of person he was.
It's going around.
Just try and remember that I was the one
that made him choose
between you and knowing his son.
All right. I've got the whole force,
what's left of them anyway,
canvassing for William.
Thank you.
You don't seem as surprised as I expected.
What, that party boy Oliver Queen
knocked up some girl?
I'm amazed there's not an army of
little Oliver's running around out there.
Well, there may be.
He certainly got around back then.
Yeah. (EXHALES) You okay?
I don't know. It's the mother, Samantha.
Um, she was with him when I was with him.
(SIGHS) Oh, baby...
I don't know why it still stings.
It was a million years ago
and it's not like I didn't know
that Oliver cheated on me.
Yeah. But that's one thing.
Knowing he had a kid...
I'm sorry, sweetheart. Oh, come here.
Thank you.
(PHONE VIBRATING)
(SNIFFLES)
It's Oliver. He knows where
William's is being held.
I count four guards patrolling the roof.
Mari's in position.
(GREEN ARROW GRUNTS)
(GUNSHOTS)
(CHUCKLES)
I wondered how long it would take for
your buddy Oliver to drag you into this.
-Where is the boy?
-Oh, he's fine.
I had him moved about two minutes before
you and your posse
disturbed my evening in.
You know what, you might want to
learn to be a bit more discreet.
Have you considered
black instead of green?
You tell me where you've taken him.
Or what? You'll fire an arrow at me?
I think we've seen that movie before.
I win. You lose. Rinse, repeat.
This time is different.
Oh, really?
Where is the boy?
(LAUGHS) You have some
very interesting friends.
(GRUNTS)
My, my... I haven't seen that trinket
in a dog's age.
M'Changa province, am I right?
Stay.
Oh, I like you.
And I don't like many people.
(GRUNTING)
I got you.
What happened? Where did he go?
-I can't track him.
-Darhk is protected by magic.
No, not just Darhk. I've lost William.
Where is William? What happened?
We had a small setback.
But we're not giving up.
-Setback, what do you mean?
-(PHONE VIBRATES)
Hey. Blocked ID.
Hello.
DARHK: (ON PHONE)
Oh, hi, Oliver. How's your evening going?
Mine, somewhat eventful.
Some of your friends stopped by my place
earlier, completely unannounced.
Very rude.
I want to talk to my son, Darhk.
I want to know that he's safe.
Oh, this must be the first time
your son's been kidnapped
because clearly you don't understand
how these things work.
I make the demands.
Well, you've made them. And I've agreed.
Friday night I'm dropping out of the race.
Why wait? Give your green friend
less time to botch things up.
So, go find yourself a television camera.
I want to know whether my son is safe.
Oh, and by the way, you are going to
completely endorse Ruvé Adams,
save us all the trouble
of those pesky little write-in ballots.
(SIGHS) He moved up the timetable.
He wants me to drop out of the race
tonight. Thea, let Alex know.
MARI: I'm so sorry.
I know you brought me here
to fight magic with magic but I...
Mari, this is not on you.
There's still so much that we
don't know about Darhk's power.
We don't... We don't even know
what the source of it is.
Wait. I get my powers from this necklace.
Without it, I'm just
a wannabe fashion designer
who lives at home with her foster dad.
So, up to now everyone
I've gone up against with mystical powers
has had some sort of a totem like mine.
What if Darhk has an object
that helps him with his magic?
I think he does.
I walked in on him once or twice
in front of this cabinet thing.
And inside, there's some kind of,
I don't know, idol.
-Can you draw it for me?
-Well, yeah, I'll give it a whirl.
Okay, Oliver, what if this little
art project doesn't yield any results?
-Well...
-And what if it takes too long?
Mari and Captain Lance are working
on a way to eventually stop Darhk.
Right now, I have to save William.
(SPEAKING IN ARAMAIC)
REITER: What's he saying?
Whatever it is, it's not good.
(GUNFIRE)
(SPEAKING IN ARAMAIC)
We have to get out of here now.
Reiter, what are you doing?
Proving what I know about you is true.
You can't leave us in here with it!
Reiter.
You...
You are worthy to pass.
Good evening. Thank you
for coming on such short notice.
When I entered this race,
it was because no one else
was willing to step into the spotlight.
It has always been my hope
that my actions would inspire others.
Four months later and they have.
Knowing that, effective immediately,
I will be suspending my campaign
and throwing my full support
behind Ruvé Adams.
Now, I'd like to take a moment to thank
all my supporters for all your hard work.
What you've done will not be forgotten.
-Thank you.
-(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
New numbers are out.
You were leading by 16 points.
Alex, I'm sorry.
I know that you put your heart and soul
into this campaign and...
And your days of speech-making
are now behind you.
Look, man, I don't want a "sorry."
-I just want an explanation.
-That's why I'm sorry.
(SIGHS)
Sucks when you can't tell the truth.
Samantha told me about her ultimatum.
I just figured that
eventually she'd trust me.
Yeah, you'd work your
Oliver Queen charm...
I didn't want to be
a part of William's life
without the opportunity
for you to be a part of his life.
John has made it pretty clear that, uh,
I should've made more of an effort
to be a part of William's life.
And that the best way to keep him safe
would've been to keep him close.
Even with all of this.
Your resignation's all over the news.
Have you heard from Darhk?
-Not yet.
-(PHONE CHIMES)
Speak of the devil. Literally.
It's not Darhk. It's Mari.
She has something.
I emailed Captain Lance's
drawing of Darhk's idol
to a friend of mine at Detroit University.
THEA: And did he recognize it?
It's a khushu idol.
Very rare. Very powerful.
But its power requires
a constant connection
to one of the Earth's ley lines.
I never thought I'd say this but, huh?
Okay. Think Wi-Fi for magic.
And the idol is his Internet connection.
If Professor Macalester's theory
is correct, and this map is accurate...
Then Darhk must be holed up
near one of these ley lines,
in order for him to
get the strongest signal.
I'll start cross-referencing all the
locations that we've encountered Darhk...
You pulled out of the race.
Why isn't this man giving me my son back?
He will, and everything will be fine.
You keep saying that
but it hasn't been yet.
You're doing everything you possibly can.
You can't beat yourself up about it.
Well, you don't know me very well, do you?
Just before Christmas, Darhk took Thea,
Felicity, John, held them captive.
We agreed that I would
trade myself for them.
I did and Darhk didn't live up
to his end of the bargain.
So you're worried
that's playing itself out again now?
We're going to get William back, Oliver.
But when we do,
I think you should consider
that maybe letting him go
isn't such a bad thing.
What do you mean?
Well, I heard what you told Felicity.
About keeping him close.
Owl ears.
Uh, I never knew my real parents.
I grew up in a foster home
and my whole life I wondered, who am I?
Where did I come from?
Why didn't my real parents want me?
A boy should know who his father is.
He should. And he will.
But knowing what William
is going through right now,
I realize that I wasn't ready
for the answers.
Learning about my heritage, my powers,
the evil my mother fled our homeland
to protect me from?
No child should have to carry that burden.
I mean, look around you, Oliver.
The best gift you can give him
is his childhood.
To keep as far away from your world
for as long as possible.
(SIGHS)
I can't imagine a greater sacrifice.
But isn't that what parenthood is?
Hey, guys, I think we've found something.
Darhk moves his idol around,
which makes sense but...
-It makes him a whole lot harder to track.
-Right.
But after referencing a butt-load of
satellite feed thermal imaging data
and the ley line map, I think Darhk is
located out in a compound in Sky Woods.
-(PHONE VIBRATES)
-Hello?
Very good speech.
You look great on television.
Nelson Plaza. Three hours.
William will be there.
Darhk says he's going to release William
three hours from now at Nelson Plaza.
There is no guarantee with Darhk.
This could be a trap.
And now we have a chance to
take out his power idol thingy.
Ollie, without his magic,
he won't be able to do this to anybody
ever again. It will be game over.
Samantha, he's your son. It's your call.
He's your son, too, Oliver.
Get him back.
And take this son of a bitch Darhk out.
VIXEN: I count 17 Ghosts.
Copy. Black Canary?
Ready.
-Spartan?
-I'm set.
FELICITY: Let's do this.
(MEN GROANING)
Vixen, you're up.
(SCREECHING)
(DARHK CHUCKLES)
I'm guessing your insurance
won't pay for that.
Cute. Buh-bye.
(GRUNTS)
When you're dead, I'll make sure
that totem gets put to better use.
Took the words right out of my mouth.
Well... That happened.
Speedy, Canary, I can't get a clear shot.
Where are you?
BLACK CANARY: On our way.
(MEN GRUNTING)
Find William. I'll take care of Darhk.
I'm sorry. I can't hear you with your
throats closing up like that. Steady.
(GROANS)
I've got the totem. Has it had any effect?
Separating it from Darhk
didn't do anything. Go to Plan B.
What's Plan B?
(GROWLING)
(GRUNTS)
(DARHK LAUGHS)
(GASPS)
Please, don't hurt them...
William.
(SCREAMING)
(GRUNTS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(SIRENS WAILING)
GREEN ARROW: Get out of here.
-Mom!
-SAMANTHA: William.
(SIGHS) Oh, honey.
Medics checked him out.
He's in perfect health.
Oh, thank goodness.
There's someone here
that you must have missed.
What's wrong?
I'm kind of over The Flash.
I want a Green Arrow action figure.
Well, the Green Arrow is pretty amazing...
I'll let you guys get reacquainted. Hey.
Is everything okay?
Detectives questioned William while
the docs were checking him out.
Darhk didn't take him.
It was a guy with a missing hand.
You son of a bitch.
I assure you, Mr. Queen,
I had all the faith in the world
that you would survive.
Yeah? Well, what about everybody else?
You are my only concern.
We've gotten this far because of you,
let's finish it.
You too, Ms. Venediktov.
Mr. Queen seems to behave at his best
when you're around.
Is William going to be okay?
Yeah, he's a tough one.
(EXHALES) Just like his dad.
Could not have done this without you.
-Thank you.
-Anytime.
Have you thought any more
about what I said?
You know, I just got him back...
Let me just say,
for all the frustrations I have
about my real parents giving me up,
I'm so grateful
I was raised in a situation
where that was my biggest issue in life.
The best thing my parents ever gave me
was that freedom.
Well, that, and this totem
that makes me a total badass.
You don't need a totem for that.
Damn right, I don't.
You take care of yourself, Oliver.
I'm just a phone call away.
Me, too, Mari. Me, too.
I heard you found the boy.
You can't believe how relieved I am.
-Cut the crap.
-Excuse me?
I know it was you.
You took him. Out of spite.
For us. You have to believe me,
I did it for us.
You purposely...
You put him in danger. How?
You know what? I'm not doing this anymore.
This song and dance where
you come over to my apartment
and you whisper your lies is over.
Thea, I did it to protect us.
Shut up. How could you possibly think
that there was an "us" to protect?
You know, sometimes I lay awake at night
and I wonder what Robert would
think about our relationship.
He raised me. He loved me.
And I threw that all away
the moment I became your daughter.
Yes. Yes, you did. And it was your choice.
And I wish I never did.
Don't you dare speak to me like that.
You would be dead ten times over
if not for me.
I taught you how to fight,
how to be strong.
I turned you from a delicate, spoiled brat
into a warrior.
And all I've ever gotten from you
in return is your venomous spite.
For a very good reason.
You have no idea what you're up against.
You are incapable of seeing
the bigger picture. But I can.
And I would rather you hate me
and be alive, than love me and be dead.
Hi, William.
I hope you're well.
And I hope you're safe.
There is something
that I want to tell you.
I wanted to tell you before, but...
(SIGHS) But this is better.
I'm your father. Biologically, that is.
As far as really being your father goes...
I haven't earned that yet.
A father should be there for his child,
every day, no matter what.
To make sure that they feel loved,
that they feel safe.
And a child should be
able to rely on their father
and go to him for guidance,
and reassurance.
I have failed to do that for you.
And now I'm going to tell you why.
I'm the Green Arrow.
And my life is very dangerous.
Which is why
we decided to keep you out of it,
for all of these years.
What happened to you in Star City,
that was my fault,
and I can't allow anything like that
to happen ever again.
And that is why I have
asked your mother to move you far away
and to not tell anyone
where she's taking you. Including me.
It's also why I asked her to wait
to show you this message
until after your 18th birthday.
I wanted to give you a real childhood.
I wanted to give you that gift.
Goodbye, Son.
I sure hope it's not forever.
How much of that did you hear?
-Enough.
-(SIGHS)
Oliver, we need to talk.
About a number of things, I suspect.
Let's start with...
I can't do this.
When your son was in danger,
I had to table what I was feeling
about everything.
But now that I've had some space,
I realize I need space.
Felicity.
I know the position Samantha put you in.
I know it was an impossible decision.
But you were right,
you should have told me.
Marriage is about inclusion.
It's about leaning on your partner
when things get complicated.
I don't think that you know
how to do that.
I'm trying.
And now you're sending William away
and I understand why.
You know that I do, but once again,
you have left me out of the decision.
Felicity?
-Oh, my God...
-Oh, my God.