PREVIOUSLY ON "ARROW"...
-WHAT HAPPENED?
-GREGOR...HIS LOYALTY LIES
WITH KOVAR,
BUT GREGOR IS
PAKHAN.
THERE IS NOTHING
WE CAN DO.
WE CAN KILL HIM.
OLIVER: THESE CORRUPT COPS ARE
TAKING DOWN BIG DRUG SCORES.
YOU SAID YOU'RE
NOT A CRIMINAL,
THAT YOU BELIEVE
IN JUSTICE.
ASK YOURSELF,
WARNER, IS THAT
STILL THE CASE?
WHAT ARE THE ODDS
OF OLIVER QUEEN
AND THE GREEN ARROW
BEING IN RUSSIA
AT THE SAME TIME?
VERY GOOD IF
OLIVER QUEEN IS
THE GREEN ARROW.
FELICITY: 4 YEARS AGO,
THE HOOD TOOK DOWN
JUSTIN CLAYBOURNE.
I HAVE BEEN WORKING
ON A LOCATION
FOR CLAYBOURNE'S MISTRESS.
PROMETHEUS' MOTHER.
WE FIND HER...
WE FIND A NAME FOR
THE SON OF A BITCH.
THANKS FOR COMING ALONG.
I KNOW THAT BEING
MY BODY MAN ISN'T
YOUR JOB ANYMORE.
SURE IT IS.
JUST A DIFFERENT
SUIT, THAT'S ALL.
NOW WE'RE SURE THIS
IS THE ADDRESS?
YEAH, FELICITY IS.
ACCORDING TO HER,
THIS IS THE HOUSE THAT
JUSTIN CLAYBOURNE BOUGHT
FOR HIS MISTRESS.
THINK SHE'LL PLAY BALL?
-THAT DEPENDS?
-ON WHAT?
WHETHER OR NOT SHE KNOWS
HER SON IS PROMETHEUS.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
-AMANDA WESTFIELD?
-YES.
HI. UH, MY NAME IS
OLIVER...
I KNOW WHO YOU ARE,
MAYOR OF STAR CITY.
MAY I COME IN?
VERY LOVELY HOME.
FOR THE PAST SEVERAL
MONTHS, UH...
THERE HAS BEEN
A SERIAL MURDERER
THAT HAS BEEN
TERRORIZING STAR CITY.
THERE IS REASON TO
BELIEVE THAT THIS
INDIVIDUAL
IS YOUR SON.
I HAVEN'T SEEN MY SON
SINCE JUSTIN CLAYBOURNE'S
FUNERAL.
BUT YOU KNOW HE'S
BECOME SOMETHING ELSE,
SOMEONE ELSE.
IT'S WHY YOU LIVE HERE
FAR AWAY FROM STAR CITY.
I MOVED AWAY BECAUSE
THERE WAS NOTHING
LEFT FOR ME THERE.
MS. WESTFIELD, YOUR SON
IS AN INCREDIBLY CAPABLE
AND INCREDIBLY DANGEROUS
INDIVIDUAL.
HE HAS ERASED VIRTUALLY
ALL TRACES
OF HIS IDENTITY
FROM THE INTERNET,
AND I AM...
WELL, I AM HERE SIMPLY
TO ASK YOU FOR HIS NAME.
AND WHAT HAPPENS
WHEN YOU FIND HIM?
HE NEEDS HELP.
HE...I WANT HIM TO
GET THAT HELP.
WHAT YOU WANT...
IS TO CAGE HIM UP
LIKE AN ANIMAL,
LIKE THE ANIMAL
WHO KILLED HIS FATHER.
HE PUT AN ARROW
IN HIS CHEST.
WHAT KIND OF MONSTER
DOES THAT?
WHATEVER MY SON
IS DOING,
HE IS DOING IT
BECAUSE HE IS HURT
AND HE IS SCARED,
AND I WILL NOT HELP YOU
DESTROY HIS LIFE.
INNOCENT PEOPLE
ARE DYING,
AND YOU MIGHT BE
OUR ONLY CHANCE
TO SAVE THEM.
GET OUT OF MY HOUSE.
I'M EASILY REACHABLE IF
YOU CHANGE YOUR MIND.
I WON'T.
HEY! GET BACK
TO YOUR SEAT!
CUPID: CAN'T A GIRL
STRETCH HER LEGS A LITTLE?
SORRY. I DIDN'T CATCH
YOUR NAME.
GUARD: AND YOU'RE NOT
GOING TO!
GUARDS AREN'T ALLOWED
TO FRATERNIZE WITH
PRISONERS.
SO TAKE ME OUT
OF THESE CUFFS,
AND I WON'T BE
A PRISONER ANYMORE.
SOUNDS FUN,
BUT I'D LOSE MY JOB.
[GAGGING]
HOW ABOUT YOUR LIFE
INSTEAD?
[BONES CRACK]
THIS IS YOUR STOP, LADIES!
COME ON, LADIES.
GO!
NEXT PHASE?
STAR CITY.
TIME TO RETURN HOME.
HOW'D IT GO WITH
MAMA PROMETHEUS?
IT DIDN'T.
SHE'S PROBABLY
PROTECTING HIM.
CURTIS: WOW. MY MOM
COULD BARELY HANDLE
ME BEING GAY.
OLIVER: SAYS SHE HASN'T
SEEN HIM IN OVER 4 YEARS,
BUT MAYBE
THEY E-MAILED.
WHAT IS THAT?
JUST A LITTLE TOY
THAT CURTIS AND I
WHIPPED UP
IN CASE THE PROMETHEUS
APPLE DIDN'T FALL
TOO FAR
FROM THE TREE.
IT'S A SNIFFER DEVICE.
IT BASICALLY PULLS
ELECTRONIC DATA
FROM ANY HARD DRIVES
OR DEVICES NEARBY.
-DID IT WORK?
-OH, YEAH!
UH, A LITTLE TOO WELL.
I GOT A PETABYTE
WORTH OF DATA HERE.
IT'S GONNA TAKE ME
A WHILE TO WORK THROUGH.
WHICH IS FINE
BECAUSE SOMETHING
HAPPENED
WHILE YOU AND JOHN
WERE AWAY.
-WHAT?
-CHECK IT OUT.
THOSE ARE SOME
FAMILIAR FACES.
OLIVER: WHAT HAPPENED?
JAILBREAK LED
BY LIZA WARNER.
CURTIS: DIDN'T YOU PUT
CHINA WHITE IN PRISON,
LIKE, FOREVER AGO?
YEAH. A COUPLE TIMES.
WHY DOES SHE LOOK
SO FAMILIAR?
JOHN: MAYBE SHE
ARRESTED YOU ONCE.
SHE USED TO BE
A COP.
WARNER WAS, TOO.
LANCE CONVINCED HER
TO TURN OVER A NEW LEAF,
WHICH I'M GUESSING
THAT THESE LADIES CONVINCED
HER TO TURN BACK OVER.
DINAH: WELL, ACCORDING
TO THE PRISONERS,
THEY TOOK THE CORRECTIONS
DEPARTMENT BUS,
AND THEY'RE HEADED
TOWARDS STAR CITY.
LET'S GET TO WORK
ON FINDING THEM.
-WE HAVE TO GO.
-YEAH.
HEY. YOU READY
FOR YOUR BIG MOMENT?
OH, IT'S JUST
A SWEARING IN CEREMONY.
WELL, YOU'RE GONNA BE
A COP AGAIN, DINAH.
IT'S NO SMALL THING.
YEAH. GUESS IT'S NOT.
MAN: THE CITY COUNCIL
WANTED ME TO REMIND YOU
THEY HAVE A VOTE SCHEDULED
RIGHT AFTER THE SCPD'S
SWEARING IN CEREMONY.
RIGHT, RIGHT, RIGHT.
THEY'RE GONNA WANT TO
GET THIS SHOW
ON THE ROAD.
IT TOTALLY GET IT. HI.
I'M GONNA NEED
A...A MINUTE
OR TWO, PLEASE.
HI.
HEY. COME HERE.
-WHAT WAS THAT FOR?
-THAT WAS "I'M SORRY."
FOR CANCELING DINNER
ON ME LAST NIGHT.
AND THE PREVIOUS
TWO TIMES THAT I ALSO
CANCELED DINNER, YES.
MM-HMM. DOES THIS MEAN
I'LL GET TO SEE YOU TONIGHT?
DO YOU WANT TO HAVE
DINNER WITH THE CITY
COMPTROLLER, TOO?
-AM I EVER GONNA SEE YOU AGAIN?
-OF COURSE.
OK.
IS EVERYTHING OK?
YEAH, I THINK SO.
YEAH, YEAH, YES.
NO. NO. DEFINITELY NOT.
UH...
WHATEVER IT IS,
JUST, UM...LAY IT ON ME.
WHAT'S UP?
ARE YOU THE GREEN ARROW?
YEAH.
REALLY?
NO. HEH.
NO. I'M SORRY.
I THOUGHT THAT YOU WERE
DOING A JOKING THING.
I...SO I DID
A JOKING THING BACK.
ARE YOU NOT?
I WAS WORKING
ON A DIFFERENT STORY,
AND, UH, WELL, SOME
THINGS CAME UP
THAT RELATE TO YOU.
AND THEN YOU JUST
IMMEDIATELY JUMPED
TO THE MOST INSANE
CONCLUSION POSSIBLE.
SO THAT'S...THAT'S
A NO FOR THE RECORD?
NO. FOR THE RECORD.
WELL, GOOD
BECAUSE I THINK
OUR RELATIONSHIP
IS COMPLICATED
ENOUGH ALREADY
JUST WITH YOU
BEING MAYOR.
YEAH, SO DO I.
ASSISTANT: MR. MAYOR,
EVERYONE'S WAITING.
I HAVE TO GO
TO THIS CEREMONY.
-OF COURSE.
-CAN I SHOW YOU OUT?
MM-HMM.
SO I FIGURE THAT WE
TAKE GREGOR OUT
AT THE BATH HOUSE
BECAUSE HE'S GONNA
HAVE THE LEAST NUMBER
OF MEN GUARDING HIM,
AND...AND QUITE FRANKLY,
WE CAN BE SURE
THAT HE'S NOT...
PACKING.
ANYWAY, HE HAS MEN
HERE AND HERE AND HERE.
-NO, NO, NO, NO.
-NO WHAT?
BATH HOUSE IS
GREGOR'S TURF.
-YOU CANNOT DO IT ON YOUR OWN.
-OK.
-WE NEED ARMY.
-WELL, THEN WHO CAN WE TRUST,
ANATOLY, BECAUSE WE'RE
BASICALLY TALKING
ABOUT A COUP.
OHH. LYING HERE
WITH MY ASS HANGING
OUT LIKE BABY.
[GROANS]
DON'T WORRY
ABOUT MY MEN.
-THEY ARE LOYAL TO ME.
-SO AM I,
AND LOOK.
I AM GONNA STAY HERE
UNTIL WE TAKE OUT
GREGOR
AND WE PROTECT
THE BRATVA.
TY SKAZAL, "STAY"?
WERE YOU GOING
TO LEAVE?
LOOK, ANATOLY.
I REALIZED
I HAVE TO GET BACK
TO MY LIFE,
BUT THEN I SAW WHAT
GREGOR DID TO YOU
BECAUSE OF ME.
YOU ARE SIN-EATER,
OLIVER.
IN SOME CULTURES,
IS...IS GUY WHO LIVES
ON THE EDGE OF VILLAGE,
AND, UH, WHEN
SOMEBODY DIES,
THEY PUT BODY THERE
AND COVER
WITH FRUITS
AND VEGETABLES,
AND HE EATS THAT.
HE EATS THEIR SINS?
YES. SO THEY GO ON
TO THE AFTERLIFE
IF HE TAKES THEIR SINS
AS HIS OWN.
YOU...YOU ARE VERY MUCH...
WHAT?
FOR THE PAST 10 MINUTES,
I'VE SEEN
THE SAME ORDERLY PASS
BY 5 TIMES
WITH AN EMPTY STRETCHER.
COULD BE ONE
OF GREGOR'S MEN.
AT ANY RATE, THEY KNOW
THAT YOU ARE BACK.
OR THEY'RE JUST HERE TO
FINISH THE JOB ON YOU.
EITHER WAY...
ANATOLY: IT IS TIME FOR ME
TO...KAK TY SKAKHESH'...
STRETCH MY LEGS.
-ALL RIGHT. COME ON.
-THANK YOU.
AND I WILL ALWAYS
HAVE THE COURAGE
TO HELP MYSELF
AND OTHERS ACCOUNTABLE
FOR OUR ACTIONS.
OLIVER: I WILL ALWAYS
UPHOLD THE CONSTITUTION,
MY COMMUNITY,
AND THE AGENCY I SERVE.
I WILL ALWAYS UPHOLD
THE CONSTITUTION,
MY COMMUNITY,
AND THE AGENCY
WHICH I SERVE.
WELCOME TO THE SCPD,
OFFICER DRAKE.
[APPLAUSE]
IS EVERYTHING OK
WITH SUSAN?
YEAH. W-WHY?
JUST, YOU KNOW, YOUR
ASSISTANT WAS CLOCKING
A LITTLE TENSION, SO...
THEA, IS...IS
MY ASSISTANT
YOUR MOLE?
I LIKE TO THINK
OF HIM MORE AS,
LIKE, MY INFORMANT,
BUT WHAT'S...WHAT'S
GOING ON?
SUSAN ASKED ME IF I WAS
THE GREEN ARROW?
WAIT. WHAT DID YOU
SAY TO HER?
I HANDLED IT.
I...I'VE BEEN DOING THIS
FOR A LITTLE WHILE NOW.
QUENTIN: CAN I TALK TO YOU
FOR A MINUTE, PLEASE?
QUENTIN, IF I DELAY
THIS VOTE ANY MORE, I'M
GONNA GET IMPEACHED.
LISTEN TO ME. LIZA WARNER
ESCAPED LAST NIGHT.
OLIVER: AND CHINA WHITE
AND CARRIE CUTTER.
WE'RE ON IT.
AS A MATTER OF FACT,
WE ARE ON IT SOONER
THAN I THOUGHT.
FELICITY HAS
THEIR LOCATION.
GREAT.
WHERE AM I GOING?
I HAVE PUT ALL 3 OF THESE
WOMEN AWAY, QUENTIN.
THIS IS NOTHING THE TEAM
CAN'T HANDLE.
MM-HMM. YEAH.
I KNOW THAT,
BUT THIS IS
PERSONAL, OLIVER.
[SIGHS]
QUENTIN: SEEMS LIKE
WE'RE A LITTLE LATE.
[SIGHS]
LOOKS LIKE CHINA WHITE
HAD A FALLING OUT
WITH THE TRIAD.
THIS IS MORE THAN
JUST A FALLING OUT.
THIS IS A MASSACRE.
OVERWATCH, ALL WE'VE
GOT HERE ARE BODIES
AND A SECURITY CAMERA.
ON IT.
THAT'S WARNER.
THIS ISN'T
ON YOU, QUENTIN.
I'M NOT SO SURE
ABOUT THAT,
BUT EITHER WAY,
WE GOT TO STOP
WHATEVER IT IS
THESE WOMEN
ARE UP TO
BEFORE MORE BODIES
DROP.
CHUCANG ZAI NALI.
HUH?!
UNH!
SO SHE SAID, "WHERE IS
THE DEPOSITORY?"
I DON'T THINK
SHE GOT HER ANSWER.
WHAT DEPOSITORY IS
SHE TALKING ABOUT?
WELL, I MEAN, THE WORD
COULD ALSO MEAN STORAGE.
JOHN: SO THE 3 OF THEM
ARE LOOKING FOR SOMETHING
THE TRIAD IS STORING?
WELL, THAT COULD
MEAN ANYTHING.
THE TRIAD'S GOT
STASHES ALL OVER
THE CITY.
WHATEVER THESE 3
ARE LOOKING FOR,
THEY JUST KILLED
AN AWFUL LOT OF PEOPLE
TRYING TO FIND IT.
WE WANT THEM TO STOP
DROPPING BODIES,
WE GOT TO FIND IT FIRST.
GO! COME ON! GO!
REGRETTING YOUR
CHOICE NOT TO
GO HOME?
NOT YET!
COME ON, COME ON,
COME ON.
THAT COUP AGAINST GREGOR
MIGHT BE SHORT-LIVED...
LIKE US.
THIS JUST ARRIVED, BOSS.
-WHAT IS IT?
-NO IDEA,
BUT IT SAID,
"URGENT," SO...
CHAPMAN, I WANT
THE ENTIRE ACU
IN THE CONFERENCE ROOM
IN 5 MINUTES.
HEY! LONG TIME,
NO SEE.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING
DOWN HERE?
OH, JUST SOME
DAMAGE CONTROL.
YOU HAVE A MINUTE?
YEAH, FOR YOU
ANYTHING.
-WHAT'S UP?
-WELL, IT'S, UM, SUSAN WILLIAMS.
-HMM.
-SHE'S SUSPECTING
THAT OLIVER'S
THE GREEN ARROW.
WHY? I MEAN, OTHER
THAN THE FACT THAT
HE IS, BUT WHY?
I DON'T KNOW.
I MEAN, HE SAYS
THAT SHE CONFRONTED
HIM ABOUT IT,
AND THEN HE CLAIMS
HE PUT IT TO BED,
BUT SHE'S NOT JUST
GONNA DROP THIS.
AGREED. WHAT ARE WE
GONNA DO?
HACK INTO HER COMPUTER
AND...AND FIND OUT WHAT'S
THERE AND DELETE IT.
YEAH, COPY THAT.
SUSAN WILLIAMS' COMPUTER.
-I'M IN.
-THAT WAS FAST.
YEAH. WELL, HER PASSWORD
IS 1-2-3-4,
AND SHE HAS A FILE HERE
NAMED "OLIVER QUEEN INFO"
BECAUSE SHE'S
SUPERORIGINAL.
-WHOA.
-OH, GOD.
-SHE...SHE HAS...
-EVERYTHING.
-SHE'S BEEN CONNECTING THE DOTS.
-THIS ENTIRE TIME.
WE HAVE TO DELETE
ALL THIS.
WELL, EVEN IF WE DO,
SHE GOT THIS FROM
AN OUTSIDE SOURCE.
SHE'S JUST GONNA BE ABLE
TO GET IT AGAIN AND AGAIN.
OK. SO WHAT DO WE DO?
FASHION MAKEOVER?
KEVLAR WEAVE
IN THE JACKET.
FIGURED IF I WAS GONNA
BE BACK IN THE FIELD
I COULD HAVE A LITTLE
MORE PROTECTION.
THERE HE IS.
JAMES WONG!
RENE: WE WANT TO HAVE
A LITTLE CHAT
ABOUT YOUR DEAD
TRIAD FRIENDS.
I DIDN'T HAVE ANYTHING
TO DO WITH THAT.
WE KNOW, BUT WHAT
WE WANT TO KNOW
IS WHAT IS
THE CHUCANG?
-WHAT?
-THE DEPOSITORY, THE STORAGE,
WHATEVER IT IS.
TOBIAS CHURCH.
IS DEAD.
YEAH, AND HE NEVER
GOT TO SPEND
THE HUNDRED MILLION
HE GOT
FOR THE AMERTEK DEAL.
THAT'S THE DEPOSITORY.
HIS CASH STASH.
WHERE IS IT?
I DON'T KNOW!
DO WE BELIEVE HIM?
SEE? IF I'D DONE THAT,
I WOULD HAVE SPRAINED
MY WRIST.
SO WHAT IS THIS PLACE?
LOS HALCONES
MONEY LAUNDERING
FACILITY.
IT'S LIKELY WARNER
AND HER NEW FRIENDS
ARE AFTER $100 MILLION
THAT TOBIAS CHURCH
LEFT BEHIND.
AND YOU THINK CHURCH'S
OLD RUNNING BUDDIES MIGHT
KNOW WHERE IT IS.
YEAH. WILD DOG
AND MR. TERRIFIC
ARE STAKING OUT
THE BERTINELLIS,
AND DINAH AND SPARTAN
HAVE EYES ON THE BRATVA.
YOU KNOW, YOU GOT TO
GET THAT NEW GIRL
A CODE NAME.
WELL, WHEN SHE'S READY,
I WAS CONSIDERING
BLACK CANARY.
YOU ALL RIGHT WITH THAT?
WELL, SO LONG AS SHE
DOES LAUREL PROUD.
SO YOU REALLY THINK
WARNER'S GONNA
SHOW UP HERE?
[GUNFIRE, GLASS BREAKING]
FORGET I ASKED.
WE DON'T HAVE TIME
FOR THAT, CUTTER.
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
THESE THINGS ARE
EXPENSIVE.
WE FIND THE MONEY,
YOU WON'T HAVE TO
WORRY ABOUT THAT.
CUPID: YEAH, AND WHEN'S
THAT GONNA HAPPEN?
NOT ONE OF THESE IDIOTS
KNEW A THING.
NO, BUT THEY GAVE ME
THE NAME OF SOMEONE
WHO DOES.
DON'T WORRY. EVERYTHING
IS GOING DOWN AS PLANNED.
OLIVER: THINK AGAIN!
YOU HAVE FAILED
THIS CITY!
QUENTIN:
YOU'RE UNDER ARREST!
GET ON THE FLOOR
WITH YOUR HANDS
BEHIND YOUR HEAD.
ON THE GROUND!
I'M GOOD. BESIDES,
I OWE THIS SON OF A BITCH
SOME PAYBACK.
FREEZE!
GET ON THE FLOOR!
I LISTENED TO YOU ONCE.
I'M NOT GONNA MAKE
THE SAME MISTAKE TWICE.
SINCE WHEN HAS DOING
THE RIGHT THING BEEN
A MISTAKE, LIZA?
SINCE YOU TURNED OUT
TO BE A LIAR!
I WAS ALL IN, QUENTIN.
YOU CONVINCED ME
TO TURN MYSELF IN,
TURN MY LIFE AROUND,
AND THEN ONE DAY,
I'M IN THE TV ROOM,
AND WHAT DO I SEE?
A NEWS REPORT ABOUT YOU
WORKING FOR ONE
OF THE WORST TERRORISTS
THIS CITY HAS EVER SEEN.
HE THREATENED
MY DAUGHTER, LIZA.
AND SO YOU DID
WHAT YOU HAD TO.
WHY SHOULDN'T I DO
THE SAME FOR MYSELF?
BECAUSE WHAT I DID
AND WHAT YOU'RE DOING
ARE NOT THE SAME THING!
SURE THEY ARE. WE ALL
DO WHATEVER IT TAKES
TO SURVIVE,
AND IF THAT MEANS
BREAKING A FEW LAWS
OR BETRAYING THE PEOPLE
WHO BELIEVE IN YOU,
SO BE IT!
[CHINA WHITE GRUNTING]
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
YOU'RE LETTING THEM GET AWAY!
OFFICER: THEY'RE NOT OUR TARGET.
YOU'RE UNDER ARREST
FOR THE MURDER
OF DETECTIVE WILLIAM MALONE.
OLIVER: LISTEN TO ME.
YOU'RE MAKING A MISTAKE.
OFFICER: DROP THE BOW,
OR WE WILL LIGHT
YOUR ASS UP.
FINE.
SON OF A BITCH!
FELICITY: WHAT DO
YOU MEAN THEY
WERE AFTER YOU?
SOMEHOW...THEY FOUND OUT
ABOUT BILLY.
-WHAT?
-UH, I...I'M WITH HER.
WHAT ARE...WHAT ARE
YOU TALKING ABOUT?
PROMETHEUS
ORCHESTRATED THINGS
SO OLIVER WOULD
KILL BILLY MALONE.
-WHAT?
-D.A. CHASE DECIDED
THAT WE SHOULD
COVER IT UP, BUT...
BUT SOMEHOW, THE ACU
KNOWS AND THINKS
THAT YOU TOOK OUT
ONE OF THEIR OWN.
WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO
HANDLE THIS,
BUT RIGHT NOW,
EVERY SECOND THAT
WE'RE DOWN HERE,
THAT CREW IS GETTING
CLOSER TO CHURCH'S MONEY.
THE MORE MONEY
THEY HAVE, THE MORE
GUNS THEY CAN BUY,
MORE DAMAGE
THEY CAN DO.
OK. LET ME TALK
WITH PIKE.
I'LL SEE IF I CAN GET
HIM TO STAND DOWN.
QUENTIN,
I APPRECIATE THAT,
BUT I...I GOT TO
HANDLE IT THIS TIME.
WHY?
BECAUSE I'M THE MAYOR.
A LOT OF FIREPOWER
IN THIS ROOM.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
WE JUST HAVE A COUPLE
QUESTIONS FOR YOU, CAPTAIN.
WE HEARD THE ACU
ATTEMPTED TO APPREHEND
THE GREEN ARROW
LAST NIGHT.
-IS THAT TRUE?
-100%.
HE'S A PERSON
OF INTEREST
IN THE MURDER
OF DETECTIVE MALONE.
BASED ON WHAT EVIDENCE?
THIS WAS DELIVERED
TO ME YESTERDAY.
OPEN IT. YOU'LL SEE
WHAT I SAW.
THE M.E. REPORT
FOR BILLY MALONE'S
AUTOPSY.
CAUSE OF DEATH WAS
AN ARROW CONSISTENT
WITH THE ONES
THE GREEN ARROW
USES.
THIS WASN'T
IN THE ORIGINAL
EXAMINER'S REPORT?
THAT ONE SAID
THE CAUSE OF DEATH
WAS UNDETERMINED.
I THINK
WE'RE LOOKING
AT A COVER-UP.
THERE'S A LOT
OF WHACK JOBS
RUNNING AROUND
WITH BOWS AND ARROWS
THESE DAYS.
DOESN'T MEAN IT WAS
THE GREEN ARROW.
LIKE I SAID,
THE EDGEWORK
ON THE WOUNDS
WAS CONSISTENT
WITH HIS ARROWS.
CAPTAIN PIKE, I HAVE IT
ON GOOD AUTHORITY
THAT THE GREEN ARROW
WAS NOT RESPONSIBLE.
ON WHOSE AUTHORITY?
RIGHT NOW, I'M NOT
AT LIBERTY TO SAY.
WELL, THEN I'M
NOT AT LIBERTY
TO DROP THIS.
LOOK. WE'RE DEALING
WITH A COP KILLER
HERE.
IF THAT'S ALL, I'VE
GOT A LOT OF WORK.
I'LL KEEP YOU
GENTLEMEN POSTED
ON THE STATUS OF
THIS INVESTIGATION.
ADRIAN: I WOULDN'T
PANIC JUST YET.
WE DON'T EVEN KNOW
IF THAT REPORT'S LEGITIMATE.
I THINK IT'S SAFE
TO SAY THAT IT IS.
THE QUESTION IS
WHO SENT IT TO PIKE?
ADRIAN, I'M SORRY.
COULD WE HAVE
THE ROOM, PLEASE?
MM-HMM.
IT WAS PROMETHEUS.
HEH. ISN'T THAT
A LITTLE PARANOID?
I MEAN, I KNOW
THE GUY'S GIVEN
YOU REASON TO BE, BUT...
THE ENVELOPE THAT
PIKE GAVE ME WAS
POSTMARKED FROM OPAL CITY.
YEAH. SO?
PROMETHEUS' MOTHER
IS FROM OPAL CITY.
I'M NOT EVEN GONNA
ASK HOW YOU KNOW THAT.
I WENT TO SEE HER.
THIS IS PROMETHEUS
TELLING ME THAT HE
KNOWS ABOUT THAT,
AND HE IS PUSHING BACK,
HE IS KEEPING ME IN CHECK
BECAUSE HE KNOWS THAT
I CAN'T MAKE A MOVE
WITH THE ACU BREATHING
DOWN MY NECK!
YOU CAN'T JUST GIVE UP.
I HAVE TO GO.
HEY. SORRY.
I GOT YOUR TEXT,
AND I...
HUH. OK. YOU LOOK
LIKE YOU'RE HAVING
AS BAD A DAY
AS I AM.
REALLY? DID YOU GET
FIRED TODAY, TOO?
WHAT?
MY PRODUCER CALLED ME
OUT ON THE CARPET.
APPARENTLY, THEY RECEIVED
AN ANONYMOUS TIP
THAT I HAVE BEEN
PLAGIARIZING MY STORIES
FOR THE PAST TWO YEARS,
AND MY LAPTOP
IS FILLED WITH
INCRIMINATING EVIDENCE.
YOUR LAPTOP?
IT HAS ALL THE FINGERPRINTS
OF A HATCHET JOB.
-OK, SUSAN...
-AND I HAVE TO WONDER
ABOUT THE TIMING
BECAUSE...NOTHING
LIKE THIS HAS EVER
HAPPENED TO ME
BEFORE I ASKED WHETHER
YOU WERE THE GREEN ARROW.
SUSAN...
I SWEAR TO YOU
I DIDN'T HAVE
ANYTHING TO DO
WITH THIS,
I DON'T KNOW
ANYTHING ABOUT THIS.
AND YOU'RE GOING TO
STAND HERE AND TELL ME
THAT YOU'RE NOT
THE GREEN ARROW.
-I ALREADY...
-BECAUSE THAT TATTOO
ON YOUR CHEST MARKS YOU
AS A BRATVA CAPTAIN.
-OK.
-I'VE GOT A PHOTO OF YOU
WITH THE BRATVA
IN RUSSIA
AT THE SAME TIME
THAT YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO BE
ON A DESERTED ISLAND.
I'VE GOT ANOTHER PHOTO,
SAME TIME,
OF A MAN IN A HOOD
WITH A BOW AND ARROW
OPERATING IN RUSSIA,
AND NOW OF COURSE,
I CAN'T GO PUBLIC
WITH ANY OF IT
BECAUSE I'VE BEEN
THOROUGHLY DISCREDITED,
SO WELL DONE.
-IF YOU COULD JUST.
-UNLESS THE NEXT WORDS
OUT OF YOUR MOUTH
AREN'T GOING TO BE A LIE,
I'D REALLY PREFER
IF YOU JUST SAID
NOTHING AT ALL.
HEY.
HEY. WHAT'S GOING ON?
DID YOU HACK
SUSAN WILLIAMS' COMPUTER?
-OK. WHOA. WHOA.
-DID YOU...DID...
BACK UP. YOU DON'T...
DID YOU HACK
SUSAN WILLIAMS' COMPUTER?
YES.
WHAT WERE YOU THINKING?
I WAS THINKING THAT YOU
WERE ONE NEWS STORY AWAY
FROM BEING OUTED.
THEA ASKED ME TO PUT A FEW
THINGS ON SUSAN'S COMPUTER.
WAIT. WAIT. WAIT. WAIT.
THEA ASKED YOU?!
YES. I DON'T KNOW WHAT
SHE WAS PLANNING ON DOING.
SHE SAID SHE HAD IT HANDLED.
WHY? WHAT DID SHE DO?
OLIVER: WE'RE GONNA HAVE
TO MAKE A RUN FOR IT.
ARE YOU READY?
KONECHNO.
[SPEAKING RUSSIAN]
WHAT ARE YOU
DOING?
I SURRENDER
AND HE LETS YOU LIVE.
HE WILL KILL YOU.
HE'S GOING TO KILL
BOTH OF US.
WE'RE TRAPPED, ANATOLY.
ONLY ONE OF US IS GONNA
MAKE IT OUT OF THIS ALIVE.
I AM AVTORITET.
THERE'S NO WAY YOU'RE
GOING TO SUFFER
FOR MY SINS, OLIVER.
THAT'S WHY I'M NOT
GIVING YOU A CHOICE.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
YEAH?
HEY, STRANGER.
HAVEN'T SEEN YOU AROUND
MUCH TODAY.
YEAH. YOU KNOW,
I WAS JUST BUSY
TAKING OUT
THE TRASH.
YEAH? SANITATION?
MORE LIKE
PUBLIC RELATIONS.
UH, I HEAR
GREEN ARROW
IS PUBLIC ENEMY
NUMBER ONE AGAIN.
YEAH. WELL, UH,
NOW OLIVER THINKS
THAT HE CAN'T MAKE A MOVE
ON WARNER AND HER CREW,
YOU KNOW.
OH. WHAT DO YOU THINK?
I THINK THAT WARNER'S
MY MESS TO CLEAN UP.
AND I'M...I'M ASSUMING
OLIVER SAID
THAT'S NOT THE CASE?
WHAT OLIVER DOESN'T KNOW
IS THAT THE REASON
HER REHABILITATION WAS
SHORT-LIVED WAS
'CAUSE SHE CAUGHT
MY CONFESSING
TO WORKING WITH
DAMIEN DARHK ON TV.
OH, WOW.
YEAH.
THAT IS
AN UNBELIEVABLE...
LOAD OF CRAP, QUENTIN.
WHAT?
LIZA WARNER IS
A CRIMINAL.
YOU DIDN'T MAKE HER
INTO ONE.
YOU'VE GOT TO STOP
TAKING RESPONSIBILITY
FOR OTHER PEOPLE'S SINS.
YOU KNOW, I REALLY LIKE HOW
WISE YOU'RE GETTING LATELY.
THAT'S JUST BECAUSE
I HAVE COMMITTED
MY OWN SIN TODAY.
WHAT SIN?
DON'T WORRY
ABOUT IT.
WHY DON'T YOU WORRY
ABOUT CATCHING
LIZA WARNER
AND NOT BECAUSE YOU
ARE RESPONSIBLE
BUT BECAUSE SHE'S
A CRIMINAL.
[SNAPS FINGERS]
LET'S GET MOVING. YO!
MAN: HOLY...
SECOND MAN: HEY,
WHAT'S THIS, NOW?
LOOKS LIKE
3 HOT CHICKS.
ESPECIALLY THIS ONE.
THANKS FOR THAT.
ANYTHING FOR A FRIEND.
HYAH! HYAH! HYAH...
MAN: UH!
WARNER: WE'RE LOOKING
FOR TOBIAS CHURCH'S
RAINY DAY ACCOUNT.
BEARDED MAN:
THE AMERTEK MONEY?
I TELL YOU
WHERE IT IS,
YOU LET ME GO?
NO. YOU'RE GONNA
SHOW US WHERE IT IS.
CHINA WHITE:
WHAT ABOUT THE GREEN ARROW?
THE ACU IS ALL
OVER HIS ASS.
WE'VE GOT NOTHING
TO WORRY ABOUT.
LET'S GO!
THEA: Y-YOU ASKED TO SEE ME?
DID YOU KNOW THAT
SUSAN GOT FIRED TODAY?
I DIDN'T KNOW SHE WAS
GONNA GET FIRED, OLLIE.
YOU SHOULD'VE COME
TO ME WITH THIS.
LISTEN, OLLIE, I JUST
WANTED TO DISCREDIT HER...
THEA, YOU SHOULD HAVE
COME TO ME WITH THIS!
AND THEN WHAT?
WE WOULD HAVE THE SAME
CONVERSATION
WE ARE HAVING RIGHT NOW.
I WOULD'VE TOLD YOU THAT SHE
WAS GOING TO OUT YOU AS THE...
[SOFTLY]
GREEN ARROW.
SHE WOULDN'T DO THAT
TO ME.
AND THEN YOU WOULD SAY THAT.
[HEAVY SIGH]
LOOK, OLLIE, THE ONLY
REASON I DIDN'T TELL YOU WAS
BECAUSE I WAS TRYING TO KEEP
YOUR HANDS CLEAN.
I KNOW YOU CARE
ABOUT HER, SO...
I DO CARE ABOUT HER.
I ALSO CARE
THAT YOU DESTROYED
HER REPUTATION.
SHE'S GONNA HAVE
A TOUGH TIME FINDING
A DECENT JOB.
SHE'S CERTAINLY NOT
GONNA FIND A JOB
IN JOURNALISM.
YOU JUST BLEW UP
HER LIFE.
HONESTLY, I...DIDN'T MEAN
FOR IT TO GO THIS FAR.
YES, YOU DID.
YOU KNEW EXACTLY
WHAT YOU WERE DOING.
AND THAT'S THE PART
THAT I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHO DOES THAT
TO A PERSON?
YOU GOT A MINUTE?
YEAH. WE'RE DONE HERE.
WHAT DO YOU NEED?
[SIGHS]
WARNER AND HER CREW JUST
HIT THE BERTINELLIS.
ONE DEAD, TWO
IN CRITICAL CONDITION,
AND THEY KIDNAPPED
NUMBER FOUR.
YEAH. THAT'S A CHANGE
IN THEIR M.O.
THEY HAVEN'T BEEN
ABDUCTING PEOPLE.
YEAH. THE GUY THEY TOOK
IS ENZO RUSSO.
I'M THINKING THEY TOOK HIM
'CAUSE HE KNOWS
WHERE THIS DEPOSITORY IS.
I'M THINKING, YOU KNOW,
MAYBE, UH, FELICITY
CAN HACK HIS CELL.
WE COULD TRACK HIM THAT WAY.
NO. WE HAVE TO LET
THE POLICE
HANDLE THIS ONE.
WHAT?
THE ACU WILL BE
ALL OVER ME.
OK. THEN SEND THE TEAM.
I'M NOT RISKING ANYONE
GETTING ARRESTED.
WHAT, YOU'RE JUST
GIVING UP NOW?
PROMETHEUS HASN'T GIVEN
ME A CHOICE.
UM, NEITHER DID SLADE WILSON
OR DAMIEN DARHK.
BUT WITH THOSE GUYS,
YOU DIDN'T JUST PICK UP
YOUR FOOTBALL AND GO HOME.
THIS IS DIFFERENT.
HOW?
BECAUSE WHAT'S HAPPENING
NOW, IT'S NOT SOMETHING
THAT PROMETHEUS DID.
IT'S SOMETHING I DID.
I MEAN, YOU'RE TALKING
ABOUT MALONE, RIGHT?
THAT WAS PROMETHEUS.
I FIRED THE ARROWS.
LISTEN, EARLIER THEA
WAS TALKING TO ME
ABOUT NOT TAKING ON
OTHER PEOPLE'S SINS.
WHAT HAPPENED WITH MALONE,
THAT'S ON PROMETHEUS,
NOT YOU.
WELL, QUENTIN,
THAT ADVICE WOULD MEAN
A LITTLE BIT MORE
IF IT WASN'T COMING
FROM THEA RIGHT NOW.
WELL, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT THAT MEANS,
BUT I DO KNOW THAT IF
YOU'RE LETTING PROMETHEUS,
ACU, OR ANYONE ELSE
KEEP YOU
FROM STOPPING
WARNER AND HER BUDDIES,
THEN JUSTICE
ISN'T BEING SERVED.
I WILL HAVE FELICITY
LOOK AT RUSSO'S PHONE.
THAT'S WHAT I WANTED
TO HEAR.
I'LL TAKE ANOTHER RUN
AT PIKE.
NO, I'LL DO IT.
YOU SURE?
I'M SURE THAT I DON'T
WANT MALONE'S DEATH
TO HAVE BEEN FOR NOTHING.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
MR. MAYOR.
DO YOU HAVE A MINUTE FOR ME?
OF COURSE.
WHAT CAN I DO
FOR YOU?
[SIGHS]
IT'S, UH, IT'S ABOUT
THE GREEN ARROW.
SIR, WE'VE BEEN
OVER THIS.
I KNOW. AND I KNOW
THAT I TOLD YOU
THAT THE GREEN ARROW
WAS NOT RESPONSIBLE
FOR BILLY.
THAT'S NOT ENTIRELY TRUE.
YOU GOT MY ATTENTION.
PROMETHEUS MANIPULATED
THE GREEN ARROW
INTO KILLING
DETECTIVE MALONE
BY MAKING IT APPEAR
THAT MALONE WAS PROMETHEUS.
RIGHTLY FEARING
A CITYWIDE PANIC,
DISTRICT ATTORNEY CHASE
COVERED UP
THE CIRCUMSTANCES OF
MALONE'S DEATH.
AND HOW DO YOU KNOW
THIS?
THE GREEN ARROW TOLD ME.
YOU'RE IN CONTACT WITH
THE VIGILANTE.
I'M THE MAYOR.
AND WHETHER WE LIKE IT
OR NOT,
THE GREEN ARROW
AND HIS TEAM ARE
AUXILIARY LAW ENFORCEMENT.
LEAVING WHETHER I AGREE
WITH THAT ASIDE,
WHY SHOULD I BELIEVE
WHATEVER HE SAYS?
BECAUSE YOU KNOW
AS WELL AS I DO
WHAT HE HAS DONE FOR
THIS CITY.
BUT WHAT'S
THE SIMPLER ANSWER?
THAT THE GREEN ARROW ALL
OF A SUDDEN OUT OF NOWHERE
BECAME A...A COP KILLER?
OR THAT HE WAS MANIPULATED
BY A PSYCHOPATH WHO HAS HAD
ALL OF US, YOU INCLUDED,
RUNNING IN
CIRCLES FOR MONTHS?
HE STILL KILLED BILLY.
YES, HE DID.
AND THAT'S SOMETHING THAT
HE'S GONNA HAVE TO LIVE WITH
FOR THE REST OF HIS LIFE.
ALL I'M ASKING IS THAT YOU
DON'T LET THAT STOP HIM
FROM BEING THE HERO
THIS CITY NEEDS HIM TO BE.
[EXHALES]
I...
I DON'T KNOW, MR. MAYOR.
I'M...I'M GONNA HAVE
TO THINK ON THIS.
THANK YOU FOR YOUR TIME.
[CELL PHONE VIBRATING]
YEAH?
I GOT A GPS TRACE
ON ENZO RUSSO.
WELL, AT LEAST
HIS CELL PHONE.
OK. TEXT ME THE ADDRESS.
UM, SHOULDN'T WE LET
THE TEAM HANDLE THIS,
CONSIDERING
YOU'RE THE...
THERE'S REALLY NO
DELICATE WAY TO PUT THIS...
THE SCPD'S MOST WANTED?
TEXT ME THE ADDRESS.
ALL RIGHT. I TRACED RUSSO'S
CELL TO OAK HILL MEMORIAL.
JOHN'S ALREADY EN ROUTE.
OAK HILL MEMORIAL.
AT LEAST IF WE
GET SHOT,
WE DON'T HAVE
TO GO FAR.
THAT IS REALLY NOT
AN ENCOURAGING
PERSPECTIVE, RENE.
HEY. UH...
JUST A QUICK NOTE.
LISTEN, UM, NOW
THAT YOU'RE
A FRESHLY MINTED
OFFICER OF THE SCPD,
WE CAN'T HAVE YOU GOING
OUT INTO THE FIELD
AND HAVING YOUR
NEW COWORKERS
RECOGNIZE YOU. SO...
THIS IS GONNA INVOLVE ME
WEARING A COSTUME, ISN'T IT?
YEAH. SOMETHING LIKE
THAT, YEAH.
YOU KNOW, I'M NOT...
I'M NOT SURE I'M READY TO
FILL HER SHOES QUITE YET.
OH, IT'S NOT SHOES.
IT'S A MASK.
PIKE: UNIT 54 SPOTTED
THE GREEN ARROW'S DUCATI
HEADING SOUTHBOUND
ON RIVERSIDE.
WE BELIEVE HE'S
EN ROUTE TO ENGAGE
WARNER, CUTTER,
AND CHIEN NA WEI.
WE'RE TRACKING HIM,
AND WE'LL BE THERE
WHEN HE DOES.
MOVE OUT.
QUENTIN: THANKS FOR
KEYING ME IN ON THIS.
I TRUST YOU
LIKE I'M TRUSTING
THAT CERTAIN PEOPLE
CAN HANDLE THE TRUTH.
SPEAKING OF,
HOW'D IT GO WITH PIKE?
OH, WE'LL SEE.
[COMMUNICATOR BEEPS]
ALPHA TEAM
IN POSITION.
RENE: THIS AIN'T RIGHT, MAN.
DISTURBING SOULS AT REST.
THIS IS HOW YOU GET HAUNTED.
I FEEL A PRESENCE.
BETA TEAM
IN POSITION.
ON SITE.
HOW DO YOU
KNOW IT'S THIS ONE?
IT'S GOT THE LEAST
AMOUNT OF DUST.
HELP ME MOVE IT.
HO HO! WE HAVE GOT
THE MONEY, HONEY.
TAKE WHAT YOU
CAN CARRY.
WE'LL COME BACK
FOR THE REST.
[CANARY CRY]
[PISTOL FIRES]
QUENTIN: YOU DID ALL THIS
FOR MONEY?
SO WHAT, YOU COULD GO
TO THE CAYMANS?
YOU THINK THIS IS ABOUT
TAKING A VACATION?
WE'RE TAKING OVER.
WE'RE TAKING BACK
THIS CITY.
JOHN: YEAH?
YOU AND WHAT ARMY?
THIS ONE!
[TIRES SCREECHING]
WARNER: IT'S AMAZING THE LOYALTY
MONEY CAN BUY.
TAKE THEM DOWN.
[CANARY CRY]
[GRUNTS]
[SIRENS]
[HELICOPTER]
I'M GONNA ENJOY WATCHING
THEM TAKE YOU DOWN.
[GUNSHOT]
MOVE ON THE TARGETS!
FREEZE!
[POLICE RADIO TRANSMISSIONS]
THANK YOU,
CAPTAIN.
HAPPY TO HELP.
IT DIDN'T HURT THAT
THE MAYOR VOUCHED FOR YOU.
I'M SORRY ABOUT
BILLY MALONE.
I KNOW THAT
IT'S SOMETHING
I'M GONNA HAVE
TO DEAL WITH
FOR THE REST
OF MY LIFE.
THAT'S FUNNY.
THAT'S WHAT THE MAYOR SAID.
[SIRENS, HELICOPTER]
COME TO SAY GOOD-BYE?
CLEAR YOUR CONSCIENCE
MAYBE?
HEH! MY CONSCIENCE
IS CLEAR.
THE HELL IT IS.
LOOK IN THE MIRROR
SOMETIME, QUENTIN.
YOU'RE NO BETTER THAN ME.
I'M SHOT THROUGH WITH
FLAWS, NO QUESTION.
BUT AT LEAST
I'M NOT USING
OTHER PEOPLE'S SINS
TO JUSTIFY MY OWN.
HEY, HEY.
ARE YOU OK?
YEAH. YEAH. I'M FINE.
JUST SHE AND I, WE GOT
A LITTLE HISTORY. HMM.
SO, UH, OLIVER TELLS ME
THAT YOU'RE
THE NEW BLACK CANARY.
OH, NOT YET.
I'M NOT
READY TO TAKE
YOUR DAUGHTER'S
PLACE, SIR.
LAUREL DIDN'T WANT
SOMEONE TO TAKE HER PLACE.
SHE WANTED SOMEONE TO CARRY
ON IN HER PLACE.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
HEY.
NICE JOB TONIGHT.
I SAW YOU ON THE NEWS.
WE NEED TO TALK ABOUT
WHAT HAPPENED, SPEEDY.
[SIGHS]
LOOK, I'M SORRY.
HAVE YOU...
HAVE YOU SPOKEN
TO SUSAN?
NO. SHE'S NOT
RETURNING MY CALLS.
I'M REALLY SORRY,
OLLIE. I...
I KNOW I SCREWED UP AND...
BUT YOU DIDN'T MAKE
A MISTAKE.
YOU MADE A CHOICE.
AND YOU REMINDED ME
OF SOMEONE.
WHO?
MOM.
SHE WOULD'VE DONE
SOMETHING LIKE THIS.
MORE LIKE SHE WOULD'VE
DONE EXACTLY THIS.
SHE WAS A WONDERFUL
MOTHER.
BUT I...I THINK
WE BOTH KNOW
THAT SHE DIDN'T ALWAYS
MAKE THE BEST CHOICES.
WHATEVER'S GONNA HAPPEN
WITH SUSAN IS...IS...
IS WHATEVER'S
GONNA HAPPEN.
RIGHT NOW...
RIGHT NOW,
I'M REALLY WORRIED
ABOUT
MY BABY SISTER.
AH.
HOW VERY SELFLESS OF YOU.
I DID NOT EXPECT IT.
BUT DON'T WORRY.
MY WORD IS GOOD.
ANATOLY WILL NOT BE HARMED.
AAH!
OH, ANATOLY, LOOK AT YOU.
HIDING LIKE A RAT
IN THE SEWER.
DID NOT EXPECT THIS
FROM BRATVA CAPTAIN.
[CLICKS TONGUE
DISAPPROVINGLY]
BUT THEN YOU'RE NOT GOING
TO BE BRATVA CAPTAIN
FOR MUCH LONGER.
WE HAVE A PROBLEM.
ADRIAN, JUST ONCE,
I'M GONNA NEED YOU
TO WALK INTO MY OFFICE
AND NOT SAY THAT.
I'M SERIOUS.
I JUST GOT A HEADS-UP
ON SOMETHING,
AND I THINK IT'S
SOMETHING YOU NEED TO
GET OUT IN FRONT OF.
MAN: MR. MAYOR,
SOMETHING'S HAPPENING.
I THINK YOU
SHOULD TURN ON THE TV.
BETHANY SNOW: REPORTS HAVE
RECENTLY SURFACED,
THERE HAS BEEN
A MAJOR COVER-UP RELATING
TO THE MURDER OF
ACU DETECTIVE WILLIAM MALONE.
ACCORDING TO OUR SOURCES,
THE MAYOR'S OFFICE ORDERED
THE FALSIFICATION
OF AUTOPSY REPORTS
TO PROTECT THE IDENTITY
OF DETECTIVE MALONE'S
KILLER.
IF ANY OF THESE ALLEGATIONS
PROVE TRUE,
IT WOULD CONSTITUTE
A GROSS OVERSTEP
OF THE MAYOR'S AUTHORITY,
ONE THAT IS LIKELY TO TRIGGER
IMPEACHMENT PROCEEDINGS
LED BY THE MAYOR'S POLITICAL...
[SHUTS OFF TV]
WELL, YOU
UNDERSOLD THIS.
THIS ISN'T A PROBLEM.
THIS MIGHT BE THE END
OF MY ADMINISTRATION.
MAN: GREG, MOVE YOUR HEAD.