[Oliver] My name is Oliver Queen.
After five years in hell,
I returned home with only one goal,
to save my city.
But I couldn't honor that commitment
and honor the promise I made
to the mother of my son.
So I asked the best man I know to help.
His name is John Diggle.
And he is the Green Arrow.
[Oliver]Previously on Arrow...
Could you tutor me some more
before the test?
-See you soon.
-She's pretty cool.
His life will be better
with you in it. Just like mine.
Cayden James is the most skilled
hacker the world has ever known.
Eight months ago
he was scooped up by A.R.G.U.S.,
and now he's being held without cause,
being tortured, who knows what else.
Helix is about to extract Cayden James.
-One...
-Two...
Three.
And Laurel,
she wasn't dead when we found her
back on Lian Yu.
Buy you a drink?
Whiskey. Neat.
Are you waiting for someone?
Is it too cheesy if I say "you"?
I'll let it slide this time.
And what about you?
Let me guess. You're a numbers guy.
You sit in front of a computer all day
and you came here to blow off some steam.
You've got me pegged.
I think the bartender forgot your order.
I have a better idea.
[both panting]
[both moan]
Uh-oh.
Looks like I know
your dirty little secret.
Oh, it's...
[shushes]
I won't tell if you won't tell.
All right.
You know my secret. Now...
Tell me one of yours.
Okay.
Only if you promise not to tell anyone.
Cross my heart and hope to die.
Mmm...
[Felicity] William did an excellent job
picking out your tie.
Yeah. He was very excited.
He wanted to come to dinner.
I told him that Raisa
was his date tonight.
Oh. Well, she's a lucky woman.
Has it, um...
Has it been three years
since the first time we did this?
Yeah, let's just hope that
this date goes better than that one.
I think it will.
[whispers] Don't jinx it.
Masked gunmen could come through the door,
and it would've been better
than our first dinner.
Well, only because
we were not being blown up.
[stammers] You know,
also because I wasn't ready.
Not the way I am now.
Well, now the time is right.
-[patron] Mr. Mayor?
-Yes?
I'm sorry to interrupt.
I just wanted to say that I'm voting
against that awful
anti-vigilante referendum.
Oh, that's very nice to hear.
Are you two back together? [gasps]
Such a sweet couple.
-Well, enjoy your dinner.
-Thank you.
Don't forget to vote, okay?
[chuckles softly]
You paid her to say that?
I had absolutely nothing to do with that.
Hmm.
Well, I am the mayor's girlfriend now,
so does that get me a break on my taxes,
or maybe a pass on jury duty?
[stammers] I mean, I was gonna offer
to bring you to a fundraiser.
Hmm...
I cannot tell you what it is
if you're gonna keep making that face.
No. Sorry. It's just, you know...
[whispers] With Overwatch and the
start-up with Curtis, and, you know...
It's our old, but new relationship.
Maybe we could
ease into some of the things.
Of course, of course.
I love rolling to those things solo.
Yeah, you're lying.
I'm kidding.
I'm really happy that you're busy,
and I'm especially excited
for this thing with Curtis,
because, truth be told,
it is important you have something
in your life that is not just...
-[cell phone vibrates]
-The team.
-Yes.
-[cell phone beeps]
No, I mean... [whispers] The team.
This is how it felt to be you, isn't it?
Oh, yeah.
I'm sorry.
Go.
What's going on?
Body dropped outside of a bar.
Dinah's on the scene with SCPD.
[Dinah Drake]The vic was dead on arrival.
[indistinct radio chatter]
Paramedics are calling it
internal hemorrhaging,
but I'd recognize this kill
from a mile away.
Sonic Scream did this.
An inch from his ear.
-Ouch.
-Laurel.
Witnesses saw the vic leaving
with a woman, a brunette.
Maybe Laurel got a wig?
According to witnesses,
they were very handsy with each other
on the way out.
What do you guys think?
Black Siren turned Black Widow?
[breathes deeply]
You know, 'cause she mates and then kills?
[both chuckle]
Dinah, thanks. We'll take it from here.
Victim was an accountant
named Jackson Klimavich.
No criminal record, boring job,
really boring Upswipz profile.
Well, he was married,
so maybe not so boring.
Boring and scummy.
Sorry. Had to help Lance finish up
the polling analysis.
Star City stands at 70% against
the anti-vigilante legislation.
That's 70% for us accounting for
the double negative you just used.
Yeah, but after everything
this team has done for the city...
You'd think it'd be higher.
What'd I miss?
Evil Laurel seduced a guy
and then killed him.
-Why?
-That's what we have to figure out.
First, we've got to find her.
Laurel's been in the wind too long.
Yeah, we're on it.
Speaking of being on it,
did you mail out
our articles of incorporation?
For our start-up? The documents
required to, you know, start it up?
Oh, my God. They are in
a manila envelope on my countertop,
-with every intention of mailing them.
-[sighs]
I was just telling Oliver
how I'm being stretched too thin.
Wait a minute. What do you mean by "just"?
We were at dinner when I got your text.
Felicity...
No, it's the job. It's okay.
No, this is all on me.
I 911'd you over one dead body.
-Can you make it back for dessert?
-Well, no.
-We have to find Evil Laurel.
-No, no, no.
I will find Evil Laurel.
You go out there and take your
ass back and get your man.
-Are you sure?
-Are you kidding me?
I was your guys' biggest shipper.
I feel like the reconciliation
taking effect is kind of on me.
-No. You're amazing.
-I'm "terrific."
-Well...
-Is that getting old?
-I kinda like it.
-You like?
-Yeah. Anyways...
-Cool. All right. Go, go.
Finally. I thought you were gonna
keep me waiting here all night.
Patience is how wars are won, Miss Lance.
Well, the first battle's already over.
Look, I don't know if this is
your first clandestine meeting,
but at this point,
most people would say "thank you."
For the item?
Or for leaving a body
for the police to find?
Better than a witness to question.
Any reservations?
Concerns about what comes next?
Of course not.
This one shouldn't be a problem.
Glad to hear it.
Until we meet again.
[door lock beeps]
I'm so sorry that I had to bail on dinner,
but I'm home now, if you want to
come by for some dessert.
Yes. [chuckles] Yes, that was
intentionally suggestive.
Okay, well, good. I'll see you soon.
Nice try, but I wasn't born...
Alena?
Do you always
announce your attacks like that?
What're you doing in my apartment?
You'd think a computer hacker
would know better
than to install a smart-lock on her door.
I mean, what are you doing here?
I need your help.
You-you? Or Helix-you?
Does it matter?
Let's pretend for a second it does.
[sighs]
Who gave you that?
Cayden James.
He's working on something terrible,
something that will hurt the entire world.
And I need your help to stop him.
I helped you break Cayden James
out of A.R.G.U.S. custody.
I went against my friends.
I went against my team,
because you told me
that Cayden James was a good man.
No, you did it because Cayden could
help you find Adrian Chase.
And he delivered.
So, at what point did he become
a criminal mastermind?
I don't know, at some point during
his eight months in A.R.G.U.S. custody.
They held him in a glorified
shipping container, Felicity.
Nutrition-withholding,
sensory deprivation.
They broke him.
In that case, he should be
in a funny farm somewhere.
He shouldn't be
planning the end of the world.
Actually, how do I know that you
being here isn't part of his plan?
Because I could never go along with
what I suspect he's planning, Felicity.
I'm a hacktivist, not a monster.
You say he has plans to hurt the world?
How?
I don't know exactly what he's planning.
But I saw a casualty estimate,
and the most conservative estimate
is 4% collateral damage.
4% of what?
The world population.
That's almost 300 million people.
If we try and hack his servers,
we might be able to figure out
what he's planning.
-Okay, where is he now?
-Corto Maltese.
But I came here because I didn't know
who else to reach out to.
-Will you help me?
-[cell phone vibrating]
We set Cayden James loose, Alena.
Of course I'm helping.
Looks like the same M.O.
Did Laurel also make out
with this one first?
It's a legitimate investigatory question.
Cause of death is the same.
This was definitely Laurel.
Yeah, victimology was similar, too,
insofar as this woman is
just as boring as the first guy.
College librarian.
May even be more boring.
Maybe Laurel's killing for sport.
Doesn't sound like her.
Black Siren isn't the Laurel
you remember, remember?
Any word on tracking her down?
Nothing usable from the CCTV cams
we found on either crime scene.
-Forensics is a dead end as well.
-And Felicity?
I tried texting her,
but she hasn't hit me back.
Fine. Let's hit the streets.
Someone has to be able
to help us find Laurel.
What about me? Uh...
I want to hit streets, too,
and maybe a couple of bad guys.
Curtis, with Felicity AWOL, we need tech.
Keep working that angle.
[stammers] But I've been
working that angle.
[cell phone vibrating]
-Another dead end.
-Did you try spoofing the sub-array?
-Yeah.
-What about the...
Yeah, but these firewalls are crafty.
I mean,
the protection protocols are just...
-Art.
-I was going to say "impenetrable."
But, yeah, that too.
Cayden would be the only one
who can get into Cayden's system.
Oh, my God, you're a genius.
You're a genius.
We need to convince Cayden's system
that we're him.
That's like saying,
"All we need is a trillion dollars."
No, we have to work off Cayden's system.
-I told you. He's in Corto Maltese.
-Yeah, but Helix is right here.
We cleared the place out, Felicity.
It's sanitized.
What about the wiring?
The digital infrastructure?
That's proprietary.
Cayden's own design.
We left that in place.
That'll work. Let's get the gear.
Does that include a ghost drive?
Because we're gonna need that
to get into Cayden's system.
I know a guy.
Whoa. What's all this?
Um, just some stuff for a start-up that
Curtis and I are trying to start up.
Oh, good for you.
-You guys are funded?
-Well, seed money
from our reputation of being
the geniuses of Palmer Tech.
Though I'd feel more like a genius
if I knew what we were starting up.
We're thinking something
in the smart-home area.
You're joking.
You left Helix...
I was kicked out of Helix. By you.
To make home appliances?
I thought you wanted to change the world.
I thought you wanted to change the world,
and look where you ended up.
-Sorry, that's... I didn't...
-No.
-We should go.
-Okay. We good?
-Mmm-hmm.
Oliver.
Hey. Hi. What are you doing here?
You invited me.
That's right.
What is she doing here?
Hi. [chuckles]
I'm just gonna go over there.
Okay, come in.
I know how much you love to say,
"I told you so."
No, that's you.
So consider this an early Christmas gift.
Cayden James is a bad person, and
he's planning on doing a bad thing.
Are you sure that you can trust her?
I wouldn't exactly use the word "trust."
Then wherever you're going,
I'm going, too.
No. This isn't your life anymore. No.
At least tell the team what you're doing.
I will tell them.
I'll call them on my way.
And then, when I'm done,
we can finish dinner.
Starting with dessert. Alena.
[Alena] Mmm.
I didn't know you guys were back together.
We sure are.
[Alena clears throat]
[Laurel] Excuse me.
[exhales]
-Here you go.
-Oh. Thanks.
I'm such a klutz.
Don't worry, me too.
I love your shoes. They're so cute.
Custom designed.
Girls can rock limited-edition kicks,
too, right?
Absolutely.
I'm Dinah, by the way.
Jenny.
It's really nice to meet you.
I don't know why
I didn't think of this sooner.
Laurel's cry resonates
in the terahertz range,
which can be triangulated,
according to geography.
Was I supposed to understand
a single word of that,
or were you talking to yourself?
Sorry. The short version is
I think I've figured out a way
to find Evil Laurel
by tracking her sonic cry.
Meaning if she uses it, we can find her.
Yeah. Only problem being, it means
-someone's probably in trouble...
-[computer beeps]
Whoa!
Talk about timing.
So that means she just used it, right?
-Mmm-hmm.
-Where?
A parking garage
between Marleau and Hainesly.
-I'll tell John and Rene.
-Mmm-hmm.
Nothing on Level C.
-[Wild Dog]D is clear.
-[Mr. Terrific]A is empty.
Except for a sweet-ass Corvette
someone left overnight.
[Black Canary] Guys.
-We're too late.
-[Laurel] Actually, you're right on time.
[sonic scream]
[Laurel] My mistake for dawdling, I guess.
It's just...
It's just she was so, so pretty.
I really wanted to hold her hand
until the end came.
You are one twisted bitch.
That really hurts my feelings.
[grunting]
[sonic scream]
[panting]
-She's gone.
-Good work tracking her down.
-Don't give me points for being late.
-Call it in.
-[techno music playing]
-[indistinct chatter]
Okay. You couldn't have told me to change?
You look great.
Are we here for a GMD
or an acid-trip techno freak-show?
[Alena] Both, if you want.
Okay, so the dealer's name is Amnesiac.
But I have no idea how to find him.
Well...
Whoa! Okay! Rude.
Maybe that door guarded by the three
scary dudes with chains for brains?
Eh.
They look friendly.
[techno music continues]
Hello.
You lost?
No. We're here to see...
-Amnesiac.
-Hmm, yup.
Now.
-[Felicity] Okay, that time...
-I don't think we should go in here.
-Hey!
-Hands off!
Hey, easy, chrome dome!
[man] Forgive my thuggish compatriots.
I pay them to uphold a certain aesthetic.
You're Amnesiac?
Your shock is exactly what
this establishment aims to cultivate.
Now, what brings you here?
We need a ghost mirror drive.
-What for?
-That's our business.
[Amnesiac]
And selling illegal tech is mine.
And I only get to stay in business
by avoiding legal entanglements.
Everything about you two screams narc.
Well...
[grunting]
[groaning]
[exclaims]
[muffled] Whoa, whoa! No!
Don't shoot! It's me!
Oliver?
-Are you okay?
-No!
What the hell are you doing here?
Trying to keep you safe.
I saw the guys take you.
Yeah. Those guys were taking me
to this guy,
who's gonna give us what we needed
to stop Cayden James.
But now he won't
because you kicked the crap out of him.
God.
You screwed up everything.
He said he thought you were police.
You know, me not wanting your help tonight
doesn't have to do with me
just needing to do this alone.
It has to do with me
wanting to protect you.
I was trying to protect you.
You are under 24/7 surveillance
from the FBI right now.
-What if somebody saw you?
-I can handle it.
What I cannot handle
and will not stand for
is you going off after a criminal
without backup.
I get that.
But I don't need that right now.
What I need...
What I need is a ghost mirror drive.
And I need to get Alena out of here
before they all come to.
-Felicity...
-We will talk about this later.
Another boring person.
Disrespect the dead much?
[sighs] He's right.
No connections, no money to speak of,
no apparent benefit to killing
three different people at random.
They weren't random.
Autopsies finally came back
on all three victims.
Apart from all three being
thoroughly unremarkable,
they had one other thing in common.
All three had traces of Dimotex 75
on their hands.
Dimotex is an adhesive polymer.
It's used on the streets
to rip off fingerprints.
Laurel was stealing fingerprints.
Why would somebody wanna collect
the fingerprints of three nobodies?
And I disrespect the dead?
They're not nobodies.
They're invisible.
Boring jobs, no connection to community.
What makes them remarkable
is just how unremarkable they are.
What're you saying, hoss? I mean, boss.
What if these peoples' backgrounds
are just a cover?
They're boring by design. To be invisible.
So you're saying they're all
some sort of covert operatives?
They could be anything.
But whatever they're dealing with,
it's big enough that they needed a cover.
Be nice to know.
That way, we could figure out
who Laurel's going after next.
Anybody got a crystal ball?
I might not be able to figure out
where she's headed,
but I might be able to figure out
where she was.
Now, sonic cries leave ripples in the air.
I might be able to backtrace
where Laurel's been
and maybe even find out a pattern.
Maybe even determine
where she's operating out of.
I heard two "mights"
and two "maybes," but I'll take it.
In the meantime,
I'll try to raise Felicity.
If anyone can hack through these covers
to these people's real identities,
it's her.
Wow, love what you
haven't done with the place.
Cat-5 hookups are there and back there.
-Yeah.
-[cell phone vibrating]
One sec. Hey, John.
Hey. Did you decide to take a vacation?
Uh, no, sorry.
I just have a situation here.
Yeah, Curtis told me about the start-up.
No. This isn't about the company.
This is about Cayden James.
And I don't have time
to talk to you about it right now,
but you were right and I was wrong
about breaking him out of A.R.G.U.S.
-Felicity, listen...
-I'm at Helix right now.
I'm just gonna clear up
this situation real quick.
I will be back to the bunker
before you know it. I promise.
All right. But get back here soon.
We need you.
I'm on it.
Got it!
The "mights" and "maybes" have paid off.
Backtracing Laurel's soundwaves
produced a probabilistic curve
of geolocations,
which I canvassed
by means of cameras of various sorts.
Curtis, less how, more what.
I've found a probable location
for Laurel's base of operation.
Tasking a keyhole satellite.
When was this?
Ten seconds ago.
Anybody know that guy?
[typing]
How about that one?
-Never seen him before.
-I have.
We should go. Felicity's in trouble.
[Felicity]
A file in here is labeled "Arclight."
Must be a code name
for whatever James is planning.
Now the question is, what is the plan?
[sonic scream]
[Alena] You're supposed
to be in Corto Maltese.
-This is Cayden James?
-[man] No, Miss Smoak.
I'm Cayden James.
Very nice to finally
make your acquaintance.
In case you're curious about why I'm here,
it's not nostalgia.
It's you.
We never finished our conversation
in Corto Maltese.
Which is where you thought I was.
Because you've been pinging my cell.
I was hurt. Truly.
Not by the betrayal so much as the naiveté
of someone I thought had potential.
Sorry, Miss Smoak.
I'm afraid you're what's known
as collateral damage.
Horrible waste of talent.
Make it as humane as possible.
One shot.
You won't even know.
[Felicity] Get down!
[grunting]
[sonic scream]
[guns firing]
How'd you guys know we needed you?
Not that I'm complaining.
Felicity.
[Alena coughing weakly]
Alena. Alena!
Call an ambulance.
[Felicity] Stay with me.
Stay with me. Alena.
It's bad. It's really bad.
Alena?
[Dinah Drake] How is she?
Stabilized.
The next couple of hours
will tell her story.
I air-gapped her ICU room
just in case if Cayden tried
to kill her by hacking
her hospital equipment. He can't.
-Hey. You all right?
-Am I all right?
That I broke a genius madman
out of prison,
who's apparently working with
the psychopath version of Laurel?
Am I okay that I didn't see
what was right in front of my face
and now Alena might die?
What the hell do you think?
Sorry.
-It's not you I'm mad at.
-I know that.
But right now we need you.
Yeah, I know. Curtis?
All set. Did everything
just like you told me.
I softened the beach, so now
you can, you know, do your thing.
Well, I couldn't do that before
because of Cayden.
All right. I'm in.
John was right.
They're hiding their identities
because they are really important.
John thought they were
some kind of spies or something.
More like "something."
All three are access managers
for the IDND, the International
Domain Name Directory.
Let's just pretend for a second
only you and Felicity know what that is.
The Internet is run on domain names.
You start messing with them
and you start collapsing
whole parts of the Internet.
So Laurel was stealing fingerprints.
To gain access, I guess.
Well, why steal
three sets of fingerprints?
Wouldn't one do the job?
No, the Internet is divided into sections,
so no one person
can take it down all at once.
Each manager controls a section.
And all three would be needed
to access the master vault,
which oversees all sections.
Right, so Cayden James wants to
take down the Internet?
Can he actually do that?
If you destroy the vault, yes.
And then what? I can't send an email?
I mean, so what?
The Internet controls everything now.
Electricity, water supply,
hospital equipment.
Also planes, trains and automobiles.
Alena said Cayden's casualty estimate
was 300 million people.
-Actually, that sounds low.
-I don't disagree.
This is all my fault.
[John] All right,
let's keep our focus here.
So James and his people
wanna hit this vault.
Do we have a location on it?
The location is so classified,
they don't even a word
for how classified it is.
Be that as it may, I have a hack running.
That'll give us a location soon.
Good. Which means you can get home,
take a shower, clear your head...
I'm fine.
It's not a request, Felicity.
[knock at door]
[both] Hey.
John told me what happened.
Hmm.
So I'm guessing this little visit is
his idea of therapy.
Actually, I'm thinking that
he probably wanted you
to speak to one of the world's
leading experts in guilt and regrets.
[Felicity] Hmm.
[whispers] What's happening now
is not your fault.
Is that what I sounded like
all these years?
You sounded smarter.
How'd you do it?
How did you balance being the Green Arrow,
the mayor, a boyfriend, a brother?
How did...
How did you do it all by yourself?
[stammers] I didn't do it all by myself.
I had you.
Yeah, well, I know you're just
saying that to get boyfriend points,
and it's working.
I'm being serious, Felicity.
Even if we weren't together,
you were always there with me.
Always there to talk me out of stuff,
to help me being the Green Arrow.
You were literally in my ear
every second that I was in the field.
And that's why I followed you
to the club tonight.
Because I wanted the chance
to be there for you
the way that you've been there for me.
So then what would I say to you
in this situation?
You would
tell me that when I... You...
[clears throat] freed Cayden James,
I did it because,
at that moment, at that time,
in your heart, you thought it was right.
Yeah.
You'd tell me not to live in the past.
You'd tell me
to make it right in the present.
You'd tell me to trust myself.
[chuckles]
Well, I am very smart, apparently.
So smart.
[cell phone chiming]
Sorry.
-This is becoming a habit.
-It is.
And I am incredibly proud.
[grunting]
Please.
[gasping]
I have a wife and two little girls.
[shushes]
I know.
I had a family once.
[grunts]
I appreciate your zeal, Miss Lance,
but we just need people down, not dead.
Do I question your methods?
Oh, a little gratitude, please.
Were it not for me,
you would've either starved
or bled to death on Lian Yu.
The Pre-Socratic philosopher
Thales of Miletus,
known as the Father of Science,
believed that for any event
there was a natural cause,
even if we couldn't see it.
And he thought that
with perfect knowledge,
man could control anything.
Everything.
You're just full of surprises, aren't you?
Oh, I'm just beginning.
Welcome to the inner sanctum.
He's gone.
Biometric hand scanners.
So cool. Except for the dead body part.
Stay sharp.
[Wild Dog] This place is huge.
Well, it has to be big to
hold, you know, the whole Internet.
This way.
-Cayden's overclocking the vault CPU.
-[Green Arrow] English, Felicity.
He put a virus in the system that's
gonna make the whole thing explode.
[Wild Dog] That's a bit too much English.
How much time do we have
before the vault goes boom?
Six minutes. I think I can stop the virus.
[stammers] I just need one minute.
There's no way Cayden James and Laurel
are gonna let you just stand there
and do that.
-[gun firing]
-Get down!
You weren't wrong.
[typing]
Your men have engaged the targets.
Our men, Miss Lance.
This partnership is a democracy,
after all.
Oh.
Miss Smoak just appeared on the server.
Clever girl.
Her ingenuity never disappoints.
I'm coding a little something
to occupy her
while I take my leave.
Do the same for her friends, would you?
No, no, no, no, no!
[Wild Dog] "No" is not what we wanna
hear right now!
Cayden just used the processor's
firewall to block me out.
I can't shut down the virus remotely now.
I'm gonna have to do it onsite
before he turns this whole place
into an ashtray.
Not to mention, you know, the Internet.
-Where's the processor?
-Northwest quadrant.
[Green Arrow] Fine. We'll cover you.
Delta formation!
[guns firing]
Fall back!
[Wild Dog] We're outgunned here.
We've got you covered.
Can you handle this?
I can handle it. Just keep them
off of me for four minutes.
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
[sonic scream]
[whimpers] Maybe doing this solo
wasn't such a good idea.
-Good thing you're not alone.
-Oliver?
Technically if I'm in this chair
that makes me Overwatch.
-You're in the bunker?
-I am. You okay with that?
I'm all right with that.
I'm so all right with that.
I'm epically all right with that.
Especially if you have eyes
on this complex.
I think I do.
You've automated this system to the point
that William could basically operate it.
Do you see the room
in the far northwest quadrant?
I do. But I also see 10 hostiles
between you and it.
So let me put on the safest path.
Take the corridor to your left.
[whispers] Are you sure about that?
Sorry, right. My left. Your right.
Just a little bit
of a learning curve here.
[groans]
Overwatch. Sitrep.
Overwatch, what's your situation?
She's fine.
Stop.
[indistinct radio chatter]
Go right.
Under the door.
Three, two, one.
-Coast is clear.
-Good.
I'm in.
Cayden's not here.
Time to get to work.
[grunting]
[Wild Dog] Company, nine o'clock.
I knew you'd be around here somewhere.
Well, I couldn't stay away from you.
Except for you've changed
something about yourself.
I just can't quite put my finger on it.
Let me help you with that.
[sonic scream]
[clattering]
So it's the crossbow?
That's cute.
Two more hostiles inbound.
[gasps]
[cadre] There! There!
Oh, thank you for that.
Just wanted to give you a little time.
Yeah, well, I'm gonna need it.
I have to break through
the processor's protective firewall
to stop Cayden's virus.
Add the fact that the processor
is exponentially overclocking,
and he's disabled the cooling system.
Did not understand a single word
that you just said.
Well, you understand blaring noises
-and really scary lights, right?
-[alarm sounding]
I know this.
You can do it.
I believe in you.
[grunting]
Time to go.
[sonic scream]
[grunts]
-Thanks.
-No problem.
[computer trilling]
If this place is going to go boom,
let's not be here when it does.
Overwatch, how're we doing?
Overwatch?
[beeping rapidly]
Good job.
And we're not dead.
Told you.
[whispers indistinctly]
Yeah. You know, if this whole
role-reversal thing sticks around,
you're really gonna
have to adopt my saying,
"I'm not saying I told you so."
You tell me you told me so.
Yeah. But not all the time.
Thank you.
I'm just glad I found a way to help.
You always do.
Thank God we saved the Internet.
My fantasy football team
was killing it this year.
[scoffs]
So this new partnership,
-is it permanent?
-I certainly hope not.
I think Mayor Queen's probably too busy
to be moonlighting as tech support.
Besides, after all those years
in the field,
it'd be a shame if you went down
for carpal tunnel.
All kidding aside, [clears throat]
we need to focus on why Laurel has
aligned herself with Cayden James.
Those operatives,
they were the same ones
that we took out last month.
Sorry. Old habits.
I will leave you to it.
I'll come with you.
I'm gonna go tell Alena the good news.
[Alena] Thank you.
No need to thank me.
Saving the world is kinda what we do.
-Mmm.
-That, and fixing our mistakes.
None of this is on you, Felicity.
I vouched for Cayden.
You were just backing my play.
Yeah, well, like you said, he changed.
Yeah. [sighs]
Now that you're no longer working
for an evil über-hacker...
-I'm just assuming.
-Hmm...
Do you know what you're gonna do
when you get out of here?
[sighs]
I'm gonna take some time.
And gain some much-needed perspective.
And then, maybe, if you'll have me,
come work for you at your start-up?
Yeah, that'd be great.
-Yeah?
-Yeah, you should.
I mean, maybe in a year or two,
Curtis and I'll actually have an idea
of what to develop.
Oh, actually,
I have a pitch for you on that.
-Yeah?
-Mmm-hmm.
Why did you get fired from Palmer Tech?
Well, besides me being lousy
at balancing my time
and working with the team?
The board actually violently resisted my...
Efforts to replicate your spinal implant.
Yeah.
You've been looking
for something to work on,
something that would change the world,
and you've literally been sitting
on the right idea this whole time.
I couldn't figure out a way
to affordably mass-produce
the implant at Palmer Tech...
Now you have Curtis
and no board oversight.
[chuckles]
You know, Curtis and I
have actually had a really hard time
coming up with a name for the company,
almost as hard a time
as we have for a concept...
So, I was wondering
how you would feel about me
appropriating the name Helix?
Well, I think you don't generally
need to worry about criminal hackers
coming after you
for trademark infringement.
-That's true.
-And I think
it would be really nice
to see something good come of the name.
-"Helix Dynamics."
-That rolls off the tongue nicely.
Cool logo possibilities,
easily engravable on a Nobel medal...
Funny, those are Curtis' criteria, too.
-[chuckles]
-I think it's possible.
A reward for a job only half done?
A means of preventing them
from tracking you
by way of your sonic scream.
And the job was done to perfection.
I thought the objective
was to take down the Internet.
Oh, no, the objective was to take down
the firewall protecting the vault.
And Miss Smoak
was most adept in complying.
Why couldn't you
find a way to do it yourself?
I've been doing this too long
to leave trails, Miss Lance.
Much safer to have Miss Smoak's
digital fingerprints
on the processor, not mine.
And once she
helped taking down the firewall,
I was able to upload
a critical piece of code to Arclight.
What happens now?
We take the next step.
[both panting]
Dinner went better than expected.
I can't believe we got through
the whole thing. No interruptions,
no armed assassins...
And I still have room for dessert.
So do I.
[Oliver grunting]
-Wait.
-That's okay.
[cell phone vibrating]
[Felicity] Oh, sorry.
-Sorry.
-That's okay.
-Oh!
Sorry. Not mine.
-Thank you.
-Oh.
-One sec.
-Yeah.
[continues vibrating]
Hello.
Hi.
Okay.
I'll be there.
Mmm-mmm. All right.
That didn't sound like John or the team.
It wasn't.
What's going on?
That was Slade Wilson.
He needs my help.