My name is Oliver Queen.
After five years in hell,
I have come home
with only one goal--
To save my city.
Now others have
joined my crusade.
To them, I am Oliver Queen.
But to the rest
of starling city,
I am someone else.
I am something else.
Previously, on "arrow"...
Man: Hello, Sara.
What are you doing here?
Oliver: Whoever did this,
I'm going to find them.
Apparently there's
another bidder for the company.
Who?
Ray palmer.
Yes, I am your boss now.
No! [sobbing]
Thea: Roy, I don't
trust you, or anyone.
Don't try to find me.
I am never coming back.
Now I've got
to go get Thea.
It's long past time
she came home.
Well done.
Thanks, dad.
[engine starts]
So, where are we going?
Wherever you want.
It's up to me?
Why not?
I'm a well-traveled man.
I've been every place
in the world there is.
But you want
to get out of here.
Because if the police
know you're alive,
they come after you.
The arrow, too.
You're very
perceptive, Thea.
Knowing when people
are hiding something
behind their smiles.
Your mother
had that talent.
Yes.
If someone knew
where I was,
It would be
unfortunate--
For both of us.
So why did you
reach out to me?
You reached first.
Still.
I don't want to feel
this pain again.
I don't want to hurt
Or get hurt
Ever again.
And you seem like someone
who can teach me how not to.
[horns honking]
[tires squealing,
horns honking]
[grunts]
I didn't do it!
A woman was killed
on a rooftop last week.
Black leather,
blonde hair, wore a mask!
I didn't kill her.
You were there!
I don't know
anything about it!
Your fingerprints
are on this.
From a fifth I drank
up there, but I--
What did you see?
Nothing!
I was up on the roof
with some buddies.
This lady,
she showed up
And she--
she told us to go!
Looked like
she could handle
herself, you know?
Whoever it is
you're looking for,
I wouldn't want
to be him.
Another dead end.
It took me a week to get
a hit off that print.
I had to reconstruct
the partial
Using a predictive
indexing algorithm.
Appropriate,
since it was
his index finger...
Not particularly
relevant now.
Don't worry, Oliver,
we'll find him.
He's out there somewhere.
No, he's not.
Trail's gone cold.
I hate to do this,
but I have to
head off to work.
Tech village
is open this early?
Have you figured out
where in Italy Thea's staying?
Yeah, about that--
she's not in Italy.
Hmm?
Or europe.
Or, well, she's--
Where is she?
I had to ping
her cell phone
to find out
Where in Italy she
was texting from.
Turns out, came back
Corto Maltese.
Corto's an island
off of South America.
What's up with your family
and islands?
Wait, Oliver.
Thea's letter said
not to come find her.
That letter
was addressed
to you, not to me.
I'm watching Laurel
go through losing Sara.
It's time
for my sister
to come home.
What are you doing?
Thea's gone because of me.
Because the lies
that I told her.
So I owe this to both
of you to make things right.
No. What are
you...Doing?
You can't travel
with that.
I've actually never
been on a plane before.
[babbling]
I know. You're not
doing anything
And I could literally
watch you forever.
Oh, yeah?
What about once
she discovers boys?
Well, that's what my glock
is for, right, baby?
Right. It's my glock.
I'm going to enjoy some
quality time with her
for the next few days.
I'm even looking forward
to changing a few diapers.
And I'm looking
forward to believing
that when I see it.
Why the time off?
You quit
the team again?
No, Oliver's going
to Corto Maltese
For a couple of days.
Could you
go with him?
Like I don't already
spend enough time
with Oliver as it is?
Team arrow may
have starling city
purring like a kitten,
But the rest
of the world is still
a very dangerous place.
Including Corto Maltese.
Lyla, I already don't like
where this is headed.
We have a field
operative down there
who's gone dark.
All right, so send an agent.
Send a task force.
He's not in any
kind of trouble.
He hasn't touched
his panic button.
He's probably just drunk
in some belleza's villa.
Mark Shaw's been known
to miss a few days
from time to time.
[exhales]
Will you just
do me a favor...
And see if he's ok?
Tell him to check in.
Two more days
and I'm going to have
to call in the cavalry.
And I don't want
to get him into
trouble with Waller.
Mark's an old friend.
She better not do
anything interesting
while I'm gone.
Next time,
keep your hands up.
[velcro tearing]
Ted grant?
Well, I guess
that badge means
you're not here
For a self defense
class.
No, I've already had
my fair share.
I'm here about one
of your students,
tom bronson.
A witness places him
at the scene
Of a break-in last night.
Well, that's not possible.
See, because tom and I
were sparring last night.
Mr. Grant, do you
know that lying
To the district
attorney
Is against the law?
If by that, you mean
am I willing to lie
In order to keep
a good kid who just happened
to make a stupid mistake
Out of this system?
I think you know my answer.
Are you admitting
to perjury, mr. Grant?
Now that's a big word.
I'm just a dumb fighter.
Right?
Look, tom was here
with me last night.
We worked on his
uppercut combinations.
Like I said, in this city,
there's a lot of good people
Who get dealt bad hands.
They lose someone,
they lose themselves,
which is why they
Come in here
to work off that rage.
I've gotten good
at picking out the types.
Types just like you.
If I'm angry,
it's because I'm dealing
With someone who's
willing to lie to a d.A.
To protect a punk kid.
I don't think
that's the case.
Either way,
If you do have something
you want to work off...
So what's the play
with Thea?
Do you mind if I talk
to her alone first?
It's been a while.
Felicity able
to pin her down?
She gave me an address.
Thea!
Señor.
Cómo puedo ayudarlo?
Estoy buscando
a mi hermana.
You must be mia's brother.
I see the resemblance.
Is "mia" around?
She works. At the cafe.
Where's the cafe?
I'll show you.
Thank you.
[exhales]
I didn't come all the way
to south america
To have you poison me, did I?
[laughs]
It's a meditative tea.
It will activate
your mind and body.
I think I'm going to need
a little bit more than tea
To learn how
to use one of those.
The sohei buddhist
warriors believed that
First you fight
with the mind...
Then your sword.
I remember when
I was training
To be a warrior.
I began
just like you--
Devastated
by my wife's death.
I was...Angry,
And hurt.
The pain
was unbearable.
Like this.
You're out of your mind!
Put your hand in here!
Every warrior
must learn
the simple truth--
That pain
is inevitable,
And suffering
is optional.
[gasping]
Please, don't--
Don't do what I think
you're going to do!
You asked me
to teach you.
No.
Aquí tienes.
Thea.
Good to see you.
You, too.
How--how did you--
Well, it's not exactly
the amalfi coast.
[sighs]
Voy a cerrar, earnesto.
Didn't you flunk
spanish?
More like
skipped it altogether.
Well, you look good.
I like
your hair cut.
Thank you. Yeah,
wanted it short, you know.
It gets hot down here.
I'm sorry I lied to you
About it, Ollie.
I just needed some space.
It's ok. You've had
five months of it.
This isn't just a visit.
Got one
for you, too.
After mom,
I understood why
you left starling.
But Thea,
I miss you.
And I would
really like it
if you came home.
I miss you, too.
And I love you...So much.
But I'm never coming back
to starling city.
[Thea gasping]
Ahh!
I can't. Sorry.
There is strength
in you, Thea.
I see it, even
if you can't
see it yourself.
I'm sorry, this--
This just isn't me.
I'm not like you.
I can't do this!
It's all right.
It's not your fault.
It's mine.
Q.C. Stock up 10 bucks
at the open.
That is love, ha!
Ah, miss smoak,
good morning--
I think. I've been
here all night.
My predecessor left
things a little, um,
What's the polite way
to say this? Little wonky.
Sorry if I'm rambling.
I'm a little
over-caffeinated.
I just had
three espressos.
Speaking of coffee--
let me stop you right there!
I told myself
that I would stand firm
On a few points.
No late night emails,
no personal errands,
And definitely no coffee.
There'll be no espressos
brought to you by me.
I stand very firm
on that last point.
And I admire
your conviction.
This is jerry conway,
your executive
assistant.
And I wanted to know
if you'd like him
to get you a coffee.
Or are you just
anti-latte in general?
Um...Executive assistant?
I think that's
a yes on the latte.
Thank you, jerry.
Should we get to
work? Excellent.
Applied sciences.
Q.C.'s bleeding edge
research division,
Till some wacko
blew it up last year.
I'm sure they had
their reasons.
The point is,
it's the cornerstone
for my plan
To rebuild
Queen consolidated
And thus the city.
I've had my people
Working day and night
salvaging what they can,
Including this--
a file server
Containing applied
science's design work.
It's not working,
unfortunately,
On account
of being caught
in a massive explosion.
You want me to access the data.
A brilliant mind
at work already.
Speaking of, I got
to get back to work.
Then why are you
leaving your office?
Oh, I'm not.
I'm leaving yours.
This is Lyla's busy
work, man, you didn't
have to tag along.
Well, I don't know how
to vacation like
a normal person, Diggle.
What's the plan?
This spot's his
usual dead drop.
Lyla sent me over
this file photo.
Just make sure
he's all right.
Got him.
I got you.
He's a friendly,
Oliver.
Shaw.
Hey, hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey, hey, hey!
Listen! I'm with
Lyla Michaels.
Have you seen any
capuchins today?
If that's a challenge
code, I got to tell you,
I'm not with a.R.G.U.S.
I'm just Lyla's
baby daddy.
Now, you didn't
check in, Shaw.
She was worried,
So she sent me
to find you.
If you're lyin',
you'll be picking
your intestines up
Off this sidewalk.
That's fair enough.
Lyla gave me a security
transcoder in my right
jacket pocket.
Pretty jumpy, Shaw.
Better jumpy than dead.
Copy that.
What's going on?
Not here.
Sorry, I had--
I had eyes on me
all week,
A whole
follow team.
Wait, Shaw. What makes
you so important?
I have hard intel.
Someone from Corto Maltese
hacked into the server
And acquired
the a.R.G.U.S. Actual.
They want to sell it.
Did I mention I don't
work for a.R.G.U.S.?
The actual
is an encrypted
data omnibus.
It's a complete record
of agent covers,
Personal details,
affiliated soft targets--
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
soft targets...
As in family members?
Yeah, as in women
and children.
You get why
this is so important?
Hi, my name is Laurel,
I'm an alcoholic.
All: Hi, Laurel.
A week ago, I...
Something happened.
Something that
I can't share
with anyone
For several
complicated reasons.
I thought that
I was going
to want to drink...
But I didn't.
Not even tempted,
really.
[inhales and exhales]
But what I am is...
Is I'm angry.
And I don't know
what to do with it
Or--or where to put
it. I just...
Thank you for
letting me share.
Are there any other
burning desires?
Erica. Alcoholic.
All: Hi, erica.
My boyfriend and me
Got into another
fight last night.
Some of you know,
he still drinks, a lot.
And I said something.
I know I should have
just kept my mouth shut.
I know I should
just leave him,
but...I can't.
Maybe there's a meeting
I should be
going to for that.
Laurel: Once a month, erica
gives a share like that
And it's getting worse.
Quentin: Yeah.
Do you know
the boyfriend has
Eight assault charges
against him?
And not just
in starling.
He's got warrants
out on him
As far off
as coast city.
And it takes everything in me
not to go after
A dirtbag like that,
but the day the cops
Start bringing their badges
into aa meetings,
That's the day that
the drunks stop coming.
I'm in position.
The sale of the actual
is going down here.
Only two of us.
You didn't want
to call for back up?
Hey.
That's the only insurance
policy you're going to need.
They're here.
You're not worried about them
seeing our ride?
How did you know
the buy was happening?
I've been a station agent
in Corto Maltese
for three years now.
I got this third-world
garbage dump wired.
What's wrong?
There's no buy,
is there, Shaw?
[groaning]
Sorry for lyin' to you,
John. Well, partially lyin'.
There is a buy going down,
just not till tomorrow.
I needed to get this first.
Thanks for helping me
decode the actual.
Oliver: Diggle!
[Thea sighs]
Should have got
the heavy duty ones.
I like your hair.
Are you and my brother
like travel buddies now?
No, we're just
worried about you.
[grunting]
Oliver said you weren't
going to come back, so...
I figured I'd come here
and try to convince you to.
Well, you can't.
Look, I get it, you're hurt.
I lied to you,
I lied right to your face.
But I--I need you to know
that when I said I wanted
to leave starling with you,
That wasn't a lie.
I didn't just leave
because of you, Roy.
My mother lied to me,
My brother.
I had to get away
from starling city
and all the secrets.
And I found
myself here.
Isn't it lonely here?
That's kind of what
I like about it.
There's no one here
who knows me
Or thinks of me
as Thea Queen
Or Thea Merlyn.
No one who lies
to me, or...
Tries to protect me
with secrets.
All I ever wanted
was for you to be happy, Thea.
I'm sorry I got
in the way of that.
I'm sorry that I hurt you.
If being here instead of home
makes you happy, then--
Then you should stay.
Roy?
Are you ok?
You look
a little tired.
I just haven't been
sleeping much lately.
You take care.
What do you mean?
It's not your fault,
it's mine.
I thought I could
do this differently,
But I can't.
I need to train you
as I was trained.
Treat you
as my student,
Not my daughter.
[gasping]
What are you doing?!
The only way to
forge steel is to
temper it with fire.
[gasping and groaning]
Stay away from me,
you sick son of a bitch!
Now we can begin.
Lyla: Why didn't you
call me sooner?
I could have helped.
I didn't want you
to worry, Lyla.
Besides, I thought
we could handle it.
Well, we've hacked
his email traffic.
He's got a buyer en route
to Corto Maltese.
Who?
The tech boys
are still working on that.
But Waller's dispatched
a wet team to your position.
They're not going
to get here in time.
They might.
Keep your powder dry.
Copy that.
We're not going to
keep our powder dry.
Hell no.
Hey.
Any luck raising
our digital lazarus
from the dead?
The hard drive
is toast.
And the power
supply.
And...The actuator.
Ah, I'm sensing
a pattern.
[cell phone vibrates]
sorry, one second.
Hello?
Hey, felicity,
this is John.
Where are you?
You wouldn't
believe me
if I told you.
Are you near a computer?
Kind of.
I'm looking for somebody
in Corto Maltese.
I'm actually a little bit
in the middle of a...
I need to know where
he is. I've emailed you
everything I have on him.
...Meeting right now.
I am so sorry.
It's a friend.
Um, well,
a few friends...
Actually. You know what,
it's a long story.
Heh. Why am I under
the impression that
you have a lot of stories,
All of which are long?
You want me
to come back later?
What? Sorry.
[beep]
Hello?
Felicity, I need a favor.
Are we favor
friends now?
Are we friends?
What?
Never mind, sorry.
[telephone rings]
Oh, dear god.
One second.
One more second. Hello?
We got cut off.
According to the file
you sent me,
This guy is somewhat
of a hacker.
Let me guess--long story?
Yeah, the guy
I'm looking for broke
into a.R.G.U.S's system.
And he left a trail.
It's faint--hacking-wise--
But with a little bit
of luck, I will find him,
Or his laptop. I will email
you when I have something.
I'm having
a bit of a day.
I need you to help me
find someone by googling
his phone or something.
Pinging his gps.
Can I call you back?
Is this what a typical day
looks like for you?
Believe it
or not, this is
better than most.
When felicity has Shaw's
location, I want you
to text me and I'll be there.
Thea?
Yeah.
Oliver, I don't
think she's going
To change
her mind on this.
She doesn't want
To hear from anyone,
and I don't blame her.
I mean, we both
lied to her. A lot.
I know, it's why it's time
to tell her the truth.
Oliver, when you say
"the truth"...
What happened
the five years
I was away,
Everything
we've done since
I've been back,
All of it.
Well, you might want
to think about that
for a second.
Lies are what drove Thea
away from starling city
In the first place.
The truth is the only
thing that's going
to bring her back.
Except you won't be
telling her the truth, will you?
You'll be telling her
that her brother has been
lying to her to her face,
With almost
pathological sincerity
For the past two years.
She won't believe
another word you say.
And you will lose her,
Oliver, forever.
Well, look around.
I've already
lost her.
I don't have
any other choice.
I hear you like
to hit women.
How about one
who likes to hit back?
[grunting]
You're right.
It's better when
they hit back.
[starts engine]
[tires squealing]
[sighs]
Baby, baby,
are you ok?
I'm so sorry.
I'm too relieved
to be mad at you,
I really am.
But, sweeTheart...
This is crazy.
What the hell
were you thinking
Going after that
girl's boyfriend?
There's just something
I needed to work out.
I know that the world
isn't fair.
I know that it's
a terrible place where...
Where people deserve
to get punished.
And they don't. I just...
[sighs]
For one night,
I needed the world
to be different.
Ok, Laurel,
Laurel...
What's going on
with you, huh?
You're not being
yourself lately.
And now you're
running around,
You're tuning
this guy up.
What are you doin'?!
Baby, you can
talk to me
about anything.
You know that,
right? You know that.
I know.
Talk to me, then.
[sighs]
Laurel, you're not
the arrow.
Or your sister.
You promise me
you'll never do anything
like this again, ever!
I promise.
It was a mistake;
I wasn't thinking.
If you want to stay
in Corto Maltese,
it's fine,
But there's not much
here in the way
of sightseeing.
I need to talk to you.
Look, between you
and your new
best friend Roy,
I'm pretty sure
you guys have
said everything.
I haven't.
Not yet, anyway.
[sighs]
Roy showed me
the note
you left him.
And you were right
about everything.
I have lied,
I have kept secrets.
The truth is that
If I tell you...
All the things
that you don't
know about me,
That I might
lose you forever.
I spent five years
in the worst
kind of hell,
And there were
things that happened,
There were things
that I did...
That if--
If you knew,
You would see me
differently.
No, I'll always
see you as my big brother.
I mean, no matter
what happened
To you on that island,
or who you became,
It's the secrets you kept
about my own life.
I mean, you lied to me
About who my father was.
Malcolm may have
been your blood.
Robert was
your father.
I lied to you
about him, too.
Dad wasn't the man
we thought he was.
He was better.
And I've kept
something from you
because I just...
Never wanted you
to know.
Dad made it off
"the gambit" with me.
You told me he drowned.
We made it to
a life boat
together.
There wasn't enough
food and water
for both of us...
So he killed
himself.
And that is one secret
that I'm telling you now
Because I need you
to realize...
Mom and dad,
They sacrificed
themselves
So that
we could live.
But if we're not
together, then...
We're not even
really alive.
You're my family.
And even if you
don't need me...
I need you.
Please just consider
what I'm saying.
John: He's here.
So's his buyer.
I was expecting
Armitage.
This country's soil
is not worthy
of mr. Armitage.
Do you have the item?
Where's the money?
And the transcoder?
We better go.
Where'd you get this?
Our hotel room.
Who are they?
Could be a.R.G.U.S.
That's not a.R.G.U.S.
Suelten sus armas!
Let's go.
Go!
A.R.G.U.S., they
know we're here.
Which is why I got a bunch
of Renta-soldiers
To secure the perimeter.
It's amazing how cheap
you can buy an army
For in this country.
Diggle!
Behind you!
I never said I didn't know
how to use a gun.
[all grunting]
[both grunting]
Lyla was your friend!
And you endangered
her and her daughter
For what, for a lousy payday!
Not a payday.
It's my ticket out.
Of what?
A.R.G.U.S.!
You don't know
the things Waller's
made me do.
The person
she turns you into.
That still gives you no right
To put a bulls-eye
on my family's back!
I had no choice.
But you do, John.
Tell Waller I died.
Tell her you put
a bullet in me.
If only.
Thea: I've been thinking.
I want to go home.
To my brother.
And all his lies
and secrets?
Maybe you haven't come
as far as I thought.
Let me prove it to you.
[both grunting]
Impressive.
I had a good teacher.
[laughs]
Looks like
you're going home.
[both breathing heavily]
You let me win,
didn't you?
I'll be seeing you soon.
Safe flight.
Thank you.
Yeah.
You ok?
She's not coming.
I'm sorry, Oliver.
You did everything
you could, man.
Oliver...
I'm glad
you changed
your mind.
Still not sure
about flying
commercial, though.
Oh!
Thea,
are you ok?
Yeah. I'm fine.
Laurel?
I didn't know
the arrow
took vacations.
Hey! What happened?
I'm fine. Please.
What happened?
I tried to do good.
It didn't work out.
Oh, Laurel.
I know that
it probably
sounds insane.
It probably is, but...
Sara.
She gave me this.
And when I wear it,
it makes me want
To help people
like she did.
Like she's alive again.
I get it.
Sara had training.
She had years--
Oliver, I know.
Which is why
I need to start,
And I need
your help.
[sighs]
No.
Oliver!
No!
No.
I...
I want you
to consider
What would happen
to your father
If something
happened to you.
Oliver, ever sense
it happened,
I have had this fire
inside of me
That I can't get rid of
with booze or pills.
I need another way!
And the other night,
even though it went wrong
It was the first time
since Sara died
Where I haven't felt that fire.
I'm sorry,
but I can't.
And even if I could,
Sara would never
forgive me.
Yeah.
Hey.
Love you.
I love you both.
The two of you
were all I could
think about.
I'm just trying
to put her down.
That's ok, I just
want to look at her
for a while.
Ok.
I have to head
into the office.
So late?
I do whatever amanda Waller
asks, remember?
You ok?
Yeah.
Just hurry back.
What's with this guy?
Outstanding warrants
for assault and battery
in coast city.
Got an anonymous tip
he was in starling.
Anonymous tip, huh?
That's a bad break,
buddy.
All right.
When can I start?
Do you know how many
of qc's techs
Said this data
was unrecoverable?
Only all of them.
Seems like this would be
a good time to ask
for a few days off, then.
[scoffs] you
just started.
I know. But...My friend
was struck by lightning
And is in a coma.
Well, was.
I don't know. Um, it's--
A long story.
See ya.
Thanks.
You did good
over there.
I had a good teacher.
A judgmental, occasionally
temperamental one, but...
Those are
the best kind.
[chuckles]
Did Thea seem...
Different to you?
Her hair's a lot shorter.
But that's not what you mean.
What do you mean?
I don't know.
She say anything?
She may be...
Seeing somebody in
Corto Maltese, or...
If Thea was with anybody else,
I've got a feeling
I'd be the last one to know.
[footsteps]
Where is she?
Where is Sara?