Previously, on "Arrow"...
[Both grunting]
Curtis: Dr. Palmer got
miniaturization to work.
Felicity: Do it!
I'm not dead.
This is field crew 237,
we're at the star city bank.
We're under attack!
Immediate assistance!
[Tires squealing]
[Canary cry]
The ghosts, they're about to
take over the armored cars.
Yeah, it's just like old times.
[Grunting]
There are guards in the back.
We'll get 'em. Go!
They burned all the money.
They didn't need it.
Federal government sent this
to prop up star city bank.
Hive just wanted to make
sure that didn't happen.
I've heard of having
money to burn,
but stealing money
to burn, that's new.
Darhk's not kidding...
he really wants
this city to die.
Yeah, but why?
I mean, what does hive
have to gain from any of this?
A base of operations.
They have to be
able to operate
out of somewhere.
What better spot
than a dead city?
With almost a dead
police department.
Any luck from that tooth
we got off the hive member
that we took down?
Only that
the deterioration
of the DNA markers
was most definitely not natural.
Which means it was
caused by what?
Curtis and I have been
trying to figure that
out for the past month.
Maybe ray will have better luck.
I will ask.
Hey, you got a sec?
Yeah.
Where'd you get this?
I got that from Lance.
Who got it from Damian darhk.
John, this...
Is pretty definitive evidence
that hive had Andy killed
because his criminal operations
conflicted with theirs.
That doesn't track
at all with what you
have told me about Andy.
Oliver, that doesn't track
with what I knew about Andy.
But...
I guess I really
never knew him at all.
There's got to be
some explanation.
Maybe he was undercover.
Hey, man, listen,
it's all right there.
The facts are the facts.
All I'm saying,
Andy was your brother,
and he deserves
the benefit
of the doubt.
Trust me.
Things aren't always
what they seem.
Yeah, yeah.
Reiter's not going to like this.
Not one bit.
Vlad was a good worker,
and they listened to him.
Well, I didn't have a choice.
He was going to kill me.
Doesn't sound like
something he'd do.
Maybe... maybe he didn't
have a choice, either.
Maybe someone put him up to it.
Maybe it was revenge.
Revenge for what?
For taiana.
That drug stealing
bitch you choked out?
Vlad was her brother.
Ah, thank you for coming
by on such short notice.
Well, happy to have
something to do.
To be honest, I'm feeling
at a bit of a loss
of what to do
with my newfound freedom.
And height. [Chuckles]
Is everything always this big?
If you're looking
for something to do,
why not try, oh, I don't know,
declare yourself
undead, try getting
your company back.
You said you had
something that
you needed help on?
Don't change the subject.
I'm not!
I am a recently undead
billionaire ceo.
My time is at a premium.
What can I do for you?
Thanks, I was wondering
where my tooth went.
John pulled this off of a ghost.
It's their cyanide
retirement plan.
We tried pulling DNA
off of it, but...
But half of the genetic
markers are missing.
That's impossible.
You mean like, "a guy who can
shrink to the size
of a French fry"
impossible?
Well, do you have any
equipment? I'm fresh
out of chromatographs.
Got that.
Can we circle back to why
you won't come back
to Palmer tech?
Your return is exactly
what our stock price needs.
It's incredible.
[Laughs]
The genetic code has
been selectively
degraded.
We know. We think
it's to scramble
the DNA markers
so they can't be
ided. But how?
Well, it looks like
it was done with
a synthetic compound.
Like a chemical crispr/cas9.
Lastrapium trioxide.
Wolfman biologics
has a patent on it.
Thank you.
Ok, tomorrow night,
patrolman's benevolent
association gala.
It's black tie,
so you need a tux.
Which one?
He's got like 50.
Uh, [Chuckles].
Maybe back in the day.
I don't have a tux.
Get a rental.
Doesn't really matter.
Every mayor in the history
of star city has
attended the pba.
I secured a spot for you
on the dais with the brass,
but we need to make sure
that your keynote is on point.
Which means, we need
to find a way to say
that the police
need our help without...
Throwing them under the bus.
Right.
I thought you failed
civics class.
A d-minus,
thank you.
Alex has a way
of making this
interesting.
[Cell phone rings]
[Sighs]
Sorry, uh, wrong number.
What were we saying?
Um, moving on
to Oliver's platform.
I got your email
about cleaning up
star city bay.
Yes!
You know, with everything
this city's facing right now,
a hippie, crunchy
program like...
program that will
add hundreds of jobs,
help gentrify
the surrounding
neighborhoods,
and encourage
outside investment.
And put voters to sleep.
We need to focus
on crime and jobs.
[Cell phone vibrates]
Which this program will address.
Hey, I will put out
a press release tomorrow.
I got to take this.
Ok.
I think your brother's onto us.
No. No, and even
if he was,
it's not like he's
the boss of me.
No, he's the boss of me.
I know.
I'm just glad
your brother's not a killer.
Oh...
Speedy!
Speedy, um...
thea. Sorry,
it's a nickname.
We have to go.
Felicity called about the thing.
The dental problem.
Uh, yes, yeah, sorry.
Um, our... our friend
has, this, uh,
tooth issue.
Yeah.
Good work.
Onsite.
We're clear for entry.
John: All right,
Felicity, what's next?
We need a sample
of the chemical.
With it, ray
can unscramble
the DNA markers
and we can have a shot at iding
some of our ghosts.
Where do we find this thing?
According to
their recently
hacked computers,
second floor, northwest corner.
It's a yellow liquid.
Incoming.
Four ghosts, north entrance.
I'm on it.
[All grunting and groaning]
Looks good, we're in.
Looking for the compound.
Got it.
Green Arrow and speedy
need assistance.
Thanks!
You should go, get out of here.
And what about you?
I've got this. Go.
Felicity, I'm going
for an ID on the ghost
that shot at us. Stand by.
Well, even death's
not permanent anymore.
Sorry.
No, no, it's ok.
Nothing seems
to make sense
anymore.
Andy.
I can't believe this.
Ok, it's obvious that
hive faked his death.
Maybe it was part
of his recruitment...
you saw the file.
You saw what kind of
man my brother was,
what kind of man he is.
We don't know anything,
not until we hear it
directly from Andy.
And how are we
supposed to do that?
We get him out of hive.
Oliver, how are you
still giving him
the benefit
of the doubt?
Because he's your family.
You said he was a good man.
Maybe a part of him still is.
I don't know.
I do. Last month
at the lumber yard,
a ghost had a chance
to kill you, but didn't.
I remember thinking
how weird that was,
unless that ghost was Andy.
So, what, he had
a chance to kill me
and he didn't,
so I'm just
supposed to forget
he's a killer?
No, but you should
still remember
he's your brother.
I can't square
that circle, thea.
That hive member
was nothing
like my brother.
The man that was
my brother's dead.
He's dead.
What brother?
The brother
of the prisoner
that stole the drugs,
but only because
he put him up to it.
You're crazy! That prisoner
attacked you 'cause what
you did to his sister...
that's a lie!
It's a hell of a lot
more believable
than me putting him up
to attacking you.
You know what,
you have had it
in for me
ever since you
found that knap...
enough! I have a means of
divining the truth.
Why did you kill that prisoner?
Because he attacked me.
Aww, come on, man,
this isn't the place
for your hocus pocus crap!
Did you have that prisoner
attack Mr. queen?
Hell no.
[Diviner crackles]
You're lying.
According to what,
a bunch of twigs?
Reiter, don't do this!
You got to hear me out!
It's him!
He's the problem.
He's the problem! Hey!
What are you going to do to him?
Nothing. I believe
the wrong should
make things right.
So, you wanted to see me.
So polite. That's
a bit atypical.
A guy gets slapped
down enough times,
he learns who's boss.
Apparently not.
I'm sorry,
what are you talking about?
After our meeting
last week, I had
an unpleasant encounter
with the green Arrow
and his compatriots.
My security personnel
are under the opinion
that you called
that meeting so as
to create an opportunity
to have me followed.
So your security guys
don't trust me,
but what about you?
Trust is an orchid...
beautiful but delicate.
Requiring ideal
conditions in
order to thrive.
Without those conditions,
it dies.
Tread carefully, Quinton.
Believe it or not,
the death of
your daughter
is not the most terrible thing
that I can threaten you with.
[Cell phone rings]
I don't want to talk to you.
Malcolm: Then why are you
answering the phone?
[Sighs] Because, I...
I would have
told you I was
stopping by,
but you weren't taking my calls.
What do you want?
To help you.
Those men you killed
in nanda parbat,
the effects of
those deaths must be
wearing off by now.
I'm fine.
The blood lust
has returned,
hasn't it?
I have it under control.
You can't control it, thea.
Who's Lawrence Tanner?
Pedophile.
Multiple accusations,
no convictions.
Lives three blocks down.
The world needs
one less pedophile.
And you need
at least a month
of peace.
Look, I'm going to go out, ok?
And when I come home,
you better not still be here,
or I am calling the police.
[Indistinct chatter,
music playing]
Hey.
Alex hired a security detail,
if you want to sit this one out.
Yeah, I'm going
to be at the bar.
Well, this is actually
a better way than how you
usually spend your evenings...
dressing in leather
and tying people up.
There he is!
They're waiting
for you on the dais.
You ready for this?
About to find out.
Evening.
It is our great
privilege to be
here tonight
to honor the star city
police department.
These are a group
of men and women
who risk their lives
for us on a daily basis.
Never been an easy job,
and it has
certainly never
been more difficult
than it is right
now in our city.
These are the people
that keep our streets safe;
who watch over us.
They protect us.
For that, I'm grateful.
And so is the rest of star city.
[Applause]
Not bad.
Not quite
as powerful
as the green
Arrow's,
but not bad.
Yeah? Maybe I should
get him to endorse me.
I need a favor from you.
Need a location of one
of darhk's foot soldiers.
Could be a little difficult.
Darhk called me
into his office
this morning
for a little chat
about how he doesn't
trust me anymore.
Wait, wait, wait,
are you in danger?
I hope not.
But listen,
when I was there,
I saw something
on his desk.
Something about
slip 52 down
at the docks.
Now, if the ghosts are there,
maybe the one
you're looking for
will be there, too.
Ok. Thank you.
All right.
Hey, honey.
How are you?
Thank you.
Club soda.
Yeah, it has to be.
Can't have the candidate's
bodyguard getting hammered.
[Scoffs]
Do you want to talk about?
Resurrected siblings
are kind of in my wheelhouse.
It's not quite
the same thing, Laurel.
[Sighs] Sara wasn't really...
a member
of an organization
of killers?
I'm sure there are
a million things
going through
your head right now.
All I'm saying is,
make one of them
an appreciation for the fact
that your brother
is actually alive.
Well, i... why, so I can...
Hold off some kind of false hope
that he might be decent?
He doesn't deserve that.
No, he probably
doesn't, but you do.
After Andy died,
a part of you
died, too.
And now, now is
your chance to heal.
How am I supposed to do that?
When I had to look...
My nephew in the eye
and tell him that...
He was never going to see
his daddy again...
[Chokes up]
The months after Andy died
were the darkest times
of my life.
I would have given anything,
anything to get Andy back.
I would have sacrificed my life
to have him back
with his wife and his son.
I would have traded
my life for a stranger.
It's so nice to meet you.
Thank you!
Do you think you can
get more funding for the scpd?
Well, that's certainly
a top priority.
That's great news,
thank you.
Sure.
Mr. queen. Huge fan.
Thank you. Mr.?
Darhk. I have some ideas
of how I might contribute
to your campaign.
Do you have a minute?
Of course.
Well, it's not just
about financial support.
I have strong relations
in the business circles,
media outlets as well.
That's all well and good,
but I am running unopposed.
So I don't totally understand
how you can help me win.
Oh, it's not about winning.
It's about how much
we can accomplish
if we worked together.
Right.
And not to be indelicate,
but a lot has
changed in star city
since your parents
held sway here.
The levers of power
have changed.
And not understanding
that is what doomed
Jessica Danforth's bid.
Hmm.
What do you want,
Mr. darhk?
I read the press
release about
your new project.
The restoration of starling bay.
Reconsider your plans.
Leave the bay as it is.
What if I refuse?
Oh, well, then
you'll no longer
be unopposed.
Mr. queen.
Mr. darhk.
Leaving to fight
ra's on the mountaintop,
going undercover
with the league of assassins,
dating the huntress...
What are you doing?
Oh...
I am just listing
all of the terrible ideas
you've had over
the past three years,
of which throwing in
with Damien darhk
has got to be the worst.
I am not throwing in
with Damien darhk!
I am using him to get at hive.
Isn't Lance already
our man on the inside?
Lance has lost darhk's trust,
making this the only way...
To get yourself killed.
You remember the last time
you tried to take down
an evil organization
from the inside?
This is different.
Why?
Because you'd be doing it
as Oliver queen?
Yep.
What about
your mayoral campaign?
You cannot be an effective
candidate for mayor
and darhk's undercover stooge.
Ahem. Taking down darhk
is more important,
especially now that
we know he has Andy
under his thumb.
First, there is a whole
long list of things that
we don't know about Andy.
Second, you didn't
decide to run for mayor
to take down darhk.
You did it to give the city
something that the green Arrow
can't give them...
hope. Inspiration.
Don't lose sight of that.
Not even for John.
This man betrayed us.
He sent an innocent man,
a useful man to his grave.
He conspired against me, you,
all of his brothers.
Baron, please...
His punishment
won't come from me,
but from the one
he sought to hurt.
Oliver, please.
Don't do this.
I'm begging you.
Come on, queen.
Please. Look, I'm sorry,
I'm sorry for everything!
Please don't do this!
Aah!
Harder!
[Groaning]
Aah!
[Giggling]
So... so, I'm sorry,
your friend was reunited
with his brother
after eight years?
It's crazy, right?
Yeah, crazy.
So you have you, uh,
given him your crown yet?
I mean, you held
the record with five years
thinking Oliver was dead, so.
[Chuckles]
I can't imagine
how tough it must have
been for you, thea.
[Cell phone rings]
Sorry.
You know, I should
probably take this.
Ok.
This is Alex. Sorry.
Yeah, what's up?
Hi there.
What are you drinking?
Maybe I can buy you another.
I don't think
my date would
like that very much.
Well, I don't see him here.
You look like the kind of girl
where no means yes.
Come on, baby.
[Groaning and grunting]
Thea! Stop!
[Groans]
What the hell are you doing?
Can't do it?
I can't believe
that Andy's back.
How am I supposed to tell Carly?
She has a right to know, Johnny.
She's better off
thinking he's dead.
I'm not sure that's
your call to make.
I'm not sure about anything.
You know, when
I first found out
about the flash,
and the Lazarus pit
and what it did
for thea...
I began to daydream
about Andy being back.
I would just play
with that idea.
My brother's back.
I never thought
it would
actually happen.
I know.
[Knock on door]
I'll get it.
Hi, Lyla.
Hi, Oliver.
May I come in?
Sure.
I'll, um, give you two a minute.
[Grunts]
[Exhales] How you holding up?
Ah, I guess as good as
can be expected, right?
Nothing really
to compare this to.
At least not this week.
[Sniffs] Ahh.
Lance has some intel for us.
Hmm?
Slip 52 at the docks.
Felicity checked it out,
and that whole area's
been shut down
for the entire night.
Think the ghosts
have something
planned there?
And maybe your brother.
Every time we face the ghosts,
it's Russian roulette.
I'm not risking
any of you for Andy.
You're not.
We're offering.
Ok. But just us.
Thea and Laurel
sit this one out.
Ok.
Gentlemen, you all come
here from different walks,
different paths.
But all burdened
with the same knowledge...
that this world is diseased.
Fortunately,
there is a cure
for this pestilence.
That cure, gentlemen,
is hive.
Those little yellow
pills you swallowed,
they do a few
interesting things...
including making you
cooperative.
Now, I understand
you all volunteered
and that's just swell.
But I think we can
all agree that in
any chain of command,
there can never be
too much compliance.
[Evil chuckle]
Perhaps a demonstration.
Kneel.
The people of this city...
what's left of them,
at any rate...
they call you ghosts.
And they have no idea
how right they are.
Up there!
Kill the green one.
[All grunting]
This isn't on you,
John, it was my call.
Ahem. I never
should have
let you make it.
Felicity, can you
give us a second?
No, I think I should stay.
I just, uh, remembered,
I got that thing
in the whatever
with the what's-it.
Oliver, let this go, man.
I have.
You almost got yourself killed.
[Coughs] I've been a lot
closer to almost killed.
Andy made his choice.
You don't know that.
John, you saw what was
going on tonight.
Those men, they were
under the influence
of something.
Whatever pill
is scrambling their DNA
is also making them
susceptible to dark suggestion.
All right, just because
you have a blind spot
for your family,
don't expect me to, as well.
That... that's not
what this is about.
The hell it's not.
Family is exactly
what this is about.
Criminal or not.
Under the influence or not.
Andy let his son
and his wife
believe he was dead
for eight years, Oliver.
Eight years!
And there's no excuse for that.
None.
John, I'm just...
you don't know.
Oliver, you don't
know. You have this
inexplicable way
of excusing
everything just
because it's family.
It's not inexplicable!
I'm asking you...
ahem. I'm asking you
to hold out hope for Andy,
because I need that hope.
I need to believe
that no matter what
happens in our lives,
no matter how much
darkness infects us,
I need to believe
that we can
come back from that!
And it was exactly that
thinking that led you
to the league last year.
Doesn't seem
like you learned
much from that.
Felicity told you?
Getting in bed
with darhk, Oliver?
I don't see how
you can even
consider it.
[Groans]
We are going
to take this guy down,
and no idea is off the table.
I thought
you're doing things
differently, Oliver.
Fighting darhk from the inside
is just fighting darhk
in the shadows.
You want to do
things differently?
You want ideas, fine.
Let's take this
son of a bitch down
in the light of day.
Hey.
Just in time.
For what?
Ah, roasted lizard
with a little bit
of coriander and sea salt.
I've gotten better
at removing the skin
with a sharp rock.
I ate already.
Thank you.
Are you all right?
It's a hard day.
Taiana...
I have to...
I have to tell you
something about your brother.
Vlad?
Is he all right?
No.
I'm sorry.
What do you mean?
Is he...
taiana...
I'm very sorry.
Hey.
Sorry, I had Curtis
grab some more toys
so I could keep
working on your tooth.
That's ok; I don't
think we're going
to be using the table
for eating tonight, anyway.
Oliver and John
are busy fighting over
John's not-so-dead
after all brother.
Do I even want to ask?
Let's just say
you no longer
corner the market
on not being dead
as people think.
Though, in John's
brother's case,
he does have
a pretty good excuse...
unlike some people.
Have you seen anyone?
Of course not;
I've been busy here
working on your tooth.
You're stalling.
Ray, when you come
back from the dead,
you're supposed to
start living again.
What's going on?
I've been catching up
on the past six months.
My company, my city, my life.
And I feel like
tom Sawyer watching
his own funeral.
Except in my case,
nobody really cares.
That is not true, ray.
Renaming starling
star city is nice,
but then take a look
to what's happened
to the place.
And my company,
this thing I've built
that was supposed to outlast me,
is now on life support.
Because it needs you.
To do what?
The same thing I was doing
before I died?
Obviously that didn't
amount to anything.
Oh, self-pity is not
a good look on you.
Ah, I don't think
it's self-pity.
I think it's self-reflection.
If I'm going
to come back to life,
I have to figure out
what it is that
I'm living for.
Ok.
I played around
with your bicuspid a bit.
Ah, the, uh, compound
definitely broke down
the residual DNA on the tooth.
It's pretty inventive, actually.
Is there any way to
reconstitute the DNA
so we have a shot
at iding these guys?
No. Once the alleles
are decomposed,
they're gone for good.
Yeah.
So since that was a dead end,
I took another look
at the polymer
the fake tooth was made of.
Uh, I found faint traces
of sodium fluoride.
Like from water?
There's no way that
the concentration
could be high enough
to leave behind
any sort of residue.
It would if there was
an unusually high
sodium fluoride count
in the drinking water,
like say in the facility
that was closed down
for that very reason.
Muller psychiatric center.
You got to admire the irony
of Damien darhk keeping
his army of bad guys
in a defunct looney bin.
Not bad for a guy who
thinks his life didn't
add up to anything.
Never going to outlive that one.
Everyone clear on the plan?
You know, I wasn't
the first 80 times
we went over it,
but now I think I got it.
What's going on, guys?
Felicity found
a probable location
for the ghosts'
base of operations.
These guys are not going
to be easy to take out.
How are you feeling?
[Sighs]
We're not trying
to take down the ghosts;
We don't have the manpower.
Going after Andy.
Guys, Oliver nearly
got himself killed
trying to help Andy.
I'm not letting you do the same.
I'm sorry, but it's not
really just up to you.
I did everything that I could
to bring my sister back,
and I think
your brother
deserves the same.
No, Laurel,
that's just it...
i don't think he does.
And I don't know
what Oliver told you...
he told them
the only two things
that matter...
Andy's under darhk's influence,
and we need to get him out.
I can't let you risk your life
for someone who
does not deserve it.
That's your call.
But we've made ours.
Let's move.
Oliver: We're onsite.
Oh, satellite's
reading a hell
of a lot of activity
for 3:00 in the morning.
I'm guessing 50
or so ghosts
plus who knows
how many recruits.
Hey, wait,
if the ghosts
are wearing
their usual Halloween costume,
then how are we
supposed to tell
which one's Andy?
That's what your fancy
new cameras are for.
A little gift from Curtis.
Infrared lenses
should virtually unmask
our ghosty friends.
Sick.
Ok, ready?
I'm in position.
In position.
This isn't just
a base of operations.
It looks like a staging area.
For what?
Equipment.
Military crates marked g6:5.
Does that mean anything?
Maybe they're playing bingo.
Let's assume that's not it.
Deadly bingo.
Ahem. We need to get
an ID on Andy.
When we do, you wait
for my signal
before engaging.
Yeah, I might not
have that option.
Speedy?
She's been spotted,
third floor,
southwest building.
Laurel: I've been spotted,
too. [Grunting]
[Grunting and groaning]
I might be able
to get a visual
on our target!
[Grunting]
Waiting on confirmation.
That's him, you got him,
the one on your right.
Actually, he's got
me! [Grunting]
[Elevator dings]
Thea: I got him.
He looks heavy,
I need help in here.
I'm on my way.
It's Merida.
Aren't you out
a little bit
past your bedtime?
I've seen something
of your fighting style.
You were trained
by ra's al ghul.
Tell me... how is Malcolm
doing these days?
[Gasping]
That usually works.
[Grunting and groaning]
[Gasping]
[All grunting]
Black canary's got Andy,
but she needs help
reaching the exfil.
I got this!
Are you sure?
Go!
It's, uh, nice
of you to show up.
My brother needed me.
The green one.
Thank you, thank you,
thank you, all of you.
Palmer, even you, thank you.
My pleasure.
Feels good to do
something useful.
It's been a while.
Does that mean I can
expect to see you
at work tomorrow?
Ah... No.
Can't keep doing
the same useless,
ineffective things.
You know? I got to
do something different.
I'm going to take some time
and figure out what that is.
But, uh, it still include
the occasional super heroics
whenever you need me.
Where are you going?
Well, I have a long overdue chat
with my brother.
I hope you were right.
Me, too.
You were right.
About what?
Darhk. I thought
about what you said,
and how to fight him.
I'm going to do it
in the light of day.
Good. What did you have in mind?
You'll see.
We never should
have gotten on
that damn boat!
Reiter's men
hijacked the yacht
that we were working on.
I was a dive instructor
and vlad was the deckhand.
They killed everyone
on our charter
and they brought us here.
What happened?
With vlad?
Conklin.
I'll kill him, that monster!
Taiana, wait, wait.
I'm going to kill him
for what he did!
Conklin is...
is terrible,
but he's not the problem.
He's just a pawn.
Pawn for what?
For reiter's plan.
What is this?
This is a map of lian yu,
and I think that it leads
to whatever reiter
is looking for.
Can you follow it?
Not without a...
Detailed survey map
of the island.
Where would we get
something like that?
Well, I had an idea.
It's a long shot,
but it's worth a try.
To get there,
I'll need your help.
[Knock on door]
Thank you for coming.
Are you sure you
don't have the scpd
waiting for me in the kitchen?
Don't be so paranoid.
You did threaten me with arrest
the last time I popped by.
So...
Did you reconsider my advice?
Yes.
And I'm still not
going to take it.
Look... I think
I might have found
a different way
for me to control my blood lust,
one that does not include
killing people.
What does it include?
Damien darhk.
Last night, we went after hive,
and I ran into Damien.
I've seen what he can
do with his powers,
but when he tried
to use them on me,
it completely backfired.
And my blood lust was gone.
I mean, at least
for a little while.
So what I want
is for you to help me
figure out a way
to make that permanent.
Andy, I don't even
know where to begin.
Andy, I need to understand.
Can you help me understand?
Is what's in this file true?!
Andy, answer me.
It's true.
All of it.
[Birds squawking]
Well, this is quite
a lot of media
for a, uh, what'd you call it?
Hippie, crunchy program.
That's right.
Always happy to admit
when I'm wrong.
Good luck up there.
Thank you.
Ok, sorry I'm late.
Ah, you're fine.
We're just getting started.
So, I...
Haven't been
arrested
for battery yet.
I keep thinking...
You would have killed him
if I hadn't stopped you.
I just had a really bad night.
I guess I'm just asking if
maybe you could be
a little patient...
With me.
[Indistinct chatter]
Thank you all for coming.
My, uh,
my campaign advisor
doesn't think that
saving the bay
is the right fight
given the state the city is in.
But I'd like everyone
to know that I'm not blind
to star city's problems.
And I wouldn't be here today
if I wasn't confident
that this program
could help solve them.
And the reason I chose the bay
is because it's in
the center of the city.
It's out in the open.
For everyone to see.
The fight to save star city
isn't going to be
fought in the shadows.
It's going to be fought
in the light of day.
And I promise you,
all of you,
that I will never
stop fighting
to save this city.
Woman: We love you!
[Cheers and applause]
Greg, move your head.