My name is Moira Dearden Queen.
I am the acting CEO of Queen Consolidated.
And God forgive me, I have failed this city.
I have been complicit in an undertaking
with one horrible purpose:
To destroy the Glades and everyone in it.
[ON TV]
If you reside in the Glades...
...please, you need to get out now.
Your lives and the lives of your children
depend on it.
Please.
Warden says we gotta evacuate.
-Help me get these out of here.
-What about the inmates?
Leave them.
[CLINKING]
[BUILDING RUMBLING]
[ALARM BLARING]
[INMATES SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
INMATE 1:
Help!
INMATE 2:
Yo, man! Come on!
INMATE 1:
Hey!
COUNT:
Hmm.
INMATE 2:
Yo, man! Come on!
INMATE 3: Come on!
INMATE 4: Come on, man!
INMATE 5: Over here. Let me out.
-No.
-No. No.
INMATE 6: Unlock it.
-Too violent.
INMATE 7: Take me.
-Too sloppy. Too stupid.
INMATE 8: Let me out.
-Get me out of here!
-Too ambitious.
You.
Love your work.
Big future.
Hey, be careful.
There's liable to be aftershocks.
Oh, I'm counting on it.
INMATE 8:
Come on! Hey!
Hey, you can't go!
REPORTER 1: There go the Queens!
REPORTER 2: Oliver!
Mr. Queen, what are your mother's chances?
Is she on suicide watch?
-What is your mother's condition?
REPORTER 3: Can you give any comment?
It's not fair. They're not the ones on trial.
That won't stop Jean Loring from using them
as props to drum up sympathy.
You don't seem concerned.
She confessed to being an accomplice
on live television.
She also said that
Malcolm Merlyn coerced her.
You have something, don't you?
I thought I was your co-counsel, Adam.
If you're holding a trump card...
-...don't you think you should share it with me?
-It's going to be a good trial.
Come on. Let's get inside.
-You don't have to do this.
-Ivo says we do.
-Your friends are a danger to his men.
CAPTAIN: Go. Quick and quiet.
Slade, Shado, run! Unh.
[GUNFIRE]
CAPTAIN:
There's no one here.
They must've moved on from their position.
Charges are set. Here's the detonator.
Make sure they have no place to return to.
Go.
And you.
Now you're gonna take us to the graves.
Let's go.
Get him up.
Let's get clear.
[DEVICE BEEPING]
-Did you find the detonator?
-Yes.
We were lucky.
I was lucky. You were good.
Either way...
...they have Oliver.
I'm going after him.
Not alone.
You can barely walk.
All the more reason not to stay here.
Give them another chance at blowing me up.
[REPORTERS CHATTERING]
-You two okay? Ahem.
-I should be asking you that.
-Yeah, well, I'm fine.
-You look like you have the flu.
If that's true,
I shouldn't have gotten vaccinated.
Diggle, whatever it is, just go home.
-Oliver, listen. I can take care of things.
-No, we'll be fine, all right? Go rest.
And don't make me call a cop.
There are a few of them around here.
MOIRA [ON TV]: I have been complicit
in an undertaking with one horrible purpose:
To destroy the Glades and everyone in it.
And it worked. The Glades were destroyed.
Homes and lives were lost.
All because of her actions.
True, she had second thoughts, remorse,
which compelled her to deliver this statement.
But on behalf of the 503 lives
that were extinguished that day...
...I say, Moira Queen,
your remorse comes too late.
For the last five years...
...under the threat for my life
and the lives of my family...
Why wouldn't those threats silence her?
Why wouldn't Moira Queen be terrified?
Malcolm Merlyn killed her first husband,
abducted her second.
Why wouldn't she be in fear for her life?
For the lives of her children?
What would you do if it were your children
in the crosshairs of a madman's rage?
SNOW [ON COMPUTER]:...they say
the S.T.A.R. Labs particle accelerator...
...will be turned on right on schedule.
In other news, we have
just received word that both sides...
...have now completed their opening statements
in the Moira Queen trial.
FELICITY: Don't take this the wrong way,
but you look disgusting.
Yeah, well, I don't feel great, Felicity.
Is there a right way to take that?
-You should go home.
-I am going.
I just need to make arrangements
for a replacement bodyguard.
Did you get the flu shot?
Personally, I never do. I know that I should.
I just... I have this thing about needles.
All pointy things, really.
Ironic, considering who we work with.
-Yeah, it's not the flu, Felicity, it's more like...
-Dig.
MAN:
Hello?
Are you here?
COUNT:
Here. There.
Everywhere.
So how goes our little science project?
Working like you said it would.
Heh. How wonderful.
Uh, so listen, doing the thing was 50,000.
Keeping quiet about it
I'm thinking should be 50 more.
Heh. Oh, I want word to spread.
That's kind of the whole objective, actually.
You see my point?
[YELLS]
You should know I find post hoc
negotiation distasteful.
[SIGHS]
Such a shame you won't get to see
what your works have wrought, doctor.
But soon everyone else will.
And they'll beg for it to end.
MAN [ON TV]:
That's exactly right...
...and given the extreme interest
in the case from all corners...
DIGGLE:
What are you doing here?
-I heard you passed out.
-I said not to call.
Before that, you said "gah" and "thud,"
so I didn't take it very seriously.
-She was right. You need medical attention.
FELICITY: He needs more than that.
When Dig passed out,
I sent his blood sample to a chemist at QC.
The guy owes me a favor. Long story.
I fixed his parking ticket.
-Huh. I guess it's not that long.
-Felicity.
-Blood sample?
FELICITY: Yeah.
It came back positive
for trace amounts of Vertigo.
-I've never used Vertigo.
-You were exposed to it somehow.
Vertigo's in play again?
When the Count recovered from his OD
on Vertigo, he was sent to Iron Heights.
That got hit in the quake.
He got out the same way the Dollmaker did?
And just like with the Dollmaker...
...prison officials worked overtime
to keep a lid on the escape.
-I know what you're thinking.
-No, you don't.
I made a choice not to put an arrow in this guy.
And it was the right choice.
There's no more killing.
I worked this up to counteract
the effects of Vertigo. Give it to Diggle.
I need to get back to court.
Work up whatever you can.
Figure out how Diggle got Vertigo
in his system without his knowledge.
Go.
DONNER: When was the first time you heard
about this so-called undertaking?
When everyone else did.
When my mother gave the press conference.
-Doesn't seem like you took it too well.
-I was surprised.
Who wouldn't be?
[CLEARS THROAT]
Uh, your mother was immediately
taken into custody...
...but I assume you went
to the precinct to see her?
Actually, I didn't see her
until she was moved.
To the prison?
Do you remember when you visited her?
Not the exact date.
DONNER:
It's okay. I have the visitor log here.
October 9th.
Five months later. Why so long?
Um, I... I...
Are you okay?
An answer, please. Why did it take you
five months to visit your mother?
-Your Honor, if I...
-No. I want to hear this.
I needed time.
-I was...
DONNER: Angry.
So angry, perhaps, that it took you
five months to forgive her?
-It was complicated.
-No.
It's very simple.
You blamed your mother for what she'd done.
So why shouldn't the jury?
Your Honor, we have no more questions
for the witness.
LAUREL:
Adam.
[GASPS]
Where is it?
Come on. Where is it?
The Hozen. Where is it?
OLIVER: What?
IVO: The arrowhead.
Every report said it was with these bodies.
You said you and your friends were here.
Now, where is it?
Take him outside.
Make him show you where his friends are.
[GRUNTS THEN GROANS]
CAPTAIN: Take us to them.
-I don't know where they are.
[OLIVER GROANS]
CAPTAIN: Tell me or you lose your hand.
-Let us suggest another option.
You hand the kid over to us,
and we don't kill you all.
OLIVER:
Hey, are you okay?
Don't worry about me. I can take it.
It's okay, it's okay. Relax.
[SIREN WAILING]
Was that as bad as it seemed?
JEAN:
Thea's testimony? It was a setback.
-We were counting on her to...
-Humanize me.
Frankly, yes.
And now we're gonna have to go another way.
-No. No, I told you, I won't testify...
-I know you did, but now you have to.
OLIVER:
She's right, Mom.
Jean, can you give us a minute?
Yeah.
I know what you're going to say.
-But if I testify, it will destroy our family.
-If your lawyer's right, you don't have a choice.
Mom, secrets are what put you
in this situation. Secrets and lies.
And now it is time to give the truth its day.
SNOW [ON COMPUTER]: I don't want us to lose
sight of the other major event in court today.
Was there any indication
of Adam Donner being ill?
No, there was very little warning
before Mr. Donner collapsed to the ground.
I've spoken to several people
in the courtroom, and a couple...
How you feeling?
-Fine.
-You have a lousy poker face, Diggle.
-Did he take the antidote?
-Didn't work.
-Count must've futzed with his recipe.
-Heard what happened with Donner.
And with Thea.
How is she?
It'll be fine.
Your poker face isn't much better
than mine, Oliver.
[STATIC CRACKLES ON COMPUTER]
-Hello, Starling City.
-Felicity.
Miss me?
Many of you have noticed
that you're not feeling like yourselves.
-He's taken over all the local station feeds.
-Track his signal.
Like our good assistant district attorney.
You might recognize him...
...from his work
in the ongoing Moira Queen trial.
Hi, Adam.
-What do you want?
COUNT: I want what you want:
-For you to feel better.
-Go to hell.
I do think you want the pain to end.
And I can do that.
With Vertigo. It's what all your bodies crave.
Fortunately, the power of relief is right here.
All you have to do is go to your neighborhood
Vertigo dealer and request the cure.
Simple supply and demand at work.
Now, tell me you want this, and it's yours.
All that pain will just disappear.
Say it.
Say you want it.
[STAMMERS]
I want it.
You see? A simple solution.
I'm Count Vertigo, and I approve this high.
What do we do now?
We find him...
...and we shut him down.
[INAUDIBLE DIALOGUE]
Where'd he broadcast from?
He bounced the signal off a S.T.A.R. Labs
satellite. Could've sent it from Markovia.
He'd want to stay local. Scrub the footage,
frame by frame if you have to.
-There is something here that gives us a clue.
-If he dosed the city...
-...why do only some people show symptoms?
-Maybe exposure was selective.
The Count contaminated something certain
people, like you and Donner, consumed.
MAN [ON COMPUTER]:
...Bethany Snow, with a special report.
A most dramatic turn.
City officials are urging calm...
...hoping to avoid widespread panic.
Deputy Mayor Levitz has enlisted...
The Count has turned Starling
into a city of junkies.
Any leads on where he's holding
ADA Donner?
Mm-mm, no. As cold as it sounds,
I've got other concerns. Laurel?
-Adam's trial notes are very thorough.
KATE: They better be.
-You're lead counsel now.
-Ms. Spencer, you're the district attorney.
Yes, but you're the one that the jury knows.
-You'll do fine, Laurel.
-I know.
I just found Adam's trump card.
[MELLOW POP MUSIC PLAYING
ON HEADPHONES]
Sorry, I didn't hear you walk up.
I just wanna be left alone.
Too bad that's not an option for you,
but maybe I know something that is.
[SIGHS]
-Hit me.
-What?
You wonder why I used to go out at night
looking to throw down with bad guys.
Part of it was to help the city.
And the other part was to help me.
Getting tuned up
by street thugs helped you?
Yeah, well, I gave as good as I got.
When I would throw a punch,
I'd be so angry.
I'd feel this heat rising inside of me.
In my jaw.
In my chest.
In my fists.
But it needed somewhere to go.
Come on.
Thea, you're angry.
At your mother, the DA, yourself maybe.
But that anger is gonna chew up
your insides if you don't let it out.
-I'm not gonna hit you, Roy.
-Try.
Try.
I said hit me, right? Because that felt like...
That didn't really feel like anything.
Better.
But keep your wrist straight. Don't just
use your arm. Put your entire body into it.
Come on. Again.
[GRUNTING]
At least let me call Lyla.
-All she could do is worry about me.
-I found something.
-I don't see anything.
-Because you have to see what Donner does.
His eye caught a reflection.
Can you enhance?
FELICITY:
It hurts me that you feel the need to ask.
-What are those, wings?
FELICITY: It's the city seal.
Starling Municipal Records Department.
It's been abandoned since the city went digital.
Dollars to donuts,
that's where the Count is operating.
Not for long.
You shouldn't be here.
-My attorney needs to...
-Moira.
I know I could be disbarred for speaking
with you, but this isn't something for lawyers.
This is a family matter.
Jean told me she's calling you
to the stand tomorrow.
-Yes.
-You can't testify.
Well, the fact that you don't want me to,
Laurel, is a good indication that I should.
If you take the stand, I have to cross-examine
you. I'll have to do it to the best of my ability.
-I understand.
-No, I don't think you do.
Forget about what this will do
to Oliver and Thea.
It also could undermine your entire case.
So, Moira, please.
Please, don't make me use this.
Everything is at stake for you.
And I don't wanna be the one
to take it all away.
Faster, please.
Faster. We have a city full of customers.
And I mean this literally.
I'm afraid my production apparatus is a little
overtaxed with the increased demand.
I can live with it, though.
Can't say the city can.
GREEN ARROW: Go.
-Be still my heart.
[BOTH GRUNTING]
GREEN ARROW:
Step away from them.
Yes, I heard you developed
an allergy to killing.
GREEN ARROW: Do it!
-Or what?
You'll kill me?
[DONNER GRUNTING]
You're really on the no-killing wagon.
Shame.
You're really letting one of life's
true pleasures pass you by.
You said you didn't want to testify.
But you have to.
Because of me.
-No.
-You have to do damage control.
None of this is your fault.
We're here because of what I did.
Now, you both know the truth,
but you don't know all of it.
-Laurel does.
-What does she have?
You shouldn't have to find this out in court.
Find out what?
Years ago... It was many years ago.
...your father was engaging in his...
His extramarital activities.
And I had a moment of weakness.
I cheated on him.
With Malcolm Merlyn.
THEA:
No.
No, I asked you about this.
Last year.
You said
there was nothing between you two.
There wasn't, sweetheart. It wasn't an affair.
It was very brief and a long time ago.
And despite it,
you remained friends with Mr. Merlyn.
In fact, he frequently
attended parties at your home.
He was my husband's best friend
until Malcolm killed him.
And this is why you claim to feel
as though you were in fear for your life...
-...and the lives of your children.
-Well, I think it's a fairly compelling reason.
Last year, your second husband, Walter Steele,
was abducted by Mr. Merlyn, is that correct?
Yes. So you see...
Why didn't Merlyn kill Walter
the same as your first husband?
I convinced Malcolm not to.
And Malcolm listened to you.
Your friend spared Walter's life...
...and yet you'd have this jury believing
that you and your children were in danger?
-We were. I was afraid...
-Afraid of getting caught.
MOIRA: Despite whatever youthful mistakes
I might have made...
...Malcolm Merlyn was a dangerous man.
To other people.
But the only person who truly posed a danger
to Moira Queen and her family...
...was Moira Queen.
-Hey.
-Look, if you wanna attack me, go right ahead.
But you should know you're not gonna
say anything I haven't already said to myself.
Whoa. I know that that was difficult for you,
and I just wanna make sure that you're okay.
No. No.
I don't understand how you could forgive me
after what I just did in there.
I don't understand how anyone could.
So obviously you three
took the Hozen out of this cave.
Lift him up.
Now, I know he doesn't have it,
which means one of you two does.
Give it to me, and we'll discuss an exchange.
We don't know what you're talking about.
Give us Oliver,
and we'll leave you alone to look for it.
[GROANS]
Anybody else wanna be stupid?
Hey. Hey!
Fine. Take him. Cut him loose.
-Move! Move!
SARA: What are you doing?
[GUNFIRE]
We have to keep moving.
They're following us.
We know.
[BOMB BEEPING]
[YELLS]
SNOW [ON COMPUTER]:We're continuing
to monitor both of these major stories...
...on what has become a significant news day
here in Starling. What can you tell us about...?
Oliver's gotta be
pretty wrapped up with his mother.
You making progress on how the Count's
getting Vertigo into people's systems?
Not much. Each dot is the home
of somebody with withdrawal symptoms.
DIGGLE:
It seems pretty random.
That's because it's very random.
DIGGLE:
Okay.
What if people weren't exposed at home?
What if they got dosed at work?
Can you do this
by their employment addresses?
I'm really starting to wonder
what it would take to impress you guys.
Look, it's a trail. A path through the city.
-Any place you've been?
-59th and Dell. Where I got my shot.
You got your vaccination from one of those
trucks, right? One of those roving flu trucks?
The route.
A flu vaccination tour,
a truck sent out by Starling City Mobile Care.
I got addicted after one injection?
That can happen?
Sure. Try heroin sometime.
-Not "try" try.
-All right, where's the truck now?
Downtown. What do you think?
-Call Oliver?
-No, no, he's busy with his family. I'll go. I'll go.
Yeah, no. That's not happening.
I'll go.
-It's too dangerous.
-It could turn out to be nothing.
If it's not, I'll call.
SNOW:
...courtroom drama you just witnessed?
Bethany, no one expected the turn
that testimony took.
A revelation that Moira Queen
once had an affair with Malcolm Merlyn...
...became the sole focus
of the prosecution's cross.
Hello?
Anybody home?
Vertigo. Gotcha.
Funny, you took the words
right out of my mouth.
JEAN: Thea?
THEA: Can we call it a night?
JEAN:
Jury signaled they could have a verdict.
The judge will not send them home.
He wants to get this over with.
-Line forms behind me.
-A verdict that quickly is bad, isn't it?
I think the two of you
should prepare for the worst.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Excuse me.
-Felicity.
COUNT [OVER PHONE]: Oliver.
Is it okay if I call you Oliver?
Surprised to hear from me, right?
Not as surprised as I was.
You see, I find this not unattractive blond
getting all up in my business.
And what does she have on her?
A Queen Consolidated ID badge.
Now, I think to myself,
"Why does that name ring a bell?"
Oliver Queen.
He tried to buy off me last year.
Just before the Hood
put me in a padded cell.
Ipso facto, Arrow.
-Where are you going?
-Um...
Something's come up at the office.
-Ollie, the jury.
-I have to go.
[RUSTLING NEARBY]
Pretty swanky offices.
You can see all the destruction
that your mom caused from up here.
What do you want?
World peace and personal satisfaction.
Though not necessarily in that order.
You poisoned me and put me in a hole.
You have no idea
how much I hated you for that.
-Turns out someone else hates you too.
-Who?
Heh. Oh, you're going to be surprised
when you find out.
He's a man of means.
Set me up with my new operation
so I could draw you out.
-To do what?
-This.
[GUNFIRE]
-You're gonna have to try harder.
-Done.
Come on.
So now we move on to plan B.
-Oliver, don't. Not for me.
-Quiet, please. I'm threatening.
Lower your bow.
[ARROW CLATTERS]
Your problem is with me, it's not with her.
Then consider this your penalty
for making me go to plan B in the first place.
Hey. Hey, hey. Shh, shh, shh.
It's all right. You're safe.
-You were shot.
-Hey.
It's nothing.
[SIRENS WAILING]
-Any news?
-Where have you been?
Something happened
at Queen Consolidated.
And you will see it on the news later.
Don't worry about it.
What would you have done
if there'd been a verdict?
Thea...
...I don't know.
Are you okay?
Hey. Jury's back.
Come on.
I have received a note
that the jury has arrived at a verdict.
Please publish the verdict.
"In the Superior Court of Star County,
State v. Moira Queen, verdict.
On one count of conspiracy in the first degree,
the defendant is found not guilty.
On the 503 counts of murder in the first degree,
the defendant is found...
...not guilty."
[CROWD MURMURING]
I don't believe it.
Mom.
I love you both so much.
[REPORTERS CHATTERING]
A stunning result
as Moira Queen is acquitted of all charges.
In a day that's provided a week's worth
of shocks and legal twists...
...many had pronounced this case
a done deal.
Congratulations. Is that appropriate?
She should have lost.
Should have been convicted.
Did you want her to be?
I expected her to be.
-Verdict doesn't make sense.
-Still, your mom must be thrilled. Beyond.
It's more like shock, I think.
They're processing her now.
I just wanted to check in on you.
-And you.
DIGGLE: I'm feeling better.
And with the Vertigo-tainted vaccine...
...Queen Consolidated's
Applied Sciences division...
...was able to formulate
a nonaddictive treatment.
Good.
Need to meet my family at home.
So you guys go home, get rest.
-Good night.
Oliver?
-I just wanted to say thank you.
-Yeah.
And I'm sorry.
For what?
I got myself into trouble again,
and you killed him.
You killed again, and I am sorry...
...I put you in a position
where you had to make that kind of choice.
Felicity.
He had you and he was gonna hurt you.
There was no choice to make.
-Why did you do that?
-You stopped the Captain from killing me.
Thank you for coming.
-Shado, he doesn't look too good.
SHADO: He's not.
-Who's this?
-It's complicated.
That Hozen thing they're looking for
is back on the plane.
No, I've got it.
There's a Buddhist inscription on one side.
It reminded me of my father.
I'm pretty sure they're not
interested in Buddhism.
What's on the other side?
"Thirty, 31, 75, 12."
Numbers, what?
Coordinates.
But to what?
A Kairyu-class Japanese submarine
which ran aground here during World War II.
What do these guys want
with a 70-year-old sub?
The sub isn't important, but what's on it...
...it'll save the human race.
Will it save him?
Well, you survived your own stupidity.
Congratulations.
You know...
...I needed you to deal with any resistance
that I encountered on the island.
I gotta say,
you've done a fairly lousy job of that.
Congratulations. You're the new captain.
I arrange for the Count to take out the Arrow.
And all I accomplish
is reigniting the vigilante's killing spree.
Sir, there's been a development.
BROTHER BLOOD:
Brother Cyrus.
How do you feel?
Stronger.
BROTHER BLOOD:
Good.
Then you're ready.
[REPORTERS CHATTERING]
Mrs. Queen, how does it feel
to get away with murder?
I want you to go out back.
There's a car waiting for you.
-Did you kill your first husband?
-Just keep going.
Obviously Mrs. Queen is overjoyed that the jury
has ruled she was acting under terrible duress.
REPORTER: Can you give us anything?
JEAN: I'm afraid...
DRIVER: This way, Mrs. Queen.
-Yes.
The freeway will be quicker.
I'm sorry, Mrs. Queen.
I was instructed not to take you home. Not yet.
Where are we? I don't know this place.
I've got her, sir.
Hello, Moira.
You... You're suppo...
They said you were dead.
There are parts of the world
where death is an illusion. I've been to one.
I learned to be very convincing.
But I returned because you needed my help.
-Help?
-With your trial.
You didn't think that jury acquitted you
without a little persuasion?
MOIRA:
Dear God.
What do you want, Malcolm?
I still have resources in Starling.
Associates.
Heh. Including one in the DA's office.
I followed Mr. Donner's investigation
of you with interest.
The ease with which you lied about us for years,
it made me wonder whether you lied to me.
No.
It was a matter of a simple surreptitious
genetics test to confirm my suspicions.
Don't.
Imagine my joy at learning
that Thea is my daughter.