My name is Oliver Queen.
After five years
on a hellish island,
I have come home
with only one goal--
to save my city.
But to do so, I can't be
the killer I once was.
To honor my friend's memory,
I must be someone else.
I must be something else.
Previously on "Arrow"...
Who's blood?
An alderman from the Glades
trying to save the city.
I'm surprised that
you wanted to meet.
I'm not your enemy.
You're not a friend.
I'm hoping
to prove otherwise.
You told me
to stay out of the Glades.
to get out of CNRI.
Tommy was only there
because I was too stubborn.
You were right.
I was blaming the Arrow because
it's all my fault, dad!
It's all my fault
that Tommy died.
What's going on
with this woman?
She keeps following you
around, helping you out.
We've got to find her.
To stop her, or to send her
a thank you note?
That depends.
On what?
What side she's on.
Mr. Queen's going to be late.
He's extremely sorry.
It couldn't be helped.
Where is he?
Um...
Over there!
Where, man?!
There, man!
Just got a little held up.
You know, tying up
some loose ends.
I'm actually in direct contact
with him now. Let me--let me check.
Where are you getting the guns?
Are you going
to kill me?
Get it over with.
Dig.
Took down two more
gangbangers.
They were armed with fully
automatic M4A1 assault rifles.
M4A1s
are military grade weapons.
Stolen, most likely.
Stolen from where?
Well, we can look into that
after your party.
What party?
He's here.
Sorry I'm late.
This party is to
attract investors
for your failing
company.
Being fashionably
late might do well
for the club circuit,
but it does not inspire
confidence
in Wall Street.
Is that blood on your face?
Hmm?
Don't worry,
it's not his blood.
I mean, of course
it's his blood.
Why would he have somebody
else's blood on his face?
Who taught you
to shave? Mister.
What kept you?
Was it our masked blonde
that carries that giant staff
to beat the sauce
out of attackers?
This time it was guns.
Guns?
We were just talking
about guns.
Hey. Oliver.
Hi.
What's your interest
in guns, Mr. Queen?
Never touched them myself.
The gun epidemic in the Glades
has gotten increasingly
out of control.
Which is why the DEA's
office has committed
to ending gun violence.
Well, I'm sure the police
are doing whatever they can
to catch whoever's bring
the weapons into the city.
Did I say
something funny?
They know who's been
arming the gangs, Oliver.
The Mayor.
The...
I thought the hood copycats
killed the mayor.
Well, not the actual mayor.
A local gang lord
calls himself the Mayor.
Think he's the man
to save our city.
But that position has
already been filled, hasn't it?
Now this mayor
has only one goal--
to create chaos
so he can rule the Glades
with the barrel of a gun.
You are noticeably unarmed, son.
Sorry, Mr. Mayor.
Um, we ran into
the Vigilante,
and, um, he ganked
our weapons.
Do you know who I was
before the quake?
I was no one.
I had no name.
None that mattered, anyway.
I was just another weak man
waiting to get fired
or evicted or killed.
But then the ground shook,
and now I matter,
because I know the guy
with the biggest gun wins,
and that's why I will
rule the Glades.
But there's no room at my table
for weak ass punks like you.
Mr. Mayor. I want
to ask for leniency.
The kid's my cousin.
I brought him in.
Oh, you did?
Now let's hope you do
your family prouder than he did.
Hey.
Please do not ask me
if I'm ok,
because I am sick to death
of everyone asking me that!
I would never do that.
Good.
You ok?
The Doll Maker was just
your garden variety
traumatic experience.
After the quake and Tommy,
I should be used
to that by now.
I've had
a few of those.
You never
get used to them.
Ahem. Excuse me, Oliver,
may I talk to you for a second?
It's urgent.
Yeah.
You can have him back
in a minute.
Excuse us.
I just realized
something.
What if our
masked friend
that keeps showing up
everywhere you go,
you know her?
What about her?
What if we've been going
about this the wrong way?
We thought she was
obsessed with you.
I mean, she showed up
in the D.A.'s office
when you were there...
And in the chemical plant where
the Doll Maker was holed up.
But who else was at
both those places?
What if our masked
friend isn't following you?
She's following Laurel.
Can it get any louder?
Why are you following
Laurel Lance?
I could ask
the same thing of you.
I guess some things
never change.
You and her,
always and forever.
Who are you?
Once you know, your life
will never be the same.
I could take it.
Not this time.
Ollie.
Oh, Laurel's
going to kill me.
Sarah?
I'll give you some time
to let it sink in.
♪ Arrow 2x04 ♪
Crucible
Original Air Date on October 30, 2013
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Sarah Lance?
Laurel's sister?
The detective's other daughter,
the one that you took
on "The Gambit" with you
even though you were
dating Laurel at the time,
which we never talked about--
Felicity, please.
I'm sorry, it's just...
Isn't she--isn't she dead?
You told everyone that she died
when "The Gambit" went down,
that she drowned.
You lied.
When "The Gambit"
capsized, uh...
Sarah was pulled under.
It was so dark and cold.
And I thought she drowned.
About year later,
I saw her.
You saw where,
on the island?
She drifted
to the island, too?
Not exactly.
Why didn't you tell the Lances
that she didn't die
in that boat?
Laurel and Mr. Lance,
they blame you.
Yeah, well,
it was my fault.
What happened was my fault.
Well, where has she been
all these years, Oliver?
I don't know!
Diggle,
I swear to God.
I was sure she was dead.
Do you have
any happy stories?
All right, so just to make sure
I understand this correctly,
after not drowning
when "The Gambit" went down,
Sarah didn't exactly
make it to the island
with you, where you would
see her die yet again.
Feel free to fill in the blanks.
Not right now.
You mean not ever,
don't you, Oliver?
Don't you think her family
had a right to know
that she made it
to the island, too?
These were five years!
Five years...
Where nothing
good happened.
And they were better off
not knowing.
Do they deserve to know now?
I need to take care of some
business at the office.
Where are we
with the Mayor?
I'm in contact with some
of my military sources.
Trying to get a line on how he's
getting his illegal army weaponry.
I'll keep you updated.
You know, Oliver,
somebody once told me that...
secrets have weight.
The more you keep,
the harder it is to keep moving.
You see how hard
I work out.
You kill two of my crew.
How many others
are with you on the island?
What are your weapon
capabilities?
Did you find the graves?
Two things will happen--
you will tell me
everything I want to know,
then I will kill you.
Or I will torture you until you
tell me everything I want to know.
And then I will kill you.
Go to hell.
Can't.
We're already there.
Told you.
The Patty Shack
on 5th and Brewer,
best burgers in town.
Well, Patty Shack's in
the Mayor's territory,
so I'll take a sub par
breakfast over a bullet.
What's wrong?
Look, I know I'm skinny, but I
can eat two of these, and I will.
Just ran into an old boyfriend.
I'm just...
worried that he might
tell my family I'm back.
You have family
in Starling?
Yeah.
My father, he's a--
he's a policeman.
And my sister,
she's a lawyer.
Well, they must be real proud
of their masked delinquent.
Yeah, they think I'm dead.
Oh, cool.
My folks think
I'm dead, too.
That, or they wish
I'd never been born.
One of those.
Why...don't you
want them
to know that
you're still alive?
'Cause I'm not
what they remember.
Good little
daddy's girl?
Actually far from it.
I was a lot like you.
Is that...
why you saved me
from those guys that night?
No woman should ever suffer
at the hands of men.
We've got to stop
meeting like this.
What would your girlfriend
think, Johnny?
Lyla,
I am checking the box
marked "single" these days.
Sorry to hear it.
What happened?
Well, another man
came between us.
Deadshot.
You're getting
in the bad habit
of letting him ruin your life.
So I've been
repeatedly told.
Anything on those
stolen army weapons?
A crate of 12 M4A1s went missing
from Camp Kirby two months ago.
Yeah, I think I know
where they went.
Every crate was fitted
with a GPS system
so they could be
remote tracked.
I tried pulling it up but it's not
receiving. Must have been deactivated.
Thanks, Lyla.
And your interest
in this is what?
Lyla, you and I went
to Afghanistan to try
to bring law and order
to a country overrun
by war lords
with weapons, right?
Should we do any less
for our own cities?
Thanks again.
Hey, Johnny.
Yeah?
These days, I check the box
marked single, too.
Mr. Blood. I see you've met
Miss Rochev.
She's my--
superior.
Partner.
On paper.
Is that why you asked me
to come down here, Mr. Queen,
to mediate your job title?
You and I have gotten
off on the wrong foot repeatedly.
Seems to be
your super power.
I was inspired
by what you said
the other night about
gun violence in the Glades.
And I had an idea
that might help.
Really? Another party
at your stately manor?
No.
I wanted to sponsor
a cash for guns event.
I give you the money
and you get your constituents
to lay down their arms.
Everybody wins.
Especially you.
Trying to repair
your family's tainted name
by ridding the Glades of guns.
You just get the money,
Mr. Blood.
I don't want
my family's name involved.
Mr. Queen, may I have
a word with you?
Let me think it over.
We are not
sponsoring that event.
Yes, I know. I am.
With what money?
Your investment party
cost QC 50 grand,
and no one
invested a dime.
I will not continue to
authorize corporate funds
just so you can keep pretending
that you are the CEO.
Fine.
I'll pay for it myself.
Maybe you
haven't noticed,
but your personal trust isn't exactly
what it used to be,
and this company
isn't, either.
As much as I would love
to make this city safer,
my first obligation is
to Queen Consolidated.
And yours is, too.
♪ Shadows settle
on the place that you left ♪
I was going to order
some takeout, you want in?
I appreciate
the offer, Adam, but--
I've eaten takeout
every night this week,
I need a meal served
on an actual plate.
So do you.
I get it. It's easy to let
the job become your life.
I keep having to remind myself
to go to the gym,
see a movie, eat a good meal.
That sounds dangerously
like having a life.
What about you?
You can't be all about work.
I'm the best me
when I am working.
And when you're not?
You don't want to meet her.
She's not good company.
I'd be willing to risk it.
Excuse me.
I have to go.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to--
No, it's ok.
It's fine.
I just have to go.
Good night.
♪ 'Cause I've been
putting you through this hell ♪
♪ for so long
♪ so I understand
your choice, my dear ♪
♪ don't lose
when we have won ♪
Crap.
License
and registration?
Is there a problem, Officer?
Have you had anything
to drink tonight, ma'am?
I'm Laurel Lance.
I'm an assistant
district attorney.
I'm sorry, Miss Lance,
but I'm going to have
to ask you to step out
of the car, please.
I need some good news.
The bad news first.
Somehow the Mayor
did get his hands
on a crate of
military-grade weapons
from Camp Kirby.
The good news?
If he kept the crate,
might be able to find
where he's hiding.
This is the same make and model
of a tracking system
the army installs
on all of its weapons crates.
If they lose a crate,
they send out a remote signal
that activates the beacon.
The Mayor's clever.
He deactivated his beacon. Send
a signal, nothing comes back.
You both need to work
on your definition of good news.
Ok. How's this--
guess which company designed
the tracking system the army uses?
I'll give you a hint--
your CEO? Always late.
Nice.
I pulled up the original plans
from the QC mainframe.
Turns out
there's a design flaw.
The beacon is still susceptible
to a subform wave
even if it's been deactivated.
The Mayor
turned it off, Oliver.
We can turn it back on.
I believe you ordered the crate
of stolen military weapons, Mr. Queen.
I thought you deactivated
the tracker!
Go, go!
Weapons are secure.
And the Mayor?
Still in office.
Thanks for the heads up,
Officer Daily.
Just fyi--
she blew .6 past
the legal limit.
Thank you.
He didn't need to call you.
No.
But you're lucky he did.
You could have
lost your job.
You could have lost your life, and
you could have killed somebody!
I had a few too many glasses
of wine at dinner.
It was an accident!
An accident.
Well, I guess those happen.
Was I not supposed
to notice that tone?
The two of us...
You got a lot
from me, Laurel.
Maybe you got
this, too.
You can hardly compare my one
mistake to your drinking problem.
So long as it is
only one mistake.
I don't know
if you've noticed...
But I've had a little bit
of a hard time lately.
I was kidnapped, nearly murdered
by a psychopath,
and my boyfriend died.
So, I don't know,
maybe...cut me some slack.
You know, when I started
having a hard time,
I wish people
had not cut me slack.
Leave your car here,
I'm driving you home.
I'll take a cab.
Laurel...
Laurel!
Did you tell my family
that I'm alive?
No.
Sara.
I saw you die.
Not the first time
that's happened, right?
And I thought
you were dead, too.
What happened to Slade?
Where have you been?
Everywhere.
That's not an answer.
Well, it's the one
you're getting.
About a year ago,
I started
hearing tales
of the Starling City
vigilante.
The man
in the green hood.
I knew it was you.
I had never known you
as much of a fighter.
Where did you pick that up?
I met some rough people.
Thought I should get
rougher, too.
Sara.
Why did you come back?
The earthquake.
Because you wanted
to make sure your family was safe.
But now you're still here,
watching over them.
Protecting them.
So, did you come here
to make sure I didn't tell them?
Or because you were
hoping I had?
I'll get rid of them.
Mr. Lance?
Hi.
Something I can help you with?
I'm here about
my daughter.
Laurel.
Is she ok?
Yeah. Well, no,
she's not.
She got pulled over
for a DUI last night.
I tried talking to
her about it, but...
She wasn't
hearing me.
I--I saw her the other night.
She...
Didn't seem like herself.
No, I know.
She seems like me.
I don't know if you know, but
when you and Sara disappeared,
I hit the bottle
pretty hard.
I know the two
of you are friends.
And she needs
a friend.
Maybe talk to her.
Sure.
Anyhow.
Mr. Lance.
Yeah?
Um...
I'd be happy to talk to Laurel.
Thanks.
Why'd they do this?
Aahh.
They make all of us do this.
Supposed to show prochnost.
It's Russian.
For strength.
They--they did it
to see if I'm strong?!
They're doing this
to see if you survive.
Living...
is not for the weak.
Aahh.
Oliver. Hi.
What are you doing here?
Is everything ok?
I don't know.
You've got
to be kidding me.
My dad went to you?
He spent the last
six years cursing your name,
and now you're what, gossip buddies?
Laurel.
He's worried about you.
Perfect.
A recovering alcoholic
and recovering party boy
trying to tell me
how to live my life.
Don't you see
the hypocrisy there?
What I see is somebody
that both of us care for
having a rough go of it.
Do you know how many
times I've had to pull
my dad out of a bar?
Or how many nights
I've had to drive him home
where he's passed out
in my backseat?
He's the one
with the problem.
Not me.
Just because he can't
cope with losing Sara
doesn't mean I can't
handle my life.
Feel free to tell him that
during the next chit chat.
Sewing is not
your strong suit.
Now we can talk.
For two years...
my crew and I have
been looking for grave site.
Did you find the graves?
Were the bodies...
Odd?
The bones misshapen?
This is
the right island.
Looks like we got
a Colt 1911,
Jennings .32,
and a K-frame revolver.
Um...
We'll give you 250 for the lot.
Keep it.
Do I even want to know where
you got those guns?
They're from the old days.
I told you.
Look, no more
being a criminal.
No more being a hero.
Just Roy Harper.
Bus boy and boyfriend.
Yo, Abercrombie.
Where's your manners?
Sin.
This is Thea.
Thea, this is Sin.
Thea Queen?
Look at you,
rolling with royalty.
By the way, the salad fork's
the small one.
It was good to see you again.
She doesn't know you're the
Vigilante's delivery boy, does she?
Nice to meet you,
your highness.
You, too.
So how do you know her?
From around.
You don't show up
when you say you will,
and when you promise
not to, here you are.
It's going well?
Last check, we've taken in
over 200 guns in only 3 hours.
Try not to look
so happy about it.
A lot on my mind, alderman.
My job is to help
the people in this city
with their problems.
Two people that
are very important to me are...
having a tough time.
Sisters, actually.
And neither one of them
is making it very easy
for me to help them.
Sooner or later,
we all go through a crucible.
I'm guessing yours
was that island.
Most people there are
two types of people
who go into a crucible--
the ones who grow stronger
from the experience
and survive it,
and the ones who die.
But there's a third type.
The ones who learn
to love the fire.
They choose to stay
in their crucible
because it's easier
to embrace the pain
when it's all
you know anymore.
That's why I'm on the clock
to help this city.
Before it becomes used
to living like this.
Living is not
for the weak.
Old friend of mine
once told me that.
That's a wise friend.
Listen up, people.
This is your mayor speaking.
Now I don't recall
this here event being sanctioned.
What happens in the Glades
only happens if I allow it.
You're not the leader
of this community!
You don't speak
for these people!
And neither do you.
Not anymore.
Hey! Are you ok? Are you hit?
No.
Sin, you all right?
All's good.
Go get help!
Go!
The shooting
was committed by the gang leader
known only as "The Mayor,"
who, until now,
has never been seen in public.
We do want to warn
our audience
that some of these images
are graphic.
The coward finally
decided to show his face.
Vanity is going
to cost him.
I borrowed the FBI's
facial recognition software.
Got a match.
Xavier Reed.
Did Mr. Reed
serve in the military?
No military history.
Family members?
Reed was in and out
of foster care his whole life.
Wait, hold on.
In 1996, Reed spent
three years with
a foster family
and their son, Ezra Barnes.
He served three tours in
Iraq. He's stateside now.
20 bucks says he was stationed
at Camp Kirby.
Pay the man.
The Mayor's foster brother
is assigned
to a weapons convoy
that carries
SCAR 16s by truck.
The convoy's scheduled to come
through Starling City tonight.
FN SCAR 16s are military assault
weapons with grenade launchers.
The man gets a hold
of these, Oliver,
it's game over.
He won't.
Bullet penetrated
her anterior abdomen.
We were able to remove
most of the fragments.
We'll know more
in a few hours.
Hey.
I'm going to stick around,
in case she wakes up.
Is it ok if I stick
around with you?
I mean, you saved
her life, Roy.
I guess you can't stop
being a hero, can you?
I want to see how you do
in a real fight.
Good.
I was looking for a fight.
They're with me.
He wasn't.
You're done being
all you can be.
Ahh.
You and I are going
to own this town.
Now let's see
what this bad boy can do.
Drop the weapon, now!
Behind you.
Old school weapon. Respect.
But can your arrows do this?
Come on, where are you?
You hurt a friend of mine.
Let him go.
You can't save a city
with forgiveness.
You don't have
to forgive him.
But you do have
to let him live.
Bitch. I knew you didn't
have it in you.
I really don't like that word.
Demonstrations
opposing the construction
of the new Star Lab's
particle accelerator
have reached a fever pitch with
five more protestors being arrested.
In other news the recent cash for
guns event held in the Glades
is credited for getting
over 800 weapons off the streets.
Still a mystery--
the anonymous donor
whose generous donation
funded the event.
I guess it's true
what they say--
one man can change the world.
I'll leave changing
the world to you, alderman.
I'm only in the world
because of you.
Thank you.
I was just acting
on instinct.
It wasn't instinct.
It was strength.
I see the signs
and the graffiti;
"Blood for mayor."
Now that the "mayor"
is in jail,
maybe
you should run.
There is more than one way
to save a city.
Mr. Harper?
What's wrong, is she ok?
Hey.
You saved my life.
I guess I have to keep
your secret now, huh?
You know you're dating
a moron, right?
It's my first
and last thought of every day.
Crap.
I like her.
Your friend.
I took care
of her medical expenses.
Thank you.
Look, I don't want
Thea to see me--
What's your plan, Sarah?
Because right now,
you just...
Well, you're whipping
across rooftops
and keeping watch
over your family
like some sort of ghost.
We're both ghosts.
We died
on that island.
But we didn't.
We both lived.
And...
I get that you have
been in pain so long
that it probably
just feels normal now.
But you can let it go
and come home.
I mean, I know that the
earthquake brought you here,
but your family
kept you here.
You have to tell them, Sarah.
They need you.
You told them
that I died on "The Gambit."
If they know
the truth...
They would never--
they would never
talk to me again.
Not one of them.
But it'd be worth it.
My daughter's
in trouble.
She's, uh, she's been through
some really terrible things.
And...
Instead of facing up to them,
she's running away from them.
She's losing herself
in her work,
and maybe even worse.
She's my daughter, I just want
her safe, I want to protect her.
But I guess like we say in our
meetings, more will be revealed.
Your days of screaming
are just beginning.
Sarah?
What the hell is this?
This ain't the police station.
Why are you wearing that mask?
This city
is in chains,
and I'm going
to free it.
But to do that,
I need an army.
Whoa, what's in that thing?!
Get that off me!
Get that crap away from me!
Are you ready to serve?
Bring me another.
Yes, brother Blood.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man