Previously on Arrow...
Mr. Darhk will be held
without bail or possibility of release.
You may now call your organization
and have that other message delivered.
He said
you were his ace in the hole.
Is that what you'd like me to call you?
Or do you prefer Mr. Diggle?
DIGGLEI Andy?
What are you doing in the dark, man?
Didn't wanna wake Sara up.
Thanks for letting me know where this was.
I want you to feel safe.
You sounded pretty rattled on the phone.
What the hell's going on?
HIVE knows I'm alive, John.
Did they come after you?
In a way.
I mean, one of them reached out.
Some guy with perfect teeth
and a missing hand.
- I didn't... He didn't tell me his name.
- Malcolm Merlyn.
- The head of the League of Assassins?
- Well, not anymore.
Yeah. Well, now he works for Damien Darhk.
- Since when?
- Two nights ago.
Andy, you should've told me this earlier.
"ANDY". I know, man, and I'm sorry. But...
This whole thing's gotten me thrown, man,
I didn't think HIVE knew where I was.
What did Merlyn want?
I think there's some kind of friction
going on between HIVE and Darhk.
Have you noticed they haven't even tried
to bust Darhk out of prison?
Yeah, I've been thinking about that.
And now this Merlyn guy
asked me to help him.
Help him with what?
Bust Darhk out of Iron Heights?
DOD's scheduled to run Paveway missiles
through Pennytown tomorrow night at 2300.
Merlyn wants me to help him
hijack the shipment.
Yeah, well, just one of those Paveways
makes for a pretty good
"get out ofjail free" card.
And that's why I'm asking you, man.
What do I do?
First kidnapping, then stealing missiles.
Merlyn's trying really hard
to be friends with Darhk.
If Malcolm's convinced
Darhk is on the winning side, it...
He's even trying to protect me
from whatever he's planning.
The only thing Darhk should be planning on
is getting convicted at trial.
Why does that thing creep
me out the way it does?
Because it's creepy.
There's something
that I haven't told you guys.
Shocker.
Sorry.
- I've seen this idol before.
- What?
Where?
Lian Yu.
You really love not talking
about that place, don't you?
Where are we with the security upgrades?
Everything's in place. We're good to go.
Because Merlyn knows
the bunker's location.
And if he's working with Darhk...
Then that means we have to worry
about him coming down here
and stealing this creepy stone-thingy.
And what about his plan
to hijack the missile shipment?
Oliver, I think we keep Andy
right where he is.
That way we'll have someone on the inside.
Are you sure that's a good idea?
Well, he's out from under the influence
of Darhk. We can trust him.
Trust is one thing,
and selling him as a double agent,
that's another.
It's a lot of pressure to put on someone.
Especially someone
that is still in recovery.
Oliver, Andy is stand-up guy.
He's got this.
And you've got this.
You can blow that off.
You don't owe Ruvé Darhk anything.
Tradition, loser attends
the winner's acceptance speech.
You didn't lose, you pulled out
of the race because of her husband.
Which I will try not to mention
to the press.
Let's get this over with.
We worked hard to get to this moment.
But now the real work begins
to make this city great again.
Thank you.
Mr. Queen.
Have time to answer a few questions?
Not a candidate anymore,
I'm just here to support the new mayor.
So, no comment on the write-in results?
What write-in results?
Forty-eight percent
of the electorate wrote in
your brother's name on their ballots.
That's a historic showing for a candidate
who pulled out of the race.
I'll let you and your former opponent
catch up.
Well, thank you for coming out
tonight, Mr. Queen.
It's a very gracious gesture.
I'm always gonna have this
city's best interests at heart.
Well, let's hope the same can be said
for your friends.
- Ms. Lance. I am so pleased to meet you.
- Mmm.
I was very impressed by your handling
of the Damien Darhk hearing.
I was just getting warmed up.
Well, my hope is that you'll be too busy
to handle the trial.
District Attorney Remz has taken on
a new position as my Deputy Mayor.
And I would like you to succeed him as DA.
Think about it.
I think that we could do great things
for this city if we work together.
Thank you.
Listen, Reiter's men outnumber us.
We have guns, but so do they.
So when we get up there,
we cannot hesitate to kill.
Do you understand?
Taiana?
Just months ago, I was a dive instructor.
I couldn't dream of taking a life.
I wouldn't.
This place truly is hell.
It makes monsters of us all.
Who's in that photo?
Me and my brother.
I forget sometimes that we were once
this happy and this innocent.
When I first got here,
I used to look at a photo from my past.
It helped for a time,
reminded me of the person
that I used to be.
But I'm telling you now
that that person wouldn't survive here.
And you won't either
if you stay focused on the past.
Do you understand?
Da.
How do we take those bastards out?
Follow me.
It's past 11:30.
It's the US Army, man.
"Late" means "on time."
Or we're staking out the wrong place.
If Andy says this is where it's gonna be,
this is where it's gonna be.
No movement yet on the missiles.
You know, we should be out there
with them.
Even with John's fancy A.R.G.U.S toys,
this place is more secure
with us watching over it.
So, are you gonna do it?
Be a District Attorney by day
and Black Canary by night?
I don't know.
I mean, it would help
having eyes on Mrs. Evil.
Yeah, well, if you believe Malcolm,
it would be a short-term job anyway.
There won't be any need for a DA
once the city's destroyed.
You stopped calling him "Dad."
That's because he's not "Dad."
Look, I know I've said that before,
but this time is different.
This time, it's mutual.
That couldn't be
further from the truth, dear.
Mr. Diggle's upgraded security
needs a few upgrades, by the way.
You know why we're here.
Hand over the idol
and there won't be any trouble.
Well, there's gonna be trouble, then.
All right, that's the signal.
Guy's dressed like League of Assassins.
Merlyn probably has a few loyalists left.
Get me in position.
Hold on! It's me! It's me. It's me.
Are you always this quiet?
Come on, we just saved the shipment,
and you made it look easy.
It's because it was easy.
The idol.
It's gone.
You two can stand down. He's gone.
- Merlyn?
- Yeah.
And a few League of Assassin members.
He took the idol.
I should have stopped him.
We should have been here. We...
I'm sure you did everything you could.
Merlyn's gonna give that idol
to his new friend Darhk
to get his mojo back.
We've been scouring the street cams,
it's like he just vanished.
Yeah, that's why
the League calls him the Magician.
I'm gonna go hit the streets.
Thea, no one is gonna give up Merlyn.
Well, then I'm gonna hit people
on the streets.
I'll check with Andy.
See if he can get a 20 on Merlyn.
Uh, John, Andy has already risked a lot.
I don't wanna put him
in a compromised position.
Oliver, he's already in
a compromised position.
There's a direct line between him
and the man we are looking for.
Let's use that.
Yeah.
Talk to me.
This missile job was too easy.
It was like Merlyn's men
weren't even trying.
Meanwhile, it pulled our focus,
Merlyn was able to come down here
and get exactly what he wanted.
You think Merlyn played Andy?
What if Andy is playing us?
Look, I'm...
I'm not saying it's not possible,
but this is John's brother
we're talking about.
I mean, he's done so much for us.
He... He saved Lyla.
Should I just trust him outright?
No. But you better be sure
before making an accusation
that you and John can't recover from.
It's my dad. I have to take this.
Help me! Please help me!
- You have to help me!
- What is it?
- What's going on?
- Conklin!
Or what remains of him.
The thing that killed those men.
It killed Oliver.
It has Reiter trapped down there.
Come on.
MERCENARY'. Who... Who's that?
Stop running.
Don't be too impressed.
That's the only Chinese
I was able to pick up from Sara.
So, listen, you thought about how
you're gonna tell our newly elected mayor
that you're turning down herjob offer?
I have.
But I'm not sure that I will.
Well, this one's a no-brainer, sweetie.
You can't go work for a murderer.
This job would put me in the inner circle.
Yeah, at the cost
of being the Black Canary.
Look, ever since HIVE had DA Bray killed,
the District Attorney has 24-7 protection,
they would not let you out of their sight.
I'll waive it.
You think Ruvé Darhk will let that happen?
Listen, I never thought I'd say this.
But I'm glad
that you are the Black Canary.
I'm glad for all the good you're doing,
and I'm glad for the good it's done you.
But you gotta know that taking this job,
that means taking off that mask, forever.
Careful. You could hurt yourself
with that.
It's not myself
I'm planning on hurting with it.
Andy. Yeah.
- I've got eyes on Merlyn.
- Okay. Where are you?
In some old box factory, I think.
- You sure this is the place?
- Yeah, I'm pretty sure.
Come on. Merlyn's this way.
Why didn't you have him radio us in?
I had him stay behind for backup.
Merlyn!
The door!
Look out!
You Okay?
Swell.
What happened?
He took an arrow for me.
Let me see. Let me see.
Don't worry about it, man.
We deal with this kind of stuff
every week. Come on.
No, no, no, no!
You gotta get to Iron Heights now.
If Merlyn's not here, then that...
That means he's on his way there
with the idol.
If Darhk gets that idol,
no prison will be able to hold him.
One of these days you're gonna tell me
how you get in and out of here.
A magician never reveals his secrets.
And what next? You're gonna make
a coin appear from behind my ear?
You know, you're awfully flippant
for a man who's asked a great deal of me.
Do you have it?
Perhaps now's a good time
to remind you of our terms.
Yes. You and your daughter get spared
from Genesis. Is that still the play?
I don't think you appreciate
what this cost me.
Oh, come on. Stop being so highhanded.
What's wrong?
Mr. Merlyn, do you know
what the khushu idol is?
Khushu is an old Arabic term
for "humbleness."
Suffice it to say, something
I wouldn't associate with you.
When the earliest Homo Magi
forged these idols,
they did so in the image of those
whose powers they wished to channel.
So attention to detail is essential.
It's missing a piece.
The Ribalvei stone.
They must have hidden it someplace else.
Find it.
Or Genesis is not what you
and your daughter have to fear.
You're gonna need a few stitches,
but, uh, this should hold for now.
I'm gonna need a whole lot more
than a few stitches.
Merlyn's men saw me
fighting for your team.
Darhk's now gonna know
that I'm on your side.
I'm a dead man.
And he's just not gonna stop with me.
He's gonna come for you,
he's gonna come for Lyla, Sara. Oh, God.
Listen, listen, he's not gonna
come for anybody, okay? He can't.
Merlyn has the idol.
Look, he's probably delivering it to him
right now!
Andy, no, he doesn't.
There's a piece missing.
What?
We separated a piece of it
and put it in another location.
The only thing Merlyn's delivering
is a big-ugly paperweight.
- Darhk will find it. He finds everything.
- Listen, listen.
Andy, listen to me, man.
He won't find anything.
- I hid it myself.
- John?
May I speak to you?
This information
needs to be compartmentalized.
Listen, he's scared, man.
And for good reason.
He's entitled to know
that we have the situation under control.
Well, that control is only as strong
as the secret.
The less people who know, the better.
He risked everything, everything for us.
He took an arrow for you.
He has my trust.
Why doesn't he have yours?
Malcolm's gonna try and get the idol
to Darhk, if he hasn't done it already.
I can go there as ADA
and have the entire cellblock searched.
Do it.
Speedy, you and Spartan
go back to the bunker.
Work CCTV, work facial recognition.
Anything that we can do
to get a line on Merlyn.
- Okay.
- And what can I do?
You should go home and rest.
You've done enough for tonight.
What about you?
I'll be right behind you,
I'm just gonna run down a lead.
You guys, get to the surface,
gather the others and go for the boats.
Go, come on!
- What about you?
- Reiter's still in the catacombs.
If he's found that idol,
you won't be able to stop him.
We don't need to stop him.
We need to trap him.
You guys are doing a wonderful job
in there.
You know, I've been meaning
to redecorate the place myself.
You know,
my office received an anonymous tip
that contraband intended for your use
was smuggled into this prison.
- Mmm.
Find anything? All right.
Search every cell in this tier.
I wanna make sure none of his friends
are stashing anything for him.
You know, you're lucky I'm not the man
that you think I am, Ms. Lance.
If I were the man
that your father so vehemently claims,
you'd be in a lot of trouble right now,
wouldn't you?
Are you threatening
an Assistant District Attorney?
Oh, no! No, no, no. Not at all.
Just merely trying to figure out where
your father gets these vicious ideas from.
On!
I hope his mind isn't starting to go.
You know, dementia is sometimes
an after effect of long-term alcoholism.
You're a son of a bitch.
Regardless, it's comforting to know
that his heart is in the right place.
A father who would do anything
to protect his daughter from the dark.
I'll see you in court.
- Looking for something?
- Oh, jeez, man.
Do you know how to knock?
Any luck finding Merlyn?
No, but I think you already knew that.
I'm gonna ask you again,
what are you looking for?
Surveillance. Okay, look.
HIVE knows I'm John's brother.
They could've hidden bugs here.
Maybe that's how that one-handed friend
of yours found me in the first place.
You always have an answer for everything.
Hey, what are you talking about?
I think that you've been working
with Darhk since the beginning.
That you and Merlyn have been playing us
this entire time,
and now you're here
looking for the missing piece of the idol.
I'm on your side, remember?
I even got hurt trying to protect you.
I remember.
I told John to trust you,
to give you another chance.
But I was wrong,
because men like you don't change.
Now, you tell me.
What does Darhk have planned?
If I'm the man that you think I am,
then you know torture
is not gonna get me to say anything.
I haven't started torturing you yet.
- What the hell are you doing?
- Showing you who he really is.
- Tell him.
- John, he thinks I'm a traitor.
I know exactly
what that Kevlar won't protect.
Let him go.
Dig, you can't trust him.
- Get out.
- John!
Now.
You had no right!
I had every right.
- This is about keeping us safe.
- No, it's not, Oliver.
This is about you controlling
everything and everyone around you.
Andy tipped us off to the missile heist,
we go there,
Merlyn comes here and takes the idol.
Then he brings us to Merlyn's hideout,
where we are met with an ambush.
- Where he took an arrow for you.
- That could've been a feint.
When I confronted him at your apartment,
he was tearing it apart!
Looking for surveillance.
Or, he was looking
for the last piece of the idol.
John, you are the one who always tells me,
"Do not have a blind spot
when it comes to your family."
And you're the one who told me
to give Andy a second chance.
You're the one
who wanted to extract him from HIVE.
You're the one who said he could come back
from the darkness, the same way you did.
But I didn't.
Ihavetfled.
I have tried harder at this
than I ever have at anything.
But at the end of the day,
I am who those five years away
turned me into.
I'm what they turned me into.
So, what, Oliver?
Just because Felicity left you,
I'm supposed to believe
that all men are incapable of redemption?
Not all men are like you, Oliver.
Some of us change.
Some of us grow.
Some of us evolve.
You are stuck, man.
Stuck in your self-pity
and your self-righteousness,
and that is why Felicity left you.
My brother is my business.
You have no idea what he's been through,
and you sure as hell
had no right to judge him.
I'm sure he didn't mean that, Ollie.
Yes, he did.
How'd it go at Iron Heights?
Turned up a few burner cell phones,
six bags of heroin,
and no idol.
THEAI Well...
We're hacked into the security system
at the prison,
so if anything happens, we'll see it.
Right.
Hey? Are you okay?
John and I had a difference of opinion.
- About Andy?
- I confronted Andy, and Dig walked in.
- Mmm.
- Yeah.
Probably should've taken your advice,
District Attorney Lance.
I'm still just an ADA.
I'm turning down the promotion.
Because it's being offered by Ruvé Darhk?
No. Because taking the job means
giving up my place here,
with you and the team.
Team's falling apart.
John's furious with me.
Thea is consumed with rage for Malcolm.
And...
Well, Felicity is gone.
Becoming District Attorney is something
that you've worked
the better part of three years for.
I might've wanted to be DA,
but that was a lifetime ago.
Sara's lifetime.
You channeled your grief
and became the Black Canary.
But Sara's not dead anymore.
Maybe you owe it to yourself
to pursue the path you were on.
You're serious?
This city has enough heroes with masks on.
With Ruvé Darhk as mayor,
it needs a hero without a mask.
It needs Laurel Lance.
Break time!
Twenty minutes! Twenty minutes!
DARHKI Ah...
Are you in touch with the land?
Spend much time in Mother Nature?
No. Well, your ancestors did.
But they knew
that life is a series of phases.
A time to be born, a time to die,
a time to plant, a time to uproot,
a time to kill.
Master the paradox of change
within constancy,
and the primordial force of nature itself
will be at your beck and call.
Ah, my idol. Julius Caesar.
"Cry 'Havoc, '
and let slip the dogs of war."
LOCK down.
Lock down cell block A.
What happened?
It was rec hour,
the prisoners were out of their cells.
- He's holding the guards hostage.
- How many?
It doesn't matter how many.
We have to put Darhk back in his cage.
Let's gear up.
Oliver, I can't prosecute him
without getting him into custody first.
One last time.
What the hell is going on around here?
You can't just stand around here waiting
for something to happen. Who's in charge?
Not you, Captain. You've been suspended.
Pike, right? That figures.
Wait it out till we got
a stack of dead bodies on our hands.
I'm sorry, sir.
You need to get back to your vehicle.
No, I wanna speak with him.
I need to speak with him now!
- I can't do that.
- Yes, you can do that.
You can do that. Go get him...
Never mind. I see him.
- Sir, no...
- Hey! Pike!
Pike! Yeah, I see you over there.
How do we get through
all those cops?
Looks like Lance has it covered.
He's laying into
Lieutenant Pike, apparently.
And he just knocked him out.
As a distraction to give us an opening.
Let's move.
I thought I told you to come alone.
You did. And I didn't.
Look, I know you don't trust me.
But that's why I'm here, to prove you can.
Darhk has the hostages in the mess hall.
Let's fan out and hit him from all sides.
I remember this guy.
Those lips.
Gross.
Not a bad warm up.
Seems like you're ready for a rematch.
Go get the others. I've got this.
- No. Let me take him.
- Go!
Let's see how well I taught you.
You know, the police took me seriously
when I said I would start killing hostages
if they moved upon the prison.
Too bad our masked vigilante friends
didn't get the memo.
Well, too bad for you, really.
Kill them.
You no longer have the drive to kill,
and it shows.
You lost a part of yourself
when they cured you of that bloodlust.
And that is why you will never beat me.
Andrew Diggle. It's been a while.
- Let him go.
- Drop your weapons.
- Don't do it.
- Suit yourself,
but on the count of three,
I'm gonna turn that wall into a Jackson
Pollock painting with his brains.
- One...
- Dammit!
Two...
Okay.
Now, was that so hard?
I believe you have something for me.
Andy?
I'm sorry, man.
I've been tracking your movements
for months.
I know everywhere you've been.
All I needed to hear
was that it was you that hid the stone.
Was there ever a chance for you?
Your brother's way beyond reach,
Mr. Diggle.
It's all over now.
You took the words right out of my mouth.
It needs a sacrifice.
Not enough.
You know what to do.
Oh, it feels so much better.
I am sorry about your buddies.
But omelets and eggs and all of that.
But I know
how to make it up to you, though.
Who wants to take go for a walk outside?
Andy, here, might have mentioned
that his brother, John,
worked for the Green Arrow,
or should I say
Oliver Queen.
Oh, and see, I know what you're all
thinking, but, no, but he didn't tell me.
It was really just a hop, skip and a jump
from the whole Diggle connection to you,
to your little sister,
to your ex-girlfriend.
But when you came to rescue that boy,
William, that look on your face...
That was a father's look.
I should have recognized it
there and then.
We need to get out of here. Now.
Pafience.
I've been waiting for this moment
for a long time.
Ms. Lance.
Nine months ago,
I made your daddy a promise.
I told him what I would do
if he betrayed me.
Impressive. Now where was I?
Oh, yeah.
I want you to give your father
a message from me.
I want you to tell him...
I'm a man of my word.
Hey! Hey. It's all right. It's okay.
Hey, hey. Look at me.
You're gonna be all right.
You'll be all right. Come on!
Help! Help in here, please!
You have to help her. Please!
She's lost a lot of blood.
I need a crash cart and the trauma team
in here stat!
- Let her go.
- What?
I need you to let her go
so I can do my job.
Now, leave! The trauma team
will be in here any second.
And the last thing she needs
right now is a circus.
Go! Go.
How do you know how to do this?
To bury a man alive?
You were right.
How this island changed you.
Do you still look at your picture?
She's beautiful. Who is she?
Her name is Laurel Lance.
And she was my home
before all of this.
I don't know what she'll think
of the man I've become.
If I don't make it off this island,
you will go to Russia and find my parents,
and tell them what happened
to me and Vlad.
If you don't make it,
I will find this Laurel
and tell her how you saved us all.
Deal?
Deal.
Baron, we've got to get out of here.
There is no getting out.
But with your deaths,
I might yet just live.
What're you talking about?
Iron Heights has left the city on edge.
Hey, Lopez. Lopez.
What happened at the, uh, at the prison?
Uh, you punched out a lieutenant.
Yeah, I mean after that.
Did they keep those inmates from escaping?
There's too many of them.
And one, Darhk, he hurt one of them.
What? Who, who did he hurt?
The vigilantes. The Black Canary.
Supposedly, he hurt her real bad.
Uh... Um...
All right, listen.
I gotta get out of here, all right.
It's really important,
so please can you get me, uh...
Can you get Lieutenant Pike on the phone?
He's out supervising the manhunt
for the escaped prisoners.
Listen, you gotta get him on the phone,
all right?
'Cause I gotta talk to him.
'Cause I gotta get out of here.
Just for an hour.
Then I'll surrender myself back in,
all right? It's fine.
Butjust, just...
Get Lieutenant Pike on the phone. Please.
Laurel, is she...
Laurel's in surgery. Um...
I don't know.
I've tried calling Lance, too, so...
What happened with Darhk?
He's in the wind.
Along with 50 or so inmates.
And Andy.
You warned me, and I didn't listen.
How am I gonna be able to forgive myself?
Oh, my God.
She's out of recovery.
She's gonna be fine.
She's a strong woman, your friend.
The strongest.
She's been asking for you.
Hi.
Hey, yourself.
Did Darhk...
Don't worry about him.
Just worry about getting better, okay?
It's not exactly how I wanted
my last night to go.
What are you talking about?
It's a long story.
I was gonna give up being
the Black Canary, but...
I realized I didn't know how I could.
Because going out there
and fighting alongside you guys,
that's what makes me feel alive inside.
And I love you guys so much.
We love you.
We should probably let you get some rest.
- We'll be right outside, okay?
- Okay.
You should probably get some rest, too.
No chance.
I'm gonna stay right here.
It's, um...
There's something in my left pouch.
Will you bring it to me?
Yeah.
- May I?
- Yeah.
You kept this?
Yeah.
It's a little reminder
of when things were simpler.
For us.
The way we used to be.
I'm really glad that you found Felicity.
I hope you find your way back to her.
And, Ollie, I know
that I am not the love of your life,
but you will always be the love of mine.
Why are you telling me this?
Why now?
Because tonight
it was just a reminder that
anything can happen.
Which is why I need you
to promise me something.
Just got off the phone with Captain Lance.
He's on his way.
I, I told him that she's doing fine.
Out of the way!
She's seizing.
Embolism! I need 5,000 units
of heparin bolus.
- What happened?
- I don't know. She was fine.
Paddles.
- Charging 200. Go.
- Clear.
Clear.
Nothing.
Let's gag her.
Open up her air way.
Come on. Come on.
"MALE DOCTOR". Lodge 30% drop.
- Come on!
- 6-12.
Come on, Laurel.
No response.
Time of death, 11:59.
English - SDH