[TECHNO MUSIC PLAYING
OVER SPEAKERS]
[CAR HORNS HONKING]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[CAR HORN HONKS]
OLIVER: How we doing?
TOMMY: We are in the black and the green.
I like how we've gone from
throwing money at clubs to catching it.
Oh, look at these.
What sort of business
has a lost and found...
-...filled with women's underwear?
-Best business ever?
Oh, having this much fun
should be against the law.
Oh, if wishing made it so.
-Sorry, am I interrupting anything?
TOMMY: Is Laurel okay?
She's fine.
This visit is about something else.
A girl just got mowed down
a couple blocks from here.
On the Starling Bridge.
Ring any bells with you two?
-No.
-Should she?
LANCE: She was in your club tonight.
-A lot of people were.
-You think someone killed her?
-Not someone. Something.
-Vertigo.
-Yeah.
-Had a problem with that in this club?
-Not that I'm aware of.
We don't allow drugs here, detective.
LANCE:
Control your clientele.
Before anyone else wanders into traffic.
Any chance she could have scored
the drugs in here?
Doubt it.
I tried not to hire too many drug dealers.
Get me a list of employees. I'll have Felicity
cross-reference it for drug arrests.
That includes the two of us, you know.
[KEYPAD BEEPING]
I thought
the Vigilante finished off the Count.
I did.
LANCE:
Just need to ask him a few questions, doc.
You're welcome to try, detective.
Not sure you'll get very far.
LANCE: What does that mean?
Is this a load about doctor-patient privilege?
No. The unrefined Vertigo overdose
he suffered...
...caused damage to the caudal portion
of his anterior cingulate.
LANCE: You'll be shocked
that I didn't go to medical school.
DOCTOR:
I've been working with him for months.
All I've gotten out of him is word salad,
the occasional spit in the face.
-Best of luck to you.
-Yeah, thanks.
Here I was born and there I died.
It was only a moment for you.
You took no notice.
[GRUNTS]
GREEN ARROW:
A woman died tonight.
-From your poison.
-Lots of women die...
...lots of nights, for lots of reasons.
Someone is selling Vertigo again.
Where is it coming from?
I remember you. Man in the hood.
You are never far from my thoughts.
Unh!
You have failed this city!
You could've just said he was nuts.
[GRUNTING]
-You're teaching me that one.
-Only if you show me where the knife was.
-Who taught you how to fight?
-My father wanted a son.
-He got one.
SHADO: Careful.
Tension on that bow's
a hundred and fifty pounds.
Snap it, you'll end up
with carbon fiber shrapnel in your eyes.
SLADE:
She's right. You're not strong enough, kid.
Go again?
You know, it's pretty exciting
that both of you are such bad asses...
...but you think that we should be
making a plan to stop Fyers?
-And I don't know, save your dad?
-Does he always whine this much?
-This is one of his good days.
SHADO: Can he fight?
I've tried. Limited success.
I'm sitting right here.
Well, I haven't tried yet.
[SLADE LAUGHS]
-Uncle John?
-Hey, buddy.
Will you read Logan Bogan to me?
Sweetheart, get into bed
and mommy will read to you.
But I want Uncle John to read to me.
Uncle John's had a long day.
He'll read to you next time.
Hey, I'm sorry.
I've been someplace else today.
-What's going on with you?
-I'm just trying to figure some stuff out.
If you need to talk about anything,
you know I'm here for you.
[PHONE RINGING]
It is Oliver Queen. With an emergency.
I gotta go.
DIGGLE: Got here quick as I could. This
about the Glyph in your father's notebook?
OLIVER: Felicity is still working on that.
We have another problem.
WOMAN [ON TV]: Starling City
is once again at war with the drug...
...known on the streets as Vertigo.
It used to be the city's most lethal vice...
...but the purple and green pill was nowhere
to be found the last three months.
Over the past few days...
...city's been flooded with new version
of Vertigo, more addictive, more unstable.
It killed a girl in the club.
Just like it almost killed Thea.
Okay, what are you thinking?
We should pay the Count a visit?
He was my first visit. Waste of time.
He's sumasshedshiy.
Duh.
Since he's the only one
who knew the formula for Vertigo...
-...I don't even know where to begin.
FELICITY: Good, you're here.
Of course you're here. Where else
would you be? Clearly love it down here.
You got to see this.
I'm here at the scene where police say
a disturbed patient escaped only hours ago.
Authorities issued an immediate lockdown...
...at the Starling County Institute
for Mental Health following the breakout.
Police are warning people to avoid contact
with the drug dealer known as the Count.
Not so crazy after all, huh?
DOCTOR:
I was administering his meds.
He was babbling, his usual ranting,
then he's ice-cold.
He overpowered me. Forced me to take him
out through the maintenance exit.
I thought he was harmless.
Basically a vegetable, you said.
I know, which means... I've interviewed him
dozens of times in the past few months.
To be deceived by a patient so completely...
Don't worry. We'll find him.
And he's going to find prison
a lot harder to break out of.
Detective, he's dangerous.
Don't underestimate him.
LANCE: Anything from the security cameras?
-Not according to the orderly.
Due to budget cuts,
the cameras were the first to go.
That is unbelievable.
There's another angle. Veronica Sparks,
the dead girl from Verdant?
LANCE: Yeah?
-I checked her LUDs.
The last person she texted
before she died was Tommy Merlyn.
He said he didn't know her.
HILTON: Merlyn has two collars for possession,
one with intent.
LANCE:
Yeah, that was over five years ago.
HILTON: Maybe he's just better
at not getting himself arrested.
Laurel says he's changed
ever since his father cut him off.
Leopard and his spots.
Maybe pushing Vertigo
is a way of maintaining his old lifestyle.
Maybe going after Merlyn
is a great way to get my daughter...
-...to stop speaking to me again, Hil.
-Quentin, I get that.
But here's the thing, on a hunch,
I subpoenaed the club's bank accounts.
Ten large
missing from their operating expenses.
Merlyn spent that money on Vertigo?
I can't explain how that much money
just gets misplaced.
I'll take a run at him, keep you out of it.
No. I should do it.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
What you need?
All right, the person-of-color
has successfully purchased your drugs.
For the record, I offered.
How will we know the tracker is active?
It already is.
Good signal off the monofilament strips
we placed in the bills.
Drug money's like a pigeon.
Always finds its way home.
-Follow the money back to the Count.
FELICITY: Okay.
OLIVER:
Keep tracking it.
So what are you gonna do
with all the Vertigo you bought?
Plan on having a party?
My only experience with drugs
was an encounter...
...with a pot brownie my freshman year.
By mistake.
Which could've been fun,
except I'm allergic to nuts.
All right. Deadshot kills again.
This time, a U.S. Senator.
-Where you been tracking him?
-Not far.
I ran his Floyd Lawton alias
through every law enforcement database.
He's made a series of calls
to an Alberto Garcia.
According to NSA, Garcia's a reputed
underworld talent scout.
He books all of Deadshot's hits.
-It's not much to go on...
-Yeah, but it's something, Felicity. Thanks.
-Don't you think Oliver should know?
-No. This is personal.
Lawton's my problem to deal with.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
-What brings you by?
TOMMY: Hey.
Like some dinner?
Your daughter ordered too much Thai food.
No, thanks.
This is a business visit, actually.
I have some follow-up questions
on the Sparks girl's death.
Sure. The girl was in the club
before she got run-over.
You said you didn't know her,
but the last text off her phone was to you.
Really? Because...
Well, I'll be damned.
Hm. I didn't reply. I get a hundred texts a night.
People wanting to get into the club.
So that's what she meant by,
"Can you hook me up?"
What else would it be about?
Ten thousand dollars is missing
from your club's bank account.
What'd you spend the money on?
No idea. There must be some sort of
bookkeeping error.
Okay, let me put this another way:
If you spent that money on Vertigo...
-...so you could hook up your clientele...
-Dad!
...the best thing for you is to cop to it,
get out in front of this.
-Don't say anything.
-I'm trying to...
To do your job? I know.
And this is me doing mine.
Laurel, I know I look like that
disapproving father, again.
But I came down here
so another cop wouldn't.
You understand?
-Tommy I...
-I'm not hungry anymore.
SHADO:
Hold up your hand up.
Palm facing me.
-Hit the water.
-What?
Hit it.
Again.
Again. Harder.
If the point of this is to make me feel
like an idiot, it's working.
"The journey of a thousand miles
begins with a single step."
Confucius. Great.
I'm starting to see the family resemblance.
Lao Tzu, actually. Again.
-Now what?
-Fill the bowl. Start again.
[PHONE BEEPS]
-What have you got?
-The end of the money trail.
Sending the dealer's location to you now.
[PHONE BEEPING]
MAN 1:
Oh, man. It's freezing.
MAN 2: Oh, hey!
MAN 3: Hey, check this.
MAN 1:
Hey, come on, let's see what we can get.
MAN 2:
Get back, guys. Get back.
Hey, yo. Who's looking to party?
MAN 1: Vertigo.
MAN 2: Right here.
That's not enough, man.
You don't pay, you don't play.
BOSS:
It's all right. Good for business.
My boss seems to like you, G.
MAN 1:
Hey. Hey, hey. Give it. Give it.
MAN 2:
How much for this?
Now that, that will buy you a brick,
my man.
BOSS:
Go, go, go!
[TIRES SCREECHING]
Don't forget to breathe.
If you won't, I won't.
Congratulations. You're officially
the creepiest person I've ever met.
-I don't feel so good.
-Get away from me, creep.
Hey, we got a problem here?
Are you okay?
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
DISPATCH [ON RADIO]:
All units. Code 99.
4-1-7 in progress, Starling Aquarium.
-All available units...
FELICITY: This came over the police frequency.
Hacked the aquarium security system
to get a better look.
You want to argue with me, huh?
Bystanders said they saw him
pop green and purple pills.
There's a lunatic high on Vertigo
who's taken hostages...
...and you're making tea?
Medicinal herbs from the island...
...counterbalance the effects
of certain drugs and poisons.
They should counteract
the effects of Vertigo.
[MACHINE BEEPING]
-Then you aren't going to...
-What?
You know...
My sister got high on this garbage.
Could've killed someone.
She didn't deserve an arrow in the heart.
This guy didn't fail the city.
The city failed him.
And so did I.
What's happening now isn't your fault.
You didn't make him take drugs.
I failed to put the Count in a grave
so he couldn't hurt anyone.
-They locked him up...
-And now the city is on fire!
So clearly it wasn't the right decision.
Get in touch with Diggle.
With the security feed out, I'm gonna need
a second set of eyes at the aquarium.
[PHONE RINGING]
-Glad I caught you stateside.
-Just barely.
-I leave in two days for Pyongyang.
-Isn't that classified?
I figure an old Army buddy
can keep a secret.
-I was glad to get your call.
-Lyla, that's not why I called.
There's something else
you'd like me to do, then.
Well, actually, I think
there's something I can do for you.
I'm gonna go out on a limb
and assume that Deadshot...
-...is on ARGUS's most wanted list.
-What do you know about him?
Well, his name, for starters.
Floyd Lawton.
We don't even have that.
Where'd you get it?
Same place I got this.
It's everything you need to locate
who's giving Deadshot his targets.
What's your interest in this?
Lawton came up in connection
with some things I'm working on.
Decided to pass it off to you.
I remember you being
a better liar than that, Johnnie.
Listen, Lyla,
Lawton is a very dangerous man.
Your people are qualified
to take him down. It's simple.
Nothing in our business is simple.
You come to ask for my help again,
Mr. Lance?
LANCE:
Eric Messner.
Who?
He's a zoning commissioner
for Starling City.
A notoriously corrupt one at that.
The missing 10 grand...
...you paid him to skip the inspection
of your nightclub.
Why'd you do that?
What didn't you want him to find?
-We've got nothing to hide here.
-Great. Then let's just take a look around.
-Absolutely.
-Yep.
When you come back with a search warrant.
You sure this is how you want to play this?
Apparently.
Doesn't my daughter know
how to pick them?
Stop laughing at me!
[WOMAN SOBBING]
[GUNSHOTS AND PEOPLE SCREAM]
Shut up! Just shut up!
[GRUNTING]
GREEN ARROW:
Stop! I don't wanna hurt you!
[GRUNTING]
Hey, easy. I'm here to help you.
[MAN GASPING]
My mom does yoga.
Hey, remember when Slade and I
rescued you?
You rescued me?
Fine.
When we all rescued each other.
You said you knew
why Fyers wanted Yao Fei...
...and how he was forcing him to help him.
Feel like sharing?
I'm almost out of slapping water.
My father was a Shang Jiang
in the People's Liberation Army.
A general.
I didn't hear the details of Fyers' plans
but he wants my father to be the face of it.
A scapegoat.
To take the blame
and conceal their own involvement.
Why was Yao Fei on the Island
in the first place?
Fyers says he murdered people.
No, he didn't.
The Chinese military committed
a massacre.
Someone had to take the blame.
They chose him.
Sent him to this island, for life.
I spent years looking for him.
A few months ago,
a man came to my apartment...
...said he had information
about my father's whereabouts.
I had given up hope.
I let my guard down,
didn't see the Taser until...
When I woke up, I was here.
I'm worried. This island...
What he must have had to do to survive.
That it changed him.
He saved my life.
He's still a good man, Shado.
Again.
LAUREL: So there I am sitting at our favorite
sushi restaurant...
...a bottle of sake, and the only thing
that's missing is my boyfriend.
Oh, God, I'm so sorry, baby.
I just have a lot going on here.
Tommy, whatever's going on with you,
I want you to know I believe you.
I'm here for you.
OLIVER: Sorry.
LAUREL: Ollie.
-What's wrong?
-Bad night.
It's about to get worse.
Mr. Merlyn, as requested,
a warrant to search these premises.
-I can't believe you're doing this.
-Believe it.
Detective, I'm not an attorney...
...but on what grounds
are you searching my club?
Your manager
bribed a government official...
...to keep him from inspecting
your building.
-What?
LANCE: He's selling Vertigo out of the club.
-Ollie, it's valid.
LANCE: Thank you.
A sublevel is not listed
on the inspection's floor plans.
However, I pulled the county records.
There's something down there.
I wanna see for myself what it is.
Oh, look at that.
Open the door.
[OLIVER SIGHS]
-You're making a mistake.
-No, you are if you don't open that door.
I said, open the door.
[BEEPING]
Thank you.
TOMMY: The place is a kind of a mess. I've
been using it to store the bulk of our inventory.
-What's in the boxes?
TOMMY: Why don't you have a look?
If Prohibition were still in effect, you might
have the basis of a criminal complaint.
Would you like to open the crates?
[SIGHS]
So if you don't have anything to hide...
...why didn't you want
the inspector down here?
Well, the ventilation system in this place
hasn't been updated since the '60s.
I mean, we shouldn't even be open.
Yeah.
LAUREL: I'm sorry. I thought he was okay
with us being together.
TOMMY:
He wasn't wrong. I bribed a guy.
That's not why
he brought out his jackboots.
It's all gonna be fine. I'll see you at home.
-Good night.
-Is there something you want to say?
-Thank you.
No, the thing that you were thinking...
...when Lance accused me of dealing
out of the club.
I don't understand
why you wouldn't tell me about the bribe.
I run the club, Oliver.
I don't tell you a lot of things.
So let me ask you a question, pal...
...what have I done in the six months
since you've been home...
...that would lead you to believe
I would sell drugs?
In the last six months, nothing.
-Yeah.
-But before I left, you played hard.
You played with bad people
who were in...
And so did you, Oliver.
But I changed. Just like you did.
Now you put arrows in people
who do illegal things.
Last time I checked,
bribing a city inspector was not legal.
Do you actually think
that I could hurt you?
Truthfully, I have no idea
what the hell you would do.
You are a complete mystery to me.
I've got no idea
how you find it so easy to kill people.
The next time you decide to think the worst
of me imagine what I now think of you.
-What's his problem?
-What's yours?
-Excuse me?
-I asked Felicity to get in touch with you.
There was a hostage situation
at the aquarium.
-Sorry, I didn't get message till it was over.
-Why?
I was busy doing something else.
Lawton.
-You didn't end up needing me.
-You couldn't have known that.
In other words, "Find your brother's killer
on your own time."
Vertigo is tearing this city apart, Diggle,
so yeah, maybe now is not the best time...
...to indulge a personal vendetta.
You're telling me...
...that you going after the Count
is not personal?
Oliver, I cannot read a book to my nephew
without knowing Lawton killed his father.
I can't move on with Carly,
I can't move on with my life...
...knowing that he's still out there.
I thought if anybody got that, it'd be you.
-What happened here?
-The Ethernet cable still works.
-Would you plug in your tablet?
-You decide to remodel?
OLIVER: Long story.
-Where's Dig?
-Okay.
The hostage-taking junkie
is our only lead to the Count.
What type of information
are you looking for?
Anything that would give us a line on
the Count's location.
Has the ME performed the autopsy yet?
Yeah. Just pulling it up now.
Check the toxicology to see
if there's something related to Vertigo.
-He didn't die from a Vertigo overdose.
-I saw it, Felicity.
According to the coroner,
cause of death was severe anaphylaxis.
He died of an allergic reaction to
chlorpromazine.
That's an anti-psychotic.
Pull up the Veronica Sparks autopsy.
Did she have chlorpromazine
in her system?
Yes. How'd you know?
The Count must've added it
in this latest iteration of Vertigo.
Wouldn't the amount he'd need...
...to manufacture enough for circulation
be huge?
-Where would he get that much?
-A mental institution.
-What if we're looking at this wrong?
-How so?
Everybody is looking for him
outside the asylum.
But what if he never left?
What if he faked his escape,
the same way he faked being insane?
[COUNT SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
Never forgets.
Always back for more.
GREEN ARROW:
I should've killed you when I had the chance.
Turn around.
I said, turn around.
[MAN GRUNTS]
Oliver Queen.
All those years on that island.
Guess you really did go crazy.
So the Count
didn't fake losing his mind, did he?
This was you the whole time.
How did you get him to give you
the formula for Vertigo, huh?
Chemistry doesn't seem like
his best subject right now.
He couldn't tell me if he wanted to.
I ordered a biopsy on his kidneys.
The tissue was suffused
with the narcotic after his OD.
When I got the results...
...I realized I could reverse-engineer
the chemical compound of the drug.
Produce a synthesized version myself
using the facilities here.
And made a few improvements
like adding chlorpromazine.
That's how you found us.
Cops came around
and started asking questions...
...you faked the Count's disappearance
to draw attention away from yourself.
It's clever.
I wasn't trying to be a criminal mastermind.
I just needed the money.
Something I'm sure
a billionaire wouldn't understand.
Believe me.
I understand you perfectly.
Open his mouth.
[GRUNTING]
From what I've read in the tabloids...
...no one will be surprised to hear
Oliver Queen died of a drug overdose.
[CLICK]
[BEEPING]
[GRUNTING]
OLIVER:
Dig!
Argh!
Unh! Unh!
[BEEPING]
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLING
AND MAN GRUNTS]
Clear.
Freeze!
DOCTOR:
You don't look so good.
I doubt you could aim a single arrow.
COUNT:
Looks like I'm the last one standing.
Sitting.
Spinning.
Something to do.
What was I going to do?
Memory not what it once was.
Nothing what it once was.
Is there a name on the gravestone?
No.
It's new...
...and clean...
...and waiting.
We're finished here.
OLIVER: Hey. How we doing?
-In the black.
Did the Hood get his man?
Well, we won't be having any problems
with Vertigo anymore.
-Look, Tommy, I'm sorry...
-I've caught up the bookkeeping...
...and all my notes on the inventory
are in there...
-...along with the list of suppliers we use.
-Okay.
-I don't see why you're telling me that.
-This club is important to me.
But for you it's just a front.
You want me to keep your secret,
help you be this thing you've become...
...but you refuse to see me
for what I've become.
I've got just a bit too much
self-respect for that.
I quit.
SLADE:
Dinner.
You're still doing that?
Fyers better be careful
with his bowls of water.
When are we gonna do actual training?
SHADO: There once was a young boy
whose father dropped him off...
-...at a Shaolin monastery to study kung fu.
-Good. A story.
After a year,
the boy came to visit his family.
When asked what he'd learned,
the boy hung his head in shame.
All the monks had him do was slap water
in a barrel for a year.
We don't have a year, so I hope
your training regimen is a bit faster.
The family didn't believe him,
so he showed them.
He raised his hand
and hit the table they were eating on.
-It broke in half.
-I'm going to be able to break a table?
Better.
[OLIVER SIGHS]
Okay.
Draw the bow.
I'll be damned.
What's next?
We teach you to shoot.
-Drinking alone?
-Oh. Well, not anymore.
Just soda?
Bartender forget the Scotch?
I didn't really feel the need for it.
So, um...
The girl who died...
...turns out that she got her Vertigo
from a co-worker.
-Guess I owe your boyfriend an apology.
-He has a name, you know.
I just can't seem to bring myself
to use it. Baby steps.
Did I screw things up between us again?
No.
I really wasn't looking to jam up Merlyn.
I knew by pursuing him
that I could throw a wrench in us...
-Then why'd you do it?
-There was evidence, Laurel.
And I had to follow it, I had to.
Your mom was right. You were right.
Like you said about me and the Vigilante,
I can't let things go.
And I close cases. It's what I do.
Everyone else be damned.
Maybe the fact that there's no Scotch
in there means you're ready to work on that.
People can change.
DIGGLE: Hey.
-Hey.
You had my back.
You needed me.
-Felicity told me where you were headed.
-You okay.
I'm the killer, remember?
I've killed before, Oliver.
It's just been a while.
If you're the killer,
why isn't the Count down too?
Sure it must have been tempting,
take him off the board for good.
-People change.
-People like the Count?
No, I meant me.
Not so long ago,
I would've put that guy down for good...
...but looking at him today,
all vacant...
...there didn't seem to be a point.
But not everybody deserves mercy.
For example.
-I thought he wasn't a priority to you.
-He's a priority to you.
And you two have unfinished business.
Where do we start?
I'd prefer we skip the I-told-you-so's,
but the nightclub...
...wasn't really working out.
I guess I need something more boring.
Stable.
Nine to 5, go home, kiss Laurel,
that sort of thing.
I guess what I'm saying is...
...I want a job.