PREVIOUSLY ON "ARROW"...
RUSSIA IS YOUR HOME.
LET ME GO SAVE MINE.
PEOPLE ARE
GONNA WANT TO KNOW
WHERE I'VE
BEEN FOR THE PAST 5 YEARS.
IT'S EASIER IF I'M
JUST A SIMPLE CASTAWAY.
[PROJECTILE FLIES]
I'M AFRAID YOU'RE GOING
TO MISS YOUR BOAT HOME.
WHAT'S SO FUNNY ABOUT
MY FATHER'S LEGACY?!
HE WAS GOING
TO DISOWN YOU.
OLIVER: WITH HELP FROM
THE GREEN ARROW AND HIS TEAM,
THE THROWING STAR KILLER IS
NOW BEHIND BARS
AND OUR STREETS ARE
A LITTLE SAFER.
FORMER DISTRICT ATTORNEY
ADRIAN CHASE FACES
MULTIPLE COUNTS
OF CAPITAL MURDER
AMONG OTHER CHARGES.
SCPD SPOKESPERSON ALISON ROU
CREDITS THE GREEN ARROW
WITH BRINGING THE MAN KNOWN
AS THE THROWING STAR KILLER
TO JUSTICE.
THEA: WELL, IT LOOKS
LIKE THE GREEN ARROW
IS A HERO AGAIN,
WHOEVER HE IS.
YUP, AND THE MAYOR AIN'T
DOING TOO BAD EITHER.
THE "SENTINEL" HAS GOT
YOUR APPROVAL RATING
BACK UP TO 70%.
WHAT? WAS IT EVER THAT HIGH?
HMM, NO, IT WASN'T.
UM, ANYWAY, LISTEN,
IF YOU'LL EXCUSE ME,
I GOT TO GO FIND
RENE AND REMOVE HIS
HEAD FROM HIS ASS.
WAIT. WHAT?
OLIVER: RENE MISSED A HEARING
ABOUT POSSIBLY GETTING
HIS DAUGHTER BACK.
-HEY, QUENTIN.
-YEAH?
IF YOU NEED ANY HELP WITH
THAT, JUST LET US KNOW, OK?
YEAH, THANKS.
YEAH, WILL DO.
OH, BY THE WAY, I'M
SORRY. I ALMOST FORGOT.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY,
MR. MAYOR.
THANK YOU.
WE SHOULD GO GET
A DRINK TONIGHT.
WE HAVEN'T CELEBRATED
YOUR BIRTHDAY IN
I CAN'T REMEMBER
HOW LONG.
I REMEMBER THE LAST TIME
WE CELEBRATED YOURS.
OH, GOD. WE DECIDED
WE WOULD NEVER TALK
ABOUT THAT AGAIN.
FOUR YEARS?
YOU'VE CHANGED A LOT,
SPEEDY.
WE BOTH HAVE.
I'M JUST NOT SURE
I HAVE FOR THE BETTER.
I'M SURE.
LOOK, THEA, UH, BEING
HAPPY DOESN'T MEAN
YOU DON'T HAVE ISSUES.
IT JUST MEANS THAT YOU'RE
WORKING ON THEM.
WHEN DID YOU
BECOME
ALL ZEN-LIKE
AND WELL-ADJUSTED?
WELL...
WE SHOULD CELEBRATE
THAT TONIGHT
AS WELL AS YOUR
BIRTHDAY.
I APPRECIATE THAT,
BUT I ALREADY HAVE PLANS.
WITH WHO?
PLEASE SAY,
"NOT SUSAN WILLIAMS."
UM, IT...NO.
UH, WITH FELICITY.
AS IN A DATE?
AS...AS IN I...
I DON'T KNOW
IF IT'S A DATE.
BUT YOU'RE HOPING
THAT IT IS?
IT'S DINNER. HA HA!
PEOPLE GO TO DINNER.
SEE, I DON'T
BELIEVE YOU,
BUT I FIND IT
INCREDIBLY CUTE.
[SIGHS]
FELICITY AND THEA:
SURPRISE!
SURPRISE.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY. EV...
EVERYTHING HURT...
EVERYTHING HURTS.
YEAH. UGH.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
YES!
HA HA!
THEA: I LOVE THE CAKE.
WHERE DID YOU GET IT?
LORD MESA BAKERY.
WHAT'S UP WITH THE NUMBER 6?
IS THAT FOR THE NUMBER
OF MEMBERS OF THE TEAM?
IT'S COOL.
ACTUALLY, I ORDERED
THE CAKE FOR A 6-YEAR-OLD
BECAUSE I WASN'T SURE THAT
I COULD ORDER
A GREEN ARROW CAKE
FOR A GROWN MAN.
[LAUGHTER]
WELL, HEY, OLIVER'S
A CHILD AT HEART, RIGHT?
THAT IS THE CONCUSSION
TALKING. YUP, FOR SURE.
I'M REALLY SORRY ABOUT
THAT, CURTIS.
NAH, IT'S OK, BUT
YOU SHOULD KNOW
THAT IF I HAD
MY T-SPHERES,
I WOULD'VE...
WOULD'VE WHAT?
I WOULD'VE STILL
BEEN ON THE FLOOR.
I'M VERY SORRY.
[CHUCKLES]
OH. OH.
[SIGHS]
WHEW! HEH HEH.
I WAS WORRIED THIS
MIGHT HAVE GOTTEN HURT.
WHAT IS IT?
THEY ARE SOUND
MODULATORS THAT I'VE
BEEN WORKING ON
FOR DINAH.
NOT ONLY WILL THEY
BE ABLE TO FOCUS
HER CANARY CRY,
BUT THEY WILL BE
ABLE TO OVERRIDE
ANY KIND OF
SONIC DAMPENERS.
-YES!
-SHE'S COMING, RIGHT?
YEAH. SHE SAID IF WORK
DIDN'T GO TOO LATE,
THEN SHE'D SWING ON BY.
THANK YOU.
CAKE.
-YES.
-HERE YOU GO.
LYLA COULDN'T MAKE IT?
SHE AND J.J. ARE VISITING
HER SISTER IN CHICAGO.
-OH.
-WE'RE GOOD, MAN.
WE'LL PATCH THINGS UP.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
I'M LATE, AREN'T I?
THAT'S ALL GOOD.
DIDN'T MISS MUCH.
JUST OLIVER FLIPPING CURTIS
OVER HIS SHOULDER.
I TOLD YOU
A SURPRISE PARTY
WASN'T A GOOD IDEA.
[CHUCKLES]
HOW WAS RENE?
HE'S NOT HOME.
AND THERE'S A COUPLE OF
DAYS' WORTH OF NEWSPAPERS
PILED UP OUTSIDE
HIS APARTMENT.
YOU'RE WORRIED ABOUT HIM.
YEAH, WELL, YOU KNOW,
RENE MAY COME ACROSS
AS AN IRRESPONSIBLE
IDIOT, BUT THAT'S...
YOU KNOW, IT'S JUST
'CAUSE THAT'S WHAT HE
WANTS PEOPLE TO THINK
OF HIM, YOU KNOW?
-YEAH.
-HEY.
HEY.
WE'RE GONNA DO A TOAST
IN ABOUT 5 MINUTES,
SO CHAMPAGNE AND...
-CLUB SODA.
-ALL RIGHT. YOU GOT IT.
LOOK AT YOU WITH
THE NICE WRAPPING.
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU ALL SO MUCH
FOR DOING THIS. CHEERS.
-CHEERS.
I ALMOST FORGOT
WHAT IT WAS LIKE
TO CELEBRATE A BIRTHDAY.
THAT'S BECAUSE WE'RE
USUALLY SAVING THE CITY
FROM BEING DESTROYED
THIS TIME OF YEAR.
THIS, UH, IT'S LIKE
SUMMER BREAK FOR YOU GUYS.
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO, HUH?
I'VE ALWAYS WANTED
TO SEE FLORENCE...
THE CITY IN ITALY, NOT THE
WOMAN OR HER WEIRD MACHINES.
[QUENTIN AND CURTIS CHUCKLE]
I'M GONNA TEACH J.J.
HOW TO FISH.
TWO DAYS WITH MY SON
ON THE WATER,
THAT WOULD BE HEAVEN.
I WAS THINKING OF
THE PACIFIC CREST TRAIL
FOR A NIGHT OR,
YOU KNOW, JUST ONE NIGHT
UNDER THE STARS
AND THEN DEFINITELY
A MANICURE/PEDICURE
AFTERWARDS.
JOHN: WHAT ABOUT
YOU, OLIVER?
I KNOW YOU
GOT CITY HALL
AND ALL, BUT...
YEAH, IT KEEPS ME BUSY, BUT
I...I NEED TO BUY SOME SOCKS.
EVERYBODY HAS THEIR THING.
I NEED SOCKS BAD.
-WELL, THAT'S...OK.
-SOCKS IT IS.
WELL, I...I THINK WE
COULD ALL USE
ANOTHER PIECE OF
CAKE, RIGHT?
YEAH, SURE.
NO, ACTUALLY, I'M GOOD. HEH! I
HAD ABOUT 3 OR 4 SLICES MYSELF.
I NEED TO TELL
YOU SOMETHING.
-OH, OK.
-YOU NEED CAKE.
-OH, YEAH. YEAH. I NEED CAKE.
YEAH.
-OHH.
-THAT...THAT WAS SUBTLE.
SO SUBTLE.
I GUESS SINCE THE DINNER
AT CHEZ MARTA WAS A RUSE,
THEY THINK WE DESERVE
SOME ALONE TIME.
DO WE?
WELL, I MEAN,
I DIDN'T KNOW
IF IT WAS A...
WE CAN TAKE IT ONE STEP
AT A TIME.
I WOULD LIKE THAT
VERY MUCH.
THIS IS HARD FOR YOU, HUH?
HYPOTHETICALLY DATING MY
EX-FIANCEE? NO. IT'S F...
WOW. NO.
I MEANT "SUMMER VACATION"
AS THEY ARE NOW CALLING IT.
IT'S INCREDIBLY HARD.
IT'S BORDERLINE
IMPOSSIBLE.
WE WON. OLIVER, WE WON.
JUST TAKE A STEP BACK,
YOU KNOW?
YOU COULD PUT YOUR FEET UP
NO MATTER THE STATE
OF YOUR SOCKS...
YOU COULD JUST...
GOD FORBID...
RELAX.
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
YEAH.
MY GOVERNMENT HEARD
RUMORS OF THIS PLACE...
AN ISLAND PRISON BUILT
BY THE CHINESE.
IT'S INCREDIBLE...
THAT YOU SHOULD LEAD ME
HERE, OF ALL PLACES.
I KILLED YOU.
ALMOST BUT NOTHING EVER
REALLY DIES.
THERE ARE ALWAYS ECHOES.
[SNAPS FINGERS]
YOU'LL LEARN THAT
SOON ENOUGH.
THE KGB CALL THIS
THE RED DEATH.
IT'S AN INTERROGATION DRUG.
MEANT TO BREAK MEN
BY INDUCING
PSYCHOLOGICAL ANGUISH.
THAT'S WHY YOU FOLLOWED ME
HALFWAY AROUND THE WORLD...
TORTURE.
MURDER CREATES INTIMACY
BETWEEN MEN.
SO I'D APPRECIATE
AN HONEST ANSWER.
IF YOUR INTENTION WAS
TO RETURN HOME,
WHY LEAVE FROM HERE?
HONESTLY...
GO TO HELL.
THAT'S
AN INTERESTING RESPONSE.
IF MY CHINESE IS CORRECT,
THIS...THIS PLACE IS CALLED
PURGATORY.
YOU KNOW THE CATHOLICS
CONSIDER PURGATORY
TO BE...
THE IMMEDIATE STATE
FOLLOWING PHYSICAL DEATH?
[GASPING]
KONSTANTIN,
WHEN I KILL YOU
THIS TIME,
I'M GONNA MAKE SURE
YOU'RE DEAD.
[GROANING]
WHEN WE'RE DONE,
THE ONLY PERSON YOU'D
WANT TO KILL IS YOURSELF.
I'M JUST SAYING YOU
COULD'VE TAKEN
A BIG KNIFE AND CUT THE
TENSION BETWEEN YOU TWO.
AND BY "TENSION,"
I MEAN SEXUAL TENSION.
YEAH, I KNOW WHAT YOU
MEANT, CURTIS.
AND THEN THE WAY YOU GUYS
DRESSED UP FOR EACH OTHER?
WHOO! SIZZLE, SIZZLE!
OK. CAN YOU PLEASE STOP?
YOU'RE WORSE THAN A SHIPPER
ON A SOAP OPERA.
OK. WELL, LOOK,
I'M HERE.
I HOPE DINAH'S STILL UP.
I THINK HER NEIGHBORS
ARE ASLEEP.
THAT'S THE WHOLE
POINT OF THIS
MODULATOR ANYWAY.
-OH, NO.
-OH, NO WHAT?
I THINK SHE WAS
ROBBED.
DO YOU NEED BACKUP?
YEAH, PROBABLY.
BUT I'M HERE NOW,
SO I GOT TO MAKE
SURE SHE'S OK.
HELLO? DINAH?
IF THERE'S SOMEONE IN
HERE, YOU SHOULD KNOW
THAT I KNOW MARTIAL ARTS.
CURTIS,
WHAT'S GOING ON?
OH, MY GOD.
[LOUD THUD, CURTIS GROANS,
GLASS BREAKING]
CURTIS? CURTIS!
CURTIS? CURTIS?
JOHN: CLEAR!
I GOT CURTIS' PHONE
BUT NO DINAH AND CURTIS.
OK, WELL, IF CURTIS
AND DINAH ARE MISSING,
I GUESS WE
CAN PRESUME THAT RENE
DIDN'T SKIP OUT
ON HIS DAUGHTER.
-WHOEVER DID THIS IS GOOD.
-WE KNOW WHO'S DOING THIS.
IT'S CHASE.
HE'S PICKING US OFF
ONE BY ONE.
NOT TO STATE THE OBVIOUS,
BUT CHASE IS
CURRENTLY UNDER
SURVEILLANCE 24/7
IN AN IMPENETRABLE
GLASS BOX.
THERE'S NO WAY HE GOT OUT
TO DO THIS.
OH, HE HAD TO HAVE HELP.
WELL, I HATE
TO SAY THIS,
BUT WHAT IF THIS WAS
CHASE'S PLAN ALL ALONG?
GET HIMSELF CAUGHT,
LULL US TO SLEEP.
FELICITY: YEAH, WELL, CONSIDER
ME OFFICIALLY WOKE.
OK, CHASE HAS WORKED
WITH EVIL LAUREL BEFORE,
BUT SHE'S CURRENTLY LOCKED UP
AT ARGUS,
AND THERE IS NO WAY THAT EVELYN
IS DOING THIS ALL BY HERSELF.
OLIVER: JOHN?
ISN'T THAT LEAGUE?
IT'S TALIA AL GHUL.
[HEAVY SIGH]
CONTACT THEA AND LANCE.
WE NEED TO GET
THEM SOMEPLACE SECURE.
THERE'S AN ARGUS SAFE HOUSE
ACROSS TOWN WE CAN USE.
OK, YOU GET THEM THERE,
THEN MEET ME AT THE BUNKER.
WHERE YOU GOING?
IT'S TIME TO TALK TO CHASE.
[FOOTSTEPS]
OLIVER: WHERE ARE THEY?
ADRIAN,
WHERE ARE THEY?!
-WHO?
-YOU KNOW DAMN...
"YOU KNOW DAMN WELL WHO!"
YOU'RE RIGHT.
I DO KNOW, JUST LIKE I KNOW
YOUR EVERY MOVE
WHILE IT SEEMS LIKE
YOU KNOW NONE OF MINE.
TELL ME WHERE THEY ARE.
OR WHAT? WE'VE ALREADY
ESTABLISHED THAT YOU THINK
YOU WON'T KILL ME.
KIND OF WEAKENS
YOUR LEVERAGE.
I'M GONNA FIND THEM, AND
I'M GONNA GET THEM BACK.
IS THAT WHAT YOU CAME HERE
TO TELL ME,
OR ARE YOU JUST
WASTING TIME?
HEH.
SEE YOU LATER.
AH, PAIN.
IT'S FASCINATING, ISN'T IT?
SOME MEN WILL DO ANYTHING
TO AVOID IT.
OTHERS WILL EMBRACE IT,
EVEN REVEL IN IT,
LIKE YOU.
THAT'S WHY YOU'RE
SO FORMIDABLE.
PAIN IS NOT A NEW
EXPERIENCE TO YOU.
THEN STOP WASTING
MY TIME.
[SCREAMING]
THAT WAS MY EPIPHANY.
FOR TRUE RETRIBUTION,
I COULDN'T MERELY
CAUSE YOU PAIN.
I HAD TO WAKE YOU UP,
OPEN YOUR EYES,
MAKE YOU SEE
THE PAIN YOU SUFFER IS
STILL WITH YOU.
THIS DRUG HELPS
SET IT FREE.
[SCREAMING]
EVERY CUT, EVERY BULLET,
EVERY WOUND LIKE YOU'RE FEELING
IT ALL FOR THE FIRST TIME.
[OLIVER YELLING]
WHY AM I STILL WASTING
YOUR TIME?
FREEZE,
JERK WAD!
SORRY.
I KNEW IT WAS YOU, BUT WHAT
IF IT WASN'T YOU YOU?
YOU KNOW. MULTIPLE EARTHS,
EVIL TWINS, ET CETERA.
"ET CETERA" BEING
THE SCARIEST THING
I'VE SAID ALL DAY.
I HATE THIS THING.
[SHUDDERS]
I'M A LITTLE ON EDGE.
I'M ACTUALLY REALLY
LOOKING FORWARD
TO BEING ALL HOLED UP IN
AN ARGUS SAFE HOUSE.
I DON'T WANT YOU
IN THE SAFE HOUSE. I WANT
YOU DOWN HERE WITH ME.
WHAT? NO. WHY? I...I CAN
RUN COMMS REMOTELY, OK?
AND IF MALCOLM MERLYN
HAS PROVEN ANYTHING,
IT'S THAT WHEN IT COMES
TO THE LEAGUE OF ASSASSINS,
LOCKS ARE MORE LIKE
SUGGESTIONS.
I CAN HANDLE TALIA AL GHUL
AND WHATEVER ACOLYTES
SHE'S FIGHTING WITH.
WHERE I NEED YOU IS DOWN
HERE WITH ME
SO THAT BOTH OF US
CAN TRY TO STOP CHASE.
IS THIS...EH,
THIS MIGHT SOUND
A LITTLE SELF-SERVING,
BUT IS TACTICS
THE ONLY THING BEHIND ME
STAYING DOWN HERE?
-HONESTLY?
-YEAH.
OF COURSE NOT.
OK, THE...THE THING THAT'S
CLEAR, THOUGH, TO ME
RIGHT NOW IS THAT I...
[INHALES AND EXHALES]
I LET MY GUARD DOWN,
AND I SHOULDN'T HAVE.
NO ONE COULD'VE SEEN
THIS COMING, OLIVER.
NO ONE.
I SAW IT COMING.
I KNEW SOMETHING WAS WRONG.
I KNEW IT HERE,
AND I IGNORED IT.
AND THEN I SECOND-GUESSED
MYSELF.
AND NOW EVERYONE THAT
I LOVE IS IN DANGER,
INCLUDING MAYBE...
YOU KNOW, MY SON.
NO, I COULDN'T FIND HIM.
THERE'S NO WAY THEY'RE
GOING TO.
NOT CHASE,
NOT TALIA AL GHUL.
WILLIAM'S
GOING TO BE FINE.
I APPRECIATE THAT,
BUT YOU CAN'T KNOW THAT.
YOU...YOU CAN'T.
WILLIAM IS
THE PUREST PART OF ME,
AND NOW HE'S IN DANGER
MAYBE BECAUSE OF SOMETHING
THAT THE WORST PART OF ME
SET IN MOTION.
[FOOTSTEPS]
OLIVER: HOW DID IT GO?
THEA AND QUENTIN ARE NOT
HAPPY ABOUT IT,
BUT THEY'RE SECURE.
[COMPUTER BEEPING]
OH, NO. NO, NO, NO, NO, NO,
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
I HAD ARGUS TRIPLE-CHECK
ON BLACK SIREN.
SHE'S NOT IN HER CELL.
THAT'S NOT
A COINCIDENCE.
QUENTIN DOESN'T KNOW
ABOUT HER.
THAT'S WHY CHASE WILL
SEND HER RIGHT THERE.
WE NEED TO GET THE SAFE HOUSE
ON THE PHONE NOW.
OH, GOD. YOU KNOW
WHAT THE WORST PART
ABOUT A SAFE HOUSE IS?
IT'S NOT BEING ABLE
TO USE YOUR CELL PHONE.
THAT'S JUST...IT'S BARBARIC.
WELL, YEAH. NORMALLY
I'D CHALK THAT UP
TO MILLENNIAL
NONSENSE,
BUT I KNOW WHAT
YOU MEAN.
I'M CHAMPING AT
THE BIT TO SPEAK TO
THAT JUDGE IN RENE'S
CASE RIGHT NOW.
WELL, WHAT COULD YOU SAY?
THAT RENE WAS KIDNAPPED BY
SOME PSYCHO THAT'S IN JAIL?
I GOT TO DO
SOMETHING, THEA.
I KNOW WHAT IT'S LIKE
TO LOSE A DAUGHTER.
AND HELL IF I'M GONNA
LET THAT HAPPEN TO RENE.
RIGHT.
[CELL PHONE VIBRATES]
AGENT KOSINESKI. HELLO?
[HIGH-PITCHED STATIC]
HEY, SHARON, WE GOT A PROBLEM
WITH THE COMMS IN...
[STATIC BURST]
KOSINESKI: STAY HERE.
YEAH, WELL,
I DON'T KNOW ABOUT YOU,
BUT I'M SURE AS HELL
NOT STAYING HERE, WAITING.
YOU READ MY MIND.
LET'S GO.
IT'S A TRANQ DART.
STOP RIGHT THERE!
STOP. TURN AROUND SLOWLY.
TURN...
HI, DADDY.
[SHUDDERS]
NO, IT CAN'T BE.
IT CAN BE.
DON'T WORRY. I'LL
EXPLAIN EVERYTHING.
DON'T TAKE YOUR GUN
OFF HER, QUENTIN.
THEA? THEA?
I KNOW. IT'S NOT
WHAT IT SEEMS.
DID OLLIE...UH!
[DART FLIES]
[THUD, PISTOL FALLS TO FLOOR]
I'M SO SORRY, DADDY.
WHAT DO WE KNOW?
YOU MEAN
BESIDES THIS BEING
THE HORROR VERSION OF
"GROUNDHOG DAY"? LOOK.
THE SECURITY CAMERA
FOOTAGE IS GRAINY,
BUT IT'S GOOD ENOUGH TO
SEE BLACK SIREN GIVING
HER BEST LAUREL
IMPRESSION.
IF WE KNOW THERE WAS
A SECOND ATTACKER,
WHO DO WE THINK IT WAS?
WELL, THE ARGUS AGENT
THAT GAVE BLACK SIREN
HER GET OUT OF JAIL
FREE CARD SAID THAT HE
WAS BLACKMAILED BY
A WOMAN WEARING BLACK,
SO IT COULD BE TALIA.
IT WAS EVELYN.
AGENT KOSINESKI GOT
A POSITIVE ID BEFORE
HE GOT TRANQ'ED.
FELICITY:
SO THESE KIDNAPPINGS
ARE WHAT, PAYBACK?
BEFORE CHASE TORTURED ME,
I TOLD HIM THAT THE TEAM
WAS MY STRENGTH.
HE'S TRYING TO TAKE IT AWAY.
SO HIS LADY FRIENDS
CAN COME AFTER YOU
INSTEAD OF HIM?
THAT DOESN'T SOUND
VERY SATISFYING.
CHASE DOESN'T THINK I CAN
GAME OUT WHAT HE'S
PLANNING, BUT IT'S OBVIOUS.
YEAH, OBVIOUS
TO A MURDERING PSYCHOPATH,
AND PRESENT COMPANY
EXCLUDED.
HE'S TRYING TO LEVERAGE
OUR FRIENDS
TO MAKE ME SET HIM FREE.
[CHUCKLING]
THAT'S CRAZY.
WHICH WOULD BE CONSISTENT
FOR CHASE.
-YOU TWO HAVE TO LEAVE THE CITY.
-WHAT?
YOU GOT TO LEAVE THE CITY,
YOU GOT TO LEAVE THE STATE,
AND YOU CAN'T TELL ME
WHERE YOU'RE GOING.
OLIVER, WE'RE NOT
LEAVING.
WE'RE NOT GOING ANYWHERE.
WE'RE NOT ABANDONING YOU.
I UNDERSTAND THAT YOU'RE
NOT ABANDONING ME.
YOU'RE DOING WHAT I'M ASKING
YOU TO DO BECAUSE CH...
CHASE KNOWS HOW I THINK.
HE KNOWS THAT IF HE PUTS
THE TWO OF YOU IN DANGER...
AND HE'S GOING TO TRY
TO...THAT...
MY INSTINCT WILL BE
TO PULL YOU CLOSE.
SO DO SOMETHING
HE'S NOT EXPECTING.
SPLIT UP.
NO, THAT'S...
WHAT ABOUT YOU?
IF I DON'T HAVE TO WORRY
ABOUT THE TWO OF YOU,
THEN I CAN PUT MY FOCUS
TOWARDS FINDING THE OTHERS.
YOU GET THIS SON
OF A BITCH, OLIVER.
I WILL.
[GROANING]
KOVAR: YOU ARE STRONG,
LIKE A PIECE OF IRON.
YOU THINK YOU CAN RESIST
ANY PAIN
BECAUSE YOU HAVE...
HUH.
BUT THE WORST PAIN
IS UP HERE,
LOCKED AWAY
DEEP INSIDE.
THAT'S WHAT THE DRUG
IS FOR...
TO SHOW YOU
EVERYTHING...
YOUR SINS...
TAIANA, I'M SORRY.
[TAIANA GASPING]
[SNAP]
YOUR FAILURES...
I GUESS YOU MADE
YOUR CHOICE.
NOOOO!
YOUR GUILT...
SHADO: OLIVER, NO!
YOUR BLOODLUST...
YOUR INHUMANITY.
AH, THAT GUN. IT
ONLY HAS ONE BULLET.
YOU CAN WASTE IT
ON ME,
BUT I THINK WE
BOTH KNOW
WHO'S RESPONSIBLE
FOR YOUR PAIN.
[MUMBLES]
I'VE SEEN
THE STRONGEST MAN
RESIST FOR UP TO
12 MINUTES BEFORE...
ENDING HIS SUFFERING.
SUCH IS MY RESPECT
FOR YOU THAT I...
I THINK YOU CAN LAST
FOR, UH, 14 MINUTES.
DASVIDANIYA.
YAO FEI: YOU'RE GOING
TO DO IT, AREN'T YOU?
BECAUSE YOU ARE
NOT STRONG
AND YOU KNOW
YOU DESERVE TO DIE.
[YELLS]
DON'T MOVE.
LET ME HELP YOU
UNDERSTAND,
I AM NOT GOING
TO KILL YOU.
I AM NEVER GOING TO GIVE
YOU THE SATISFACTION
OF BEING THE MAN
THAT YOU THINK I AM.
YOU'RE NEVER GETTING
OUT OF HERE.
NOT TODAY. NOT TOMORROW.
NOT EVER.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND?
NO, I DON'T,
BUT ONLY BECAUSE
YOU'RE WRONG.
I TOLD YOU, OLIVER,
EVERYONE IN YOUR ORBIT
SUFFERS
AS THE PRICE FOR YOUR SINS.
AND THE ONLY WAY TO KEEP
THEM FROM PAYING THAT PRICE
IS TO LET ME GO.
I'M GONNA FIND
ANOTHER WAY.
FIND IT QUICK.
THEY'RE TRANSFERRING
ME TO IDAHO TONIGHT.
AHH. AND ONCE
THAT HAPPENS,
THIS OFFER'S
OFF THE TABLE.
I DON'T WANT TO SEE
THAT HAPPEN, OLIVER.
LIKE I TOLD YOU,
I THINK THAT YOU'RE
ONE LOSS AWAY
FROM GETTING DESTROYED.
WHO WOULD IT BE,
I WONDER?
THEA OR FELICITY?
MAYBE SOMEONE ELSE.
I MEAN, LOOK, I DON'T
UNDERSTAND, ALL RIGHT,
BUT THAT WAS LAUREL.
NO, QUENTIN, IT WASN'T.
IT LOOKS LIKE HER,
AND IT SOUNDS LIKE HER...
LOOK, THAT WAS MY
BABY GIRL, ALL RIGHT?
SHE'S BACK JUST LIKE
WITH SARA.
LISTEN, THERE...
IT IS HARD TO EXPLAIN,
BUT THERE ARE
THESE OTHER EARTHS, OK?
PARALLEL UNIVERSES.
NOW YOU'RE TALKING CRAZY.
LISTEN TO YOURSELF.
I...I KNOW. I KNOW HOW
CRAZY IT SOUNDS...
TRUST ME...BUT IT IS REAL.
IT'S REAL.
JUST AS REAL AS META-HUMANS
AND ALIENS.
[SIGHS]
THEN THAT WASN'T LAUREL.
IT WAS A LAUREL.
IT WAS...
IT'S JUST NOT THE ONE
THAT WE KNEW.
OK, BUT, LOOK, SHE'S
VERY CONVINCING.
AND I NEED YOU
TO REMEMBER THAT
BECAUSE THAT IS EXACTLY WHY
CHASE HAS BROUGHT HER HERE.
LET'S GO.
WHERE ARE WE GOING?
THAT'S A SURPRISE.
FELICITY, I ALREADY
HAVE MAJOR ANXIETY.
YOU GOING SILENT ON
ME IS NOT HELPING.
YOU KNOW, MY MOM'S REALLY
BIG INTO INTUITION, LIKE
STARS, SIGNS, HOROSCOPES,
OUIJA BOARDS EVEN.
I ALWAYS THOUGHT IT WAS
EITHER STUPID OR RIDICULOUS.
I NEVER REALLY TOOK IT
SERIOUSLY.
UNTIL NOW, RIGHT?
YEAH. I HAVE THIS REALLY
BAD FEELING.
IT'S RIGHT IN THE PIT
OF MY STOMACH.
WHAT'S IT TELLING YOU?
WE NEVER SHOULD'VE LEFT
OLIVER ALONE.
I AGREE WITH YOU,
FELICITY.
LEAVING OLIVER FEELS
WRONG, BUT MAYBE
THAT'S WHY IT WAS
THE RIGHT THING TO DO.
YOU REALIZE HOW BACKWARDS
THAT SOUNDS, RIGHT?
I DO REALIZE THAT,
BUT THIS IS CHASE WE'RE
DEALING WITH, REMEMBER?
YEAH, I KNOW, BUT WHAT IF
WE OVERTHOUGHT IT
AND NOW OLIVER'S
VULNERABLE?
I SEE YOUR SENSE OF
HOSPITALITY REMAINS INTACT.
YOU ARE NOT WELCOME
HERE, MALCOLM.
YOU AIM TO CUT OFF
MY OTHER HAND, OLIVER?
MAYBE. YOU GONNA TELL
ANOTHER PERSON
ABOUT MY SON?
LAST TIME I WAS DOWN HERE,
I SAVED YOUR LIFE.
DO YOU REALLY THINK THAT
GIVES YOU A PASS
FOR SERVING UP WILLIAM
TO DAMIEN DARHK?
I'M SORRY ABOUT THAT.
I WASN'T THINKING CLEARLY.
I LET MY EMOTIONS
GET OUT OF HAND.
THAT IS ALL IN THE PAST.
THE ONLY THING I'M
CONCERNED ABOUT NOW IS
SAVING MY DAUGHTER.
WHAT'S THAT?
FELICITY: ANGRY WOMAN
WITH TWO SWORDS.
ARE YOU GETTING MAJOR
ISABEL ROCHEV
FLASHBACKS RIGHT NOW?
YUP.
YOU REMEMBER HOW WE
HANDLED THAT, RIGHT?
YUP.
[SHIFTS GEARS]
[TIRES SCREECH]
[FELICITY COUGHING]
-OH, GOD.
-WE GOT TO GET OUT OF HERE.
OH. THAT WORKED BETTER
WITH ROCHEV.
[COUGHS]
DIG.
I TOLD YOU I HAD
A BAD FEELING.
JOHN! FELICITY!
THEY'RE GONE,
OLIVER.
DAMN IT!
THEY WERE TAKEN
ALIVE. FOCUS.
I WOULD'VE THOUGHT
YOU WOULD'VE TAGGED
YOUR...YOUR PETS
BY NOW.
THEY'RE MY FRIENDS, MALCOLM.
AND CURTIS DID PUT TRACKING
NANITES IN FELICITY,
BUT THEY WERE RENDERED
USELESS
WHEN CHASE SET OFF AN EMP.
WELL, I'LL GIVE HIM
THIS MUCH.
HE'S 50 MOVES AHEAD.
BUT THE QUESTION IS
TO WHAT END.
HE WANTS TO LEVERAGE ME INTO
BREAKING HIM OUT OF PRISON.
AND MY DAUGHTER,
YOUR SISTER,
ISN'T SUFFICIENT
LEVERAGE?
YOU'VE BLACKMAILED
PEOPLE, MALCOLM.
HOW OFTEN HAVE YOU KEPT UP
YOUR END OF THE BARGAIN?
AND, QUITE FRANKLY,
I AM SURPRISED
THAT SOMEONE LIKE YOU IS
WILLING TO GIVE IN
TO A MAN LIKE CHASE.
I WILL GIVE IN
TO SOMEONE
IF IT GETS THEA
BACK.
THE FACT THAT SHE
HATES ME
DOESN'T MAKE HER ANY
LESS MY DAUGHTER.
AND SOMETHING YOU
LEARNED LAST YEAR...
FRIENDS ARE ONE THING,
BUT FAMILY IS FAMILY.
AND YOUR CHILD?
YOU WOULD DO ANYTHING,
ABSOLUTELY ANYTHING,
TO KEEP HIM SAFE.
A LITTLE WHILE AGO,
I WORRIED TO JOHN...
THAT THE PERSONAL
CONNECTIONS THAT I HAD
WERE MAKING ME VULNERABLE
BECAUSE AS LONG AS THERE
ARE PEOPLE IN MY LIFE
THAT I CARE FOR,
I HAVE TO BE SOMETHING ELSE
TO PROTECT THEM.
THAT'S SOMETHING THAT
I CAN'T LEAVE IN THE PAST.
I ADMIRE YOU, OLIVER.
IT TAKES A SPECIAL
KIND OF IDIOT
TO ACTUALLY GET DUMBER
WITH TIME.
I AM NOT IN THE MOOD, MALCOLM.
HUMAN CONNECTIONS ARE
WHAT KEEP US HUMAN.
AND IT'S SAD THAT IT...
THAT IT'S A SOCIOPATH WHO'S
GONNA HAVE TO POINT THIS OUT
TO YOU.
YOU CAN'T LIVE ON AN ISLAND.
YOU'VE ALREADY TRIED.
BUT YOU ARE ALWAYS GONNA
HAVE PEOPLE IN YOUR LIFE,
OLIVER, AND THEY WILL
ALWAYS NEED YOU,
FOR BETTER OR WORSE,
BAGGAGE AND ALL.
AND IF YOU CAN'T
ACCEPT THAT, WELL,
YOUR PAST IS GONNA STAY
YOUR ANCHOR.
[CELL PHONE VIBRATING]
YEAH.
MAN: MR. QUEEN,
THE MARSHALS ARE HERE
TO TRANSFER THE PRISONER.
YOU SAID YOU WANTED TO KNOW.
THANK YOU.
I'M ON MY WAY.
I AM GOING
TO ENSURE
THAT CHASE'S
PRISON TRANSFER
GOES SMOOTHLY.
WE ARE VERY CAPABLE
PEOPLE.
AND WE ARE GONNA
FIND A WAY
TO RESCUE EVERYONE.
YOU'RE NOT REAL.
I AM AS REAL AS
YOUR CONSCIENCE.
SHENGCUN.
REMEMBER? "SURVIVE."
MY DYING WISH
FOR YOU
AFTER I GAVE
MY LIFE FOR YOURS.
BUT YOU SQUANDERED
MY SACRIFICE
AND NOW MY DAUGHTER,
MY DEAR SHADO,
IS DEAD.
YAO FEI, I'M SO SORRY.
I'M SO SORRY.
APOLOGIES WON'T BRING
HER BACK.
AND IT WON'T BRING
THE OTHERS BACK.
PLEASE STOP.
TAIANA, AKIO, SARA.
EVERYONE YOU'VE LOST
OVER THE PAST 5 YEARS...
ALL OF THOSE YOU HAVE
YET TO LOSE.
THIS ISN'T REAL.
IT'S NOT REAL.
YOU'RE IN MY HEAD.
AND WHO BETTER THAN YOU
KNOWS THE TRUTH?
WHAT TRUTH?
THAT THOSE CLOSEST TO YOU
ARE FATED TO SUFFER
FOR YOUR SINS.
BUT YOU CAN SAVE THEM,
OLIVER...
BY MAKING THE SAME
SACRIFICE I MADE FOR YOU.
AH. I LOVE WHAT YOU'VE
DONE WITH THE PLACE.
YOU GOT
SHIPPING CONTAINERS
AS NICE AS THIS
ON EARTH-2?
EVERYTHING'S EXACTLY
THE SAME AS IT IS HERE, DAD.
DON'T CALL ME THAT.
YOU'RE LAUREL, BUT
YOU'RE NOT MY LAUREL.
-IS THAT TOO TIGHT?
-YOU CARE?
YOU THINK THIS ISN'T
HARD FOR ME?
DOESN'T MUCH LOOK
LIKE IT.
[SCOFFS]
I OWE MY FREEDOM
TO ADRIAN CHASE.
IN EXCHANGE,
I GIVE HIM MY HELP
AND HIS ASSURANCE
THAT YOU WON'T GET HURT.
CHASE'S ASSURANCE!
MY LAUREL WOULDN'T
BE THAT STUPID.
I KNOW...YOU LOVED HER.
AND I KNOW YOU LOST HER.
AND I KNOW
HOW IT MAKES YOU FEEL
SEEING ME.
YOU'VE GOT NO IDEA.
[DOOR SHUTS]
DON'T WORRY, SIR.
IF CUSTODY'S THREATENED,
WE HAVE ORDERS
TO SHOOT ON SIGHT.
TICKTOCK.
YOU'RE NOT PULLING
MY STRINGS ANYMORE, ADRIAN.
AT LEAST YOU ADMIT
THAT I HAVE BEEN.
HEY, BUT JUST SO
THAT WE'RE CLEAR...
THE MOMENT I GET
ON THAT TRANSFER
CHOPPER,
MY FRIENDS HAVE ORDERS
TO KILL YOURS.
WE'LL SEE ABOUT THAT.
I THINK YOU'RE ABOUT
TO GET A PHONE CALL.
[EXHALES]
[CELL PHONE VIBRATES]
[VIBRATES]
HELLO?
HELLO.
SOMEBODY HELP ME.
PLEASE HELP ME.
PLEASE. PLEASE.
I NEED THE VAN.
SIR, WHAT
ARE YOU DOING? STOP.
[ALL GRUNTING]
[DARTS FIRING]
HE TOOK YOUR
SON, DIDN'T HE?
HOW DID YOU KNOW?
LIKE MINDS. HERE.
SOMETHING FUNNY, NUTBAG?
NOT YET BUT SOON.
[EXPLOSION]
SEE WHAT I MEAN?
[ARROWS FLYING]
THIS WOULD BE EASIER
IF WE COULD KILL THEM.
THEN IT'S NOT GONNA
BE EASY.
[MEN SHOUTING COMMANDS]
OFFICER: WE'RE COMPROMISED.
TAKE THE PRISONER OUT.
[EXPLOSION, GUNSHOTS]
-THEY'RE TARGETING CHASE.
-GO. I'LL COVER YOU.
REALLY.
HYAH! HYAH! HYAH!
CHASE!
THANKS FOR
THE ASSIST, PAL.
-WHERE IS MY SON?!
-NO, NO.
THAT WASN'T
THE DEAL, OLIVER.
THAT WASN'T THE DEAL.
I SAID, YOU LET ME GO
AND I'D KEEP
YOUR LOVED ONES SAFE,
BUT I'M NOT GONE YET.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
WHY DID YOU INVOLVE WILLIAM?
THAT'S MY BOY.
HE'S AN INNOCENT.
SO WAS MY WIFE, MAN,
BUT YOU
INVOLVED HER.
I ALREADY TOLD YOU,
OLIVER.
EVERYONE THAT YOU
CARE ABOUT SUFFERS.
EVERYONE.
I'LL SEE YOU
ON THE BOAT.
OK. CHASE'S
HELICOPTER FLEW TO
AN ABANDONED AIRFIELD
IN DAWN VALLEY, UTAH.
THEN 5 MINUTES LATER,
THIS AIRCRAFT TOOK OFF
FROM THE SAME FIELD
AT A VECTOR OF 2-7-0.
DUE WEST. THAT WOULD TAKE
HIM BACK TO STAR CITY.
CHASE SEEMS SMARTER
THAN THAT.
I'M TRYING TO TRACK
THIS PLANE,
BUT IT'S NOT EASY
WITHOUT FELICITY.
THE NIGHT BEFORE
THE UNDERTAKING,
SOME OF MY ASSOCIATES,
ESPECIALLY THOSE WHO WERE ON
THE WRONG END OF YOUR BOW,
THOUGHT THAT THE HOOD
HAD COMPUTER SKILLS.
I HAD GOOD HARDWARE
AND A SPECIFIC PURPOSE.
CHASE TURNED OFF
THE TRANSPONDER
ON THE PLANE.
LUCKILY,
FELICITY HAS ACCESS
TO A KEYHOLE SATELLITE
THAT CAN TRACK
THE HEAT SIGNATURE
OF ANY AIRCRAFT
IN THE WORLD.
-IMPRESSIVE.
-HAVE TO GET LUCKY.
[COMPUTER BEEPING]
ARE YOU EXPECTING SOMEONE?
YES, I AM, BECAUSE
CHASE IS WORKING
WITH AT LEAST
BLACK SIREN,
EVELYN SHARP,
TALIA AL GHUL,
AND WHATEVER ARMY SHE'S
CURRENTLY CONTROLLING.
SO YOU CALLED IN
REINFORCEMENTS.
IF I WASN'T SUCH
A CONFIDENT INDIVIDUAL,
MY EGO MIGHT BE BRUISED.
MALCOLM, YOUR EGO IS
WHAT I'M GONNA NEED YOU
TO KEEP IN CHECK.
WHY? WHO DID YOU
REACH OUT TO?
[DOORS OPEN AND SHUT]
HUSBAND.
MR. MERLYN. I ASSUME YOU
STILL HAVE NO TITLE.
-NO.
-MALCOLM.
-I WILL NOT WORK WITH HER.
-I TOLD YOU.
I'D SOONER SLICE
HER THROAT.
TRY TO, YOU MEAN.
MALCOLM, YOU SAID YOU
WERE WILLING TO DO
WHATEVER IT TAKES
TO GET THEA BACK.
SO HERE WE ARE!
FINE.
BUT DOES SHE KNOW?
KNOW WHAT, MR. MERLYN?
ONE OF THE PEOPLE WE
ARE UP AGAINST IS
YOUR SISTER.
[SIGHS]
NYSSA, I WANTED
TO EXPLAIN IT
TO YOU IN PERSON.
[COMPUTER BEEPING]
WE HAVE CHASE'S C-130.
FLEW OUT OVER THE COAST,
BANKED SOUTHERLY
12 DEGREES, WHICH...
WHICH MEANS...
WHAT DOES IT MEAN?
I KNOW WHERE HE'S
TAKING THEM.
WHY WOULD YOUR ADVERSARY
BRING THEM HERE?
FOR THAT MATTER, HOW DID HE
EVEN KNOW ABOUT THIS PLACE?
TALIA.
SHE RESEARCHED ME.
PROBABLY TOLD CHASE
EVERYTHING.
IRONIC.
WHEN I WAS A LITTLE GIRL,
MY FATHER TOLD ME
TO VISIT THIS PLACE.
IT'S WHERE I FOUND SARA.
FEMALE VOICE:
DON'T.
I'M SORRY
THAT I HAVE TO,
BUT IT'S BETTER
FOR EVERYONE.
THIS IS...THIS IS THE ONLY
WAY TO MAKE SURE...
THAT I D...I DON'T INFECT
EVERYONE THAT I LOVE.
BUT WE LOVE YOU IN
RETURN FOR IT, OLLIE.
AND WE NEED YOU AT HOME.
PLEASE COME HOME
TO ME, OLLIE...
TO THEA, YOUR MOTHER.
PLEASE. WE NEED YOU.
IF YOU DON'T, THEN YOUR
FATHER AND MY SISTER
WOULD HAVE DIED
FOR NOTHING.
[FIRES PISTOL]
[JOHN GRUNTING]
AGH!
CURTIS: DIGGLE?
FELICITY?
WE'RE OK. YOU OK?
QUENTIN: WE'RE FINE. A LITTLE
NORTH OF PISSED OFF, THOUGH.
RENE, DINAH.
WHERE ARE THEY?
NOT WITH US.
[BIRDS CALLING]
ADRIAN: RELAX.
ENJOY THE WEATHER.
[CHUCKLES]
MS. SMOAK.
ANYBODY
EVER TELL YOU
HOW MUCH YOU SUCK
AT LIFE?
NO. CARE
TO BE THE FIRST?
THEA: WHY ARE WE HERE?
SO YOU RECOGNIZE
THIS PLACE?
THAT'S GOOD.
OLIVER'S GONNA
COME FOR US.
YEAH, I'M COUNTING
ON IT, SIS.
DAMN IT.
CHASE IS USING US AS BAIT.
HE WANTS TO DRAW OLIVER OUT.
QUENTIN: THE NUMBERS
AREN'T EXACTLY
IN HIS FAVOR.
HE'S FACED WORSE ODDS
BEFORE.
YEAH, WITH THE HELP
OF YOU AND JOHN,
ROY AND LAUREL
AND THEA,
THE REST OF US.
CURTIS IS RIGHT. OLIVER
CAN'T DO THIS ALONE.
[EXHALES]
I NEED YOUR HELP.
HEY, KID.
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
I'M GLAD YOU CAME BACK.
MAN: GREG, MOVE YOUR HEAD.