My name is Oliver Queen.
After five years in hell,
I returned home with only one goal,
to save my city.
Today I fight that war on two fronts.
By day I lead Star City as its mayor.
But by night I'm someone else.
I am something else.
I am the Green Arrow.
Previously on Arrow and Flash...
You ran back in time, and then came back
and noticed that things were different?
Who's that young boy with Digg?
- He didn't have a kid before?
- Baby Sarah.
Baby John.
I used your gun.
No one will ever believe your story.
Police never caught
your brother's shooter.
You leave Andy out of this.
Floyd Lawton. He is the sniper.
I'll kill you for what you did to Andy.
I have space for you right here,
right next to your brother.
I can't do it alone. I need a team.
You're not just joining up
with the Green Arrow.
You'd be joining up with me.
- I'm in.
- Me too.
So, what're we looking at here?
Carl Roberto.
Frequent flyer at Iron Heights.
Seems like the only thing he's good at
is getting arrested.
He's not much of a challenge
for the Green Arrow.
He's not looking for a challenge.
This is about teaching the four of you
what happens out there
and how to handle it.
Well, I'm up for any lesson
that doesn't involve
him punching us in the face.
Wait. He hits you guys?
Oh, man, dude's gonna get it now.
Always assume that the target's armed.
Always assume that they're dangerous.
Stardust.
Who's "Stardust"?
It's not a "who", it's a "what."
Latest designer drug.
Makes PCP look like children's aspirin.
I want your supplier.
I can't, he'll kill me.
What do you think I'm going to do?
His interrogation technique
is a little unrefined.
He's not going to kill him, is he?
That's a terrific question.
You're not gonna do it.
Give me a name and I won't have to.
Word's out on you, man.
You Kill, but only when you have to.
Son of a bitch!
Oh, don't worry. You'll live.
All right. All right!
His name's Sampson. Derek Sampson.
Where can I find him?
I don't know. I pick up a package
on a different corner each night.
- And never from him.
- Give me the package.
The Stardust? Sure. It's in my pocket.
Good idea.
You really could use a high,
chill out a bit.
I am not gonna Kill you.
But I can't guarantee
you'll walk away from this.
So, what did we learn?
- Don't piss Oliver off.
- Like we needed that lesson.
Information.
Okay. It's the currency of our business.
When Oliver gets back here,
he's gonna ask me to analyze the drugs,
so we can find out
where it's being manufactured.
I hate drugs.
Not in a recreational sense. I have a life
like anyone else. It's just...
I saw what all the gang violence
did to my hometown.
Um...
I'm gonna make DVDs
of tonight's surveillance footage.
Oliver wants you to study them
like a football player
would break down a game tape.
And then he'll let us
get out on the field?
I'm guessing not.
That guy is seriously overestimating
my patience...
I am.
Because I didn't think that
you had any patience, Rene.
Cute.
Let's analyze this, see if we can
figure out where it's manufactured.
Look, analysis and forensics is
cool and all, but that stuff takes time.
I know the neighborhood where this dealer
is slinging out of.
I think I can guess
where the Stardust is being made.
Rene, we don't deal
in maybes and guesswork.
Or maybe rich boy Mayor Queen
doesn't know the streets so good.
Everyone get back to your training.
You impress me in here, then maybe
I'll let you impress me out there.
Text me when the analysis comes back.
B and E in a shipping center,
on 8th and Amsterdam.
Gunmen armed with an AR15.
I give up.
Detective Billy Malone.
Please don't shoot me.
Sorry about the fake radio call,
but I didn't have your e-mail address
and I thought we should meet.
- Whoa. Okay.
- What do you want?
I discovered some intel
that I think concerns you.
I caught the Conahan murderer.
He was a member of Mayor Queen's...
Anti-Crime Unit. Killed two weeks ago.
By a guy who's somewhat promiscuous
with his choice of weapons.
Apparently, he threatened someone else
you might be familiar with, Tobias Church.
What was his problem with Church?
According to the word on the street,
Church nearly killed you last week.
Well, this guy
wants to do the job himself.
Johnny...
- They tell you what happened?
- Just the charges.
Espionage, murder, conduct unbecoming.
I need you to tell me what happened.
And I need you to start at the beginning.
We were in Chechnya,
on an op to retrieve a trigger
from one of Damien Darhk's nukes.
Turns out,
my C.O. had a better plan for it,
sell it to the highest bidder.
Something went sideways, Lyla.
The buyer didn't show. I don't know.
I don't know.
I think pinning it on me
was the backup plan.
It's time.
You believe me, right?
Johnny, how can you even ask that?
Lyla, I love you.
Tell John Jr. I love him
and it'll be all right.
Hey, get me out of here.
You can't leave me here with him.
Hey, John.
Looks like we're cellmates again.
Ain't that something?
Your Honor, we need to talk.
Where'd you go last night?
I looked around the theater
after the movie and I couldn't find you.
Mr. Mayor, we need to
take your security detail more seriously.
I was serious when I said
that I didn't want a security detail.
And look where that got me.
Late for a meeting.
What're you doing here?
You're not supposed to be here till 9:00.
Our meeting was scheduled for 8:00.
Exactly.
What? Who's this?
This is Susan Williams,
and she's officially
my least favorite person on the planet.
It's not just that Oliver Queen's pick
for Deputy Mayor
has a history of alcohol abuse.
Recent reports confirm that Quentin Lance
suffered a relapse right before
Mayor Queen appointed him.
I told you not to offer Quentin a job
in the administration
and you decide to offer him Deputy Mayor?
Okay, see, that's what
those five voicemails were about.
The thing that I told you not to do.
I listened to what you told me not to do,
but then I decided to do
what I thought was right.
Anyway, and guess who I got that one from?
I'm an elected official.
I have to answer to voters
and a free press.
Unravel this, Speedy. Make it go away.
That's gonna be a little hard to do
now that the story is already out there.
I don't care.
You made this mess, you to clean it up.
Some nights, I still feel the sea.
Rocking, rocking. Oh.
In that cage.
- On that boat, The Amazo, you remember?
- Yeah.
Then I wake up, I realize where I am.
With family, with friends.
You are only one who knows
what I went through. That nightmare...
Here. I brought you something to drink.
No. No, I can't.
Not vodka. It's water.
How you feel, my friend?
Like I might have made a mistake.
But what of Kovar?
You still wish to kill him, no?
I tell you before, Bratva only way.
I think I'll take my chances.
This is about other men being killed?
That was first test. Two more left.
What was the point of the test?
To trust Bratva.
Well, I'm sorry, Anatoly,
but I don't trust Bratva
after I watched them
execute three innocent men.
Ah!
Mmm.
There is miscommunication.
You want to leave, leave.
But come with me first.
I have something I need to show you.
I cannot believe
I let you talk me into this.
Yeah, I'm a little surprised, too.
But it's just recon.
If this is just recon,
then how come
we didn't bring along Rory and Curtis?
'Cause Curtis would just tell
Mommy and Daddy.
And Rory?
Guy just weirds me out.
Ready?
Knew this'd be the place.
When's Queen gonna trust me?
I'm sure it'll be right after he finds out
we went here without his permission.
Night's still young.
Bring the Green Arrow back
and bust this place up.
You mean he will bust this place up.
He'll never let us get out in that field.
It's easier to ask for forgiveness
than permission.
You brought that?
What happened to this just being recon?
We did the recon part.
Mrs. Conahan,
this person will be apprehended.
I have the Anti-Crime Unit
working overtime on this.
Trust me,
we will get justice for your husband.
Thought that was my job.
Goodbye.
I'm sorry, you are?
Pissed. Royally. Off.
I'm getting that.
What I don't understand is who you are
and what you're doing in my office.
Adrian Chase. Your new...
District Attorney.
I'm sorry that we haven't met.
I'm buried up to my eyeballs
in motion practice and indictments
with a staff who's barely made it past
three rounds of budget cuts,
so how about we save the pleasantries
for the next fundraiser
- and get down to why I'm so...
- You're so pissed off?
Royally. Remember Vertigo?
Believe it or not,
I tried to buy some once.
Yeah, I believe it.
Well, what's hitting the street
is a million times worse.
"Stardust." I'm not as out of touch
as most people think.
But I do have some work to get done,
Mr. Chase.
So why don't we get to the bottom of why
you're so pissed off.
I've been building a case
against the dealer, Derek Sampson.
I was going to flip him,
but last night, somebody killed him.
- Rival dealer?
- A vigilante.
That doesn't sound like the Green Arrow.
Not him. Some idiot in a hockey mask.
I'm sorry. Did you say hockey mask?
Everything okay, boss?
A Stardust dealer was killed last night
by a vigilante!
Lots running around the city...
- Wearing a hockey mask.
- Hey, short fry was there too.
Thanks, Rene.
Rory and I didn't, though!
Just for the record.
Okay, I ain't gonna deny I was there,
but neither were you, man.
This guy was all sorts of nutso, loco.
It was either him or me.
You never should have been
in that position.
So, you're saying,
this city isn't better off
with one less dealer on the streets?
Have you told the mayor that?
You have no ability to think big picture.
Stardust is still out there.
The DA's office had a plan,
they were going to flip Sampson,
and then he was gonna give up
the suppliers.
They can't do that anymore.
How about you put an arrow in my other leg
and we'll call it even?
Last week, you said
you needed to be able to trust me.
Fine.
Well, I need to be able to trust you.
If I can't,
then why am I wasting my time with you?
Never in my entire life,
did I think that I was gonna meet somebody
more stubborn than him.
I would've lost that bet.
Is this normal behavior around here?
More than I'd like to admit.
Sorry, my friend's visiting
from Marseille.
No problem, Miss Williams.
I really appreciate you taking the time
to meet with me.
Anything for a fan.
I'm assuming you watched
the other night's broadcast.
Yes, actually, I...
I really appreciated
all the wonderful things you were saying
about my brother's administration.
Uh...
- Can you give us a minute?
- Mmm-hmm.
You're right. I was out of line.
My producer,
he's always pushing me to be "edgy,"
to do stories
that'll generate Internet traffic.
Sometimes I push too far.
Well, thank you.
I really appreciate that.
Of course.
I mean, we're coworkers, in a way.
Um, "co-worker to co-worker,"
I was hoping you'd do me a favor.
I need you to walk back your story.
The truth is, Oliver hasn't appointed
Quentin Lance, Deputy Mayor yet.
- That's not what my sources tell me.
- Well, they're wrong.
Because honestly,
my brother doesn't even know
that I offered him the job.
- Well, that certainly changes things.
- Yeah.
- I'll update the story.
- Really?
Co-workers, right?
How the hell are you alive?
Great question. But you know the answer.
They never found your body.
A hell of a world we live in, ain't it?
I survive a freaking building
exploding under me
only to get pinched a couple months later.
And it is hard going on the I am
with an eye-patch.
What's your excuse for being here?
I re-enlisted back into the Army.
Didn't go good.
Can't really picture you ever giving up
your day job as a superhero.
- I just couldn't do it anymore.
- Why's that?
I'm not here
to play 20 questions with you, Lawton.
All right.
How about we play cards?
Deceased male. Late twenties.
Six feet two inches, 214 pounds.
Found in a body of unknown chemicals.
Based on the lack of epidermis erosion,
the chemicals were non-acidic.
Autopsy was commenced at 18:25
with a Y-incision.
Why can't I feel anything?
Good night. I'm headed home.
Give me a sec, I'll join you.
Not home, I mean.
Bow! I'm a happily married man. Happy.
I meant join you out.
I figured. Besides, you're not my type.
- Are you gay?
- No.
Which makes you not my type.
Of course, yeah, I was...
Yeah, speaking of which, uh,
you were talking about home.
Hometown, are you not from Star City?
No. Havenrock.
Havenrock.
You know, I just realized that I...
I remembered, that I...
Oh, yeah, I promised Felicity
I would help her with some things.
- Yeah. No problem. Good night.
- Night.
Good night, Felicity.
Night.
Yes?
You knew, didn't you?
About Havenrock?
He told Oliver. I overheard.
Does he know? Rory, I mean.
Know that I destroyed his hometown
with a nuclear missile five months ago?
No. It hasn't come up.
You didn't destroy anything, Felicity.
That was Damien Darhk.
Darhk sent the missile to Monument Point.
I sent the missile to Havenrock.
I killed tens of thousands of people.
To save millions.
Tell that to Rory's family.
What is that?
911, from Starling General.
Where the hell are the cops?
We need backup!
Get out of here.
Derek Sampson, you have failed this city.
Hey, Rory, thanks for coming back.
Oliver should be here any second.
- What happened?
- Well, first meta-humans. Then magic.
And now you can add into the mix, zombies.
The guy that Rene killed
is kind of still walking around.
Sampson is not a zombie.
According to the coroner's
toxicology workup,
Sampson's body was infused
with a mixture of chemicals
that must have put his body into a state
that fooled the paramedics.
It was a matter of time before he woke up.
And kicked Oliver's ass.
He didn't kick Oliver's ass.
And can we please not say things like that
when Oliver could enter in,
like, any second.
Like, now, see?
We need to find this guy
before he hurts anyone else.
I'm tapped into all satellites
and CC feeds.
What happened?
Physiology changed. Enhanced strength.
And I don't think he can feel pain.
Felicity thinks it's from exposure
to whatever chemicals were in the vat
that Rene dumped him into.
- Any way to reverse it?
- I could run some tests.
But it would take time
and I'd rather keep my eye on the
"find Sampson
before he hurts anyone else" ball.
Well, good thing
I was a biochemistry major in college.
I'll get on it.
Text me as soon as you have anything.
We can't let the cops get to him first.
I want to help too.
I think you've done enough.
I'm sorry about before. But I get it now.
I'll do whatever you need.
What I need is to trust
that when I do ask for your help,
you're not, immediately, gonna
make the problem worse.
He said he was sorry. Let us help.
Yeah. We could canvas the city.
After what happened the last time
you went out looking for Sampson? Pass.
The recruit was a murderer?
Yeah. Police catch him
but he is son to friend of Kovar,
so he goes free.
Bratva step in to bring justice.
How is recruiting him
into the Bratva justice?
But he was not recruited, was he?
What if I wasn't the one
to ring the bell, Anatoly?
We still bring justice.
If you're trying to convince me
to trust the Bratva,
you're not doing a very good job.
You must trust process.
Not everything what it seems.
To defeat Kovar, you need army.
Bratva army.
You come this far. Why give up now?
Six of hearts?
Come on, six of hearts, where are you?
My kingdom for a six of hearts.
Will you shut up for five minutes
and I won't have to kill you?
Whoo! There's that temper.
Good thing your kid won't have to grow up
with it like your brother did, huh?
What'd you say to me?
How's all that going, anyway?
You ever find that group
that paid me to off him?
They didn't.
What's that now?
They didn't want him dead.
He was alive.
Like I said, hell of a world, ain't it?
I mean...
Wait, why did you say was alive, just now?
Huh?
Hello? John? Anybody home?
Because I killed him.
So all that hate that you poured into me
for killing your brother,
you really should've been
pouring into yourself.
I was just on my way to see you.
What can I help you with?
SCPD's working on locating Sampson.
I want to start with a search
of his last known address,
but Judge Pittson
won't sign the search warrant
for Sampson's prior residence.
I helped get Pittson elected.
Which is why I'm talking to you.
Could you lean on her?
- Absolutely. All hands on deck.
- Thank you.
Hey, you, uh...
You probably don't remember this,
but we actually met 12 years ago.
You tried to pick up my girlfriend.
I did a lot of things back then
that I'm not especially proud of,
but I'm sure she ended up
with the better man.
Hell, no. She went home with you.
It's okay. I don't hold grudges.
Looks like your Chief of Staff
needs a minute.
Let me know when you talk to Pittson.
I appreciate it.
Of course.
How'd it go with that reporter?
Well, I thought it went well.
Thought?
Unfortunately, Mayor Queen
doesn't seem to have the first clue
of what's going on
within his own administration.
For those of you who may recall...
- I'm so sorry.
- What did you say to this woman?
That...
That part's coming next.
Chosen
may be too strong of a word.
Not only was a disgraced public official
re-hired by the city,
in an even higher position,
but Mayor Queen wasn't even aware of it.
The decision was made by his sister.
Okay, look,
I am going to issue a statement
taking full responsibility for this, okay?
And, then I am going to offer you
my letter of resignation.
- Thea, that...
- No, Ollie, look,
you said it yourself.
I made this mess.
I'm gonna go clean it up.
You know, it's only a matter of time
before Rory figures it out.
What?
The "you and Havenrock" connection.
I mean, you can't seem to be around
the guy for more than two minutes
without acting widgy.
And sooner or later, he's gonna ask why.
Well, I will take the "later." Thank you.
Have you talked this out with Oliver?
No. Oliver and I don't have
that type of relationship anymore.
And you're right. I am acting "widgy."
Because having him on the team
is like having a constant reminder
about what I did.
So clear the air.
Look, if the past four years
have taught you anything,
it should be that keeping secrets
never works out.
I hardly even know Rory.
And what I do know about him
is that he has
several-thousand-year-old rags
that he can mystically use to strangle me.
He must be great at parties.
Look, I think that you need to just
trust the fact that he will not kill you.
And trust that he may be able
to see things clearer than you do
and know that this wasn't your fault.
Whoever called this meeting,
you best step up.
The text I got came from Sampson's cell.
Sampson is dead.
What'd Mark Twain say?
"Reports of my death
have been greatly exaggerated."
Man, he wasn't kidding.
Righteous. So we're back in business?
Stardust? No. I'm thinking bigger.
You go bigger,
you draw attention from Tobias Church.
I'm not afraid of Church no more.
He should be afraid of me.
Ever see Lethal Weapon? My favorite scene.
Gary Busey, man. That guy, he could act.
If you can't feel pain,
you can't be stopped.
So we all get this treatment
and we take back this city
from Tobias Church.
I didn't know you were still here.
Oh!
That looks painful.
It's par for the course.
How'd things go at City Hall?
- Oh. That bad, huh?
- Channel 52.
Unfortunately, Mayor Queen
doesn't seem to have the first clue
of what's going on
within his own administration...
I already don't like her.
I can't keep my people in line.
As mayor or as Green Arrow.
"Heavy is the head that wears the crown."
Shakespeare. Or Tupac.
So this is Green Arrow brooding
or Mayor brooding?
What's happening with Susan Williams
is just politics.
Arrow brooding. That's excellent.
'Cause I have more experience with that.
Rene didn't listen to what I said.
And he created a superhuman.
Well, I used to have a dog.
Lucky. Adorable, but peed on everything.
A trainer told me that
next time it happened,
that I should roll up a piece of newspaper
and smack myself on the head.
Because it was my fault.
Lucky was just doing as dogs do.
You're pushing this "Wild Dog" codename
thing a bit too far.
My point is, when you're in charge
everything your team does is on you.
Even what Rene did?
He was right about being able to locate
Sampson's operation.
If you listened to him
instead of shutting him down...
Right, then none of this
would've happened.
And we both know why you shut him down.
Because I don't trust him.
Like you said, if you don't...
If you won't,
why are you wasting your time?
What's that?
I'm running an algorithm,
pings in case anything unusual happens.
"Unusual"?
That's casting a pretty wide net.
Well, all my other nets
are coming up empty.
Break-in at Allman Industrial.
That could be anyone.
Well, do you know anyone besides Sampson
who could get shot by security guards
and just shrug off the bullets?
What'd he steal?
Don't know. This is gonna take
a lot of time and typing.
Their warehouse
is the size of three football fields.
- Let me know what you find out.
- Okay.
Wait, wait. Where are you going?
To get the team.
I ran Walker through every database.
Initially he came up clean, but
there are some financial irregularities.
I want you to stop.
What?
Stop digging.
I'm not gonna fight these charges.
Johnny, that's insane!
Actually, it's the first thing
that's made sense to me in a long while.
- Ever since I killed Andy...
- You think you need to be punished.
I know I do.
Lyla.
I didn't have to pull that trigger,
but I did.
Something's wrong with me, baby.
Then let me help you.
We will figure this out together.
When I thought Lawton killed Andy,
all wanted to do
was bring his murderer to justice.
I still do.
Floyd Lawton was an assassin for hire.
You're a good man. And you're alive.
Floyd Lawton is long dead.
No, Lyla, he's not. He's...
Johnny?
Stop fighting for me, Lyla.
I have.
You ain't gonna get me this time.
I've won eight in a row.
Are you sure you were an Olympian?
Having quick reflexes is not
the only quality in an Olympian. Okay?
There are other things.
Like determination. And stubbornness.
I guess a sense of fashion
isn't one of them.
Come on, man,
where did you get that jacket?
It's retro in all the wrong ways.
Wait, you don't know "Fair Play",
Terry Sloane?
Terry Sloane, Mr. Terrific?
The greatest wrestler
in the history of wrestling.
He was so good that he wore an outfit
with the words "Fair Play"
written across it.
Like I'm so good
I don't even need to cheat to beat you.
He was kind of my idol.
Did you have a little crush on him too?
Hey, that's beside the point.
- Something on your mind, boss?
- You've a good natural form.
'Cause it's not natural.
I've been working on it for years.
Rene, if I've been too hard on you,
it's because I want to make sure
you're taking this as seriously as I am.
Wouldn't be here
if I wasn't taking it seriously.
You were right about Sampson's operation.
You've have a knack for this
and I should've trusted you.
Whoa.
- That almost sounded like an apology.
- I'm still learning, too.
All right, well, before you guys
hug it out, you should really see this.
Found out what Sampson stole
from Allman Industrial.
- A molecular transmodality processor.
- What?
It replicates chemicals
based on their molecular structure.
What would Sampson need with that?
- The vat you dropped him in...
- It was full of Stardust.
But when we were fighting, a pipe burst
and some liquid drained from it
into the vat.
Sounds like you stumbled on the recipe
for making a superhuman killing machine.
And now he's gonna use the...
- Molecular transmodality processor.
- To make more of them.
And he'll need the original mixture,
which means that he'll return to... Oh!
I've always wanted to say this,
"The scene of the crime."
If Sampson is building an army
then I'm going to need mine.
- For real?
- For real.
Suit up! Oh.
I thought we were all going, like,
it was going to be a nice moment
where we all said it the same time.
Is that just your thing?
That's you, only? Okay, yeah.
That's you, that's just him,
for the record, for everybody.
This area's closed off, pal. Crime scene.
Yeah. I know.
Move in.
Y'all gonna be fearless.
Painless.
Unstoppable.
Let's do this.
In position. Ten seconds.
Make sure to activate the pressure sensor
before the detonation.
So the spark ignites the entirety
of the pipeline, yeah, I know.
Now let me concentrate.
Why're you smiling, dirtbag?
You are a freaky kind of scary.
It's the whispers, right?
It just does that. I have no idea how.
New mask looks cool, by the way.
Well, thank you. Actually,
still feels a little weird on my face.
I think you dropped this, Mr. Fair Play.
Thank you. Okay.
Thought we've been over this.
You can't hurt me.
Just because you can't feel your tendons
being sliced,
doesn't mean you don't need them.
Too bad my guys still have you surrounded.
No. I trust that
my guys took care of them.
Okay, Curtis. Kaboom time.
Where exactly are we going?
Did the people who built this elevator
know your secret, too?
You know, I've been meaning to ask.
What kind of vigilante
wears a hockey mask?
I think it's cool.
Okay, everyone, uh,
just breathe normally.
I know it's a lot to take in, so...
He fainted the first time he saw it.
I had the flu. I had the flu, ya'll.
So this is the cave... I like to call it
the Arrow Cave. It's Oliver-esque.
Bratva. Do you know what this word means?
Brotherhood.
If you are hungry,
brothers will feed you.
If you are hurt, brothers
bring 10 times pain to men responsible.
If one brother succeeds,
all brothers are rich.
If one brother fails, all brothers suffer.
Your brothers would kill for you,
would die for you.
As you would kill and die for them.
If these men
are supposed to be my brothers,
why would I fight them?
These men are not here to fight you.
Most of these men in this room
have tried to kill me.
And with these knives, they could.
But, you must trust they will not.
Do you trust your brothers?
I trust my brothers.
Take off jacket, turn around.
Sorry. I keep on seeming
to interrupt you two.
Don't be. I was just telling the Mayor
that Derek Sampson was apprehended.
- By the SCPD?
- No.
Based on forensics, the Green Arrow
is either as fast as The Flash
or he's got a new team behind him.
This city never seems
to get easier, does it?
Well, as promised, I will stay on
until you can find a more qualified
and experienced replacement.
I don't want experience.
I want someone that I can trust, Speedy,
and that person is you.
I messed up, Ollie. Big time.
No, Thea. You didn't. Follow me.
Thank you all for coming.
I would like to address, head-on
and with brutal honesty,
some of the recent reports
regarding my administration.
Reports that suggest
that while the voters may have elected me,
others have been making decisions
in my stead.
The truth of the matter is
that every decision
made by any member of my administration,
is my decision.
The buck, as they say, stops with me.
Because when you're in charge,
everything that your team does is on you.
And I trust my team.
That team
will include former Police Captain,
Quentin Lance.
Who'll be serving beside me
as Deputy Mayor.
Appreciate the vote of confidence,
Mr. Mayor.
You're the right man for the job.
Trust me.
Susan. A word?
Thea, I'm so sorry.
You must think
I'm the worst kind of person.
No, I actually already know that's true.
Thea, let me...
Explain? Lie?
No, I'm just gonna
save us both the trouble.
I already know exactly what happened.
You played me.
You only get to do that once.
And the next time
you try to cross me like that,
you'll be lucky if you even have a blog.
Never gets old.
Paul! I was just about to call you.
I'm on my way home from work now.
No, I never said that.
Well, traffic was crazy.
So, if Curtis is married, what's the rule
on dating while vigilanting?
Uh... One sec. The short answer is don't.
Rory, wait up, can I talk to you?
- Everything okay?
- Yeah.
No.
There's something that I need you to know
about Havenrock.
Havenrock was not the intended target.
Monument Point was.
Someone redirected the missile
to reduce the number of casualties.
That someone was me.
I am so sorry.
Oliver.
Lyla.
We need to talk about John.
- Is he all right?
- No.
He's back in the country.
And he's in prison.
And I need you to break him out.
English - SDH