[Oliver] My name is Oliver Queen.
After five years in hell,
I returned home with only one goal,
to save my city.
Today, I fight that war on two fronts.
By day, I lead Star City as its mayor.
But by night, I'm someone else.
I am something else.
I am the Green Arrow.
[Oliver]Previously onArrow...
Promise me that you'll be his father.
I promise.
William blames me for Samantha's death.
Now, you don't have to like me.
I'm your dad.
I'm gonna be there for you,
whether you want me to be or not.
[groans]
[John]Curtis and Lance took Rene
to Dr. Schwartz for treatment.
Saw you take the shot at that merc,
never seen you miss.
Turn on Channel 52, right now.
[newsreader]
This photo provides unequivocal proof
of the identity of the vigilante
known as the Green Arrow.
What are we gonna do?
I don't know.
[Oliver] Anything interesting
on the news last night?
[reporter 1] Can you comment
on the photo released last night?
[reporter 2] How do you feel about
the accusation of being the Green Arrow?
[Oliver] Ladies and gentlemen.
Ladies and gentlemen, please.
If you wanna know what I have to say,
it would probably help
if you could hear me.
Thank you.
I'm gonna tell you two things,
both of which you probably already know.
First, this is important,
I am not the Green Arrow.
[reporter] If you're not the Green Arrow,
then who is?
Number two,
photos can be doctored.
They could've put
Bruce Wayne's head on that body.
Has Bruce Wayne left Gotham
to hangout in Star City recently?
No.
Now, if I was running around the city
during the day, and managing it as mayor,
while running around at night
fighting criminals as a vigilante,
that really would make me a superhero.
But I'm not, I'm just the mayor.
Thank you very much.
[reporters clamoring]
[Quentin] You seem to be
taking this in your stride.
I've been here before with you.
Yeah, but I didn't have a photograph
of you in flagrante de Arrow.
-Where did Channel 52 get the photo?
-Anonymous source.
Arrived in yesterday's mail.
No return address.
Get the envelope,
let's get it to forensics,
and let's figure out who leaked it.
And why.
We can't let this distract us.
Where are we with rebuilding SCPD?
Well, I fast-tracked the insurance claim.
So, we should have 20 million
burning a hole
in our account by the end of the day.
Our account?
I figure we peel off
a few bucks and fly off to Vegas.
[Quentin laughs] That's cute.
I think it might be a little suspicious
if Oliver left town right about now.
I need to be in town
for the Markovian delegation.
So, it's all right for me to go
to Vegas, is what you're saying?
[Oliver] Hello?
I don't think you have an appointment.
No, but I really don't need one.
Special Agent Samanda Watson.
Uh, can we help you with something?
Not really. I'm here as a courtesy,
to inform you of the investigation
I'll be conducting in your city.
Investigation into what?
You.
[scoffs] You gotta be kidding.
Yeah, because the FBI is
world-renowned for its sense of humor.
[sighs]
You were on the news last night
wearing the outfit of a known criminal.
Can you honestly say you're surprised
there's an investigation?
No, but I wasn't expecting the FBI.
Well, quite frankly,
the local law enforcement
has proven ineffective
where the Green Arrow is concerned.
Agent Watson?
-Yes.
-I was cleared five years ago.
Of being The Hood, not the Green Arrow.
And you were cleared by the guy
who's now your deputy mayor.
Would like me to send you a copy of
the polygraph that Mr. Queen passed?
For starters.
The local AG will be issuing
subpoenas later on today.
It was nice meeting you, gentlemen.
I'm sure we'll be seeing
a lot more of each other.
At least they caught his good side.
Sorry, not funny.
All right, John said
you guys have experience
putting this particular genie
back in the bottle.
Well, yeah, I mean,
John's put on the hood on before,
but I don't see how that's gonna work now,
not with photographic evidence.
What about the human target?
The human what-now?
Best cosplayer ever.
He can literally make himself
look like someone else.
Yeah, Chance is out of the country
right now, only God knows where.
We have to think of a new way
of getting out of this.
And if we can't?
Because assuming Oliver
does not go to prison,
he's not gonna be able to do anything
with a million eyes on him.
Not to mention that if he's outed...
Rather if he stays outed,
it won't be much of a leap
to the rest of us.
-One step at a time.
-[Felicity] Okay.
First step being, figuring out
where this picture came from.
[keyboard clacking]
It came from nowhere.
What do you mean?
I mean, this envelope wasn't
mailed, delivered or sent.
It came from inside
the Channel 52 news offices.
-How do we know that?
-Barcode.
Channel 52 uses it for internal traffic.
How many people work there?
-Five-hundred and sixty-eight.
-[Oliver sighs]
I'm just gonna say it to say it,
what if this was Chase?
He could've put this in motion
months ago, a little parting gift.
Seems like his style
messing with you like this.
[sighs] It is more than possible.
How's your boy holding up with all this?
Okay. I wanted to keep him home from
school, but he insisted on going.
-Like his father, huh?
-I wasn't much of a student.
I mean, he's tough.
[door opens]
[Curtis] Where's he standing?
If we can figure out
when and where this was taken,
it could give us something to go on.
I wrote an image analysis algorithm,
but there's just not very much
for the computer to chew on.
Was the original photo taken digitally,
or was it taken the old-fashioned way?
Digital. Printed on standard inkjet stock.
-Hmm.
-Okay, maybe if we can get the file,
there may be metadata on it and
we can figure out who took the photo.
That's a pretty epic maybe.
Yeah, well, like you said,
if we don't figure this out and fast,
we're screwed.
-I did say that, didn't I?
-Yeah, you did.
This could destroy our whole lives.
It's hard to think that, before,
my biggest worry was
getting a new job, and now...
It's about whether or not
we'll end up in jail.
I thought you were sitting pretty
from your Palmer Tech severance.
Yeah, from like a year ago.
What are you gonna do?
Assuming that we're all not in jail.
I mean, I'd definitely
rather go to Iron Heights
than work at Tech Village again.
That place was horrendous.
What about you? I mean, you've been
out of a job as long as I have.
Not really. I've been doing some
freelance coding in my spare time.
[stammering] What? What spare time?
Yeah, tell me about it.
Barely any, but I did not take a dime
from Paul in the divorce,
and a man's gotta eat.
You just got a secret job this whole
time you didn't tell anyone about?
I thought we all, like,
had, like, secret jobs.
-No.
-Except for John maybe.
What does he do for money?
That's something
that's been perplexing me.
Well, he's married
to the director of A.R.G.U.S.
Ah. Yeah, that's right.
She does make a lot of money.
[Oliver] This building has been vacant
since being claimed by the city
under eminent domain four years ago.
[reporter] Do you have any comment on
the FBI investigating you
on murder charges?
[Oliver] We're not gonna talk about that.
[Quentin] Except to say
it's a load of crap.
By offering subsidized leasing to
Markovia's Vortex Industries,
they're gonna be able to create
a high-tech factory here,
bringing, at the very least,
800 new jobs to Star City.
Can you shed light on
the accusation of being the Green Arrow?
You have said you're not
the Green Arrow, then who is?
-Why are you being...
-[Oliver] Guys, enough!
If we're not here
to discuss the Markovian initiative,
then you can just get back on the bus,
because I will not, for the last time,
be answering questions on the Green Arrow.
But I'd be happy to.
Alec Tarkov. I'm the Vortex CEO.
And if your mayor is truly a superhero,
which seems ludicrous...
Thank you.
We will double our investment.
A safe city is a good place
to do business, no?
Well, I'm sorry
to disappoint you, Mr. Tarkov,
but not even my son considers me
much of a superhero.
[gunshots]
-Get down! Go for cover!
-[crowd clamoring]
Get to the van! Go! Come on!
Get up. Go!
-[grunts]
-Get to the van! Go! Come on!
[grunts]
[gunshots]
Go, go, go!
Hurry up!
Go on. Hit it. Go!
[all exclaiming]
[tires squealing]
All right, hold on! Hold on!
[Quentin groans]
-[panting]
-[groans]
Is everyone okay?
Hello, Mr. Mayor.
Hope you are having pleasant day.
You look like maybe you want
to throw a punch at me.
Don't worry. We are not here for you.
We have business
with our Markovian cousins.
These are legitimate businessmen.
I never said my business
was not legitimate.
Unless, you know something
maybe a mayor should not know?
[speaking Russian]
We'll be in touch.
[men grunting]
[men shouting indistinctly]
Are you okay?
My best friend is under a microscope
by everyone in this city and the FBI.
So he couldn't stop the Bratva
from taking hostages.
So, let's just assume I'm not.
I wasn't talking about
what's going on with Oliver.
Dinah, I'm fine.
The only thing that's really bothering me,
is you being up in my business.
[door opens]
Hey, we came as soon as we heard.
We need to know why
Anatoly took the Markovians
and we need to find him now.
Oliver, Felicity and Curtis are on this,
but you need to stay here.
Look, I know I said before
Chase could be behind this,
-but now I'm thinking...
-It's Anatoly.
He leaked the photo to tie my hands.
We're on this. We'll take care of it.
-SQL or Java?
-What?
In your job, as a secret programmer.
Are you coding in SQL or Java?
Both. Plus, a little SWIFT.
I can't believe you've had
a secret job this whole time
and you didn't even tell me about it.
Is this relevant to locating
the Bratva and/or their hostages?
I am multitasking. Thank you very much.
And yes, if you must know,
I am running my image analysis
algorithm on the photo of Oliver.
What, get something?
[Felicity] Just my algorithm
crapping out again.
Don't despair.
I think I might have a line
on our friend Anatoly.
Now, working on the assumption
that he hasn't been in town that long,
I wondered how he was fixed for cash.
I bet his Bratva buddies
are good for it, no?
Well, he has to pay them somehow.
Cash would set off too many alarm bells,
plus he'd have to convert it from Rubles.
Credit cards are way too
easy to track. But then there's...
Crypto-currency is virtually
impossible to track.
For mere mortals.
But we're Mr. Terrific and Overwatch.
Overwatch and Mr. Terrific.
[chuckles]
No, I can assure you.
-We're doing everything...
-We haven't determined the motive
-to the kidnapping.
-...to recover the hostages back.
But the police are working
around the clock.
-All right?
-Thank you, Minister.
Yes, that's right.
We'll be in touch. Thank you.
The Markovian consulate
is losing their minds.
It's the same with the Vortex home office.
They wanna send private security
to get their people back.
I told them we've got it handled, but...
It felt like you were lying?
Where are we with the SCPD?
Dinah's got people rounding up
every Russian thug with a record,
but they're shorthanded down there.
[knock on door]
We got a new problem. [coughs]
[newsreader]
We received an anonymous message
from the group claiming
responsibility for today's abduction
of the contingent of
executives from Markovia.
In what can only be a small consolation,
the mayor and the reporters
at the delegation
-were not among the kidnapped.
-Lady's getting a lot of
anonymous messages these days.
[newsreader]As for what exactly
this group wants,
they said they will
execute the hostages in 12 hours
unless the city pays them
a ransom of $20 million.
Mayor Queen could not be reached
for comment.
-Rene.
-In related...
My comment is
we don't negotiate with terrorists.
Yeah, but if we did, we've got $20 million
from the reconstruction
of the police department.
It's funny, that's the exact number
your buddy Anatoly chose.
I don't care what number he chose.
We're not paying him 20 cents.
[cell phone vibrating]
Yeah.
This is he.
Is he okay?
No, of course. Of course.
I have to go.
Wanna tell me what happened?
No.
Did you see who hit you?
Your teacher was saying
it could've been a couple of kids.
Buddy, I can't help you if you don't...
They know you're the Green Arrow.
-What?
-They said you're the Green Arrow.
They said you're not here to help me.
Oh, man. Look...
-William, I'm really sorry...
-They were really big.
Eighth graders.
Eighth graders, huh?
You should go for the nose.
What?
If something like this happens again,
go for the nose.
Find the biggest one,
the biggest one in the group.
Walk right up to him
without saying a thing
and punch him the nose
as hard as you possibly can.
He will have no idea what is going on.
He won't be able to see.
If he can't see, he can't fight.
And all his buddies, all the guys
that were being so brave,
-they will back off.
-[cell phone vibrating]
Trust me on that one.
-But what if...
-Hang on.
-Yeah.
-[Felicity] It's me, hang on a second.
[crackling]
-What was that?
-I had to secure the line.
Curtis and I found Anatoly.
Russian restaurant owned
by a dummy corporation.
Thermal satellite reads
four bodies in an industrial cooler.
Must be the hostages.
That's what we're thinking.
Text me the address. I'll be there soon.
Stop the car please.
-What are you...
-I gotta get out.
Listen, [clears throat]
the driver and security,
they're gonna make sure
that you get right home to Raisa.
-But...
-I promise we'll talk about this
when I get home, but for now, I gotta go.
Listen, please trust me.
[sighs]
Three access points,
north, south and east.
Lance said these guys are
packing some heavy artillery.
-Where's GA?
-[Green Arrow] Right here.
We thought maybe you couldn't get away.
It wasn't easy.
Terrific, keep eyes on the perimeter.
Spartan, Canary, occupy the guards.
I'll extract the Markovians.
[grunting]
[clattering]
[grunts]
[screams]
[groans]
[grunts]
[grunting]
-There were four of you.
-Alec Tarkov, our CEO. They took him.
-Where?
-They did not tell us.
Spartan, Canary, we are short one hostage.
-We just did a sweep...
-There's no one else here.
-Overwatch?
-I don't know what happened?
Thermal read four warm bodies inside.
They must have moved one.
[Felicity] In the least
surprising news ever,
the Bratva-run restaurant
is lacking in security cams.
Oh, you mean, Russian mobsters
like their privacy?
So, what now?
So now I show you security camera
footage from outside the restaurant.
Okay, where's Anatoly going with Tarkov?
From this feed,
it looks like he's headed northeast,
but then we lose him right about there.
We could cross-reference our list of
Bratva crypto-currency activity
with Bratva-owned properties,
see what comes from that direction.
John, Dinah, be prepared to hit
whatever location
Felicity and Curtis come up with.
-Copy that.
-What about you?
I have to meet
Quentin and Rene at the FBI.
The agent pursuing the investigation
wants to interview me.
[Felicity] You have a lawyer
for that, right?
Or an army of lawyers,
that would probably be better,
that would work for you?
If you had an army of them.
I don't wanna look like
I have anything to hide.
Where are we with the photo?
Oh, I'm doing a re-code
into Felicity's analysis algorithm.
Should have something
working within an hour
to 30 days, give or take.
-[Felicity clears throat]
-Much closer to the hour mark though.
-Thank you.
-[cell phone chimes]
Keep me updated.
[clock ticking]
[sighs]
Did you always know you were gonna be FBI?
'Cause I have a little girl
who I think has that potential.
I mean, of course,
a woman can do anything a man can.
And why wouldn't they?
Exactly, I mean, they can.
I'm a feminist like that.
Look, it's been over an hour
and my patience is beyond gone.
Actually, you know what,
that's the Mayor himself.
Got a family emergency.
He's at home with the kid.
Look at that.
So, it must be a coincidence
that during his family emergency,
the Green Arrow was spotted rescuing
the Markovian executives
from the Russian mob?
Definitely a coincidence.
Do I really look that stupid?
You don't look stupid at all.
We're really sorry about
keeping you waiting, all right.
But I don't know if you know this,
but the mayor's actually
recently a single dad.
Yes, after the boy's mother died
unexpectedly in a car accident.
Well, most car accidents are unexpected.
And most leave behind
a car wreck and a body.
The only proof of Miss Clayton's death
was the accident report and the autopsy,
both of which
could have been easily faked.
You're not exactly a very trusting person,
are you, Special Agent Watson?
Trust isn't part of my job description.
But let me make one thing
clear as glass to you both.
If you're protecting Mr. Queen,
I'll find out.
And I'll have you both
indicted for obstruction.
Now get out of my office.
You've wasted enough of my time.
Let's go.
Hey, William.
That was a gift
from a very good friend of mine.
It's all fake.
Superheroes don't save anyone.
Buddy, I know that I ran out on you.
And I'm sorry, but people needed help.
I know that you needed help too,
so I'm here.
-Do you wanna learn a few more moves...
-No.
Because I don't wanna learn how to fight.
I don't want you to learn how to fight,
but you can't always reason with bullies.
You just left me, by myself.
I know. I know, and I'm sorry.
I didn't know if you were gonna come back.
William, look at me.
I will always come back.
Just like my mom?
-This is different.
-Yeah, it's worse.
Because there's a million psychos
always trying to kill you.
-I can handle them.
-What if you can't?
Then I'll be alone. I'll have nobody.
You wouldn't understand.
I do understand.
I lost my mom.
And I lost my dad.
And I was a lot older than you are now,
but I remember exactly how it feels.
It's sad. It's scary.
And it's lonely.
And I swear to God,
I will never let that happen to you.
It's not up to you.
[cell phone vibrating]
I'm sorry, it's work.
Which work?
[cell phone vibrating]
Hello, Oliver.
-Anatoly, why are you doing this?
-I need money.
And from what I understand,
your city recently
came into possession of $20 million.
There are plenty of cities in Russia.
Mmm. True. Beautiful ones.
But, you see, I have been exiled.
Apparently, Bratva thinks I am too weak,
due to my friendship with you.
So now, I show everyone.
I am not weak.
And you and I, no longer friends.
I know sometimes you need
persuasion to do the right thing.
So I help you.
This nice man has paralysis of muscles,
soon will have lung collapse,
and not be able to breathe.
This happens in maybe three hours.
Now, I have cure for his problems.
Do you have cure for mine?
[call disconnects]
All right, so you got this
off Oliver's phone?
-Five minutes ago, yeah.
-Any clues?
Wait, look at his face.
-I was trying really hard not to.
-What is that?
If we can analyze the facial rash,
we might be able to diagnose the poison.
Find the right cure. On it.
Anatoly said Tarkov has maybe three hours.
Yeah, sounds about right.
Got it.
Tetrodotoxin.
That's a neurotoxin.
Yeah, inhibits the firing
of action potentials
preventing the nervous system
from carrying messages
and muscles from flexing
in response to nervous stimulation.
I have no idea what you said,
but that doesn't sound good.
Is there a cure?
Yeah, they should have something
down at Starling General.
That's great. All we have to do is
get it to him before the poison
takes over his entire body.
-John
-Starling General, I'm on it.
[Dinah Drake] John, I'm coming with you.
Administer this to the patient,
and it'll neutralize the TCCD poison.
I don't wanna know what this is for, do I?
How long will it take
to reverse the effects?
It starts working immediately,
but I'd say 72 hours
until a full recovery.
Thank you, Doctor.
And, um, how are you feeling?
-I feel fine.
-[cell phone vibrating]
Excuse me, I have a patient.
Keep taking those pain meds.
Yes, ma'am.
It seems like you have another
chance to lie to me again.
I'm not lying.
I'm telling you
this is none of your business.
I'm out in the field with you
at less than 100%.
This is damn well my business.
And it's Oliver's.
What doesn't he know?
In Lian Yu, Felicity and I
got caught in one of the explosions.
-I thought you guys were fine.
-Felicity was.
But I caught some shrapnel.
-And didn't tell anybody?
-Thea was comatose.
Samantha dead. I was low priority.
John, that was five months ago.
Dr. Schwartz said I have nerve damage.
Degenerative.
That's why you haven't been
pulling your gun.
Dinah, I have this handled.
Yeah? Why don't you tell that to Rene?
He ended up in the hospital
because you couldn't even
get a single shot off.
It's just a tremor.
I can manage it.
I'm a soldier, Dinah.
Soldiers push through.
So what, I'm just supposed
to lie to everybody now
just like you've been doing?
You have to do whatever you have to do.
But I'm asking you, please...
Will you trust me on this one?
We should get going.
[Felicity] I know Python.
-Super villain?
-No, the programming language.
Look, maybe you could send some
of your freelance coding my way?
Look, I think that'll be a waste
of your prodigious talents.
Felicity, you are a... Son of a bitch!
Not really a son, Curtis, more of a...
No, I'm talking about this.
I revised your photo analysis algorithm
and got back this.
What? That's impossible.
Data analysis doesn't lie, Felicity.
Question is, what do we do with it?
[computer beeping]
What's that? Come on, no more bombshells.
I can't handle anymore
for the rest of the night.
It's not a bombshell, Curtis.
It may just be the key
to the Bratva's location.
[elevator dings]
What are you doing here?
Working, obviously,
what are you doing here?
Felicity and Curtis
are working on locating Tarkov.
He has maybe an hour left.
So, why aren't you home with William?
Sorry if I hit a nerve.
When have you ever been sorry
about hitting a nerve?
[Rene] That's a fair point.
-Speaking of William...
-Yeah?
We received a person of interest
list from Agent Watson.
-She wants to interrogate my son?
-He's an alibi.
And probably not a very good liar.
Absolutely not.
She's not going anywhere near him.
I don't think that's up to you.
I'm going to use
every single thing in my power
to keep him as far away
from this as possible.
This...
This kid has been through enough.
[Rene] All right, um...
Lance told me about
what happened at school.
Kids are mean.
He's not worried about bullies.
He's worried about me.
He thinks I'm gonna make him an orphan.
Damn.
I told him, I said, "That will not happen.
I will always come back."
I have never lied to my kid before.
You know...
I'm not exactly father of the year...
But...
White lies are kind of, like,
an important parental tool.
I remember telling Zoe
that she came from a cloud.
I really hope her mom
set her straight on that one.
[Oliver] So, help me with this.
How do I reconcile
that he's right?
Because every time that I'm in the field,
there's a chance I don't come back.
And then he's alone.
And now you're telling me
that he's gonna have to lie
to an FBI agent
so that he doesn't
lose his father to prison?
-[sighs]
-[cell phone vibrates]
[clears throat]
We have Anatoly's location.
All right, you go out
the back entrance. I'll lose him.
Rene, are you good
to get back in the field?
Hells yeah.
All right.
[Spartan] Team's in position.
You sure this is the place?
Oh-ho! I am so insulted right now.
Easy, it's just that an abandoned shipyard
doesn't feel like Anatoly's speed.
Yeah, well,
neither is being a complete jerk.
People change.
The problem is this place is massive.
So, I can't pinpoint the location of
the hostage, even with satellite.
Figure we'll split up.
I distributed the antidote,
so whoever gets to Tarkov first
can inject him.
You okay?
Yeah, I'm fine, let's do this.
[Mr. Terrific] If one of us spots Tarkov,
we should have a signal.
[Wild Dog] I was gonna go with
something like, "I see him."
Or maybe even, "Hey, over there."
Not terribly original, but effective.
What if we spot the Bratva?
[Wild Dog] How about, "Heads up?"
[Mr. Terrific] Heads up!
[screams]
-You okay?
-Look out!
[metal clattering]
[choking]
[grunts]
[gunshots]
I asked for 20 million specifically
because I know you had it.
You'd trade this man's life
for a new police station?
Not exactly.
I do not think you understand how
this whole rescue thing works.
No, I think I do.
Some sort of antidote?
Very clever.
Now step away from him, Anatoly.
He's not a part of this.
I made him part of this.
-[gunshot]
-[groans]
And I never got my money.
What the hell has happened to you?
-Not even Gregor would've done that!
-Yes, he would have.
You never saw because you were too naive.
You still are.
-We were friends.
-Yes.
But I see how you treat your friends.
No, Anatoly. No.
This is on you.
-You used to be an honorable man.
-I am an honorable man.
Did I have bomb
planted in your son's school?
Did I have him kidnapped?
Tortured? No.
Because even though we stand apart,
I am still good man.
I wonder.
What would happen to William
if you ran afoul of someone
who is not good?
Anatoly!
-Don't you move.
-Don't bluff.
We have been here before.
We both know you will not kill me.
Why did you leak that picture of me?
As Kapiushon?
I did not.
I told you.
I am honorable man.
Thank you for agreeing to meet.
I can always make time
for the subject of my investigation.
But I should advise
you have a lawyer present.
Why do I need a lawyer?
I haven't done anything wrong.
You know the kind of person who says that?
-No.
-The kind that needs a lawyer.
[chuckles]
Agent Watson, if you feel
the need to investigate me,
I am more than happy to open up
my entire life to you.
With the exception of my son.
He's off-limits.
You're aware that telling an FBI agent
how to conduct their investigation
is obstruction of justice.
If I really am the man
that you think I am,
how far do you think such a man would go
to keep his son
from being scrutinized by the FBI?
[knock on door]
-Miss Watson?
-A little busy here.
There's something on the news
that you need to see.
Channel 52 just received
exclusive evidence,
which conclusively establishes
that the photograph of Mayor Queen
as the Green Arrow was digitally doctored.
This is the second time that
Mayor Queen has faced allegations
of being a vigilante,
and twice he has been exonerated.
-Lucky you.
-Not really.
Like I said...
I'm not the man you think I am.
No, Mr. Queen, I think you are.
And if you think this means
I'm dropping my investigation,
then you're the one who's mistaken.
You should do whatever it is you have to.
[newsreader continues indistinctly]
The evidence received by Channel 52
showing that Mr. Queen's face
had been placed on the Green Arrow's body
was received earlier today
from an unknown source...
[Felicity] Nailed it.
You know, I don't wanna sound arrogant,
but we may very well be the smartest
human beings on the planet.
Oh, well,
it's not arrogant if it is accurate.
[chuckles] yeah. True that.
And you still find the time
to look bummed out. Crazy.
I mean, our photo analysis
algorithm was right, right?
The photo of Oliver was doctored.
-So...
-So? What's the problem?
So, who would want to frame
Oliver for being the Green Arrow?
Wow.
Way to kill the mood.
-Sorry.
-No, listen.
That is future us' problem.
I'm not gonna, like, let you take
away my buzz right now, okay.
Present us is only worried about
you quitting your nobody-told-about job.
When are you gonna let that go?
When you go into business with me.
I'm sorry, go into what with you?
Wait, what?
Work with me on this.
We work so well together.
Okay, that photographic analysis algorithm
is just one of many in a long list
of amazing tech
that you and I have collaborated on.
Think about all the good we could do.
All the cool stuff we could do.
All the cool things we could make.
Please don't say no.
-Yes.
-Oh, thank God, good.
Because I already filed the paperwork.
[Curtis] Oh, man, this is so cool.
We'll be like Woz and Jobs,
like, back in '76.
Wait. Who's Woz and who's Jobs?
-Shotgun Jobs!
Hey.
Can we talk for a second?
There's nothing to talk about.
We both know that's not true, Dinah.
[sighs]
What do we both know?
I need you to say it.
You nearly got killed last night
because you couldn't rely on me.
-Because you're compromised.
-I know.
I know.
Things just got worse
than I was willing to admit.
That's okay.
But what are you gonna do about it?
Tell Oliver.
Go from there.
[indistinct grunting on TV]
-You're home early.
-So I am.
I'm hoping to make that
more of a regular thing.
If that's okay with you.
Whatever.
I would like to apologize.
For what?
For making you a promise
I wasn't 100% sure I could keep.
You were right, and I was wrong.
Raisa said you have a hard time
admitting when you're wrong.
You have no idea.
Buddy, I heard what you said
in the limo and I hear you.
But I also meant what I said.
I am going to do
everything in my power, forever,
to make sure that you never
end up alone in this world.
And I know that you think that
that's not up to me.
And that's a fair, smart, point.
Which is why I think...
I found a way so that maybe it can be.
-How?
-I'm working on the details.
I want you to believe me when I say
that I'm trying to make it happen.
All right?
One more thing.
I promise
that I will do my best every single day
to be the very best father that I can be.
And that I know how to be.
That promise is 100%.
Okay.
Wanna play with me?
-What is this?
-Honestly, I don't know.
All you got to do is just button mash
and see where we can win.
All right, let me try.
-Yeah.
-All right.
[footsteps approaching]
Thanks for meeting me.
Yeah, well, I wanted to talk to you
about a few things.
What is it, Oliver?
I'd like you to do something for me.
If it's suit up as Green Arrow,
Felicity and I already talked
about it and we don't think
it's enough to take the heat off of you.
That's not what I'm asking.
You're serious?
Every time, that I'm out there
as the Green Arrow,
I'm a target.
Of the FBI, of the Bratva...
Of the threats that are out there
and the threats that are
undoubtedly coming.
And on my own,
I can take it.
I'm not on my own anymore.
I cannot be responsible
for my son losing
the only parent that he has left.
-Oliver...
-Star City needs the Green Arrow.
It just can't be me anymore.
So, I'd like it to be you.