My name is Oliver Queen.
After five years
on a hellish island,
I have come home
with only one goal--
to save my city.
But to do so, I can't be
the killer I once was.
To honor my friend's memory,
I must be someone else.
I must be something else.
Previously on "Arrow"...
I could save you,
or I could kill you.
Slade has the Mirakuru
in his system now.
The ones who survived,
they became someone else.
Whoa!
This Mirakuru,
it's messing with your head.
I know you
and your new friends
have the Mirakuru.
In exchange,
I'll promise you
and your friends
safe passage
off this island.
Slade's gone, and he took
the Mirakuru with him.
You know who he is under
that hood, don't you?
Once he has lost everyone
and everything he values...
I will drive an arrow
through his eye.
Welcome to
St. Walker's, alderman.
Or should
I call you Mayor?
Thank you
for letting me come by so late.
Well, I can imagine how
busy your schedule is.
It's really great
of you taking the time
to come and visit
your aunt.
Her health
has taken a bad turn.
Of course.
She's family.
Maya, look who came to see you.
It's your nephew, Sebastian.
Don't go.
Please.
We'll be fine.
Thank you.
Still worshipping
the old Gods, I see.
They're the last thing
I have from your father's.
They protect me.
You were supposed
to protect you.
A friend of mine, Laurel Lance,
came by to visit you
a couple days ago.
Do you remember her?
She's muy Linda.
Yes, she is.
What did you both
talk about?
Nada.
Nothing.
You know I don't like it
when you lie to me.
I told her
the truth.
That you--
you kill him.
Your father.
Mi esposo!
I don't know
what came over me.
I am so, so sorry.
I hurt you, mijo.
Esta bien.
No te preoccupes.
But you are
my child, my son.
And I hurt you.
I forgive you, mama.
I forgive you
for everything.
La luz de dios me rodea,
amor de dios me envuelve,
El poder de dios
me protege,
la presencia de dios
vela por mí.
Los dioses
están muertos.
♪ Arrow 2x11 ♪
Blind Spot
Original Air Date on January 22, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Oh! Ah!
Oh, please!
I don't know anything.
The man in the skull mask.
Where is he?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
He's been experimenting
on people in the Glades.
He's leaving a trail
of corpses
with blood running
from their eyes.
No, no, no, no, no.
I deal in stolen
merchandise, that is it.
Ah, ooh, please!
Ask him
what color his shoes are.
What?
You want this guy
to take a polygraph
via Bluetooth, cool,
but I need to hear him
establish a base line.
I need to hear him tell the truth
just once.
What color
are your shoes?
What?
They're blue!
He's not lying.
Please...
He's out there.
Somewhere.
Come home.
We can't do
any more tonight.
Slade?
Slade!
Thought maybe
he'd come back here.
He has the Mirakuru
serum in his bloodstream.
He's not thinking clearly.
So what do we do now?
I don't know, Sara.
The sensor grid
is still active.
So at least we're going
to know if Ivo
and his men come back
to the island.
So we just sit here and wait?
Well, do you have
any other ideas?
'Cause right now,
I'm open to suggestions.
We find Slade, and...
Maybe we consider Ivo's offer.
What?
Look, if we get the serum
back from Slade,
then we can go home.
And I can try to talk to Ivo.
I can get him to listen to me.
Like he listened before he shot
Shado in the head?
He's just tired,
and he's frustrated.
You don't understand
what finding
the Mirakuru serum
has meant to him.
You're right, Sara,
I don't understand.
And I don't get
how you can even consider
trusting him after what he did.
He's not evil.
He kept me safe
on that ship for over a year.
And I mean, not just safe,
he taught me things.
And I learned a lot.
I learned a lot, too.
This island taught me
that you can't trust anyone.
Ms. Lance?
I have a call for you
on line two.
Thank you,
Katherine.
Laurel Lance.
This is nurse Downey
from St. Walker's.
You asked me to call if there was
any changes Inaya Resik's condition.
I'm sad to report
she passed away.
What?
Her heart gave out
on her, poor soul.
You think Sebastian Blood,
the saint of Starling City,
killed his own mother?
He was the last person
to see her alive.
That isn't a coincidence.
He's a devoted nephew
visiting a sick relative.
You're right,
that's very, very suspicious.
He didn't go there
to visit her.
He went there to
kill her;
to cover up the fact
that as a child,
he killed
his father.
Maya Resik told me
what happened.
From inside
a padded room, right?
Which he had her
forcibly committed.
She tells me the truth and then
two days later has a heart attack.
You don't find that strange?
Well, for one thing,
there's no record that Maya Resik
was even Blood's mother,
and according
to the hospital,
she was in the late
stages of heart disease.
I need you to call
in a favor with Judge Carlin.
Get a search warrant
for Sebastian's campaign headquarters,
his phone records; I--I
have to start somewhere.
Laurel, this isn't
some casual request.
I'm the ADA
who took Vertigo on live TV.
I take a shot
at Sebastian Blood and miss,
my career is done.
Adam!
Please.
I'm sorry, Laurel.
You're on your own.
Hello, Roy.
Lurking in an ally.
That's not
at all creepy.
When I ran the club,
I learned
all the secret entrances.
I never got a chance
to thank you
for saving my mother's life.
Thea told me.
She said that
you were very brave.
I did what anyone
would have done.
Not anyone.
It takes a lot to run
towards danger,
not away
from it.
That sounded like praise.
I thought where I was concerned,
you didn't approve.
Thea said that you also got
hit by some falling debris.
How are you feeling?
Actually, it mostly missed me.
I'm fine. Look,
I got to get back to work.
Has Roy mentioned
anything about the man
in the skull mask
who injected him?
Roy is not
the kind of guy
who is comfortable
discussing his feelings.
Not like you and me.
Don't yell at me, but I really think
we need a new plan
on how to find
this creepy mask guy.
Scaring the crap out of low-lifes
isn't yielding results.
Felicity, I am open
to any and all suggestions.
Oliver, maybe we're
over thinking this.
What if the mask simply got wind
that you were after him
and decided
to skip town?
He didn't go
to all the trouble
of recreating the serum
and testing it on people
just to walk away.
He is still out there, and
we need to locate him.
Lance,
for the Arrow.
Yes, Detective?
Can we meet?
What is it?
Someone wants
to talk to you.
Hello, Laurel.
You're late.
I had to circle around to make sure
there wasn't a SWAT team
waiting for me again.
That's fair.
Trust me, I wouldn't
have asked my father
to put me in touch with you
if I had any other choice.
What do you need?
Sebastian Blood.
He's about to be
the new mayor of Starling City.
I know who he is.
No, you don't.
No one does.
A few weeks ago,
I was approached
by your groupie, Roy Harper,
and his girlfriend.
They asked me to investigate
the death of Max Stanton.
You think Blood was involved in
Stanton's death?
Blood, or a man that works
for him named Cyrus Gold.
Gold killed
four cops,
including my father's
partner, Lucas Hilton.
Blood and Gold knew each
other from the orphanage
that Blood was raised at.
He would do anything to keep
the truth about his past hidden.
Including murdering
his own mother.
Why would he do that?
To cover up the fact that he
killed his father.
I tried going to the DA.
No one will believe me.
I swear to you,
Sebastian Blood is dangerous.
And you're the only person
in this city who can stop him.
Laurel was right.
I hacked Blood's
cell phone records.
The alderman and Gold have
stayed buddies
since Zandia
orphanage.
So what? They
kept in touch.
Doesn't exactly mean
that Sebastian Blood
is the man
in the skull mask.
His last name is Blood.
That can't be a good sign.
Felicity, he's dedicated
his life, risked his life
to help the people
of the Glades.
And in his spare time,
he's a murderer
trying to create an army
of human weapons?
You're a personal bodyguard
who fights crime at night
with his billionaire boss.
Not a lot of people
show their real face in public.
Oliver, what
are you thinking?
Laurel gave me
a case number to start with.
We need to know if Sebastian
really killed his father,
then we figure out
if there's a chance
he has the Mirakuru formula.
I'm on it.
And what if this
is just another trap,
set by Laurel?
She could be setting you up,
and this time, you wouldn't
have Sara to save you.
Asking a cute girl to meet you
down by the tracks, Harper?
Good thing Thea and I are tight.
I have to show you
something.
Easy there, tiger.
You're not even bleeding!
When did you start juicing?
I'm not.
Then how do you explain
what I just saw?
You remember that night around
Christmas when I went missing?
Yeah, Thea
and I were pissed.
I never told you guys
what really happened.
You were right
about your friend Max.
He didn't OD,
he was murdered.
He was injected with something,
and I was injected with the same thing,
but it didn't kill me.
It made me--
it made me stronger.
Thea must be
freaking.
No, she doesn't know,
I don't want her to.
Why not?
No, I can't, not yet.
Not until I know more about
what happened to me.
I don't want to scare her.
And you're not worried
about scaring me?
Come on, I was going crazy
not telling someone.
So what are you
going to do?
Well, the Arrow once told me
all I was good for was taking a beating.
Maybe it's time I started
handing out a few of my own.
I don't follow.
Now I don't need his help
to protect this city.
Let's find us a bad guy.
I have good news
and bad news.
I suggest the good news first;
it tends to soften
the blow of the bad news.
Okay, dealer's choice.
Good news is we found the case file
on Sebastian's dad's murder.
Anything in it
to suggest he killed him?
Oliver, meet bad news.
That file was
sealed years ago.
And since the file
is over 27 years old,
there is no digital copy
for me to hack.
The only hard copy
is stored the old-fashioned way
in the city archives.
So I go in
and take it--
the old fashioned way.
Except security in the file room
is so old school,
you need a key card to get in,
which, even if you had,
you wouldn't know where
to start looking for the file.
An assistant DA would.
You said
you needed my help.
Now I need yours.
What do you need?
You.
You know what I really miss
about being home?
My bed.
I don't know if I even remember
what a bed feels like anymore.
And you probably
never will.
And neither
will I.
Sara...
You don't have to do that.
We're going to find
a way off the island.
Ok?
You just--you just
have to trust me.
Last time
I trusted you
was right before
the "Gambit" went down.
I haven't gotten
a chance to say this...
I'm sorry.
I know this is my fault.
And none of this
would have happened
if I hadn't invited you
on the boat with me.
That's not
exactly true.
I mean...
I was the one
who said yes.
And it was only
half because of your charm.
And the other half?
Do you remember
when you spilled that beer on me
at Tommy's party?
No.
But I never left
one of Tommy's parties
with my memory intact.
Well, I wasn't even
supposed to go.
But I snuck
out of the house
because I knew
you were going to be there.
And I had this--
I had this embarrassing
crush on you.
And Laurel,
she knew it.
And that's why the party got
broken up by the cops.
She tipped off our dad.
Then I was grounded
for a month,
and the next thing
I knew...
You and Laurel
were together.
You think she did
all that on purpose?
Not everybody's
what they seem.
We should
get some sleep.
You ready for this?
Whatever it takes.
We're going in.
At least the security cameras
are from this century.
And now
they're toast.
You have exactly seven minutes
until the system reboots.
Hey, check it out.
This could
take a while.
You have six minutes.
I'm rebooting the monitors.
There's a trojan
plugging our system.
It's probably some punk.
Uh-oh.
Oliver...
What's wrong?
It looks we've got the one
rent-a-cop with a brain here.
If there's a camera nearby,
I recommend hiding.
Look there.
You got to send
some officers here.
Starling's finest
will be there any minute.
You need to get
out of there now.
We're not leaving
without the file.
Laurel...
I can't find it!
Up there, third floor.
Hurry, Oliver.
Wait! Case number SC43878!
This is it!
Vigilante,
we know you're here!
Close everything off, now!
They're blocking
our only way out!
It's not our only way.
Get to the east wall
and wait for me.
Drop your weapon!
We tried going through
all the security footage
at the city archives
to see if anyone swiped the file
over the last few days.
Did you see anyone?
Just this.
It's all been erased.
So what happened
when you reversed the footprint
to see who hacked in
before you?
I struck out again.
It must have been an inside job.
Meaning?
As a city alderman,
Blood would have
had access to the files.
Oliver, anyone on city payroll
could have done this.
He's running for mayor.
One hint that
he killed his father,
and his political future
is dead in the water.
Wait, I thought you two were
supposed to be friends.
Don't you think you ought to give him
the benefit of the doubt?
Please keep digging
into Blood's past
and see if there's
anything that could help us.
Where you going?
To give a friend
the benefit of the doubt.
What, are you still
giving me the cold shoulder?
Are you still
not telling me
what the hell
is going on with you?
Am I interrupting?
He and I would
actually have to be talking
for you to be
interrupting.
Can I try?
Be my guest.
Tell her.
No.
Now what do you
got for me?
This guy in the Glades,
the Starling Slasher.
Word on the street is,
he's got a thing for prostitutes.
And by thing, I mean he has
a thing for slicing them up.
Mostly hunts in Crescent Circle.
Sounds like
a great guy.
Hmm, yeah. Problem is,
he's some big shot lawyer,
so no one has
the sack to ID him.
Wait, this sounds exactly like someone
the Arrow would go after.
But we don't need
the Arrow anymore.
We're going to have
to bait him.
What pro is going to let us
dangle her in front
of a psycho?
No. No, no way--
Thea.
No!
Um, Sin has a date.
She has hoping
to borrow an outfit.
You know, something slutty.
I have the perfect
first date outfit.
Guarantees a second one.
Great.
This guy won't know
what hit him.
Or girl.
Whatever you're into.
I could do your make-up
or your hair.
You are not touching
the hair, Queen.
Ok.
You looking for me?
Sebastian.
Good to see you.
You too, man.
Listen, I'm so sorry, but I'm
right in the middle
of a polling snafu.
I'll be quick. I just
had a question about Laurel.
Of course.
Is everything ok?
Not sure. I ran
into her the other day,
and something just seemed off.
I know the two of you
have been spending
a lot of time together,
I just wanted to know
if you knew anything.
Well, we've traded
phone calls,
but she's in trial,
I've been campaigning.
We haven't really
been able to connect.
Nothing happened
between the two of you?
Not an argument
or a fight or something?
If I didn't know
any better,
I'd say you were coming to me like
a jealous ex-boyfriend.
No. Just--no, I'm just
looking out for a friend.
And I hope you do the same.
Of course.
Listen, I will
take care of Laurel.
Thank you
for letting me know.
You're new.
Got to start
somewhere, right?
Get in.
Romantic.
You're pretty.
You're disgusting.
I see you'd like
to play rough.
Wait!
I've got money!
Keep it.
Roy, Roy, stop it,
you're killing him!
Oh! Sin?
Sin, I'm sorry.
We have to call
an ambulance.
Point blank range.
Single shot to the heart
from a low angle.
Obviously the handiwork
of someone quite scared,
and very small.
How come the police
didn't arrest you?
I knew how to cover my tracks.
A skill you've obviously lost since
you've gotten bigger.
You know how close you came
to allowing the Vigilante
to destroy everything?
Someone spoke out of turn.
I've taken care of the problem.
Your mother was
not our problem.
Laurel Lance is.
You were the one who told me
to get close to her.
You said that it was part of the plan
to hurt the Vigilante.
It is.
But you being
sloppy isn't.
Fix this, Mr. Blood.
You don't want me
to fix it for you.
Brother Daily.
I need you to take care
of something for me.
Whoever you are,
I'm calling the police!
No need to.
Remember me?
Officer Daily, right?
What's this all about?
What are you doing
in my apartment.
I have a warrant.
A warrant for what?
We found these
in your bedroom, Ms. Lance.
These aren't prescribed to you.
That's a felony.
What?! This is ridiculous!
You're under arrest for possession of
a controlled substance.
You have the right
to remain silent.
Anything you say
can and will be used against you
in a court of law.
I know what
this looks like.
But you have
to listen to me.
I know what's happening.
Sebastian Blood...
He's setting me up,
because he knows
I'm onto him.
He's--he's trying
to frame me!
So he planted drugs
in your apartment?
But--no, no!
Forget about the drugs.
The point is, is that he
is the one
behind this witch hunt.
Sebastian called your boss.
He's worried about you.
No, no!
He wasn't worried
about me.
He's trying
to discredit me!
Don't you see
what he's doing?
What I see is that you
have tested positive for opiates.
I see that you have been
lying to me,
and I see that you have been
stealing from me!
I can explain that.
Every person that stands
where you're standing now
says the same thing.
Dad...
The DUI,
the paranoia about Blood,
you're looking like hell.
You got a problem, Laurel.
No.
It's addiction.
No!
It runs in the family.
You can't pin it
on Sebastian Blood.
Daddy, please,
you have to believe me!
Please!
Please.
I don't, baby.
No!
How is she?
I don't know.
I don't know
anything anymore.
I'll--I'll get her home.
Thanks.
Anthony?
Are you there?
I'm here, Sara.
I was hoping that
you would reach out to me.
Are you alone?
Yes.
Are you all right?
You're not hurt,
are you?
Do you even care?
You were going to shoot me.
No.
No, Sara.
I swear, you were
never in danger, I swear.
So it's ok because you were just
planning on murdering Shado?
Her name was Shado.
Yes.
And you killed her,
Anthony.
And I'm going to have to live
with that for the rest of my life.
I never set out to hurt anyone.
I started this quest
to save people;
to save the human race.
I know.
Sara.
I know you think
that this ship rescued you
when you were stranded at sea.
The truth is...
You rescued me.
But now the darkness,
it's threatening me again.
I need you, Sara.
Please.
Save me.
How's he doing?
The damage done to his head
and lower abdomen is severe.
He ruptured his spleen
and he has massive
swelling in his brain.
Thankfully, he got medical
attention quickly,
so he's got a shot.
You did a good thing
here, Roy.
What happened to you out there?
I don't know.
We nearly killed this guy.
Roy?
Are you ok?
What are you
doing here?
Sin called me.
Why did you do that?
Because she was
worried about you.
Who is that guy?
He was my date.
We put him there.
You--you did this?
Just drop it.
Please.
Roy, something
is happening to you.
I'm not judging you.
I'm not angry with you.
I'm on your side.
I just want to help you.
You can't.
I--I got to go.
Roy!
You haven't
said much.
Are you working
on your lecture?
No lecture.
I suppose you think I was wrong
about Sebastian, too, though.
I think...
that you have everyone fooled,
because you want people to think
that none of this gets to you.
And that you don't need
anyone's help.
I don't!
Except, I know you!
This isn't you.
What happened
to no lectures?
I just--I need
a glass of water.
Do you mind?
Please.
Leave him. He's not important.
Hello, Laurel.
Laurel.
It's me.
Someone
came after Laurel.
Do you know
where they took her?
I think I have
a pretty good idea.
If that mask
is supposed to scare me...
All that it's doing
is confirming what I've already
known for a while now.
You're one sick
son of a bitch, Sebastian.
30,000 years ago,
masks invested
their wearer with authority,
like a God.
You're insane.
I'm not the one
making drug-addled,
unsubstantiated accusations
against Starling's favorite son.
If I can find out
the truth,
then others can, too.
You found out
nothing.
You know nothing.
Get away from her!
Or I will put...You...Down.
And to think,
a few short months ago,
you were trying
to arrest him.
You wanted me here.
I'm here.
Let...Her...Go.
No, I think
she should witness this.
Aaah!
Take off his mask.
I need to see.
Sweetheart.
Are you all right?
Yeah.
Looks like Daily
was behind this whole thing.
Son of a bitch volunteered for the raid
that got Hilton killed.
And we found
the accelerant that he used
to torch the Langford Institute
in his apartment.
I thought it was Sebastian.
I was so sure.
Yeah.
Well, that's the thing about
the booze and the pills.
You know, same thing
that dulls your pain...
clouds the judgment.
Can we have a minute?
Yeah.
Are you here to say,
I told you so?
We're dropping
the possession charges
and you won't be charged
in Daily's shooting.
It was clearly self defense.
You don't seem
that thrilled for me.
Are you going
to look me in the eye
and tell me you don't have
a substance abuse problem?
The DA's office has
a generous severance package.
Wait!
Wait, let me explain
to DA Spencer.
I can--I can tell
her everything!
This isn't coming
from Spencer, Laurel.
This is me.
I'm the one that hired you.
I'm sorry.
But you're done.
Did Laurel
really shoot him?
She saved my life.
That's a good thing,
Oliver.
You ok?
She really had me believing
that Sebastian Blood
was a criminal mastermind,
and the only reason
that I nearly believed her
was because it was Laurel.
I do have a blind spot
where she's concerned.
Not anymore.
Certainly know how
to talk yourself out of a victory.
It's a gift.
Take the win, man.
Daily's dead, you destroyed
the serum.
It's over.
No, it isn't.
Hey.
Slow night?
Something I said?
Don't take it
personally.
He won't even make
eye contact with me.
Something happen?
He put someone
in the hospital.
He's a little stingy
with the details,
but.... You should have
seen this guy.
I don't understand
how any human
could have done that
to another.
Each day, he becomes
more and more like somebody
I don't even know.
He won't even
listen to me.
I know someone
he'll listen to.
Sara,
are you still there?
When you first
found me,
I felt like
you were my savior.
And letting me
into your work,
I felt like I was a part
of something bigger.
You are, Sara.
It was only because
I didn't want to see
what you were
really doing.
I mean, what you did
to those people on the boat,
and how you tortured
them for science...
How I was glad
that I wasn't one of them.
But now...
I'd rather be dead
than keep being a part of this.
You ungrateful bitch.
You think you know
what torture is?
You have no idea.
But I will show you.
I am going to hunt you down.
Both of you,
and I will show--
Let's go find Slade.
It's done.
They think
it was all Daily.
He sacrificed himself
for our cause.
A good start.
But the magnitude
of your negligence
requires a greater sacrifice.
Your incompetence has now
cost four lives, alderman.
Fail me again...
and yours will be
the fifth.
If that was supposed to
go through my other leg,
you missed.
You seem to be
healing pretty well.
You're stronger,
you heal faster,
but you're not in control.
The serum that you were
exposed to, it changes your body
but it also warps your mind.
How do you know
so much about it?
I've seen it before.
It twists men.
Turns them into
someone they don't recognize.
Someone dangerous.
Maybe you should put
another arrow through me.
This time through my heart.
There's another
way, Roy.
I can teach you...
to control
your new ability.
And to control
yourself.
Let me help you.
When do we start?
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man