A life that hasn't had a chance
to fully grow
and live out its purpose in this world
is a life that has been taken
from this earth too soon.
Oliver Queen,
whom I'm told is practically family,
will be delivering the eulogy.
Mr. Queen?
Mr. Queen, are you ready?
Uh, I could probably say a few words.
(SIGHS)
Tommy Merlyn was one of the
greatest people that I've ever known.
(VOICE BREAKING)
He was so much more than just a...
A billionaire playboy.
I loved him.
I loved him in...
In every way you could
possibly love someone.
And so did Oliver.
And I'm sure if Oliver could
be here today, he would say so.
But clearly it's too painful.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
I don't understand.
I'm sorry.
-I...
-(BREATHES DEEPLY)
(WHISPERS) Where is she?
-Excuse me, are you a relative...
-OLIVER: Doctor.
It's her father.
DOCTOR: I'm terribly sorry for your loss.
Uh, these are her belongings.
(WHISPERS)
Uh, I can take care of those for him.
(SOBBING GENTLY) Laurel.
Baby.
We should get you out of here.
I love you too.
Give that baby girl a kiss for me.
Didn't expect to see you standing there.
Where else would I go?
How's Lyla?
She and baby Sara are
at an A.R.G.U.S. safe house.
I have an army buddy looking
after Carly and Andy Jr.
You worried about your brother?
I don't think he would do
anything to hurt my family, but...
I don't know.
Clearly, I never knew him.
All right, John.
As the world's leading expert
in blaming yourself,
please don't do it.
You warned me, Oliver.
Straight up, you warned me.
If I had listened to you
instead of trusting my brother,
Laurel would be alive right now.
You can't know that.
SPOKESMAN: (ON TV) On behalf of
Mayor Adams and everyone in City Hall,
I'm very sorry to announce the death
of Assistant District Attorney,
Laurel Lance.
Ms. Lance was conducting a deposition
of Damien Darhk
prior to tonight's incident
at Iron Heights Correctional Facility.
I'm informed by the
Department of Corrections,
Mr. Darhk remains at large
and is the leading suspect
in Ms. Lance's death.
(SLOWLY) I'm gonna get some air.
OLIVER: John.
Smith &amp; Wesson, 460XVR revolvers,
.50-cal Desert Eagles,
Boberg nine-mil semi-autos.
Fifteen large and they're all yours.
How about it?
-(EMITS SHRILL CRY)
-(ALL GROANING)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
Hi, I didn't know that...
You called for the team.
-What's going on, Oliver?
-Well...
Darhk is out there
and he has his magic back.
As much as I'm sure all of us wanna
climb up inside of our own grief...
We have to get that son of a bitch.
THEA: Definitely, but...
We haven't even put her in the ground yet.
-Uh, Captain?
-(SIGHS) Page three.
(STAMMERS)
This was last night, after Iron Heights.
This article says that she used a
sonic weapon against a dealer and a buyer.
Guys, CCTV footage
from last night's attack.
So Sara came back.
All the crazy things that we've seen.
Maybe my baby...
My baby girl, maybe she's not gone.
THEA: I mean, we...
We saw her.
(STUTTERS) Yeah, but you know, I mean,
everyone thought Oliver was dead
when the Gambit went down.
Everybody thought Ray Palmer was dead.
Your brother?
Captain, I know, I know,
but this is different.
John's right.
This bag from the hospital
was supposed to contain
all of Laurel's belongings.
"Supposed to"?
Her sonic device is missing.
You know, that explains it.
There were people in and out
of Laurel's room.
Doctors, nurses, orderlies...
(STAMMERS)
What, you think someone took it?
Yeah.
Laurel.
Captain, let's not go there just yet.
Now you don't think that with everything
that we have seen...
That we have all seen, that there is
a chance that Laurel is back?
DIGGLE: Cisco keyed the sonic device
to Laurel's vocal chords.
No one else is supposed to be able
to use that.
QUENTIN: Right, right.
What are you thinking?
(SIGHS)
(DOOR OPENS)
-Quentin?
-(DOOR SLAMS)
Yeah.
Dr. Schwartz.
(CLEARS THROAT)
I'd like to thank you for your
discretion throughout all of this.
Doctor-patient privilege.
And in any case, she, um,
helped this city.
I mean, the least I can do
is help her and you.
At least 12 staffers saw me
bring her into the hospital last night.
And they saw the Black Canary.
But we operated on Laurel Lance.
Who, I believe, was injured
during an Iron Heights prison riot.
(SIGHS)
There was a Black Canary
sighting last night.
This person was wearing a sonic device.
The same sonic device that was taken
from Laurel's belongings in her room.
Are you saying...
I have reason to believe that someone
walked into her room and took it.
Now can you put me on a path?
(SIGHS)
There's a frequent-flier.
"Frequent flier"? What does that mean?
A patient who pays repeated
visits to the ER.
Now I've treated her a few times
and there's something...
-There's something off about her?
-Mmm-hmm.
Would you give me her name?
Doctor-patient privilege
applies to all my patients, Mr. Queen.
Yeah.
LAUREL: Oliver.
I'm sorry, I...
I didn't know where else to go.
Do you wanna come inside?
I don't think that it's the best idea.
I'm sorry they didn't let your mom
attend the funeral.
(CHUCKLES SLOWLY)
It was a nice service.
Tommy would've liked it.
He would've liked it more
if you would have said a few words.
Stayed up all night.
I was working on the eulogy.
I just filled page after page with
stories of us.
But then I realized that I just didn't
have the right to say any of those things.
(SOBS GENTLY)
What are you talking about?
Oliver, Tommy loved you.
Laurel, I failed him.
I came back from that island
with another chance.
A chance to help people. It was...
It was a chance to make this city better.
And I couldn't.
And now Tommy's dead.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Oliver,
you can't blame yourself.
You'd blame me too if you knew the truth.
What truth?
That was Oliver.
Laurel's still, you know, there.
But he thinks he has a lead on some woman
who recently visits
the emergency room a lot.
I'm gonna try
and cross reference facial-recog
from last night's attack
with the hospital's security footage.
Hey.
At the hospital, you said that you'd never
forgive yourself for what happened.
Andy's working with Darhk,
has been the entire time.
He helped him find the idol,
helped him out of jail.
Oliver warned me,
but I pretty much told him to go to hell.
Laurel's dead because of me.
I don't know what happened,
I wasn't there.
I don't know what to say.
There's nothing to say.
Thank you for everything at the hospital.
I don't think any of us were ready
to talk to the media.
One of the few advantages
of dating a political operative I guess.
(CHUCKLES)
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to joke.
Please, I could...
I could use some jokes.
Anything to keep my mind off of...
Everything.
Speaking of actually, you've...
You never told me why you became
a "political operative" anyway.
WOMAN: Alex Davis.
(EMITS SHRILL CRY)
You work for them!
(GRUNTING)
What are you talking about?
(WOMAN GROANING)
(EMITS SHRILL CRY)
(THEA GROANS)
(PHONE BEEPS)
-Ollie!
-What's going on?
Alex just got attacked by some girl
wearing Laurel's sonic device.
You know where she went?
(ARROW WHOOSHING)
You're dressed like a friend of mine. Why?
(EMITS SHRILL CRY)
Why did you abandon us?
We needed your help and all you cared
about were your friends.
You didn't care about any of us.
What are you talking about?
(EMITS SHRILL CRY)
You left us.
You left us at Reddington!
You left us there to die!
You failed this city.
(EMITS SHRILL CRY)
It wasn't Laurel, but it was sure
like seeing a ghost.
And hearing one.
That sonic device has been modified.
My earplugs did not do a thing.
The sonic device is what shouldn't have
done the damn thing.
But you said Cisco keyed
it specifically to Laurel.
It should have only worked with Laurel.
The crazy part is that this girl
is using it at much higher decibels
than Laurel ever did.
OLIVER: Okay, so who is this girl?
Well, when she attacked Alex,
she accused him of working for someone.
Ruvé Darhk?
HIVE.
She said the Green Arrow left
them at Reddington to die.
-What's Reddington?
-Reddington Industrial is where
Darhk held you all hostage over
the holidays.
You think this girl was one
of HIVE's prisoners?
They weren't prisoners, remember?
They were volunteers.
Right, but still let's check
missing persons for a family
with at least one teenage daughter
who went missing over Christmas.
The Sharp family.
Mom and dad's bodies
were found two days after Christmas.
Cause of death, hypoxia.
Could be HIVE's gas chamber.
What about the daughter?
-(KEYS CLACKING)
-(COMPUTER CHIMES)
Class president,
academic decathlete, gymnast.
Basically a 16-year-old badass
in the making.
She never even missed a day of school.
Until her parents met Damien Darhk,
I'm guessing.
She said we left them there to die.
-And we did.
-What do you mean?
All those people at Reddington...
Were there of their own choosing, Oliver.
And we know that HIVE drugs people
to make them susceptible to suggestion.
She told me that we've failed this city,
and she's not wrong.
Thanks for coming.
I fear I lack the words to convey
the true depths of my sympathy.
To lose a child once is unimaginable.
But for it to be both children...
Listen, I know you and I haven't always
been on the same side of things,
but Laurel, uh, you know,
thought of you as a friend.
Just as I thought of her.
She brought me comfort
during a difficult time period.
The world will be a darker place
without her.
Yeah, well, not for long.
Okay, I got all her things.
What else do I need?
I'm afraid I don't understand.
What else do I have to bring for her
when she comes out of this, you know,
Lazarus Pit thing.
I would do anything for your daughter.
But I destroyed the Pit months ago.
Um...
Okay, well,
there's got to be, uh, something else.
I am so very sorry.
So you don't wanna help me?
Fine.
I'll find some other way
to bring her back.
(SIGHS)
Just scouring traffic cameras for Evelyn,
but I keep striking out.
What are you doing here?
I'm thinking.
Which is Oliver-speak
for beating yourself up.
I thought you were reformed from that.
Feels like as good a time
as any to bring it back.
Because of Laurel
or because of what that girl said?
Bit of both.
I tried to do the right thing
and I came up short.
I came up short for that girl,
and for Laurel.
Maybe I shouldn't feel responsible,
but I do.
Yeah, it's going around.
You mean John?
No, I mean me.
And John was looking for someone
to absolve him.
Reassure him that
what happened wasn't his fault
and I couldn't do it.
(VOICE BREAKING) I think for a second,
I let him blame himself because for
a minute it saved me from blaming me.
I should have been there.
I wasn't there,
with the team in the bunker.
I know I would have just been
behind a keyboard
and I know it seems like hubris,
but I've made a difference before,
and I can't help
but think that if I was there,
you know, maybe she'd still be here.
Do you know why
I always blame myself
in situations like this?
Because at least it's an answer.
Sometimes we just need a reason
when a situation
is completely unreasonable.
(SIGHS)
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
-Hello?
-THEA: Lyla called asking for John.
Except he's supposed to be
checking in on her.
I'm getting a bad feeling about this.
I have trackers on all of you,
I'll check and I'll get back to you.
LYLA: Well, tell those curious,
that the city has undertaken to do
a massive upgrade of the sewage system.
I mean, what happens below ground
is simply not their concern.
(TIRES SCREECHING)
Why are we stopping?
-Get down.
-(GLASS SHATTERS)
Get out!
What do you think you're doing?
I am the mayor of this city.
I don't care who you are,
you're gonna be a lot less
if you don't get out
of that limo right now.
Move.
Can I help you with something?
I mean, I always enjoy spending time
with my constituents.
-Shut up!
-(GROANS)
You know who I am.
You know exactly who I am
and you know who my brother is.
-I don't know what you're talking about.
-Stop lying!
(INHALES SHARPLY)
Fine, we'll do this your way.
Maybe you can give your husband
a message for me.
Let him know I'm not playing games
with him anymore.
(GROANS)
Get away from her, John.
Stay out of my way.
What the hell do you think you're doing?
Trying to find Andy.
By attacking the mayor of the city?
By going after Damien Darhk's wife.
It doesn't matter if she's Darhk's wife.
She is the mayor.
She has the media, she has the police!
I don't give a damn! (PANTING)
I'm so angry, I can hardly breathe.
Every minute he's out there is a...
Is another minute he can hurt
someone I love.
John,
I know.
But this isn't who you are.
I don't know,
I don't know who I am anymore, Oliver.
All I know is all I can hold
on to is that...
I have to find my brother.
(STUTTERS) And do what?
Laurel's gone and finding Andy
and whatever you're gonna do to him,
it's not gonna bring her back.
But, if she were here,
she'd tell you the same thing
that I'm gonna tell you.
You cannot forget who you are.
And we,
we can never become them.
Where have you guys been?
OLIVER: Doesn't matter.
Have we had any luck tracking down
Evelyn Sharp?
No, I keep hitting dead ends. (SIGHS)
-Not the best choice of words.
-(COMPUTER CHIMES)
News alert.
Tonight, my security detail and I
were attacked
by one of these lawless vigilantes
who claim to protect this city.
This attack came less than 24 hours
after another vigilante,
named the Black Canary,
assaulted my chief of staff, Alex Davis.
Now these same masked criminals
were confirmed to be at Iron Heights
when one of this city's beloved
civil servants, Laurel Lance,
was fatally injured.
Well, tonight I say, no more.
Tonight I asked District Attorney Wallace
to issue arrest warrants
for these so-called vigilantes.
Beginning with Mr. Davis' attacker,
the Black Canary.
We will dedicate the arrest and
prosecution of this so-called Black Canary
to A.D.A. Laurel Lance,
one of this city's brightest lights.
Turn it off.
Thank you.
She knows Laurel was the Black Canary.
And now she has
the whole police force gunning
for a scared, frightened teenage girl.
THEA: (SIGHS) I'll call Alex.
Okay.
We need to find Evelyn
before the SCPD does.
-(CELL PHONE VIBRATING)
-Yes.
Yeah.
Mr. Lance's agony is understandable.
But its pain is sharpened by denial.
I fear that, that refusal
to accept reality
will lead Mr. Lance
to take desperate action.
Thank you for letting me know.
I will keep an eye on him.
Oliver,
are you all right?
Our friend was killed
at the hands of a man
that I am currently powerless to stop,
and his wife is dragging her legacy
through the mud.
And after everything she's done,
everything she's stood for,
it just doesn't seem right.
(OLIVER SIGHS)
I'm glad you finally decided to come over.
Oh, it's been a week.
I feel like Tommy would be pissed at me
if I didn't eventually come out
of my self-pity.
(CHUCKLES) Yeah.
You know, he loved you so much.
This was right after you won
student body president our senior year.
(SIGHS) Do you remember how I won?
Of course, you were the most
deserving candidate by far.
Well, the gift baskets encouraging people
to vote for me, that didn't hurt either.
That was Tommy's idea.
(BOTH LAUGH)
No, but...
Seriously it's easy to buy people off
with money that you didn't even earn.
-You did all the hard work.
-Hmm.
We always did make a great team.
You know, I was thinking about
what you said in the hallway
after Tommy's funeral,
and wanting to help make the city
a better place.
(WHISPERS) We still can.
Laurel Lance,
always trying to save the world.
Yeah, but it doesn't have to be just me.
You can too.
We can do it together.
I'm really excited
about the future, Ollie.
What are you... (GROANS)
There's no one in there.
It's where the League of Assassins
hang their black hoods.
No, that's right,
but there is no Lazarus Pit,
and no League in there.
No, but it might be something,
just some clue, all right.
Next step on the trail.
There's no trail, Quentin!
Laurel is gone
and there is no bringing her back.
No, no, no. To hell with that.
And if you don't wanna help me,
to hell with you too!
I am helping you.
No, you're not because you know why?
Because you do not know
what it is like to lose a child.
No idea!
But I have lost a father,
I have lost a mother
and I have lost Laurel!
We have lost her!
(PANTING)
-(SOBS)
-We have.
If there was a way, if there was, any way
to bring her back,
I would find it and I would do it.
But there isn't.
For either of us.
You don't understand.
Right when we lost Sara
when I became a drunk,
when no one else believed in me, she did.
She's always been there. She's my rock!
You're right.
(CRYING) She was my rock.
I can't do this.
Oh, God!
Oh, no.
I can't do this.
(QUENTIN CONTINUES CRYING)
Oh, my God.
-John?
-You got something?
Yeah, an apology.
I never should have let you think that
you could have prevented
what happened to Laurel,
not even for a second, I was just dealing
with my own guilt for not being there.
Well, you have nothing
to be sorry about, Felicity.
If I had listened to Oliver
and not trusted my brother,
Laurel would be alive.
No, you don't know that.
Oliver keeps saying the same thing,
except I keep going through this
over and over again in my head and it...
It's true.
Only thing I don't quite get is
how I could have been so blind.
Well, Andy's your brother, you know?
We make exceptions for family.
Yeah,
and I'm the one constantly telling Oliver
not to have a blind spot for family.
And here you are, taking the blame
for something that's not your fault.
You're just one illegitimate child away
from a really awesome
Oliver Queen impersonation.
(CHUCKLES)
But, just like we tell Oliver,
what happened was not your fault,
and Laurel would have wanted you
to know that.
(COMPUTER CHIMES)
What's that?
Evelyn Sharp. Facial recognition picked
her up outside of Star City Plaza Hotel.
What's she doing there?
That's where Ruvé Darhk is.
She's getting revenge for her family.
Well, if she's gonna kill Ruvé Darhk,
my vote is yes.
It's not just killing Ruvé Darhk,
in that mask, in that costume,
she'd be killing Laurel's legacy.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
Hello, pleasure to meet you.
-Excuse me.
-Not right now.
Keep your eyes peeled.
She's out there somewhere.
I'm on site.
Yeah, so is the Anti-Vigilante Task Force.
And they've come ready to play.
We need to find that girl before they do.
Hey! (GROANS)
Heading in.
(DOOR OPENS)
GUARD: Ma'am, you shouldn't be in here.
Funny, I was gonna tell you
the same thing.
(EMITS SHRILL CRY)
(LOUD FEEDBAACK)
The Black Canary is in the building.
I need to get you to a secure location.
Oh, you will do no such thing.
Let her come.
Let her try.
I found her. Second floor, 200 feet
from the Liberty Ballroom,
Ruvé Darhk and a lot of innocent people.
On it.
(MEN GROANING)
Don't.
Don't go in there.
Get away.
I can't do that.
And you can't do this.
Now, I know you want revenge on HIVE
for what they did to your parents.
But this isn't the way.
It's the only way I have left.
(EMITS SHRILL CRY)
Evelyn, don't.
(GROANS)
You've failed this city.
ARROW: I understand that you're trying to
make things right.
That is not how you get justice done.
What did you know about
the real Black Canary?
what she stood for?
She was there that night.
I saw her.
You saw what kind of person she was.
She was a hero.
Now, maybe you're wearing
that mask for a reason.
But right now I need you to ask yourself,
what would the Black Canary
want you to do?
Come on.
(SCOFFS)
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
Arrest him.
I've seen this movie before.
(GLASS SHATTERS)
No sign of Evelyn.
Kid must've found out I was tracking her.
I really missed her out there tonight.
In a way, she was out there.
In spirit, I mean,
not in a Lazarus Pit kind of way,
and ultimately, she made the right choice.
I think Laurel would've liked
that she inspired someone.
How can you say that?
Evelyn Sharp just destroyed
Laurel's memory out there tonight.
Now the Black Canary is only gonna be
remembered for whatever Evelyn's done.
Evelyn's not the Black Canary.
Well, to every reporter and person
with a camera in the room tonight,
she was.
Ruvé Darhk's gonna make sure
everybody sees that footage.
(SIGHS)
As far as the rest of the world
is concerned,
the Black Canary is now a gun-toting,
would-be murderer.
I'm not gonna let that happen.
Oh, Quentin,
I never thought we'd be here again.
Me neither.
I figured we were punished enough
first time around.
We were.
Oh.
At least for a while and
then Sara came back to us.
I don't think that's gonna
happen this time.
(SCOFFS) How can you say that?
Our girls always come back to us, Quentin.
Yeah, maybe before, but not this time.
I'm sorry, Di, but she's gone.
She's never coming back.
She's...
Mr. Queen has requested
to say a few words.
So...
This doesn't seem right. Uh...
I knew Laurel Lance for
almost her entire life.
She was my friend and I loved her.
Before she died I was...
I was lucky enough
to hear her tell me that
she loved me too.
Laurel Lance became a lawyer to
help people who may have
appeared helpless.
She wanted to give a voice to the silent.
But just
being a lawyer wasn't enough.
She wanted to do more for those people,
and for this city.
And she loved this city so much.
By now everyone knows that
Laurel was killed
in the Iron Heights prison riot.
And while it's true that she was
an assistant district attorney,
that's not what she was doing there
that night.
Before she died, Laurel told me the truth.
Laurel Lance was the Black Canary.
(SOBBING)
And for the past few days,
I have had to sit and listen to people try
and paint the Black Canary as a criminal.
She was not a criminal.
She was a hero.
She was a hero in every way
that a person can be.
And if Laurel were here,
I know that she would expect all of us
to live up to the example that she set.
She'd want us to save our city.
(DOOR SHUTS)
OLIVER: Dear Laurel, I wrote this letter
because I don't have the courage to see
the disappointment on your face.
I know you're gonna go on
to do amazing things,
to help people and to raise this city up
because that's who you are,
it's who you've always been,
and that's why I have to go away.
I would only hold you back.
You're the hero, Laurel.
Maybe I'll come back eventually,
but for now I have to spend
some time alone.
I hope someday you'll understand
my decision.
Never doubt my love for you.
You've always seen the best in me,
because you've always been the best of me.
All my love, Oliver.
I'm sorry I missed the funeral.
-Zoom?
-Yeah.
There was a time
I would have thought this was my fault.
That I brought this darkness upon us.
Now I know it's not my fault.
It's my responsibility.
Responsibility to do what?
To end it.
I'm gonna kill him.
Is there anything I can do?
I wanna be left alone.
Are you okay?
Are you?
(SLOWLY) No.
You know what you have to do, right?
You have to kill this son of a bitch.
I know.
I don't know how.
Because of his magic.
His ma... It's too strong.
I've seen it before,
back on Lian Yu,
and it is not just magic.
It's darkness.
And whenever I have come up against it,
I have gone nowhere.
It...
He feels unstoppable.
I refuse to believe that.
And I refuse to let you believe that.
If Darhk wins, Laurel died for nothing.
I fell in love with you for many reasons
and one of those reasons is,
is that you always find a way,
and you have to find a way now.
For Laurel,
for the city,
for all of us.
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)