Previously on "Arrow"...
This place looks exactly
like it did when I was 13.
We had planned to come
back here with both of you.
Yeah. That didn't really work out.
Because I died.
Have you come to doubt your commitment
to this mission?
It might help if I actually knew why.
The recovery of your universe
will require a single task.
You must betray Oliver Queen.
If saving it means going back
to the person that I used to be,
the what the hell is the point?
I'm sorry.
Passes it quickly over to the right.
Tark drives the lane.
Kicks it to Aldrich in the corner for 3.
Bingo! Count it and the foul!
That's an 8-0 run by the Comets,
who have stormed all the way back
to tie it up here in the fourth quarter.
No way. It tastes the same.
I'm telling you this big
belly burger's just better.
I think he's right. This
is pre-gwespin foods merger.
Dad, what are you still doing here?
How did we get here?
What do you mean?
Uh, I was on a roof
with John and Laurel,
and we were tranqed.
Yeah. By Lyla.
Dad said it was all just
a big misunderstanding.
Ahem. What did we do with
Burov's plan for the weapon?
You said we didn't need it anymore.
Why? The Monitor's still out there.
He's still a threat.
Dad, are you okay?
You... you look like you
don't remember any of this.
I...
I need to talk to John.
That should be easy.
He's waiting for you at
that fancy fundraiser.
What fundraiser?
The one you're very late for.
I mean, you do remember
you're Oliver Queen, right?
Hey, Queen, what's the difference
between a cop and the Green Arrow?
A cop doesn't need to play
dress-up to do his job.
Ha. Yeah, sure. Whoa!
- I'm so sorry, Mr. Queen.
- It's fine, it's fine.
There you are, man.
The party started an hour ago, Oliver.
Do you remember getting
tranqed last night?
Yeah. Uh, Lyla feels awful about that.
By the way, that wasn't last night.
- That was two days ago.
- What? No.
No, no. That... John,
that is the last thing
that I remember before waking up
in my apartment earlier tonight.
You okay, man?
No. This is... this... Is this the...
This is the Monitor.
- Oliver.
- Your wife is working
with the Monitor, John. What...
I thought we already settled this.
I have been working with the
Monitor but as a double agent,
which I told you on the roof.
I don't... I don't remember that.
I'm not remembering anything.
Oliver, look. Just maybe
you should go home, man,
get a little sleep, okay?
Oliver, there you are. Mayor's
looking for you. Come on.
What?
- What happened there?
- Oh.
Can't give a speech
with a stained shirt.
Give a s... what speech?
I'm giving a speech?
Very funny. Your joint
remarks with the mayor.
Rene, um, serious question.
When did Palmer Tech get rebuilt?
You really need to drop
this amnesia routine quick.
This fundraiser is
our only chance to take
the SCPD vigilante pilot program global.
The mayor needs you to be on point.
- He's waiting for you.
- He who?
Isn't... isn't Pollard the mayor?
In her dreams maybe.
What's the matter, Oliver?
You look like you seen a ghost.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
So listen. I was thinking about making
a few changes to the speech,
so I figured I should
run it by you first.
This is not possible. This is...
What? Don't tell me you're scared
of a little last-minute
memorization, Oliver.
It's been a while since I've seen you.
Couple of days maybe.
You're looking at me
like it's been years.
No. You're right. A couple days.
Right. So listen. I was thinking
about adding a line about, you know,
me telling you it was
a bad idea to unmask,
but, you know, maybe a joke about how
you'd rather take it to Supermax
than take my advice.
Heh. You know? What do you think?
You know that I went to Slabside?
Uh... yeah. What's that,
your way of saying I should
have come visit more often?
Quentin, right before
I turned myself in...
Diaz shot you, right?
Oh. Yeah.
That son of a bitch almost killed me.
Almost died in the
O.R. you don't remember?
I remember it differently.
Well, the doctors called it a miracle.
I was without oxygen for so long,
I should have been 6 feet under.
Felt like I escaped
my fate or something.
Hey. There's something you need to see.
So... there's a hostage situation
at the SCPD.
The leader's demanding
to meet with the mayor.
No. No. You can't go down there.
We'll call in a special-ops team.
I'm the mayor. Nobody
does my dirty work for me.
Give my apologies to the guests.
I'm... I'm gonna come with you.
Okay, but you might want
to bring a change of clothes
because something tells me
we're gonna need the green guy.
Get the feds on the line.
Tell them I need backup
here now, right now.
What's the situation, Captain?
Armed mercs stormed my precinct,
took a dozen of my guys hostage.
How'd they get by your men?
It's a long story that I
don't have time to tell.
The only demand was
to speak to the mayor.
All right. Well, I'll go talk to them.
I appreciate that, but there is no way
I'm sending you in there.
Listen. I wore the blues a long time
before I wore this monkey suit, okay?
- I can hold my own.
- I know, sir.
It's not the point.
She's right. It's too risky.
Says the man who risks
his life every day
for this city?
Give me a vest. I'll go in there,
I'll distract the son of a bitch,
and in the meantime,
you sneak around the back
and do your thing, okay?
The longer this drags on,
the worse it gets.
Let me do this.
I'll have his back.
I want you on comms the whole time.
Sure.
This is mayor Quentin Lance.
I'm unarmed. I'm coming in.
- That's far enough.
- All right.
Just... just take it easy, okay?
Take it easy.
I'm in position. Keep him talking.
You asked for me. Here I am.
What do you want to talk about with me?
You're the mayor. You're a guy
who can make things happen.
Why don't you let a few of
these guys go while we talk?
So I can get stormed by the cops?
No, thanks. I'm not stupid.
But it would show that you
don't want anybody to get hurt
because if anybody gets hurt,
you're in real trouble.
Actually, I think you're
already in trouble.
I'm the one holding the gun.
Not for long. Put it down.
Agh. Err.
This... is... over.
This isn't over until
you stop it, Oliver.
That's the only way out.
What are you talking about?
- No!
- Quentin!
Ahh!
Tark drives the lane.
Kicks it to Aldrich in the corner for 3.
Bingo! Count it and the foul!
That's an 8-0 run by the Comets,
who have stormed all the way back
to tie it up here in the fourth quarter.
88 apiece. What a
comeback for the Comets,
and there's a timeout...
No way. It tastes the same.
I'm telling you this big
belly burger's just better.
I think he's right. This
is pre-gwespin foods merger.
Ooh, dad. What are you still doing here?
I'm late for a fundraiser.
Yeah. Really late.
You want a burger? Those
things never have good food.
Did something happen at
the SCPD headquarters?
Like what?
Never mind.
Hey, Queen. What's the difference
between a cop and the Green Arrow?
A cop doesn't need to play
dress-up to do his job.
Ha ha ha!
- Ooh! Nice reflexes, Mr. Queen.
- Thank you.
There you are. You know the
party started an hour ago, right?
I need to speak with you.
Uh, this is gonna sound crazy.
Um... I have been here
before. So have you.
What are you talking about?
About the Monitor
dropping me into some sort
of alternate reality
t-t-time loop or something,
where everything is different,
where Lance is still alive.
Oliver, Lance has always been alive.
No, he hasn't. You just don't remember
because the Monitor has done
something to people's memories,
but I... I think I know
the way out of this,
but I... I need to
stop a bomb at the SCPD.
Oliver, will you just calm down, man?
If there was a bomb,
we would know about it.
Lyla would know about it.
Lyla's a part of this.
Part of what?
Oliver seems to think that he's caught
in some sort of time loop.
If we're traveling back in time,
I'd like to revisit my 20s.
I... I need to speak with Quentin.
They mayor's waiting for me.
Yeah. How'd you know?
Mr. Mayor.
Oh. Hey, Oliver. Listen.
I, uh... I made a few last-minute
changes to the speech, so...
- We need to talk.
- Sure. Let's.
Uh, yeah. I wanted to run
these changes by you anyway.
You want to add a joke about Slabside,
about how I would rather spend time
in a Supermax than take your advice.
You steal a copy of
my speech or something?
We've had this exact
conversation already.
What are you talking about?
Fully aware of how
this is going to sound.
Quentin, I'm trapped in
some sort of... time loop,
where the same events just
keep repeating themselves.
Like "Groundhog Day."
Sure except this one
ends a lot of people dead,
including the two of us.
Okay. How can I help?
Do you actually believe me?
Oliver, I've seen one daughter die
and come back to life twice.
I've seen another come
from some other Earth.
I've seen a guy in red run
so fast he can reverse time.
This is not exactly
outside the norm, is it?
Also, I'm done learning my
lesson about doubting you
because that always
bites me in the ass. Heh.
What happens now?
Very shortly, we are gonna learn that
there is a hostage
situation at the SCPD.
They're going to insist that
they talk to you and only you.
And how does it go south?
There's a hidden explosive device
that I didn't know about
the first time through,
and judging from the blast,
it's underneath the building.
Okay. So you find it, you
keep us from going boom.
- What then?
- I break out of the loop.
Great. Out of the loop.
Here you are. There's
something you need to see.
Get the feds on the line.
Tell them I need backup now.
What's the situation, Captain?
Armed mercs stormed the precinct,
took a dozen of my guys hostage.
They have a bomb.
We already did a sweep
of the entire building.
It's not in the building.
It's underneath it.
How could you possibly know that?
I trust him. Instinct thing.
So what do you want to do?
This is Mayor Quentin Lance.
I'm unarmed. I'm coming in.
Stop right there.
Oh. It's you. Would you relax?
We are both here for the same thing.
Hey. How did you know to come down here?
I may have learned about the existence
of this place as a
part of a former career.
How did you know about the bomb?
You wouldn't believe me if I told you.
Well, actually, since you're
not going to remember anyway,
there is a crazy space god who
has me trapped in a time loop.
Yeah? Me, too.
It's my second time through.
Same. I wake up in the bunker.
I wake up in my apartment,
so clearly, the Monitor is doing this.
- You mean punishing us?
- Yeah.
We are the two people who have
royally pissed him off the most.
In Russia, I disobeyed him,
and you... you tried to destroy him.
At least we're in it together now.
I think disarming that
is the way out of here.
How long do you think
until this thing goes boom?
Oh. Your guess is as good as mine.
Quentin's upstairs buying us some time.
- Quentin... he's here?
- Yeah.
I think we just activated
some kind of failsafe.
Look. We need more time
with the next loop, Laurel.
It would probably help if we
found each other faster next time.
There's a party at the
Palmer Tech building.
- Meet me there.
- Are we talking formal wear or...
Tark drives the lane.
Kicks it to Aldrich in the corner for 3.
Bingo!
No way. It's the same.
I'm telling you. This big
belly burger is just better.
Guess you realized you're late.
Something like that.
Hey, Queen. What's the difference
between a cop and the Green Arrow?
Cop doesn't need to play
dress-up to do his job.
Sorry.
Mr. Mayor.
Hey, Oliver. Listen. I made
a few last-minute changes
to the speech.
And you figured you should
run them by me first.
Yeah, exactly.
Hey, baby girl.
I didn't think you were gonna make it.
Me either.
You okay, honey?
I'm just really happy to see you.
Oh. I'm happy to see you, too.
Though I got to say I'm glad you left
the black lipstick at home tonight.
You know that I'm Earth-2 Laurel.
Who else would you be?
Look. I'm really sorry to interrupt,
but you and I need to go.
You're coming with
us. We need your help.
What do you mean there's a bomb?
I know how to stop it,
but you have to trust me.
I'm gonna need a vest.
Not this time, Quentin.
This is Mayor Quentin Lance.
You wanted to talk. Let's talk.
The detonator operates on
an oscillating frequency.
If we can find the right one,
we should be able to disrupt it.
Vincent, listen to me.
I know you don't really want to do this.
And I know that if you don't get in here
these men are gonna die.
I have an idea.
We did it.
Okay. Fine. You did it.
We stopped the bomb. What the
hell are we still doing here?
I don't... I...
We must have missed something.
- No!
No! No!
Tark drives the lane.
Kicks it to Aldrich in the corner for 3.
Bingo!
All right. Quentin's
death is the reset point,
which means that
saving him must be the key.
What kind of sick game
is the Monitor playing?
I don't know. We need to find out
who is behind this hostage situation.
If it's just about killing
Quentin, then why plant a bomb?
It seems like a lot of extra work.
Maybe whoever is behind this wants
their involvement kept a secret.
Do you really think there's
a larger conspiracy here?
Those were mercenaries, Laurel,
which means that
somebody had to hire them.
Great, and I'm sure they're
gonna be really easy to find, too.
Any idea where to start?
Let's get Quentin out of here.
Why don't you take him to the bunker?
What about you?
I'm gonna go take a look at that bomb.
Laurel, I didn't think
you'd make it tonight.
I am really not in
the mood for small talk
with the Monitor's bestie.
- Excuse me.
- It turns out tranq darts,
they don't feel so good.
I told you that was a
big misunderstanding.
Well, understand this.
The second I get out
of this sadistic "edge
of tomorrow" reboot,
I am going to make sure to tell everyone
exactly what kind of
traitor you really are.
Laurel, I truly have no idea
what you're talking about,
but whatever it is
you're feeling toward me,
that's on you.
Thank you for the advice, Dr. Phil,
and now here's some for you.
The next time you decide
to double-cross someone,
don't pick a woman who
specializes in revenge.
You're threatening me.
Yes. Yes, I am, but don't worry.
You won't remember anyway,
and by the way, I pull off
the short hair way better than you do.
What are you doing here?
Well, word came down that the
Green Arrow called in a bomb threat,
so I thought to myself,
"How did he know about that,
and why didn't he call me?"
Because the Monitor has
me trapped in a time loop.
Already told you that.
Okay. Definitely not the
answer I was expecting,
but if the Monitor's
involved, anything is possible.
Any idea how to break out?
I have to save Quentin's life.
I thought that this was the key to it,
but I'm not finding anything.
Well, has to be something.
No case is unsolvable.
This might be impossible.
Well, you'll figure it out.
I do wish I was as sure as you are.
You want to know what
makes me so sure? You.
You, Oliver. You always figure it out.
You never stop fighting.
You never give up.
You always keep at it.
Why should this be any different?
Whatever version this is of you,
you still give the best advice.
- Yeah. I'm flattered.
- Well, A.R.G.U.S. has
some more sophisticated
analytical equipment.
Any chance you can get me in there?
Yeah. I bet I can make a few calls.
So you're telling me we're in some kind
of a alternate reality based on
the plot of a Bill Murray movie?
Well, I was gonna go with a
tom cruise flick but basically.
Also just really glad
that you believe me.
Well, it's not the craziest
thing you ever told me.
I mean, I'm just glad this Monitor guy
just kept me as mayor, you know?
What? What's that look?
It... it's just that, uh, in my world
or in the real world, uh,
you're not mayor anymore.
Really? Ohh. Pollard.
She always had it in for me. Heh.
There something else?
Laurel. Sweetheart, I
always know when you're
hiding something from me.
Please tell me. What is it?
It... it's a year and a half ago
when Diaz... when he shot you
in... in the real reality or whatever,
you... you didn't exactly, um...
I didn't recover.
No. No. You died to save me.
Best way I could have gone.
What?! I'm sorry. I basically just
told you you're a ghost, and
you're completely ok with that?
It doesn't... it doesn't faze
you? You're completely calm?
I always felt like I
cheated death with that one.
Guess that's because I didn't.
Fate's just tricky like that.
- It's Oliver.
- Yeah?
He figure out who wants me dead?
Not yet, but he did
figure out the location
of the mercs' hideout.
Okay. So we better go.
How'd you find this place?
Uh, we analyzed the bomb
and traced the chemical signature
back to this building.
Interesting.
What?
Your mouth but Felicity's words.
It still doesn't tell
us who hired these bozos.
Maybe this will help.
Bomb!
Ohh.
Lyla, what the hell are you doing?
Helping you. You're
missing the point, Oliver.
- What?
- You can't fight this.
Lyla!
Passes it quickly over to the right.
Tark drives the lane.
Kicks it to Aldrich in the corner for 3.
Bingo! Count it and the foul!
No sign of Lyla anywhere. You?
John just told me she got called away
on a last-minute A.R.G.U.S. mission,
meaning she's never even been here.
Maybe the Monitor deleted
her for going rogue.
Heh. Wouldn't that be so, so sad?
She's clearly helping him.
There's no reason for her
to switch sides right now.
So why reveal her
hand? It makes no sense.
You spoke with her.
Was there anything, anything at all
in the conversation that stood out?
She said how I feel
towards her was on me
like it's my fault that I'm stuck here.
I told you the Monitor's punishing us.
I'm not so sure.
We've had to watch Quentin
die over and over again,
and we can't save him.
If I had to design
hell, this would be it.
But right before Lyla disappeared,
she told me she was trying to help me.
She also told you you can't fight this.
It seems pretty clear to me
that we're not supposed to win.
The first time that I met Mar Novu,
it felt... it felt the same.
It was like I was put in a
situation where there was no way out,
but it was a test, Laurel.
It was a test just like
I think that this is.
- A test of what?
- I don't know,
but there is a way out of here,
and I'm gonna find it.
- You just never give up, do you?
- No, I don't.
Are you with me?
Fine.
What's our play?
We go back to the mercs' hideout.
We know where the danger is this time,
so we can do things differently.
You grab Quentin, and
I'll meet you there.
Okay.
So you're telling me
we've been here once
and still came back for more?
At least now we know what not to do.
Okay.
That should disable the bomb.
Well, I certainly hope
so because I am getting
sick and tired of getting blown up.
Okay. So now what?
We find out who hired
those mercs to kill you.
Money leads to a man
named Anderson White.
Never heard of him.
Looks like he's been accused
of not too many nice things...
Money laundering, racketeering.
Doesn't explain why he'd want me dead.
Well, that's what we're gonna find out.
CEO of a company named Global Solutions.
They have a warehouse down by the docks.
Let's go.
We need to find white.
No! No! I got you.
Come on, come on.
I'll take care of the rest.
Err! Ugh.
Oh, I'm sorry, baby girl.
Looks like we lost this round.
No. No! I am not letting you die again.
- It's too late.
- No.
It... it's... it's time to say good-bye.
I'm not giving up on you, Quentin.
Quentin, I am not giving up on you.
You never gave up on me.
You believed in me when nobody else did.
Well, that's what dads do. They believe.
I want you to know that you
are the reason that
I'm trying to be a hero.
It's because of you.
Sweetheart... you are a hero.
You are.
Thank you.
Thank you. I never had
the chance to tell you
how much you mean to me.
- Well...
- Thank you.
I think you just did.
I love you. I love you.
Good-bye.
Damn it.
All right. Okay. All right, Laurel.
We fix this next time. We'll fix it.
I can't do this again.
I'm done, Oliver.
All I have ever wanted was a chance
to say good-bye to Quentin.
Now I have.
Tark drives the lane.
Kicks it to Aldrich in the corner for 3.
Bingo! Count it and the foul!
Laurel?
Laurel!
She's not here.
- Where is she?
- Gone.
What did you... what did you do, Lyla?
I didn't do anything. Laurel
got what she needed from this.
I don't have time for these games, Lyla,
so whatever this is, get
me out of here right now!
I can't do that, Oliver.
Mar Movu needs you to understand
no good will come from struggle.
The only way to win is
to accept the inevitable.
I have no idea what that means.
Learn that, and this will end.
Lyla!
So if me dying is the problem,
maybe bringing me into the
lion's den isn't so smart.
Couldn't think of a better
way to keep you safe.
Yeah. That makes sense.
Huh!
Ah-ah-ah-ah. Unless you
want a hole for a head.
Are you Anderson White?
You really think Mr.
White would be here?
He ordered a hit on my friend. Why?
I guess the clock's ticking.
Looks like a list of hits.
And clients. Coded and anonymous.
White's just the middleman.
A CEO with a healthy
side business brokering
hits for wealthy asshats.
All right. We're back to square one.
We have no idea how deep
this rabbit hole goes.
We got to get going.
Unh!
Get down! Get down!
Hey. You okay? You all right? Okay.
No time. Come on.
Come on.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Whoa!
Go, go, go, go, go, go!
Go, go, go.
Let's go.
Get down, get down!
Over there!
Ohh. Oh, it's the last one.
How many arrows you got left?
Not enough.
Oh, boy. Aren't we the couple?
We are gonna find a way out of this.
There has to be a way to fix it,
and we are gonna find it, Quentin.
It doesn't matter how many
times. We're gonna find it!
Heh heh. Yeah? Sure. What's it gonna be,
60 times, 100 times?
It's gonna be however
many times it takes!
You know, getting hunted like this
in a space like this is kind of like
what I was doing to
you all those years ago.
Remember?
Ohh. Oof.
Sort of makes sense I'd go out
like this now, don't you think?
Would you please just
save your strength.
For what?
Oliver, you take care of these guys,
there'll be more behind them,
there will be more behind them.
There is no saving me from this!
Okay? You ever think that's the point?
Maybe you're not supposed to.
I'm not giving up...
And you're not giving up either.
Oh, no, no, no. I'm not giving up.
Maybe I'm giving in.
You see, I've been outrunning
death for a while now.
The siege, the island,
but when Diaz shot
me, that felt different
like I was finally at the end,
and I made my peace with that.
And maybe it's time you did, too.
It looks like fate's knocking.
Just... just...
You just get ready to move.
I'll see you on the other side, Oliver.
Quentin.
Tark drives the lane.
Kicks it to Aldrich in the corner for 3.
Bingo! Count it and the foul!
That's an 8-0 run by the Comets,
who have stormed all the way back
to tie it up here in the fourth quarter.
88 apiece. What a
comeback for the Comets,
and there's a timeout...
No way. It tastes the same.
Dad, what are you still doing here?
Hey, guys. I'm just
heading out the door.
Wanted to let you know, all of you know
what a... just what a gift
getting to know you all has been.
Dad, you're going to a fundraiser.
It's not like you're going into war.
Heh heh.
Although I guess I can
see the similarities.
I think he's talking about Crisis.
I'm just really proud of all you guys.
I'm really proud.
I got to go.
Dad...
You're gonna be fine.
So are you.
All of you will be
whatever happens.
Hey, Queen. What's the difference
between a cop... hey!
Quentin, excuse me.
Yeah.
What's the matter, Oliver?
You look like you've seen a ghost.
Maybe I did.
May I speak with you for a second?
Sure.
Uh, yeah, you want
to go over the speech?
Because I was thinking
about adding a few lines.
I have a question for you.
Sure.
Back when I was running
around as the hood,
you were trying to arrest me.
- You remember that?
- Heh heh heh.
Ah. Yeah. The good, old days.
How could I ever forget?
The question is...
What made you decide that I wasn't
your enemy anymore?
What changed your mind?
Heh. Oh, you know, my daughters for one.
Because I didn't raise dummies,
and, uh, you know, if
they were okay with you,
then I figured I should be, too.
- Yeah.
- They trusted me,
and you trusted them.
Yeah. They got me to
listen to what I always knew
in my gut, that we were on the same side
and fighting for the same goal,
and it just took me
a while to get there.
Sorry.
It's okay.
Oliver, is there any particular reason
for this trip down memory lane?
Yeah.
God, I've been hanging on to something.
Someone told me just recently that,
uh... it's about time
I made peace with it.
Okay. Sounds like a smart someone.
Yeah.
Oh, I shouldn't have to
say good-bye to you again.
Good-bye?
Evening's just getting started.
Yeah.
Thank you, Quentin for everything.
Mr. Mayor.
We're gonna see each
other again, Oliver.
Mr. Mayor!
Ahem.
I hope so.
Congratulations, Oliver.
Now you understand.
I couldn't change Quentin's fate.
I can't change mine either, can I?
No. I'm sorry.
Why did the Monitor go to all
of this trouble just to...
Just to prove a point?
You've always been a man who needed to
see things for himself.
Telling you wouldn't have been enough.
How long have you worked for him?
A while.
You lied to us, Lyla.
You...
You lied to John.
Keeping this from John has been
the hardest thing I've ever had to do.
Then why do it?
The same reason you
left Felicity and Mia
in that cabin... to protect my family.
Do you honestly believe that working
with the Monitor is
the best way to do that?
It's the only way.
The Crisis is coming.
There is no stopping it.
All we can do is try to survive it.
Okay. Help me out here, Lyla.
I don't even know what it is.
I know, but you will... soon.
What I can tell you
is there is an evil
coming that is greater
than anything we've ever had to face.
Can we stop it?
I don't know...
But you are the only chance we have.
So everything I've done
from the moment I left that cabin,
this has all been some...
Bigger part of a test?
He needed to be sure you were ready.
He's just been sending
me on useless missions.
They weren't useless.
The Dwarf Star particles, Dr. Wong,
even the antimatter weapon,
they all have a purpose,
just not the one you were expecting.
Why did he involve my children?
Time is a gift.
What now?
You complete your final mission.
I'll see you there.
Ohh.
Where are we?
You okay?
I have a killer headache.
The last thing that I
remember is Quentin...
dying in that warehouse.
I was wearing these on the roof
when we got tranqed, so
does that mean that...
We got out.
How?
We learned our lessons.
I got out after I said good-bye.
Why would the Monitor let
me see Quentin one last time?
It was a reward for not betraying me.
Didn't really think
rewards were his brand.
No. We were wrong about him.
And Lyla was right?
That's annoying.
So why did you have to
learn to let Lance go?
Because deep down, I still believed
that I could fight my fate.
Now I know I can't.
Lyla said we had one last thing to do,
one final mission.
I can't wait to find out what that is.
Where that is.
We're not in Star City anymore.
Dad.
You okay?
Where the hell are we?
We're on Lian Yu.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --