MY NAME IS OLIVER QUEEN.
AFTER 5 YEARS IN HELL,
I RETURNED HOME
WITH ONLY ONE GOAL...
TO SAVE MY CITY.
TODAY, I FIGHT THAT WAR
ON TWO FRONTS.
BY DAY, I LEAD STAR CITY
AS ITS MAYOR,
BUT BY NIGHT,
I AM SOMEONE ELSE.
I AM...SOMETHING ELSE.
I AM THE GREEN ARROW.
PREVIOUSLY ON "ARROW"...
FOLLOW ME OR DIE.
UNH!
HELLO, MR. QUEEN.
MY NAME IS TALIA.
I'VE BEEN
LOOKING FOR YOU.
AS SOON AS I'M OUT
OF HERE, WALKER
WILL CONCOCT
SOME REASON TO PUT
A BULLET IN MY HEAD.
I THINK I'M GONNA HAVE
TO PROSECUTE THIS ONE MYSELF.
IT COULD TAKE A WHILE.
I HAVEN'T KEPT
MY PROMISE TO LAUREL.
YOU'RE GONNA TRAIN
A NEW BLACK CANARY?
I THINK THAT SOMEWHERE
OUT THERE THERE IS
A WOMAN WORTHY
OF LAUREL'S LEGACY.
[SONIC SCREAM]
NOW ALL WE GOT TO
DO IS FIND HER.
PROTESTS CONTINUE INTO
THE FINAL COUNTDOWN
FOR TONIGHT'S IGNITION
OF STAR LABS'
CONTROVERSIAL
PARTICLE ACCELERATOR.
STAR LABS FOUNDER AND CEO
HARRISON WELLS
PROMISES A NEW ERA
OF SCIENTIFIC ADVANCEMENT
IS AT HAND.
WOULD YOU LOOK
AT THAT?
FUTURE'S GETTING BRIGHTER
EVERY DAY.
WHAT DO YOU THINK, BABE?
YOU A FAN OF PROGRESS?
WHY DON'T YOU JUST
PUT A BULLET IN MY HEAD
AND BE DONE WITH IT?
OR MAYBE YOU DON'T HAVE
THE SACK TO PULL THE TRIGGER.
I WAS GONNA PLAY
ANOTHER HAND,
LET YOU REST SOME,
BUT LAY DOWN A CHALLENGE
LIKE THAT, WHAT'S A GUY
GONNA DO?
I'M GONNA GET
WHAT I NEED FROM YOU
OR MAYBE ONE
OF THOSE MOLARS BACK THERE.
MAN: FORGET HER.
HEY, TINA.
YOU'RE NOT LOOKING
TOO GOOD,
BUT I GOT SOMETHING HERE
THAT MIGHT PUT A SMILE
ON YOUR FACE.
LOOK WHO WE GOT HERE.
OH, MY GOD.
VINNY.
I'M SORRY, TINA.
MAN: AW, SO SWEET.
I THOUGHT YOU TWO
WERE JUST COP BUDDIES,
BUT...YOU CAN
TELL ME, VIN.
YOU'RE TAPPING THAT
SWEET ASS, AREN'T YOU?
HA HA HA!
HEH HEH HEH.
I WASN'T SURE WHICH
ONE OF YOU TO KILL.
THANKS FOR MAKING UP
MY MIND FOR ME.
GET THE TARP.
TINA: NO, PLEASE, PLEASE,
PLEASE DON'T HURT HIM!
SHUT UP!
REPORTER ON TV: WAIT.
WE ARE NOW BEING TOLD
TO EVACUATE THE FACILITY.
THE STORM MAY HAVE CAUSED
A MALFUNCTION
TO THE PRIMARY
COOLING SYSTEM.
OFFICIALS ARE NOW...
TINA: SEAN, I...
I AM BEGGING YOU.
PLEASE.
[ENERGY CRACKLING]
NOOOOOOO!
[SONIC SCREAM]
OLIVER: NOPE.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN "NOPE"?
-DID YOU EVEN READ HER RESUME?
-YEAH, I DID.
SO YOU KNOW SHE FLEW
600 SORTIES OVER IRAQ,
LAUNCHED A PROGRAM
FOR INNER CITY KIDS
TO GET INTO FLIGHT SCHOOL
AS A WAY OUT OF POVERTY,
PLUS SHE'S GOT SKILLS
IN KRAV MAGA,
AND A THIRD-DEGREE
BLACK BELT.
CURTIS: IF "TOP GUN"
HERE'S A MAYBE,
HOW THE HELL DID I
EVEN GET ON THE TEAM?
DON'T ANSWER THAT.
LOOK. FINDING
A NEW BLACK CANARY ISN'T
JUST ABOUT
REVIEWING RESUMES.
IT'S A...IT'S
A FEEL THING.
WELL, I FEEL LIKE
WE'RE BUSTING OUR ASSES
TO FIND NEW CANDIDATES,
AND YOU KEEP
SHOOTING THEM DOWN.
I PROMISED LAUREL THAT
I WOULD CARRY ON HER LEGACY.
I JUST DON'T WANT
BLACK SIREN TO BE ALL
THAT'S LEFT OF HER.
WELL, WHAT ABOUT
THIS WOMAN?
ALLISON SLATER. OK.
SHE'S A DECORATED
CIA OFFICER
WHO ALSO HAPPENS TO BE
A WORLD CHAMPION IN JUDO.
OH. NO. OK.
WHAT ABOUT TARA MICHELE?
ARMY SPECIAL OPS,
BUT THEN SHE DECIDED
TO OPEN A CLINIC DOWNTOWN
TO OFFER FREE HEALTH CARE
TO THE HOMELESS.
OK. WELL, I WILL
KEEP DIGGING.
OK. HOLD ON.
WHAT ABOUT THIS ONE?
THIS WOMAN GOT
HER ENGINEERING PH.D.
AT AGE 20,
WON GOLD IN THE KARATE
AT THE OLYMPICS,
TURNED DOWN OFFERS
FROM THE NSA AND ARGUS
TO JOIN NASA
AS AN ASTRONAUT BY DAY
WHILE AT NIGHT SHE
SECRETLY PROTECTS
THE CITIZENS OF HOUSTON
AS, GET THIS,
A NINJA VIGILANTE.
OH, AND SHE WORKS
SOUP KITCHENS ON SATURDAYS
AND RESCUES PUPPIES
ON SUNDAYS.
ASTRONAUT NINJA.
YOU'RE MAKING THAT UP.
HE DID. KARATE WON'T BE
AN OLYMPIC SPORT UNTIL 2020.
FINE. YOU GOT ME.
THIS IS JUST SOME WOMAN
WHO TEACHES PRESCHOOL
IN THE GLADES,
BUT MY POINT
STILL STANDS.
THAT POINT BEING?
THAT NO MATTER
HOW AMAZING THEY ARE
NO ONE'S GONNA BE
GOOD ENOUGH FOR YOU.
FELICITY: BECAUSE YOU KEEP
COMPARING THEM TO LAUREL,
WHICH IS
AN IMPOSSIBLE STANDARD
YOU MIGHT WANT TO
CONSIDER LOOSENING.
OLIVER: WE JUST NEED
TO KEEP LOOKING.
WE NEED TO THINK
OUTSIDE THE BOX.
HOW FAR OUTSIDE THE BOX
ARE WE TALKING HERE?
ARE WE TALKING WAY
OUTSIDE THE BOX,
LIKE, URBAN LEGENDS
OUTSIDE?
BECAUSE IF WE ARE, I THINK
I MIGHT HAVE SOMETHING.
FELICITY: WAIT. WHAT DO
YOU MEAN "URBAN LEGEND"?
I MEAN...HER.
RENE: BY "HER,"
YOU MEAN WHO?
WELL, ACTUALLY,
I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT
HER NAME IS,
BUT ACCORDING
TO THE CHAT ROOMS
I VISITED,
SHE'S A KICKASS WOMAN
WHO APPEARS OUT OF NOWHERE
AND SAVES
CRIME VICTIMS.
-IN STAR CITY?
-ALL OVER AMERICA ACTUALLY,
AND GET THIS...
SHE EVEN HAS A CRY
LIKE A CANARY CRY.
SHE'S A META
WITH THE SAME POWER
AS EARTH-2 LAUREL?
IF THAT ISN'T
BASHERT, I DON'T
KNOW WHAT IS.
-WHAT?
-BASHERT MEANS FATE, DESTINY.
FELICITY: ACCORDING
TO THE ARGUS DATABASE
I JUST HACKED,
SIGHTINGS STARTED 3 YEARS AGO
IN CENTRAL CITY.
THAT IS RIGHT
WHEN STAR LABS EXPLODED.
AND SHE EVEN HAS
A BLACK LEATHER JACKET
AND EVERYTHING.
ONLY THING THAT'S
REALLY MISSING IS
THE BLOND HAIR,
AND YOU CAN FIX THAT
WITH A WIG.
[CELL PHONE VIBRATES]
I HAVE TO HANDLE
SOMETHING FOR JOHN.
LET'S SEE IF THIS
URBAN LEGEND IS THE REAL DEAL,
AND CALL ME
WHEN YOU HAVE SOMETHING.
[ELETRONIC LOCK WHIRRING]
-HEY.
I JUST GOT A TEXT FROM ADRIAN.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT IT'S ABOUT?
MAYBE THEY FIGURED OUT
HOW PROMETHEUS FAKED
LYLA'S VOICE TO GET ME
OUT OF THE BUNKER
AND INTO HERE.
I'M LESS CONCERNED
WITH HOW YOU GOT IN HERE
AND MORE CONCERNED
WITH GETTING YOU OUT AGAIN.
GENTLEMEN,
SORRY I'M LATE.
HOW YOU HOLDING UP?
WELL, WALKER'S
GONNA HAVE CUSTODY
OF ME IN A WEEK, SO...
WOW. AS SOON AS WALKER
GETS HIS HANDS ON JOHN,
HE'S GONNA THROW HIM
INTO A HOLE.
MAYBE NOT.
I'VE GOT A BUDDY
AT THE NATIONAL
SECURITY AGENCY.
TURNS OUT THEY HAVE
GENERAL WALKER
UNDER INVESTIGATION
AND WERE PUTTING TOGETHER
QUITE THE CASE...
WIRE TRANSFERS AND SOME
KEYHOLE SATELLITE IMAGES
OF HIS MOVEMENTS
WITH THE NUCLEAR TRIGGER.
THAT'S ENOUGH
TO EXONERATE JOHN.
EXCEPT I DON'T
LIKE THE WAY YOU
JUST SAID, "WERE...
BUILDING A CASE"
JUST NOW.
WALKER HAS FRIENDS
IN HIGH PLACES.
MANAGED TO GET
THE INVESTIGATION
SLOW-ROLLED.
BUT THE FILE
STILL EXISTS.
I MADE A FOIA REQUEST,
BUT SEEING AS ALL THIS
IS CLASSIFIED,
THAT COULD TAKE MONTHS,
MAYBE EVEN YEARS.
THAT'S TIME WE
DON'T HAVE.
I'M SORRY I DON'T
HAVE BETTER NEWS.
OLIVER: NO, ADRIAN.
YOU HAVE GONE
ABOVE AND BEYOND ALREADY.
-THANK YOU.
-YEAH.
WELL, FELICITY'S
GOING TO REALLY ENJOY
HACKING THE NSA.
YOU MEAN, AFTER SHE'S
BROUGHT YOU A HUNDRED
BLACK CANARY CANDIDATES
FOR YOU TO SAY NO TO?
YOU'RE NOT THE ONLY ONE
WHO VISITS, OLIVER.
JOHN, I UNDERSTAND
WHAT I PROMISED LAUREL.
NOW THAT WE'RE ACTIVELY
DOING IT,
TRYING TO REPLACE HER,
IT JUST...
FEELS WRONG.
SHE DIDN'T WANT YOU
TO FIND SOMEONE
TO REPLACE HER,
JUST SOMEONE TO TAKE
ON THE MANTLE,
AND FROM WHERE
I'M SITTING,
THAT'S TWO
VERY DIFFERENT THINGS.
SLEEPING BEAUTY AWAKES.
WHERE AM I?
SOMEPLACE SAFE.
I HAVE TO GET BACK
TO THE BRATVA.
WHY? SO THEY CAN
FINISH KILLING YOU?
THAT WAS GREGOR.
I HAVE ALLIES THERE.
I THINK YOU'LL COME
TO DISCOVER CIRCUMSTANCES
WITHIN THE BRATVA ARE
A BIT MORE COMPLEX
THAN YOU THOUGHT.
WHY DID YOU SAVE ME?
WELL, FROM WHAT
I COULD TELL,
YOU NEEDED RESCUING.
[GROANS]
WHERE'D YOU GET THAT?
WASN'T HARD.
SNEAKING PAST A BUNCH
OF OAFISH BRATVA IS HARDLY
A TEST OF MY SKILLS.
WHY DID YOU DO THAT?
SHIPWRECKED
ON LIAN YU,
FLED TO HONG KONG,
THE OMEGA VIRUS,
SHADOWSPIRE,
AND NOW YOU'RE MIXED UP
WITH THE BRATVA,
BUT ALONG THE WAY,
YOU WENT BACK TO HOME
TO STARLING CITY,
BUT YOU COULDN'T BEAR
TO REVEAL YOURSELF
TO YOUR FAMILY.
HOW DO YOU
KNOW THIS?
I DID MY HOMEWORK.
WHAT MAKES ME
SO INTERESTING?
AGH! UNH! UGH!
UNH!
YOU WEAR THE HOOD
OF ONE OF MY STUDENTS...
YAO FEI GULONG.
YOU GET MY TEXT
ABOUT JOHN?
IF THERE IS ANY
TRACE OF THE FILE
THAT DIG NEEDS,
IT'S GONNA BE BURIED
BEHIND SOME SERIOUS
FIREWALLS.
ACTUALLY FIREWALLS
DON'T EVEN BEGIN
TO EXPLAIN IT.
IT'S GONNA BE MORE
LIKE FIRECASTLES
OR FIREMOUNTAINS.
HOW DID YOU KNOW
WHERE TO START?
ALL THAT I TOLD YOU
WAS THAT CHASE MIGHT
HAVE SOMETHING.
YEAH, YEAH, AND THEN
I HACKED HIS LAPTOP.
[SIGHS]
SAVING DIG IS GONNA BREAK
AT LEAST 12 FEDERAL LAWS.
HACKING YOUR D.A.
IS JUST SMALL BALL.
PLUS, YOU ARE THE MAYOR.
YOU CAN PARDON ME.
-ACTUALLY, I CAN'T.
-IT DOESN'T MATTER
BECAUSE I AM
HAVING FUN.
I HAVEN'T DONE
A GOOD, OLD GRAB
GOVERNMENT SECRETS
KIND OF HACK
IN A REALLY LONG TIME,
AND IT'S A GREAT
CHANGE OF PACE,
AND IT FEELS AWESOME,
AND IT WILL KEEP ME
BUSY WHILE YOU'RE GONE.
I'M...I'M GOING
SOMEWHERE.
MAYBE HUB CITY.
WE'RE THINKING THAT'S
WHERE THE NEW BLACK CANARY
IS HANGING OUT.
YEAH. LET'S NOT
CALL HER THAT
JUST YET.
I'D LIKE TO SEE
HER IN THE FIELD
AT LEAST FIRST.
ASK, AND YOU SHALL
RECEIVE.
I WAS ABLE TO TRACK
DOWN CELL PHONE FOOTAGE
OF HER LATEST ACT
OF HEROISM...
HEROINEISM?
HEROISM. ANYWAY,
TAKE A LOOK.
THE VIDEO ISN'T
CLEAR ENOUGH FOR
FACIAL RECOG,
BUT SHE'S REAL ALL RIGHT.
I'VE WATCHED IT,
LIKE, 10 TIMES.
THE WOMAN CAN FIGHT.
[SONIC SCREAM]
SHE CAN FOCUS THE SOUND
BETTER THAN BLACK SIREN,
AND SHE IS MORE SKILLED
AT HAND-TO-HAND.
THIS IS ALMOST LIKE...
WHAT WAS THAT WORD
THAT YOU USED?
-BASHERT.
-YEAH, THAT.
IT ALMOST SOUNDS LIKE
YOU'D BE WILLING
TO GIVE HER A LOOK.
CALL RENE. WE'RE
GOING TO HUB CITY.
[CAR DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR SHUTS]
OLIVER: STOP.
HA! WOW!
COSTUME WAREHOUSE
HAVING A FIRE SALE
I DIDN'T KNOW ABOUT?
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
YOU'RE A VIGILANTE
AND A META-HUMAN,
AND FOR THE PAST 3 YEARS,
YOU'VE BEEN WORKING ALONE.
WE HAVE A PROPOSITION
FOR YOU.
OH. SORRY.
YOU WERE DOING FINE.
YOU...YOU...YOU TAKE IT.
YEAH.
WE'D LIKE YOU
TO JOIN US.
WE CAN GIVE YOU A HOME,
A TEAM, AND A PLACE
TO BETTER TRAIN THE USE
OF YOUR POWER.
I CAN TAKE CARE
OF MYSELF.
OH, AND, UH, IF YOU
GET IN MY WAY,
I'LL SEND THE 3 OF YOU
BACK TO STAR CITY
WITH YOUR NUTS
IN A SLING.
I THOUGHT THAT
WENT PRETTY GOOD.
HEY, MAN. WHAT ARE
WE STILL DOING
AROUND THIS DUMP?
LEATHER JACKET LADY
MADE IT SEEM PRETTY CLEAR
ABOUT US SCREWING OFF.
WHEN HAVE YOU EVER
KNOWN ME TO GIVE UP
THAT EASILY?
NEVER. THE ANSWER
TO THAT IS NEVER.
OH, THAT MIGHT
HAVE BEEN IMPLIED.
WE'RE NOT GONNA FIND
A BETTER CANDIDATE.
ANY PROGRESS
ON THE FACIAL RECOGNITION
FROM THE BODY CAMS?
SORRY, BUT
THE WI-FI IN HERE IS
INCREDIBLY SLOW.
WELL, YOU TAKE YOUR TIME.
GOT 3 PATTIES
AND 3 SLICES
OF CHEDDAR TO GO.
THAT'S DISGUSTING.
OK. ACTUALLY GOT IT.
OUR SCREAMING
SONIC LADY HAS A
NAME...TINA BOLAND,
FORMERLY
OF THE CCPD.
THAT TRACKS.
SHE WAS IN CENTRAL CITY
WHEN THE PARTICLE
ACCELERATOR EXPLODED.
AFTER THAT, SHE
WENT OFF THE GRID,
WHICH MEANS THAT
WE HAVE NO WAY
OF FINDING HER.
YES, WE DO.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
CAPTAIN SINGH.
I NEED INFORMATION.
WHO IS THIS?
IT'S
THE GREEN ARROW.
OR SOME NUT JOB
WITH A VOICE MODULATOR.
YOU WANT HELP,
I'M GONNA NEED PROOF.
VERY CLEVER. FINE.
WHAT DO YOU WANT TO KNOW?
TINA BOLAND.
SHE WAS CCPD.
-WHAT HAPPENED TO HER?
-NOTHING BUT TRAGEDY THERE.
SHE WENT DEEP UNDERCOVER,
AND HER PARTNER GOT
KILLED IN ACTION.
HER PARTNER'S NAME
WAS...
VINCENT SOBEL.
YEAH. TINA QUIT
THE FORCE THE DAY
AFTER HIS FUNERAL,
AND WE HAVEN'T HEARD
FROM HER SINCE.
SHE IN SOME KIND
OF TROUBLE?
NOT SURE YET.
YOU GET ANYTHING,
GIVE ME A CALL.
I'VE ALWAYS HAD
A SOFT SPOT FOR BOLAND.
SHE'S A GOOD KID.
WILL DO.
LOOKS LIKE OUR TINA IS TRYING
TO AVENGE HER FORMER PARTNER.
WHICH MEANS WE
HAVE A LEAD.
UGH!
YOU TRAINED YAO FEI?
HOW'S THAT POSSIBLE?
YOU'RE HALF HIS AGE.
DON'T YOU KNOW IT'S
IMPROPER TO TALK
ABOUT A WOMAN'S AGE?
LET'S JUST SAY IT'S
A FAMILY SECRET.
SO YOU FOUND ME
BECAUSE OF YAO FEI.
[COUGHS]
CONGRATULATIONS.
YAO FEI'S GONE.
I FOUND YOU BECAUSE
THE WORLD NEEDS
PEOPLE LIKE YOU.
THE MAN WHO SURVIVED
ALL THIS
IS DESTINED FOR SO MUCH
MORE THAN PLAYING
GANGSTER IN RUSSIA.
YOU KNOW, IF YOU KNEW
ME SO WELL,
YOU'D KNOW THAT I
MADE PROMISE.
A PROMISE, YES,
TO GET REVENGE
ON KONSTANTIN KOVAR.
I HAVE SOMETHING
THAT WILL HELP.
THAT IS MISHA YURIEVICH,
A BLACK MARKET SMUGGLER
WITH A PARTICULAR
SPECIALITY...
YOUNG GIRLS.
YOU MIGHT GUESS
HIS TOP CUSTOMER.
KOVAR.
WE TAKE DOWN YURIEVICH,
AND THAT LEAVES KOVAR
WITHOUT HIS KEY
REVENUE STREAM.
WE?
YOU SHOULD BE HONORED
I'M OFFERING MY SERVICES.
LET ME HELP YOU DISPOSE
OF YURIEVICH,
THEN YOU WILL HEAR ME
OUT WITH WHAT I HAVE TO SAY.
AT THE VERY LEAST,
YOU'LL BE DEALING
A MAJOR BLOW
TO YOUR ENEMY.
[TYPING]
OH, THANK GOD.
YOU ARE A LIFESAVER.
YEAH. WELL, I FIGURE
YOU GOT TO GET
YOUR SHARE
OF FAST-FOOD
BEFORE THEY
LOCK YOU UP
IN LOMPOC FOR
HACKING THE NSA.
LOMPOC DOESN'T HOUSE
FEMALE INMATES.
THEY'D PROBABLY SEND
ME TO HAZELTON...
OR THEY WOULD
IF THERE WAS
ANYTHING TO HACK.
-UH, YOU LOST ME.
-THE FILE CONTAINING
ALL THE DIRT
ON GENERAL WALKER,
IT'S GONE, SCRUBBED.
SO WHAT DOES
THAT MEAN?
WELL, IT MEANS THAT JOHN
IS BACK TO BEING
TOTALLY SCREWED.
THERE'S NO SIGN
OF BOLAND.
SURE THIS IS
THE RIGHT SPOT,
MR. TERRIFIC?
AM I STILL MR. TERRIFIC
IF I'M ON COMMS
AND NOT IN UNIFORM?
HEH HEH!
ANYWAY, YEAH,
I CROSS-REFERENCED
THE ATM WITHDRAWALS
AND PINGS
FROM HER BURNER CELL PHONE.
DETECTIVE BOLAND IS HERE.
ROOM 511...
SHOULD BE STRAIGHT
DOWN THE HALL.
WHOA.
HOMEGIRL CLEARLY NEVER
MET A TRASHCAN.
EVEN THOUGH SHE'S
NOT ON THE FORCE,
SHE'S STILL PLAYING
DETECTIVE.
NO, SHE'S NOT PLAYING.
SHE'S OUT FOR BLOOD.
THAT'S HER DEAD PARTNER.
MR. TERRIFIC, ARE
YOU SEEING THESE NAMES
ON THE BODY CAMS?
ALREADY RUNNING THEM.
[MAN SHOUTING]
-DROP THE HAMMER.
-GET OUT!
NO. DON'T GO.
HELP ME, PLEASE!
TINA.
[SONIC SCREAM]
[SCREAM STOPS]
SONIC DAMPENER,
NEW AND IMPROVED.
HE'S DEAD.
HELLO? TEAM?
LOOKS LIKE WE'RE GONNA
HAVE SOME COMPANY.
CAN'T LET HER GO!
GET HER!
I'VE GOT THIS!
WE DIDN'T GET TO FINISH
OUR LAST CONVERSATION.
YOU'RE PERSISTENT.
YOU KILLED THAT MAN.
BEFORE, I THOUGHT YOU
WERE WORRIED
I WAS THE ONE WHO WAS
GONNA END UP DEAD.
MAKE UP YOUR MIND.
DETECTIVE BOLAND.
IF YOU KNOW
I WAS POLICE,
THEN YOU KNOW THAT GUY
BACK IN MY PLACE
HELPED KILL MY PARTNER.
YOUR VENDETTA DOESN'T
END WITH HIM.
NOPE. I'M STILL LOOKING
FOR HIS BOSS.
HIS FRIENDS ARE THE ONES
CURRENTLY SHOOTING IT
OUT WITH YOUR FRIENDS.
WELL, WE CAN HELP YOU
GET HIM WITHOUT ANYONE
ELSE DYING IN THE PROCESS,
INCLUDING
AND ESPECIALLY YOU.
YOU KNOW, FROM WHAT
I HEAR, THERE ARE
PLENTY OF NUT CASES
RUNNING AROUND
STAR CITY, LOOKING TO
MAKE IT A BETTER PLACE.
WHAT MAKES ME
SO SPECIAL?
IF YOU STAY IN THE SAME
SPOT FOR MORE THAN A MINUTE,
AND I'LL GET A CHANCE
TO TELL IT.
WELL, IF YOU'RE GONNA
MAKE A SALES PITCH,
MAKE IT GOOD.
YOU WENT THROUGH
SOMETHING TRAUMATIC.
FOR THE PAST 3 YEARS,
YOU'VE BEEN TRYING TO
UNDERSTAND IT
BECAUSE YOU'RE AFRAID
OF WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU
AND OF WHAT
YOU'VE BECOME,
SO YOU'RE RUNNING
FROM IT.
HOW WOULD YOU KNOW?
BECAUSE I'VE
BEEN THERE,
AND I CAN HELP YOU
FIND YOUR WAY BACK.
OK.
WHAT'S THE RANGE
ON THAT, UH...
WHAT DID YOU CALL IT...
SONIC DAMPENER?
THAT'S WHAT I THOUGHT.
[SONIC SCREAM]
AGH!
♪ I KNOW WE'RE
AT THE END ♪
♪ THERE'S NOTHING
LEFT TO DO ♪
NOW THAT'S WHAT
I'M TALKING ABOUT.
CURTIS: YOU KNOW,
I WOULD TELL YOU TO CHEW
WITH YOUR MOUTH CLOSED,
BUT I DON'T EVEN
KNOW HOW YOU COULD DO
THAT WITH THIS THING.
5-STACK, BABY.
NOTHING BETTER.
-CURTIS.
-OH, YEAH.
UM, SO I MADE
SOME SENSE OUT
OF TINA'S CRAZY
MURDER BOARD.
MEET SEAN SONUS.
3 YEARS AGO,
HE WAS A PLAYER
IN CENTRAL CITY'S
CRIMINAL UNDERWORLD
AND THE TARGET
OF TINA'S
INVESTIGATION.
INTERESTINGLY,
SONUS DISAPPEARED
AROUND THE SAME TIME
THAT TINA DID.
THAT'S WHY SHE'S
BEEN TRAVELING
ACROSS THE COUNTRY.
SHE'S BEEN
FOLLOWING HIM.
THE ONLY
THING I DON'T
UNDERSTAND IS
WHY SONUS IS
IN HUB CITY NOW.
[MOUTH FULL]
OBIAH URRSE.
YOUR BELLY HURTS?
YEAH. THAT'S
NOT SURPRISING.
TOBIAS CHURCH.
HE HAD ALL THE GANGS
IN HUB CITY
UNDER HIS THUMB
JUST LIKE HE TRIED
TO DO BACK HOME.
I'M THINKING
WITH CHURCH'S DEMISE,
IT LEFT
A POWER VACUUM HERE,
ESPECIALLY
IN THE DRUG TRADE.
WHAT'S SONUS PUSHING?
SOME DRUG I'VE NEVER
HEARD OF BEFORE
CALLED "SLY-DEE"?
IT'S PRONOUNCED "SLIDE,"
LIKE IN PLAYGROUND
BECAUSE IT HOOKS KIDS YOUNG
AND MAKES THEM MOVE
TO THE BIG STUFF FASTER.
IF BOLAND'S
AFTER THIS SCUM BAG,
I VOTE WE GET OUT
OF HER WAY AND LET
HER DO HER THING.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
I'M ABOUT TO
SAY THIS,
BUT I ACTUALLY
AGREE WITH RENE.
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT EITHER.
THEN THERE'S THIS,
THE AFTER-ACTION
REPORT ON HER
PARTNER'S DEATH.
SONUS' MEN CAPTURED
HER AND TORTURED HER
FOR TWO WEEKS,
SO EVEN IF SHE
DIDN'T DROP OUT
OF THE POLICE,
SHE WOULD HAVE BEEN
PUT ON INDEFINITE
LEAVE BECAUSE
OF PSYCHOLOGICAL
TRAUMA.
THAT'S ALL THE MORE REASON
NOT TO LEAVE HER
OUT THERE ALONE.
LOOK. I DIDN'T KNOW
THIS LAUREL CHICK,
BUT YOU'RE TAKING ON A LOT
TO KEEP THIS PROMISE TO HER.
I'M THINKING
THIS IS ABOUT MORE
THAN JUST LAUREL.
IF SONUS IS CONNECTED
TO CHURCH'S MEN,
THAT MAKES HIM
MORE DANGEROUS
THAN WE THOUGHT.
WE NEED TO FIND BOLAND
BEFORE SHE GETS INVOLVED
IN SOMETHING THAT
SHE CAN'T HANDLE.
OLIVER:
WHAT'S THE PLAN?
FOLLOW MY LEAD.
HEY. HEY, HEY, HEY.
WE'RE WALKING
INTO A FORTRESS,
AND YOU'RE GONNA USE
JUST A BOW?
TO USE A BOW AND ARROW
REQUIRES PATIENCE
AND DISCIPLINE.
[COCKS GUN]
[ARROW WHOOSHES]
UNH!
TALIA: THAT'S
YURIEVICH.
I WILL TAKE ON
HIS GUARDS.
YURIEVICH...
YURIEVICH IS MINE.
PLEASE TELL ME YOU
DIDN'T SLEEP DOWN HERE.
I DIDN'T...SLEEP.
I THOUGHT THE NSA
WAS A DEAD END.
THE FILE WAS ERASED.
YEAH, AND THEN I REMEMBERED
NOTHING ON THE INTERNET
IS EVER ERASED.
EVERYTHING LEAVES
BEHIND A DIGITAL SHADOW,
AND I'VE BEEN
SCOURING THE DARK WEB,
TRYING TO FIND IT.
WHAT'S THAT?
A TERMINAL MESSAGE.
FROM WHO?
I HAVE ABSOLUTELY
NO IDEA.
AND HOW'D THEY GET
INTO YOUR SYSTEM?
I HAVE ABSOLUTELY
NO IDEA.
WHO'S GHOST FOX GODDESS?
THAT'S ME.
IT WAS MY HACKER HANDLE
IN COLLEGE.
I MADE A LOT
OF BAD CHOICES IN COLLEGE.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN
BAD CHOICES?
I USED TO BE
A HACKTIVIST.
THAT'S A HACKER ACTIVIST.
I LEFT THAT LIFE
WAY BEHIND.
IT WENT WITH A GOTH LOOK
THAT WAS NOT GOOD FOR ME.
-GOTH?
-MM-HMM.
DARK HAIR, DARK FELICITY,
TAKING ON CORPORATIONS
AND GOVERNMENTS.
IT WAS A POWER TRIP
THAT WASN'T HEALTHY.
WHAT'S "IRL"?
IN REAL LIFE.
RENE: YO. YOU KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE DOING THERE?
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
I HACKED ALL
THE TRAFFIC CAMS IN MY
HOMETOWN ON A DARE.
SO THIS IS GONNA
HELP US FIND
MISS LOCO BANANAS?
OR SONUS. EITHER WAY...
EITHER WAY, WE'RE
GONNA PUT OURSELVES
IN THE MIDDLE
OF A SHOWDOWN
BETWEEN A NUTBAR
AND A PSYCHO DRUG DEALER.
WHEN OLIVER EXPLAINED
HIS THINKING TO US
ON THIS,
WHICH HE RARELY
EVER DOES BY THE WAY,
I THOUGHT YOU WOULD
BE MORE ON BOARD.
HOW'D THE LAST
CRAZY RECRUIT TURN OUT?
OK. EVELYN DID HAVE
HER ISSUES, TRUE,
BUT SO DID RORY,
AND OLIVER CHANNELED
HIS VENDETTA INTO
SOMETHING POSITIVE,
AND AS FAR AS NUT CASES
ARE CONCERNED, Y...
"AS FAR AS NUT CASES
ARE CONCERNED" WHAT?
NOTHING. I...THAT WAS
THE...IT WAS A PERIOD.
"AS FAR AS NUT CASES
ARE CONCERNED PERIOD."
THAT WAS JUST...
WASN'T...SO...
YOU WERE THINKING
OF ME, WEREN'T YOU?
I MEANT IT
IN THE NICEST WAY.
-I GUESS YOU'RE RIGHT.
-I AM?
YEAH. MAYBE THIS TEAM
IS ALL ABOUT FINDING
SECOND CHANCES.
COULD YOU HAND ME THAT
ADAPTER AND, UH, TABLET?
YEAH.
THANKS.
GOT A LOCATION.
NUTBAR
OR PSYCHO DRUG DEALER?
PSYCHO DRUG DEALER.
GREAT.
[GRUNTING OUTSIDE OF ROOM]
CHECK IT OUT.
HEY, SEAN.
BEEN A WHILE.
DETECTIVE BOLAND.
A LITTLE OUTSIDE
YOUR JURISDICTION,
AREN'T YOU?
I'M NOT A COP TONIGHT.
GET AWAY FROM HER!
UNH! SON OF A BITCH!
UNH!
[OLIVER GROANS]
WHAT THE HELL
WAS THAT?
SONUS...HE'S
A META-HUMAN, TOO.
-HOW IS SHE?
-STILL UNCONSCIOUS.
I DON'T KNOW
ABOUT YOU, MAN,
BUT MY HEAD IS STILL
SPINNING A BIT.
IT'S HIS META POWER.
I THINK HE CAN CONTROL
SONIC WAVES.
IT WOULD EXPLAIN HOW
HE DISORIENTATED YOU GUYS
AND COUNTERACTED TINA AND...
THEIR POWERS ARE RELATED.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
I THINK I HAVE AN IDEA.
I DIDN'T SIGN UP
FOR METAS, MAN.
ENHANCED ABILITY OR NOT,
SONUS IS RUNNING
A DRUG TRADE
THAT SELLS TO KIDS.
THAT MEANS WE'RE
MOVING ON FROM
TRYING TO RECRUIT
THIS CRAZY LADY
AND FOCUS ON TAKING
DOWN THIS PRIG?
I'M ALL IN.
YEAH, BUT WE HAVE TO
FIND SONUS FIRST.
TINA: I KNOW WHERE
HE'S GONNA BE.
WHAT TIME IS IT?
11:40.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
SONUS IS TAKING IN
A MAJOR SHIPMENT
OF SLIDE.
AND YOU KNOW WHERE.
AND SOMETHING TELLS ME
YOU'RE NOT GONNA TELL US.
AFTER 3 YEARS,
THE MAN WHO KILLED
MY PARTNER
IS FINALLY
IN MY SIGHTS.
I'M NOT LETTING
ANYONE GET
IN MY WAY.
LADY WANTS TO
COMMIT SUICIDE,
WE SHOULD LET HER.
FREE COUNTRY.
HE NEARLY KILLED YOU
LAST TIME.
AGAINST HIM,
YOUR ABILITY IS
A LIABILITY.
LET US HELP.
HEY. THANKS
FOR THE SAVE.
SAFE TRIP BACK
TO STAR CITY, BOYS.
UNH! AAH! AGH!
[SCREAMING]
[BONES CRACK]
YURIEVICH IS DEAD.
GOOD.
NOW WE CAN TALK.
FELICITY: LOOK SHARP.
IF THIS GOES SOUTH ON ME,
I WANT YOU TO TAKE
THIS GUY DOWN HARD.
PARANOID MUCH?
YOU DON'T KNOW
THE DARK WEB LIKE I DO, OK?
THESE GUYS AREN'T EXACTLY
KNOWN TO BE FRIENDLY.
-OMG!
-O...MG!
THE GHOST FOX GODDESS
HERE IN MEATSPACE,
THE REAL
GHOST FOX GODDESS.
YOU'RE
KOJO SLEDGEHAMMER.
YEAH. I KNOW.
IT'S NOT NEARLY AS COOL
AS GHOST FOX GODDESS,
BUT THEN I CAN ONLY ASPIRE
TO YOUR LEVEL OF COOL,
WHICH I DO.
UH, ASPIRE TO, I MEAN.
TAKE HER DOWN HARD
YOU SAID, RIGHT?
[BEEP]
HEY.
IT IS SO GREAT
TO MEET YOU.
WHEN I SAW YOUR TRAFFIC
ON THE DARK NETS,
I WASN'T EVEN SURE
IT WAS YOU.
I MEAN, YOU'VE BEEN
A BLANK FOR, WELL, YEARS.
I'VE BEEN BUSY.
-I KNOW. PALMER TECH.
-MM-HMM.
I JUST FIGURED
ONCE YOU GOT FIRED YOU'D...
FIGURED I'D WHAT?
IT'S NONE
OF MY BUSINESS.
OK. WELL, UM...HEH.
I BECAME A HACKER,
A HACKTIVIST,
BECAUSE OF YOU,
THE GFG.
I READ ABOUT YOUR HACK
OF THE DEPARTMENT
OF EDUCATION,
AND I WAS LIKE,
"I KNOW WHAT
I WANT TO BE,"
BUT THEN YOU JUST
TOTALLY STOPPED
AND BECAME THIS, LIKE,
INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY
SUPPORT PLAYER, AND...
SORRY. NEVER MEET
YOUR HEROES, YOU KNOW?
NO. I HAVEN'T JUST BEEN
CORPORATE, YOU KNOW?
I'VE BEEN DOING WORK
THAT IS...IMPORTANT.
OOH. IF IT WAS,
I WOULD HAVE HEARD ABOUT IT.
OOH. SORRY.
THERE I GO AGAIN. HEH.
I GUESS I WAS JUST
EXCITED WHEN I SAW YOU
ON THE DARK NETS.
IT WAS LIKE...LIKE YOU
WERE RETURNING, YOU KNOW?
THE OG GFG WAS BACK.
WELL, I WAS LOOKING
FOR AN NSA FILE
TO EXONERATE
AN INNOCENT MAN.
-JOHN DIGGLE.
-YES.
MY ORGANIZATION DOES
ITS HOMEWORK.
ORGANIZATION?
A HACKTIVIST GROUP.
WE CALL OURSELVES HELIX.
A MONTH AGO,
WE HACKED ECHELON.
THE NSA'S INFORMATION
GATHERING PROGRAM?
MM-HMM. WE HOOVERED UP
8 PETABYTES OF DATA
INCLUDING EVERYTHING
YOU NEED TO HELP
YOUR FRIEND.
WE'RE CALLING
THE DATA CACHE PANDORA.
WITH IT, YOU CAN
TAKE DOWN POLITICIANS,
BANKRUPT COMPANIES,
SPARK REVOLUTIONS.
SO YOU'RE NOT JUST
GIVING ME THE FILE
FOR JOHN.
YOU INSPIRED ME TO MAKE
THE WORLD A BETTER PLACE,
AND NOW I INTEND
TO INSPIRE YOU
TO BE THE HACKTIVIST
YOU USED TO BE,
THE GREAT
GHOST FOX GODDESS.
LET ME GUESS.
YOU'RE TRUSTING ME
WITH YOUR MASK OFF,
SO NOW I'M SUPPOSED
TO TRUST YOU.
NO. I JUST THOUGHT
THAT IF YOU WEREN'T
GONNA LISTEN
TO THE GREEN ARROW
THAT YOU MIGHT LISTEN
TO OLIVER QUEEN.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
I SPENT 5 YEARS IN HELL,
NOT UNLIKE WHAT HAPPENED
TO YOU WHEN YOU WERE
UNDERCOVER
IN SONUS' ORGANIZATION
OR WHAT HE PUT YOU
THROUGH WHEN HE
DISCOVERED
YOU WERE A COP.
AND WHAT? YOU THINK
YOU SEE A LITTLE BIT
OF YOURSELF IN ME?
IT'S MORE THAN THAT.
THERE IS A MAN
IN STAR CITY
WHO'S TRYING TO
CONVINCE ME
THAT I DESTROY THE LIVES
OF EVERYONE THAT I TOUCH
BECAUSE I AM
BEYOND REDEMPTION.
YEAH, YEAH. YOU THINK
IF YOU CAN SAVE ME
YOU'LL PROVE HIM WRONG.
DON'T PUT YOUR ISSUES
ON ME.
ABSOLUTELY RIGHT,
BUT IF YOU THINK THAT
YOU CAN TAKE ON SONUS
AND HIS MEN,
THEN YOU ARE WRONG.
LET US HELP.
LET US HELP,
AND THEN...
WE'RE GONE.
CURTIS: ALL RIGHT! I'M READING
15 SHOOTERS ON THE ROOF
AND A HELICOPTER INBOUND.
COPY.
WE'RE IN POSITION.
SHIPMENT'S LATE.
SOME SCREW-UP
IN BLUDHAVEN.
TAKE 100 GRAND OFF.
WE NEED TO MOVE.
BE PATIENT.
YOU STILL HAVE
CURTIS' INSURANCE
POLICY WITH YOU?
YEAH. I'M STILL GONNA GET
TO USE MY GUNS, RIGHT?
[SIGHS]
CURTIS: CHOPPER'S ABOUT
TO LAND, GUYS.
MOVE.
SONUS: KILL THEM ALL!
NOT SO FAST, DIRT BAG.
YES!
[QUIET] YES.
-THEY GOT AIR SUPPORT.
-ALL RIGHT.
I'LL TAKE CARE OF IT,
BUT, WILD DOG...
I GOT HER SIX.
GUESS I SHOULD BE
FLATTERED.
TO THINK YOU'VE HELD
OUT A CANDLE FOR ME
AFTER ALL THESE YEARS.
WHAT ARE YOU
WAITING FOR?
OLIVER: TINA!
DON'T DO IT.
YOU'RE BETTER THAN THIS.
YOU KNOW I'M NOT.
IF WE'RE AS ALIKE
AS YOU SAID,
WE BOTH KNOW
YOU'D KILL HIM.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
MAYBE IT'S TOO LATE
FOR ME...
AND MAYBE I DON'T GET
A SECOND CHANCE...
BUT YOU DON'T HAVE TO
GO DOWN THAT ROAD.
TINA, WHAT WOULD VINCE
WANT YOU TO DO?
HE'D WANT ME
TO DO THAT.
HEY!
LET HER GO.
OH, MAN.
I WAS GONNA
ASK HOW IT WENT
WITH THE NEW CANARY,
BUT I CAN TELL
BY THAT...LOOK
ON YOUR FACE.
HMM.
WELL, I HAVE SOME
GOOD NEWS, THOUGH.
I AM IN THE MARKET.
I'VE GOT ALL WE NEED
TO EXONERATE JOHN.
THAT'S INCREDIBLE.
HOW'D YOU DO THAT?
LONG STORY.
IS THERE SOMETHING
YOU'RE NOT TELLING ME?
I KNOW THAT WE ARE
NOT USED TO GETTING
GOOD NEWS,
BUT THIS IS WHAT
IT LOOKS LIKE.
I AM GONNA GO LEAK
THE FILE ON WALKER.
WHY DON'T YOU GO TELL
JOHN THE GOOD NEWS?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
YOU TELL HIM.
TELL ME WHAT?
EARLIER THIS EVENING,
I RECEIVED
THE NSA'S CASE
AGAINST WALKER
FROM AN ANONYMOUS SOURCE.
-ANONYMOUS?
-ON THE STRENGTH OF IT,
I WENT THE JUDGE ADVOCATE
EX PARTE
AND GOT YOU RELEASED
ON BAIL.
-WAIT. WHAT?
-I FILED A MOTION TO DISMISS,
WHICH IS AS CLOSE
TO A SLAM DUNK
AS THESE THINGS GET GIVEN
THE CARDS WE'RE HOLDING.
WHAT DOES THIS MEAN?
IT MEANS THAT YOU
CAN GO HOME
AND HUG YOUR WIFE
AND SON.
YOU WANTED THIS,
BAITED ME
WITH YURIEVICH.
YES.
TO SEE FOR YOURSELF
WHAT I'VE BECOME?
TO REMIND YOU.
WHY GO TO ALL
THE TROUBLE, HUH?
WHAT DO YOU CARE?
YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW ME.
I THOUGHT I'D
PROVEN OTHERWISE.
GENERAL SHREVE,
BARON REITER,
KONSTANTIN KOVAR.
YOU KEEP LOOKING
FOR NEW FIGHTS
WHEN THE REAL FIGHT
HAS BEEN IN FRONT
OF YOU ALL ALONG.
YOUR FATHER LITERALLY
WROTE IT FOR YOU,
A LIST OF ALL
THE YURIEVICHES
AND KOVARS
IN STARLING CITY.
HE TOLD ME
HE LEFT ME A MESSAGE.
AND YET YOU STILL DON'T
RETURN HOME.
WHY DO YOU DENY
YOUR FATHER'S WISH
FOR YOU?
YOU SAW
THE REASON TONIGHT.
I AM NOT THE MAN
THAT MY FATHER RAISED!
NOT ANYMORE.
YOU'RE AFRAID OF WHAT'S
HAPPENED TO YOU,
OF WHAT YOU'VE BECOME,
AND YOU'RE RUNNING
FROM IT.
HOW DO YOU KNOW
ALL THIS?
BECAUSE I'VE
BEEN THERE...
AND I CAN HELP YOU
FIND YOUR WAY BACK.
YOU THINK YOURSELF
A MONSTER.
NO.
I AM A MONSTER.
THERE IS A MONSTER
INSIDE YOU, YES,
BUT IT IS NOT YOU.
I DON'T SEE
THE DIFFERENCE.
NO. YOU NEED TO
CREATE ONE.
YOU NEED TO GIVE
THE MONSTER AN IDENTITY.
IT'S ONLY WHEN
THE MONSTER BECOMES
SOMEONE ELSE,
SOME...THING...ELSE
THAT YOU'RE FREE TO BE
OLIVER QUEEN.
I DON'T KNOW
IF I'M READY.
I WILL HELP YOU
BECOME READY.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
MAN: MR. MAYOR.
EXCUSE ME,
BUT THERE'S SOMEONE
HERE TO SEE YOU.
HER NAME IS TINA BOLAND.
OH. YEAH.
SEND HER IN, PLEASE.
MAYOR QUEEN.
IT'S IMPRESSIVE.
MAYBE YOU SHOULD
HAVE LED WITH THAT.
I GOT TO ADMIT...
I DIDN'T THINK I'D
SEE YOU AGAIN.
YEAH. NEITHER DID I.
I GUESS I THOUGHT
I WOULD FEEL DIFFERENT
WITH SONUS GONE.
I THOUGHT I WOULD FEEL
LIBERATED.
I WISH IT WORKED
THAT WAY.
HEH.
HOW DO YOU DO IT?
HOW DO YOU KEEP
LIVING
WITH SO MUCH PAIN?
I'M STILL WORKING
ON THAT MYSELF,
BUT I CAN TELL YOU IT
HELPS TO NOT BE ALONE.
THAT'S WHY YOU'RE
HERE, RIGHT?
THAT'S WHY I'M HERE.
BACK ON THE ROOF,
YOU ASKED WHAT VINCE
WOULD HAVE WANTED.
WE WERE MORE
THAN JUST PARTNERS.
WE WERE LOVERS.
I HATED SONUS
FOR KILLING VINCE...
BUT I HATED MYSELF MORE
FOR NOT BEING ABLE
TO STOP HIM.
RENE, THE...THE GUY
IN THE HOCKEY MASK,
TOLD THE OTHER GUY
THAT WAS WITH US...CURTIS...
THAT THIS TEAM IS
ALL ABOUT FINDING
SECOND CHANCES.
YOU SAID MAYBE WE DON'T
GET SECOND CHANCES.
WELL, MAYBE
I WAS WRONG.
MAYBE YOU'RE
MY SECOND CHANCE.
THAT'S A LOT
TO PUT ON MY SHOULDERS.
WELL, TINA, THERE'S
SOMETHING THAT TELLS ME
YOU CAN HANDLE IT.
SO ABOUT THAT NAME.
TINA BOLAND WAS
MY OFFICIAL COVER
FOR UNDERCOVER WORK.
IT WAS TO PROTECT
MY FAMILY.
MY REAL NAME IS
DINAH, DINAH DRAKE.
DINAH?
DOES THAT NAME MEAN
SOMETHING TO YOU?
I HAD A FRIEND
NAMED DINAH.
SHE'S THE REASON
I SOUGHT YOU OUT.
WHAT DO YOU THINK SHE'D
THINK ABOUT ALL THIS?
I THINK SHE'D BE PROUD
OF BOTH OF US.
GREG, MOVE YOUR HEAD!