[Oliver]Previously onArrow...
Star City needs the Green Arrow.
So I'd like it to be you.
[John]The nerve damage in my arm
spread to my back.
And because of the steroid use,
I caused permanent damage.
As soon as you're healed up,
I want you to put that hood back on.
I've been good
for the past two months, good,
but instead of
giving me back the hood,
you've had Cisco make me a new suit.
Ricardo Diaz is pushing Vertigo.
I checked for any Vertigo-related cases.
They've all been kicked by Captain Hill.
She did it for Diaz?
The Orchid Bay night market
runs three blocks,
east, west, along R-U-L-O.
About midway down there's an alley.
And that's where Anatoly Knyazev
has been making his drop.
He is not a physical threat,
but the two men who will be with him are.
I've been to this market.
Lot of civilians there.
Hopefully not in the alley.
We're going to pin him in,
take him out, clean and fast.
Any questions?
This group's a little light
to take on three Bratvas.
Well, Diaz has God knows how much
of the force under his control,
including Captain Hill.
Only cops I'm sure I can trust
are here in this van.
Still, it'd be nice to have some backup.
We're covered. Trust me.
All right. Two minutes out.
Let's get ready.
Tango's heading into the alley.
[Dinah]Move in.
[John] Looks clean, so far.
Overwatch, any surprises?
Ha. Tricky, tricky, Anatoly.
Thermal reads four bogeys, east alley.
-I'll flank left.
-I'll take right.
Okay, good. Now that we are alone,
I know this might not
exactly be the right time...
You understand that
I'm gonna be punching people
in about 60 seconds, right?
Yes, but it's been about a week
since you decided
that you're not giving John the hood back,
and I was just wondering
when you were planning
on talking to him about that?
I'm waiting for the right moment.
That moment is not now.
That's a fair point.
Should try apples. It's good season.
SCPD.
Easy.
[grunting]
You are under arrest for possession
and attempt to distribute.
Miss Drake.
Cuff him.
[groans]
I see your face.
Maybe not so good for you.
Load him up.
Toss the three stooges
into lockup for processing.
I want Knyazev in interrogation.
[Captain Hill] What's goin' on here?
We just got Diaz's
right-hand man. Incredible, huh?
Why wasn't I informed?
That was my fault, Captain.
I authorized the operation.
I figured you wouldn't mind
given the stakes.
And we also took the liberty
of calling in DA Armand
to expedite the charges.
There's no sense in waiting, right?
Guess not.
Good work, Lieutenant.
Thank you for letting John and I
backstock you tonight.
'Cause you think we couldn't have
stopped Anatoly otherwise?
Because I appreciate the trust.
Well, try necessity.
Curtis is busy watching Zoe,
while Rene is in the hospital
nursing the wounds you gave him.
Yeah, I told him to stay down.
Matter of fact, I gave him every chance.
You guys made a move
on our team in the field.
These things are in the past, all right.
Tonight is a good night.
[sighs]
Where's Anatoly?
Interrogation.
Can you buy me a few minutes with him?
Uh-huh.
Thank you.
[sighs]
Oh, how nice.
You've come to visit.
Came to see you locked up.
Hmm. Enjoy it...
[speaking foreign language]
While you can.
I know all about Captain Hill
and crooked cops on the force.
Oh. You think this is
just your police force? [chuckles]
[laughing]
This is your city, kapiushon.
Your entire city.
Diaz has people everywhere.
All levels of government.
[door opens]
We got a problem.
I'm sorry, Mr. Mayor,
but Mr. Knyazev wasn't arrested
pursuant to an arrest warrant.
That's crap. You know it.
You're really gonna kick this case
on a technicality?
I'm not bringing charges
that will only get dismissed
the first time they end up
in front of a judge.
You have made exceptions before, Sam.
You're gonna draw the line now?
On this case?
You're under indictment, Mr. Mayor.
Do you really wanna add a civil suit
for wrongful imprisonment on top of that?
Cut Knyazev and his friends loose.
Sorry, Mr. Mayor.
What the hell just happened here?
Ugh. It seems pretty obvious to me.
It's not just Hill who's working for Diaz.
He's got Armand too.
So Diaz has the police captain,
the DA and...
Other members
of the city's infrastructure.
Anatoly wasn't specific,
he just said that Diaz
has people everywhere.
I'll run background checks
on all the city officials.
Makes sense to start at the top,
work your way down.
Look, Oliver, if you need to spend
more time at City Hall,
I get it, man.
[deep breath] Keep your focus there.
I can cover us here.
No, my focus is fine.
But, Oliver,
why split yourself in two, man?
Let me carry the load for you.
The city needs the mayor now
more than it ever did.
[Oliver clears throat]
It also needs the Green Arrow.
And that's not me anymore.
I've been waiting for the right moment,
the appropriate moment to tell you.
I'm not giving up the hood.
I guess I should have taken the hint
the way you kept putting me off, right?
You know, John, this team,
this mission...
It's all of us.
You helped build it.
I don't understand why it matters
what somebody's wearing.
I guess it doesn't.
That's the moment
you were waiting for. That one?
At least now he knows.
[sighs] John's an adult, Felicity,
he'll be fine.
Hope so.
[siren wails in distance]
Hey, pal. Get your butt off my car.
You eat like crap, officer.
Freeze!
I heard about you.
You're real brash.
You gotta show everybody
how tough you are, huh?
Poking around where you don't belong.
Get your hands up.
Funny thing about that, though,
you always end up
pissing off the wrong guy.
You didn't want to torture him a bit?
You know, maybe slit his throat.
What happened to all that Russian
vengeance I heard so much about?
Is new suit.
His dead body will send
good message to other police.
That's right.
We're all on borrowed time.
Still no suspects
in the death of Officer Hurst,
a six-year veteran with the SCPD
found dead last night
under mysterious circumstances.
Not so mysterious if you're Ricardo Diaz.
I need to contact Dinah
and have her sequester the other officers
involved in arresting Anatoly.
What about your DA friend?
Any idea how Diaz flipped him?
I'm guessing cold, hard cash.
[Oliver] Cash he took from the city?
Should all be dried up by now.
So he has another source.
Well, according to Curtis,
Diaz is involved
in an extensive Vertigo operation
and if my math is right,
and it definitely is,
he'll be pulling in
at least a million a day.
So we take out his Vertigo stash,
we kill his cash supply.
Unless he's got a rich aunt somewhere,
yeah, that'll work.
Right. I'll just go check in with Lyla.
See if A.R.G.U.S.
can give us any information
on this Vertigo operation
that can help us.
Yeah. That'd be great. Thanks, John.
That was unbearable.
He was fine.
The fuming, the standing
in the corner, that was fine?
John is not going to get bent
out of shape over a uniform.
He's a soldier, Oliver.
Look, I get what you're saying.
That this is not like John.
But you have to see
what he's not saying. He's upset.
Then he's gonna have to get over it.
This is not our first fight.
Well, if you don't want it
to be your last,
you should probably say something.
-Like what?
-Something to ease the pain.
[deep breath]
We need to know more
about Diaz's Vertigo operation.
I need to get to City Hall
and talk some sense into Hill and Armand
before somebody else gets killed.
Yeah.
I think I found a secure location.
To sequester the clean cops?
I'll come with.
No, Curtis. I'm the one
who brought these guys
into the fight against Diaz.
I'm the reason
he's retaliating against them.
This is all on me.
Well, don't be all Oliver Queen on me now.
If we have to take out Diaz,
there's going to be casualties.
And they're not going
to be your fault, Dinah.
No, they're not,
because I'm going to make sure
there are no more casualties.
We're going to make sure.
I'm gonna bring cops to a secure location
nobody knows about
except my good friend Curtis.
I'll be your tech guy.
Look, I don't like the idea of you
doing this without backup.
That, or you want to spend some
quality time with your new boyfriend.
We've only been on three dates.
But, yeah, he's cute,
and I don't want him to get murdered,
so sue me.
Let's go, lover boy.
Yes!
This is everything A.R.G.U.S. could find
on the Vertigo trade in Star City.
Yeah, thanks.
Uh-uh-uh.
It's not free.
I need intel in return.
What kind of intel?
The kind where you tell me
what's going on with you.
Lyla, you know what's going on.
[sighs] I'm frustrated that Oliver
strung me along for so long.
Being the Green Arrow,
you know what that meant to me.
But you save this city
every night as Spartan.
It's not like you to care this much
about a title or a hood.
Oliver made a similar point.
-But...
-I don't know.
I just don't know.
This is bothering me
way more than I expected.
I think you owe it to yourself
and to your partnership with Oliver
to figure out why.
Thank you both for coming.
I have to say, Mr. Mayor,
I'm more than a little uncomfortable
meeting with you
without your attorney present.
Well, it's not about the case, Sam.
It's about the two
of you working for Ricardo Diaz.
Who? I'm not sure
I've ever heard that name before.
You're smarter than this.
You're better than this.
Both of you are better than this.
Talk to me.
Less than 24 hours after you promoted me
to take over Pike's command,
I got an email.
Surveillance photos of my niece,
my father and my sister.
-So he found a way to apply pressure.
-Yeah.
Okay.
My boy has cancer.
Leukemia. Stage four.
Even with the city's insurance,
we couldn't afford the treatments.
I needed Diaz's money.
All right. We can protect your family.
We can pay
for your son's treatments. This city...
Is bankrupt.
The idea of you
protecting anyone is a joke.
The whole force is under Diaz's thumb.
Or were you offering your protection
as the Green Arrow?
If I was the Green Arrow,
I don't think you'd wanna
be in this room right now.
I don't think either of you would.
Are we done here?
You are.
You're both fired. Effective immediately.
-You can't do that.
-If you work for him...
Then you don't work for me.
Get out.
I know you're the Green Arrow,
but this is unlike anything
you've ever gone up against.
Diaz has already beaten you
and you don't even know it.
Still no suspects
in the death of Officer Hurst,
a six-year veteran with the SCPD found...
Looks like you've had an exciting day.
I wouldn't call the death
of a respected SCPD officer exciting.
It is when you've been
sitting on the couch all day.
Well, no one's holding you prisoner.
Why don't you get out?
Go get some sun, maybe.
No. Sounds boring.
Helping you with your Diaz situation,
now that sounds interesting to me.
I'm guessing the death of that cop
wasn't exactly random though, was it?
You know something about that?
I know Diaz and he's not
gonna stop at one officer.
Yeah, we figured that.
We sequestered the rest. They're safe.
Safe where, though?
[chuckles]
How do you expect me to be like Laurel
when you won't let me act like her?
You want to act like Laurel?
Why don't you do something good, huh?
Get a job, help this city.
I've never had a real job
in my whole life.
I don't even think
I know how to write a resume.
You don't need to write a resume.
You're Laurel Lance, remember?
How well did I do in law school?
Wait here.
I kept all of Laurel's old law books.
Look at that.
Maybe you could start right here.
You wanna home-law-school me?
Beats sitting around
on a couch, doesn't it?
I mean, who knows?
You could give it a shot,
you might just enjoy
doing something good for a change.
[grunting]
Hey, how did it... Oh!
I can tell by the look on your face,
won't even ask.
Would you please give me some good news.
Lyla clued us in on one of
Diaz's suppliers. Marshall Katz.
I'm running location on him now.
-Thank you.
-Yeah.
[sighs]
-I'll be right back.
-Mmm-hmm.
Thanks for grabbing that intel from Lyla.
No problem.
About the hood.
-I'd like to apologize.
-Oliver...
It's just a piece of cloth.
Just like you said.
-You were right.
-I was wrong about a few things.
It's very important that you know this.
When I asked you to take over for me,
I meant it.
When I put the hood back on and said,
"It's just until
you get back on your feet."
I meant it, but I did
put the hood back on and...
It's a part of me.
It makes me feel
like I'm being
the best version of myself and...
I feel whole.
And I feel complete.
And I really, really hope
that this is making sense.
Yeah.
The hood is part of you now.
I should have been upfront with you.
And I avoided having what I thought
might be a tough conversation.
Well...
I appreciate you telling me this, Oliver.
[computer beeps]
Thank you.
[Felicity] Got a location on Katz.
Yeah, let's move.
Baby.
I want some V.
I told you before...
Can't do it.
Only top-grade for my lady.
[chuckles] Well, don't you know
how to make a girl feel special.
Hmm.
We got a problem.
Moore downstairs spotted one of the masks.
-He's on his way up.
-Go! Do something!
-Get behind us.
-Yeah, no kidding.
Sit.
You're gonna tell us
where you make your Vertigo shipment.
And turn on the Dragon?
You'll have to shoot me, man.
I don't want to waste my arrows.
[Spartan] I think you should.
This punk deserves it.
I'm not nearly as stingy with my bullets.
[groans]
Where do you ship the V from?
[stammering]
I'm too high to die man, please.
Spartan, stand down.
When he tells us what we need to know.
[stammering] You wouldn't kill me
in front of my lady.
Last chance. Where's the Vertigo?
Spartan!
Stand down!
And what?
Do this your way?
-He'll fold.
-[gun clicks]
-Talk.
-Fine.
But you gotta send me
to, like, Mexico, man.
-Diaz will find me.
-[gun fires]
My loyalty is to Diaz, not him.
[grunts]
That was a bust. Get it?
'Cause it's drugs.
It's like a play on words
and it's almost a little fun.
Never mind. Tough crowd. What happened?
We lost Katz.
[sighs] Oliver, he was gonna talk.
If you had just let me
keep the pressure on him
for one minute longer,
we would be at the location right now
instead of back at square one.
No. He still would have gotten shot
because you picked a fight.
You pulled our focus and you
allowed our target to get killed.
Because you know everything
and I just need to keep my mouth shut.
I'm sorry. What?
Look, guys, we're all just whipped-up
with adrenaline from the field.
And we're gonna catch Diaz.
We always catch the bad guys.
So we're just going to breathe together.
Inhale...
John, what's going on with you?
First, you were mad at me
because you're not the Green Arrow.
That is...
That is way
out of character for you, my friend.
But I explained myself.
I apologized.
You accepted.
And now you're going to
take a shot at me like that?
I was getting someplace with Katz.
And you
didn't back my play.
'Cause it wasn't working.
No, Oliver!
Because it wasn't your play.
Let me know when you find the Vertigo.
I need some air.
I already told you. I don't know
where they sequestered the cops.
And if you're here
to put pressure on Lance,
don't.
Because I'm all healed up now.
You want to calm down?
I brought you dinner.
I'm not hungry.
What are you doing here?
Just checking up on things.
Looks like some light reading.
Just trying to maintain my cover.
Don't waste your time.
People like us don't learn the law.
People like us...
We are the law.
You trying to make your daddy proud?
Why would I ever want to do that?
'Cause I used to be like that
with my old man.
Before he died.
It's exhausting trying
to be something you're not.
Oh, so what?
You're gonna tell me
what I'm supposed to be,
is that it?
No.
I see what I like.
I know you're pretending
to be the real Laurel,
but the one standing
in front of me right now...
She don't need changing.
Your fries are getting cold.
[knocks] Hey.
[typing]
Hi.
-Everything all right?
-Fine.
I've been out of town for so long,
I just found the gift
you left for me back in December.
I wanted to say thank you.
-You're welcome.
-Funny though,
the same day you delivered it
I also found a security breach
on my computer.
I guess I now know how Cayden James
got a hold
of our nano aluminum amplifier.
I was gonna tell you about that,
Lyla, but, um...
City was at stake.
Yeah, well, the city is always at stake.
You don't have to lie to your wife
in order to save it.
You're absolutely right.
I'm sorry.
I know.
What brings you by?
Well, Oliver apologized for
stringing me along about the hood.
It was actually a good apology.
Wow.
That's not exactly Oliver's strong suit.
No, it's not.
But?
[sighs deeply]
I don't know.
I thought we cleared the air.
We go out into the field,
we come back and then I...
I just take a piece right out of him.
Over nothing.
It was over nothing.
You're right, there's something wrong.
And I'm worried that
when I find out what it is,
I'm not gonna like it.
Well, from everything you've told me,
there's not a lot to like these days.
The team breaking up,
Rene's in the hospital,
Diaz is running rampant.
Maybe the reason Oliver holding on
to the hood bothered you so much,
is because you think none of these things
would've happened if you had
been the one still wearing it.
Seriously, thanks for helping us out here.
I mean, anything for Dinah.
Maybe I was a little
worried about you too.
I'll be fine.
Just hate leaving the city
to be overrun by a bunch
of corrupt cops and vigilantes.
Don't you think there's a little bit
of a difference between
bent cops and vigilantes.
None that I can see.
They're both criminals, right?
Yeah.
Hey.
Listen, do you think, uh,
we could have the room?
[Felicity] Uh...
Yeah, yeah, of course.
-Get some air?
-Yeah, I did.
And with it, some clarity.
Oliver, it's totally within your rights.
To keep the hood, it's yours.
You're right, my frustration
was never with the uniform.
It was with the man underneath it.
I don't understand.
I didn't either, not at first.
[sighs]
I so appreciated your apology.
But something about it gnawed at me.
That you needed to be the Green Arrow,
that it completed you.
This was supposed to be about
saving the city.
Helping the people.
Not ourselves.
I know that.
It's a little too dangerous.
And I've lost just a little too much
along the way for it
-to be about that.
-But yet here you are.
You've gotten married, raising a son,
-you've become the mayor.
-So what?
So, Oliver, you were never
supposed to stretch yourself so thin.
And in so many different directions,
that the people suffer.
We have been in tough spots before.
We have with a team.
Even before Curtis, Rene and Dinah,
there was Roy, there was Thea,
but, Oliver, the way you lead
alienates everyone and everything
around you, look.
Putting the team under surveillance
was a mistake.
We had an opportunity
to save the Vigilante.
You made a different call.
The same with Laurel and the money.
When did all of these
just magically become my decisions?
I seem to remember
you right there next to me.
Begging you to exercise restraint,
caution, Oliver.
But that's not you, you have changed,
you have grown so much
and it's been my honor,
it's been my privilege to watch you.
But Oliver, you're still you
and if you're just doing this for you,
-like you just admitted...
-I didn't say I was doing it
-just for myself.
-If this isn't 100%
for our city,
then you are not the hero
that it deserves.
And you never will be.
Ricardo Diaz
has...
God knows,
how much of our city in his grip,
and you're picking now
to lecture me or to whine
about not getting a promotion?
Promotion, this isn't about
a promotion, man.
This is about you and Diaz,
you still can't see it.
-See what?
-He's already won, Oliver,
he has the city wired
and it happened under your watch.
He showed up
while you were the Green Arrow!
You bought drugs from him, John.
You funded what he is doing right now!
The entire time I put you in that hood
and you hid having a drug problem.
And I was putting my body through hell
-for the sake of our city.
-No, you put the team at risk
by lying!
I had to dive off a bridge
to save Rene's life,
because you were in the field,
you weren't 100%,
and nobody knew it.
You really wanna bring up Rene right now
when he is still hospitalized
for the beating that you put on him?
We were in the field against
Dinah, Curtis and Rene,
he pulls a gun on me.
-You think he gave me a choice?
-I think that you leave
a trail of bodies
every damn place that you go.
Sure, you've changed.
But what comfort is that to William?
Whose mother is dead because
of the bad decisions
that you've made.
My trail of bodies
doesn't include my own brother.
[both grunting and yelling]
[both grunting]
[Felicity] Stop!
What are you two doing? That's enough.
Have you two gone
completely over the edge?
Diaz is running through the city
like a cancer
and you two are in here
doing what exactly?
Okay.
This is what's going to happen.
I am gonna go back to work,
looking for the needle
that is Diaz's Vertigo operation
in the city's haystack, and the two of you
are gonna pull your heads
out of your asses!
-She's right.
-She usually is.
Sorry I punched you, Oliver.
Sorry I punched you back.
For what it's worth,
I know you've done a lot of good.
I know lately it seems like everyone's
been questioning your leadership.
Me included.
Found the location of Diaz's
Vertigo operation,
have you two found any shred of sanity?
Perhaps?
Let's go.
So he just drops it casually,
"I hate vigilantes."
Not "hate" but "hate,"
like capital letters, "hates vigilantes."
This is Paul all over again.
Well, that's kind of a leap.
Paul divorced me
because I was a vigilante.
Curtis, you're getting ahead of yourself.
Yeah, you're right,
he's not gonna break up with me.
-That's the spirit.
-He's going to arrest me.
I know I'm the last person
who should be giving you
relationship advice.
Yet you're about to give me some.
It's more of a life philosophy.
Just live in the moment.
Because you can only see
the step that's ahead of you,
you don't know what's
at the end of the road.
[beeps]
Someone just set off
one of my proximity alerts,
make that some-many.
All headed toward the front door.
-How did they find us?
-Who?
Diaz's men, they're about
to hit us from the west,
the north, the south,
they're about to hit us
-from every angle.
-I know.
I'm sorry, but we can't defeat Diaz.
We tried and we failed.
No!
You stay with Curtis.
Curtis.
I count 13 bogies in this den alone,
heavily armed.
[Oliver] No Diaz.
Got at least 20 million
of Vertigo here. He's gonna miss it.
The only way that we'll make it
out of here
is if we trust each other.
We've been through worse, Oliver.
I'm not sure that we have, John.
You're quarterback.
Call it.
Let's move.
[crackling]
[shouting] We're under fire,
get the product out of here now.
[machine guns firing]
[men grunting]
[beeping]
[grunting]
Hold on, Curtis,
we're gonna get you to a hospital.
Okay? Hold on.
[coughs and cries out in pain]
[groans] I'm okay.
Actually that's a lie,
I think my ribs are broken.
-You were shot point blank.
-No!
-You're...
-It's not what it looks like.
Okay, it is what it looks like.
Okay, go.
Place is bigger than expected,
how many more explosives do we have?
-[John]I'm all out.
-Then we improvise.
Vertigo's flammable in its liquid state.
-Headed there now.
-You won't make it.
Not alone I won't.
It's just like John Wayne,
"It's better to have loved and lost
than to never have loved at all."
Are we getting out of here or not?
Okay. There's an opening
on the east side of the building.
You know there is no opening
on the east side of the building!
Well then, make one.
[guns firing]
[Canary cry]
All right, let's go!
Move, move, move, move!
Let's go, everybody come on. Move!
Do it.
Thanks for having my back.
Judging by the burn radius
of the warehouse,
looks like we got all of Diaz's stash.
Oliver, I'm really sorry
about what I said.
You apologized already, John, so did I.
I know.
But what I said
about the calls you've made.
Where you've brought us.
The team, the city...
I just can't shake them.
What, you can't shake that you said it?
I can't shake that it's true.
Oliver, for six years,
I have followed the chain of command
without question,
even when my heart told me
there was a better way.
I trusted it, I trusted you.
But the inescapable truth
is that people have lost faith
in your leadership.
Truth is, Oliver,
you have become a better man.
But with your focus split...
A worse leader.
The Green Arrow allows you
to become the best version
of yourself and I respect that.
I respect you.
But if I'm gonna be
the best version of myself,
Oliver,
it can't be with you.
I hope you find what you're looking for.
John.
Don't do this.
Thank you so much for helping me get Zoe
-up for school.
-Yeah, sure.
Just don't understand how a girl so small
generates this much mess.
You know,
I actually don't mind tidying up.
Kind of like it.
Keeps my mind off of things
like the fact that my boyfriend
is going to break up with me,
because he found out I'm a vigilante,
and he hates vigilantes.
So he is your boyfriend.
My mind works in hyperbole.
[sighs]
Ignoring for a second
the operational risk of having
a cop know your identity.
Do you regret him knowing the truth?
[knocking at door]
Besides the fact that it means
ending our relationship,
-I don't.
-Well...
Then it was worth it.
Speak of the devil.
-It's Nick.
-Wait, what?
-Lieutenant Drake.
-Not looking for me,
I assume?
No, but I'm glad you're here.
Hill just canned me.
And you.
And the rest of us,
anyone who wasn't dirty.
Last thing she did
before clearing out her desk.
We're gonna fight this, Nick, okay?
Don't worry.
Come in.
I should probably find a reason to leave.
See you later.
-Hey.
-You go first.
-Okay.
[chuckles]
Listen.
I know
you're not a fan of vigilantes.
So, I get it, if you wanna...
Step away from this.
Curtis, I just lost my job
for being a clean cop.
I know.
With the department compromised,
maybe vigilantism is the only way
to take back the city, I don't know.
To be honest,
I don't know how I feel about vigilantes.
But I do know how I feel about you.
You okay?
I know it had to be done.
[sighs]
You had to do this your way.
I wish I knew what this was,
Lyla.
I know I wanna keep fighting for the city.
I just don't know
what that looks like on my own.
Maybe you don't do it alone.
Maybe you do it with me.
Here.
A.R.G.U.S.?
I've got people breaking into my office,
stealing stuff.
And really...
I could use an extra pair of hands.
Hey.
I know it's rough.
But you'll always have me.
I'm not going anywhere.
What's up, Quentin?
Turn on the TV, any channel.
Obviously the Mayor terminated us
to impede the prosecution
of his activities as the Green Arrow.
What Oliver Queen did
is an impeachable offense.
It was a gross overstep of power.
Our Mayor should be held
accountable for his actions.
Thank you.
Armand said that was your idea.
Looks like reading those law books
really paid off.
Guess I was wrong.
You were right about
something else though.
I'm not changing who I really am.
I have one last surprise for you.
There is one left.
And I know just how to use it.