Previously on "Arrow"...
- need your help, Roy.
-You really think
an energy weapon's
gonna stop this Monitor guy?
We got the plutonium
with an assist from Roy.
You're working with the Monitor.
Mar Novu is trying to save
worlds, not destroy them.
1 didn't want to believe it.
The only way to win is
to accept the inevitable.
Where the hell are we?
We're on Lian Yu.
The name of the island
they found me on is Lian Yu.
It's Mandarin for "purgatory."
Now I understand why.
The memories, the pain,
I've never escaped them.
They're always with me,
a reminder of what
I had to endure
with only one
thought, one goal--
survive.
To save the multiverse, I
must become something else.
To do that, I have to return
to where my journey began...
purgatory.
So this is the famous Lian Yu.
I did not want a return
ticket to this place.
The three of you were supposed
to be safe and sound in Star City.
How'd you get here?
A bunch of guys in tac gear came
and stormed the bunker.
AR.G.U.S. agents.
Sounds just as
fun as tranq darts.
I'm sorry about that.
I needed you here,
and I didn't have
time to convince you.
What the hell's going on, Lyla?
Mar Novu needs
us to build a weapon,
and it has to be
done on this island.
I'm not doing
anything for that guy.
No, we have to.
Since when do we take
orders from the enemy?
We were wrong about Novu, John.
He's not our enemy.
Since when?
He dropped me in
an alternate reality
in order to teach
me the lesson that
to fix the multiverse
we need to work with him.
This is crazy.
I know it's hard
to hear, Johnny,
but it's the truth.
John...
Um...
how do we build the weapon?
The materials we
need are already here
in the crates outside.
Dr. Wong has been experimenting
with the dwarf star particles
since leaving Hong Kong.
He's designed
schematics for the build.
Schematics? Why
does that make me think
that this Dr. Wong guy
won't actually build this thing?
We're counting on you for that.
-Say again? ~The
device is powered
by plutonium.
Dinah, Roy, and Rene
are on their way here
with samples from Star City.
So my mission was part of this?
All of our missions
are a part of this.
With all due respect,
what am I doing back on Lian Yu?
In the past few days,
the island has seen
arash of energy spikes.
Is that your reason
for it being green?
Because the last
time that I was here,
Adrian Chase blew it up.
Yes. Harnessing
that energy is the key,
and we need to do
it right away because
we have no idea how long
the energy spikes will last.
Okay. Wait. So we build this
magic weapon for the space god
and we stop Crisis?
There is no stopping Crisis.
Well, then what's
the weapon for?
I don't know,
but Novu said this
is how we survive it,
and I believe him.
If we can't stop Crisis...
Sorry.
What is he talking about?
Oh, my God.
Would the group mind if I
had a moment with my kids?
Of course.
There's no easy way to say this.
Mar Novu has seen my fate.
1 don't survive Crisis.
‘What do you mean?
- mean that he told me
what would happen to me
the day that he walked in
and asked for my help.
And when exactly were
you planning on telling us?
I've been fighting my fate
because of the two of you,
and I can't fight
it, I can't change it.
So you're just giving up?
I am attempting to
save the multiverse,
and I'm trying to keep
the two of you safe.
We gotta build the weapon,
and finish this mission,
and that's the way
that it has to be.
Well, then I guess
we better get to it.
Lyla, what happened to no
more secrets between us?
I'm sorry I couldn't tell you.
So you thought tranqing
me and bringing me here
of all places was somehow
a better explanation?
Mar Novu made it
clear that silence was
a requirement of the mission.
We couldn't risk interfering
with the journeys
of the other players.
As in Oliver's journey
ending in a death sentence?
What did Novu
ask you to do, Lyla?
He didn't give me details.
He just told me that
when the time comes
I would know what to do.
You're just fine with that? Why?
Faith.
You remember that IED that
took out my unit in Afghanistan?
I remember that. Of course I do.
You were the only survivor.
Took you years to stop having
nightmares about that blast.
Mar Novu when
he first came to me,
he told me he
rescued me that day
because I have
a greater purpose.
-And you believed him?
-A grown man in costume
prophesizing the apocalypse?
I thought it was a joke,
but then he came to me again,
and he showed
me...us, our future
just wiped away, gone
as if it never existed.
So you made a deal with him?
We would work
together to find heroes
strong enough
to face this Crisis.
He told me it was the only
way 1 could protect our family.
Lyla, you may have accepted that
this was the only way to move forward,
but I have not.
won't.
Guess I shouldn't be surprised
the Black Canary knows how to fly.
Flying's easy.
Landing's the hard part.
Kidding.
There it is...
purgatory.
Looks a little less bombed
out than I remember.
Wow. After everything
I've heard about this place,
1 didn't imagine it to be so...
Terrifying?
Beautiful.
Makes sense you'd think so
since apparently
you're moving here.
Maybe not.
This time around,
you are part of a team.
Island team, do you copy?
We are five miles south
and inbound for landing. Over.
We copy. Island
team will meet you
at the airstrip to unload. Over.
No wind to speak
of. Looks like we're in
for a relatively smooth landing.
Hang on. Hang on.
What the hell is that?
Something's wrong.
Hey. Is everything
all right up there?
We're picking up--
something's incoming.
Did she say, "incoming"?
Dinah, are you there?
Can you read me?
Oh, my God.
Brace for emergency landing.
Hold on!
They're not gonna make it.
“We need to find the crash
site. I'm working as fast as I can.
I can't get in contact
with Roy, Rene, or Dinah.
Something keeps
blocking my signal.
Not something, someone.
Whoever shot down that plane.
You should have told
us we weren't alone.
I thought we were.
I had AR.G.U.S.
sweep the entire island.
Okay. I just got
the coordinates,
but the plutonium
landed in a different spot.
There's a tracker in the case,
but it's nowhere near
Rene, Dinah, or Roy.
The people are the priority.
Well, obviously, but we still need
the plutonium to build the weapon.
All right. John, let's split up.
I'll run point on the rescue.
Connor, you're with me.
I'm coming, too.
I called them
here. This is on me.
Whatever the three of
you do, just be careful.
We don't know who these
people are or what they want.
Copy that.
And I guess that means,
what, the three of us,
we are on nuclear weapon duty?
I'm staying here.
Are you okay with that?
Someone needs
to protect William.
Gee. Thanks.
It's fair.
Thank you.
William synced this map
to the plutonium's location.
Gonna get us close to the case,
but the coordinates
won't be exact,
so we're gonna have
to sweep the area.
Well, the sooner
we find it, the better
because I am not
a fan of this island.
Yeah? Well, it has
that effect on people.
You know, I, uh--
I never expected
to be on a mission with
you like this, you know.
I'm glad you're here.
No offense, but shouldn't
this Kodak moment
be with you and someone else?
What? You and Mia.
Oh. Trying to give
her a little space.
Sure you're not trying to
avoid a difficult conversation?
I'm pretty sure she doesn't
want to talk to me, Laurel.
Oliver, don't be an idiot, okay?
All that girl wants to do
is live up to her father.
Fine. All this father wants
is to complete this mission
so that my kids actually
have a world to live in.
“We are almost there.
Come on. «Oliver.
Piece of advice.
Don't leave this island
with more regrets
than you already
have buried here.
Oh. Building this weapon with
2019 tech may actually kill me.
I miss the future.
What's this?
Those are very volatile
dwarf star particles
that could level an
entire city or island.
All right. What can
I do to help, huh?
Well, do you know how to
calculate the volume of a sphere?
43 pi times radius cubed.
I was raised by
Felicity, too, remember?
Right. Well, do you know what
the Pauli exclusion principle
of quantum physics is?
Didn't pay that much attention.
Well, then that pretty much
takes you out of the running
of helping me in
any meaningful way.
Damn. I'm gonna
need a wire stripper.
These are the most
complicated coding
and design sequences
I have ever seen,
and I'm including
2040 when I say, "ever."
It's not like you to
hide out in the bunker
and miss out on all the action.
Still mad at Dad?
It's his life.
He can do whatever
he wants with it, right?
Always has.
You're being a bit
harsh, don't you think?
And you are being a
bit chill, don't you think?
I was right all along.
Yeah. He has always
been a hero first
and a dad second.
We never should
have trusted him.
Mia.
-I'm getting your wire stripper.
I'm sorry our first
meeting had to be this.
I envisioned getting to know
my future son over a meal,
not en route to a plane crash.
This--this feels about
right for our family.
Most of our milestones
got interrupted
by some sort of international
emergency or another.
Yeah. I guess your dad
and I weren't really there
for you and JJ.
You were there when it counted.
Besides, I was beyond
proud to be the son
of the two superspies that
co-founded Knightwatch.
You never mentioned that.
I think maybe I
wasn't supposed to.
Time travel rules and all.
Have to assume that the
timelines are different now
unless you remember
your mother being in league
with a evil deity.
Mar Novu is not evil.
Our friends' plane got
shot out of the sky, Lyla.
How do you know that
wasn't part of his cosmic plan?
And don't say faith.
Because I'm fresh out.
Okay, okay.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
You guys okay?
I think so.
We have no idea where Roy is.
Okay. You are
definitely not okay.
We cannot let this get infected.
You guys keep searching.
I'll take Rene back
- and get him fixed up.
- Okay. Go, go, go.
“We need to find
Roy. ‘Where? Where?
This way.
Laurel, I found it!
Laurel!
- Let her go.
- I'm afraid he can't do that.
Hello, Oliver.
Fyers.
- You're dead.
- What?
Seems I've been given
a new lease on life,
though this time I'l be
sure to finish the job.
Drop your weapon.
Drop...your weapon!
Friends of yours?
Edward Fyers and
Billy Wintergreen.
They were on the island
when I first got here,
and they're both dead.
So now we're fighting ghosts?
How is that even possible?
-Get this to William.
“Where are you going?
I have to go after Fyers.
Or you come with me,
and we finish this weapon
and get the hell off
this nightmare island.
Fyers is my mess.
He's a mercenary
that I fought and I killed.
He clearly wants revenge,
and ma--makes
him my responsibility.
All right. I'll be back
as soon as I can.
Yao Fei?
-Are you real?
-As real as the men you hunt.
Why'd you try to shoot me?
Like the first time.
To keep you from danger.
No one can keep me from
danger, okay, not even you.
Because you are fated to die?
There are forces at play
that want you to not succeed.
Fyers and his men
know about the weapon,
and they want to
use it for themselves.
All right. Well, who
else has, um, returned?
Only those who were with
you from the beginning,
but you must not let the evil
that tempted you at the start
distract you at the end.
He's coming after more than my
mission, Yao Fei, you understand?
I'm not gonna let that happen.
Last time you tried to
do alone did not end well.
I'm not that person anymore.
1 will hope.
Roy! John] Roy!
Roy!
There!
I can't-- I can't move!
Roy, we're gonna
get you out of here.
His arm is pinned.
-Can you feel anything? No, no.
We got a problem. Fuel.
Okay. “We got to
get him out of here
before this whole thing blows.
Let's get this off of him, okay?
Yeah, -One, two, three, lift!
How bad is it?
Tell me!
Your arm is crushed.
If you can't feel it, then
that means pretty badly.
If we can't move
what is pinning you,
then we need to start thinking
about other contingencies.
What are we talking about here?
We don't have much time.
The best way to get Roy out
might be amputation.
- What?
- Can you do that?
Ihave a med kit in
my pack back there.
It'll have what I need.
If we can just move
this off of him, okay,
we have a chance
at saving his arm.
I mean, the odds
aren't very good.
We owe it to him to keep trying!
So let's move
this thing, all right?
Let's go!
-Dinah, -I'm gonna check it out.
Yeah. All right. Look.
Let's try to find a lever
to help get this
off of him, okay?
Roy, just hang tight.
We'll be right back.
Oh, good. You're not dead.
Or maybe I spoke too soon.
Rene is injured but okay.
Roy's in a bad spot.
Well, we're all gonna
be there with him
if--if we don't keep moving.
Sounds like you found the
guys who shot down our plane.
Oliver's old island enemies.
They've been dead
for the last 12 years.
Of course they have.
Where is Oliver?
He went after them,
made me the
radioactive material mule.
Let's go.
1,2, 3!
It's got to be caught
on something,
-a root system or something.
-All right. Then we dig him out.
- We dig him out.
- We have to hurry.
Guys, we're about
to have company
-and not the good kind.
We can hold them off!
The fuel's about to spark,
John. We don't have time.
We can trench it, Dinah!
-Dad, we are out of options!
-We are not out of options!
-l don't accept that!
“We don't have a choice!
We always have a choice, Connor.
Then I'll make it.
Doiit. Just cut me free.
No. No, Roy.
John, it's better my
arm than our lives.
Get the kit. Get the kit.
Laurel and I will distract them.
Here. You apply the tourniquet.
I'll get ready.
Just hold on,
okay? Just hold on.
Okay.
<This will be over fast.
-Am I gonna feel it?
Probably.
I'm with you, Roy.
I'm with you, okay?
You ready?
Do it!
Hyah!
Fyers' camp is just up ahead.
We should not be back here.
You don't have to help, Yao Fei.
I help for Shado.
I'm sorry I couldn't save her.
You know the bond now
between a father and child.
I do. It's exactly why I
have to put Fyers down.
Should be right up here.
They're gone.
Okay. That doesn't
make any sense.
He should be here.
Fyers knew you'd come here.
Well, now he's free and clear to
attack my friends and my family.
We need to get out of here.
How?
Use your how?
It's pinned.
All right, Well, we will
have to cut our way out.
The net is made
of braided steel.
-That blade
won't cut. It'll cut.
- Ohh!
- Gotchu, gotchu, easy. Shh.
What the hell happened?
His arm got pinned
underneath the landing gear.
We had to amputate.
I'm sure you did what
you needed to do.
- Roy?
- William.
Not sure it's really a good
time for a meet and greet.
Is Oliver back yet?
We thought he was with you.
No. He went after the
bad guys on his own.
“Why would you let him do that?
-Seriously?
Okay. We have to go after him.
No. No. William has
to finish the weapon.
I don't care about your weapon!
Oliver knows this island better
than anyone, Mia. He'll be fine.
Plus it's smarter for
us to stick together.
No. We are not
leaving him out there.
Fine. I'll go on my own!
-This is a bad idea.
Then don't come with me.
You heard Laurel. We
should stick together.
t's smarter tactically.
-Are you really gonna lecture me
on tactics right now?
Well...no, but...
Dig is right.
I mean, Dad and this
island, they go way back,
and he knows every
inch of this place.
You going out there
could make things worse.
I'll take my chances.
Get out of my way.
William.
Look. It is okay for you
to be afraid of losing him
especially after the
way that you left things.
You don't know what
you're talking about.
This is exactly what
happened with Felicity.
You were angry with her, but
you still wanted to save her.
I'm not just gonna sit
here and do nothing, okay?
1 will not leave him
alone out there. I--
1 will not...let him die.
I let myself believe for just...
just a minute that I could
actually have my dad.
Look. When I was a kid, I spent
a lot of time pushing him away
because I never thought
that I could lose him,
and then he disappeared.
Yeah. Now we
might lose him again.
How are you so calm about this?
I'm not, but when I was little,
Felicity had me
down in that bunker
watching Dad out in the field,
and I saw that he could
cheat death more than anyone,
but if this really is the end,
I don't want to waste the time
that I have left with him being angry.
Do you?
I was wrong. You
haven't changed.
Still that impatient
boy I found.
You realize that
insulting me is not gonna
make this go any faster, right?
Breathe. Remember
in everything, breathe.
I'm trying to cut my way out of a
net, Yao Fei, not shoot an arrow.
We wouldn't be in this
net if you had breathed.
You know what Fyers
is capable of, right?
I need to get back to my family,
and I'm running out of time.
You could be with your family,
but you chose here instead.
I chose to protect them.
You avoid them because
you're fated to die.
I've been fighting that
fate for a long time.
I've accepted it.
That hasn't made
things any easier.
What am I supposed
to say to my kids?
What I could not to Shado.
You say good-bye.
I don't think that I can.
My kids have spent basically
their entire lives without me.
And they're about to
have to do it all over again.
You think you have failed.
The first thing that you
taught me--shengcun, survive.
Well, I can't do that anymore.
Shengeun is more than body.
It is spirit, what lives on,
like I did in Shado,
like she does in you.
That is survive.
How do I do that?
You live now
with your children
with the time you have left.
I need to get out
of this net first.
Always have patience.
Like I said, patience.
Just came by to check
on you. How you feeling?
I--I've been better.
I'm so sorry, Roy.
I should have found
another way to get you out.
This wasn't your fault.
Yeah. Well, that's
where you're wrong.
I mean, you wouldn't
even be in this situation
if I hadn't come to
find you in Hub City.
Roy... I can't protect
the people I care about.
You know I worked with you
and Oliver for a really long time,
and if I've learned
anything, it's that this team
has each other's backs
no matter the cost.
Things just didn't
exactly go as planned.
That's an understatement.
No, but I would rather be here.
I would rather be here with you
and with the team
than back in Hub City,
living a life all alone.
Heroes make sacrifices, John,
and for better or for worse,
this just had to be mine.
John...we got a problem.
Fyers and his men have
surrounded the camp.
We can expect an
attack any minute.
How long before
the weapon is ready?
I'm done building it. Once
the plutonium finishes
transferring the
energy, I can turn it on.
- How long will that take?
- I'm not sure.
Can we take this to a
safer part of the island
«and finish it there?
-No, no. It has to be here.
I've tapped into the center
of the island's energy.
We can't move.
-And it has to be tonight.
We don't know when the
next energy spike will be,
and we can't afford to wait.
We need to buy
William more time.
Dad, you're okay.
Yeah. An old friend
steered me back.
I'm sorry that 1 took off.
I should have been
here with the two of you.
You're here now.
How are we supposed
to beat an army of ghosts?
Power up the device.
The sphere's absorbing
the energy of the island,
and if that's what brought these dead
people back to life in the first place--
Activating the device
will destroy them.
We're talking about
plutonium here.
That's nasty stuff.
It can take out
this entire island, us included!
If this is our best chance
of surviving the Crisis,
then we need to take the risk.
Lyla's right. She's right.
This is it.
This is our best shot.
Suit up.
You are as foolish
as ever, Queen.
Surrender!
I suppose that means you're
not here to surrender to me.
I'm the one who
killed you, Fyers.
I'm very pleased
to return the favor,
a task you've made much
easier by coming alone.
I'm not alone.
Now that the plutonium
has transferred the energy,
all I have to do is power it on,
and voila!
It doesn't look on.
Why isn't it working?
- have no idea.
It doesn't matter how
many people you have.
The outcome is the same.
Kill them!
William, we're
running out of time.
Okay. I think I have something.
There was a double
helix genetic sequence
in Dr. Wong's formula.
I thought it was an error, but now 1
think the device can only be powered on
using a specific DNA code.
Oliver. Oliver, we
need you back here
to activate the device.
Oliver, you got to go!
Yao Fei, if this works...
We will part again, but the
dead are never really gone.
I've got your six.
They're not gonna be able
to hold them off much longer.
- ‘- We need to hurry.
- The sphere is touch-activated.
It'll turn on the moment
you pick it up and...
1 don't know what
happens after that.
Okay.
Wow. That was anticlimactic.
“What the hell?
“What? What is it?
Dad's DNA doesn't match the
algorithm's specified sequence.
- Does that mean we can't turn it on?
- Sequence match.
You can't....
but she can.
What are you talking about?
The DNA sequence isn't Dad's.
It's yours.
Is it me, or is this
not going well?
We gotta buy them some time.
God, I hate this island!
Might as well go
out with a bang.
I thought this weapon was
supposed to help us survive Crisis.
That's what Novu told me.
Does this mean
you're the weapon?
Johnny...
I understand why
you have to do this.
Lyla, are you all right?
I have to go.
Hey, guys. 1 just, uh--
I just connected with ARG.US.,
and Lyla organized a rescue boat
before everything happened.
Should be here any minute, so--
so we're all going home.
Did Mom--did she know what
was gonna happen to her?
No. No. She was just as
surprised as the rest of us.
Novu just loves
surprises, doesn't he?
Whatever Mar Novu
has planned for Lyla,
she can handle it.
How much time do we have
before the Crisis?
Not long.
Should, um,
probably finish packing
before the boat arrives.
Agreed. No more
island vacations.
Uh, hey, guys.
Listen. I just wanted to...
I wanted to thank both of you
for just being there
for me no matter what.
Why does this sound
like a good-bye speech?
Pass. Do not accept.
This ain't over
till it's over, Oliver.
All right.
Come on.
Hey.
I don't really know what to say.
I'm really happy that you're
back with the team, and...
I'm really sorry.
I'll be okay.
Plus Dig's gonna set me up with
one of those fancy
AR.G.U.S. doctors, so...
Uh, the boat's almost ready.
Uh, we good down here?
Yeah. We should go.
Oh. Uh, almost forgot.
This is what led
me here in the future
to you and, uh, to the team.
Thought you might like it back.
I don't need it.
Plus I think it should
stay in the family.
You know, when
Felicity gave this to me,
she told me it was a
symbol of reconnection.
-She was right.
-She normally is.
No. You keep it.
William, what you
were able to do,
you're a hero.
Well, I had a pretty
good example.
It means a lot to me
that I've had a chance to...
to see the type of
man you've become.
I hope you'll forgive me
for lots of things eventually.
Dad, I already have.
I mean, I know for you
I only left a year ago.
For me, it's been 20 years,
and back then when I was a kid,
I didn't understand
what it meant
to fight for something
bigger than yourself,
but now I do.
I'm really proud of you, Dad.
Not as proud as I am of you.
-I'm gonna hug you now.
-You better.
Okay.
Thinking about where Lyla went?
Can't think about anything else.
I know this is a
sacrifice she has to make
for the multiverse.
I feel like I'm always
asking you favors.
Anything you
need, Oliver, always.
I need those kids back in 2040
somehow, some way before
whatever's gonna happen happens.
Yeah. I was thinking
about the same thing.
I'll make sure
they get home safe.
One more thing.
When this is over,
track down Felicity and...
just tell her that
I don't want...
Mia and William kept separated.
I think that they deserve
to grow up with each other.
I'll tell her.
Yeah.
You know, Oliver, I once
told you a long time ago
that uh, a soldier never lets
a brother go into battle alone.
I think that's why it was so hard
for me to accept the idea that...
you weren't gonna
make it out of this.
I felt like I'd be failing you.
You could never fail me, John.
I'm gonna stick by your side
for as long as I can,
but I know you
have to do this alone.
Every mission has an end.
I wish this one didn't.
I couldn't have
done any of this,
any of it without you.
You've always been my rock.
Don't mean the best
man you've ever known?
I also mean that.
Hey, let's get out of here, man.
Don't want to keep
the boat waiting.
I'll be right behind you.
One more thing 1 got to do.
Hey.
Um, William said I
might find you here.
Figured you'd be the
first one on the boat.
You okay?
My whole life I heard
nothing but stories about you.
You know, this legendary
Green Arrow and his team.
I should have been proud of you
because you were a hero, and...
all I could see is that that is
the reason that
you weren't with me,
and it's--it's kind of
hard to let that go.
I never meant to
cause you any pain.
Your mom and me just
wanted to protect you.
I know.
I, uh--l understand that now.
For a very long time,
I have hated this place.
Just, I'd think about all the
people that it took from me.
It would just--it would
just make me so angry.
But you're not now?
I'm still a little bit angry.
This island taught
me to survive.
It turned me into someone else,
somebody better than
the person I was before.
So despite my feelings...
there are no stories about
the Green Arrow to tell
if don't make my way to Lian Yu,
and I'm also not
standing at this moment
looking at my daughter.
Thank you for letting
me be a part of your story
even if it was only
for a little while.
Mia, something tells me you're
gonna create your own stories.
So what now?
We need to get back home
and just be prepared
for whatever's coming next.
Okay.
Dad.
Lyla? Not anymore.
I'm now a harbinger
of things to come.
-And that's-- “Yes.
The Crisis has begun.
For so many years,
I've traveled across worlds,
across the multiverse
to do one thing--
kill you,
and now here, you save my life.
Submit and begin your life anew.
Show me.
The knowledge is within you.
Greg, move your head!