My name is Oliver Queen.
After five years in hell,
I have come home
with only one goal--
To save my city.
Now others have
joined my crusade.
To them, I am Oliver Queen.
To the rest
of starling city,
I am someone else.
I am something else.
Previously,
on "arrow" and "flash"...
Hello?
It's barry.
I woke up.
I could use some advice.
I don't think that bolt of lightning
struck you, barry.
I think it chose you.
You can inspire people
In a way that
I never could.
So what are you guys doing
in central city?
Working a case.
Suspicious homicide,
In a style where
the murder weapon...
Is a boomerang.
Partners?
Partners.
Barry has super powers, Oliver
has a bow and arrow.
If I had a sample I was unable
to fully break down,
Do you think you could isolate
the genetic markings for me?
What's the sample from?
Canary's murder.
In position?
In position.
Neighborhood's
clear.
You know, I probably should have
brought this up before,
But if this place doesn't
belong to the killer
You chased to central city
and back, well,
We're going to have
a lot of explaining to do.
It's his.
Why, because the residue
S.T.A.R. Labs
Found on the boomerang
says so?
Because the whole
place is rigged.
[beeping]
I can see a trip wire connected
to pressurized gas.
Front door
will be the same.
Our new friend doesn't want
any surprise visitors.
Well, he's going
to get a surprise.
Looks like
we interrupted his dinner.
We just missed him.
Drop your guns.
Sure thing.
Right when
You learn
how to count.
You're outnumbered,
jerkwad.
You're not scpd.
Unless police
uniforms have gotten
Really interesting,
neither are you.
A.R.G.U.S.
Your flanking patterns
haven't changed in years.
Why is a.R.G.U.S.
In on this?
The man who was killed
by the boomerang...
He was an a.R.G.U.S. Agent?
Which makes this
an A.R.G.U.S. Matter.
Bug out.
Target's not here.
Let this go.
Are we going
to let this go?
What do you think?
What about this
a.R.G.U.S. Angle?
Oh, well, a.R.G.U.S.
Wiped all evidence
of their agent's death
After he was killed, or at least
they thought they did.
Our boomerang victim,
kai wu.
The man's profile is so clean, I should
have known it was an A.R.G.U.S. Cover.
Well, now that we know
wu is A.R.G.U.S.,
Maybe lyla
can get us a lead?
If this an a.R.G.U.S. Thing, Lyla's
going to want it to stay that way.
Then tell her to stop letting people
get killed in my city.
You really don't care
about my marriage, do you?
Well, I would...
If you and Lyla
were still married.
Thank you
for coming.
Like I had a choice.
I see you made a new friend.
This is katsu cheng.
Mr. Cheng
fancies himself
Something of a munitions
specialist.
According to HKPF,
Cheng planted an explosive device
somewhere in hong kong,
I need you to talk to him,
find out the bomb's location.
So I'm just going
to talk to him
And he's going to
give me information?
It won't be easy.
That's why I brought you
your tools.
What tools?
We recovered these
from the freighter
When we recovered you.
You're welcome.
You want me
to torture this guy
To find out
where the bomb is?
I want you to find out
where the bomb is.
How you do so
is of little interest to me.
[door opens]
Almost done here,
jerry.
You should have
gone home hours ago.
Caitlin:
Who's jerry?
This place is bigger
than my apartment.
What are you guys
doing here?
You asked us to analyze the DNA
off the arrow
That killed Sara.
I was just going
to mail you the sample.
We had some vacation
days coming--
We want to see the arrow cave.
We don't call it that.
Ever.
I want to see
the toys!
I need to see
the toys.
Do you guys have
an arrowmobile?
Don't touch that.
Or that.
It's a jettisoning arrow.
Uses compressed co2--
Compressed co2 to jettison
high tensile
Strength polymer cables.
Yep.
Since when did we start selling
admission the the arrow cave?
It's...
Do you see what you've done?
Incredible.
I have so many ideas
for improvements.
And this. Oh, oh, man!
This--this is the bomb.
And I mean, red is so much cooler
than green, am I right?
Hmm. I am really starting
to like this guy.
Hey, what's that for?
[sighs]
Distracting me
from work.
So where's mr. Diggle?
He's running down a lead.
We have this
handled, johnny.
I told oliver that already.
Seriously. It's an internal
A.R.G.U.S. Matter.
I told him that, too.
Listen, sweetie,
A guy who kills
with boomerangs?
That's a little outside
you guys' wheelhouse.
While exotic killers
are more...
Our thing.
You only call me "sweetie" when
you want something.
Is it working?
[beeping]
Hang on a second.
Is there a problem?
Something strange
with your id.
I'm going to have to detain you
for a minute.
Hmm.
If that's a problem,
I really don't care.
You know,
You should how you treat
people, my friend.
After all...
What goes around,
comes around.
[beeping]
I appreciate
the offer, johnny,
But really,
we have it handled.
[alarm sounding]
Is that your
"we have it handled" alarm?
[alarm continues]
We have a breach.
Initiate lockdown protocols.
[cell phone vibrates]
diggle.
We have a bit
of a situation here.
Our man's at A.R.G.U.S.
Lyla's here.
Oliver, this guy?
He's the real deal.
Our target is storming A.R.G.U.S.
And Lyla is there.
Cisco: Mm-hmm. Bad ass.
So cool!
It'll be over by the time
they get there.
[alarm continues]
Sweetie...
You only call me "sweetie"
when you want something.
No, chase, just
because we kiss,
It doesn't mean
anything, ok?
[sirens in distance]
Are you sure
you're ok?
What was that?
A better question--
Who attacked you?
And don't tell him it was an
internal A.R.G.U.S. Matter.
His name is Digger Harkness.
Former asis.
His specialty is weapons and
technology before he went rogue.
Started selling his services
to the highest bidder.
We caught him three years ago.
Well, looks like
he escaped.
Not exactly.
Harkness' skills
Made him an ideal recruit
for task force x.
You mean the suicide squad.
They had an op in tanzania.
Assassination
of a local warlord.
But the warlord
had bigger guns.
The mission went south...
And the team
had to be sanitized.
You mean killed, Lyla.
Waller couldn't be reached.
It was my call.
The micro bomb in Harkness' neck
must have malfunctioned.
We need to consider that every
A.R.G.U.S. Facility is compromised.
There's only one place
we can keep you safe.
How often does
oliver do this?
Felicity:
At least every Wednesday.
There's a lot of sweating.
I don't see what's
so hard about that.
I'm not sure
she should have called you.
Oliver doesn't
play well with others.
Ah, come on. Barry and oliver
kicked ass last week.
Yeah!
They were in, like...
A league of their own.
Yeah, that was, like,
a one time thing.
The dude was tossing around
exploding boomerangs.
They needed
some back-up.
And I need some dinner.
That salmon ladder made me hungry
for sushi.
And I need to get
some paperweights down here!
Caitlin: I should have
warned you about that.
Yeah.
Are you ok?
Can't work
for A.R.G.U.S.
Without making
a few enemies.
I'm sorry to involve
all of you in this.
Is that A.R.G.U.S.
Property?
It's evidence.
Hey!
Secret identity?
They're married.
Both: We're not married.
Or together.
Whatever.
He told her about me.
You didn't?
I keep secrets
for a living, man.
Ah.
My bad.
You're--you're--
The flash. Sushi?
We need a location on the man
who's after Lyla.
His name is Digger Harkness.
The first step is
to work the evidence--
Barry, can I speak
to you for a moment, please?
I appreciate your help back
at A.R.G.U.S.,
But we have this handled.
You don't want
to team up again?
Things work differently here.
Starling city is meaner.
I seem to remember helping you
pretty good last year,
And that was without powers.
I've been practicing
Everything you taught me.
I'm--I'm casing
new environments;
I'm not running in blind.
[exhales]
We do this my way.
Yes! This is
going to be awesome.
Ok, what's
our first move?
We need to reassemble
the evidence.
It will take some time,
but it'll--
But it'll be worth it.
Rad!
These are a bit more
teched out
Than the one you guys brought
to central city.
3D printed polymer with
a circuitry weave.
Some of harkness'
boomerangs exploded.
Oh, yeah, there are
grooves in here
That could definitely
pack a C4 charge.
Maybe if we figure out where
Harkness got the supplies,
We can use that
to track him.
These weren't made
by ka-boom-boomerang?
Ka-boom-boomerang?
Yeah, you know, he has
exploding boomerangs?
That's not your best.
Really? It makes
perfect sense--
cisco.
If harkness didn't make them,
we need to find out who did.
And who he made
the buy off of.
Marcos. You see
This collapsible
node design?
Dead giveaway.
That's his signature.
We need a location
on this...
Klaus marcos.
No known home address
or place of employment
For Marcos.
But he was arrested
Last year by
an officer quentin lance.
Dad, I absolutely
understand,
But my boss wants answers on
what the department is doing
About the rash of b&es
on the south side.
Well, you can tell'em
I got a whole squad on it,
But it can only
move so fast!
Hey, Laurel,
detective--
Captain. Cap--
captain. Sorry.
Don't worry about it.
It's been a while.
Is everything ok?
Oh, it's fine.
This is, uh,
Ah, bart allen, right?
You get hit by a bus or something?
Barry. It was lightning.
Huh. Ow. We worked together on
a case last year.
Barry's a friend.
He's in town
With the central city police
department
And I was hoping that you could
help with...
He'll explain.
Sure.
Oliver, can I talk
to you for a moment?
Yeah.
The arrow was in central city.
This is a follow-up.
Kind of.
I'm looking to
track down a suspect
You apprehended last
year--klaus markos.
You know where we might be able
to find him?
None of his last knowns
are checking out.
Well, I don't
really keep up on
On the skels I busted
walking the beat, you know?
I'm not real sentimental
that way.
Ok. Uh,
What did you
arrest him for?
Urmm...
Identity theft.
He was using some gizmo
to steal credit card numbers
For the bratva.
Russian mob.
Ok.
I cannot believe you're a member
of the russian mob!
Former member, probably.
We had a falling out last year.
This is where they run
their cyber crime operation.
Hey, nice outfit,
by the way.
This place
looks like a fortress.
Kalishnikovs everywhere.
Roy, take
the southeast corner.
Barry, scan the perimeter.
Dig--
I've got northwest.
Are you going to be ok?
You think I'll lose it because
Harkness is after Lyla?
I'm good.
I had eight seconds to kill.
Was that wrong?
What?
My friend wants to have
a conversation with you.
[groaning and grunting]
You made this
for Digger Harkness.
I want to know where he is.
Go to hell.
[groaning and grunting]
The only thing that hurts worse
than an arrow going in
Is an arrow coming out!
Whoa, hey, what are you doing?!
Getting information!
Where is he?!
I don't know!
He said he doesn't know!
He's lying. If you want
To be able to raise
your arm again,
Tell me where he is!
Here! Harkness gave it to me.
It's encrypted.
I had an order
ready for him.
I called,
he came.
I don't know where he is,
I swear.
I swear!
Felicity can crack
the encryption.
Use this to track
down harkness.
You tortured that guy.
I interrogated him.
[scoffs]
When my friend said your tactics
made you a criminal,
I defended you because I thought
you were supposed to be a hero.
I thought we were supposed to be
better than them.
Barry...
You live in central city,
Where it's sunny
all the time
And your enemies
get cute nicknames.
You're not in
central city.
Yeah.
I live in a city
Where my best friend
was murdered,
Where a woman that I loved was
shot full of arrows
And sent tumbling
off a rooftop.
Where my mother was murdered
right in front of me.
So before you--
my mother was murdered
In front of me, too.
But I don't use
my personal tragedies
As an excuse to just torture
whoever pisses me off.
Well, I'm sorry,
barry,
I'm not as emotionally
healthy as you are.
What's wrong
with you?!
When we agreed
that you were staying,
We decided that
it would be on my terms.
If that is proving
too difficult for you,
You know your way
back to central city.
Everything
all right between
you and speedy?
What? Roy?
Yeah, we're fine.
I meant him.
Oh.
We had a...
Difference of opinion about
the way the world works.
Yep.
I know what
that's like.
Well, sometimes
they don't see it.
There are people in the world
who deal only in extremes--
And it would be naive to think that
anything less than extreme measures
Will stop them.
Sometimes bravery
isn't enough.
Sometimes the world requires
us to be bold.
Whatever the personal cost.
Felicity: I got him.
He's in a warehouse at the corner of
infantino and adams.
Is that--
A.R.G.U.S. Spy satellite?
Yeah. Maybe.
Thermographic imaging
shows ten bodies inside.
Harkness knows we're coming.
I can track the cell phone's
position with this.
Cisco, you're
with Diggle and Roy.
I'll race you there.
Where's the bomb?
[speaking chinese]
My chinese sucks.
But that doesn't sound like
a location.
[grunting]
Last chance.
Your hands are shaking.
I knew.
You don't have it in you.
You've killed,
but torture is different.
For those with a conscience,
inflicting pain
Is more difficult
than inflicting death.
I'll figure it out.
No, you won't.
You don't have
the stomach for it.
I do.
To save all those
people, I do.
Where's the bomb?
Where's the bomb?!
[explosions]
You ok?
My daughter's mother tried
to detonate a bomb
In a man's head and now he's
trying to kill her.
So that would be a no.
Look, you don't know
me that well.
But I'm the type of guy who's only
thought about one thing--
How do I keep the people
I love safe?
Well, you seem to me
to be pretty good at that.
Maybe before.
I remember a world
where people
Didn't kill each other
with boomerangs.
Or walk on water?
Barry can run on water.
You guys, harkness
has been around
Long before
people like barry.
I mean, this world was crazy
Before all these meta-humans
and super powers, right?
What's--what's your point?
Well, maybe meta-humans
And superpowers
were given to us
To deal with the crazy.
You mean by god?
No. By a dark matter wave
Released from a failed
particle accelerated reaction.
Either way, I think
People like barry
are the hope
For saving people like us.
People like your wife
and daughter.
She's not his wife.
She's not my wife.
Ok.
Anyway, you see
my point, right?
Plus, you got to admit,
It's all pretty
freakin' cool, right?
[punching]
[men groaning]
You're late.
I knew he was there.
He's not dead,
right?
Tranq arrow.
Same thing I used
on you in central city.
Cisco has the van running.
I see you met
harkness' hired muscle.
Harkness isn't here.
Hey!
Where's digger harkness?
Never met 'em.
But he paid us 10 gs
to give you this.
Ten'll get you twenty
this belongs to harkness.
What does that mean?
That harkness played you.
[beep] I swear I turned
that off.
What?
Marko's phone.
I shut it down
after I decrypted it.
Did someone turn it
back on remotely?
And back trace
the trace?
We have to get
out of here now!
Hello, lyla.
It's been
a long time.
[grunting]
Guns!
Cabinet, third drawer!
Know what I like most
about boomerangs, lyla?
They're proof that things
can come back to haunt you.
You had a bomb in
the back of my head.
I have a little something special
for the back of yours.
Lyla! Get down!
No!
[gasping]
caitlin!
Caitlin!
Stop the bleeding.
I need lidocaine.
We have
epinephrine!
That'll work.
Hey, hey, stay with me!
Ok.
Just try and keep her awake.
Can you hear me? Lyla?
Lyla! Lyla!
Lyla!
She's not breathing!
John: Lyla!
Lyla!
She's not moving.
I've got her
stabilized,
But I can't operate
on her here.
Barry...
Starling general's
at eighth and wilcott.
Hkpf ided her
as sumilu kang.
She was a student at the
university of hong kong.
A biology textbook
in her backpack.
Apparently she was studying
to become a veterinarian.
He would have told me.
I just needed more time.
No, mr. Queen, what you needed
was conviction.
And the men who do things like
this have it.
Tonight you didn't.
I thought I could--
you thought what?
You could
reason with him?
Look around you, mr. Queen.
Look around and tell me
that the men
Who do this type of thing
understand reason.
There are people
in this world
Who deal only
in extremes.
It's naive to think
that anything less
Than extreme measures
will stop it.
The bomber was katsu cheng.
But make no
mistake...
This blood
is on your hands.
Cheng said I didn't have
the stomach for torture.
He was right!
Because you need
to practice.
Torture
is an art form.
It's a skill
one must cultivate.
How do I do that?
I think cheng was wrong.
I think you not only have
the stomach for this work;
You have the talent.
[dance music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
Felicity:
It feels wrong.
Being here,
it feels wrong.
Oliver needed to be alone.
He made that pretty clear.
Three doubles,
straight up.
You guys ok?
We're just having
a tough night.
Anything I can do
to help?
No. We're--we're good.
But thanks for the night off.
Yo, who was that hottie?
My ex-girlfriend.
Oliver's sister.
So stay away,
is what you're saying.
She's in surgery.
Mr. Diggle is with her.
She going to be ok?
I hope so.
She's strong.
How do you guys do it?
How do you guys live like this?
Where anyone you care about
could be struck down?
We haven't been
taking this seriously.
It's all been a game. We give
the bad guys code names.
I think the fact we go
up against meta-humans
Made it all
kind of clean.
Like, the fact that
they've got these powers
Makes what
they're doing less...
Real.
This is all my fault.
It's really not.
I tortured marcos
to give up that phone.
None of this would have happened
if it wasn't for me.
I get the feeling you don't
say that very often.
To do what I do, barry,
it takes...Conviction.
But...
More often than not,
It's the will
to do what's ugly.
Every time I do
that, I'm...
I'm trading away
little...
Pieces of myself.
So...You asked
what's wrong with me,
That's--
that's what's wrong,
Because the part
that I'm trading away
Is oliver queen.
And lately I've been
feeling like there is...
Nothing left
except the arrow.
I think you're full of crap.
Look,
You've convinced yourself
That everything
you've been through
Took away your humanity.
But I think it's because
of your humanity
That you made it through.
You wouldn't have survived,
Much less come out
the other end a hero,
Somebody who wants to do good,
If you didn't have
a light inside of you.
[door opens]
I'm sorry
if I'm interrupting.
I ran facial recognition
on harkness and I have a match.
Where is he?
Get on the ground.
[laughs]
Why would I want
to do that?
You hurt a friend of mine.
You really think
there's anywhere
In the world
you could run where
we won't find you?
Hmm, probably not.
Which is why I have
a contingency in place.
[beep]
Five bombs planted
throughout starling.
Now, you can stop me,
Or you can stop
the bombs.
But you can't do both.
Bombs are armed.
In 90 seconds,
This city
will be on fire.
Go.
Guys! Harkness just triggered
five bombs throughout the city.
We don't know where.
To blanket the entire city,
he'd have to use--
Radio controlled ieds.
But if we key into
the detonator's frequency...
We can pinpoint
the location of the bombs.
[groans]
Barry: I need a location!
I need five locations!
The five receivers.
Nearest one
Is behind a restaurant
at faith and flower.
Ok, hey, guys, I found it.
I'm going to run it
out of the city.
Barry, wait!
That's not an option.
We think the bombs
might be linked.
What?
Press the emblem
on your suit.
I installed a mini-cam there
last week.
Ok. You see
the secondary trigger?
It's not just
a receiver...
It's a transmitter.
Barry, if you try
to defuse the bomb,
The secondary trigger's
going to transmit a signal
And the rest of the bombs
are going to explode.
We're running out of time.
You have to defuse all the bombs
at the same time.
You're thinking of
multiplex. I can't be
In five places at once.
But I don't have to be.
Stop the countdown!
Go to hell.
Last chance!
Or what?
You'll inflict pain?
Ah, I can tell you've done it before,
so let me ask you this--
Why are you hesitating?
Whoa!
Ten more seconds.
We should be able
to see at least, ah,
Three explosions
from here.
Ok.
Everyone has
to cut their wire
Exactly on three.
1, 2,
3!
[exhales]
Screw you,
captain boomerang.
You think you've accomplished
something here?
You think you not killing me
makes you strong?
It just means...
You're weak.
It means I have
some humanity left.
[groaning]
You just couldn't
resist, could you?
Hey, sweetie.
You only call me "sweetie" when
you want something.
I do.
I want you
to marry me.
I can't believe
I waited this long to ask.
I need you,
Lyla.
Now, forever, official.
I need you.
Will you please
stop talking...
So I can say yes?
[both moaning]
Some of the str markers
on the dna sample
Have degraded, but I've got
a computer back at the lab
That I think will
help fill in the gaps.
Thank you,
caitlin.
I'll let you know as soon as
I have the results.
I'll call this time.
Roy: It's cool.
You guys are fun.
So are you guys.
Well, you could be
if you realized
You were working
under a nightclub.
Oh, did you guys
take care of business?
Digger harkness
is now cell mates
With one
slade wilson.
We've got a pipeline, he's got
a gorgeous tropical island.
With landmines.
Caitlin: Hmm?
What?
It's a long story.
What's this?
Oliver helped me
put that in while
You guys were
at the hospital.
Wait, this
is for me?
For the next time
you're in town.
There'll be
a next time?
I'm still calling the shots.
We'll talk about that.
Yes, we will.
And then I'll call the shots.
We got a gift
for you, too, oliver.
Early christmas present.
Turns out S.T.A.R. Labs'
industrial fabricator
Was based out
of starling, so...
Polymer kevlar weave.
It's 25% lighter and
can carry 15% more gear.
I've got designs I'm working up that
I'm really excited by.
It's, uh,
it's subtle.
I wanted
to replace the hood,
But, uh, felicity said it had
sentimental value.
Thank you.
Any time.
You guys headed back?
It's possible
That dr. Wells didn't
sign off on us leaving town.
Hey, do you still,
like, take the train?
Yeah, sure, if I feel
like taking a nap.
But oliver and I have
some unfinished business
To take care of first.
You guys aren't going
To punch each other,
are you?
Why'd you summon me here?
To make me feel worse?
No, I summoned you here to give you
a second chance.
Is this a joke?
No.
This is
li khuan hui.
That name should sound
familiar to you.
You work for china white.
Chien na wei. Yes, mr. Hui
is on her payroll.
He's chinese triad,
And he knows her agenda
here in hong kong.
Fortunately for you,
mr. Hui has been
Less than forthcoming
with the details.
Fortunately?
You get a stab
at redemption.
Barry: You could have invited
everybody, they'd like this.
Oliver: Well, no, they would
love this,
But this is just
for the two of us.
You mean, the one of you.
This was your idea.
You can't expect me
to believe
That you don't want to know,
once and for all,
Who would win--
Me or you.
You mean if you don't
shoot me in the back.
You got to get
over that, barry.
Ok, I have super powers.
You have arrows that run out.
I have strategy
and tactical awareness.
When I'm fighting you, it's literally
like you're standing still.
[chuckles] that's tough talk,
you ready to back it up?
Oh, yeah.
Hey, by the way...
Yeah?
You were wrong.
When you told me
I could inspire people,
You said you couldn't.
But you were wrong--
you can inspire.
Not as the arrow,
that guy's a douche.
[laughs]
But as oliver queen.
Thank you.
Since we're sharing,
You were wrong, too.
When?
Right now.
Because you think
you can kick my ass.
I can tell.
All right, well, if you think
you can kick mine,
You better do it fast.
I get it, barry,
I get it. You're fast.
Ready...
Set...