Previously, on "Arrow"...
You have but two choices--
ascend to the calling of Ra's al Ghul,
or you will spend
the rest of your days
in a cage.
I love you.
Wow.
Lance knows.
The whole city knows, Oliver.
Mr. Queen should be considered armed
and highly dangerous.
Captain Lance...
I'm here
to turn myself in.
What the hell
are your men doing?
I told them to stand down.
Get down on the ground!
You've got the wrong guy.
Oliver Queen isn't the Arrow.
I am.
Bethany Snow: To repeat,
we're just getting word
from the authorities
that Roy Harper,
a Glades resident with a long history
of run-ins with the police,
has been identified as the vigilante
known as the Arrow...
What the hell
was that?
Probably just
a power surge.
That wasn't a power
surge. Check it out.
Bethany: There were earlier reports
implicating Oliver Queen,
now appear...
Bethany: ...Transported
to SCPD by police caravan,
and should be
arriving imminently.
We're now going live
to the SCPD.
All right, let's go.
Get him, come on.
All right, bring him,
come on, come on.
Is it safe to assume you're calling off
the manhunt for Queen?
No comment.
Come on, bring him through.
You proud of yourself?
Letting the kid take the fall?
I'm not going
to let him do that.
Give me a pen and paper,
I will sign a full confession.
Oliver, not another word.
Uncuff him.
Sure,
in 25 to life.
More like right now.
Habeas writ.
The district
attorney's office
won't be pursuing
charges against Oliver Queen
while it's charging
Roy Harper with the same crime.
Nice try. Five hours ago,
Queen turned himself in.
He confessed!
To you, alone
and uncorroborated.
And then the Arrow
turned himself in.
Your so-called
confession
is looking rather
fabricated right about now.
That's just crap.
The D.A. is
ordering Oliver
to be released.
Are you the only one
who's allowed to put themselves
above the law?
This isn't over.
What the hell are you doing?
I'm just making sure you.
both don't end up in prison.
Ray: Hey.
What are you doing here?
Proofing the quarterly
earnings report.
And finalizing the subsonic ionizer
patent application,
and I'm trying to debug
the sequential--
I mean, what are you
doing here?
Oliver and Roy Harper
are both in handcuffs.
I have a lot
of work to do.
And Oliver was released.
How do you know
about Roy Harper?
Apart from it being plastered
all over the television,
I'm able to put one
and one together,
and I get that
Oliver's sister's boyfriend
is obviously
part of your team.
Obviously.
You ok?
Yes.
How are you?
Pss, yeah.
Let's--let's not
get into that. Uh...
I said "I love you,"
but it was like, heh,
it was like with a lowercase "l,"
you know, not, um, so
let's not make it a thing.
Um...You know,
you had just saved my life,
I had 6.2 billion nano-robots
coursing through my epithalamus,
and my emotions were
a little all over the place.
Well, I'll let you get back
to work-slash-worry,
and, um...
Keep a good thought for Roy.
Ok.
What were you thinking,
Roy?
Tell me why.
Do you remember what I told you
when I found out you were the Arrow?
Yeah. You told me
I saved your life.
Now I get
to save yours.
I can't let you do that.
Oliver, ever since
I found out
that I killed that cop,
I have been trying
to make it right as Arsenal.
But maybe what I need
to do is make it right as the Arrow.
No, Roy...
I killed a police offer.
Mirakuru or not,
I should be punished for that.
I should be in prison.
That won't bring
the officer back.
This city still needs you.
It needs you more.
For the first time
since I remember what I did...
I'm ok.
You sure
this place is safe?
Safe as I can manage.
Who's that?
Someone eager
to repay a debt.
Ok, but for how long?
Waller has men all over
Hong Kong looking for us.
Even if we could make
it out of the city,
there's nowhere we could run where
Waller won't find us.
So, what are
we going to do?
I'm going
to find Waller first.
You're going to break
into A.R.G.U.S. by yourself?
No.
He's going
to walk in.
My passcard
to the field office.
What do you want?
Setting Harper up as your patsy.
I applaud the gamble--
I had nothing to do
with Roy turning himself in...
But I will
get him out.
And then what?
Ra's won't stop
until you're wearing
the Demon's Head ring on your hand.
It's not going
to happen.
People are being murdered.
Your days as the Arrow
are finished.
But of course, no one
close to you has died.
Have you considered that
leading the League of Assassins
might be a preferable outcome
as to what alternatives
Ra's might devise?
I have a lot
of work to do.
I'm going to break
Roy out of prison.
Ironically, before
turning to vigilantism,
Harper was
a career criminal,
with an arrest record
for breaking and entering,
petty theft, and grand
larceny. Until recently--
Thea...
Please tell me it wasn't you
that put him up to this.
Of course not,
but I'm going to do
everything in my power
to make it right.
Are you ok?
I'm fine,
but we need to get
Roy out of prison.
Well, it looks like we might have
another problem
to add to our
ever-growing list.
Bethany: ...Multiple
homicide at Starling National Bank.
Channel 52 has acquired
surveillance footage of the incident...
Makes sense.
As a bank-robbing meta-human,
why stay in Central City when you have
plenty of banks and no Arrow?
Ok. Ok,
we need a plan
to extract Roy.
In the meantime,
Felicity, call
S.T.A.R. Labs,
see if they're tracking any meta-humans
that have left Central City.
SCPD. According
to city records,
you got a basement
down here.
You already have
Roy Harper in custody.
Yeah, and I got
a warrant that says
I can search
that basement.
Sorry for the rush,
but I didn't want
to give you a chance
to turn that place
into a storage
room again.
Gentlemen.
Here you go.
Break it down.
I got you now,
you son of a bitch.
♪ Arrow 3x19 ♪
Broken Arrow
Original Air Date on April 15, 2015
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Oh, uh, my Chinese
is a little rusty,
but this looks like a crate from
the North China Sea.
You've spent some
time there, right?
And this is my favorite.
You actually put those
things on display?
Captain, we have
fingerprint matches
for the latents we lifted
off all this equipment.
Hold that thought.
What do you got?
We only got one match.
What is it?
Roy Harper.
Roy--
just--
Uh, did you check
the other computers?
Captain Lance,
it's clear--
Shut up! Whatever line of crap
you're thinking about giving me,
you just save it.
Smart as you all are,
you are bound to make
a mistake eventually.
And I'm going to be there
when it happens.
You wiped the entire place?
And moved some of your more
sensitive trunk items. You're welcome.
But you didn't wipe
Roy's prints.
Oliver, Roy
already confessed.
We didn't see any point in
losing both of you.
I'm not losing Roy.
What about that meta-human
that is out there
killing people?
We need to grab
my back-up weapons cache
in the secondary layer.
You see those
plainclothes?
Lance will have them follow you
everywhere you go.
You try to nab even so much as
a purse snatcher,
and they'll pounce.
Somebody needs
to protect this city.
We are dealing with a meta-human.
Call Barry.
Oh, he can't help
right now, mm-mmm.
He's got on a lot on his plate with
Dr. Wells, I think.
It's really hard
to keep up with him.
But...What if there's someone else
that could help?
Oh, hey, Felicity,
check this out.
I finally got
the neural network online,
so when my brain tells
the gauntlet to wave, and...
Hi.
Sorry to hear about
what's happening to you.
Uh, if there's anything
I can do to help...
Well, actually,
that's why we're here.
Oh.
You know how I try
to keep my work life
and my other work
life separate.
I meant to tell you that.
Did I tell you that?
Well, there's a--
there's a meta
in Starling City
that's killing people.
A meta, as in human?
Yeah.
So, obviously
we need to catch this
plasma death thing guy.
Ugh, now I see why Cisco
gives them all names.
The police are
all over Oliver,
so...we need you.
And you're ok with this?
We need your help.
So it's
a team up. High-five!
Don't shoot!
What the hell is going on?
They've been
holding me here for weeks.
What, you don't
trust me?
Look at him.
He's army,
not A.R.G.U.S.
Oh, so you're saying
this is General Shrieve?
He held me hostage.
Targeted you
and the Yamashiros,
for death.
Why would he do that?
The Alpha omega.
Shrieve plans
to unleash it on Hong Kong,
claiming that
the Triad mishandled
a bio weapon they never
should have had.
That's insane.
Well, Shrieve
seems to think that
China is a military
and economic threat.
So he'd kill himself
and his men
just to hurt China?
His team has
developed a vaccine
they can inoculate
themselves with.
Run.
Get as far away
from Hong Kong as you can.
If you make it...
I hope we meet
again someday.
Inmate: You better watch
your back in here, hood.
Second inmate: You're dead,
Arrow, you're dead.
How are you?
I told the guards
I didn't want to see you.
Why?
Roy, please.
Tell me what is going on.
When we got
back together,
hell, even before
that, I...
I made a promise to myself that
I would never lie to you again.
Ok.
That's why I didn't
want to see you.
I don't want to break
that promise.
Why would you?
Roy!
Thea...
Thea, please just...
Know that I'm
going to be fine.
Is that a lie?
Oliver: Thea, don't worry.
Roy's not going to be
in there much longer.
I'm working on it.
Bye.
Roy holding up?
For now.
Hot off the presses.
What are those?
I visited
the bank today.
Uh, manager's
a friend of mine.
I beat him at squash
every Tuesday.
And I took a few photos
of the crime scene.
Actually, "photos"
is a bit reductive
these are enhanced
resonance scans.
It occurred to me that
if we can't see his face
because
of the radiation,
we need to remove
the radiation.
Oh, I could kiss you
right now. Awkward, sorry.
Boundaries.
We're working on it.
So, if we interlace the
resonant scan's frequency with our
news footage,
we get this.
There he is.
Run a facial recognition.
Way ahead of you.
Jake Simmons.
He's already in the system.
Serial bank robber,
which explains Starling National.
Last known address,
Central City.
Where is he now?
He was last seen
on a traffic camera
at the corner
of Gantner and Yount.
There's a processing
plant there;
he went in, never came out.
On it.
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
hold on a second.
I thought the whole point
of this team-up
was you not being spotted
out as a vigilante.
Stop calling it
a team-up, Ray.
This Jake Simmons
is not just a meta-human,
he is a killer.
And you're not ready for that.
Look, I'm--I'm not going to try to
equate our experiences,
but superpowers
are based in science,
and I am a man
of science.
So if there's any way
to defeat this guy,
I'm the one who's best able
to figure it out.
Fine.
The second that you get in
over your head...
I'll run.
Fly, probably.
Ray: How many abandoned
warehouses do you think are in this city?
No, no, I'm--I'm
genuinely curious.
Oliver: Stay
focused, Ray.
Maybe Simmons
isn't in there.
Do you get this anxious
when I'm out in the field?
I honestly can't think of an answer
to that question
that doesn't
get me in trouble.
Still nothing.
Not a visual sighting or any
other reading at all from the atom.
And when I say atom,
I mean the suit,
not myself
in the third person.
There's a decent chance
that you and Palmer
are related.
Well, that's
equally fascinating
and terrifying.
Be my eyes, Ray,
what's going on?
Oh, tin man?
You shouldn't be here.
Actually, I should.
See, you're the bad guy,
and I am--
Ray?!
Thanks for the top off.
Ray!
Felicity: Ray,
where are you?
Ray, Ray!
Oh, my God, Ray,
are you hurt?
Heh, "hurt" would be
a step or two up
from how I feel right now.
But...just a second.
You're lucky to have gotten
out of there alive.
It wasn't that
bad, was it?
It was way worse, Ray.
Right.
I need shields!
That's not the answer.
You need to anticipate
your opponent.
You need to trust
your instincts
and not just
your tech.
My instinct
is to trust my tech.
Ray, when I'm out in the field,
my bow, my arrows,
those are just tools.
I'm the weapon.
That's poetic.
My point is that
if you rely on that suit
more than you rely
on yourself...
It's going
to get you killed.
So when is Shrieve going
to distribute the virus?
I don't know. If he's going to pin it
on the Triad, though,
he'll have
to do it soon.
We need to get out
of Hong Kong.
My contact says Shrieve
has men everywhere,
with even more resources
at his disposal than Waller ever had.
Shrieve has assured
we won't get off this island alive.
Well, if we can't run,
Waller said Shrieve
had a vaccine
for the virus.
You want to steal
some of the vaccine?
He has to have it
somewhere in Hong Kong.
Get down!
Let's see how good you are
without your arrows.
Good enough.
Just remember--
that was without arrows.
Get down, on the floor!
All right, turn this
place inside out.
We know how this guy loves
his secret hiding places.
Hey, Frank.
What brings you out
of your downtown office?
The Chief of D's asked me
to have a word with you.
Yeah?
What about?
He wants to know
why you're still going Ahab
on Oliver Queen when we got
a different suspect already in custody.
We got a patsy in custody. Trust me,
Queen is our guy.
Well, there's no evidence
against Queen.
Why do you think
I'm searching his condo?
Friend to friend--
you've come so far.
You're a captain.
Don't throw all your hard work
away on something personal.
Look, I don't know what
it is you think that you're going to find,
but it's not here.
There's nothing here!
Kind of like how there was
nothing in the basement of your club?
You're either complicit or just about
the most naive girl I ever met.
You know that your brother
is letting your boyfriend
rot in prison
for his crimes, right?
Get out of my home.
I know you went
to visit Harper yesterday.
Does he even know why
he's throwing his life away?
Lance.
Is he all right?
All right,
I'll be right there.
Your boyfriend
was just attacked.
He's all right, but I can't imagine
it'll be the last time.
Your brother dropped
a lot of bodies.
And when, and it's not if, it is
when Roy gets a shiv in the back,
that body will be on him, too.
The suit recorded
over ten terabytes of data,
which were uploaded
in real time
to a geosynchronous
satellite.
That is a huge
energy suck.
This is all fascinating.
How do we find Simmons?
Light bulb, literally.
I--no, actually,
figuratively.
Uh, just
before Simmons beat me,
I blasted him with my
compressed light beams,
and he thanked me
for topping him off.
He absorbs energy and turns it into
weaponized plasma.
And if we can manually get into
the city's power grid,
we might be able to track where he's
getting his extra juice.
Thea: Ollie!
What's going on?
It's Roy!
He was attacked
by a bunch of inmates.
He's fine, but there's
hundreds of them in there!
I'm going
to break him out.
Oliver. You can end up
in a cell right next to him.
John, if you know
what's good for you,
you'll get out
of my way.
Oliver, if you know
what's good for you--
and for Roy--you're going
to need to stay put.
I can't do that.
Oliver, listen--
Get your hands
off of me!
Listen, I know what
you're going through, man!
You have to rely on Palmer
to take care of this meta
while Roy sits in a prison.
But listen to me, man--
you have to throttle this back,
Oliver. You have to.
Before you lose everything.
I've already lost
everything.
I'm not going
to lose Roy.
Oliver!
I can't believe
that you and Diggle are ok
just sitting
on your hands while Roy
fights off all of Iron Heights!
It is not that simple!
No, Felicity,
if anything was ever simple,
it's this.
Then what? You're
going to jail, too?
I can't just do nothing.
I think John's right.
I think you're struggling
with doing nothing;
with Roy, with Ray,
but right now,
you need people to help you.
You need to let them.
Maybe...there is
something more
going on with you than just what's
happening with Roy
and this meta-human.
You have sacrificed
everything to be the Arrow.
Even you and me.
But...
Whether or not you break Roy
out of Iron Heights,
there is no more Arrow.
Ra's took that
from you.
I was told once that a man
cannot live by two names.
Well, right now,
I can't live by either.
So I don't know who I am.
I know who you are.
Whether you're
in a--in a suit
or under a hood,
you're the man that I...
You're the man
that I believe in.
Uh, Ray finished
the transponder.
I have to upload it
to a power source
and, uh, hopefully it'll bring us
right to Simmons.
I'll go with you.
It is adorable
how you keep forgetting
that Lance is after you,
but, uh, it's a quick errand
and you need practice
in letting people help you.
You sure this is it?
It doesn't look like
a typical army base.
Matthew Shrieve isn't
a typical army general, apparently.
Quiet!
Where's the vaccine?
You can end up
unconscious
or you can
end up dead.
Two lefts,
second door on your right.
Good choice.
Somebody coming.
10 seconds.
Up there.
Thank you.
Can you give us
a minute?
I already signed
my confession.
Yeah, it's a hell
of a story.
All that stuff about
setting up shop
under your
girlfriend's club.
And I particularly like how
you managed not to implicate her.
What are you doing here?
You remember that, uh,
that corpse
I showed you?
The one that
the Arrow killed?
I knew you had
an obsession with the Arrow.
And, hey, I was trying
to wave you off
'cause I knew,
just somehow I knew,
that if you stayed
obsessed with him,
that you would
come to a bad end.
And here I am.
Two years later, I'm still trying
to save you, son.
I don't need saving.
Look, I know you got to be doing this
'cause you think you owe Queen something.
But you don't.
You don't deserve to be here.
Patrol officer Gabe Vincent
left behind a wife
and a nine-year-old boy.
I know.
I killed him.
I stabbed him in the chest
with an Arrow.
So don't think for a second
that I don't deserve to be here.
No. You don't
think for a second
that what you're doing here makes up
for any of at you did out there.
Guard.
I'm sorry, miss,
but I don't think
you're supposed to be here.
I'm supposed to access
your grid for the city.
Think you can help?
Sure.
It's this way.
Thank you.
So, uh,
what's with
the sunglasses, man?
We're indoors
and it's, well, night.
Do you have a sensitivity
to the--
To light?
No.
I love the light.
Do you think the plan to find
Simmons will work?
Well, it's Felicity,
so, yes.
Heh. Except the tracking
firmware seems to be malfunctioning.
What?
It's not a malfunction.
It's Simmons.
He's drawing energy
directly from a power station.
Which one?
The one Felicity
just went to.
Come on, Felicity,
pick up.
I'm sorry, but the blonde can't
come to the phone at the moment.
I swear to God,
if you hurt her--
You'll what...
fly away again?
I am talking
to the man in the suit,
right? The one who thinks a piece
of scrap metal
makes him some
kind of hero?
It doesn't.
I am sorry
for the interruption.
Where were we?
Waiting for you
to come closer.
Diggle...
Oliver, you can't go out there.
It's Felicity!
Oliver, you won't
make it in time.
Power station is still
eight minutes away
going 60 on the Ducati.
But the Atom?
Well, the Atom can fly.
You need more than
your tech this time!
You're right.
My tech and your instinct,
maybe there's
a way we can get him.
Ok, I'm entering
the power station now.
Activate the link.
It's working! Oh,
I'm just a passenger now.
Ooh. Let's get this guy.
Sorry.
But I have
to kill you now.
No, and you're going
to leave her the hell alone.
Kick his ass.
You ok?
You got to get out of here!
No! I'm not going
to leave you here alone.
Ray, get her
out of there!
I'm not alone,
but I can't fight him
and worry about you,
now, go, Felicity!
No!
Felicity, go!
Get out of here!
I'm really hoping
you played video games as a kid.
I'm trying to concentrate.
Sorry, sorry,
it's just, I'm trusting
you with my--
Ray, can you take this beating?
I can pull you back.
I'm fine. Get this bastard!
Ray, I've lost control.
The transmitter's been severed.
Get up.
Get up, Ray!
Fight back, Ray,
fight back! Ray!
He's too strong!
This is not about strength.
This is about heart.
When the mayor was killed,
you put yourself
in harm's way to save Felicity.
Normal people,
they don't do that.
Heroes do that.
Fight back!
Come on, Ray!
Take him out, Ray.
Oh, I'm sorry, sorry!
No, it was
totally worth it.
Felicity: Are you ok?
I was so worried.
Ray: I'm fine.
Everything's ok now.
Guard: Eyes front, Harper.
I told you, eyes front.
My instincts are
to keep my head on a swivel.
Won't happen again.
No, it won't.
Thea?
It's Roy.
Harper was killed
an hour ago.
I'd say I'm sorry,
but I think we both know
whose fault this is.
I shouldn't have listened
to either of you.
I might not have been
able to save Roy...
But I'd feel better right now
if I tried.
We know that, Oliver.
We also know you may
never forgive us.
I make my own
choices, John.
I made this one.
He doesn't mean
forgive us for that.
He means...
forgive us for this.
How?
Don't be mad at them.
This was my idea.
If any one of us were
in there and Oliver was here,
he would think of something.
You're right.
If one of us deserves
to go to prison, it's me.
Roy, we can't allow
you to do that.
There's no way in hell Oliver's
going along with it.
That's why you're not
going to tell him.
You could have
gotten yourself killed for real.
I figured that I could hold off
until Dig's guys got into position.
One of Lyla's contacts,
an A.R.G.U.S. freelancer.
Has a special talent for knifing people
in just the right way.
Leaves a convincing
amount of blood without the kill.
He laces the blade with a beta blocker,
crawl the heartbeat.
Gives the illusion of death.
Everyone thinks
the Arrow is dead.
Which means
Oliver Queen is innocent.
You did all this
without asking.
How many times have you
saved one of us without asking?
This time we had to save you.
If everyone thinks
you're dead...
Then what happens
to Roy Harper?
Tell Thea, well, tell her
I'm alive, first.
Then tell her that I'm sorry I had
to leave without saying good-bye.
I feel like you're throwing
your life away.
I'm not.
I'm starting
a new one.
Anywhere,
any time.
You need something,
you call me.
Take care of yourself, Roy.
I'll miss you most
of all, Scarecrow.
Just be ready to get
a million calls
on that untraceable
satellite phone
I stuffed
in your bag.
Thank you.
So, on a scale
of one to ten,
how...mad at us are you?
I need to learn
to let people help me.
Yeah.
You could use
the practice in that.
I just think sometimes
you're so focused
on people you love,
you forget...
to see that there are people
who love you.
Just enough
innoculant for us.
And Akio.
What about her?
We need to inject Akio
and ourselves
and then the three of you
need to get somewhere safe.
And what about you?
I lifted this when
I took the vaccine.
And clearly, it belongs
to one of Shrieve's men,
because it has the plans for how
they are going to distribute the virus.
I'm going to use it
to stop them.
No. You won't.
We are.
Tatsu!
What example are we
setting for our son
if we have a hope to save
millions of innocent people,
but only save ourselves?
Listen to me--
the two of you need
to take care of Akio.
I am not going
to be responsible--
You need to learn
to let people help you.
And Maseo and I are going to.
What about...
Deathbolt.
Nice!
Mmm. You know,
you're the only other person
who's good at the names.
So, uh, how do
they get fed?
And, you know,
complete the transaction,
so to speak?
Cisco?
You said Simmons
is from Central City, right?
Yeah. Last known address,
4160 Dixon Canyon. Why?
According to this,
Jake Simmons was a guest
of the Opal City
police department
on December 11th,
2013.
What do I know that date from?
That was the date
of the particle accelerator test.
But if Simmons
wasn't in Central City
the night of the dark matter
explosion, then...
How can he be
a meta-human?
Do you know
who I am, child?
You're the Demon.
I am the Demon's Head.
As those were before me,
and very soon,
your brother.
He will never take your place.
He will.
Once I've given him
sufficient motivation.
Oh, my brother's
going to kill you!
No.
He's going to beg me.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man