MY NAME IS OLIVER QUEEN.
AFTER 6 YEARS
OF BEING A VIGILANTE,
THE ONLY WAY TO ACHIEVE MY GOAL
AND SAVE MY CITY WAS TO CONFESS
TO BEING THE GREEN ARROW.
NOW MY FAMILY AND FRIENDS MUST
CARRY ON MY MISSION WITHOUT ME.
I AM NO LONGER A HERO.
I AM INMATE 4587.
PREVIOUSLY ON "ARROW"...
HMM?
FELICITY, DON'T.
WE NEED HIM
TO HELP OLIVER.
I MADE A DEAL
WITH THE FEDS, A TRADE...
DIAZ FOR YOUR HUSBAND.
OLIVER'S COMING HOME?
WHY'D YOU KILL DUNBAR?
I DIDN'T KILL
THAT GUARD.
OLIVER: YOUR BLADE SAYS YOU DID.
GUARDS FOUND
PRINTS ON IT.
TURNER, YOU'RE
GOING TO THE HOLE.
W-WAIT. YOU GOT
THE WRONG GUY.
IF YOU HADN'T FOUND
TURNER'S BLADE,
IT WOULD HAVE BEEN
ALL OVER FOR ME.
YOU WERE IN THE HOLE,
STANLEY,
SO HOW'D YOU KNOW
IT WAS TURNER'S BLADE?
I GUESS I MUST HAVE
HEARD IT SOMEWHERE.
GOOD MORNING, 4587.
A BEAUTIFUL DAY.
BE READY FOR AN ESCORT
TO RECEIVING AND
RELEASING IN 6 HOURS.
AS OF THIS AFTERNOON,
YOU WILL BE A PAIN
IN SOMEONE ELSE'S ASS.
[GATE BUZZES]
GUARD: RICARDO DIAZ.
DID YOU KNOW QUEEN'S
GETTING OUT OF HERE TODAY?
I DID, ACTUALLY.
HE TOLD ME...
WHEN I TOLD HIM HOW
MUCH I WAS GONNA PAY.
GET ME A CHANGE OF CLOTHES.
GET RID OF THEM.
I GOT A SCORE TO SETTLE.
[CHUCKLES]
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
YOU'RE GONNA GET OUT
OF HERE,
BE ABLE TO EAT REAL FOOD,
NOT THIS CRAP.
I'M REALLY HAPPY
FOR YOU, MAN.
I MEAN, I'M GONNA MISS YOU,
BUT THE GREEN ARROW
NEVER SHOULD'VE BEEN
PUT BEHIND BARS.
REMEMBER WHEN I TOLD YOU
THAT I WAS WRONGFULLY
ACCUSED?
I WAS THINKING MAYBE NOW
THAT YOU'RE GETTING OUT,
YOU COULD ASK YOUR
FRIEND LAUREL
TO HELP WITH MY APPEAL, TOO.
STOP.
I KNOW. IT'S A BIG ASK,
BUT, HONESTLY, I DON'T KNOW
HOW LONG I CAN SURVIVE
IN HERE WITHOUT YOU.
STANLEY, I'M NOT
GONNA HELP YOU, OK,
BECAUSE IN HERE IS
EXACTLY
WHERE YOU BELONG.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
YOU KILLED DUNBAR, AND
THEN YOU MANIPULATED ME
INTO BLAMING TURNER
FOR IT.
[CHUCKLING]
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
OLIVER, WE'RE, LIKE,
BEST FRIENDS.
WE WERE NEVER FRIENDS.
I WAS JUST DOING WHAT
THE GREEN ARROW ALWAYS DOES
TO BAD GUYS.
I DON'T KILL
INNOCENT PEOPLE.
BUT YOU HURT THEM.
REMEMBER WHAT YOU DID
TO YORKE?
TO THOSE OTHER GUARDS
TO GET SENT TO LEVEL 2?
PRISON CHANGES PEOPLE.
IT DIDN'T CHANGE ME.
WHEN I GET OUT OF HERE,
I PROMISE YOU...
YOU WILL FACE JUSTICE
FOR WHAT YOU DID.
IF YOU DO THAT,
I'M GONNA SPEND THE REST
OF MY LIFE IN HERE.
I KNOW.
THAT'S WHAT YOU DESERVE.
DON'T DO THIS.
DON'T DO THIS TO ME.
BRICK: I HEARD THE NEWS...
EARLY RELEASE.
YOU'RE A LUCKY BOY.
TOO BAD TURNER
WASN'T SO LUCKY.
YOU KNOW, AFTER TODAY,
YOU'RE NEVER GONNA SEE
MY FACE AGAIN.
BRICK: TOSSERS LIKE YOU
DON'T STAY ON
THE OUTSIDE FOR LONG.
WOULDN'T BE SURPRISED IF YOU
WAS BACK HERE PRETTY SOON.
THIS AIN'T GOOD-BYE, QUEEN.
TURNER.
YOU HAVE A DEATH WISH
OR SOMETHING?
I'M GONNA FIND MY WAY
OUT OF HERE.
AND WHEN I DO,
I'M COMING FOR YOU.
I KNOW THAT YOU DIDN'T
KILL OFFICER DUNBAR.
I MADE A MISTAKE,
AND I'M SORRY.
WHAT THE HELL DO I CARE
IF YOU'RE SORRY?
I'M GETTING RELEASED.
I'M GONNA MAKE THIS
RIGHT FOR YOU.
OF COURSE YOU'RE
GETTING OUT TODAY.
I'M GONNA SPEAK WITH
LYLA MICHAELS
AT A.R.G.U.S.,
AND I'LL JUST SEE
IF WE
CAN MAKE SOME KIND
OF DEAL, OK?
YEAH, I KNOW HOW MUCH
PROMISES ARE WORTH
TO PEOPLE LIKE YOU,
ESPECIALLY WHEN YOU
MAKE THEM TO PEOPLE LIKE ME.
THAT'S NOT TRUE.
YEAH. YOU THINK
I'M A CRIMINAL...
YOU SAID IT YOURSELF...
AND CRIMINALS
BELONG BEHIND BARS.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT?
I THINK THAT YEARS AGO,
YOU SAVED LYLA'S LIFE.
NOW, I DON'T KNOW
IF YOU CAN BE THAT KIND
OF HERO AGAIN...
BUT I THINK YOU DESERVE
THE CHANCE TO TRY.
[INDISTINCT P.A. ANNOUNCEMENTS]
I HAVE TO GO.
I'M GONNA
MAKE THIS RIGHT.
GET UP, 4587.
YOU GOT A VISITOR.
HELLO, OLIVER.
HUH.
I SEE THAT PRISON LIFE
HASN'T BEEN TREATING
YOU SO WELL.
YOU LISTEN TO ME
VERY CAREFULLY.
I DON'T THINK YOU'RE
IN THE PLACE
TO BE GIVING DEMANDS
RIGHT NOW...
GIRL: HI, DADDY.
NOT UNLESS YOU WANT
A WHOLE BUNCH OF
INNOCENT PEOPLE TO DIE.
[SIGHS]
WHEN I HEARD THAT...
YOU WERE GETTING
RELEASED TODAY,
IT FELT AS IF...
MY LAST CHANCE AT PAYBACK
WAS GETTING AWAY.
AND I COULDN'T HAVE THAT.
SO THAT'S YOUR PLAY?
YOU'RE GONNA COME AFTER
ME IN A FEDERAL PRISON?
MM-HMM.
SEE, I'VE BEEN IN AND OUT
OF PLACES LIKE THIS
MY WHOLE LIFE.
I KNOW HOW TO HANDLE
GUARDS LIKE THAT.
NOW, YOU, BROTHER...
THEY DON'T SEE YOU AS
GREEN ARROW IN HERE.
YOU'RE JUST A NUMBER.
IT'S PRETTY DEHUMANIZING,
ISN'T IT?
BET YOU WEREN'T
THINKING ABOUT THAT
WHEN YOU WERE LOCKING
THESE PEOPLE UP IN HERE.
WELL...
I'M NOT GONNA DO
THAT TO YOU.
I'M GONNA END YOU.
YOU'RE GOING TO DIE TODAY.
AND I'M GONNA BE THE ONE
WHO'S GONNA DO IT.
BUT BEFORE THAT...
I'M GONNA MAKE YOU SUFFER...
THE WAY YOU MADE ME SUFFER.
AND WHEN I'M DONE WITH YOU,
OH, I'M JUST GONNA,
YOU KNOW,
PAY A LITTLE VISIT
TO FELICITY...
YEAH...
AND LITTLE WILLIAM.
AND I'M GONNA MAKE SURE
THAT THIS TIME,
I FINISH THE JOB.
GUARD: HEY! GET IN THERE!
GET IN THERE NOW!
OLIVER: HEY! LET ME GO!
THAT'S RICARDO DIAZ...
GET OVER THERE!
GET HIM! PICKUP!
OLIVER: THAT'S RICARDO DIAZ!
GET OVER THERE.
[GROANING]
HEY, YOU,
WHERE DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE GOING?
YOU'RE LUCKY WE DIDN'T
THROW YOU IN THE HOLE,
INMATE.
I DON'T CARE IF THIS
IS YOUR LAST DAY.
AS LONG AS YOU ARE
IN HERE,
YOU WILL STILL
FOLLOW THE RULES.
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
[GROANS]
THAT WAS RICARDO DIAZ.
HE IS HERE INSIDE
THE PRISON.
YOU NEED TO LET ME
HELP YOU STOP HIM.
SLABSIDE IS A LEVEL 4
SUPERMAX FACILITY.
THAT DOESN'T MATTER.
WE HAVE 50 OFFICERS
ON DUTY,
EACH ONE OF THEM
A TRAINED PROFESSIONAL.
TRUST ME.
WE HAVE IT COVERED.
THAT IS NOT GONNA BE
ENOUGH AGAINST HIM.
YOU ONLY HAVE A FEW HOURS
LEFT IN HERE, INMATE.
I SUGGEST YOU STAY
QUIET UNTIL THEN.
DIAZ IS HERE?
OLIVER, PLEASE TALK TO ME.
WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO?
I KNOW YOU'RE STILL MAD
ABOUT THE DUNBAR THING,
BUT THIS IS DIAZ.
I MEAN, EVERYONE DESERVES
A SECOND CHANCE, RIGHT?
OH, MY GOD. YOU'RE
"SHAWSHANKING" OUT OF HERE.
OLIVER, YOU GOT TO
TAKE ME WITH YOU.
STAY OUT OF THIS!
4587, STAND DOWN.
IF YOU ARE NOT GONNA CALL
FOR BACKUP, THEN I WILL.
LET ME GO.
YOU DON'T WANT THIS.
I SAID, STAND DOWN.
[INMATES SPEAKING EXCITEDLY]
[COUGHS]
WHOA.
KISS YOUR
EARLY RELEASE GOOD-BYE.
TARGET'S ON
THE THIRD FLOOR.
INITIATE LOCKDOWN
PROCEDURE NOW!
MAN: LOCKDOWN, LEVEL ONE...
SECURE PERIMETER DOOR NOW!
MAN: LOCKDOWN, LEVEL ONE.
[ALARMS BLARING]
HEY! ARE WE GONNA
BE HERE ALL DAY?
GUARD: YOU ARE GONNA BE
HERE AS LONG AS WE SAY.
YOU GOT THAT, INMATE?
DIAZ: INMATES!
[ALARM]
LOOK AT YOURSELVES.
YOU'RE ON YOUR KNEES.
YOU'RE COWERING BEFORE
MEN WHO ARE WEAK...
MEN WHO ARE
BENEATH YOU.
I'VE BEEN WHERE YOU ARE.
I KNOW HOW IT FEELS
TO BE TREATED LIKE
AN ANIMAL.
YOU CAN ONLY TAKE THAT
FOR SO LONG.
HEY, WHY DON'T
YOU ZIP IT, PAL?
HYAH!
[PISTOL THUDS]
STAND UP!
THESE GUARDS,
THEY IMPRISONED YOU.
INMATES: YEAH.
THEY DISRESPECTED YOU.
YEAH!
THEY TAUNTED YOU.
YOU ALL WANT
TO MAKE 'EM PAY?
YEAH!
YOU ALL WANT
TO MAKE 'EM PAY?
YEAH!
MAKE 'EM PAY!
NO SIGN OF 4587.
[GUARD HITS FLOOR]
YOU MADE QUITE
THE MESS THERE, QUEEN.
TAKING OUT PRISON GUARDS
DOESN'T SEEM
A VERY GREEN ARROW
THING TO DO.
I GUESS THIS PLACE
REALLY HAS CHANGED YOU.
I DON'T HAVE TIME FOR THIS.
RICARDO DIAZ IS HERE!
AND HE WILL NOT THINK TWICE
ABOUT KILLING US ALL.
NO, HE WON'T THINK
TWICE ABOUT KILLING YOU.
YOU SEE, I JUST MET HIM.
HE SEEMS
A REASONABLE CHAP.
OF COURSE YOU'RE WORKING
FOR DIAZ.
NO. I DON'T WORK
FOR ANYBODY.
YOU SEE,
ME AND SAMPSON,
WE GOT OUR OWN
PLANS, AS PER USUAL,
BUT I COULD
ALWAYS TAKE
A LITTLE TIME OUT
FOR A BIT OF FUN.
[BONE CRACKS]
AAH!
[PUNCHES ARE THROWN]
[GROANING]
UGH!
AAH!
BEEN WAITING TO DO THAT
FOR A LONG TIME NOW.
[CLANG]
BAD MOVE, TURNER.
SAMPSON...
THAT WAS YOUR
FEMORAL ARTERY.
YOU'VE GOT
MAYBE 6 MINUTES
BEFORE YOU
BLEED OUT.
[YELLS]
-HYAH! HYAH! HYAH...
YOU'RE NOT GOING
AFTER THEM?
I'VE GOT BETTER
THINGS TO DO.
THANKS FOR YOUR HELP.
IT DOESN'T MEAN I LIKE YOU.
TURNER...
HOW DID YOU GET OUT
OF YOUR CELL?
OF YOURS?
[THUD, RATTLE]
WHAT ARE YOU LOOKING FOR?
RICARDO DIAZ BROKE
INTO THE PRISON.
PEOPLE USUALLY BREAK OUT
OF PRISON.
HE WANTS TO KILL ME,
AND HE WILL KILL AS
MANY PEOPLE AS HE HAS TO
IN ORDER FOR THAT
TO HAPPEN.
I THOUGHT I HAD A LOT
OF ENEMIES.
DON'T HAVE A SIGNAL.
COME ON.
DIAZ: HELLO. ARE YOU HAVING
TECHNICAL DIFFICULTIES?
IT'S A LITTLE, UH,
LITTLE GOING AWAY PRESENT
FROM THE LONGBOW HUNTERS.
THEY JAMMED THE SIGNAL,
SO NO CALLS IN AND OUT.
YOU ARE SO PREDICTABLE,
YOU KNOW THAT?
YOU'RE TRYING TO MAKE
A CALL FOR HELP?
YOU'RE
TRYING TO SAVE THE DAY?
OHH.
I HAVE SOMEONE HERE THAT
WANTS TO SAY HELLO TO YOU.
GO AHEAD.
DON'T DO ANYTHING HE
TELLS YOU TO DO.
TRY AGAIN.
YOU HAVE FAILED THIS CITY,
OLIVER QUEEN.
DIAZ, THAT'S ENOUGH.
LET HIM GO!
YOU SPEAK
AND PEOPLE DO AS YOU SAY?
THAT'S HOW IT GOES?
DOESN'T MATTER IF YOU'RE
RIGHT OR WRONG?
NOT THIS TIME.
NOT ANYMORE.
[GAGGING]
[GAGGING STOPS]
HOW'S THAT FEEL?
HOW'S IT FEEL, SOMEBODY
ELSE PLAYING GOD?
THIS IS BETWEEN
YOU AND ME,
AND NO ONE ELSE
NEEDS TO DIE, OK?
DIAZ: WRONG!
WRONG AGAIN.
I WANT YOU TO SPEND
THE LAST HOURS
OF YOUR PATHETIC LIFE
KNOWING
THAT THESE MEN, THEY DIED...
THEY DIED BECAUSE OF YOU.
I'M COMING FOR YOU.
BUT WILL YOU MAKE IT
IN TIME TO SAVE THE GUARDS?
IT WAS HARD ENOUGH GETTING
THROUGH A FEW PRISONERS.
I WONDER WHAT IT'S
GONNA BE LIKE
GOING AGAINST
THE ENTIRE PRISON.
[ALARM]
KEEP YOUR HEAD DOWN.
THEY'RE NOT GONNA MESS
WITH ME. THEY KNOW BETTER.
IT'S NOT ABOUT THEM.
DIAZ KNEW WE WERE
IN THE LOCKER ROOM,
WHICH MEANS HE'S
WATCHING US.
THERE ARE ONLY TWO ROOMS
WITH CAMERA ACCESS.
THERE'S THE MAIN
SECURITY ROOM...
NO WAY HE GOT IN THERE.
IT'S TOO FORTIFIED.
THEN HE'S IN THE CONTROL
ROOM IN THE MESS HALL.
THAT'S WHERE WE
HAVE TO GO.
THERE'S NO "WE."
I SAVED YOUR ASS
SO YOU COULD GET ME
A DEAL WITH A.R.G.U.S.
DOESN'T MEAN WE'RE
SOME KIND OF TEAM.
DID YOU HEAR DIAZ?
HE'S KILLING HOSTAGES.
YOU SAID I WAS WRONG
ABOUT YOU?
YOU SAID YOU'VE
CHANGED?
PROVE IT.
THE ONLY WAY TO
THE MESS HALL IS
THROUGH THE CELL BLOCK.
IT'LL BE 10 TIMES WORSE
IN THERE.
THIS PLACE IS ALREADY
A POWDER KEG,
AND IT'S ABOUT TO BLOW.
IT'S THE ONLY WAY TO
THE MESS HALL.
[ALARM]
THESE INMATES ARE
GONNA KILL THEM.
AND IF WE DON'T GET OUT OF
HERE, THEY MAY KILL US,
AND, CLEARLY, WE'LL NEVER
MAKE IT TO THE MESS HALL.
I'M NOT GONNA LET
INNOCENT PEOPLE DIE.
[GROANING]
[CLANG]
UH!
HYAH!
NO!
COME ON!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
THANKS, QUEEN.
WHERE ARE THE REST
OF THE GUARDS?
A FEW OF THEM MADE IT
TO THE PANIC ROOM.
SOME WERE TAKEN TO
THE MESS HALL.
DIAZ SET THE INMATES LOOSE.
HE CONVINCED THEM
TO GATHER UP THE GUARDS.
LISTEN, A FEW OF MY BUDDIES
HAVE ALREADY DIED.
IT'S LIKE DIAZ IS
KILLING THEM FOR SPORT.
HOW MANY INMATES
IN THE MESS HALL?
LAST I HEARD, AROUND 30.
YOU GOOD TO WALK?
YEAH, I'M GOOD.
ALL RIGHT.
TAKE THEM
TO THE PANIC ROOM,
AND I'LL MEET YOU AT
THE COMMISSARY.
NOT THE TIME FOR
A SNACK.
IF WE'RE GONNA FIGHT OUR
WAY THROUGH 30 INMATES,
WE'RE GONNA NEED WEAPONS.
[SYRINGE DISCHARGES]
I REALLY, REALLY NEED
TO TALK TO YOU.
[THUD]
OH, GOOD.
YOU'RE AWAKE.
[EXHALES]
I'M SORRY ABOUT
THE SEDATIVE.
I WAS JUST TRYING
TO GET YOUR ATTENTION.
IT'S OK. I...I UNDERSTAND,
STANLEY.
I WAS JUST, UM...
[CLEARS THROAT]
BUSY TRYING TO STOP
DIAZ FROM KILLING
EVERYONE IN THE PRISON,
YOU KNOW?
SO, HONESTLY, STANLEY, I
THINK I COULD USE YOUR HELP.
REALLY?
YEAH. REALLY.
[EXHALES]
JUST, WHY DON'T YOU
UNTIE ME,
AND WE'LL MAKE A PLAN
AND YOU CAN BE MY SIDEKICK?
OHH! HEH.
ACTUALLY, I ALREADY
HAVE A PLAN.
[SNIFFLES]
YOU KNOW HOW TO GET
OUT OF HERE
THROUGH THE MORGUE,
RIGHT?
SO WHY DON'T WE
ESCAPE THIS PLACE,
YOU...YOU AND ME?
YEAH, WE COULD,
BUT WHAT ABOUT DIAZ, RIGHT?
WHO CARES ABOUT DIAZ?
THESE PEOPLE DESERVE
WHATEVER HE'S GONNA
DO TO THEM.
YOU KNOW THAT.
YEAH. I...
I CAN'T LEAVE ALL
THESE PEOPLE TO DIE.
YOU WERE GONNA LEAVE ME.
YOU WERE GONNA
ABANDON ME
TO BRICK AND SAMPSON,
AND I SHOULDN'T EVEN
BE IN HERE.
I DID NOTHING WRONG.
HEY, COME ON.
IT WAS JUST BECAUSE
YOU WERE GOING TO
ATTACK ME. OK?
WHY WOULD I ATTACK YOU?
BECAUSE YOU'RE
THE GREEN ARROW,
AND YOU FIGHT BAD GUYS,
AND YOU THINK
I'M A BAD GUY.
AND YOU JUST THINK
THAT I'M WHAT EVERYONE
SAYS THAT I AM.
HOW COULD I?
I DON'T...I DON'T KNOW
WHAT PEOPLE SAY.
THAT I'M A KILLER,
THAT
I'M A MONSTER,
THAT EVERYTHING I DID,
EVERYTHING I DID...
THAT WHOLE DUNBAR THING.
IT WAS JUST LIKE
THE DUNBAR THING. I...
I DIDN'T HAVE A CHOICE!
AND ALL THOSE PEOPLE
HAD IT COMING.
YOU KILLED OTHER PEOPLE
BEFORE DUNBAR?
HONESTLY, WHAT YOU AND I
DO IS NOT SO DIFFERENT,
RIGHT?
SO, LIKE, WE MAKE
SUCH A GREAT TEAM.
SO WHY DON'T WE JUST
GET OUT OF HERE,
MAYBE WE COULD WORK
TOGETHER AGAIN?
OH!
WHY'D YOU DO THAT?
[ROPES SNAP]
WHAT THE HELL
TOOK YOU SO LONG?
IT'S A LONG STORY.
HOW ARE FELTON AND MILLER?
THEY'RE SAFE.
TURNER:
I CAN'T BELIEVE
I'M WORKING WITH
THE GREEN ARROW.
YOU AREN'T.
HEY, MAYBE...MAYBE PRISON
HAS CHANGED ME,
COMPROMISED MY
JUDGMENT OF PEOPLE.
YOU SURE THAT'S
A BAD THING?
LOOK...
NO OFFENSE.
OK.
BUT THE OLD GREEN ARROW,
HE WASN'T THE BEST.
HE SAW THE WORLD
IN BLACK AND WHITE,
BUT NOW YOU...
YOU KNOW
THERE'S GRAY
OUT THERE, TOO.
MAYBE THAT MAKES YOU
A BETTER HERO.
YEAH.
AND I KNOW IT'S
BAD FOR YOU,
BUT DO YOU REALLY THINK
YOU'RE GONNA STOP DIAZ
WITH A CAN OF SODA?
WE'RE ABOUT TO FIND OUT.
[GUARD SCREAMING]
[INMATES SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
ARE YOU PLANNING SOME
KIND OF LIGHT SHOW?
SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
IT'S NICE TO KNOW
SOMEONE HATES QUEEN
AS MUCH AS I DO.
IF IT WASN'T FOR HIM, I'D
STILL BE RUNNING STAR CITY.
YEAH, ME, TOO.
HE'S A COCKROACH.
HE REFUSES TO DIE.
DIAZ!
[BATON HITS RAILING]
LOOK WHO DECIDED TO
COME TO MY PARTY.
LET THOSE GUARDS GO.
I TOLD YOU...
THE ONLY THING I WANTED WAS
TO SEE YOU SUFFER...
BEFORE YOU DIE.
YOU'RE NOT GONNA GET
WHAT YOU WANT.
NO?
UH!
[GROANING]
OOH. I'VE BEEN
WAITING TO DO THAT
FOR A LONG TIME.
YOU GET YOUR SHOTS IN
WHILE YOU CAN
BECAUSE I'M GONNA SEE TO IT
THAT YOU SPEND
THE REST OF YOUR LIFE
EATING YOUR MEALS
IN A SPOT JUST LIKE THIS.
I PROMISED MYSELF
I'M NEVER GONNA
DIE IN PRISON.
AND I'M GONNA TAKE
YOU WITH ME.
OH, YOU SURE ABOUT THAT?
HYAH! HYAH! HYAH...
TURNER: QUEEN!
[TURNER GROANS, BRICK YELLS]
[COUGHS, GROANS]
QUEEN!
CALLING FOR HELP WON'T SAVE YOU!
THIS PLACE...
IS GONNA BE ASH
LONG BEFORE ANYONE GETS HERE.
[COMPUTERS BEEPING]
[BELL RINGING]
OLIVER: COME ON.
-GET UP! GET UP! COME ON!
-LET'S GO. GO! GO! GO! GO!
GET GOING.
WHAT THE HELL HAPPENED?
DIAZ HAS
SOME SORT OF DEVICE.
IT MUST HAVE TRIGGERED
AN ELECTRICAL FIRE.
THE WHOLE PLACE IS
GONNA GO UP.
YOU NEED TO GET THEM
TO THE SECURE COURTYARD.
WHAT ABOUT YOU?
I'M GOING AFTER DIAZ.
YOU'LL NEED THESE.
NO HALF-MEASURES.
[ALARM RINGING]
[BLADE IS UNSHEATHED]
JUST THE TWO OF US?
[YELLS, GROANS]
AAH! UH! UH!
HYAH!
[YELLS]
[GROANS]
I'M A LOT STRONGER NOW.
[COUGHING]
UH! OHH!
UH! UH!
PRISON'S MADE YOU WEAK.
COME ON.
GET UP.
YEAH. YEAH.
YOU'RE NOT
SURVIVING THIS.
YOU JUST DON'T KNOW
WHEN TO QUIT, DO YOU?
[COUGHING]
I GUESS WHAT YOU
AND FELICITY HAVE
IN COMMON, HUH?
DON'T YOU SAY HER NAME.
[COUGHS]
FELICITY.
DO YOU KNOW SHE TRIED
TO KILL ME?
SHE PUT A GUN
RIGHT TO MY FACE.
SHE WAS ABOUT TO PULL
THE TRIGGER.
I DON'T BELIEVE YOU.
THAT'S NOT HER.
IT IS NOW.
THAT'S WHAT YOU MADE HER.
[OLIVER YELLING]
[GROANS]
ARROW'S LITTLE SIDEKICK.
HOW DID YOU FIND OUT
ABOUT THIS PLACE, DOVER?
I COULD ASK YOU
THE SAME QUESTION.
[CHUCKLING]
WELL, THE ONLY WAY OUT
OF THIS PLACE IS
THROUGH THE MORGUE.
BUT YOU DON'T HAVE
TO BE DEAD.
[BLADE STABS]
[THUD]
ACTUALLY,
I THINK YOU DO.
YOU SHOULDN'T HAVE BEEN
SO MEAN TO ME.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
TURNER...
THANKS.
FOR WHAT?
WITHOUT YOU, WE
WOULD ALL BE DEAD.
[POLICE RADIO TRANSMISSIONS]
MAN: GREG, MOVE YOUR HEAD!