Previously on "Arrow"...
Anatoly said that
you had a plan
to take control
of this city.
It's like you were
firing Overwatch.
I need to stop Diaz,
and in order
to do that,
I need to bring the mission
back to basics.
The impeachment was
just the latest step.
And what's
the next one?
Star City,
it's open for business.
AmericasCardroom.com brings poker back
Million Dollar Sunday Tournament every Sunday
Get your ass
out of bed, chillón.
You can look at that
picture all you want.
Your father ain't never
coming back, Diaz.
Getting breakfast.
When I come back,
this place better be clean
for inspection.
No wrinkles
on the bed--seriously--
or...
Get another souvenir
to help remind you.
If you do it again,
I'll tell sister Heller.
You think they'll believe
someone like you, chillón?
What? You want to
take a shot at me?
Go ahead.
I'm right here.
Give it back.
That's my only one!
No family's gonna want to
take you in.
Why would they?
You're nothing.
You're a loser.
You need
that reminder now.
You know that they invited
us here, right?
Breaking and entering
is a bit disrespectful,
don't you think?
I'm tired
of waiting.
You're the one that wanted
to tag along.
To see how you operate,
to see your big job.
So far, all we've done
is drive in the car for 3 hours
and wait outside...
For two more.
Patience.
It's one of the most
important virtues
a person can have.
Meaning?
If you think
short-term,
you're gonna drift
moment to moment.
You want something big,
something truly
remarkable,
you got to think
long-term.
We've been waiting
out here long-term.
Let me put it
in perspective.
I've been working
on something for 5 years.
What's waiting two hours?
A slap in the face.
Small price to pay
for an introduction to the Quadrant.
I thought they were
an urban legend.
They're very real.
They control all
criminal enterprises
across the entire country.
4 corners.
Yeah. Quadrant.
I get it. Very clever.
They didn't get that type of power
without patience.
Well, if they're
so powerful,
then why didn't you
come with any backup?
I'm not. I got you.
You're early.
My father couldn't
make it.
You don't mind, do you?
Let's get started.
We have a lot
to discuss.
Indeed we do.
Hey. You made it.
Yeah. Um...I did.
Well, that's great.
I'm glad you did.
- Hmm.
- What's wrong?
You know, it's just
been a while since we've done
any Helix Dynamics
stuff.
Yeah. Well,
we've been busy.
We've been fighting.
Not you and me.
I mean, our teams, yeah,
but that's not
an issue for me anymore.
Glad it's not for you, but, you know,
Rene's still in the hospital.
He's only now
just getting out.
I'm sorry about
our teams. I'm...
I'm sorry.
I'd really like
Helix to work.
Looks like you're trying to stabilize
the neuro-interface.
Yeah. I mean, it's just
still really twitchy.
You know, actually,
I had a thought about this.
I think the serotonin
interface is a result
of the pathogenic
reaction.
Star City's
open for business.
We have the police,
the ports, the whole city.
We got it wired.
Now, you want to
run merchandise,
you want to move product,
launder money, anything,
Star City's the place.
Assuming we're interested--
not saying that
we are but assuming,
how much you looking
to charge?
- It's free.
- Heh heh heh.
Nothing's ever free.
I just want a seat
at the table.
Of the Quadrant?
Mm-hmm. That seems
reasonable to me.
Well, you make the Quadrant sound
like it's a potluck,
as if there's always
room at our table
for anyone with
something to add,
but it's not.
We're a family.
We're not really
that welcoming
to outsiders
at least not
before we know--
ahem--that you can
operate at our level.
I just offered you
a whole city.
Now, if you can't see
the opportunity in that,
why don't I talk
to your father?
He sent me.
We're just looking
for a little something extra.
Call it establishing
your bona fides.
What'd you have
in mind?
This is Robert Baylor,
one of our guys.
Ahem. The FBI
pinched him.
- That's not ideal.
- Right?
We need to know where
the federal marshals
are holding Baylor
so we can get him out.
You want him
to audition.
Well, that's not a very
productive way of putting it.
And yet.
It'll be nothing for me.
It's not a problem.
Whatever it takes to get
the deal done, right?
Champion mind-set. Heh.
You got a John
in this place?
It's right
over there.
♪ Arrow 6x19 ♪
The Dragon
Original Air Date on April 19, 2018
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
I'm at the location now.
Thanks for the address.
I'd say I owe you one,
but you owe me 20.
Armand's contact
at the FBI.
Oh. So more
waiting, then.
Have to get a picture
of the guy--
proof of life.
They tell you to fetch,
you fetch.
So what's next--
roll over?
Oh, that's right.
You've already done that.
You think I'm giving in
to these people too much?
I don't think it.
I know it.
It's just business.
You're ok with all this,
how that guy
talked to you?
Cartier's nothing.
He's a steppingstone.
Long-term thinking.
Remember?
Yeah, I remember.
How's that working out
for you?
Smoke break.
Fetch. Roll over,
sit. Good boy.
You know that the Quadrant's
the most powerful
criminal organization
on the continent?
When I joined up
with Camden James, I gained a city.
When I join
the Quadrant,
I'm gonna have
an empire.
Ok. Try it.
- Success.
- Yes!
Pathogenic reaction's
completely stabilized.
- Ha ha ha! Yes!
- Ha ha!
Damn, we make
a good team!
- Well, speaking of team--
- No. Don't do that.
Why would you do that?
We're having such a good time.
Well, earlier, you said the team thing
wasn't an issue for you anymore.
- Did I say that?
- Yeah, you did.
The question is why.
Oliver sort of
fired me.
I mean, he--he's
saying that he didn't,
but--heh--it sure
feels like he did, you know.
Not sort of fired.
He fired me.
Wait, wait. I'm sorry.
What happened?
Long story short--
Oliver had a run-in with Vertigo--
the pharmaceutical,
not the person--
and he came out of it
with this epiphany
that to stop Diaz
he has to
"Go back to basics."
- Meaning?
- Meaning he's a lone wolf,
so no more team Arrow.
So did he also
fire John?
No. Uh, John left
about a week before.
Wow! Ok. Uh, well,
I'm gonna have to try
not to take satisfaction
out of that.
Try really hard.
Ok. So it was down
to you and Oliver.
- Mm-hmm.
- Now it's just Oliver.
Yep.
How are you doing
with all this?
Oh, I'm fine.
You're not fine.
Heh. What?
So none of your
people could find him.
I did.
Hmm.
I'll tell them to start
carving the monument.
They brought your
boy out for a smoke.
Looked more like
a guest than a prisoner.
H-honey, ease up.
That's a 30-year-old
single malt. Heh.
Call me "honey" again,
and I might only
break your legs.
Mmm.
I like this one.
So I held up my part
of the bargain.
Time for you
to deliver yours.
You know, uh, your
pretty little friend makes
an inconvenient point.
It seems that Mr. Baylor's
gotten a little chatty.
- So what?
- So my father's going to
have to debrief him,
you know, to find out
what he told
the Justice Department.
- You want me to--
- Fetch him?
What's a little favor
between future business partners?
So what's next?
You want me to
roll over,
you want me to
play dead?
You're absolutely right.
Forget I asked.
Thanks for tracking down
Baylor for us.
We'll take it from here.
You should have asked
me from the beginning.
You wasting my time?
I don't react well
when people waste my time.
Hey. I--I had no idea
that Baylor would be cooperating
with the frisbees.
Heh heh.
I'm gonna deliver
Baylor to you.
Afterwards,
I meet your father.
You solve this
little problem for us,
and my dad will be asking
to sit down with you.
Call me when you've
got Baylor.
I'll send over a car.
Oh. What happened
to your hand?
I got angry
at someone.
The Quadrant's making you jump
through a lot of hoops.
I hope it's worth it.
Why don't I knock
on the door?
Unh!
Hello, boys.
Agh!
Who are you?
Doesn't matter.
You gonna kill me?
If you keep asking
me questions.
On your feet.
Send the car.
Move.
Move!
Cartiers take care
of their own.
Once you're in,
you're family.
That's my expectation.
All's I'm saying is
I knew they'd send for me.
I would never snitch.
Sure you wouldn't.
I wouldn't take
the chance, though.
You're lucky you
don't work for me.
Baylor, buddy!
Feds treat you all right?
Whoa. I didn't say
nothing, I swear to God.
Tell him in person.
They're gone.
That packs a punch.
And what would you have done if they
shot you in the head?
I'd be dead probably. Heh.
Getting shot...
Wasn't part
of my plan.
Understatement
of the year.
You just can't trust
anyone these days.
Dad.
Is it done?
Baylor's
off the board.
And Diaz?
Never saw it coming.
Heh. Idiot really
thought he had a shot.
As if we'd share
space with a thug like him.
Tomorrow, we'll send
a crew to Star City
and lean
on Diaz's networks,
and we'll make
his city...Ours.
So this whole plan of yours
has gotten a little complicated.
Anything worth wanting
shouldn't be simple.
Hmm. Not my philosophy.
Plans are like men.
It's best to avoid
the complicated ones.
Aw, shucks.
You think I'm
not complicated.
You do realize that the guys
that you wanted to impress tonight
are the same guys that
just tried to kill you.
And I was prepared.
It still doesn't explain
what we're doing back here
at their place when we
should be on our way back to Star City.
Maybe that's the difference
between us.
When you get knocked down,
you give up.
- I get up.
- I get up!
I just don't get
stupid, too.
Must be nice
being pretty.
You pout your lips,
you bat your eyes,
everybody gives you
what you want.
Everything I wanted
I had to take.
♪ Hello, girls.
Hello, boys ♪
♪ I'm feeling confrontational ♪
Bar's closed!
Everybody move!
Move!
Son of a bitch.
In your enthusiasm
to take out your man...
You forgot I was standing
next to him
when you started
shooting.
But you're sorry
about that, aren't you?
It wasn't anything
personal.
Bullets make
things personal.
- May I ask you something?
- Um...
Did you ever have to
fight for a meal?
Um, uh...
Not once.
Not one time.
Mr. Silver Spoon.
I had to fight for every scrap of food
I ate as a kid.
You don't know
what it's like to be hungry,
to want something
so bad
you'd kill for it.
Ha! I've killed
plenty.
Not--not for survival.
Now when the outcome
of your life
hangs in the balance.
It's funny you should
put it that way.
You really got to
tell your guys,
creep a little quieter.
There's two to my right,
3 more behind me.
Heh. That's
pretty confident
for a thug
who's outnumbered.
You wouldn't think
I was outnumbered
if you knew what
she can do. Hmm.
Wow! We really need
to restock the fridge.
Do you think soda
can go bad?
I should probably already know
the answer to that.
- Felicity?
- Hmm.
Hey.
Um, it's working,
remember?
- We high-fived.
- Yeah. Doesn't mean it can't
be improved.
Sure. Uh, so maybe
improve it tomorrow
when you've had some
sleep and some food
and some
non-expired soda.
Yeah. I just want to make
a couple adjustments here.
Because that's easier than talking
about your husband?
Hey. He's going back
to basics, so, so am I.
You're the one who described it as
getting fired.
I said, "kind of,"
and that was just shorthand.
As much as I love
being a part of Team Arrow--
as downsized as it
may have become--
it was taking us away
from our real work, Helix.
This is where it's at.
And you're not
worried about him?
Nope. He can take
care of himself,
and I have been doing
this for 5 years.
Yeah. In the bunker
with computers
and body cams
and GPS
so you knew
where he was
and what
he was doing
and if he was ok.
Curtis.
Yeah. I thought throwing myself into work
would work, but it's not working.
I mean, I don't know
where he is.
He doesn't tell me where
he is anymore.
I need to know if he's ok.
I'm dying here!
Oh. Sorry.
News alert: Shootout
in the Glades. Oliver?
The Green Arrow
was last seen in the center
of an altercation moments
before the explosion
overtook the area.
SCPD has yet to issue
a statement.
We will keep you updated.
You're toying
with him.
Oh, come on.
What's a little fun
between future
business partners?
Well, we wouldn't want
him to think that we're wasting his time
by sending him
on some fool's errand.
Yeah. That would make
anyone furious.
Your daddy buy you
this place?
Not-so-shiny toy
to distract you
while he's running
the real business.
I never got anything
from my family.
You know I'm an orphan?
It's true. I grew up
in a real-deal orphanage--
nuns and...
and everything.
The full package.
There was this older boy.
His name was Jesse.
Jesse thought he was
better than me,
and I believed him,
and I was afraid of him.
I'd cry every night.
For years, he--
he treated me like a worm,
like I was worthless...
like I was
beneath him.
I'd make his bed,
I'd clean our room.
He treated me like
I was his damn servant.
- Hyah!
- Unh!
Look at me.
I'm nobody's servant now.
If you cut me, my father will never
give you what you want.
That's prospective,
the future.
I'm more interested
in the past.
Why'd you try
and kill him, Eric?
- Because I could.
- That's not good enough.
Stop!
It was
my father's idea!
We were gonna take
Star City,
co-opt your networks.
Take credit
for my sweat equity?
That is
so inconsiderate.
Sounds like your
precious little Quadrant is
a bunch of selfish jerks.
They didn't know.
We never told them
about you.
What?
My father and I,
we never brought
your proposal
to the Quadrant.
You're a nobody,
so...
Agh! Ugh.
Unh!
Satisfied yet?
No.
You're alive now.
You want to stay
that way?
Tell me when
the Quadrant's meeting.
Tonight.
Well, isn't that
convenient?
You gonna give me
all the details?
They're not just
gonna let you in.
I'm not planning
on knocking.
Somehow, we moved
past complicated
and straight
into crazy.
What I did
to Cayden James,
you think that's
crazy?
This is manning up.
Ugh. Manning up.
I hate that phrase.
Ok. Let's talk
this through.
If the Quadrant is
as powerful as you say,
who knows what kind
of firepower they have in there?
You're selling
yourself short, kiddo.
You're better
than 10 men.
And if there's
more than 10?
Trust me.
While I appreciate
your self-confidence,
you could be overestimating
your powers of persuasion
by just a little bit.
You might not be their
favorite person in the world
considering what we've
just done
to the prince
of hair gel.
I said, trust me.
And I would find it
a whole lot easier to do so
if you could just tell me
why it is so important
for you to be a part
of this exclusive club.
There are other ways
you can build your empire.
It's not
about empire building.
It's about respect.
Right, which you want,
and you're willing
to disrespect yourself in
order to get it from them.
- That's not how it is.
- Really?
Because that's how
it looks like it is.
Back at that bar,
you were talking
about Jerry like he
still haunted you.
Jesse. It's Jesse,
and he does.
Little bastard was
right. I was nothing,
you know, a loser.
Not anymore.
Hey. Now you're a king.
Forget about him.
I can't.
I was afraid of
Jesse for so long
that all I had
was my fear...
So I--I named that
fear The Dragon.
That's cute.
I lived with The Dragon
for so long...
It's all I had...
But now being a part
of the Quadrant,
I'm gonna have
something else...
The type of power
where I'll never be nothing again.
You remind me of the guy
that brought me here...
To this earth.
He...He had so much
hate inside of him.
Took control over him.
I control The Dragon.
It doesn't control me.
We're here.
You coming or not?
Glad you decided
to come.
Someone's got to make sure
you don't get yourself killed.
That's why I'm glad.
If the Quadrant's
everything you say they are,
they're gonna see
this coming.
Maybe. Family can be
blinding.
What the hell?
You think they saw
that coming?
We got incoming!
Sounds like a little bit
more than the 11 guys
he said there were.
Had to soften
the beach.
C4 sends a message.
Why don't you send
another one?
Now the beach is soft.
Unh!
Agh!
I went through a lot of trouble
to get to this meeting.
It didn't have
to be, though.
You killed
my son.
C4 killed your son.
Do you have any
idea who I am, who we are?
Yeah.
That's why I wanted
to meet.
If you know
who we are,
you know I'm not
going to kill you
for what you did
to my boy.
Well, that's a relief.
I'm going to send you
someplace far away from here,
to a hospital I own.
They know every way
there is to keep a man alive
as other men carve
pieces out of him.
Sure. Sure you could
go that way.
You could try...
But if you do,
it'll cost you
billions annually.
Take him, but make sure
he doesn't die.
Wait.
He killed my boy.
Frankly, I'm surprised your
idiot son made it this far.
Talk as if your life
depended upon it because it does.
Like I said...
It wasn't supposed
to be this way.
Mr. Cartier's son...
was supposed to arrange
this meeting without bloodshed,
but Cartier senior,
he wanted to go another way.
Because you're not fit to be in
the same room as us.
You're a street thug,
not even qualified
to work on one of our crews.
I came to this meeting
because I have
a business proposition.
You know what's happening
in Star City, right?
I see it's
falling apart.
I've seen chaos.
No, no, no, no.
Controlled chaos.
What you see
as dysfunction,
I see a machine running
on full efficiency.
I control the PD,
city hall, the ports, the rails.
I control everything,
and it could all be yours,
all of it in exchange
for one thing,
one thing.
A seat...
At this table.
I don't see
an empty chair.
Even if there was one,
I would never sit
beside the man who killed
my own blood.
He pushed me to it.
And he pushed,
and he pushed, and he pushed.
A man's got
his limitations.
And you are mine.
Look at you.
A street thug
who couldn't even
keep himself out of prison.
You're nothing...
A loser.
Oh.
Lookit here.
That's
an empty seat.
We are successful
because we're deliberate,
disciplined,
and precise.
We're not animals killing
each other for scraps.
We are civilized.
This is not,
but your proposal
intrigues us, Mr. Diaz.
We'd like to hear more.
Heh. Heh.
Let's get started.
What's wrong?
You got what you wanted,
you're not
a loser anymore.
You are a legitimate
crime lord,
and yet you still
seem on edge.
You think a ring
and a seat at the table
changes things for me.
I think we ran a gauntlet because
you thought it would.
It's not over yet.
There's still one last thing
I have to take care of.
Can I help you?
Oliver?
There are no survivors
in the explosion
that consumed a city block
in the Glades earlier
this evening.
Given the power of the blast,
experts say that forensics
may be required to determine
the fate of the Green Arrow.
Oh. Go!
Hey, you.
- Oh, my God!
- You ok?
Oh, my God!
Oh, I saw the explosion
on the news,
and you were right
in the middle of it.
Yeah. No. I fired
a grappling arrow,
and I flew...
- You--
- backwards right out of there.
I'm f--I'm fine.
- Well, I'm--I'm not!
- Ok.
Worrying about you
out here is--
well, it's completely different
from worrying about you in the bunker.
Right, because when you're
in the bunker,
you feel like you can
make a difference.
I can. I can
I can--I can deploy backup.
I can do--I don't know.
I can do something.
Out here, I c--
I'm helpless out here.
You aren't helpless
anywhere ever,
but I'm not helpless
either, all right?
Made a promise
to that guy in there
I would always
come back.
Well, William made
an excellent point
when he said you
coming back
is not always gonna
be your decision.
William does make
excellent points,
but I made
the promise anyway.
I'm making the same
promise to you
right here
and right now.
Felicity...
I will always
come back.
I've been waiting an hour.
Get up the stairs.
I know you hate waiting.
Who's this?
That last thing
I have to take care of.
I've got kids.
They need me. Please,
please don't hurt me.
Whatever you want,
I can give it to you.
You're lucky if you got
two dimes to rub together
on a good day.
How--how do you know me?
What?
How do I know you?
I've known you
my whole life.
What?
Laurel, meet
Jesse Fredericco.
Jesse...
Meet Laurel.
I don't think people are
supposed to know
that Laurel's working with
a crime lord.
"Crime lord. Crime lord."
I love the sound of that.
You really don't
remember me?
Hmm?
Chillón?
Diaz?
That is really
disappointing.
I thought I made
a bigger impression.
On your knees.
- Unh!
- Agh!
Hey. What
are you doing?
Getting my payback.
I think that this is a little bit
more than payback.
Hey.
See that?
I took this
from the fire.
I stuck my hand
right in.
I had blisters.
I had raw, cracked skin!
For weeks!
Hey, Jesse.
Hey.
You still like fire?
Ricardo.
I promised myself...
When the time was right...
That I'd get my payback...
When I wasn't a loser.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
OpenSubtitles.org require your login in mx player
for uploading subtitles, please login now