Previously on "Arrow"...
I think I finally figured out a plan B
to keep us hidden from Archer
while we try to destroy it.
We'd have to steal it
from Keven Dale's computer
in his office at Galaxy One.
Something's come up which
requires my immediate attention.
We should get out of here.
Seize them.
- Where is William?
- Mom, what's wrong?
Frak!
By the authority of Galaxy One,
you are under arrest.
Emiko!
She has the weapon.
And we have no idea
where she's gonna use it.
We'll find her.
This is SCPD aerial support.
Hold your positions.
Stop right there!
We are not the enemy, Lieutenant.
The enemy is still out there,
and we should be working
together, not wasting time.
Six arrows and six
dead cops say otherwise.
Talk to Sergeant Bingsley.
He'll tell you we didn't do this.
Sergeant Bingsley is unconscious
in the back of an ambulance right now.
Lieutenant.
Turn around.
Put your hands behind your head!
All of you, do it now!
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
What do you think is worse,
Emiko being in possession of a bioweapon
or the team being Star
City's most wanted?
Can I choose both?
I'm going to go with the
warrants out for our arrest.
The real us, not the vigilante us,
which means our lives
in this city are over.
Been there before.
Guys, this team always
finds a way to come through.
Yeah, but this feels different.
Emiko has a personal vendetta
against you and your whole family.
She has a bigger ax to grind
than Adrian chase or Slade.
Fine. But there has to be
a way to get through to her.
And she knows we're alive now.
That'll make her even more
determined to destroy the city.
Which means we need to
figure out where in the city
she's planning on deploying the Cygnus.
Yeah. Well, easier said than done,
because Emiko must've found out
that I was tracking the Cygnus
by using its chemical signature
because she's figured
out a way to block me,
which brings us back to square one.
Sounds like you all could use some help.
It's a good thing you called for backup.
In accordance with Star
City penal code 10101971,
you are all under arrest.
Turn around. Put your
hands behind your head.
Ohh. Smoak Tech flex-restraints.
Nice to see another one of my creations
being used against me.
And what if we don't want to go quietly?
Failure to comply will result
in summary execution.
Wrong answer. Hyah!
- Alena!
- Uh!
They know what we're gonna do...
Even before we do it.
Archer's predictive algorithm!
Hyah!
Hey, troublemaker.
I had him.
You're welcome.
We have to find William.
Not from here. This place is burned.
I know somewhere that isn't.
What are they gonna do with us?
You mean before they
torture us to find out
what you stole off Keven
Dale's computer or after?
I'm gonna stop asking questions now.
Look, I'm sorry I blew your cover.
It's not your fault.
Dale's been suspicious ever since
I questioned what they did to Felicity.
On the bright side,
I did manage to steal
Galaxy One's secret
evil plans for Star City.
They plan to use the zetas to establish
martial law
and remake Star City
in The Glades' image.
Which means they're gonna hunt
down everyone with a record
no matter how minor and
kill them on the spot.
Which is basically everyone
on that side of the wall.
It will be a bloodbath.
Duck.
Dad, I was so worried.
We're okay, peanut.
We need to get out of here.
You're back just in
time for the fun stuff.
I'm so happy Roy's back.
I love a good reunion.
You seem awfully positive
about the stuff with your sister.
I know how to break my
family's cycle of violence.
Ooh, I hope it goes
something along the lines of
stopping Emiko from destroying
the city and killing us all.
That's part one,
but it needs to be more than that.
Felicity, I... I want to
help her redeem herself.
If I don't break this cycle of violence,
I just don't ever see
us being able to provide
a secure future for our family.
Hey. We just got some strange chatter
over the SCPD scanner.
Someone called in a bomb threat
at a shopping complex downtown.
Somebody using a signal-bounced
untraceable number.
Suspicious.
Why would Emiko give an advance
warning on her own attack?
It doesn't make sense.
So that the whole complex will
evacuate into the Plaza outside,
where she'll deploy the Cygnus.
Maximizing the casualty count.
Well, we can't let that happen.
We won't. Let's move out.
This place is jammed.
Cops, too. This could get messy.
That's exactly what Emiko wants.
Overwatch, do you have eyes on?
Okay. Still no sign of
Emiko, but we are tracking
what is most likely a detonation signal
to a package on the
northeast corner of the Plaza.
It's got to be the Cygnus X-1.
All right. We need to
get these people clear
and find that device now.
Copy that.
We're focused on the weapon.
Let's get all these people out of here.
Listen up! Everybody move now!
We have to go!
Move. Hey! If we don't evacuate
this building right now,
all these people are gonna die.
You're the vigilantes who
killed those transit workers.
You're under arrest.
All right. Enough. We
don't have time for this.
Stand down.
You should still be
in jail... All of you.
We're not gonna stand for this...
He's trying to save you, dumbass.
Questions later. How can I help?
Clear a path.
Aah!
Overwatch, what happens to the Cygnus
if I shoot it down?
An accelerant will augment the effects.
You need to freeze them.
It worked! The Cygnus didn't spread.
You got all of them. You contained it.
Not fast enough.
Star City is reeling tonight
following a horrific terrorist attack
perpetrated by its own
heroes, which injured hundreds.
The vigilantes' motives
are still in question.
I cannot believe they still
think we're behind this
after everything we've
done for this city.
Well, not everyone. I'm out
on parole thanks to you guys.
Look, I know tonight
didn't go as planned.
That's an understatement.
That doesn't mean it's over.
You can't possibly think
Emiko could have a change of heart.
Oliver's right.
What? I'm happy that you two
are on the same side finally.
But how can you be siding with the woman
who tried to destroy your life?
She actually did me a favor.
If I hadn't had toyed around
with being Black Siren again,
then I never would have realized
that that's not the
life that I want to live.
Maybe Emiko will have
the same realization.
If people were correct in their thinking
that Laurel and I couldn't change,
well, we wouldn't be here helping you.
I hope you guys are right
because Emiko only used
a fraction of the Cygnus.
She has a lot of scary
nightmare bacteria left.
Any idea where she
may be targeting next?
At the moment, everywhere.
The detonation signal's
been purposely scrambled,
which means the target keeps moving.
Yeah. It's like a whack-a-Cygnus.
Ha ha! Ohh, I missed you.
Our descrambling algorithm is working,
but it's going to be slower than normal.
Even if you find the targets,
we still need to find a way to
contain the drones at each site.
Are you all familiar with the term
"Optimized Cryogenic Chambers"?
Oh, no, they aren't.
Yeah. It's just us? Okay.
Basically I was able to modify
an old portable freezing device
so that it can contain
the Cygnus on the drones.
Good thing you guys didn't toss
all of my old tech equipment
when you did the new bunker upgrades,
which, by the way, are very cool, so...
- Right?
- Okay, look...
Uh, it's not that I don't
have faith in this team,
but if this scary bacteria
gets all over the city,
I got to get Zoe somewhere safe.
Okay. Well, Lyla took J.J. to
a secure A.R.G.U.S. location.
She can pick up Zoe as well.
You have a son, right? Connor?
- Yeah.
- We'll bring him as well.
Thank you.
Jackpot. I got two detonation sites.
Okay, Digg, Turner, and I will
go to the water treatment plant.
Roy, Dinah, Laurel, you go
to the convention center.
All right. And I will
stay here with Felicity.
All right. No one die.
- "No"... wow. What?
- Uh, I'm rusty. Sorry.
Well, I'm glad everyone is safe
to say the least.
Does anyone need anything?
Do we need any water?
It's very important to hydrate.
No. And we don't need any snacks either.
According to the information
William got on Dale's
computer, the ZETAs
are marching into Star City tonight.
We have to disable Archer before
they start their mass execution.
That won't be easy.
Archer doesn't have a server room.
Its server is the actual wall
outside of The Glades.
Wait. The ZETAs use
Archer to track our DNA.
They'll know the second we get
anywhere close to that wall.
- Mom...
- Hmm?
Why are you making that face?
I am not making a face.
This is my face.
I might have put a backdoor into Archer
that utilizes Queen/Smoak DNA
so that you wouldn't be in the system.
So you basically just erased me.
I...
You know, just add that
to the list of lies.
I was protecting you.
Wait. Hold on.
Yes, what she did may be overprotective
- and overbearing...
- Yeah.
But it could be the break
that we've been waiting for.
I mean, if Archer doesn't
recognize Mia's DNA,
she could be the key
to shutting it down.
You're right. If Archer inputs your DNA,
it theoretically creates an opening
for a virus to be uploaded.
I mean, I don't know if it would work.
Well, even if it did,
Archer only inputs data
to its main server at one location...
The checkpoint between
Star City and The Glades.
That's where Dale plans
to march the zetas into Star City.
So we go there, we scan Mia's DNA,
we upload the virus.
Even with the Archer
blindspots put in place,
we're way too publicly recognizable
to get anywhere near that checkpoint.
I mean, you can't, but we can.
- No.
- Uh, the... the public
doesn't even know who we are.
No. It is much too dangerous.
Mom, you've trained me
my whole life for this.
Trust me.
Got to hand it to you, Curtis.
Your containment chamber
worked like a charm.
Nice to know you still
think I'm terrific. Heh!
Heard it. That was bad.
Any luck unscrambling
the detonation signal?
Dinah started transmission
at the convention center.
Her data plus your
data should do the trick
and help us identify the targets.
Okay, perfect. If we can
neutralize the rest of the Cygnus,
then we can turn our
focus back to Emiko.
Uh-oh.
What's happening?
Okay, so we have a good
news/ bad news situation
going on here, guys,
the bad news being we
just got 15 new targets.
We don't have time to
neutralize that many.
We might not have to.
All the Cygnus devices are
linked up to the same detonator.
- That was the good news, right?
- Uh-huh.
Ok, well, if we destroy the detonator,
we can neutralize the
rest of the targets.
I'm working on a location for you now.
Oh, double frak.
It's at Palmer Tech.
Formerly Queen consolidated,
our father's company.
She wants to tear down
our family's legacy.
This is her target.
Call the team.
Two of the Cygnus dispersement sites
have been compromised.
The circle, they're concerned.
Look, they want to detonate
the remaining devices now.
That isn't the plan.
The plan was only to profit
on the destruction of Star City.
I mean, this extra chaos is unnecessary,
especially now with
the D.I.A. closing in.
Chaos is the point.
Without terror, there is no profit.
The Circle respectfully disagrees,
and they worry that your
focus on your brother
has led to our exposure.
Your personal vendetta is only
drawing more attention to us.
I think you...
And the circle
have forgotten who their leader is.
My brother deserves to suffer
just like I have suffered
all of these years.
And when he sees his city burn
with his family to blame,
he will.
Overwatch, we're on-site.
We're in the telecom suite.
B.C., Laurel, and Wild
Dog are still en route.
I'm picking up over a
hundred heat signatures
in the building, including the penthouse
that is still under construction.
One guess as to where your sister is.
She really knows how to maximize
collateral damage, doesn't she?
If we try to evacuate the
civilians, we'll blow our cover.
We need to find that relay trigger
before the ninth
circle knows we're here.
Actually, just the device
relaying the signal.
There's a power surge coming
from the room you're in,
so the relay must be somewhere nearby.
We shut down Emiko's
ability to detonate,
we save the city.
Find the relay device
and then evacuate the building.
You going after Emiko?
I've got your back.
Got to go alone.
Communication is mission critical.
The last thing we need are comms failing
while we're out there.
While we're out there?
Sounds like you still haven't budged
on Mia and William taking the reins.
We are about to stop a small army
from infiltrating Star City.
I can't be the only one
worried about the kids.
Of course I'm worried,
but I taught Zoe everything she knows
about being a hero.
Almost everything.
And now my little
girl's a grown-ass woman
and one of the Canaries.
I know she can handle herself.
And your kids, they're no
slouches either, Felicity.
They're like their parents.
This is not the life
that Oliver and I wanted for them.
They're supposed to be living
happy, normal lives right now.
That was the only thing
that Oliver asked me to do.
It was the only thing that I
promised him I would do.
And I failed.
Some mother I turned out to be.
It's time.
Be safe. I love you.
I love you, too, dad.
I'm going to be watching
over both of you.
We'll need you.
Mia...
Thought you might need these.
What happened to us being
public enemy number one?
I told pollard the truth
about what really went down.
You guys are heroes.
Is the relay down, Overwatch?
Oh, so down, it's in Australia.
Emiko can't trigger the devices now.
Every remote device.
There's still an active
one in the building.
Enough to take this place down?
And then some.
We need to evacuate this building now.
You heard the captain. Move!
Oliver, the relay's deactivated,
but the building is still
armed. Do you have Emiko?
I do now.
I have been waiting for you.
Emiko, it's over.
This was his view, wasn't it?
Your father.
His perch above the
city, above everyone.
I'm glad you'll get to see it all fall.
Not tonight.
What did you do?
I'm giving you a second chance...
Before it's too late for both of us.
I don't need bombs to kill you.
Welcome to Galaxy One.
Proceed to checkpoint.
This couldn't be creepier.
Just keep your heads down.
Once the scan starts, it'll only take
a few seconds to upload the virus.
Proceed.
Prepare for identification.
Done. Let's get out of here.
Mr. Clayton. What a surprise.
I thought you'd be smarter than this.
Turns out you're just like your father.
Looks like you're having
technical difficulties.
No, no, no.
Don't tell me you
actually liked that creep.
No, it didn't work.
The virus didn't destroy Archer.
It's rebooting itself. We failed.
You have every right to be angry.
I was angry, too,
because you let our father die.
And that led to a ripple
effect in my life of loss.
I lost Tommy, my
mother, Laurel, Quentin.
And I wanted to kill you for all of it.
Hyah! Hyah...
I know his death affected you, too.
Instead of finding the hero
that I really believe is inside of you,
you went down a dark path.
And it killed your mother.
Dante killed my mother.
No, he didn't, Emiko.
Your allegiance to the Ninth
Circle killed your mother.
Your hatred of our
father killed your mother.
His worst impulses drove you away,
and it led to every terrible
moment in both of our lives.
I think that together, we can be better.
So if you're gonna kill me, do it.
Well, if you're not gonna kill him,
we'll gladly oblige.
Galaxy One must have found a weak spot
and modified the system.
Okay. How long until the
ZETAs are back online?
Uh, best-case scenario, 5 minutes?
Dad, you said the brain
of Archer is in the wall,
so if we destroy the wall?
When we built the wall,
we installed explosives
inside of each control tower.
They're linked together electronically,
but they can only be detonated
from inside one of the towers.
Yeah, but there's no way
anyone can make it up there
in 4 minutes.
An Archer could.
No way, Mia. Look.
Even if you got up there, you wouldn't
be able to make it back down in time.
You'll die.
Once I'm inside the tower,
can you talk me through it?
You know it's the only way.
If you can get inside, I can
access the system remotely.
- Mia, listen to me!
- Sorry, Mom. I have to do this.
Beatrice, you don't have
the authority to be here.
The council was promised
the total destruction of Star City,
not a sibling spat.
And for the first time in history,
the world knows of our existence.
The Ninth Circle answers to me.
Not anymore.
Finish them.
Almost in position.
Ready when you are.
You're still here.
Yeah. I don't leave my family.
Detonate the building.
Aah!
Okay. The device is installed.
Now all I have to do is bypass
the encryption protocols,
reconfigure the detonation commands,
and voila.
Ready when you are.
Take care of mom.
She's already lost so much.
Here goes nothing.
I just started getting
used to having a sister.
I'm not losing you now.
You have 60 seconds
until that wall goes boom.
Get out of there.
I'm sorry.
I know. It's okay.
You need to hide.
Your family's gonna
die. I made sure of it.
You need to hide Felicity and the baby.
Emiko.
I... I...
I wanted to be a Queen.
Aah!
Uh-oh. The ZETAs are back online.
You think?
You have 20 seconds.
So this is what it feels
like to save a city,
minus Palmer Tech becoming a crater.
No civilian casualties. That's a win.
We really couldn't have
done this without your help.
Thank you.
Laurel, thank you.
That last-minute SCPD assist
really helped turn the tide.
Oh, well, I'm just
relieved the department's
back on our side and
we can show our faces
- in the city again.
- Yeah.
Because you proved this
is a team of heroes.
I'm sorry about Emiko.
Thank you. I... I know
I tried to save her.
Oliver, I know this wasn't how
you wanted her story to end.
Hey. I'm sorry. I hate to save and run.
- Ohh.
- But I have to go back to D.C.
The jeweler called.
The ring I picked out for Nick is ready.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
You're popping the question?
Yeah. The holtnastases
are gonna make it official,
assuming he says yes.
Of course he'll say yes!
He'd be a fool not to. Oh!
Congratulations.
Any thoughts about what
you're gonna do next?
A man with your set of skills,
a lot of people will be looking.
Lyla... well, she's always looking.
I just want to spend time with my son,
who I need to get back to.
- Copy that.
- All right.
And then there were six.
Actually, five. I can't stay.
You're gonna catch up with Thea?
There's a lot I still
have to figure out.
I killed two innocent people.
I have to find a way to atone for that.
Well, since we're on
the subject of good-byes,
we have an announcement, too.
Hmm?
We're stepping back.
We're leaving Star City. Not forever,
but, uh, for now.
You just saved the city.
You don't want to take a victory lap?
I didn't do anything.
Our team did.
The fact that the city is safe is
the reason why we can leave.
I've spent a long time thinking about
my legacy as the Green Arrow.
I always hoped it would
be saving the city.
But now I know that
my greatest legacy...
Is this team.
I started this mission alone.
I was certain that I would end it alone,
but the truth of the matter is that
every bit of success that
I've had along the way
is because of all of you.
The city is safe
because of your courage,
your compassion, your selflessness,
and your loyalty.
Courage, compassion,
selflessness, loyalty.
Oliver, that sounds like the
4 pillars of heroism to me.
We should find a way to remember them
to symbolize we will all be
there for each other always
no matter what.
Ooh, like a signal, you know.
One of us is in trouble,
we'll all come running,
including you, Roy.
We should just call it
the mark of four, right?
That's brilliant.
Man, I really hope
this isn't the last time
we're all in this bunker together.
Hear! Hear!
But it does feel like the end of an era.
Okay, well, let's
just try to think of it
as the beginning of a new one.
Star City is a wall-free zone once again.
Restoring The Glades won't be easy.
The Glades hasn't been
open to outsiders in years.
Plenty of people will be
trying to take advantage.
Seems like the city's gonna need heroes.
We were thinking the same thing.
The four of you are the
heroes that the city needs.
What are you talking about?
Passing the torch.
Zoe, you are a born leader.
And I think you are more than ready
to rebuild and take
control of the Canaries.
I don't understand.
Someone's gonna get
blamed for what happened.
It should be us.
You'll be fugitives.
We've spent the last two
decades living in hiding.
Going off-grid won't be new for us.
Wait. I just got you back.
I'm so sorry,
but the four of you having a future,
that's worth any sacrifice.
Thank you, both of you.
I should be thanking you.
You got me off that island.
You never really told me
how you got on that island.
It's a long story. Look,
we should really get going.
Um, I'll catch up with the two of you.
There's something I have to
do before we say good-bye...
Something to honor your father.
You having second thoughts?
- Ahh.
- No.
Right. Yeah. Me either.
It's the right thing to do
for our family.
I do wish we could tell
the team about the...
Yeah.
Baby, but I understand it just
puts them in the Ninth
Circle's crosshairs.
When that threat is over.
Until then, it's the
best thing for them...
And us.
You know, the spirit of this place
will live on long after we're gone.
You've inspired so many people, Oliver.
They will carry on your legacy.
Sounds like a cycle for good.
Far better than that.
A cycle of heroes...
Who will fight to defend this city
with every fiber of their being.
Anyone ever told you you
always know exactly what to say?
I have been told.
- Ha ha!
Mm.
Let's get you two to your new home.
Good-bye, old friend.
Well, it's not Ivy town, but it'll work.
Well, it's temporary.
Well, basically, this
whole neighborhood is
ex-C.I.A., ex D.I.A., and ex-A.R.G.U.S.
This is one big safe house.
You two will be fine here.
Please thank Lyla for us.
Of course.
Well, I guess this is home now.
At least until the threat
against our baby girl
is taken care of.
Your baby girl? You're having a girl.
Mia.
Mia. That's beautiful.
It's beautiful.
Well, I guess since the
city's in good hands now,
you two can focus on your family,
which is exactly what you should do.
Well, you are part of that family, John.
Maybe it's the pregnancy
making me overly emotional,
but, oh, I'm gonna miss you so much.
We love you.
I love you.
And you.
Yeah.
I'll reach out to you two later.
Hey. You maintain my bunker.
No food by the monitors.
There's nothing worse
than crumbs in a keyboard.
What now?
Well, this isn't a tropical paradise,
but we never did take our honeymoon.
Oh. Yes. Mom juice. Mm.
Ahh. You know,
as much as I miss the team
and the action of
taking down the bad guys,
- this has been so nice.
- Yeah.
I wish William were here.
Me, too.
You know, if this is
gonna be the new normal,
we should talk with his grandparents
about getting shared custody.
Yeah. I would love that.
Mia's gonna need her older brother.
Now?
I thought I had more time.
The universe is a complex
piece of machinery,
and balance must be maintained.
One change requires another.
How would you propose
I keep the balance?
Will you help me save
Barry and Kara or not?
No. But I will give you
the means to save them.
Tell me what you need in exchange.
Whatever the multiverse requires
to survive the crisis that is looming.
When it is time.
It's okay.
So what bargain have I made?
What does the multiverse require?
You assist me as we seek
to prevent the inevitable.
But that sounds impossible.
The multiverse is more
complex than you could fathom.
What are you not telling me?
I've seen your future, Oliver,
inexorable and unavoidable.
I have watched you die.
During this crisis?
I am truly sorry.
No. You are not taking him.
- Felicity.
- Oliver.
I am not here to bring harm
to you or your daughter.
Trust me, the world needs her.
You think that I'm just
going to let you leave here
with my husband's life?
This is bigger than us...
Than all of us.
Why does it always have to be you?
I cannot prevent his passing,
but he can prevent the deaths
of countless more, including you
and your daughter.
But he needs to come with me tonight.
Mom?
- Hi.
- Are you okay?
Yeah.
I wanted to say good-bye to both of you.
- Here?
- Yeah.
I just wanted us to be
all together one last time.
What do you mean, one last time?
Just because you're a fugitive,
it doesn't mean we
can't still communicate.
Well, things are gonna
be different this time.
You two don't need
my protection anymore.
You're our mom.
We still want you in our lives.
I promised your father
that I would protect both of
you until you didn't need me.
He would be so proud...
So proud of you two.
I miss him so much.
I know.
I wish I got to know him.
I know, but he lives
on in the two of you.
It's time for me to go
on a journey of my own.
I love you both so much.
So you promise me...
That the two of you are gonna
take care of each other, okay?
Okay?
Hey.
This is why we can't have a normal life.
This is why our children
will never have normal lives.
I had to make the deal.
Oh, there's always gonna be some danger
or some threat...
The league of assassins
or hive or the Ninth Circle
or...
The end of the friggin' universe.
I need you to make me a promise.
Yeah, okay.
No matter what happens to me...
No matter what...
You need to do everything
in your power...
You...
You need to keep William and Mia safe.
I will keep them safe.
But wherever you go...
Whatever happens to you...
You'll never leave me.
On our wedding day, you told me
that I was the best part of you,
but the truth is...
We are the best parts of each other.
And that is so much bigger
than the friggin' universe.
When I came back to Star City
to start my mission,
I didn't think that I was
capable or deserving of love.
But you opened up my heart
in ways that I never th...
thought were possible.
My only regret is not telling
you I loved you sooner.
No regrets.
Would you tell Mia that
I love her every day?
And I know that she will grow up to be
as smart and as beautiful
as her mom.
I will find you... again.
I promise.
I love you.
I love you so much.
I'm ready.
Where I'm taking you,
there is no return.
I have waited a very
long time to see him.
I'm ready.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --