Previously on "Arrow"...
The Dante painting.
It's being used as some sort of
highly advanced identification protocol
within terrorist circles.
I'm here to offer you a deal.
You give us Dante, you go free.
No one said anything about
sticking a bomb in my head.
What do you see?
I'm with my father at sea.
His bodyguard Ha-Hackett,
my dad shot him.
Your father was a murderer.
Mr. Queen is officially working
for the SCPD.
We need to analyze this DNA.
It belongs to the new Green Arrow.
The vigilante is your sister.
The DNA match is on your father's side.
He had a second family.
How... how could he abandon them?
Hello, Emiko.
We're talking tonight
with two former vigilantes
turned public servants...
Oliver Queen and Laurel Lance.
Ms. Lance, you've had
an impressive start
as district attorney.
Tell me what these last few
months have meant to you.
Well, Rich, when I first got this job,
I didn't think I could do it,
considering... the
trauma that I had endured.
But I wanted to honor
my father's legacy.
And I think you have.
Well, I know she has.
Mr. Queen, you've talked
before about how much
your own father's
sacrifice inspired you.
Yes.
Do you believe that's his legacy?
Hello, Emiko.
I know everything.
You've wasted your time coming here.
What our father did
to you, to your mother
was unforgivable.
I need to try and make things right.
My father did sacrifice
himself for me, and...
I'll always be grateful.
Still, that experience on the raft...
Just the two of you...
Watching your father commit
suicide right before your eyes,
that must have been harrowing.
What a true hero your father was.
I can prove to you that
I'm nothing like him.
You're a Queen.
All you know how to do is
leverage your own privilege
to help yourself.
What happened to you was wrong.
You should have been
a part of our lives.
You should be a part of my life now.
Why do you think I want
anything to do with the Queens?
'Cause your family destroys
everything it touches.
I just want a chance.
Just give me a chance.
Emiko...
You're my sister.
I have no family.
My goal has always
been to serve this city.
I understand that
there are people who...
They disagreed with my methods before.
So I would like to assure
the people of Star City
I will no longer be
hiding in the shadows,
and I promise to always
be on the side of the law.
I believe that trust can be built
through transparency.
And I'm gonna prove it.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
Thank you.
You were amazing.
You were genuine and
heartfelt and amazing,
and for a second there, I almost
believed that you liked Laurel.
I almost do.
If Dinah's goal is to convince the city
to accept you as SCPD,
I would say mission accomplished.
We'll see.
Emiko will come around, too.
Well, she has every right to be angry.
My father abandoned her. I just...
I need her to see
that he and I are not the same person.
Well, she will, because
you're not the same person.
Look, that was an excellent first step.
If you can prove yourself to the city,
you can convince your
sister to give you a chance.
I hope you're right.
You're here because
A.R.G.U.S. is assembling
a unique task force,
and you've been identified
as a potential candidate.
For a bomb in my head? No, thanks.
I heard what happened
to the members of your last squad.
We are offering you a chance
to lessen your prison sentence
by repaying your debt to society.
And what about your debt to society?
Arrow was a criminal,
and you fought alongside him.
You've demonstrated a
severe negative response
to male authority figures.
Yeah. Well, when you grow
up with a father like mine...
Daddy issues.
You're only alive right
now because of your friends.
Welcome back to A.R.G.U.S., Ms. Cutter.
"Ms. Cutter." So formal.
Tell us about a challenge
that you've worked to overcome.
Well, the love of my life rejected me...
For a blonde.
Man, what the hell is going on?
China White, Spawn of
Slade, and now Cupid?
It's like the ghost of
villains past in here.
Have we met?
Agent Holt, a word.
You're not my type.
The Ghost Initiative is just
a cooler-sounding name for suicide s...
Look, I know you're angry,
but this is about Dante.
So I was right.
There's a hidden
meaning in that painting.
It turns out Dante's a person...
A very dangerous one.
Intel from our overseas office indicates
that he is the financier
behind dozens of terrorist
attacks all over the world.
Apparently, there's only a few people
who have direct contact with Dante.
We tracked one back
to a compound in Egypt.
We get a hold of this
guy, we catch Dante,
and the Ghost Initiative is
our best shot at doing that.
How did you all find all this out?
Why was I left in the dark?
The lead came from a source...
Our first member in
the Ghost Initiative.
Have you all lost your mind?
Ricardo Diaz?!
The same Ricardo Diaz
we just put in prison,
the guy who stabbed me,
who tried to kill all of
us about 17 times? This...
Curtis, we know that it's not ideal.
That is the definition
of an understatement.
Do Oliver and Felicity know?
No one knows, and it
has to stay that way.
A.R.G.U.S. knows that we
restarted the Ghost Initiative,
but they don't know
that we're using them
to go after Dante.
And if they did, they
would kill the mission.
Remember Switzerland?
Now that you're looped
in, we need your help.
I'm not putting any
bombs in anyone's heads.
I don't care how evil
that head might be.
You don't have to.
We just need you to make sure
the bomb tech isn't rejected
by the subjects' bodies
after insertion.
Yeah, 'cause that's so much better.
Curtis, this is how we catch Dante.
And it's not a request.
I hope you like Malbec.
If it's alcohol, I love it.
Good. Well, actually, I don't know
your Earth-Two situation.
Maybe you shouldn't be drinking?
Oh, please.
I don't have a problem with alcohol,
maybe the first thing I've managed
to one-up your Laurel on.
Well, then here you go.
So what's going on?
What do you mean?
- You told me to meet you here.
- Mm-hmm.
Usually, there's a reason,
like a kidnapping
or maybe you need help
torturing someone again.
I just wanted to celebrate with you
after your incredible interview.
Oh. Okay.
Quentin would be really proud of you,
the work you've done as a D.A.
and the person that you've become.
Really.
Thank you.
I'll be right back, but pace yourself
because we are gonna
drink this whole bottle.
...Including a start
on Pro Bono cases at CNRI,
the question as to
whether Laurel Lance was
the right person to take over as D.A.
was put to rest after
a recent poll indicates
she is the most popular D.A.
in the past 10 years.
The district attorney's position is
not an on-the-job training type.
It requires experience to lead, train...
Laurel Lance.
It is a must to know
criminal law inside and out.
That's impossible.
Hello, Brett.
Who the hell are you?
I discovered a new talent.
I thought you should
be the first to hear it.
We both know you're not as
perfect as you say you are.
You should be behind bars.
I think you've had enough, buddy.
What just happened? Who's that guy?
I guess not everyone's a fan of the D.A.
Okay, but the wine, the wine.
Oh, my producer loves the piece.
Yeah. He thinks it's gonna be huge.
Yeah, I'm still here.
Hey. I'm gonna have to call you...
Rich Kannon left the
studio just after 8:00
to meet his wife for dinner
but never made it to the restaurant.
Never even made it to his car.
They found it in a
parking lot this morning.
Security cameras?
Every single one of them shorted out
just a few minutes
before Kannon disappeared.
Oh. Overhead lights were blown.
Suggests a power surge.
That means our kidnapper knows his way
around an electrical grid.
That takes planning.
This wasn't just some random attack.
Well, maybe someone saw my interview
and didn't like what they saw.
This doesn't feel like a coincidence.
Well, probably not.
But until we know more,
we can't assume anything.
Captain, you need to see this.
Oliver Queen is not a hero.
He's a fraud and a liar.
He does not deserve to represent
the people of Star City.
And if he does not quit the SCPD,
measures will be taken,
people will suffer.
How's the analysis coming?
Almost finished with my algorithm.
And then after that, I should
be ready to start testing,
assuming they don't
trip-walk into the bathroom
and accidentally set off
the bombs in their neck.
I guess that saves me from asking
if you're still having
a problem with all this.
Look, I know these are bad people,
but what we're doing is inhumane.
Curtis, restoring the program is
the only way we can get Dante
without A.R.G.U.S. oversight.
And that makes it right?
How can you be okay with that?
I'm not. I'm not.
We are fighting evil
that most people don't even know exists.
And sometimes that means making
very difficult decisions, Curtis.
The bombs are just a
failsafe. That's all.
There has to be a better way.
I wish there were.
District attorney Laurel Lance entering
Queen residence.
Phase one is online and operational.
What the hell was that?
Just a little something
I've been working on.
Oh, good. That's why I'm here, actually.
I was hoping to utilize
some of your skills
to help me with something.
- Ooh.
- Hypothetically...
Okay, let me stop you right there
because we both know that
"hypothetically" means
that this is definitely happening.
I need to know if someone
from Earth-Two is here.
Okay. That's not where I
thought you were going with that.
Is it that guy from the bar?
I knew you recognized him. Who is he?
The more I know, the
more I can help you.
Do you remember when I helped you
with that whole torturing
the assassin thing?
No questions asked?
Vaguely. Okay, fine.
I will see what Cisco can dig up,
but then we are done
playing hypothetical games.
Deal.
His name's Brett Collins.
You know, one of these days,
you are going to realize
that you can trust people.
- Hey.
- Yeah.
You know, we knew not everyone was
gonna be a fan of you working here.
I mean, you should see
my stack of hate mail,
and that was without
everyone knowing about me.
Mm-mm. This guy's an amateur.
The video quality, the execution...
He's new at this.
He also didn't do a very
good job covering his tracks.
The video was uploaded
from a coffee shop
in the southeast quadrant of The Glades.
Do we have satellite imagery there?
I think so. Hold on.
What are we looking for?
We're looking for windows.
If he didn't know to cover his tracks,
he might not have
gone too far from home.
There.
That's a match.
Let's go get him.
Kannon's been moved.
Nothing down here either.
I got a visual, southeast corner.
Copy. Closing in from below.
Oh, God. Please help me!
Come on, now.
You don't want to do that.
Wrong. People without the last
name Queen are human beings, too.
Oh. Oh, God.
I got kannon. Anyone
have eyes on the target?
Lost him.
We got the reporter.
The kidnapper got away.
That's not the only thing
that's bothering you.
It was something that he said:
"People without the last name
Queen are human beings, too."
Oh, and you disagree?
I agree. The timing's funny.
What with your secret half-sister
mysteriously returning into your life,
it's strange.
It's not that it's
strange. It's familiar.
The psychiatric records from Slabside
that you leaked to the press.
Can you pull up my
transcript with Dr. Parker?
Not exactly sure what that
has to do with anything,
but, yes, I can.
Thank you.
Here you go.
Can you scroll down
a little bit, please?
- Mm-hmm.
- There.
"What became of Hackett?
Your father shot him. Then what?
He doesn't matter in this story,
just collateral damage?
People without the last name
Queen are human beings, too."
The files I sent to
the press were redacted.
The ones you sent to the D.A. weren't.
So the kidnapper hacked them, but why?
Why these particular
sessions with Parker?
Can you look up Hackett,
first name David?
Hackett, David, died in 2007.
Survived by his son Sam,
no other living relatives.
I met Sam a few times growing up.
Yeah, he's got quite the rap sheet...
Assault, assault with intent,
a bunch of drunk and disorderlies.
His father was lost at sea.
Or so he thought
until he read your sessions with Parker.
And he found out his father was murdered
by my father.
Emiko was right.
My family destroys
everything it touches.
Crap.
Hey, I have to go.
- Okay.
- And I'm sorry.
I love you.
I love you, too.
Lookie here. Mr. Terrific.
It's been a while, my friend.
You look a little nervous.
Is that because the last time we met
I had my knife in your gut?
Wasn't personal.
It's probably best not to
talk during the procedure.
Hey.
He looks a little nervous, doesn't he?
I can smell it on him from here.
It's okay, sweetie. I'll protect you.
You know, it's really gonna be nice
to finally have some peace and quiet.
What the hell are you doing?
Making sure the bombs
inside of your neck work.
But to do that, I need to turn them off,
which means that you have to take a nap.
It's strange...
You thinking it's a good idea
to give me drugs.
No. No, no, no, no.
This can't be right.
No, no, no, no, no.
I thought you were some kind of genius.
- Wake 'em up!
- Not a chance.
I said, wake them up!
Okay, okay. It doesn't matter.
Even once you get out that door,
A.R.G.U.S. guards are
gonna be all over you.
You let me worry about that.
Move!
Up. Hey. Get up.
What the hell's going on?
Early release for good behavior.
What about the bombs in our necks?
Thanks to our friend here,
out of commission.
Move.
_
You're still a disgusting drunk.
You haven't changed a bit.
But you have.
Look at you, pretending to be reformed,
playing make-believe lawyer
in those fancy D.A. suits.
You're a wolf in sheep's clothing,
a wolf that this city
needs to be rid of.
- Uh! Hyah...
- Hyah! Hyah...
You should have stayed on Earth-Two.
What the hell is Earth-Two?
You know, threatening me...
That was a bad idea.
Then again, your judgment's
in a perpetual state of impairment.
I should've finished
you off the first time,
although I doubt anybody
would've missed you.
Laurel!
We're leaving now.
You followed me here?
I didn't follow you. I...
I... I followed your DNA,
which you left on my door handle.
It's all part of this new
program that I'm working on
that tracks genetic material.
And here I thought I only had one
stalker that I had to worry about.
So you should be flattered
because I only stop people that I like.
And now that I've found you,
you are going to tell
me what is going on.
Hey, I know you're new
to this whole cop thing,
but the SCPD is not exactly
too popular in The Glades.
Right.
Where are we anyway?
Kidnapper's apartment.
His name is Sam Hackett,
and he has a degree in
electrical engineering,
and he has motive.
His father, Dave, was
my father's bodyguard
on the Queen's Gambit.
Wh... why would he be
going after you for that?
Dave made it to the life raft
with my father and I.
When my father realized
that only one of us could survive,
he shot him.
I didn't know.
Nobody knew until Dr. Parker.
Sam Hackett, SCPD. Open up.
Huh. Sam had a search trip planned
to the North China sea.
I'm sorry. He was still
looking for his father?
Still holding out
hope he was alive? Why?
Because you survived.
And here are
my unredacted transcripts
with Dr. Parker.
All these years, Dinah.
All these years he never got closure.
Oliver.
You got to see this.
Looks like he was building
some sort of weapon.
Remember, they're the
ones that need us alive,
not the other way around.
I love it when a plan comes together.
Unh!
Looking for these?
You just keep trying and failing.
This time I came prepared.
Not prepared enough.
This time, I'm gonna finish the job.
This is the Dragon.
A.R.G.U.S. is coming for you.
And we'll be sure to send him
your regards when we do.
What's the matter?
You look like you've heard a ghost.
What the hell just happened?
Well, first, I overrode
the explosive program
A.R.G.U.S. put inside your head
with a virtual reality simulation that
started running about 20 minutes before
you remember getting your sedative.
Then I owned your ass.
You're dead.
No. See, that all
happened in your head, too.
By the way, harsh.
Get me out of here.
See, I don't think you're gonna
want to be getting out of here
because if you were to do that,
Dante would be waiting for you.
And I think he's gonna be
really pissed when he finds out
you gave us everything
we need to get him.
A.R.G.U.S. thanks you
for your cooperation.
As Star City's newest kidnapper
continues to elude the police,
there have been renewed calls
demanding Oliver Queen step down.
A recent poll showed
that as many as 77%
of Star City citizens
would support his removal from the SC...
Any luck with the evidence
at Hackett's place?
Well, the guys in tech are
still working on I.D.-Ing
the fragments, but
judging from his notes,
plan "B" involves a lot more
than just kidnapping a reporter.
But we can't stop him if
we don't know where he is.
I know one way you can stop him...
Fire me.
77% of Star City agrees with me.
So that's what this is
about, public opinion?
No. I...
I wore that mask for a reason.
Now that I've taken it off,
maybe the consequences are
finally catching up with me.
Well, you can't take responsibility
for every choice some
lunatic makes, you know?
No. I have to take
responsibility for this.
Me being on the force
puts your reputation at risk,
and it's putting lives in danger.
Cops face risks every
day. That is the job.
And you are not putting
anyone's life in danger,
not unless you stop fighting for them.
You think you're gonna do one interview,
and all of a sudden, your
problems go away overnight?
I think I have been so obsessed
with proving to people I'm not my father
that I didn't stop and
look at all the ways
that I am exactly like him.
I should have come
clean with Sam years ago.
But you didn't,
and you can't stop the
past from haunting you.
The only thing you have control over is
what you do going forward.
Let me break this down for you
in words that I think that you're
going to be able to understand.
You are the D.A.
You cannot be seen attacking randos
outside of a bar!
Brett Collins isn't a rando.
He's supposed to be dead.
What does that mean? What
are you talking about?!
Collins is the drunk driver
who killed my father, okay?
I was 13.
And I spent so many years just dreaming
of the ways that I
was gonna make him pay.
And you know what? I did.
When I got my cry,
I tracked him down, and I killed him.
Or at least I thought I had killed him,
but, apparently, he's still alive
and... and stalking me
on another earth. Here.
What? What?
It's you haven't had
a problem talking about
the dozens of other people
that you have killed.
Um, so why... oh, why
keep this one a secret?
If someone had killed my dad,
I would want revenge, too.
Collins... he caused the accident
that killed my father,
but he wasn't the reason my father died.
He never should've been
on the road that day.
He was working a lot, which...
I hated...
But I knew on my birthday
that we would be able to celebrate,
only he...
He showed up without my cake,
and I threw a tantrum.
So he went back out.
That's when Collins
drove him off the road.
And do you know the last words
that I said to my father?
The last thing that I said
to him was "I hate you."
My dad died because of me.
Well, now that you've said it out loud,
can you understand
how irrational that is?
This is exactly the reason
I've never told anyone before.
Well, you should've so that that someone
could tell you that it's not your fault.
If someone is after you on this earth
or on any other earth,
we are going to get him
whoever they are together.
Officer Selway, what do you got?
There's something strange
about these fragments.
There's a partial
etching on some of them.
Separately, they don't mean much,
but you put them together,
you get the logo for Star City Electric.
They use it to tag proprietary parts.
Well, Hackett has a background
in electrical engineering.
Do you think he was
moonlighting for this company?
I ran his SoC.
There's no record of him working there.
Maybe try Dave Hackett.
After his father died, Sam spiraled.
Severe depression, got
picked up for drugs.
If he wanted to get a job,
he'd have to find a way to hide that.
Well, damn.
Someone with the father's SoC
has been working at
SC Electric since 2015.
Hey, doesn't the sce use GPS
trackers in their work vans now?
Yup, I'll run a trace.
How did that 240 go?
A couple of drunk frat
bros. Waste of time.
What's going on over there?
I guess the box needed work.
And 3, 2, 1. Bam. Huh.
Found the location?
Yeah, but it can't be right.
It says the Van's here.
Hey, did somebody call this in?
Not yet.
- Come on!
- What's happening?
Hey, did somebody call SC Electric?
You okay?
Yeah.
Dinah, you okay?
What the hell was that?
I don't know.
That was only a warning.
Because you've aided
and abetted Oliver Queen,
you're all going to suffer.
Uh!
The static generated by the electricity
coursing through these walls right now,
it makes this vest
and every substance that
can hold a current deadly.
What the hell do you want?
Oliver Queen.
Until I find him,
every minute, a body drops.
He must've hacked into
the electrical grid.
I want you to get outside,
and you shut it down.
I'll stall him.
How? He wants you dead.
Just hurry.
So much for your hero.
Who's ready to die?
Sam, that's enough.
You want me? I'm right here.
But I need you to let these people go.
They have nothing to do with this.
Of course they do.
SCPD, the news.
They're the ones who allow you
to fool everyone into
thinking you're a hero,
but I know what you really are.
I'm a liar, right, Sam?
Because I did lie about your father.
He was on the Queen's Gambit.
He made it to the life raft.
And before my father took his own life,
he murdered your dad
so that I could survive.
Good. You finally...
You finally admit it.
I was worried that I was gonna be judged
by the sins of my father...
But... but not coming to
you for all of these years
and not telling you the truth,
I never gave you a
chance to get closure.
That's on me.
I'm truly sorry.
No, no, no, no.
We are way, way past apologies.
My father is gone because of you,
and I need to make that right.
Uh!
I'm going to give everyone here
the chance to make a decision
my father never got to...
Whether to live or die.
Sam, no one is dying tonight.
Kill him, you live. Don't, you all fry.
You have till the count of 3. 1...
Don't do this, Sam.
2...
I don't want to die.
If you really believe
that you have to do this,
I understand.
3.
Pull the damn trigger.
Then I guess we all die.
Gun!
Like I said, nobody dies tonight.
That includes you.
I think the entire city
can sleep a little more
soundly knowing that
Sam Hackett is behind bars.
Well, that's the reason
I asked to be here today.
I'd like to set the record straight.
12 years ago,
when my father's boat went down...
He and I weren't the only two people
to reach the life raft.
A third individual, his
bodyguard, Dave Hackett,
was also aboard.
Now, when my father realized that there
wasn't enough food and water
for everyone, as you know,
he sacrificed himself for me.
But before he took his own life,
he took Dave Hackett's.
Your father killed Dave Hackett.
My father killed Dave Hackett.
The people of S-Star
City deserve the truth.
Why come forward now?
Hackett has been apprehended.
The threat is over.
Because transparency is about
more than just not wearing a mask.
I've made mistakes.
I'm sure that I will
make mistakes again.
But what I will not do is lie.
That is my promise to you,
the people of Star City.
I have waited a long time
to wipe the smirk off of Diaz's face.
Curtis, this is very, very good work.
Well, I am happy to help
make Diaz's life miserable
anytime anywhere.
Your VR program, it is a game changer.
Now that we got the Dante info,
we can get rid of those neck bombs
and finally cancel the Ghost Initiative
once and for all, right?
Right?
Curtis...
The Ghost Initiative
program still has value.
We need boots on the ground.
Look, thanks to you, we
can now get in their heads,
predict problems before they arise.
This is going to save a
lot of lives in the field.
Except maybe theirs.
When the Dante threat is over,
I promise you we will shut
this thing down for good.
There's always gonna be another Dante.
There's always gonna be
a logical reason to compromise,
but I'm not doing that anymore.
We've had this conversation.
Walking away is not the answer.
Oh, I'm not walking away.
I'm just not going to be
following orders blindly anymore either.
I'm gonna call my own shots.
A stalker from a different earth.
Of course. Why wouldn't there be?
Ah. I hope you're not leaving
because I have some good news.
We have Brett Collins in custody.
And after what you just told me,
I'm gonna make sure he stays
there for a very long time.
But how can you hold him
for crimes he committed
on another earth?
This scumbag is, unfortunately,
our earth's problem.
Beat cop picked him up
for public intoxication,
and it looks like he
has a history of stalking
and anti-vigilante violence.
Well, that makes sense.
I mean, he would've seen your interview,
and you are the former
black Canary, so...
And the Karma gods must
really be on your side,
because Cisco just texted
that Brett Collins from your earth
died 5 years ago on his porch
from unknown causes.
So 5 minutes ago, I
had 2 Brett problems,
and now I have none.
None.
Well, thank you. Thank
you to the both of you.
It's not so bad having other
people back you up, is it?
Hey.
Laurel had a stalker?
Yeah, it's been a crazy couple of days.
Yup.
Speaking of, I saw your interview.
I'm so proud of you. That
couldn't have been easy.
It's a start.
It's gonna take a lot
more to convince this city
I've changed.
Oh, I think you'd be surprised.
I, um, I forgot...
I forgot something over here.
I saw your interview.
Hmm.
That took guts.
It was the truth.
It took me too long to say it.
But you did.
And that's a start.
When I was little, I imagined
what it'd be like to
live in the Queen mansion.
Your lives seemed so glamorous...
But even more than that, I imagined
what it must have been
like to have a family.
Your father robbed me of that,
something I swore I could never forgive.
But I see now you are
different from him.
I'm trying to be.
Does all this mean you're ready to talk?
It means I'm ready to
think about talking.
I'll take that.
_
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --