My name is Oliver Queen.
For 5 years,
I was stranded on an island
with only one goal--
survive.
Oliver Queen is alive.
Now I will fulfill
my father's dying wish--
to use the list
of names he left me
and bring down those
who are poisoning my city.
To do this, I must
become someone else.
I must become
something else.
Previously on Arrow...
Felicity, I want you to find out
all you can about that notebook.
I'll be driving your mother
around for a few days.
She's not a suspect.
Oliver, something's going on
in this city. You know it.
Walter, please. You've got
to stop looking into this.
It's not safe.
Well, accidents tend
to befall people
who are too curious.
And he won't be harmed?
It's done.
Nor will ever discover your
involvement. You have my word.
I'm not sure I'm ready
for the kind of commitment
- that you're looking for.
- You can't be serious.
This is me serious,
Laurel.
Call Cayman Fidelity.
Tell them their
favorite accountant
is flying in to make
a special deposit
for a special client.
That elevator's supposed
to be on a key.
Go. Check it out.
Harold Backman,
you have failed
this city.
I'm only an accountant.
I'm just the money.
The money that leads
to extortion,
kidnapping, and drugs.
It's the destruction
of innocent lives!
You think you scare me
more than the people I work for?
No.
They can deal with you.
Hmm. Let me guess.
Some bad guy missing
his fancy new laptop.
Harold Backman. He's who
Starling City's worst call
when they want to
launder money in the Caymans.
Shouldn't we just
turn this over to,
I don't know, the IRS?
We will. Just as soon
as you return the money
to the rightful owners.
Well, it sounds like
a very nice idea.
Backman's files
are all protected
with an asymmetric
encryption algorithm.
Really? So it's gonna
take a while to break in.
Days, at least.
Better get started, then.
At the risk of ending up
with an arrow in my eye,
can I ask...
When are you planning
on making peace with Diggle?
He's the one who left,
Felicity.
I did everything I could
to stop him.
Except apologize.
You promised you'd help him track
down Floyd Lawton and then you--
Made a choice
that I can life with.
If he can't,
then I don't need him.
I need to get back to the club.
Oliver--
Let me know
when you break in.
I wish someone would
send me off to the Caymans.
Yes, I know it's been
6 months. But--
I am very well aware
of the statistics.
But I haven't given up hope
and neither should you.
That didn't sound
too good.
Oh, it's fine.
Who were you talking to?
Just the insurance company.
They insist on paying out
Walter's life insurance policy.
I know we haven't talked
about Walter in a while,
but I--I miss him, too.
It's like losing dad
all over again.
You look radiant.
Flatterer.
I think you're
the last to arrive.
How's Tommy?
Tommy is Tommy.
How's Oliver?
Still in bed.
It's only noon.
Well, look who
I just found.
Get lost trying
to find the house?
You say that as if
your driveway's
not longer
than most roads.
Can I get anyone
anything else? Frank?
We're fine, dear,
thank you.
Oh, excuse me.
Hello, Mrs. Queen.
I'm sorry to bother you at home.
Oh, no, no. Don't be silly, Walter.
Come in, please.
You're here
to see Robert.
Yes. There's just some
papers he needs to sign
for the stock offering.
Well, he's in some
private meeting right now,
but you're welcome
to wait for him in his study.
Thank you.
Unless you'd like
to help me
get my children
out of the house.
You don't have
children, do you, Walter?
Not yet, I'm afraid.
Well, save yourself
the trouble and don't.
They eventually
all turn into teenagers.
Adam Hunt
was reluctant at first,
but was more cooperative
upon being informed
we knew about
his embezzlement.
Police communication system
could use an upgrade.
I think Mr. Hunt
can be persuaded
to make an anonymous
donation.
Well, that will certainly
cure what ails this city.
What's that, Malcolm?
We're emptying the Atlantic
with a tablespoon.
For years we've been forcing
the city's worst to do what is best,
leverage them to help us
save the city.
But it's... not working.
Crime in the Glades
is rising.
The cancer is spreading.
We just need to...
Take some more time.
Did Rebecca get more time?
Did the man who raped Frank's daughter
give her any quarter?
Everyone in this room has lost
something or someone to the Glades.
And we have committed
ourselves to fixing it.
But what have we truly
accomplished?
Nothing.
Maybe it's because
the Glades can't be fixed.
You're saying we should
abandon the project?
Yes.
In favor of a new
undertaking.
Like Ben Tre in Vietnam.
The village must be destroyed
before it can be saved.
Are you suggesting
we somehow...
level the Glades?
Down to the bedrock.
Only then can we truly
rebuild Starling City
and make it safer for everyone.
That's 24 square blocks.
And if we did--
and I'm not saying
we should--
if we did,
wouldn't suspicion
fall on us?
Not if the destruction
appears to be caused
by a natural disaster.
You've always had something of
a God complex, Malcolm.
It's part of your charm.
But even you can't create
a natural disaster.
Have you ever heard of
Unidac Industries?
It's a small company.
They have an idea...
An idea that will serve
our purposes.
My sources tell me they're
5 years away from prototype.
And any undertaking of value
is worthy of patience.
And restraint.
One man alone
can't save this city,
Robert,
and we both know that.
Of all the gin joints
in all the towns in all the world,
she walks into mine.
This coffee's terrible,
Oliver.
That's what you get
for ordering coffee in a bar.
You look tired.
Too much work?
Too much crying.
Tommy broke up with me.
What happened?
I have no idea.
Things were good.
They were...
Great, and then suddenly
he's packing up his things
and telling me
that it's over.
Did he say anything
to you?
No. Tommy and I haven't
talked very much since he quit.
But he'll come around.
It's probably
just cold feet.
Like it was with you.
Oliver, you don't sleep with
your girlfriend's sister
unless you're looking
to blow the relationship up.
If you still want
to be with Tommy,
do what
we should have done.
Talk to each other
and be honest.
Oliver,
I need to show you what--
I just totally walked in
on a thing, didn't I?
I'm sorry, uh,
who are you?
Nobody. I mean,
I'm not nobody.
I'm someone,
obviously.
And so are you.
You're Laurel, right?
That Laurel.
Gorgeous Laurel.
This is Felicity.
She's setting up my Internet.
Router. And I need
to show Oliver
something very important
related to it.
I'll let you go, then.
Thank you for the coffee...
and the advice.
Tell me you got in.
Better. I hacked
Cayman Fidelity
and put together a list all the
deposits Backman made last year.
Felicity, what good
does that do us
if we don't know
whose money it was?
Look at the biggest deposit
Backman made last year.
Bottom page.
$2 million on Decem--
December 12.
That's...
The day Walter
disappeared.
What if one of Backman's clients
was paid 2 million
to kidnap Walter?
Then we find out
which client it was...
And we use them
to find Walter.
1x21
The Undertaking
Original Air Date on May 1, 2013
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Resync for WEB-DL by lost0ne
www.addic7ed.com
Ok, back-trace the account,
follow the money,
hopefully it will lead us
to whoever kidnapped Walter.
After all this time,
do you think Walter might
still really be alive?
I don't know.
Got it.
Dominic Alonzo.
- Name ring any bells?
- Yeah.
Alonzo runs the biggest
underground casino in Starling City
when he's not busy
kidnapping.
He looks like the kind of lowlife
someone would hire to kidnap Walter.
How many arrows do you think
you'll have to put in him
before he gives up Walter's location?
Say a lot?
It's not that simple.
That casino has
its own private army.
We need to access
Alonzo's computer,
but without setting off
any alarms.
Looks like we're gonna need
all the help we can get.
It's too bad there's not
someone else we could call.
That's enough. We can
do this on our own.
Well, then... Looks like someone's
going gambling tonight.
Those guys would make me
the minute that I walked in there.
Oliver Queen would never be
caught dead in a place like that.
I wasn't talking about you.
Absolutely not.
I can count cards.
It's all probability theory
and mathematics.
Have you met me?
Bottom line--I know my way
around a casino.
Felicity, I'm not
letting you walk--
The reason I joined you
in the first place
was to find Walter,
and for the first time,
we have a real chance
of finding him.
You have to let me do this.
All right.
But we do it my way.
Come on.
I'm sorry I had to
pull you away
from whoever
you were meeting.
Oh, it's nothing.
Everyone's left already.
Besides, it's my fault for forgetting
to sign the K-5s this morning.
I hope you don't mind me asking,
but is everything all right?
Just, uh, taking care
of some odds and ends.
Well, if ever you need
a friendly ear.
You're a good man, Walter.
I thought you'd left.
I'm still waiting
for your answer.
How can you even think
of doing this?
That place took
your soul, Robert.
Doing this won't give it back.
It won't bring back
Rebecca, either.
It still feels like
yesterday, that day.
When she called my cell
phone for the first time,
I remember being annoyed.
She knew I was busy,
so I just let it ring.
When she called back
a minute later,
I shut my phone off.
A little after midnight,
two SCPD officers
showed up in my office.
All I remember them
saying was...
She'd been shot.
Murdered in the Glades.
After the cops left, I sat in my
office the rest of the night
listening to Rebecca's messages.
She kept calling my name...
Asking for help...
until she was just
struggling to breathe,
gasping for air.
I listened to my wife die
over and over
and over again.
I can't imagine, Malcolm.
Try.
Imagine it was Moira
lying on that pavement,
bleeding, calling your name.
And then tell me you wouldn't
be prepared to do what I am.
What do you want?
Is that any way
to treat a girl
who just walked up
6 flights of stairs?
No, it's not. Where are my manners?
Come on in.
Thank you.
Welcome.
Did you do these?
You know, Felicity,
Oliver and I don't need
a relationship counselor.
That hasn't been
my experience.
We have a lead
on Walter.
I need you to come back
and help us find him.
Oliver put you up to this?
No.
He doesn't even know
I'm here.
Look.
I know Oliver
didn't help you
find your brother's killer
and that hurts.
It sucks. But...
You gotta know
if it was your life on the line
on not just your...
very understandable vendetta,
he would be there
for you.
No hesitation.
And I don't want
a partnership
with those kind
of qualifications, Felicity.
I know Oliver's religiously
against admitting he's wrong.
Truth is, he needs you.
Yeah.
And when Oliver
is ready to say that,
he knows where I live.
Sorry for bothering you.
It's no bother.
I hope you find him.
Wow, you really
look like your father.
I never thought so before,
but just now
I saw him in you.
What are you doing here?
We need to talk.
I said everything
I have to say.
Well, I haven't.
Tommy, I love you,
and I think that
you still love me,
so whatever problems
that you think that we have,
I know that if we
face them together--
You don't understand.
Then help me understand.
If our relationship
is gonna end, at least
let it end with honesty.
Ok, Laurel.
Honestly...
You belong with Oliver.
Excuse me?
He's still in love
with you.
I have a meeting.
You ready?
I think so.
Just to be clear,
the plan is for me
to get caught counting cards
in an underground casino
filled with hardened criminals.
So you can get a friendly
warning from Alonzo
and plant a bug
on his office computer.
Right. Which will
hopefully lead us to Walter.
That is assuming I get
the friendly warning
and not a bullet.
You don't
have to do this.
Yes, I do.
Ok. If anything happens,
I'm right outside.
Ok.
Password?
Snapdragon.
Password is snapdragon.
Password?
Snapdragon.
What do you see?
6 armed guards,
2 pit bosses,
and a floor man.
No slot machines.
How do you call yourself a casino
without any Lucky 7s?
Stay focused, please.
I'll be with you
the entire time.
Thanks.
It feels really good
having you inside me.
And by "you,"
I mean your voice.
And by "me," I mean my ear.
I'm gonna stop talking
right now.
That would be my preference.
One stack of High Society,
please.
Thank you for stopping by.
Of course.
Uh, you said
you had news.
I do.
It's ready.
The Markov device passed its final
beta test this morning.
Applied Sciences
is loading it on a truck
bound for Starling City
as we speak.
Well...
Congratulations
are in order, then.
To both of us.
Moira, you may be
surprised to know
that I sometimes
waver in my convictions.
But your friendship,
your endless support...
always gives me
the strength to carry on.
After all, you and I
will always have a connection.
I'm just sorry that
Robert's not here
to celebrate with us.
I'm sorry I had to
take him from you.
If anyone's to blame
for his death, it's me.
To Robert.
To Rebecca.
Are you feeling all right?
I know tonight was
just another Ted Kord fund-raiser,
but you were
surprisingly quiet.
Moira, there's something
I need to talk to you about.
Robert, if this
is what I think it is,
I don't want to know
her name. I don't--
No, it's about Malcolm.
He wants to level the Glades.
And how does Malcolm
propose to evacuate
an entire section
of the city?
He doesn't.
Robert, that doesn't
sound like you.
Because I'm not the man
you think I am.
About a month before
the opening of Steele factory,
the one in the Glades,
I was approached
by a local councilman.
He wanted money.
Told me that's the way
everything was done in the Glades.
I told him I'd never
paid a bribe in my life.
We got into an argument.
I didn't want to hurt him.
I swear, Moira.
But he fell.
Oh, dear God.
The work I'm doing
with Malcolm, with the list,
it's my penance, Moira.
What, so you'll atone
for one murder
by committing hundreds,
thousands?
Oh...
Robert.
You listen to me.
Whatever wrongs
you've committed,
whatever mistakes
you've made,
preventing this horror
is your chance to make it right.
Please...
Please, Robert, promise me
you won't let this happen.
Oh!
Blackjack!
Miss...
Can you come with me?
Is something wrong?
Get up.
Oh, since you ask
so nicely.
Oh, there's the bathroom.
I should have known
the manager's office
would be down the hall
and to the right of the bathroom.
Mr. Alonzo.
Have a seat.
What's your name?
Megan.
Do you know where the term
"86" comes from, Megan?
As it happens, I do.
It's from prohibition.
There was a--
an illegal casino,
not like this one,
located at 86 Bedford
street in New York,
and... God, you know,
I'm just gonna stop talking.
Now it means
to ban someone,
someone who's cheating.
You're 86'd.
Leave your chips and go.
Thank you.
Oh, yeah, Megan,
one more thing.
You see, the thing
about card counters is, uh...
sometimes they work...
with a partner.
You're gonna be really upset
when you meet my partner.
Aah!
I heard you never miss.
I don't.
Uhh!
Where's Walter Steele?
What? What a you
talking about, huh?
6 months ago
you had him kidnapped!
It was just a job.
I was given a name.
I didn't ask
any questions.
Last chance.
Where is he?
Below ground.
You're lying!
I'm not.
I delivered him
and they killed him.
I heard the gunshot.
He's dead.
Oh, let's see that blouse
in that violet shade.
You're
a miracle worker, Thea.
Oh, when it comes to shopping,
it's not work, really.
Hey. I'm teaching mom
the joys of online clothes shopping.
Ollie?
Are you ok?
I need to talk to you both.
What is it?
It's about Walter.
Did the police
contact you?
One of Mr. Diggle's
army buddies
works for the FBI now.
And they got news tonight.
No.
I'm very sorry.
No, no, no, no, no.
There must be
some mistake.
Who did Mr. Diggle
talk to?
Did they find a body?
Mom...
Walter's gone.
No. This isn't right.
- Where are you going?
- Out.
- It's 10:00 at night.
- I need some air.
Mom, you're in shock.
Don't tell me what
or how I feel, Oliver.
Why is she acting
like that?
Come here.
I suspect I know
what this is about.
You and I got in bed
with Malcolm
to cure what ails
this city.
But I think you agree,
killing thousands of people
is not the answer.
Indeed. If we
were to wage a war
with Malcolm Merlyn,
we will lose.
My family has already
suffered enough.
And I have no desire
to endanger mine.
Fortunately,
there's another option.
6 months ago, Malcolm
started buying up buildings
in the Glades
through an offshore company
called Sagittarius.
And he made it sound as if this
undertaking of his
was a recent inspiration.
If you're right,
he has been thinking
about this for months.
If he can't rebuild it,
he'll abandon the project.
How much of the Glades
does he already have?
About a third.
Now, if we can quietly
buy up the rest before he can,
he won't be able to gain
the control he needs.
We will need capital.
Do you still have
your contacts in China?
I already have a flight planned
for Shanghai tomorrow.
Come with me.
We shouldn't travel together.
Malcolm might get worried.
He already knows
I have my doubts.
Besides, I'm getting the urge
to take out the "Queen's Gambit"
for another voyage.
Dad! Do you have any cash?
Jerk pizza guy
can't break a 100.
Oliver, you remember
Mr. Chen?
- Hi.
- Hey.
Waiting. Thank you.
♪ 1, 2, 3, 4, tell me...
Pizza.
My hero.
I'm starved.
- Hey, Ollie.
- Yeah.
Where do you keep
the bottle opener in this thing?
Bottom drawer.
Did you talk to Ray today?
About the ski trip?
No. He asked Jean
to move in with him last night.
Oh. Guess they've
been together forever.
We've been together longer.
Guess we have.
I only bring this up because your
mom busted me yesterday.
And obviously we can't
hang out at my house.
Why? Because your father
threatened to tase me
the last time that I closed
the door to your bedroom?
So wouldn't it be nice
to have a little place of our own?
Yeah.
Maybe.
This is a little fast,
Laurel.
I know that you like
to think of yourself
as a bad boy,
Oliver Queen, but...
I feel like we're ready
to take the next step.
Yeah.
Let's do it.
Mm.
You lied to me.
We had a deal.
Gong dag. Gong-pa-ma-tsom.
What are you talking about?
You promised if I cooperated
with the Undertaking,
Walter wouldn't be harmed!
He hasn't been.
I'm a man of my word, Moira.
We both know
better than that.
And I know...
I know you've
had him killed.
Turn on the camera.
Oh, Walter...
Like you said, Moira,
we have an agreement.
Walter would stay
in my custody until
the Undertaking was complete.
We're both in this together.
I've been sitting
in the dark all night , too.
All these months
I kept thinking
if I could find a clue,
I could get a lead on him.
Guess it wouldn't
have mattered.
I can't imagine what
your family's going through.
Walter's alive.
What?
But Alonzo said--
I need you to pull up
Malcolm Merlyn's phone records.
He made a call
from his office
to wherever Walter
is being kept at 10:30 p.m.
Malcolm Merlyn?
Tommy's father?
Why would he kidnap Walter?
Felicity.
L.U.D. showed he made a call
to a tenement complex
located in Bludhaven.
Can you pull up
a satellite view?
Ok.
That's a lot of security
for low-income housing.
There's two guards
stationed at all access points.
There's just one
on the roof.
Exactly. There's no other
buildings in that area.
If you want to get
onto the roof,
you're going to have to
jump off of something.
I've got something.
There's a problem in quadrant 4.
Mr. Steele.
Walter.
What?
What's happening?
You're going home.
I thought I'd never
see you again.
I'm all right.
Welcome home, Walter.
Thank you, son.
Thea.
This is totally
a family thing, isn't it?
I'm sorry, who are you?
This is Felicity.
She's my friend.
Mine, too.
It's good to see you.
You, too.
I'll let you guys
get back to your hugging.
Oliver.
We're all together again.
Everything's
gonna be all right.
Robert, I don't like
the idea of this.
It's gonna be ok.
Yeah, well, how long
will you be gone?
A few weeks. Maybe more,
depending on what I--
Why can't you just
fly to China?
I think it's better
the less you know.
I just hate
that stupid boat.
Look at me.
I love you.
Everything's gonna be fine.
Ok.
Hey.
Got room for one more?
No.
Mom, let me keep dad company.
Oliver, you're in school.
Not really.
I tried to tell you that.
I could use an extra hand
on the ship.
Robert...
Moira, let the kid
take the boat out
with the old man.
All right.
But you promise me
that you'll behave yourself.
All right. I promise.
I love you so much.
I love you, too.
♪ Everywhere you go
I totally spaced.
I gotta call Tommy
and let him know
I'm out of town
for a few weeks.
I'll see you on board in 5.
Sara? You here?
Yeah, you might want to circle
around the block a few times,
because your sister
just showed up.
Hi. What are you doing here?
You're leaving
for 3 weeks.
I wanted to come say bye
to you in person.
I'm glad you did.
And...
I wanted to bring you
something.
Oh.
In case you get
lonely at sea.
Thank you.
Hey, is everything ok?
I mean, I didn't totally
freak you out
when I brought up the whole
apartment thing earlier, did I?
No.
Good.
Mm.
♪ Every time you're leavin' ♪
♪ I keep cryin'... ♪
But I do have to get back
to the boat.
Yeah.
Is it done?
Yes. The bomb
is in place.
And there's
a storm front
moving in along the "Gambit's"
projected course.
Ok.
When the "Queen's Gambit"
goes down,
no one will suspect it's anything
other than an act of God.
Oliver.
Ah. What a miracle.
How's Walter?
The police are saying that he
was rescued by the Vigilante.
Yes, he was.
Has he said anything
about his ordeal?
Was he able to identify
any of his captors?
No.
Hmm.
That's too bad.
They'll get
what's coming to them.
I'm just glad that
my family is back together.
We all are.
Ollie.
Excuse me.
Is Walter ok?
I saw it on the news.
Yeah.
Are you ok?
Of course.
I promise you
now is not the time.
It's you and Tommy.
You and me, actually.
I talked to Tommy yesterday,
and the reason
he broke up with me
is because he thinks that you
and I still belong together.
What did you say?
Nothing.
He walked out on me.
I just want you
to be happy.
It's what
I've always wanted.
Then will you please
go talk to Tommy for me?
And say what?
Say that you and I
are over.
That you're not
still in love with me.
I can't do that.
Why not?
Because it wouldn't be true.
And I have enough lies
in my life already.
I guess you do know
where I live.
I've always known
where you live.
May I?
I'm sorry.
You were right.
And I was wrong.
About Deadshot?
About everything.
About my mother and about her
involvement in the Undertaking.
She lied to me.
To Thea.
She's working with
Malcolm Merlyn.
They're planning something.
Something...
Terrible.
I don't know what yet.
But I just know one thing.
I need your help to stop them.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Resync for WEB-DL by lost0ne
www.addic7ed.com