Oh, my God.
Oh, my God
what?
Who is that?
That's Tommy Merlyn.
He died over
4 years ago.
Oliver, who's
Tommy Merlyn?
Thea's other brother...
and my best friend.
We're gonna need
a moment alone.
- He's a crony.
- Anachronism.
That's what
I said.
Lately we've been dealing
with anachronisms.
It's people and things
displaced throughout time.
Ok, but why would Nazis
from 1945
want to crash my wedding?
Crab legs. They
were delicious.
Well, Iris
has a point, though.
If they're out of time,
they would've targeted
the military
or law enforcement.
Tommy was plucked
from 5 years ago
and put in the Prometheus
wardrobe.
That doesn't make any sense.
It does if we're not dealing with
an anachronism.
Visitors
from another earth?
Whoa. There are more
than one?
There are 52,
actually.
Though
I'm hard pressed
to think of one where
Nazis are ascendant.
I can.
There's
a 53rd earth,
and it's called
Earth-X.
It doesn't have
a designation
because it's a place
so awful, so horrific,
no sane person would
ever travel there.
It's basically
our earth--same history,
same timeline--
with one crucial
and critical difference.
So let me
hypothesize.
The Nazis developed
the atomic bomb
before
the United States did,
and they were more
than happy to use it.
Yes,
the Nazis won the war,
and New York, London, Paris,
Moscow--all obliterated.
The SS set up outposts not
only all throughout Europe
but also all throughout
the Americas,
and Hitler continued
his brutal reign
aided by prime ministers
and presidents
sympathetic to him
until his death in 1994.
Now they're not happy
ruling just one earth.
God. This is making me
physically ill.
Yeah, the line starts
behind me.
W--we have to find them.
I mean, do you think
they're using the breach
to hop between worlds?
That or they're operating
from a staging area
somewhere in Central City
or close by.
Well,
good thing we have
a metric ton of smart people
in this building...and Rory.
Let's get to work on finding
our new friends from Earth-X.
Earth-X.
That's right.
And I'm dead
on this earth.
"This earth."
I'd almost prefer that.
I was born into the Reich.
The whole world
is the Fatherland.
We don't have
elementary schools
and summer camps.
We have youth groups,
military training.
We all grow up
without choice.
You have a choice now.
You can tell me
where to find
the others from Earth-X.
On my Earth,
you are my best friend.
I would die for you.
I would've died for you.
Would have?
You beat me to it.
I lost you.
It was like--
it was like
losing a limb.
And...
You weren't just
my best friend.
Tommy, you were
my brother,
and you sacrificed
yourself
for a woman that
we both loved.
And I was there, and
I had you right here.
You were
a good man here.
And I believe that
you still can be.
No. You don't understand.
If I--if I talk,
if I break,
the Fuehrer will kill
my father.
He'll kill my mother,
everyone that I love.
I will not let
that happen.
I will stop him.
Do you think you
can do that?
I promise you that
I can do that.
Then you really are
a special kind of idiot.
Your naivete would be
charming
if your weakness
wasn't so pathetic.
Is this how it is
on your planet--
everybody swayed
by sentiment?
Is everyone here
really so weak?
The Reich will change that.
The weak will be eliminated.
Your entire world
will be enslaved,
but you, you...
You won't be around
to witness it.
He is going to feel
your skull crack
under the weight of his boot.
Everyone you care about,
everyone you love,
they're going to die badly...
In ways that would give
even monsters nightmares.
I really wish that I
could live to see it.
No.
T--Tommy, don't!
♪ Arrow 6x08 ♪
Crisis on Earth-X, Part 2
Original Air Date on November 27, 2017
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
He's gone.
Who?
Merlyn?
The biosensor in his suit
indicates his heart stopped.
He always seemed
kind of soft to me.
Oliver.
He died for you.
And we will make
his death worthwhile.
That doesn't change
the fact
that now we're down
a man.
Keep your focus
where it belongs
and get to work on
locating that Prism.
Watch your tone,
or I'll watch it for you.
Oliver!
Did you just tell me
to watch my tone?
You're angry...
And I like it.
Don't you mock me.
Don't threaten me,
or have you forgotten?
I can end your life
before you birth your
next thought.
Try it once I break
every bone in your body.
Ok, we're all
a little emotional.
Here's what I suggest.
I will stop vibrating
my hand;
you stop breaking my wrist;
and you be
10% less brooding.
We accomplish nothing by
arguing amongst ourselves.
It's the accomplishing nothing
that has me concerned.
We came here
to conquer this Earth,
or have you forgotten?
Locate the Prism...
Please.
Once we have identified
the location
of the target,
I will devise a plan
of attack.
I'm sorry about Merlyn.
He should've died
in the Church
before he allowed
himself to be captured.
Kara, we need
that Prism.
We are running
out of time.
You have to trust
in the plan, Oliver.
You should. It's yours.
And do you trust me?
Yes, with all of my heart.
You're kidding me.
Are you kidding me?
This feels like a really bad
wedding prank.
No, I wish.
You want us to come, then?
I mean, Dig's on the mend,
but Dinah, Rene, and I can
be up there in a--
what's another word
for "Flash"?
No, I need you guys in
the bunker, expanding
our search for
the Earth-Xers.
I linked S.T.A.R. Labs'
system up with ours
so you can know what's
going on as we do.
Copy that.
I will get to work
on hacking
Palmer Tech's
spectrometers--heh--
to help the search
for Nazis.
See you soon.
Hey, Caitlin
and Wells are trying
to track down
the Earth-Xers using
some sort of
dimensional something.
Vibrations. I told Curtis
to do the same thing
with quantum field analysis.
I'm sorry about Tommy.
It wasn't Tommy.
He said that they are
trying to mount
some sort of invasion.
Guess the silver lining
to Black Siren is that we
have experience
with doppelgangers.
So if it's not Tommy
I'm reading on your face,
what's up?
You know what it is.
Well, maybe we should wait
until we repel invaders
from another earth
to have this conversation.
Remember when we got
back from Ivy town?
Do you remember
Ivy town?
Mm, so fondly.
When we got back, you
said that we could do this
and we could still
have our lives.
- Hmm.
- That was you.
Yeah.
So, um...
This impending invasion
notwithstanding,
may we take 2 minutes
and talk about this?
Yeah.
Maybe what wasn't fair
was me saying
I didn't want to marry you.
I mean not the way I did,
not with the most terrible
timing in the world.
Well, was it
how I said it?
Because I know that
it was really--
I mean, it was
spontaneous.
No, it was so lovely.
It was so sweet.
I love you.
I just don't want to be
married.
I don't...want
to be married to anyone.
You didn't feel that way
when we got engaged
two years ago.
Right. And then 10 minutes later,
I got shot and paralyzed,
and Barry and Iris have a wedding,
and Nazis crash it.
You didn't know that
was gonna happen
when you said
you didn't want to marry me.
My point is...
We have something so good,
we have something
so great going.
Let's not change that.
Let's just stand pat with
the cards that we're holding.
I want to move forward.
Felicity, I love you...
And I want to marry you.
I love you. I love you.
I will always, always,
always love you.
Please respect me on this.
Ok.
Thank you.
Felicity's got her
friend working on
Palmer Technology's
spectrometry satellites.
Ok, but what about
the Waverider?
I mean, a time-traveling
spaceship must have
some sort of tracking
technology that we can use.
Yeah, not exactly.
It's, uh, it's
in the stone age.
Oh, like,
literally in
the stone age.
Ok. Well, parallel earth
jumping is kind of
Cisco's specialty.
And since he's so busy
being unconscious right now,
I guess we're on our own.
Oh, perfect
timing, man.
We're trying to find
the guys
from Earth-X,
and we're coming
up with nothing.
I'm sorry. W-would
you excuse us for a moment?
Happily. We don't
want to step on whatever...
- Come on, Harry.
- Awkward, awkward thing...
- It's not about you.
- That is.
Grey, we got Nazis
from a parallel earth running around.
We don't have
time for--
Which is precisely why
we cannot afford to be
at odds with each other
right now.
I hardly need a psychic
connection to know
that you're upset
with me,
but I could stand
to know why.
Just forget about
it, man.
It would make some sense
if my decision to be
with my family forced you
to leave the Waverider,
but I--I accounted
for that variable,
and yet you're--
you're still upset.
- You just don't get it.
- No, I don't get it.
My retirement requires
you to give up nothing.
It requires me
to give up you, Grey.
Look, I thought I made
my peace with it.
I thought, "Ok, fine. I'll stay
on the Waverider.
"Maybe I can't be
Firestorm,
but I can still be
a Legend."
But then it hit me.
I still can't be
Firestorm
and I can't be a Legend
with you.
I never knew my father,
but I got to know you.
You're the closest thing
I've got to a dad,
and now you're leaving.
Hey.
How are you?
Um, well, punching Nazis,
that was definitely
as satisfying
as I imagined it would be.
It's...
You ok?
Yeah. Oh, me? No. I'm--
I'm fi--I'm ok.
I'm completely ok.
I'm ok, ok?
- Ok.
This isn't gonna
be a thing, right?
Yeah. No, no, I'm--I'm ok.
I'm good.
Hey. I was
looking for you.
- Hey.
- Are you ok?
Why does everybody ask
me that question? Heh.
Uh, well, you
sort of look like you
just killed
someone's puppy.
Uh, no.
I'm--I'm fine.
It's just this whole
thing with Sara was--
God, it was
a mistake. Heh!
A mistake, but you came here
to have fun at a wedding,
and, um, ok,
Nazi invaders aside,
you--you had
a good time, right?
No. I mean, this--this
was all kinds of wrong.
Waking up with a strange
woman in a strange bed,
I have never had a
one-night stand before.
And this whole thing
has just,
it's got me spinning,
Kara.
I mean, what--what if
I made a huge mistake?
- No, Alex--
- Ok, no, no, no.
I mean, look, I know
I want to have kids,
but Maggie was real.
I mean, what we had,
that was real.
And now, um, with
everything, I just--
I chose to
let her go.
I chose that.
I mean, what was
I thinking?
Alex, Maggie was amazing,
and you two were amazing
together,
but the best
part about her
was that she showed you
how to be true to yourself.
You want kids.
She doesn't.
You--you just had to do
what was right for you.
What if I was wrong?
How long till you brainiacs
find these Nazis?
Oh, my answer hasn't
changed in the 2 minutes
since you
last asked me.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
I'm dealing with
some Oliver stuff,
not "Nazis ruined
the happiest day of our life" stuff
but...
Stuff.
Stuff. Like you don't
want to marry him stuff?
You might have said it
a little loudly
at the rehearsal dinner.
- Ah.
- What happened?
I thought at the salon, you
said you guys were good.
We are good. And we're
great. We're just as--
we're just as good as we
were the last time we got engaged
and I got shot.
That was the beginning
of the end for us.
I don't want to
tempt fate again,
you know?
A break-in at
Dayton Optical Systems?
Ohh! I know
this sounds terrible,
but maybe we should let
the police handle it.
I mean, we need our peeps
to focus on the Nazis.
- This is Nazis.
- How do you know?
- I'll go get Barry.
- Yeah, ok.
Just a quick reminder,
super speed--
I don't have it.
Noted.
So what do we know
about this place?
Why are the Earth-Xers
targeting it?
Dark Arrow, distorted:
Because...
They had something
we need.
Whatever you stole...
We're gonna
want it back.
Your confidence is
predictable.
You've faced some of
the greatest evils known to man,
and you've
defeated them,
but if you think so
highly of yourselves
that you can defeat
any threat
that comes
your way...
How do you feel
about us?
This is sick.
Do you mean looking
at your reflection
and seeing only
weakness? I agree.
Thawne?
Direct from Earth-1.
Do you like my face?
It's the face you were
wearing
when I became the Flash.
I thought I'd put it
on again.
You know, for
old time's sake.
Plus, handsome.
I watched you die.
Or did you?
It's time travel,
Barry.
So very confusing.
I always seem to be
saying that to you,
don't I?
Tommy killed himself.
I heard your Tommy
died years ago.
That's what
this earth does.
It makes people soft.
We've been watching you.
We've been watching
all of you
and how you've squandered
the potential of 2 worlds.
On our earth, we've developed
a meritocracy.
We've accomplished
greatness.
You're perverse.
No, Kara, you're
the perversion.
The most powerful being
on the planet
rendered weak by
saccharine Americana?
My pod was blessed to
crash in the Fatherland.
Then go back there.
This is not your earth.
Leave.
I don't
answer to the likes of you.
My allegiance is to
the Fatherland
and to my wife.
His wife?
Gross!
No offense.
Last chance. Go home.
And stay there
all of you.
And what
do you think that's going to do?
Bullets bounce off of me.
Oh, this arrow won't.
Is that a kryptonite
arrow?
Why do you have
a kryptonite arrow?
In case an evil you
ever showed up.
Get the Prism
out of here!
Are you all right?
I'm pissed.
Well, take it out
on that.
Hey.
It's gonna fall.
All right.
Get me over there.
Get the workers to safety!
We need to stabilize
the building.
The site's cleared.
- And stabilized.
- Nice work.
Let's not
celebrate just yet.
We gave those doppelgangers
the window they needed to escape.
Escape with what?
Dayton Optical Systems
calls it the Prism.
What on earth do they need
a sub-light generator for?
It's basically
a spectral emitter that...
Uses quantum entanglement.
You could also
use it to create
a stable
fusion reaction.
Ok, which
all means what?
No. Guys, really,
I would like to know
what you're
talking about.
You got this.
Well, basically, the device
they stole can be converted
to a neutron bomb.
Pfooo.
I take it back.
The bottom line is
that we have to catch
these parallel-earth
goose-steppers.
This might help.
- Is that a kryptonite arrow?
- Yup.
I know I shouldn't
have to ask this question,
but I have to ask
this question.
Oliver didn't
shoot Kara, did he?
Sort of. The other
Archer and flying woman
are Oliver and Kara
of Earth-X.
When you said that
Earth-X was horrible,
you might have
undersold it.
Wait a minute. How--how
could there be another Kara?
Well, there are 53 karas,
just like there's
53 Kryptons
and 53 Earths.
And the Thawne
from our earth
is working
with them.
He's an idiot.
Ok, if that arrow has
not-so-Supergirl's blood on it, we c--
We could track it using
quantum analysis.
We could.
Hey, guys, I think
I might have a quicker way.
These red blood cells
are suffused
with shortwave
radiation.
- Solar radiation?
- Yeah, incredibly high amounts.
Like nothing
I've ever seen.
Can you track it?
Well, I once caught
a deranged serial killer
off his face cream, so...
No joke. Heh!
Let's just do it
and fast.
Ok.
Will it work?
It will with
a few adjustments
and a significant
power source.
My husband's on his
way to handle that
as we speak.
Your husband
has a choice to make.
Me or the Reich?
That's right.
Because we have 2 goals,
and my worry is if we can't
accomplish them both,
he's gonna choose you
over a second earth
flying under our banner.
Oliver will not
abandon our mission.
I've seen this before.
In 1945, Hitler and his men
were equally shortsighted.
Hitler was driven
by passion
and childish need.
Oliver is 10 times
the man Hitler ever was.
Not when he's blinded
by his love for you.
If it comes to Oliver
choosing between me
and the Reich,
I'll make sure he
chooses the Fatherland.
How?
If it comes to it...
By taking the choice
out of his hands.
Maybe tracking her off
of face cream would've been easier.
Supergirl-X's blood
is filled with solar radiation--
more than it should be--
but if I could try to get that to act
as a kind of beacon.
Hey, ahem.
How do you do it?
Do what, Rory?
Bring the other you
out of you.
You don't want to know.
Sure I do.
It happens when I am
scared or angry.
Oh.
So if I were to, um, boo!
Nice try.
Boom. Whatever's going
on with Kara-X's blood,
it's intensifying.
Worse for her is
better for us.
Better for us for
tracking her at least.
We should have her
location any minute.
I can't believe
he's back.
I don't know if I'll
ever be rid of him.
I know. And I know
how much you're hurting.
I just keep looking
for closure,
but every time I see
him, all I see is--
your mother dying.
You're gonna stop him.
How do you know?
Because you always do.
And because we're not
gonna let you do it alone.
We're getting close
on a location.
Look, guys, I'm sorry.
This is not how this week
was supposed to go.
We can't think about
that right now.
You should.
We fight to protect
the people that we love,
so you guys recognize
what you have.
Recognize it and cherish it
and let it make you stronger,
because if you do that,
you will always find your
way back to one another.
It's the same for you
and Felicity, man.
I don't know, Barry.
I d--I--
she told me she doesn't
believe in marriage.
I'm not feeling sorry
for myself.
I just--I think that if
she loved me
the way I loved her, she
would want to marry me.
Oliver, I've known
Felicity for 5 years,
and I'm
here to tell you,
as sure as I'm standing
here, she loves you.
Felicity...
- And I appreciate that.
- Is standing behind you.
She's right there.
We got 'em.
They're at a shipping
depot outside Danville.
All right. We'll
get the band back together.
Yeah.
- Oliver, I--
- It's ok.
We can talk when
I'm--when I'm back.
But right now,
I need--
I need to have
my head in the game.
Get your head in the game.
Supergirl and Firestorm
are sweeping the perimeter.
It's done. It's
wall-to-wall Nazis in there.
Alex and I will take
up breach positions
on the northwest
corner,
if that's ok
with you.
S.T.A.R. Labs thinks
they converted
the sub-light
generator--
the Prism that
they stole--
into some kind of
superweapon.
Speaking of super, theirs
is our biggest threat.
Agreed.
Let's take her out first.
Hey.
You ok?
Yeah.
No. You know?
It's gonna be ok.
Mustard.
You people have breaches
but no mustard.
Um, what are you
even doing here?
Yeah, why didn't
you go with them?
Go where?
Couldn't have left one
for me?
I'm saving Nazi you
for you.
There's no sign
of the Prism.
Well, it's got to be
here somewhere.
We got incoming.
I see...
Their Flash,
their Supergirl.
Hyah!
Yeah, I see them.
Where's their Arrow?
It was in the fridge.
Did you check
the fridge?
Oh. Thank you, sweetheart.
Any word from the team?
They're over at
the shipping depot,
but it's just radio silence.
Oh, God.
There is no God.
You and you, hide.
What about Caitlin?
It's gonna get a lot
colder in here.
Burn.
Afraid of a little heat?
No.
I'm afraid of nothing.
Bet you're pretty angry
and scared right now.
I told you, I don't
fear anything.
Actually...
He was talking about me.
Didn't think
this through, did you?
Just you against us.
I don't need to think
to kill you.
Anyone else want to be
a hero?
They wanted to wait,
but I didn't think
we'd ever get
a better entry line
than that.
Uh! Thanks.
What the hell is that?
Metallo.
Hate to do this
to that handsome face, but...
Is everyone all right?
We're gonna have
to work on
your definition of "all right,"
Oliver.
Yo, Grey,
you good?
It seems my retirement
was somewhat tardy.
Well, here we are.
This is fun...for me,
not so much for you.
All the times you've
killed me,
and now here all I have
to do is kill you once.
Enough, Eobard. Enough.
Hey, you might want
to listen to her.
We know that if you
wanted to kill us,
you wouldn't have put these
dog collars on us first.
Now I know what it feels
like to hate myself.
Well done.
It wasn't a problem.
Hey. Uh!
The pain, the pain.
I don't know how much
longer I can bear it.
It's all right.
You're gonna be all right
because we found her.
We found her,
and now we have her.
I love you.
Now, very soon, this
nightmare will be over,
and I'll take you home.
So stand.
S.T.A.R. Labs is secure.
If you
hurt my friends...
I did hurt your friends.
I really enjoyed hurting
your friends.
Are they alive?
Yes, yes, for now.
We need your Kara's
cooperation.
Well, we don't need it.
It would be preferable.
But for the time being,
you are more valuable
as leverage.
What do you want
my sister for?
To save my life.
That's your little
mission statement, isn't it?
Help people, save lives.
Well, now's your chance.
The General is dying.
Her blood.
She's been exposed to
too much solar radiation.
Yes, like Icarus,
I flew
too close to the sun.
But we can save her.
We're going to save her.
All we need is a new heart.
And, luckily,
on this planet, we found
the perfect donor.
You stay the hell
away from my sister.
Mmm. Such loyalty.
My sister tried to
kill me.
That's why
you stole the Prism?
So you could duplicate
a red sun, weaken Kara,
and cut into her?
Can't make an omelet
with invulnerable eggs.
Hey.
I'm gonna kill you.
Nah, you won't.
You're weak.
And all of you choose
the high road.
You're heroes.
I thought we were
gonna die.
If I had a dime for every
time I thought that, I--
I'd have $2.40.
I really thought I'd
have more than that.
It was Oliver,
but it wasn't Oliver.
It was Oliver
in the high castle.
I just mean there is
so much out there
for us to be
afraid of--
Multiple earths,
aliens,
doppelgangers from
the third Reich.
I mean, what else
is coming?
And that thought
wakes me up at night.
How do you ever
get back to sleep?
Barry's by my side.
- Shut up.
- I'm sorry.
- I know you and Oliver--
- No, no.
Shut up.
We're not alone.
Stalag S.T.A.R. Labs.
What are we gonna do?
Kara.
Where's Kara?
They're gonna kill her.
It's ok. We're
gonna get her back.
We need to figure
out where we are first.
Yeah, about that.
This is somewhat
disconcerting.
I don't think
this is our earth.
We're on Earth-X.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man