ISABEL: You were supposed to sign this report
at last night's board meeting.
Know why you didn't?
OLIVER: Because I didn't attend
last night's board meeting.
-Where were you?
-I have interests outside of this company.
-I don't.
-Mr. Queen?
ISABEL: I thought you were serious
when you said we're partners.
-Isabel, I missed one meeting.
-This week.
-Last week, it was two meetings.
-Mr. Queen?
Company-wide revenue is up double digits
since you and I took over...
-Oliver!
-Yeah?
I'm sorry to interrupt your...
[GROWLS]
Um, I need to talk to you
about your plans for this evening.
With Mr. Harper.
You'll have to excuse me.
We have work to do. It's important.
So are my evening plans. I'm sorry.
We are going to have to work
on your excuses.
You're right.
GREEN ARROW:
You should be more careful.
You're completely exposed.
I knew you were there.
You wanted me to tell you when the
funny-money guys were ready to make a sale?
-Here we go.
-Not "we."
Go home. I already have help.
Here's the fake.
Let's see the real.
[ARROW WHISTLES]
[GRUNTING]
DIGGLE [OVER COM]:
You got two right above you.
Another at your six.
[SIRENS WAILING]
Stay where you are. Don't move.
-I wanna make a citizen's arrest.
-Don't move.
That's it. I'm clear.
[TASER CRACKLING]
[DIGGLE GRUNTS]
Strike Force X to Mockingbird.
We have the prize. We're coming home.
[DOOR OPENS]
DIGGLE:
Who are you people?
-NSA? CIA?
-My name is Amanda Waller.
[SIGHS]
Thought you A.R.G.U.S. guys
were supposed to be subtle.
For us, this was subtle.
-Then I wanna see Lyla Michaels.
-So do I.
-Agent Michaels has gone dark.
-Lyla's missing?
-What happened?
-She was running down a lead in Moscow.
She's missed two of her scheduled call-ins.
-What are you doing about it?
-Speaking to you.
Even if we knew where in Russia Lyla is...
...my superiors believe sending in an extraction
team could cause an international incident.
As far as they're concerned, she's already
a framed picture on our lobby wall.
Why are you telling me all this?
Because I know how you and Oliver Queen
spend your nights.
And I know your passport is up-to-date.
It'd help to start with what Lyla was doing
in Moscow in the first place.
-Who was this lead she was tracking down?
-A line on the whereabouts of Floyd Lawton.
Deadshot.
Lyla was in Russia for me.
Agent Michaels is an asset
I can't easily replace.
I know you find her similarly irreplaceable.
Bring her home, Mr. Diggle.
[CHATTERING]
Thanks.
It's been a while since I arrested you.
I've forgotten how good it feels.
I was working for him.
Him who?
The guy who cost you your shield.
I'm on his team.
You are too, right?
THEA:
Anybody else having serious déjà vu?
[LANCE SIGHS]
It's all right, we're letting him go.
It's our mistake.
He was just in the wrong place
at the wrong time.
Okay, uh, let's just get out of here
before anyone changes their mind.
The potentially catastrophic risk
of turning on this machine...
...far outweigh any scientific gain
that might come from it.
The people need to understand
just how dangerous technology like this is...
...and the very real possibility
of a cataclysmic event.
[DOOR OPENS]
Where'd you go? Is everything okay?
Yeah. I just need a few personal days.
-What's going on?
-Have to help a friend.
Who?
Lyla Michaels.
It's his spy girlfriend
that works for A.R.G.U.S.
She went to Russia looking for Deadshot.
For me.
And now she's missing.
Felicity...
...I think it's time we visited
our Queen Consolidated subsidiary in Moscow.
-Yeah.
-Oliver, what are you doing?
Just need to help a friend.
-I can't ask you to do that.
-You didn't.
Sara?
My name's Ivo.
What's your name?
Tommy.
IVO:
So...
...how did you come to be on this island,
Tommy? I assume it wasn't by choice.
My, uh...
My boat was shipwrecked here.
And I was the only survivor.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Did you explore the island much?
Some of it.
Why?
You didn't happen to run across
a Japanese Imperial Navy submarine, did you?
During World War II...
...every country was trying
to develop the ultimate weapon.
The United States had the Manhattan Project,
of course, the Nazis had Das Uranverein...
...and the Japanese, well...
...they had Mirakuru.
Stem-cell and genetic therapies.
Decades ahead of their time.
Every war advances the cause of science.
The Japanese, they developed a serum...
...that caused increased strength
and rapid cell regeneration.
-They called it Mirakuru.
-"Miracle."
Thought they could create an army
of super soldiers.
They were transporting their only supply
via submarine...
...when that sub came under heavy fire
by the Allied forces...
...and it ran aground in this chain of islands.
Thanks to you...
...we now know it's this island.
You killed my friends.
Which means it's up to you...
...to help us find that sub.
Are we forgetting something?
Where do you think you're going?
Tahiti.
That's funny. The flight manifest says
you're going to Moscow.
Well, we're gonna stop by there,
you know, after Tahiti.
What kind of partner decides to interact with
our overseas holdings behind the other's back?
-It was an oversight.
-Oh.
Well, lucky for our partnership,
I'm a fast packer.
Oliver, her tagging along
does not help matters any.
I will take care of her.
John...
...we're gonna bring Lyla back...
...wherever she is.
[CHATTERING]
MAN:
Okay, Mr. Queen.
I've arranged a meeting
with the chief operating officer...
...of our Moscow subsidiaries, tomorrow
at 10 a.m. Try your hardest not to miss this.
-I'm not this person you seem to think I am.
-That depends.
On what?
On if I think you used the corporate jet
for a weekend of fun with your assistant.
Excuse me?
A blond IT girl all of a sudden gets promoted
to be assistant to the CEO.
There are only two ways that happens.
One is nepotism...
...and she doesn't look like your cousin.
That is absolutely not happening.
What were her qualifications?
Aside from an abundance of short skirts.
Her skirts aren't that short.
-What was that about?
-Nothing. Everything with Knyazev is set.
You have friends in the Russian mafia?
Color me not-at-all surprised.
-You're going to the hotel.
-You're leaving me with her?
Dig and I need to get a drink.
I wouldn't mind a drink.
THEA: Miss Loring.
I didn't take you for the club-hopping type.
-Heh. Well, I'm here on business.
-Is everything okay with my mom?
We need to discuss something
about this case.
-Your boyfriend, Roy, was arrested last night.
-I know. It was actually a misunderstanding.
-He got released-
-A few reporters got hold of the story...
...and they now know
you're dating a known felon.
Thea, your mother is on trial for her life.
Her defense pivots on being seen
as a loving mother...
...who did what she had to do to protect
her children, what kind of parent she was.
We need the people to know
that she raised you to make good decisions.
So if you care about your mom...
...you're gonna have
to end this relationship immediately.
[UPBEAT DANCE MUSIC
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
[CHATTERING IN RUSSIAN]
KNYAZEV:
Oliver Queen? Ha!
My favorite American.
[SPEAKS IN RUSSIAN]
It has been too long.
-John Diggle, this is Anatoli Knyazev.
-Thank you for meeting us.
[IN ENGLISH] If Oliver vouches for you,
you're my second favorite American.
[KNYAZEV LAUGHS]
First, a toast.
None for me, thanks.
[SPEAKS IN RUSSIAN]
Strength.
Now business.
This is woman you look for, yes?
Picture is from two days ago.
From gulag. Prison.
Lyla was arrested?
Not quite. From what I hear,
she was trying to break in.
-Why?
-I do not know.
But clearly she had issues
breaking back out.
Gulag is worst in Russia.
It's called Koshmar.
"The Nightmare."
It's full of violent psychopaths and killers.
And that's just the guards.
Anatoli, we need a way into the gulag
to extract her.
You get in, you get shot before you get out.
Or end up like your friend. It is impossible.
The only thing that's impossible
is us leaving this country without this woman.
[CHUCKLES]
I like this guy.
We have no word for "optimist" in Russian.
The only way into Koshmar is as prisoner.
Now, I have guard there, owes me favor.
It could work.
I give you one shot in 20.
-Set it up. I'll go.
-No, it has to be me.
-No...
-What if something happens to you in there?
What happens to me, Felicity,
or Isabel for that matter?
You have to be on the outside,
making the moves.
I'll go inside.
I've got this.
[SPEAKS IN RUSSIAN]
Now, that is a lot of drugs.
Courtesy of Knyazev. I'll have enough weight
to land me into Koshmar.
FELICITY: You need to be wearing this
when they process you.
The guards will take it, but that's the point.
This is Knyazev's man inside the prison.
A guard.
He'll know where in the gulag
Lyla is being held.
When all hell breaks loose,
meet us at the rendezvous point with Lyla or...
Or I am a permanent Russian.
Just thinking out loud...
...but are we sure this is the best plan
we can come up with?
I know Lyla's your friend, but...
Felicity, Lyla isn't my friend.
She was my wife.
Explain that sentence.
Lyla and I met in the Army
back in Afghanistan.
But we didn't stay married long
once we got stateside.
[SIGHS]
We couldn't figure out a way to stay married
without a war to fight.
So she joined A.R.G.U.S.
and I circled back for my third tour.
I can't leave here without her, Felicity.
I just can't.
[CELL PHONE BEEPS]
Two-minute warning.
Good luck, John.
[SIREN WAILING]
[SPEAKING IN RUSSIAN]
[GRUNTS]
They have him.
The clock's running.
[GUARD SPEAKS IN RUSSIAN]
[IN ENGLISH]
Hurry up.
[SPEAKING IN RUSSIAN]
What crime fits your punishment?
-Drugs. And you?
-Ah.
I gave speech.
For government corruption.
Right.
[GRUNTS]
It is rare
to see one of your people in Koshmar.
What, American?
[PRISONER SPEAKS IN RUSSIAN]
-Uh...
-Heh.
[IN ENGLISH]
Chernokozhiynot popular here.
Shocker.
You think Dig's okay?
I think he's doing the same as he was
when you asked five minutes ago.
They're coming.
They sell us Russian police truck for cheap.
[SPEAKING IN RUSSIAN]
What'd you say?
[IN ENGLISH]
"Please."
You know, in Russia there is gulag.
Almost as bad as this.
-Sara...
-Don't say my name.
If they find out we know each other,
they'll kill us both.
I thought you drowned.
When I came up, the boat was gone,
and I thought you were too.
I was floating out there for days
when this ship, they found me.
And they saved me.
Is that why you're helping them?
I don't have a choice.
I need to warn my friends.
You said they were dead.
They're not that easy to kill.
[SLADE GRUNTING AND GROANING]
SHADO:
Try not to move.
It smells like puke.
It'll heal your wounds.
You have to go.
Get out of here.
Get to high ground.
I'm not leaving you.
I don't wanna be the reason
something happens to you.
Then we're in agreement,
because I make my own choices.
You're a strong woman.
When I care about someone,
there's nothing I won't do for them.
Another thing we have in common.
[SHIVERING]
It's the burns.
They lower your body temperature.
Here.
ROY: Where you been all night?
THEA: Working.
ROY:
Oh.
Well, you deserve a break.
Um, actually, I've been thinking.
Maybe we should take some space.
I mean, we work together and live together.
It's kind of getting hard to breathe.
Since when? Oh, wait, does this have to do
with that lawyer lady dropping by?
This has to do with the fact
you've been arrested twice in the last month.
Come on,
I've been trying to stay out of trouble.
My body hasn't had a scratch on it in weeks.
-I mean, excluding the ones that you put there.
-And the other night?
Was a misunderstanding.
Roy...
...this just isn't working, okay?
Not for me.
Thea, you can't mean that.
I do.
I'm sorry.
[CHATTERING IN RUSSIAN]
Those men...
...they are vory.
They are in charge.
Is best to stay away.
Got it.
Listen, I'm looking for a guard
named Sergei Pavelski.
PRISONER:
Far corner. Over there.
American, you are a suka now.
Are we seriously gonna do this?
I guess so.
[GRUNTING]
[INMATES CHEERING AND SHOUTING]
Fighting strictly prohibited.
[SPEAKS IN RUSSIAN]
You missed the tour.
What happened to you?
I saw a Russian vehicle
that I simply had to have.
Is that why you came to Russia?
Car shopping?
Oh, I just only ordered one.
One's for me.
[IN RUSSIAN]
DIGGLE:
What is this?
GUARD:
Cold room.
[DIGGLE GRUNTS]
Six hours for you.
Six hours?
You can't keep me in here that long.
Now seven hours.
Well, that was pretty stupid.
Then again, you never really were
one of the brightest guys.
Deadshot.
Your spine frozen through yet?
Trust me...
...my problem here isn't with the cold.
You haven't forgiven me
for shooting your brother?
-Argh!
-Man, you really hold a grudge.
[YELLS]
I know why you're here.
That girl from A.R.G.U.S.
Lyla didn't find a lead on you...
...she found you.
Does everyone really think
that Felicity and I are...?
No. Just everyone who works
at Queen Consolidated.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
She's just a friend.
You don't seem the kind of man
who has female friends.
Can I ask you a personal question?
With some vodka in me, I just might answer.
Why does saving my family's company
mean so much to you?
Despite what Sheryl Sandberg might say...
[CHUCKLES]
...it still isn't that easy
to make it as a woman in business.
I've given up a lot.
Which means, if I don't succeed at everything,
then what was the point?
Hmm.
May I ask you a personal question?
Others have tried and failed.
Why do you try so hard to make me think
you're a lazy idiot?
I know you're not.
Underneath that swagger,
I see you pretty clearly.
Really?
And what do you see?
You're intelligent...
...driven...
...and lonely.
How do you see that?
Because it's what I see
when I look in the mirror.
SERGEI:
We don't have much time.
[SERGEI SPEAKS IN RUSSIAN]
[IN ENGLISH]
Let's go, let's go.
Nice seeing you, John.
[IN RUSSIAN]
You speak Russian.
I was raised in Moscow until I was 9.
Then adopted by a family
that took me to America.
Took me years to get rid of my accent.
It isn't easy making friends in grade school
when you sound like Natasha.
[CHUCKLES]
[IN RUSSIAN]
I don't have a lot of time.
ISABEL:
I'll be quick.
Five minutes. Must hurry.
Remind me to get you a pack of cigarettes
when this is all over.
I don't smoke.
[GRUNTS]
You weren't gonna leave without me,
were you?
I should kill you right now!
You won't.
Why?
Because I'm the only one who knows
where your little girlfriend is.
You're not stupid. You wouldn't put yourself
in here without an exit strategy.
I take you to the girl, you take me out.
OLIVER:
I just really have to go. I'm sorry.
Do I strike you as someone
who needs to cuddle?
-Hi.
It's time. Ready?
-Yeah, but...
-I think she can take the night off, don't you?
-Uh...
-Felicity...
What happens in Russia, stays in Russia.
Even when it makes no sense whatsoever.
[GRUNTING]
Guessing, uh, you wanna hold onto that.
This way.
FELICITY: What were you thinking?
OLIVER: What?
FELICITY: Almost 64 million women
over the age of consent in Russia...
...and you sleep with her.
So we're not doing the
"What happens in Russia, stays in Russia"?
We're still in Russia.
There is nothing money cannot buy
in this country.
Diggle should be heading out with Lyla
in two minutes.
Breaking out of prison is harder
than it looks.
You of all people should know that.
[FOOTSTEPS]
Stay quiet. Follow me.
You'll remember the rest of us?
Yes?
I promise.
I'll come back.
Come on.
Are we making a swim for it?
No, they'd shoot us
the second we hit the water.
You said your friends, they have
one of the radios from the ship, right?
Yeah.
Look like you know what you're doing.
The past year,
I learned things I never expected to.
You and me both.
They won't respond
unless they hear your voice.
[GROANS]
[SPEAKING IN CHINESE]
[IN ENGLISH]
Slade?
Come on. Can you hear me?
Can you hear...
[SPEAKS IN CHINESE]
-Thank God you're alive.
-Yeah, I'm on the...
[RADIO BEEPS THEN WHINES]
-Sara, what are you doing?
CAPTAIN: There's only two of them.
They haven't moved from the location
of the mortar attack.
What the hell is going on here?
You just confirmed
that your friends are alive.
Which means they're still a threat.
You know, until we kill them.
You son of a... Unh!
If I say she's in there,
what's keeping you from shooting me?
Honor.
You should try it sometime.
Lyla.
LYLA:
Johnnie.
Ready to go home?
You came for me.
Always have.
Always will.
Deadshot's here. In the prison.
I know.
What's your extraction plan?
It depends. What time is it?
[IN RUSSIAN]
[DEVICE BEEPING]
[ALARM WAILING]
DIGGLE: That's it. Let's go. Go, go, go.
Move, move, move.
[CLAMORING]
This way.
I got it. I shut down the phones.
The guards can't call for help.
If your friend and the woman
are not here by now, they will not be here at all.
Much better.
[IN RUSSIAN]
[GRUNTING]
[GUNFIRE]
DIGGLE:
Oliver, get down.
Follow me. Move!
KNYAZEV:
We're clear.
Stop the truck.
Get out.
Move, Lawton.
That's the thing about honor, John...
...you can't turn it on and off.
[CHUCKLES]
I'm just curious.
How is it you think
your brother ended up dead?
You shot at a client that Andy was protecting
and you missed.
I don't miss.
Your brother was the contract.
Who would wanna kill Andy?
Don't know their names, just an alias.
H.I.V.E.
Food for thought, John.
Food for thought.
Are we going to discuss
what happened last night?
Why would we?
OLIVER:
No reason.
I'll see you in the office tomorrow.
Thank you.
You had my back.
And now you know what it feels like.
What are you...? What are you doing here?
Good question. I've gotten a lot of calls from
prison, but never from my girlfriend's mother.
It occurred to me that I've never been given
the opportunity to meet the man in your life.
I don't know if she told you,
but your daughter kind of dumped me.
And what you should know
is that she did it for me.
Jean told me she came to see you.
I told her she shouldn't have.
-Why didn't you just tell me the truth?
-Look, us being together...
...it can hurt her case.
Thea, your social life is not going to be
the determining factor in my trial.
Sweetheart, what you've had to endure
this last year...
...is more than most people go through
in two lifetimes.
But you've not only survived,
you've flourished.
I think a lot of that has to do with Roy.
So as your mother,
I forbid you not to see him.
[CHUCKLES]
-Thank you.
MOIRA: Ha, ha.
I have to admit, this is not how I anticipated
my trip to Russia ending.
You just feel lucky
we made it out of there alive.
Thank you.
Not just for coming for me.
For doing what you had to once you did.
You mean working with Deadshot?
You know, me and Carly broke up
because I couldn't love her...
...and hate him at the same time.
I'm honored to be the exception.
Lyla, you were always the exception.
I have a debrief with A.R.G.U.S. at 0800.
No, no. Let Waller stew.
Stay for breakfast.
Throw in your blueberry pancakes
and you may be able to convince me.
[LYLA CHUCKLES]
Can you deliver this to Isabel's office,
please?
FELICITY:
Why her?
I mean, besides the obvious
leggy-model reason.
It just kind of happened.
It didn't mean anything.
Hey.
Because of the life that I lead...
...I just think that it's better to not...
...be with someone
that I could really care about.
Well, I think...
I think you deserve better than her.
We have their location.
This one's no longer of use to us.
Let's see how good you are...
...at removing a bullet from your head.
Wait.
He could still be useful.
IVO:
She's right.
Once we get rid of his friends,
we'll need him to lead us to the graves.
Sometimes I wonder
who gives the orders here, you...
...or your little bouzin.
You're going back to the island.
Oliver.