[Oliver] Previously on Arrow...
Last night, a group of vigilantes
saved hundreds of lives.
So if we are going to decide
on diverting police resources
towards stopping them,
we are not going to do that until
the people of Star City have spoken.
How the public will decide
on the issue of vigilantism
is anyone's guess.
Mayor Queen didn't mention
he was under investigation.
-Of course he did.
-Which makes us overdue for a chat.
-I'm not the man you think I am.
-No, Mr. Queen, I think you are.
I was able to upload
a critical piece of code
-to Arclight.
-What happens now?
We take the next step.
-[Oliver] Thanks very much, guys.
-[William] Thank you.
[Oliver] That's very generous of you.
Thank you, buddy.
-All right.
-[William] Oh, cranberry sauce.
-[Oliver] Okay. Happy Thanksgiving, guys.
-Awesome. Happy Thanksgiving.
Nice turnout. You're having fun?
Yeah. I'm really glad we're doing this.
Me too, buddy, me too.
Hey, how do you think Felicity's doing?
Uh, you should go save her.
Can you comment on speculation
Mayor Queen converted
Councilwoman Pollard's bill
into a city-wide referendum
as a distraction from speculation
that he's the Green Arrow?
If I was dating the Green Arrow,
I think I would know.
Besides, the Flash is much more my type.
Sam, she's a civilian,
-just give her a little space, okay?
-Mmm-hmm.
How is it that you don't put an arrow
into one of those people?
-[Oliver] Hey.
-Oh, did Oliver save you?
-He is heroic that way.
-She was doing just fine on her own.
All right, listen, we're all set inside.
Rene, he's a complete pain in the ass,
but he's a very good advanceman.
-Detective, what's the tally?
-Um, I got it all here.
Good. Good. All right, listen,
everybody, please gather around.
Gather around. Mayor Queen will be
making an announcement
and then we will be touring the site
of the new SCPD headquarters.
Thank you so much
for being here today, guys. Uh...
It means a ton to Felicity,
to William, to myself, that...
we can all gather together as a city,
and help our neediest neighbors
on Thanksgiving.
Across these various food drives,
with your help,
the SCPD has collected enough food
to feed over 1,200 families.
And it is why I am incredibly proud
to be here today at
the unveiling of our new precinct.
A top-of-the-line facility
for a top-of-the-line police force.
One that might actually make
federal agencies jealous.
Are you here to tour our new headquarters?
Turn around.
-You're doing this here?
-Oliver Queen, you're under arrest.
On what charges?
Murder, assault, burglary, and kidnapping.
All stemming from your activity
as the Green Arrow.
Dad?
It's gonna be fine, buddy. I promise.
[Watson]
You have the right to remain silent.
Anything you say can and will be
used against you in a court of law.
Okay. The Mayor's about to
come in, press in tow.
You'll give the formal salute,
he'll say a few words and...
I want this man processed
and I'm gonna need an interrogation room.
-This is the Mayor. You can't...
-I'm a Federal Agent,
with a valid arrest warrant.
I want this man bound over
until arraignment.
-Yes, but you are federal. This is...
-Temporary holding request.
I'm gonna need
the ranking lieutenant to sign off.
-Then get him here.
-I'm the ranking lieutenant.
Can I expect my prisoner
to be here when I come back for him?
Could you process the Mayor
through booking, Joe?
Joe?
You did this in front of my son.
In front of my son!
Agent Watson,
when I get out of here, and I will,
I'm going to sue you
for malicious prosecution.
Express yourself. In the meantime,
you're being prosecuted
for multiple felonies.
You show up after five years
and The Hood just "happens to"
show up with you?
That was Roy Harper.
Wearing the hood at your instruction.
Same way John Diggle's been doing
since I started my investigation.
I've got more than you think I have.
A confession
will make this easier on all of us.
I'd like to see William.
You're not in a position to make demands.
I demand to see William.
Until then, you get nothing.
You said you weren't
the Green Arrow anymore.
I am not the Green Arrow anymore.
Even the FBI would agree with me there.
I've kept my promise to you.
You're in jail.
I'll get out of here
as soon as I possibly can.
For now, go home with Felicity
and Raisa will be there
and I will be there just as soon as
I can. Okay? I just...
I need you to be as strong
as I know you can be.
Okay, buddy?
Come here.
Okay. This is gonna sting.
And by sting, I mean hurt really bad.
Okay, well, as long as it will stop this.
Well, I can't say 100% that it will.
This is a prototype that
Felicity and I have been developing
to mass-produce her spinal implant.
Spinal as in not sure
if it will work for your issue,
prototype as in, well, prototype.
Let's do this.
[grunts]
Took Felicity's a while to work.
Hey, you guys need to see this.
Watson just arrested Oliver in front
of basically the entire world.
[female reporter] ...a lot
to be thankful for this holiday season.
At the Thanksgiving food drive this
morning, the FBI arrested Mayor Queen...
-That son of a bitch.
-Pretty much. Yeah.
Did she just do all this now
because she just got through
talking to all of us?
Sorry, she didn't talk to all of us,
she actually never talked to me.
If you've got FOMO about being
interrogated, don't worry.
Think you won't miss out
when we all get arrested.
I actually think we're all
in the clear for now.
No, because cops arrest
up the food chain in criminal enterprises,
not to say that we're
criminal enterprises.
They don't arrest
the kingpin and his underlings,
they arrest the underlings first.
That's how it works.
I've seen every episode
ofThe Closer.Twice.
Well, I'm a real life cop
and I observed Oliver's interrogation
and it didn't sound like we were targets.
That's enough.
We have to focus.
This might be the most difficult
thing we've ever had to face.
If the people think
that the Green Arrow's in prison,
then the floodgates will open.
Now, more than ever,
we have to protect this city.
If the criminals here think
that it's open season,
then this city will become a war zone.
You got us in here so easily.
I didn't have a chance to kill anybody.
Well, homicide is not
our objective here, Miss Lance.
Two guards inside.
What's the holdup?
Your generation is so impatient.
Why can't you just savor the anticipation?
Cry havoc and let slip
the dogs of war, Miss Lance.
[guards grunt]
That was a literary epigram,
Miss Lance, not a directive.
Potato, po-tah-toe.
Now, what am I looking for?
The nano-thermite device is inside
the containment unit at the far end.
They do not have the keys.
-[Cayden] Wait.
-[Laurel] Why?
And don't say, "Savor the anticipation."
Nano-thermite is highly explosive.
Your scream will detonate...
[sonic scream]
You do see how that
could've gone wrong. Yes?
Yes. But it didn't.
[door opens]
[footsteps]
-Tell me what you need.
-I need some sleep.
I think I can do one better.
FBI transfers can get lost.
-Locks can be left open.
-I appreciate that.
But if I make myself a fugitive, then,
obviously I'm making William an orphan.
-You got to do it the right way.
-Yeah.
-I got to do it the right way.
-Okay.
Good night.
[sighs]
Hand's feeling a bit better.
What you got?
There was a break-in last night
at Sunderland Corp.
Why didn't we get an alert?
Felicity has us wired...
Up the wazoo. I know.
Trying to figure it out.
We're basically
the Big Brother of Star City.
Not in a creepy way.
[Curtis] Okay. This makes more sense now.
Laurel.
Yeah, who works with Cayden James,
who can hack any security system
to bypass any alerts, such as ours.
What did they steal?
Nano-thermite. It's a metastable
intermolecular composite.
A reactive particle, you know,
like mint inside a soda?
Alone, harmless. But together,
kaboom, as in kill lots of people,
not spill grape juice
all over your clothes...
What are they targeting, Curtis?
I don't know.
Nano-thermite needs to be combined
in order to be combustible,
but once it is, there are
many, many, many possibilities.
-Can you narrow it down?
-No. But Felicity might be able to.
Hey, talk fast. Oliver's arraignment
is in two minutes.
Laurel and Cayden James got their hands on
a mess of nano-thermite last night.
That means they'll be in the market
for an accelerant.
What kind of accelerant?
That's a really long list.
The nano-thermite heist,
did it involve a computer hack?
It involved Cayden James,
so what do you think?
I think that you can back-trace his hack,
maybe you can get into his system.
Can you come back and do this?
Because you're like,
way better at this than I am.
I got to go.
-Hey.
-[man] Mr. Mayor?
Sam? I didn't realize
you were joining my defense.
-Can a city district attorney...
-He can't. And I'm not.
I'm sorry, Mr. Mayor. But considering
that the charges against you
stem from actions taken
within this city...
Is the FBI handing you the case?
Sorry, Oliver.
All rise!
Docket Q-R-2-8-6-1, State vs Oliver Queen.
Judge McGarvey presiding.
I understand the defense have waived
the reading of charges
in favor of a motion?
Yes, Your Honor.
Defense moves to dismiss
for lack of probable cause.
The photograph with the defendant
wearing the Green Arrow outfit
was debunked a month ago.
We're not relying on that photo.
The FBI has provided definitive proof
that Oliver Queen is the Green Arrow.
Then let's see it.
Show my whole card during
an arraignment? I don't think so.
Sorry, Miss Loring,
but we're not skipping over steps here.
But good for you, I'm gonna release
the defendant on bail.
Your Honor, the defendant faces
seven counts of murder.
And he's the Mayor
and sole parent of a minor.
Something tells me
he's not going anywhere.
Particularly not with a $5 million bail
and a $500,000 bond.
[gavel pounds]
We're gonna ask for an accelerated
docket and an early trial date.
Please tell William not to worry.
You tell him yourself when you get home.
I'm sorry, do you have
half a million dollars lying around?
-Actually I do.
-What?
The first round of the angel investment
for Curtis' and my start-up came through.
-No. I can't let you do that.
-I can't let you not let me.
[straining]
That is so not fair.
It's not supposed to be fair.
But thanks to you,
I might be able to keep my job.
-No tremor?
-Almost gone.
You're a genius, Curtis.
I bet you say that to all the geniuses.
[alarm beeping]
-What's that?
-Hacker tracker.
Our friend Cayden
just infiltrated security at AmerTek,
which, as it happens,
has 20 different possible accelerants
that could combine and cause,
well, lots of damage.
[sighs]
Wanna say it?
Call in the team. And suit up.
[newscaster reports indistinctly]
What's this I'm hearing
about Watson having a smoking gun?
She gave it to D.A. Armand.
We need to find out what kind
of ammunition they work with.
No, no, no. I'm not risking
Felicity hacking the FBI.
Ooh, too late, also, too little.
Whatever information they have,
they're keeping it offline.
I can check around the SCPD,
see if anybody's heard anything.
Good. Quentin, let's see if
whatever it is came from City Hall.
Yeah, sure. Been a while
since I used my detective skills.
You know, on the plus side,
you getting arrested
has done wonders
for your approval ratings.
Yeah, and it's had the opposite effect
on the anti-vigilante referendum too.
-There's a silver lining.
-[cell phone beeping]
Oh, we got to go. Well, us. Not you.
There's a bad guy or girl
who's breaking into AmerTek.
I'm assuming all those, uh,
squirelly looks
mean that the girl in question is, what,
-Laurel's evil twin?
-She's working with Cayden James,
a criminal
we've been tracking for some time.
I have been wrestling over
whether or not to tell you.
Well, I'm glad you didn't.
'Cause I don't want
anything more to do with her.
Well, Quentin, now that you know...
I will distract myself
clearing your good name.
Wow. What a warm welcome.
You really know how to treat a girl.
'Tis the season.
I suggest keeping
your lovely singing to a minimum.
There are over a dozen highly
reactive compounds in this facility.
No promises.
[Green Arrow] Sitrep.
You got four turkeys near the entrance
and five more stuffed in on the floor.
All puns intended.
Your window to move is now.
Copy that.
Me and Terrific have the guys on the left,
you two, the guys on the right.
Move out. Go.
[grunting]
[groans]
[grunts, exclaims]
Arrow.
John, what the hell's going on?
-I'm okay.
-No, he's not.
We need to get you out of here. Now!
No. You need to stop Laurel.
Go. [panting]
Go! Now! Go!
[strains]
[panting loudly]
Merry men are approaching your position.
Robin Hood is laying back for some reason.
[grunts]
[Black Canary] Take cover.
[gunshots]
Our objective here
is the package, Miss Lance.
[sonic scream]
Digg's been keeping this
a secret for months?
With some kind of drugs?
And he told you guys.
And he didn't loop me in?
It was right
when Oliver got home from Kasnia.
And he figured he'd be okay
after Curtis hooked him up
with that prototype thingy.
What prototype thingy?
You might have to ask him.
Hey, speaking of, any word
from Curtis on Digg's condition?
Stable.
They're running tests.
Feels wrong us not being
at the hospital with him.
All of us showing up in his room
right now is the last thing we need.
Well, Digg needs to get back
on his feet pronto.
'Cause we did not exactly
shine out there without him.
What did Laurel steal this time?
Only 100 pounds
of polymer-bonded explosives.
When combined with the nano-thermite...
Well, actually, I don't know
what happens when they combine.
It'll take a little time
for this blood work to come back.
But if I had to guess,
you're suffering withdrawal
from the drug you've been taking,
in combination with
Mr. Holt's experimental treatment.
Is he gonna be okay?
I'll know more once
Mr. Diggle's panels come back.
Thank you, Doctor.
[sighs]
I should have ran
a mountain of tests on you
before injecting you with that prototype.
It was my choice.
Don't beat yourself up, Curtis.
[cell phone vibrating]
[Curtis]Felicity.
We have a problem.
We have a massively huge problem
and considering it's in the same week
Oliver's been arrested.
-What is it?
-[Felicity] The nano-thermite,
when combined with the explosive,
creates a thermobaric weapon.
What's a thermobaric weapon?
It disperses what is essentially
a cloud of fire
and then pressure cooks everything
within 200 yards.
I'm guessing we're giving up hope
that Cayden James has to cook
a lot of turkeys for Thanksgiving.
[Felicity] The only good news is that
a thermobaric bomb
is extremely difficult to make.
Yeah. Well, Cayden James could do it,
given his history.
He'll probably detonate it
in a populated area.
Maximize casualties.
Go help Felicity. See if you can
find out where's he's targeting.
[Felicity] Hey, John.
I just heard about
what's been going on with you. And...
I'm really sorry
you've been dealing with this.
Thank you, Felicity.
-Have you told Oliver?
-No.
Really think that you should tell him.
Look, he just got arrested. I don't
want to add anything to his plate.
John, I think he'd really want to know.
Not this week.
Thanksgiving Day.
There's a million events going on.
I mean, if you're Cayden James,
what do you target?
-Soup kitchens, parade?
-Door-buster sales.
That's where my mom took me.
Cayden wouldn't guess.
He would be logical, be calculating.
Calculating.
I saw one of his algorithms at Helix
that's based on traffic patterns
and can extrapolate to predict
population movements.
-Maybe if I can recreate it...
-I'm here. Uh...
What can I do to help?
You can start by telling me what prototype
you used to treat John's condition.
Our prototype.
The one we've been developing
to cure paralysis.
You injected our friend with
our company's proprietary technology
and you didn't think to, I don't know,
involve me in that at all?
I thought Lone Ranger was just the way
we did things here at Helix Dynamics.
You know, the name of the company
you picked without consulting me?
I'm gonna work on an algorithm over there
when I figure out what an algorithm is.
I can't believe you just equated
a company name
to exposing a friend of ours
to an untested procedure,
one you still haven't told me about.
It's the prototype of your spinal implant.
Well, mine, seeing as how
I'm the one who invented it.
Which is why I probably don't understand
how you get to be so offended here.
Okay. We don't have time
for this right now.
[keyboard clacking]
You should cross-reference
the crowds' patterns
with the bomb's path of destruction.
I'll work on a particle cloud sim.
Could've just told me
you didn't like the name.
It's more than just the name, Felicity.
You picked the product we're making,
we're working out of your loft.
That's called being decisive,
taking initiative.
I didn't do anything in secret.
Can we, maybe, fight about this
when we don't have
a thermobaric bomb to stop?
You don't have to ask me to do anything,
because that's how
you and I work together.
It's done. Let's hope it works.
[John sighs]
I told Felicity
not to bother you with this.
Which part?
You being in the hospital?
The experimental steroid or...
The nerve damage
that has affected you for months?
-Are you gonna be all right?
-I'll be fine.
I didn't want you to worry, Oliver,
which is why I didn't tell you.
No, no. John, you didn't tell me
because you knew I'd never let you
go out there compromised.
And that I'd certainly never let you
compromise the team.
I've been mad at you before,
John, this is...
The first time
I've ever been disappointed.
Oliver, you gave up the right to judge me
when you gave up that hood.
You don't get to claim the moral
high ground here, my friend.
I'm not, Oliver.
But I apologize to the people
who I endanger.
The team, Oliver.
The team.
My obligation begins and ends with them.
I don't owe you a damn thing.
For the sake of our friendship,
I hope that's withdrawal talking.
I put on this hood
because you asked me to.
-Don't blame me for this.
-I'm not blaming you, Oliver.
I blame myself.
For putting your needs, your goals,
even your family above my own.
I've done that from the very beginning.
-That was my biggest mistake.
-That was your biggest mistake?
Mine was trusting you
to be the Green Arrow.
[door closes]
Hey, Speedy.
I miss you. [chuckles]
I miss chatting.
They say that, um...
people in comas can hear
other people talking to them.
If you can hear me,
just wake up, all right?
Please.
'Cause I need you now.
Should we order
our traditional Thanksgiving meal?
I can call Big Belly Burger.
I'm gonna crush my french fries,
and pretend they're mashed potatoes.
Got it.
Maximum damage for a thermobaric bomb
is Starling Stadium.
Today is Thanksgiving.
Yeah. We just covered that
when we talked about
ordering turkey burgers.
I'm saying Billy Joel
is playing there tonight.
Sold-out crowd.
I happen to like a wide variety of music
and The Stranger is a treasured
piece of rock and roll history. Yeah.
Starling Stadium seats 35,000 people.
Guess that sold-out crowd's gonna
get pressure-cooked today.
So how do we go in without Diggle?
We have to step it up. Fight without him.
'Cause that went really well at AmerTek.
We got four hours until showtime.
That's definitely the place,
because Cayden
already has control over the system.
What can we do about shutting it down
or cutting the power or something?
Tried that, didn't work.
That's how I know Cayden
has me locked out of the grid.
I know the saying goes, "The show
must go on," but this can't.
I might be able to help with that.
I'll declare a state of emergency
and they will cancel the concert.
-Did you talk to John?
-John and I spoke.
Wanted to apologize to everyone.
I didn't know about John's injury and...
I should have.
I will have them shut down the concert.
I wanted to see Billy Joel.
[man] Like I said on the phone, Mr. Mayor,
I'm not canceling.
The cost would be catastrophic.
So would a terrorist attack.
You have no actionable intelligence
or confirmation from law enforcement.
You're asking me to set a match
to millions of dollars on a hunch?
Have you even brought this to Mr. Joel?
Brought what?
You haven't given me anything substantive.
I'm trying to save lives.
You're trying to save your ass.
You give me some proof, something
more than your gut to go on,
and I'll cancel. But without it,
we open the gates at 7:00 p.m.
Oh, come on.
-You all right?
-Yeah. Why're you asking?
-'Cause you don't look it.
-Well...
Well, I get it.
No one wants to believe
someone that they care about
is capable of unspeakable things.
I've been there.
[scoffs] Oh, yeah?
Has your daughter's
otherworldly doppelganger
been on a murder spree lately, Dinah?
Not exactly. No.
But I did find out my ex-boyfriend
is a vigilante.
What, the guy in the ski goggles?
I never thought in a million years
that he had it in him.
And ever since I found out,
I've been trying to reconcile
the man that I loved
with the monster he is now.
[sighs] Um...
I'm sorry.
Um...
Last month when...
Laurel attacked the bunker,
I had a chance to stop her.
-What?
-Yeah.
I had a gun on her,
but I couldn't pull the trigger.
Not like I did on Lian Yu.
The point being all those people that
she's been killing you told me about,
they're on me.
That's not anywhere close to true.
Why're you saying that?
I'm hoping it.
Because I had a chance to stop Vince
and I let him go too.
We're good people, Quentin.
And we see the best
in the people we care about.
And I, for one, am not ready
to believe that that's a bad thing.
Come back for Round Two?
No. No.
Back to apologize.
You said you put
my family in front of yours.
You did.
Then I asked you to put on the hood
to make things better with my son.
And I...
I didn't give
proper consideration to yours.
I'm truly sorry.
I was thinking about William today, a lot,
you getting arrested in front of him.
-How's he doing?
-Oh, he's fine.
He's a tough kid.
But he is very grateful
and thankful that you are the Green Arrow,
so I don't have to be.
Don't know how much longer
I can keep doing that.
Especially in the short term.
You get your test results back?
Yeah.
[sighs]
The nerve damage
in my arm spread to my back,
and because of the steroid use,
I caused permanent damage.
If I continue out in the field,
I could end up paralyzed.
Oh, John,
I really wish you hadn't
have gone to these lengths for me.
[exhales] Well, now it's my turn
to apologize to you.
I should have never said
that I was doing it for you.
Remember last year, when the Dominators
put us into this "alternate" Star City?
Yeah. Kind of difficult to forget.
We got to see what our
perfect life would be.
Mine was being the Green Arrow.
So you asking me to take the mantle
was not selfish,
it was giving me the one thing in
the world that I never knew I wanted.
Well...
Felicity thinks that Cayden James
is going after Starling Stadium.
It's gonna be 35,000 people there tonight.
-You're the Mayor. Shut it down.
-I tried.
Getting arrested is not doing
a lot for my credibility.
What're you gonna do?
I've been working on a probable location
for Cayden's thermobaric bomb,
but Starling Stadium, it's massive.
We'll have to split up.
Still, who's gonna be calling
the plays out there?
I vote Dinah.
She has the least field experience
of the three of us. No offense.
She has superpowers, tactical training,
and police experience.
It's all right, Felicity. It's all right.
We just cannot have a repeat
of what happened at AmerTek.
Anybody have any suggestions
on how we do that?
I have a suggestion or two.
Overwatch, we're on site.
Any luck locating the bomb?
I'm running a code to find
the building's weakest
architectural joints,
targets of opportunity. So, stand by.
And I'm still trying to get into
the venue's security system,
but Cayden has me frozen out.
-[concert audience cheering]
-[Billy Joel singing]
Couldn't we pull the alarm here
and evacuate stadium that way?
[Wild Dog] I'll do it. Can't risk the SCPD
spotting you as the Green Arrow.
I have Overwatch running
interference for me on that.
If there's a cop near you,
you'll be the first to know about it.
Still, better safe than sorry.
[Billy Joel singing "This Is The Time"]
♪ Now we're gonna get the closed circuit ♪
♪ Now we're gonna get the Top 40 ♪
The bomb is definitely down there.
I'm locking in on it.
About 400 feet up, down corridor 52.
[song continues in the distance]
[indistinct chatter]
[Wild Dog] Overwatch,
I see the fire alarm,
but I'm not gonna pull it
like I did in high school.
[fire alarm ringing]
I'm not seeing you on any security cams
near an alarm box. How did you...
A magician never reveals
his secret, hoss-ette.
False alarm, everyone. False alarm.
Go back to your seats. Everything's okay.
[Wild Dog] The cops aren't letting anyone
out these doors.
That doesn't make any sense,
they can't know it's a false alarm.
[Wild Dog] Then let's remove any doubt.
-Everybody, get the hell out of here.
-[people screaming]
The police have locked all the doors.
-Why would cops do that?
-Because they're not cops.
Put your damn hands up.
Easy, I'm just a fan in a mask.
Overwatch, what's happening?
All you need to know is that there's
no SCPD or FBI folks near you.
Just focus on the bomb. You're, like,
super close, like, 50 yards.
Guys, a little help here.
Terrific, Canary, go.
[officer] Make this easy on yourself.
[Wild Dog] It's cool, hoss.
[grunts]
[device beeping]
Overwatch, I'm at the device.
The wiring's all wrong on the thermobar.
That's not a bomb at all. That's a...
Decoy.
[officer] Get down!
[woman exclaims]
[sonic scream]
-[Mr. Terrific] You're welcome.
-[Wild Dog] She did all the work.
[Cayden] I know what you're thinking.
Where's the horrifically huge bomb?
This is going to be
an incredibly insightful evening.
Where is it?
No need to play nice.
Those jerkwads aren't cops.
[grunting]
Get those fans out of there.
Where is it?
Your generation is so impatient.
Why can't you just savor the anticipation?
There is no bomb. So, relax.
-And all of this?
-To get your attention.
To talk. That's all.
It's not like I have your number.
You're insane.
Thomas Szasz,
the renowned psychiatrist
and psychoanalyst,
says that there is no
such thing as insanity.
Revenge, on the other hand,
is very real.
Revenge?
I've never even met you.
And yet you cost me something dear to me.
Someone very dear.
My son.
That's why I've arranged
this little tête-à-tête.
So that when your city burns,
you'll know why.
[sonic scream]
We ran facial recognition
and none of those "cops"
are on the force. No surprise.
[scoffs] Fake cops,
fake uniforms, fake bomb.
That's a lot of trouble to go through
just to have a conversation
with the Green Arrow.
Now, did he really lose his son?
Alena helped connect the dots.
There is a boy named Owen Post who
has Cayden James listed as his father
on his birth certificate, but he's
never been known to live with Cayden.
Two months after A.R.G.U.S.
put Cayden into custody last year,
Owen went missing and was never found.
How does this have anything
to do with the Green Arrow?
Or any of us?
We need to keep digging, because
even if we bear zero responsibility,
we need to know why
Cayden James thinks we do.
Guys, a dude I used to code for
just blasted out this link.
It's super-trending.
Yep. Local news stations
are picking it up.
And of course, no one knows
that these cops aren't legit.
Does anyone else find this timing
just a little bit too convenient, right?
The whole city is voting on
the Anti-Vigilante Referendum today.
Guess we know which way
Cayden James wants 'em to vote.
He pulled us in to get those videos.
To sway the referendum.
That's not all he did.
The man has a real thermobaric bomb now.
Which he doesn't intend to use.
At least not yet anyway.
-Still sounds pretty dangerous.
-Yes, it does.
But it's a problem for another day.
How's the polling going?
It's gonna pass, boss.
Let's prepare a statement.
I'm right behind you.
Just need to finish up with Lance.
You know, if the bomb had been real,
we still would've stopped it
from going off.
Yeah. I know.
It's just good to have
Oliver back in the saddle.
Yeah, that and...
You and I knew where Cayden was targeting
because we worked
on the trace algorithm. Together.
'Cause we're a good team.
I'm sorry that I named the company
without consulting you.
And I'm sorry
that I picked our first project.
I'm sorry that I took the prototype
without asking you.
So, there's just one more thing
that I'm also sorry about.
What?
You know the angel investment we got?
Evening, everybody.
I think we all would like
to applaud city officials
for conducting today's vote
in such a professional manner.
I believe, in my heart, that vigilantes
have worked to make this city
a safer and better place.
I also recognize, as Mayor,
that it is my duty to honor
the will of the people.
You have spoken today
and demanded the harshest possible
penalties for anyone
caught engaging in acts of vigilantism.
Some people still believe
that includes me.
But I remain confident that
my innocence will be proven
and I will be exonerated at my trial.
Thank you very much, everyone.
[reporters clamoring]
We would've won
had it not been for the video.
You did great out there.
I feel like
I just kicked myself in the teeth.
Maybe it's because you didn't believe
a single word that you said.
Give us a minute.
I'm headed back to Washington.
Something tells me you'll be back
in time to testify at my trial.
The time of vigilantes
is coming to an end.
Because how can you idolize someone
hiding in the shadows
who won't show his face,
who refuses to own up to
his shortcomings and culpability?
That's not a hero.
That's a coward.
What does your boy think of you?
Leave my son out of this.
Doesn't matter what I do, Mr. Queen.
It matters what you do.
Are you okay, Mr. Diggle?
Well, I'm happy as hell
to be getting out of here.
-And it's John.
-[Oliver] William.
It's Mr. Diggle.
And you were the Green Arrow
for my dad. Right?
That's right, William.
But if you were here last night,
who was at the stadium?
The Green Arrow wasn't at the stadium
last night, buddy.
Just... Just his team.
Okay.
Hey, man, let's go pull
the car around here for...
-"Mr. Diggle."
-All right.
I'm sorry you had to step in.
And I'm sorry you had to lie to your son.
I don't want to lie to him.
But I can do it if it's temporary.
If I'm just, uh...
subbing in for the real Green Arrow.
-What do you mean?
-I mean as soon as you're healed up,
I want you to put that hood back on.
Oliver, I like the way that sounds.
-Makes two of us.
-[door opens]
-[John] I'm almost ready, Doc.
-Um, actually, I'm here for Mr. Queen.
It's your sister. Something's happened.
Hi, Ollie.
[sighs]
Well, that stuffing smells a whole
lot better than this cranberry jello.
William made the stuffing.
-The young man can cook.
-Yeah, just like his father.
Raisa helped me a bit.
Raisa? As in our Raisa?
[Oliver] As in our Raisa.
Yeah. I have a lot to catch you up on.
Yeah.
I will save you some stuffing for
later if you want, Auntie Thea.
I would love that.
How'd you make such a miraculous recovery?
Lazarus Pit water.
[Felicity] She's kidding.
For blast victims like Thea
in a minimally conscious state,
the trick is just to find
the right drug to literally
wake her brain up.
In this case, a new form of Zolpidem.
It's not even on the market yet.
So more like
cutting-edge neuroscience
than, I don't know, a miracle.
It seems pretty miraculous to me.
I missed you very much.
Hell of a Thanksgiving.
I've never had more to be thankful for.
Come here. You too.