Previously on Arrow...
He can't know that you're his father.
And nobody else can.
Samantha, there is someone in my life now.
Please, don't make me keep this from her.
You will if you want
a relationship with my son.
I know who Oliver Queen
cares about more than anyone.
Nora, honey,
there's someone I'd like you to meet.
This is William.
It's an implantable bio stimulant.
This little piece of technology
is gonna help me walk again?
After it's implanted in your spine. Yes.
I can do this. I can do this.
I can so totally do this.
Yes, you can.
But either way, we've got you.
There's no pressure here, Ms. Smoak.
Curtis' implant
is the longest of long shots.
I was expecting
a little more encouragement
from the husband of the genius
who invented the thing.
My man works miracles with technology,
but the human body
doesn't play by the same rules.
Well...
Here we go.
Here we're going.
Okay. It's okay.
Got you. Got you. Got you.
Here we go.
Well, that went nowhere.
- Curtis ever tell you how we met?
- Mmm-mmm.
He came in with an Achilles tendinitis.
He was training to qualify
for the Olympics,
- so all he cared about was results.
- Mmm.
Took me weeks just to get him
focused on what really mattered.
How handsome his therapist was?
Healing.
You gotta be patient with yourself.
These things take time.
Are you sure
what Conklin told you was the truth?
Conklin was dying.
He had no reason to lie.
Whatever Reiter has planned,
he is gonna kill everyone here.
Mr. Queen.
It appears we are within
striking distance of my prize.
I want you both at my side
when I claim it.
I don't give a damn
about your superstitious crusade.
Nevertheless,
you'll both bear witness to its fruition.
You Okay?
Me?
I knew you were gonna ask me,
so I thought I'd beat you to the punch.
Are you okay?
A guy, a brilliant guy,
says he can put a microchip
in my spine and I will walk again.
I'm enough of a geek to know
science fiction when I see it.
You're still disappointed.
- Yeah. You know. It's stupid.
- No.
Talk to me.
I wanted to be able to walk down the aisle
on our wedding day.
Aw, you two just melt my stone-cold heart.
You almost make me believe in love again.
Nice to see you, Mr. Queen.
How was your Christmas?
Son of a bitch.
Oh! You're so brave for a political
candidate and reformed party boy.
Oh, sorry about the limo.
Love the wheelchair.
Might I suggest motorized?
We have extremely powerful friends.
You do not know who you're messing with.
If it makes you happy,
the "messing" ends today.
I tried to bring you
into the fold, Mr. Queen.
I tried to kidnap
your nearest and dearest.
I tried to kill you,
but none of that took.
Like she said,
you don't know who you're messing with.
I suspect that is true.
But as they say... Well, or should,
the fourth time is the charm.
Go ahead. Take a look. I'll wait.
William thinks that
I'm friends with his mother.
Funny.
Anyhoo, 6:00 on Friday
you're going to hold a press conference
and drop out of the mayoral race.
Oh, that's 6:00 p.m., by the way.
I'll be at home watching you
from my brand new television.
What did he show you on your phone?
Who's William?
He's my son.
Please say something.
Look, Felicity, I can explain...
Stop.
I cannot hear another lie.
You know, it's more complicated than that.
God, Oliver,
you are the only person on the planet
that considers the truth complicated.
Just to be clear,
I don't care that you have a child.
I can't believe that you have a child
that you didn't tell me about.
What does it say about our relationship
if your first instinct
is to always hide the truth?
William's mother made a condition
that the only way I would be
allowed to meet my son
is if I agreed to keep him secret.
Even from you.
Who even makes that kind of ultimatum?
I just don't...
A mother who is trying to protect her son.
And she thought that
the best thing for him
was to keep his world separate from mine.
After everything that's happened,
can you really say that she was wrong?
Well, it didn't work, did it?
Somehow Darhk still found out.
Hey, we got your 911.
Darhk paid us a visit.
He's holding a 10-year-old boy hostage.
Says that he'll release him
if Oliver drops out of the mayoral race.
Let's get in touch with Alex.
Have him schedule a press conference
for Friday at 6:00 p.m.
You are not actually
going for this, are you?
The boy Darhk has, William...
He's my son.
Yeah, I just found out, too.
Apparently, the only two people that knew
about William were Oliver and Darhk.
Actually, I found out too.
Um, what's our next plan?
William lives in Central City, right?
Yeah.
I will call Barry.
See what the CCPD can do.
Is it okay if I tell Barry
that William is your...
Barry knows too.
Let's also get in touch with Malcolm.
He has an ax to grind after
what happened with the League, and, um...
Malcolm knows as well.
Maybe it would be easier to list the
people who don't know about your son.
- Samantha's here.
- Who's Samantha?
It's William's mother.
Alex?
She said her name was Samantha Clayton.
The name struck a bell
from the million dollar check
you told Thea
wasn't going to be a problem.
It's not going to be a problem.
Okay.
Then why did I
just get a 911 text from Thea
telling me that
you're pulling out of the race?
Have you heard from William?
Do you know where he is?
I don't, but I'm doing everything I can.
I knew it.
I knew it the second
I realized he was gone.
I knew that you had to have
some sort of involvement in this.
My God, what was I thinking
letting you get into his life?
Two months later, and he's missing.
Samantha, I need you to tell me
exactly what happened.
No, Oliver. You need to tell me
what the hell is going on
and you need to give me
my son back right now.
I'm trying, but you need to tell me
what happened, please.
I went upstairs to get him for dinner,
and he was gone.
Gone.
No... No note, no sign of struggle.
Just vanished.
I called the CCPD,
and they've been looking everywhere,
but it's already been
48 hours and still nothing.
But then a crime scene technician
pulled me aside,
and said that
I needed to talk to you about this.
Barry Allen?
Yes, that's the one.
- Oliver, you promised.
- L...
You promised me that
you wouldn't tell anyone about my son...
Barry figured it...
That's not what's important right now.
What's important is
I'm going to do everything,
and I mean absolutely everything
in my power and we will get him back!
What can you do, Oliver?
What can you do that the entire
police force hasn't been able to do?
Samantha...
I'm the Green Arrow.
This doesn't make any sense.
Well, like I said,
I'm not the person that I used to be.
Samantha, these are my friends and
they are going to help us find William.
You probably remember...
Laurel Lance?
I'm so sorry
that you're going through this, Samantha.
We will help you get William back.
Look, Laurel... It was one time.
And I knew that
you and Oliver were together,
but I was young and stupid and selfish.
And I should have been honest with you.
No. Oliver should have been.
Come on.
Does CCPD have anything?
No. it was a clean grab.
Do we have any other angles we can work?
Other than Malcolm.
Finding William isn't the problem.
Beating Damien Darhk is.
Every time we've faced him
we have been beaten, thoroughly.
It's because
we can't go against his magic.
We just need to fight harder,
we need to fight smarter.
No, Oliver.
Insanity is doing
the same thing over and over again
and expecting a different result.
We need a new strategy.
What about Constantine?
He's in hell.
Really? What's going on?
I mean, he's actually literally in hell.
Oh.
But I might know someone else.
Her name is Mari McCabe.
She possesses a totem
which is powered by magic.
She calls herself Vixen.
What the hell was that thing?
Cerico doesn't pay us enough to find out.
Come on out. Face us like a man.
I've got a better idea.
How about I kick your ass
like a woman instead?
What the hell?
- I had that under control.
- I know.
What, not enough in Star City
to keep you busy?
I need your help.
I have got to get me one of these.
- Mari.
- Laurel, hey.
- It's good to see you.
- You too.
Mari, this is John Diggle
and my sister, Thea.
Pleasure.
It's nice to meet you.
Sorry it's under
such horrible circumstances.
You spoke to Felicity on the phone.
_H€Y-_H€Y-
And this is Samantha. William's mother.
She's a friend.
A hero in Detroit they call "Vixen."
Mari and I had
an animated encounter last year
and we've stayed in touch ever since.
How are you going to help me find my son?
With magic.
- Magic?
- Yeah.
It's a long story,
but the short version is that this totem
gives me the ability to channel
the ashe or the spirit of any animal.
Do you have anything
of William's with you?
Yes, I do. Just this. It's his favorite.
Don't you dare
tell Barry about this.
He's in the city. I think I can find him.
Okay, good. Dig and I will cover you.
Laurel, get in touch with your father,
we're gonna loop in the SCPD.
Felicity, I need you to...
Would it be all right
if you sat with Samantha?
Working up a search profile. Sure.
Thank you. Thea.
Yeah, Malcolm's coming over.
I'll go talk to him.
We're going to find him.
And he's going to be okay.
Okay.
Can you feel it? The energy. Primordial.
What is that?
Destiny, Mr. Queen.
I know you're here.
There's no need to lurk in the shadows
like the boogeyman.
You haven't seen me in a while.
And I'm not the man I used to be.
Yeah, I know.
They told me.
- Not pretty, is it?
- Mmm.
It could have been a lot worse.
Could've chopped your head off.
And I would've been better off for it.
He took the League away from me
and gave it to Nyssa al Ghul.
And that was more important
than saving your daughter's life?
Yeah, heard about
that part of the story too.
Refusing to bargain with Nyssa
to save me...
My intention was to save your life
and to keep my seat of power
for the betterment of the world.
Did you tell Darhk about Ollie's son?
Do you really think
I'd do something like that...
Just answer the question.
No.
No, I won't.
Because you should know me better
than to ask me the question.
I know you all too well.
You should know one thing, Thea,
no matter what happens,
I will always love you.
It's what fathers do.
Crazy world we live in, huh?
Metahumans. Magic.
Oliver Queen, father.
- I'm sorry I didn't tell you.
- No, man, I totally get it.
Samantha put you in a tough spot.
Couldn't have been
an easy decision for you,
and I totally get why you made it.
She was right.
William was safer
when I didn't know about him.
So maybe if I never found out I...
Can't even go there, man.
You'll eat yourself up inside with the
"What if this" or the "Maybe that."
Part of being a parent.
Most important thing now is focusing
on getting your boy back home safe.
John“.
How do you do it?
I know where Sarah is every night, Oliver.
I know what she's doing. Who she's with.
She sees my face every single day
I'm there for her.
And she knows, and I know
that I would never
let anything bad happen to her.
I keep her close, man, and that's how you
keep your children safe.
He was wearing a blue hoodie,
plaid shirt, gray corduroys,
and, um, a Diamonds baseball cap.
He's a big fan.
Oliver likes baseball too.
Here's hoping that the innate
fatherly influence stops there.
Um, does he have any
distinguishing features?
Freckles, birthmarks, anything like that?
Oliver told me that
there was someone in his life.
Someone special.
And her name was Felicity.
He wanted to tell you
and I wouldn't let him.
I didn't know who he was now.
I didn't know what kind of person he was.
That's going around.
Just try and remember
that I was the one that made him choose
between you and knowing his son.
All right, I've got the whole force,
what's left of them anyway,
canvassing for William.
Thank you.
You don't seem as surprised as I expected.
What, that party boy Oliver Queen
knocked up some girl?
I'm amazed there isn't an army of
little Olivers running around out there.
Well, there may be.
He certainly got around back then.
Yeah.
You okay?
I don't know.
It's the mother, Samantha.
She was with him when I was with him.
Baby...
I don't know why it still stings.
It was a million years ago
and it's not like I didn't know
that Oliver cheated on me.
Yeah, but that's one thing.
Knowing he had a kid...
I'm sorry, sweetheart.
- Come here.
- Thank you.
It's Oliver.
He knows where William's being held.
I count four guards patrolling the roof.
Mari's in position.
I wondered how long it would take for
your buddy Oliver to drag you into this.
- Where is the boy?
- Oh, he's fine.
I had him moved about two minutes
before you and your posse
disturbed my evening in.
You know what?
You might wanna learn
to be a little bit more discreet.
Have you considered black
instead of green?
- You tell me where you've taken him.
- Or what?
You'll fire an arrow at me?
I think we've seen that movie before.
Iwin. You lose. Rinse, repeat.
This time's different.
Oh, really?
Where's the boy?
You have some
very interesting friends.
Atta boy.
My, mY-
I haven't seen that trinket
in a dog's age.
M'Changa province, am I right?
(Sta)'-
Oh, I like you.
And I don't like many people.
I QOt you.
What happened? Where did he go?
- I can't track him.
- Darhk's protected by magic.
No, not just Darhk.
I lost William.
Where's William? What happened?
We had a small setback,
but we're not giving up.
"Setback"? What do you mean?
Hey, blocked ID.
Hello.
Oh, hi, Oliver.
How's your evening going?
Mine, somewhat eventful.
Some of your friends stopped by
my place earlier, completely unannounced.
Very rude.
I wanna talk to my son, Darhk.
I wanna know that he's safe.
Oh, this must be the first time
your son's been kidnapped
'cause clearly you don't understand
how these things work.
I make the demands.
Well, you've made them and I've agreed.
Friday night I'm dropping out of the race.
Why wait?
Give your green friend
less time to botch things up.
So, go find yourself a television camera.
I wanna know that my son is safe!
Oh, and by the way, you're going to
completely endorse Ruvé Adams.
Save us all the trouble of those
pesky little write-in ballots.
He moved up the timetable.
He wants me to drop
out of the race tonight.
Thea, let Alex know.
I am so sorry.
I know you brought me here
to fight magic with magic, but I...
Mari, this isn't on you.
There's still so much
that we don't know about Darhk's power.
We don't... We don't even know
what the source of it is.
Wait.
I get my powers from this necklace.
Without it,
I'm just a wannabe fashion designer
who lives at home with her foster dad.
So up to now, everyone I've gone up
against with mystical powers
has had some sort of a totem like mine.
What if Darhk has an object
that helps him with his magic?
I think he does.
I walked in on him once or twice
in front of this cabinet thing.
And inside there is some kind of,
I don't know, idol.
Can you draw it for me?
Well, yeah, I'll give it a whirl.
Okay, Oliver, what if this little
art project doesn't yield any results?
- Well...
- And what if it takes too long?
Mari and Captain Lance are working
on a way to eventually stop Darhk.
Right now, I have to save William.
What's he saying?
Whatever it is, it's not good.
We have to get out of here now.
Reiter, what are you doing?
Proving what I know about you is true.
You can't leave us in here with it!
Reiter!
You...
You are worthy to pass.
Good evening.
Thank you for coming on such short notice.
When I entered this race,
it was because no one else
was willing to step into the spotlight.
It has always been my hope
that my actions would inspire others.
Four months later and they have.
Knowing that, effective immediately,
I will be suspending my campaign
and throwing my full support
behind Ruvé Adams.
Now, I'd like to take a moment
to thank all my supporters
for all of your hard work.
What you've done will not be forgotten.
Thank you.
New numbers are out.
You were leading by 16 points.
Alex, I'm sorry.
I know that you put your heart and soul
into this campaign and...
And your days of speech-making
are now behind you.
Look, man. I don't want "sorry."
I just want an explanation.
That's why I'm sorry.
Sucks when you can't tell the truth.
Samantha told me about her ultimatum.
I just figured
that eventually she'd trust me.
Yeah, you'd work your Oliver Queen charm.
I didn't wanna be a part of William's life
without the opportunity for you
to be a part of his life.
John's made it pretty clear
that, uh, I should've made more of an
effort to be a part of William's life.
And that the best way to keep him safe
would've been to keep him close.
Even with all of this.
Your resignation's all over the news.
Have you heard from Darhk?
Not yet.
Speak of the devil. Literally.
It's not Darhk. It's Mari.
She has something.
I emailed Captain Lance's
drawing of Darhk's idol
to a friend of mine at Detroit University.
And did he recognize it?
It's a Khushu idol.
Very rare. Very powerful.
But its power
requires a constant connection
to one of the Earth's ley lines.
- I never thought I'd say this, but huh?
- Okay.
Think Wi-Fi for magic.
And the idol is his Internet connection.
If Professor Macalester's theory
is correct, and this map is accurate...
Then Darhk must be holed up
near one of these ley lines
in order for him to get
the strongest signal.
I'll start cross-referencing all the
locations that we've encountered Darhk.
You pulled out of the race.
Why isn't this man giving me my son back?
He will and everything will be fine.
You keep saying that,
but it hasn't been yet.
You're doing everything you possibly can.
You can't beat yourself up about it.
Well, you don't know me very well, do you?
Just before Christmas, Darhk took
Thea, Felicity, John, held them captive.
We agreed that
I would trade myself for them,
I did,
and Darhk did not live up
to his end of the bargain.
So you're worried
that's playing itself out again now?
We're going to get William back, Oliver.
But when we do,
I think you should consider that...
Maybe letting him go
isn't such a bad thing.
What do you mean?
Well, I heard what you told Felicity
about keeping him close.
Owl ears.
Uh, I never knew my real parents.
I grew up in a foster home
and my whole life I wondered, "Who am I?"
"Where did I come from?
Why didn't my real parents want me?"
A boy should know who his father is.
He should. And he will.
But knowing what William
is going through right now
I realize that
I wasn't ready for the answers.
Learning about my heritage, my powers,
the evil my mother fled our homeland
to protect me from,
no child should have to carry that burden.
I mean, look around you, Oliver.
The best gift
you can give him is his childhood.
Keep him as far away from your world
for as long as possible.
I can't imagine a greater sacrifice.
Isn't that what parenthood is?
Hey, guys. I think we found something.
Darhk moves his idol around,
which makes sense but...
It makes him a whole lot harder to track.
Right, but after referencing
a buttload of satellite feed,
thermal imaging data in the ley line map,
I think Darhk's located out
in a compound in Sky Woods.
Hello?
Very good speech.
You look great on television.
Nelson Plaza. Three hours.
William will be there.
Darhk says he's going to release William
three hours from now at Nelson Plaza.
There is no guarantee with Darhk.
This could be a trap.
And now we have a chance
to take out his power idol thingy.
Ollie, without his magic, he won't be able
to do this to anybody ever again.
It will be game over.
Samantha, he's your son. it is your call.
He's your son too, Oliver.
Get him back.
And take this son of a bitch Darhk out.
I count 17 Ghosts.
Copy. Black Canary?
Ready.
- Spartan?
- I'm set.
Let's do this.
Vixen, you're up.
I'm guessing
your insurance won't pay for that.
Cute. Buh-bye.
When you're dead, I'll make sure
that totem gets put to better use.
Took the words right out of my mouth.
Well, that happened.
Speedy, Canary, I can't get a clear shot.
Where are you?
On our way.
Find William. I'll take care of Darhk.
I'm sorry. I can't hear you
with your throats closing up like that.
Steady.
I've got the totem.
Has it had any effect?
Separating it from Darhk
didn't do anything.
Go to plan B.
What's plan B?
Please don't hurt them.
William.
Get out of here.
- Mom.
- William.
Hi.
Medics checked him out.
He's in perfect health.
Oh, thank goodness.
There's someone here
that you must have missed.
What's wrong?
I'm kind of over The Flash.
I want a Green Arrow action figure.
Well, the Green Arrow is pretty amazing.
I will let you guys get reacquainted.
Hey-
ls everything okay?
Detectives questioned William
while the docs were checking him out.
Darhk didn't take him.
It was a guy with a missing hand.
You son of a bitch.
I assure you, Mr. Queen,
I had all the faith in the world
that you would survive.
Yeah? But what about everybody else?
You are my only concern.
We've gotten this far because of you.
Let's finish it.
You too, Ms. Venediktov.
Mr. Queen seems to behave at his best
when you are around.
- Is William gonna be okay?
- Yeah.
He's a tough one.
Just like his dad.
Could not have done this without you.
Thank you.
Anytime.
Have you thought any more
about what I said?
You know, I just got him back.
Let me just say,
for all the frustrations I have
about my real parents giving me up,
I am so grateful
I was raised in a situation
where that was my biggest issue in life.
The best thing my parents
ever gave me was that freedom.
Well, that, and this totem
that makes me a total badass.
You don't need a totem for that.
Damn right, I don't.
Take care of yourself, Oliver.
I'm just a phone call away.
Me too, Mari. Me too.
I heard you found the boy.
You can't believe how relieved I...
- Cut the crap.
- Excuse me?
I know it was you.
You took him. Out of spite.
For us.
You have to believe me. I did it for us.
You purposely...
You put him in danger. How...
You know what?
I'm not doing this anymore.
This song and dance
where you come over to my apartment
and you whisper your lies...
It is over.
- Thea, I did it to protect us.
- Shut up.
How could you possibly think
that there was an "us" to protect?
You know, sometimes I lay awake at night
and I wonder what Robert
would think about our relationship.
He raised me. He loved me.
And I threw that all away
the moment I became your daughter.
Yes. Yes, you did. And it was your choice.
And lwish I never did.
Don't you dare speak to me like that.
You would be dead 10 times over
if not for me.
I taught you how to fight.
How to be strong.
I turned you from
a delicate, spoiled brat into a warrior.
And all I've ever gotten from you
in return is your venomous spite.
For a very good reason.
You have no idea what you are up against.
You are incapable
of seeing the bigger picture,
butlcan.
And I would rather
you hate me and be alive,
than love me and be dead.
Hi, William.
I hope you're well.
And I hope you're safe.
There is something that I wanna tell you.
I wanted to tell you before, but...
But this is better.
I'm your father. Biologically, that is.
As far as really being your father goes,
I haven't earned that yet.
A father should be there for his child,
every day, no matter what.
To make sure that they feel loved,
that they feel safe.
And a child should be able
to rely on their father
and go to him for
guidance and reassurance.
I have failed to do that for you.
And now, I'm gonna tell you why.
I'm the Green Arrow.
And my life is very dangerous.
Which is why
we decided to keep you out of it
for all of these years.
What happened to you in Star City,
that was my fault.
And I can't allow anything like that
to happen ever again.
That's why I have asked your mother
to move you far away,
and to not tell anyone
where she's taking you.
Including me.
That's also why I asked her to wait
to show you this message
until after your 18th birthday.
I wanted to give you a real childhood.
I wanted to give you that gift.
Goodbye, son.
I sure hope it's not forever.
How much of that did you hear?
Enough.
Oliver, we need to talk.
About a number of things, I suspect.
Let's start with...
I can't do this.
When your son was in danger,
I had to table
what I was feeling about everything.
But now that I've had some space,
I realize I need space.
Felicity.
I know the position Samantha put you in.
I know it was an impossible decision.
But you were right,
you should have told me.
Marriage is about inclusion.
It's about
leaning on your partner
when things get complicated.
I don't think that
you know how to do that.
I'm trying.
And now you're sending William away
and I understand why.
You know that I do,
but once again,
you have left me out of the decision.
Felicity?
- Oh, my God.
English - SDH