Previously, on "Arrow"...
Twitch, and I will
open your throat.
Slade Wilson.
Oliver Queen.
Let me show you
how I'm going to die.
There might be a fighter
inside of you after all.
Sorry.
For what?
For not telling you
how I really feel.
Time to choose, Oliver,
who lives and who dies.
No! No!
No!
Whoever did this to her
is going to suffer.
You cannot die
until you have known...
Complete despair.
And you will.
I promise.
A new player
we've been tracking.
We've been calling him
Deathstroke.
Slade's goal is to create
in the Mirakuru.
I can't stop him
from doing anything.
Five years ago,
I made you a promise.
I'm here to fulfill it.
There is still one person
who has to die
before this can end.
Oliver.
Oliver, man, you ok?
The cure's not working.
We don't know that.
He still has a lot of Tibetan pit viper
venom in his system.
What's that?
Proximity alarm.
I rigged the tower
with sensors
just in case Slade's
goons came here to kill us.
Slade's goons
are here to kill us.
Talk to me, Felicity.
They're inside,
they're right
underneath us.
Where am I?
They're inside, there's
too many of them!
Felicity!
Down the cable!
♪ Arrow 2x28 ♪
Unthinkable
Original Air Date on May 14, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Oh, my God!
What the hell
happened?
Slade's army. You were right about
this place being compromised.
Lyla, your boss is going to bomb
the city at dawn.
Yeah, Waller's never
seen a problem she didn't think
couldn't be solved
with a drone strike.
Why do you think I'm here?
You knew Waller was
looking to level the city and you
came here anyway?
You're here.
You need to go back
to A.R.G.U.S.
You need to stop Waller
or buy us enough time to stop Slade.
Not without me.
Till death do us part, right?
This time it might.
Guys? I need you to scrounge
as many weapons as you can find,
especially
injection arrows.
We're going to fill them with the cure--
which clearly works--
and this ends tonight,
without killing.
There's been enough
death already.
No!
Thea.
It's called Kevlar.
If you're going
to kill me, just...
Get it over with.
Kill you? Why?
Because you shot me?
I'm glad you did.
You're sick.
Perhaps.
How else to explain
the fact that not a year ago,
your brother held a gun to
my face as well.
Tommy?
He lacked conviction.
The strength to pull the trigger,
but not you, Thea.
You are made of iron.
You are truly my daughter,
and I could not
be more proud.
Remember your training.
You be smart,
you take clean shots,
and you don't miss the--
Fall
back to Meltzer Avenue.
We need SWAT at Union Plaza.
City hall's a crater.
They're--they're everywhere!
Fall back,
fall back, I'm hit!
Ok, listen,
I know you're scared.
You wouldn't be human
if you weren't.
But tonight,
this city, our city...
It's counting on each
and every one of you.
So you go out there
and you be the heroes
I know you all to be.
Go.
Where's your sister?
I don't know.
Detective.
I've got one-P-P
on the line.
Lieutenant Pike in the field,
you're the ranking officer.
You should go.
I'll find Sara.
Listen, I don't want you stepping foot
outside this precinct, you hear me?
I won't. I promise.
All right, sweetheart.
What do we got?
My sister can't be
a part of this.
I don't want her getting hurt.
Sara!
What's going on?
Laurel...
Well, it seems like
I missed a lot.
Well, what do you remember?
Leaving town
and heading to Blüdhaven.
Was I out cold
the whole time?
Felicity.
You were out.
The whole time.
Slade has at least 50 or
so of those human weapons.
We'll need a whole army if we plan
on hitting 'em with the cure.
I know.
Which is why an army
is what I've brought.
Gee, Sara, you could have
called before you invited...
5, 6, 7 assassins down
into our top secret lair.
What is she
doing here?
I asked her to come.
I'm Nyssa,
daughter of Ra's al Ghul.
Heir to the demon.
Felicity Smoak.
MIT class of '09.
This is where you
went? Nanda Parbat?
The League of Assassins?
These people are mercenaries, Sara.
Whatever they promised you,
it comes at a price.
You don't have to worry about it,
because I've already paid it.
You agreed
to go back.
Look, I'm not going to let Slade Wilson
hurt Laurel or my father.
And I'm willing to do
whatever it takes
to keep the ones
that I love safe,
and I hope you're ready
to do the same.
Especially after what happened.
Ollie, I'm sorry
about your mother.
I am willing to do
whatever it takes,
but that doesn't mean
cold-blooded killing
is the answer, Sara.
We have the cure now.
To fight the unthinkable,
you have to be willing
to do the unthinkable.
You may not want
my help, Mr. Queen,
but there's little question you are in
desperate need of it.
First we need to find
Slade's base of operations.
Slade Wilson
and Isabel Rochev are using
your former office
building as their base of operations.
How are you feeling?
Ready to serve up
some payback.
Then remember your training.
Remember everything
that you've learned.
Are--are you
for real?
Someone--a friend--
once told me that if you
survive a crucible,
you grow the stronger for it.
This is to remind you of that.
What happened to
Thea? Is she...Ok?
She's fine. She was
headed out of the city
before this started.
We do this my way.
The league does not
take prisoners.
It does tonight.
Thea, it's dangerous
out there.
Better than here
with my psycho-villain dad,
who's happy
I tried to kill him.
Roy?
Thea, it's--
it's me.
I just wanted to make sure
you were all right.
I'm fine.
I'm at the train station.
Thea, listen to me.
You're not safe there. Can you
please meet me at my place?
I'll be there.
Soon as I can.
Ok, be safe.
Who was that?
Roy?
You're my daughter. There's not
much I don't know about you.
Interesting how
you run back to him
after resolving to run away to
escape all the lies
and half-truths.
He's no different, Thea.
No different from
your mother or Oliver.
If you don't
believe me,
then you should
go to him.
I will.
And if you try to follow me,
I'll shoot you again.
When you need me,
I'll be there.
Elevator bank's clear.
Conference room's clear.
You must have
quite a bit
of faith in this cure
if you've come alone.
We didn't come alone.
Sara, don't!
Kill me.
Don't kill me.
It doesn't matter.
I beat you.
I took away the one--
Your reticence to do
what is necessary
is why your city burns.
This isn't working.
I can't get close enough to Slade to
hit him with the cure.
So what do we do?
Another
disappointment!
Bring me another!
Come on, Slade,
what are you doing?!
Advancing
the cause of science.
Wait, no, no, wait,
I know you blame me for Shado's death!
I blame myself!
He should!
It's his fault
we aren't together.
You said once
that we were brothers.
And right now,
I am begging you,
brother to brother,
just listen to me!
Don't listen to him!
All his words are lies.
I wouldn't be alive
right now if it wasn't for you.
I would be alive
if it wasn't for him.
Think about Shado!
She--she cared
for both of us.
She wouldn't
want this.
She wants us
off Lian Yu.
She'd want all
of this to end!
He's right!
This needs to end.
You need to kill him.
Two hours now.
Prosti menya, moy drug.
I'm sorry, Oliver.
Do it.
Slade, no!
Pull the trigger!
Slade!
Laurel! Laurel!
Sweetheart, sweetheart!
What--what happened?!
Sara!
She's gone, sweetie.
Oh, my God.
You ok?
She's with that woman!
The woman that took mom.
Please, no!
Stay right here.
Stop right there!
Don't take one more step.
One more step!
Slade Wilson
wants to see you.
No, no!
Drone's locked
on target.
Starling City.
Why does this
Wilson guy have such
a mad-on for the Queens?
I don't know.
Good thing Thea and Oliver got
out of town in time.
So they have to go
after my family?
What's she doing here?
She's here to help.
Just trust me,
please.
I guess today I'll have
to work with anybody
who can help get
my daughter back.
What?
One of these masked guys,
they took Laurel.
I--I couldn't stop them.
Believe me,
I-- I tried.
Oh, we have a new,
big problem.
Which, considering our other ones,
is really saying something.
I hacked a satellite and tasked it for
thermographic imaging--
all of Slade's men are gathering at
the Giordano Tunnel.
I thought these guys were trying
to destroy the city, not escape it.
A.R.G.U.S. is going
to level the city
to stop them
from getting out.
That's what Slade's planning on.
He knows Waller's tactics.
Fortunately,
with Slade's men
attempting to leave
via the tunnel,
all our targets will be grouped
in a single place.
We need to take it.
Gather your men.
What about Laurel?
Wilson took her for a reason.
I know what it is.
But the city
comes first.
This is my daughter.
This is your sister!
You can't just
leave her like this!
Look, I know you said
you were trying another
way, and I respect that.
But Slade Wilson? His men?
They're monsters.
And monsters, they need
to be destroyed.
You've killed
before.
Tonight, I suggest
you get back in the habit.
He's wrong.
He's right.
I've lost everything
because I'm fighting Slade Wilson
with one hand tied
behind my back.
The man murdered
my mother.
I have to kill him.
You told me you had
a choice.
That years ago, you could
have cured Slade
but you chose to kill him instead.
This isn't happening because
you're not willing to be a killer;
it's happening
because you were one.
You're right. That's
how this started.
It's how it has to end.
The only move that
he has left for me is to kill him.
I can't cure him,
I can't capture him,
I can't even
out-think him!
Then don't. Don't...
Just make him out-think you.
Residents are being urged
to stay in their homes
amidst unconfirmed rumors that
mayor Blood is among the casualties
as masked men
terrorize the city...
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry
for everything.
I...
No, it's ok.
I know--I know that
I haven't exactly
been myself
for the past few months.
I was injected with...
With some drug. I know.
Sin told me.
But are you ok now?
Yeah, I'm fine.
I woke up here. I lost
a lot of time, but...
And what about the Arrow?
He said he was going
to take care of you?
I don't know anything
about the Arrow.
I'm done with all
of that, but I...
You're the only person that I've
ever cared about.
Are you okay?
Did something happen to you?
It doesn't matter.
Look, let's just--
let's just get out of here.
Let's start over.
We can be whoever we want to
without anyone
getting in our way.
I'm never
losing you again.
Yeah, there's just--
there's just one thing
I need to take care of
before we go, ok?
So just stay here
and get some stuff
packed and I'll be right back.
No, Roy, it's dangerous.
I know.
But I have to do this.
I wouldn't feel
right if I left without trying.
Do you trust me?
Yes.
Then when I get back, we're getting
out of here forever.
I love you.
Oliver.
What are we doing here?
The whole city's falling apart.
I know.
You need
to stay here.
What?!
Why? You can't just ask me to--
I'm not asking.
I will come and get you when
this is all over.
No!
Felicity...
No! Not unless you tell me why.
Because I need you
to be safe.
Well, I don't want to be safe.
I want to be with you.
And the others, unsafe!
I can't let
that happen.
Oliver.
You're not making any sense.
Slade took Laurel because he
wants to kill the woman I love.
I know, so?
So he took
the wrong woman.
Oh...
I love you.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Johnny.
Yeah?
Never mind.
Hey, Lyla.
I love you.
You know that, right?
I do, actually.
But it's good
to hear it.
Time to impact?
Drone is 52 minutes
out from target.
Get me sergeant Gomez
at the Giordano Tunnel.
Easy company's not
responding, ma'am.
I need a visual.
They're in a tunnel,
ma'am, I can't get a picture.
What the hell is going on
in that tunnel?
Sergeant Gomez,
come in! Sergeant Gomez!
No kill shots.
Let the cure do its work.
Ready?
Ready?!
Ready, fire!
Agent Michaels, this area's restricted
to all unauthorized--
What the hell is this?
Early parole?
Waller's looking
to bomb Starling City.
We need your help
to stop her.
As much as I'd love to show
the Wall what we think of her,
there's just that little matter
of tick, tick, boom!
Ok? We've got all that
miniature bombs in our spines.
You have
to trust me.
And Lawton,
no dropping bodies.
Yeah, sure, take
the fun out of it.
Nyssa!
Get off the ship!
Not without you!
Give it to me!
Give me the Mirakuru!
No!
Ollie!
Sara!
Prep the drone to fire.
Weapons hot was set
for oh-six hundred.
Prep the drone to fire!
Down, now!
Everybody get
down, down, down!
Waller, call that drone off!
This is treason,
agent Michaels.
Treason that risks hundreds of
thousands of lives.
Have you thought
about that?
about how
you're going
to explain that to your son?
Or is it
your daughter?
Did doctors specify,
or did you want to
keep it a surprise?
Congratulations, Mr. Diggle,
you're going to be a father.
Go!
You've
been busy, kid.
It's over, Slade!
Your army is broken.
And I pity them.
But once again,
you miss the point.
I have the one you love.
You're going
to meet me where I say.
Otherwise,
I'm going to kill her.
No, you do what you have to.
I'm done playing your games!
You're done when
I say you're done!
I was surprised.
I thought you had a thing
for stronger women,
but now that I've met her...
I can see the appeal.
She is quite lovely...
Your Felicity.
Twitch, and I will
open your throat.
My first words to you.
Do you remember? I do.
I remember the exact moment.
My blade against your neck.
Just like my blade is against
the neck of your beloved.
If only I'd killed you then,
everything
would be different.
Drop the bow, kid.
Do it.
Yes.
Countless nights dreaming
of taking from you
all that you took from me.
By killing the woman I love?
Yes.
Like you love Shado.
You see her.
Don't you?
Well, what does she look like
in your madness, Slade?
What does she say to you?
I remember her being beautiful.
Young. Kind.
She would be horrified
by what you've done
in her name.
What I have done?
What I have done
is what you lack
the courage to do!
To fight for her!
So...
When her body
lies at your feet,
her blood wet
against your skin,
then you will know
how I feel!
I already know how you feel.
I know what it's like to hate.
To want revenge.
And now I know how it feels
to see my enemy
so distracted,
he doesn't see the real danger
is right in front of him.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Kill her!
Get them out of here!
Poor Sara.
How many times
you going to watch her die?
You can't kill me.
The Mirakuru isn't
what made me hate you!
The end is near.
But maybe
I'll be merciful enough
to let you live
and see your city burn!
We both know
there's only one way
that this can end.
To beat me, kid,
you're going
to have to kill me.
But in the moment
of my death,
you'll prove one thing--
that you are
a murderer.
What are you going
to do, kid?
Stick me with the cure?
It doesn't matter.
I'll keep my promise!
I'll take away everything
and everyone you love!
Sara was only the first!
She was only the first!
Your sister,
Laurel, your mother!
You can kill me,
or not.
Either way, I win.
Amanda, it's over.
Slade's down,
his army's been taken out.
Call back the drones.
Amanda, it's over!
So what now, kid?
It's time.
Why--why are they
making you do this?
Why are you making her do
this, huh? Why?
Dad, she's not
making me do anything.
I chose this.
What am I going to
tell your mother?
Tell her that for the first time
in my life,
I'm deciding my own fate.
She'll understand that.
Yeah.
I love you,
sweetheart.
I love you, too, Dad.
I know the power
of a father's love,
and I would die before
I let anything happen to your daughter.
Well, here's hoping.
So, where
you're going,
will you be able
to email or call?
I'll see you again.
I know.
If there's anything that
I've learned this year,
it's that you always
find your way home.
And we'll always
be here waiting.
I love you.
Oliver needs you.
And, hey...
I think that this would
look good on you.
It fits.
Bye, Dad.
Bye, sweetheart.
About that jacket...
Don't get any ideas.
I could really use a meeting.
Yeah, probably a good
idea for the both of us.
Listen, I got to pick up
a little pepto on the way, though,
'cause I'm feeling
kind of weird.
Dad, she'll be ok.
Yeah, I know she'll be ok,
but ok what is what bothers me.
Dad?
Dad!
Oh, my God. Dad!
Oh, my God!
I can't get
my breath!
I can't...
Dad, stay with me!
Daddy, daddy, stay with me!
Hello?!
I need an ambulance.
My father's with SCPD. Yes, now!
Daddy, stay with me!
Thea.
Thea!
Roy...I'm sorry.
I made a mistake.
I thought I could
still be with you.
still be Thea Queen.
But Thea Queen was trusting.
And I don't trust you.
Or anyone. Not anymore.
Thea Queen was also weak.
And no matter what it takes,
I will be strong.
Don't try to find me.
You won't.
Even I don't know
where I'm going.
I only know one thing--
I am never coming back.
Where am I?
As far away from the world
as I could get you.
Where you can't hurt
anyone ever again.
That's your
weakness, kid.
You don't have
the guts to kill me.
No. I have the strength
to let you live.
Oh, you're a killer.
I know, I created you.
You've killed plenty.
Yes, I have.
You helped turn me
into a killer when I needed to be one.
And I'm alive today
because of you.
I made it home because of you.
And I got to see
my family again.
But over the past year,
I've needed to be more...
And I faltered.
But then I stopped you.
Without killing.
You helped me become
a hero, Slade.
Thank you.
You think I won't
get out of here?
kill those you care for?
No, I don't.
Because you're in purgatory.
I keep my promises, kid.
I keep my promises!
I keep my promises.
Last time I didn't notice;
It's actually kind of beautiful here.
Don't get me wrong,
I'm counting down the seconds
until we shove off
minefield island.
So you think
that'll be enough to hold him,
A.R.G.U.S.'
super Max?
Him, and anyone else
we send here.
This battle may be over,
but there will be others.
Starting with getting
my family's company back.
That's not going to be easy,
since you're poor now.
You're going to have
to get a job.
If Slade doesn't
scare you, that's got to.
Do you know anyone hiring
ex-billionaires
with superior archery skills?
Hey, why
don't I, uh,
give you two
a second?
Well, you did it.
I had help.
Yeah.
That's really smart.
How you out-foxed him.
Talk about unthinkable.
You and me, I mean.
When you told me
you loved me,
you had me fooled.
For a second,
I...
Maybe you might have meant it.
What you said.
You really sold it.
We both did.
Let's go home.
Dig, what was the news
about you and Lyla?
It can wait.
I'm flying.
Be my guest.
I got one more
question!
Wouldn't be you if you didn't.
If you spent
five years on this island,
when did you
learn how to fly a plane?
Gun ngo lei.
My name is Amanda
Waller, Mr. Queen.
We have a lot
to discuss.
Welcome to Hong Kong.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man