My name is Oliver Queen.
After five years
on a hellish island,
I have come home
with only one goal--
to save my city.
But to do so, I can't be
the killer I once was.
To honor my friend's memory,
I must be someone else.
I must be something else.
Previously on "Arrow"...
Blood's trounced every potential
candidate we've focus-tested.
You want me to run
against Sebastian Blood?
The child of Ra's al Ghul
awaits your return.
Tell Ra's al Ghul
that my family is off limits!
You've got to come back home.
I can't!
If they knew I was alive,
Laurel and mom,
they would never
stop looking for me,
and that could
get them both killed.
Thea Queen, telling me
enough is enough.
Now, that is rich.
Sara?
Welcome to
Starling City International Airport.
Please have
your passports ready,
and your customs forms
filled out.
All passengers
with departing flights
will need to show
appropriate identification
and declaration papers.
International passengers
are required to have a passport
and an airline
boarding pass to travel.
Business or personal,
Miss Raatko?
Personal.
All passengers are required
to pick up their luggage
in the baggage claim area
of the international
arrivals and safety.
My computer's froze.
Can you hold on a sec?
I'll be right back.
Down on the ground,
down, down!
Put your hands on your head!
I said, hands on your head,
lady. I will shoot you.
Aaah!
Welcome to Starling City.
♪ Arrow 2x13 ♪
Tremors
Original Air Date on February 5, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
A successful mayoral campaign
isn't about polling,
it isn't about fundraising
or hot button issues.
It's about connecting
with people.
That's why right after
we announce tomorrow, Moira,
I want to get you in front
of as many cameras as possible.
Morning shows,
talk shows--
Mark, I want to help
rebuild the city,
not pander to it.
It's not pandering,
Mom. It's campaigning.
Let the people get
to know the real Moira Queen,
and they are going to fall
in love with you.
Speaking from
experience,
this man knows what he's
talking about, Moira.
Hmm.
Mr. Steel?
May I talk to you
about something?
I'm no longer
your boss, Felicity.
So let's make it
Walter from now on.
- Ok.
- Walter.
It's about Tempest.
Mrs. Queen's
super sketchy offshore LLC
you asked me
to look into last year.
I remember.
That's right.
So, the thing is, I left
an embedded account alert on it
so we'd know if anyone
ever accessed it again.
A few days ago, there was
a wire transfer made
from Tempest to a numbered account
at Starling National Bank.
Probably the campaign accountant
shutting it down.
Or it could be something else.
That is the money Mrs. Queen
used to do some really bad things.
I mean, you guys did get divorced
for pretty good reasons.
Which is not my business.
I'll talk to Moira
first thing.
And thank you
for bringing it to my attention.
Of course.
Well...
We're starting a campaign.
Oliver, can I have a word?
Yes.
I know that you
and he are friends,
but you'll need to end your support
for Sebastian Blood.
I will speak to Sebastian.
Good.
Hello?
I'll be right there.
Oliver.
Mrs. Lance.
I came back
as soon as I heard.
Thanks for coming.
Hey.
How you feeling?
I've been better.
Don't worry, baby.
We're going to get you
all the help you need.
There's a great rehab
outside of Starling,
they got a bed
waiting for you--
Dad, I already told you.
I didn't OD.
I didn't take
any pills last night.
I swear.
Laurel...
The doctor wants
to check your eye.
What happened
to her eye?
Minor subconjunctival
hemorrhaging.
Probably
from hitting her head
when she lost
consciousness.
You feel better, ok?
Thank you.
We'll be outside.
Let's go.
Dad.
What is it,
sweetheart?
Before I passed out...
The strangest thing happened.
I saw Sara.
I mean, I know I was
hallucinating, but I saw her.
She was standing
right over me.
I mean, I've dreamt
about her over the years,
but this was so much more real.
That's crazy, right?
Yeah, it's crazy.
She's been doing that
for like an hour.
You saw Laurel.
Is she going to be ok?
You saved her life.
Hey, thanks for calling me.
And I never did ask you--
how did you find me?
I wasn't going
to lose you again.
I should get going.
Hey, so that's it?
You're back in town
for 24 hours,
now you're
just going to take off again?
The League of Assassins
is still after me, Ollie,
and staying in town would
put my whole family at risk.
I only came because
Laurel's in trouble.
Well, she's still
in trouble, Sara.
Your entire family needs you.
So do I.
Do me a favor and dig up
a copy of Laurel's bloodwork
from the hospital, please.
Sure. What are we looking for?
I just want to make
sure of something.
It's for you.
Hello, Detective.
Put my daughter on.
I know she's there.
Hilton, tell the Lieutenant
that the perp
was practically
lawyering up
when I read him
his Miranda.
If we don't get on top
of this situation,
the Lieutenant is not
going to be happy--
Oh, it smells amazing, Dad.
Ahh, yeah.
Here, try one of these.
Ok.
Beautiful. No,
I'm talking to Laurel.
Quentin, hang up the phone.
Spend time with your family!
Oh, my family. You heard that,
I got to go. Bye, buddy.
Sorry, ladies. Our do-er hired
some dirtbag lawyer, and--
Says the dad whose daughter
just applied to law school.
That is not the kind of lawyer
that you're going to be, young lady,
because you,
you're going to be a judge
or you're going to be a professor,
just like your mother.
Yeah, come over to academia.
The fun never ends.
Dinner is at
a crucial point.
- Ahem!
- Hey!
Hi!
Sar-bear!
Hey!
Hi!
Hi.
Sara, what a surprise.
Hi, mom.
Please don't tell me
you got kicked out of college.
Oh, well, thank you for
the vote of confidence.
I had a three day weekend,
so I figured I'd drive down
and surprise everybody.
Well, you're just
in time to eat. Come here.
Get yourself another
plate. Come on.
Here you go.
Hi, Dad.
Come here.
I only have a minute.
Well, a cup of tea
is all I ask.
Sit down.
Oh, baby.
I have missed you so much.
How's Laurel?
She saw you.
Right before she passed out.
She thought it was,
I don't know what.
A hallucination.
Well, good.
No, baby, you don't understand.
Seeing you, it made her happy.
Dad...The league,
they're still hunting me.
So what, you're just going to pop back
every time one of us is in trouble?
We can't live like this,
Sara, and you can't.
It's time we started
facing things together.
I've had better greetings.
I'm sorry, I did--
I just--I didn't know
what you were
going to do.
To be honest, neither did I.
We should talk.
Of course.
Do we need permission
from your boyfriend?
I am Nyssa.
Daughter of Ra's al Ghul.
Heir to the demon.
What are you doing here?
Sara swore her allegiance
to the League of Assassins.
It's time for her
to return home.
That...is not going to happen.
Nyssa...
Please, would you
give us a moment?
Take your time.
Good-byes
are never easy.
Is that why
I didn't get one?
I can explain.
You don't have to.
But you're not leaving.
I don't trust her.
Then trust me.
Mrs. Queen?
Hmm?
A Miss Smoak
is here to see you.
Who?
Uh, me.
If you're looking for
Oliver, he's not here.
I know. I'm to see you.
Really? What about?
Tempest.
I flagged a large
wire transfer you made.
When I mentioned it to Walter,
he said he would
talk to you about it.
I could tell in his face
he wouldn't.
British people
are really bad liars.
Yes, they are.
So I looked into it myself,
because--full disclosure--
I--I don't trust you.
You paid a substantial
sum of money to a Dr. Gill.
He was the doctor
who delivered Thea,
which didn't make any sense to me.
So I went through
like a dozen different theories
until I remembered...
Your testimony. At trial.
You had an affair
with Malcolm Merlyn
one year before Thea was born.
Merlyn is Thea's father.
I can see why Walter and Oliver
have such a high appraisal
of your capabilities.
So.
What are you going to do
with this information?
Felicity.
I don't know.
Confronting you
in your living room
was as far
as my plan went.
I thought you
deserved the chance
to tell Oliver yourself. He should
hear it from you.
I'm not going to tell
my son anything.
And neither are you.
If you won't keep my secret
for Oliver's sake,
you should keep it
for your own.
I see the way you look at him.
If you tell him this,
you will rip his world apart.
And a part of him
will always blame you.
Oh, he'll hate me, for sure.
But he will hate you, too.
We all have to keep secrets,
Miss Smoak.
You look different.
I'm still me.
The Sara I know
wouldn't have betrayed us
and fled Nanda Parbat
under the cover of darkness.
I didn't have a choice.
The earthquake--
I needed to see my family,
make sure they were safe.
And so they are.
Come home.
I can't.
Look, I can't
go back, Nyssa.
I don't have
much of a soul left in me,
but what there is,
it can't take the killing anymore.
You swore an oath.
My father sent me here
to make sure you honor it.
One way or another.
We both know the real reason
why you came here.
When I found you,
you were starving,
and alone,
simply waiting to die.
The League took you in...
nursed you back to health.
The only reason you're alive
today is because of me.
Hey, I wasn't with you
because you saved me.
I was with you
because I loved you.
But not anymore.
Ra's listens to you.
And you can ask him to release me.
My father has never released
anyone from the League.
He released
Malcolm Merlyn.
An action he and the citizens
of this city dearly regret.
Do what you have to.
It's been two hours,
and she should have gotten back
in touch with me by now.
Felicity.
Felicity!
What?!
Sorry. What?
Are you ok?
Uh, yeah, I'm fine.
It's just...
things in here.
The League is never
going to let me go.
At least if I'm halfway
around the world,
then I can keep
my family safe.
I wouldn't be
so sure about that.
Just got a copy of
Laurel's bloodwork.
She tested negative
for drugs.
Well, then why did she collapse?
Because they found traces
of snake venom in her blood.
From a Tibetan
pit viper.
Wait.
So Laurel didn't OD?
She was poisoned.
She was poisoned by Nyssa,
who did it
to draw you back here.
And it worked.
My family's
in danger.
Who are you texting?
No one.
Did you meet a boy at school?
Cut it out.
Boys at school are lame.
Hey, how's everything
with you and Oliver?
Great.
We decided to start
looking at apartments together.
I know it's a big step, but...
We're ready. I think we'll
live together for a year,
engaged for another,
and then...
Mrs. Laurel Queen.
Maybe one day.
This is kind of assuming
that he's ever ready to settle down.
What's that supposed to mean?
Well, we both know at least ten girls
that he's slept with.
Can't you just be happy for me?
I mean, if you met
some amazing guy
who wanted to spend
the rest of his life with you,
I would be so supportive,
and so happy for you--
Ok, Laurel, I wasn't trying
to be a bitch.
The title
of your autobiography.
I'm going to get
some sleep.
No!
Dad, it's my fault,
I'm so sorry.
The assassins group that you're
a part of, they took your mother.
Not exactly.
Well, what exactly?
A woman.
Nyssa. She's a powerful
figure in the League.
And she poisoned Laurel.
She took mom.
To get you to come back
to the League?
To get me
to come back to her.
Oh.
Nyssa,
don't do this.
I tried to warn you,
but you wouldn't listen.
I thought it would be
instructive
for you to know
what it feels like
to suddenly lose
someone you love.
To have them ripped
from your life without warning.
You do not want
to hurt my mother.
You're right.
I don't.
You have one day,
ta-er sah-fer.
Make the right choice.
We have 24 hours.
Detective...
We'll find her.
Ok, Laurel's inside,
she's losing her mind, I got to go.
Keep me updated.
Oh, come on!
You ought to buy a ticket
if you're going to play like that!
Hey, kiddo. How's
the apartment hunt going?
Terribly. I really wanted to find
the perfect place
to show Ollie when he gets back
from his boat trip.
Everything good
was already taken
by the time I walked
in the door.
Maybe it's a sign that you're not
supposed to move in
with the frat boy
that you call a boyfriend.
You and mom were my age
when you moved into that
place on Spring Street.
You weren't even
engaged yet.
Well, that's
'cause your mother
kept turning down
all my proposals.
She did?
Oh, you know your mother,
free spirit and all.
Why do we need rings
when we have love?
You know I spent a year
with that damn ring
burning a hole
in my pocket?
A mayday transmission
was heard, but so far there has been
no trace
of the "Queen's Gambit."
Among those missing are local residents
Robert and Oliver Queen.
Do we have a lead on Dinah?
We researched the poison
Nyssa used on Laurel.
Luckily for us,
Tibetan pit viper venom
is surprisingly
difficult to transport.
It starts losing its potency
the moment it leaves the fangs.
Yet another sentence I never
thought I'd actually say out loud.
So it was bought locally?
Not bought. Stolen.
From where?
The zoo.
A local break-in.
The perps didn't steal anything,
so the cops chalked it up
to a bunch of kids looking for a thrill.
I pulled up the zoo CCTV footage
from the night of the break-in.
I caught a plate.
The car's a rental.
Address
is in the Glades.
Sara.
Call your father.
Sebastian, I am so sorry.
I have a bad habit
of standing you up.
Look, I know you have to pull
your support for my campaign.
Blood is thicker
than politics.
And it should be.
Well, thank you
for understanding,
and I really hope that this
doesn't affect our friendship.
It's important to me.
And to me.
Can I help you,
alderman?
Oh, I had a meeting
with your son.
I'm sure you can
guess the topic.
I hope my decision
to run against you for mayor
doesn't affect
your relationship.
Out of respect
for that relationship,
can I offer some advice?
Please.
Get out.
Now.
The fact that you are
advising me to get out
before I even announce
my candidacy
suggests that you're threatened.
I'm apprehensive about destroying
my friend's mother.
I can take care of myself.
Really?
During your trial,
you portrayed yourself
as a fragile creature
living under Malcolm Merlyn's thumb.
So which is it?
The woman strong enough
to lead this city,
or the one too weak
willed to save it?
The one who should not be
underestimated.
So what exactly
is the plan here?
We wait. The Arrow
will lead him right to us.
You know,
you never did tell me
how you joined up
with the Arrow in the first place.
Where did you two
even meet?
Vigilante club.
Same old Sara.
Well, not exactly
the same.
I loved her, Dad.
Are you upset?
Honestly, Sara,
to think what
you've been through
these past six years?
The pain,
the loneliness...
I'm just happy to hear you
had someone that cared for you.
What's the matter,
they didn't teach you
about right crosses
in assassin school?
Where is Nyssa?!
Tell me where my wife is!
What the hell is he saying?
He's praying.
No, don't!
Son of a bitch!
It's over, Detective.
He's gone.
How's Sara
holding up?
Not well.
And I need you
to pick up
the trail on Nyssa,
because Mrs. Lance
is running out of time.
I'm on it.
Oh, Oliver.
Felicity.
Hi, hi.
Ohh. Well, I haven't
been this nervous
since my wedding day.
Both of them.
Moira, it's time.
Oliver, are you ready to introduce
your mother?
With pride.
Felicity?
Felicity.
What is going on
with you?
And don't say--
nothing.
Don't say "nothing."
The truth, please.
Might have noticed
that I talk a lot.
It has not escaped
my attention.
You might have also noticed
that I don't talk a lot
about my family.
I have noticed that.
My mother is...
She's...
She's my mother.
And...
I don't really know
what my father is,
'cause he abandoned us.
I barely remember him.
But I do remember...
How much it hurt
when he left.
And just the thought
of losing someone
that important to me again...
Hey.
You're not going
to lose me.
Whatever it is
that's bothering you...
Is it about
your family?
No.
It's about yours.
Time's up.
Have you made your decision?
Let my mother go.
And I will return with you
to Nanda Parbat.
You're doing
the right thing, Sara.
For both of us.
Here you go,
sweetie.
Your chamomile,
like you like.
Is there anything else
I can get you?
My mother.
Laurel, there's
something I got to tell you.
It's about
your sister.
What about her?
Hello?
Dad, I found mom.
Meet me at the lower boat
yards in 30 minutes,
and come alone.
Don't tell the Arrow.
Copy that.
I got to go.
What about Sara, Dad?
I'll explain everything
later, all right?
Just sit tight.
I say this
with confidence.
Because the Moira Queen
that I know is more
than a successful CEO
and philanthropist.
She is a loving mother
who has devoted her life
to raising
two wonderful children.
Just to tell you
how special she is,
I'd like to welcome her son.
CEO of Queen Consolidated,
Mr. Oliver Queen.
Phew. Thank you.
Well, I'm here today
to say a few words...
about Moira Queen.
I bet many of you
think that you know her,
because you...
read about her
in the press,
or you saw her on TV.
But I can promise you...
You don't know my mother.
You don't know her
like I do.
And you don't know
what she's capable of...
When it comes to helping
the people of Starling City.
Ladies and gentlemen...
My mother,
Moira Queen.
I know.
Thank you!
Thank you, Starling City.
Sara!
The snake venom,
it's gone.
She found Nyssa.
And she's going
to poison her?
We need to stop her
before she does.
Activate her tracer.
You put a tracer on her?
She has a bad habit
of disappearing on me.
Oliver, I hate to sound cold,
but why do we care
if Sara kills some bad ass assassin
that wants to get her and her family?
Because, Diggle,
if half of the stories
that I have heard
about Ra's al Ghul are true,
if Sara kills his daughter...
We will all pay.
They're coming for you now.
Dinah! Move away
from her! Move away!
It's all right,
it's all right.
What's happening?
Sara...
It's me, Mom.
It's me.
Oh, my baby!
My baby!
I love you so much, Mom.
I have to go.
What? What
are you doing?
Dad, get mom out of here!
What?!
We've got to go.
No!
You took the poison.
I can't go back.
I can't take
the killing anymore.
It needs to end.
Sara! Delta Charlie 52,
to Central,
need back up at
the lower boat yards.
Ambulance, paramedics...
If you want to be with
your family so badly,
they can join you
in eternity.
You get the hell away
from my daughter.
Live or die.
It's up to you.
Sara. I can still save her.
Worry more
about saving yourself.
Don't kill her.
Please.
Sara...
Sara!
Sara, hold on.
Stay with me.
Come on.
Come on, stay.
Not again.
No more killing.
Nyssa.
Please.
Ta-er sah-fer,
in the name
of Ra's al Ghul...
I release you.
Thank God you're ok!
Are you all right?
Oh, I can't believe you.
Look at you.
You're all right, baby.
I can't believe it.
Look at you.
You're ok, baby.
Because Starling City
is our city.
And starting today,
we're going to take it back.
I know we need to talk.
You need to listen.
For the past year,
I have stood by your side...
And I have fought,
because I wanted to believe
that you weren't this...
Monster.
And I needed to believe
that I still had a mother.
You do, Oliver--
Oliver, I only lied about Thea
to protect her from Malcolm.
No, you lied
because that is what you do.
And that is who you are, Mom.
Lies.
And now you've made
a liar out of me.
Because Thea could never
find out about Merlyn.
And she could never
know the truth about us.
Which is that as of right now,
we have no relationship.
I will keep up appearances
for Thea's sake.
And publicly, I will
support your campaign.
But privately...
You and I are done.
Oliver...
Oliver.
Oliver!
I know you have
a lot of questions.
Nope.
How could you not
have any questions?
Because I already know
all of the answers to them.
How could you still be alive;
where have you been
all this time?
Why didn't you call us.
And the answer
to all of them...
Is because it's Sara.
Baby, don't do this--
Dad, I swear to God,
if you say one more word.
Laurel, look,
I know you're angry.
And you have
every right to be.
But please don't
take this out on dad.
If you need someone
to blame, blame me.
Oh, I do blame you, Sara.
Every single thing
that's gone wrong in our lives
is your fault.
You got on that stupid boat
with my boyfriend.
You didn't call us to tell us
that you were still alive,
even though it probably would
have saved mom and dad's marriage.
And you brought some crazy assassin
into Starling City
who nearly killed mom
and who poisoned me.
You.
You stole my whole life
away from me.
Now get out.
Laurel...
Get out.
I'm sorry.
I said get out!
Hold on.
Please, come in.
Tell me Oliver is ok!
Tell me everything's ok!
I wish I could.
Moira, I'm so sorry about Robert.
About Oliver.
I really am.
Yes, um, I need
to tell you both something.
What is it?
Robert and Oliver
weren't the only ones lost.
Along with the crew,
a friend
invited along by Oliver
at the last minute.
Tommy.
No.
It was...
It was Sara.
Your Sara.
I'm so sorry, Quentin.
The dock master
saw her sneak on board.
With Moira Queen's
impressive speech
earlier today, some pundits
are suggesting her candidacy
might not be so far-fetched.
And while Blood's campaign has yet
to issue a public response
to Mrs. Queen's announcement...
I warned you not
to underestimate Moira Queen.
What do you want me to do?
Thank you!
Thank you, Starling City!
Nothing.
I'll take care of it.
You've been crying.
Yeah, I was happy
to know I still could.
Are you ok?
Well, Laurel wasn't as thrilled
to see me as you thought.
Give her time.
I gave her six years.
What exactly are you
taking out on that dummy?
My mother...
She's not who
I thought she was.
I guess it's going around.
So what now?
I don't know.
I don't, either.
I know one thing.
What's that?
I'm home.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man