Previously, on "arrow"...
Where's your mother?!
The white-haired woman!
She took her!
Deliver Sara's killer,
or the citizens of Starling
Will see what the league
of assassins is capable of.
I will tell Ra's
this was you,
That Thea was
under your control.
And he will still kill her.
She fired the arrows.
There's nothing
that I won't do
to protect you.
What does that mean?
I killed Sara.
By league law,
I have the right
to challenge you
To a trial
by combat.
You covet death that much?
[car horns honking]
[tires squealing]
[sirens]
Hey, I want
air support now!
These bastards,
they shot one
of our own!
That cop was just asking
for my license, man,
You didn't have
to shoot him!
Get me closer!
[tires squealing]
Come on!
Damn it!
Yes!
It's him!
I thought
he was green.
Roy: This bike is sick!
Felicity: Ok,
not supposed to be
having fun right now.
No, sorry
is what you'll be
When Oliver finds
out you took out
his motorcycle.
Roy: Ok, I've got him
headed your way.
Aim for the engine block.
There's the green one.
This suit is too tight.
Felicity: If they
make it to the tunnel,
we're going to lose them.
You're not helping.
I thought he was
supposed to be good!
Who the hell
are you?
I'm more of a glock
kind of guy.
I didn't say anything.
One caught,
one got away,
But even Oliver bats
.500 sometimes.
Not yet, but I have
every reconnaissance
satellite I could hack,
Which is a lot,
looking for him.
So the second
he steps outside,
we'll know.
If he steps outside.
It's what
we were all thinking.
I'm not. It's only
been three days.
I have to head
to my other
office for a bit.
Ok, I know
it's only been
three days,
But how much
longer before
We actually
have to start
worrying?
I expected this kind of
blunder from Mr. Queen,
But not from you.
You were too bold.
You should have
checked with me
Before abducting
that scientist.
We were just following
the trail for omega...
I ordered you to be
cautious. That's how
you protect yourself.
And your loved ones.
We need to assemble
an extraction team
to free my wife.
From where?
We don't know where
Chien na wei
is located,
And we have more
pressing concerns.
She has the omega.
We find her, we find tatsu,
We get them both
out of wherever they are.
If only it were
that simple.
We've learned that
the bio weapon
Is actually
comprised of
two components.
The omega she has is
harmless without its
counterpart, alpha.
And where's that?
Currently
in the possession
Of the Hong Kong
military.
Oh, so it's safe.
Far from it.
The only way to secure
the counterpart alpha
is to destRoy it.
And by the time we do,
my wife will be dead.
Alpha is being
kept here,
In a pla military
laboratory.
The two of you,
with back-up,
Will break into
the facility
and recover the vial.
It's tagged
with a gps tracker,
Which you'll need
to disable before
extraction.
And what about tatsu?
Stop ignoring me!
I'm not ignoring
you, Mr. Yamashiro.
I'm merely focusing
on the task at hand,
Which,
at the moment,
Is not
recovering
your wife.
[exhales]
Ahh. All right.
This will be
gauntlet pulse
test, 37 alpha.
Two second burst
at 800 volts.
In 5, 4,
3, 2, 1.
Oh, damn it!
Clowns?
Practice targets.
Clowns always
freaked me out as a kid.
Well, you're showing
them who's boss now.
Well, I would be,
if I could figure out
how to modulate
The stress-energy tensor.
Hmm. Ray,
I've been thinking.
About overclocking
the magnetic coils?
Because I tried that.
No.
About what you're doing.
And about me helping you do it.
Save the city,
you mean?
Risk your life.
I know you think
you're going to be safe
inside that suit of armor.
I know there's like
a gajillion movies
that make it look easy.
Well, the arrow
and his partner go out
there every night,
Without armor.
And... One night,
Hopefully very far
off in the future,
They're not going
to come back.
I don't want that
to happen to you.
Let's not get
ahead of ourselves.
Just see if you can get
the nanite chip to function.
[indistinct chatter]
Quentin: The cop he shot?
Father of three.
Doc says he may
never walk again,
and that's if he makes it.
'cause right now,
he's 50/50.
All right, miss lance,
You're up.
The people versus
Jermaine Fisher.
Mr. Fisher
is charged with
41 counts
of attempted murder,
Including 16 counts
of attempted murder
of a police officer.
So no bail
is what you're saying?
Vigorously,
your honor.
Just as the defendant
vigorously moves
to dismiss all charges.
Mr. Fisher's apprehension
was not affected by the police,
But rather by vigilantes.
The circumstances
of Mr. Fisher's arrest
are irrelevant.
Produce the arrow
as an eyewitness
and we'll find out.
That won't be necessary.
We have the weapon
with Mr. Fisher's
fingerprints
All over it,
your honor.
Motion to dismiss
denied, bail denied.
Please remand
Mr. Fisher into custody.
[bangs gavel]
How did it go
at a.R.G.U.S.?
Lyla tapped all of our
worldwide contacts.
No sign of Oliver.
And no idea
where he could be.
Well, he'll tell us
when he gets back.
Until then, we should focus
on keeping the lights on.
The two cop shooters
we took on last night;
I've been trying to find
the one that got away.
Anton is attached
to a new crew
working the glades,
The head of which
is this gentleman.
I know that guy.
That's Danny Brickwell.
His street name's brick.
But I thought
he was in iron heights.
He was.
Until a week ago.
And then the case
against him imploded.
By which I mean
every single witness
Suffered some sort
of fatal accident.
Three guesses
as to who the police
suspect in those cases.
Jermaine Fisher
and the guy who
got away last night.
So they kill witnesses
in order to get
brick out of prison,
And then shoot
a cop to do... What?
That's what
we have to find out.
I'll hit the streets.
[inhales, exhales]
You have that look
you always get
Right before you tell
Oliver something...
Sagely.
Yes, and this is
about Oliver.
You think I'm in denial.
I think four
days ago,
Oliver
challenged
the world's
Greatest
assassin
to a duel.
He survived Lian Yu.
And Hong Kong,
and god knows what else.
He defeated Malcolm Merlyn
and Slade Wilson.
You have to believe in him.
Oh, I do believe
in him, Felicity.
It's just,
I'm preparing myself
for the possibility
That things didn't
go Oliver's way.
Not this time.
You need to prepare
yourself, too.
[sharp inhale] please,
Oliver, where are you?
[wind blowing]
[groaning, gasping]
Y'all best step off.
Brick is a friend
of mine.
You're more than
a friend,Anton.
You're like a brother.
Always had my back.
Always loyal.
Stand up.
So when they told me
Someone ignored
my orders to lay low;
When they told me one
of my crew shot a cop...
I beat the man
who said it was you.
I'm sorry.
Danny, that cop?
It was a mistake.
What we're planning here
requires two things.
No mistakes,
and the cops not
knowing anything.
They still don't.
Fisher's not going
to say anything.
Was this side job
his idea or yours?
It doesn't have
to be like this.
Bro!
I dropped
my first body
with that piece.
You know the deal;
You take me
down first,
you walk out alive.
[grunting]
He actually
tagged me.
[chuckles]
All yours, boys.
Your attorney doesn't
have your best interests
at heart, Mr. Fisher.
Otherwise,
you'd be walking
out of here a free man.
Yeah, more like
a dead man.
Do you think
you scare me more
than brick does?
Think again.
You have
a real nice day now.
No, he didn't flip.
He likes breathing
too much.
[both grunting]
When your opponent
is the mountain,
you must be the sea.
When he is the sea,
you must be the mountain.
Poetic.
Switch your attacks.
Never do the same move
more than twice.
Otherwise, your opponent
will learn to read you.
Something like that?
[cell phone vibrates]
Well, I wouldn't
recommend texting
during a real fight.
Sorry.
I... I thought
it might be Ollie.
He hasn't been home.
He hasn't returned
any of my calls or texts.
I didn't realize
his absence was
weighing on you.
It's not weighing,
it's worrying.
If you like,
I could have
some of my
old associates
Look into Oliver's
whereabouts.
Would you?
Of course.
He's family.
According to Laurel,
Fisher's lawyer called brick
With the time and the place
of the outgoing call.
Can you trace that call
back to where brick is?
At least where
his phone is.
His burner phone,
to be exact.
It's at a warehouse
in the glades.
I'll have to talk you
in from palmer tech.
I'm crazy-late.
This is the only
vulnerable entrance.
Because it's not
actually an entrance.
Not until
we make it one.
I'll shoot out
the glass.
You get in
and find the alpha.
We won't have much time
once we breach.
Two minutes max before
the alarms draw attention.
Head directly for the lab.
I'll be right behind you.
You ok?
Waller said
when we get
this done,
She'll get
tatsu back.
She's lying.
[gunshot]
Ahh!
[groaning]
On the move!
30 seconds.
John: Copy that.
I've got eyes
on the target warehouse.
But no signs of life.
Felicity, you seeing
something I don't?
The warehouse
doesn't have any
security cameras,
But someone disabled
all the traffic cams
on that block,
Which probably
means you're in
the right place.
Roy: You sure ditching
the arrow suit was a good idea?
Only if I need
to move or shoot.
In position.
John: Clear.
Yeah, I got
something.
It's not big enough
to be brick.
Yeah, I know.
What's this?
[sighs] they burned
their burners.
Yeah,
torching evidence,
Tying up loose ends.
Evidence of what?
I don't know.
These just look
like numbers.
I found this.
What looks like
some industrial blueprints.
Hmm. These numbers look
completely random.
I can run a pattern
recognition algorithm.
Oliver?
Oliver?!
Malcolm: Could you
put the gun away?
They don't scare
so much as annoy me.
I've only come
here to talk.
Would it be possible
to do that?
Talk about what?
Oliver.
I need to know...
Is he still alive?
He's alive.
Have you heard
from him since
he went off to face
Ra's al Ghul?
He's alive.
If he were, I suspect
you would have heard
from him by now.
Unless Ra's
took him prisoner,
And demon's head does
not take prisoners.
What are you doing?
I'm running
the pattern analysis
On that list of numbers
you guys found.
No, I mean, what's the point?
Malcolm Merlyn didn't
tell us anything
we don't already know.
Nothing has changed.
You're right,
Felicity.
He didn't tell us
anything new.
But he may have been
right all the same.
I know you guys
think I'm in denial.
But if there's one
thing Oliver taught
me... he taught us...
Is that sometimes,
all you can do
Is keep pushing
forward.
All right.
I've got the m.E.'s report.
Did they id
the body?
JoseAnton.
Career criminal with ties
to Danny Brickwell.
I think brick severed
those ties pretty thoroughly.
Is everything ok?
Where's Oliver?
He went to fight
the head
Of the league
of assassins.
What?!
And we haven't
heard from him
since he left.
There's something else...
Malcolm Merlyn stopped by
for a little chat.
He says Oliver's dead.
And you guys believe him?
Look, Laurel,
Merlyn said...
There isn't one thing
that Malcolm Merlyn can say
That any of us should believe.
This isn't the first time
That I've heard
that Oliver was dead.
He's been back before.
He'll be back again.
[grunts]
[beep]
clear.
Found it!
Aah!
Hong Kong military?
Triad.
Chien na Wey's men.
Any luck?
The number pattern
is consistent with
cataloguing numerics.
What kind of catalog?
If I knew,
I would be
telling you.
I'm sorry to interrupt.
We really need
to change the locks.
The league conducts
matter of significance
such as duels
On grounds sacred
to its beliefs.
I went there.
And found this.
It's Ra's' custom
to leave behind
The instrument
of death
As a memorial
to honor
the fallen.
Merlyn, did you see...
Oliver's body?
It fell into
a ravine.
His remains were
unrecoverable,
I'm afraid.
Then how do we know
that's Oliver's blood?
Because
after I leave,
you'll test it.
And after you
confirm that
it is his blood,
You'll exhaust
yourself with
conspiracy theories
As to how I planted it
or how it's all a lie.
And after enough
time passes,
You'll be left with
one inescapable truth...
That Oliver Queen
is dead.
This is your fault.
Oliver went there
because of you...
Because of what
you did to Thea.
You made her a target
for the league so he would have
To challenge Ra's
just to save her.
You killed him.
You are right.
And I will live
with that guilt
For the rest of my days.
I am truly sorry.
I can see how much
you loved him.
Save it, Merlyn.
You're enjoying this.
Miss Smoak
is correct.
I orchestrated
the matter
To eliminate
the death warrant
Ra's placed
on my head.
Oliver was that way.
His death
means my own.
Good.
[beep]
What's that?
The blood analysis
on the scimitar.
It's Oliver's.
99.997% match.
If Merlyn's lying,
he's being thorough about it.
Felicity...
Thanks for not saying
"I told you so."
I got to go to work.
You really don't.
It's fine.
I'm glad we know now.
Run for the exit!
I'll cover you!
What about you?
You get the alpha out of here!
But...
Away from them! Go!
You had him.
Why didn't you
take the shot?
We need to get out of here.
Now.
You know, it's weird.
I don't think
I've ever actually
seen you drink alone.
You ok?
Yeah.
I just got some bad news
about a friend.
Anyone I know?
How are you doing?
Still freaking
out, actually.
Worried about Ollie.
I was going
to ask you a favor,
But it doesn't seem
like the right time.
Well, it depends.
What's the favor?
You and the arrow, you're...
You're close, right?
I mean, that's you
I've been seeing
on the news
In the red hood?
Thea...
Look, I haven't seen him,
I haven't heard from him,
He's not answering
any of my phone calls.
I'm actually starting
to get really worried.
So... I thought
maybe the arrow
Could look for Oliver?
I just thought maybe
if you saw him,
You could ask.
Thank you.
You're the best.
Look, I...
I better go check
the stock room.
Thea just asked me
to talk to the arrow
About finding Oliver.
And what'd you
tell her?
What else? I lied.
Oliver didn't want
Thea to know.
That was then.
But now, what's the point?
I keep asking myself
the same question, Roy.
Then why do you keep
going over the case evidence?
Because it helps me keep
my mind off of Oliver.
Doing this
without him
While we're waiting
for him to come back
is one thing,
But doing all
this without him,
without him?
That's a whole
other situation.
What do you want me
to tell you, Roy?
I can only see one inch
in front of me
And this is the only thing
in front of me right now.
I keep looking
at this file, and...
Something about it
feels familiar.
Yeah. Felicity did say
that Fisher andAnton
were connected with brick.
No, it's more
than that.
I've seen
this file
somewhere...
Else.
What are the chances
that's a coincidence?
Hey, there's only
way to find out.
What are you
doing?
Bringing up
the case numbers
On the all guys
we've put away over
the past eight months.
Some of these are guys
that we caught.
Yeah. And others
were apprehended
by the authorities.
There's a pattern here.
All these guys
are awaiting trial
For assault... assault
with intent, murder,
Attempted murder.
Street enforcers.
Muscle.
Why would brick
have a list of
these case numbers?
[cell phone vibrates]
Ah, I'm sure you're wondering
if I ever go home.
Unfortunately
for my assistant,
the answer's no.
Any luck with our
nanite problems?
Yeah, it's the transplex
interface, isn't it?
I knew my designs were off.
It won't... Work.
Yeah, well, you've only
been at it for a day, so.
Not the chip.
Not your suit.
Your plan.
It won't work.
Using an enhanced exoskeleton
to fight crime and save the city
Is a loony tune idea.
It won't
bring her back.
Anna.
Your fiancé.
I know who she is.
She's not coming back.
When we lose...
Someone,
When someone dies,
They're gone.
Forever, and there
is nothing...
There is nothing
Nothing that we can
do that is going
to bring them back.
So you have to stop.
You have to stop,
Because it's not
what anna would
have wanted. It's...
You're upset.
I can see that.
And if you want,
We can talk about it.
But never tell me again
What anna would have wanted.
You don't get to do that.
I am sorry.
I shouldn't...
Be here right now.
[sighs]
[cell phone vibrates]
What?
John: We got
something on brick.
Roy: The blueprints
we found?
They're schematics
For the warehouse
where the police
Store all their
physical evidence
and active cases.
And brick has a list
of case numbers.
We think he might be looking
to steal or destRoy evidence
To get those cases
thrown out of court.
Yeah. I'll call
lance, tell him.
A lot of these cases
are on guys who were put away
within the past eight months.
This is everything
we've been doing since
we took slade down.
This is everything
Oliver was working for.
I'll be right there.
Three minutes.
[tires squealing]
[sirens]
Seal off every exit.
Give me a two block
perimeter.
John, shooter at your five.
I'm out!
Here, use mine.
So here's the deal...
You take me down,
you walk out alive.
I don't fancy
your chances,
though.
[siren in distance]
Smart man.
Nobody thinks
about going
for a head shot.
[both grunting]
Shots fired! I need esu
and back-up here, now!
Felicity!
Where's Diggle?
I'm pinned down!
Felicity!
Any... Last... Words?
Or are my hands too tight
around your neck?
I guess arrows work
a little better on
this guy than bullets.
[sirens]
You ok?
Yeah, I will be,
after we find
the son of a bitch.
Damn it!
Oh, my god, john!
It's ok, it's all right,
I'm fine. I'm fine.
Brick?
Got away. They put
one guard in the hospital
On the way out, but he's
going to pull through.
If that door hadn't
shut, we would
have had him.
Just bad luck.
Unless it wasn't.
You were pinned down.
You both were. They
were going to kill you!
Felicity...
They had machine guns.
You had a bow and arrow.
You let him
get away?
I saved your lives.
Felicity, it wasn't
your call to make.
It wasn't my call
to let Oliver go
challenge Ra's al Ghul
To a fight
to the death, either!
Brick has who knows
how much evidence,
Felicity.
And it was either that
or the two of you.
My friends being killed.
So I made my choice.
I chose not
to let anyone else
I care about die.
We've been in
tough spots before
and we've always managed
To come out on the other side.
No.
Oliver did.
But he's not here
anymore,
Because he's dead.
Ok.
The point is,
If we're going to do this
without Oliver,
Felicity, we have
to trust each other.
You don't get it.
There is no "this"
without him.
It's done. I'm done.
[wind blowing]
[banging on door]
I'm sorry.
But I have no one else
to turn to.
And he needs your help.
I was
out of line.
And I'm sorry.
You want to tell me
what had you so upset?
I lost a friend of mine.
He was more than
a friend, actually.
He was...
[exhales] I'm not
sure what we were,
But... He's gone.
I'm sorry.
And three months ago,
another friend of mine died.
I'm 25 years old.
I'm over my quota where
losing my friends are concerned.
And you're a friend.
So if you want
to go out there;
If you want to commit suicide,
I can't stop you.
But I don't have to help you.
[sighs]
Eight months
to put him away...
Eight minutes
to set him loose.
Laurel:
I'm sorry.
I tried.
Without
the evidence,
The judge had
to let them go.
He's not coming back.
Oliver.
I know you don't want
to believe it, Laurel.
God knows I don't, but...
He's not coming back.
Are you?
Are you coming back?
I don't know.
For the first time
since I met Oliver Queen...
I don't know what happens next.
I know it's silly, but I...
Still like to think of myself
as Oliver's bodyguard.
I just couldn't protect him.
It's funny.
He was worried something
would happen to me.
I could have killed you!
Heh. It's cute
that you think so.
Did you hear anything
about Ollie?
I'm afraid not.
[sighs] then what
are you doing here?
We're in danger,
Thea.
We need to leave
Starling city
and never return.
Thank you all
for coming.
But seeing
as I'm the reason
None of you are
sitting in a prison
cell right now,
I figure
it's the least
you can do.
I know I'm the guy that
made all the evidence
against you go away,
But as you can see,
It didn't go too far.
You are all part
of my crew now.
And if any of you
have a problem with that,
I can send a gift wrapped
package to the d.A.
Together, not only will
we make a lot of money,
We will make history.
Together,
We are going to take
over the glades.
You think brick's crazy?
Take over a whole
section of town?
I know he's crazy.
I don't know what
he's got planned,
But whatever it is, I'm in.
[alarm shrieking]
Who the hell are you?
I'm the justice
you can't run from.
Well done, Mr. Queen.
I'm glad to know my
investment in you hasn't
entirely been for naught.
Although I was
disappointed to read
Agent pierson's
after action report.
You let one
of chien na wey's
men get away.
I hesitated.
It was a mistake.
It really was.
Now we have no one
to interrogate.
You mean torture, right?
I saw you with that man.
You didn't
hesitate.
You chose
not to shoot him.
I put the gps from the vial
in his pocket.
And now he is going to lead us
right to tatsu.
You're going to get
her back, maseo.
I promise.
Oliver...
What you've done,
I will be forever
in your debt.
[gasping]
Don't move.
You'll pull out the sutures.
Oliver.
Tatsu.
Maseo: I asked her
to come here...
So she could
bring you back to life.