OLIVER:
My name is Oliver Queen.
For five years, I was stranded
on an island with only one goal:
Survive.
Oliver Queen is alive.
OLIVER:
Now, I will fulfill my father's dying wish...
...to use the list of names he left me...
...and bring down those
who are poisoning my city.
To do this,
I must become someone else.
I must become something else.
Previously on Arrow:
You told me to stay away
from your family.
But your family isn't staying away from me
which means something must be done.
Where can I find the man
in this picture?
Do you not think it convenient
you captured me easily?
YAO FEI:
Run!
[GRUNTS]
FYERS: Do you even know
what this island really is?
It's a prison.
What would you do in my position?
[CLUB MUSIC PLAYING OVER RADIO]
Whatever you're listening to,
it ain't music.
[JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING OVER RADIO]
- There ought to be a law.
- Well, there's not. So...
[CLUB MUSIC PLAYING OVER RADIO]
[GUN CLICKS]
GUARD:
Yo, watch it.
Hey, he's got a gun.
[MEN GROANING]
[BOTH COUGHING]
[GUNFIRE]
THEA:
Tahitian Green or Midnight Black?
- What do you think?
- You've been dropping hints all week.
Mom still isn't buying you a car.
- I could not have said it better myself.
- Oliver got a car when he turned 18.
Yeah, but I could back it out
of the driveway without hitting a tree.
I do remember you taking the paint off
your dad's Maserati.
- Hmm.
MOIRA: Thea, the party planner's waiting.
Sorry to run off like this.
But we have a convertible to go buy.
OLIVER: Good luck.
MOIRA: Yes.
- How's she holding up?
- Oh, she's okay.
Thea thinks she's actually
a little bit too okay.
- What do you mean?
- Just...
...behaving erratically. Shut-in one minute,
running the company the next.
Her husband is missing
and presumed who-knows-what.
If anyone had an excuse to be erratic,
it's your mom.
That's what I told Thea.
Department's got the same comment about
this heist as the other two. No comment.
S.C.P.D. may not be willing
to go on record...
...but traffic cameras got the entire heist
in this exclusive.
MAN: Shortly after 1 a.m.,
three masked robbers...
...approached the armored vehicle
after launching what appears...
TOMMY: That's why you keep
all your money offshore.
MAN [ON TV]: One guard was
pronounced dead on the scene.
The other died en route
to Starling General.
Their identities have not yet
been released.
DIGGLE: With all the guys up top,
you might want a side entrance...
...for your, uh, Arrowcave.
OLIVER: Unh!
Just put one in. South alleyway.
Ah. There's something I wanna show you.
You're into online dating
and you need help with your profile.
Not exactly.
But there's somebody I'd like to meet.
Yeah, I read about this.
Third truck to get hit this month.
I saw it on the news this morning.
Couldn't figure out
why it seemed so familiar.
Then I remembered this. Kandahar, '09.
The Marines took out
a Taliban transport vehicle.
DIGGLE:
Yeah. Well, there's a reason...
...why that looks similar. These guys run
the same technique. Where'd you find this?
Researching someone.
Bodyguard who works for a security firm.
Blackhawk Squad Protection Group.
His name is Ted Gaynor.
Oliver, Ted Gaynor was my commanding
officer my first tour in Afghanistan.
Dig, I'm sorry...
...but Gaynor's on the list.
Gaynor's a few
hundred thousand dollars short.
I never said it was just
1 percenters, did I?
This guy saved my life.
Received a commendation for it.
Don't care what your book says,
he's not a stick-up man.
- You haven't known him a long time.
- We both kept in contact...
...since we got stateside.
Six months ago,
he even offered me a job at Blackhawk.
Trust me, you don't know this man
like I do.
I know in Afghanistan his training specialty
was M32 multiple grenade launchers.
The exact same weapon used
in these heists.
Not exactly something you find
at your local sporting goods store.
Two months ago we found out
this wasn't even your father's book.
Written by whoever hired the other archer.
Doesn't that beg the question...
-...what else you could be wrong about?
- I can be wrong. The list isn't.
Now, I'm gonna have a pointed
conversation with Mr. Gaynor tonight.
We'll see what he has to say.
I understand
if you wanna take the week off.
Yeah, well, thank you.
Sir.
[MEN CHATTERING]
[SOLIDER SPEAKING
IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
SOLDIER:
Different day, same slop.
- You new?
OLIVER: Yeah.
[SOLDIER CHUCKLES]
SOLDIER: Don't worry. Took me a year
to find my way around the island.
OLIVER:
Well, hey, hey, hey.
I'm supposed to be transporting
a prisoner.
Chinese guy who wears a green hood?
SOLDIER: Sounds like the guy
they took to east camp.
I'm heading over that way.
You can hitch a ride.
Let's go, come on.
Hold up, hold up. Unit one, two.
[FYE RS GROAN I NG]
That wall over there
still has to be taped and textured.
I need you to grout the hallway floor as
soon as they're done with the tile install.
[PHONE BEEPING]
MAN:
All right.
- Yeah.
- Hey, Tommy.
- Dad, I am really busy.
- Tommy, I know things have been...
...well, strained between us since--
Since you cut me off
and told me that I was a loser?
I was just trying
to jolt you into adulthood.
And look at you now.
You've got your first job, heh.
My tough love worked.
What do you want, Dad?
Nothing more than to share a meal
with my son.
Dinner, tomorrow night?
- Laurel and I have plans.
MALCOLM: Bring her along.
I think it's time I got to know her
a little better. Tommy...
...I've said some pretty hurtful things
and I regret them.
But you're still my son...
...and I still want
what I've always wanted.
For us to be close.
Let me check with Laurel
and I'll get back to you.
[DART GUN FIRING]
[GRUNTS]
Ted, we're gonna have a conversation.
You make a move, go for a gun,
anything and things will end badly for you.
[GUN COCKS]
Put the bow down.
[SIGHS]
It's all clear. You okay?
Uh,yeah.
Well, I gotta talk to my boss
but after what I just saw...
...I'd say you're as good as hired.
Hell of a job interview, Ted.
Usually the vigilante
only goes after rich schmucks.
Any reason why he would change
his MO for you?
[SIGHS]
You've known me a long time, John.
What do you think?
[SIGHS]
I think he made a mistake.
Got the wrong guy.
OLIVER:
I could've shot you, killed you.
- What the hell?
- Not gonna let you William Tell...
-...an innocent man.
- Gaynor isn't innocent.
You seem to think that
because of your book...
-...which you trust more than you trust me.
- I trust my father.
And he explained to me that every name
on that list has a reason to be there.
You took that book off your father's
dead body. How could he be so chatty?
A few years ago, I found a message
he left me explaining the list.
How was that possible?
You were on a deserted island.
I didn't say that I found it on the island.
Diggle, for the past four months,
I've lied to...
...hurt and hid things
from all the people that I care about.
Do you really think that I would do all this
if I wasn't sure?
Oliver, listen,
Gaynor got me into Blackhawk.
And I'm gonna prove he's innocent.
And if he's isn't?
[GUN COCKS]
You owe me that.
You owe me at least that.
- Were you stationed by the perimeter?
OLIVER: Yes.
- And your report?
OLIVER: Everything's good, sir. No trouble.
- How long have you been stationed here?
OLIVER: Uh, just arrived, sir.
Yes, you do seem rather green.
I don't recall the submarine bringing
in a phalanx of new troops lately.
OLIVER:
Submarine?
I thought everybody came in
to the island on the plane.
Indeed they do.
I think you've tried on
every dress in the city.
Heh. Totally worth it.
[CHUCKLES]
My friends are gonna freak.
Yes, well, if your father were still alive,
he'd freak too.
Though in an entirely different way.
Heh, like when he saw what I was
wearing to my first boy-girl dance?
That poor boy you went with.
Oh, Robert scared him to death.
You know, Dad used to say his saddest
day would be when I turned 18.
Now he's gone
and I'm the one that's sad.
[PHONE RINGS]
Ah, sorry.
I need to take this.
Hello?
Yes, I understand
but I'm with my daughter.
All right. I'll be there.
[SIGHS]
We were gonna
spend the whole day together.
I know, but, uh...
...compliance needs to file
the 8K connected...
...to my assuming Walter's position
at the company and they can't wait.
I'm sorry.
- Is everything okay? You look worried.
- Not worried. Just...
My father called.
Oh.
- And how did that go?
- He invited us to dinner.
For tonight.
Oh.
Yeah. Apparently,
he wants to mend some fences.
But thanks to him, I can't afford a fence.
I assume he's got some other agenda.
Well, there's only one way to find out.
And maybe he really is trying to extend
an olive branch.
You really do look for the best in people,
don't you?
Lucky for you.
[CHUCKLES]
I'm sorry to have to pull you away
from your family.
What do you want, Malcolm?
We have a problem with your friend,
Carl Ballard.
He's trying to gentrify the Glades.
Carl knows that's not part of the plan.
Which is why you're gonna shut him down.
You're his friend. He'll listen to you.
You want me to help you with Carl,
I want something in return.
Proof Walter's still alive.
My word isn't enough?
[MOIRA SCOFFS]
What's that saying? "Trust, but verify"?
Words to live by.
GAYNOR: Two days later,
I'm still digging regurgitated tacos...
...out of the car vents and he asks me
why I won't turn on the AC?
[LAUGHING]
All right, you win.
Bodyguarding Queen was never that bad.
Six years serving, the only thing I'm
qualified for is babysitting spoiled brats.
Ted, they're not all like that.
I haven't met one yet
that would survive a single day in-country.
Hmm.
Makes me wonder
what I was doing over there.
CARLY:
Specialty of the house.
- Thank you, Carly.
- Uh-uh, where is my cake?
Tired of listening to you complain
about the cleaners shrinking your suits.
- Oh, yeah.
- Heh.
[SCOFFS]
- She likes you.
- She's my sister-in-law, Ted.
Not anymore. Your brother's gone, John.
But you are here.
Car's waiting outside.
We got a client to drop off
at the art gallery opening.
GAYNOR:
You remember Paul Knox?
He was a couple of ranks under us
back in the 'Stan.
Good to be working with you.
I'll be outside.
Didn't know Knox
worked at Blackhawk.
They recruited him
when his tour ended last month.
Mm-hm.
People change, John.
And everyone deserves
a chance to prove it.
[TYPING ON KEYBOARD]
[COMPUTER BEEPS]
[DOOR OPENING]
OLIVER: Knocking is not just a suggestion.
- I need to talk to you.
Thea, I'm not telling you
if Mom's getting you a car.
Heh, it's not about that.
Remember last week when I asked you
if you thought Mom was acting weird?
- Yep.
- Well, I found out why.
She's hooking up with Tommy's dad.
[SCOFFS]
- That's insane.
- I just saw them together.
-It's happening all over again.
- What are you talking about?
Um...
A couple months
before you and Dad left on the Gambit...
-...Mom and Dad were arguing a lot.
- About what?
I don't know. But she was having a lot
of these lunch meetings with Mr. Merlyn.
And now Walter's gone too...
...and Mom and Mr. Merlyn
are back at it. It's gross.
Mom never would've cheated on Dad.
She's not cheating on Walter.
[SIGHS]
You don't wanna believe because you have
this perfect image of Mom in your head.
That's not who she is, Ollie.
She's a liar and a cheater.
And you really don't know her at all.
Malcolm and I, having an affair?
That it started when Dad was still alive.
- Why would she think that?
- She says you and Dad were fighting.
- Oh, dear God.
- Mom?
-It's not your concern, sweetheart.
- Thea made it my concern.
What was going on?
Robert was unfaithful to me.
Repeatedly.
It made our marriage difficult,
to say the least.
I'm sorry. But your father wasn't always
the man you thought he was.
[SCOFFS]
I know you thought he walked on water.
But you see, that's how I wanted you
to remember him...
...as a good man who loved you.
That's how I want Thea to remember him.
So promise me you'll keep it a secret.
Of course.
_Mom?
'Yes?
Why would Thea think you and Mr. Meryln
are still sneaking around?
Well, I can't imagine.
Have you seen him lately?
Oliver.
[CHUCKLES]
He's been the CEO
of Merlyn Global Group for years.
I've been running
Queen Consolidated mere weeks.
Yes, I occasionally go
and ask for advice.
Is my interrogation over?
FYERS:
See, this is where we, uh...
...detain prisoners prone to running off
before I've finished with them.
[OLIVER GRUNTS]
[THUDS]
[OLIVER COUGHS]
[PANTS]
Prisoners like you, Mr. Queen.
At Christmas one year,
Tommy wanted a puppy.
He wanted to name it Arthur,
as in King Arthur...
...because he's a Merlyn.
Heh. Well, you used to be
so incredibly adorable.
- I still am.
- Heh.
My wife would've liked you, Laurel.
LAUREL:
I wish I would've known her.
She passed away
before Tommy and I became friends.
She was killed.
There's no need to be polite about it.
You are just a ray of sunshine today.
Please forgive me.
Talking about my wife has a tendency...
...to make me a little bit maudlin.
And here I was beginning
to think my days of being...
...Oliver's geek were coming to an end.
- Is that your way of saying you missed me?
- No, but if that works for you, go with it.
Heh. A friend is running
a scavenger hunt...
...and there's a case
of Lafite Rothschild 1982...
-...waiting at the end.
- Oh, I love red wine.
But in order to find it,
I first need to get through this.
Hmm.
Security fob.
[DEVICE BEEPS]
[TYPING ON KEYBOARD]
It's PIN protected.
Response goes back to a company called
Blackhawk Squad Protection Group.
My friend had his bodyguard
set it up for him.
Personally, I think it's cheating,
but whatever.
This is a military-grade cryptographic
security protocol.
- Your friend really went to all this trouble?
- The idle rich are hard to entertain.
Listen, you get through it
and one of those bottles of wine is yours.
This has been lovely, Mr. Merlyn.
Thank you.
Thank you for joining me.
It's been wonderful
getting to know you better.
If Tommy doesn't mind me
mixing business with pleasure...
...I could use your signature on these.
You wanna shut down
Mom's free clinic?
-It's not hers anymore, Tommy.
- That clinic meant everything to Mom.
You were 8. I don't think you were in
a position to know what was important.
- I just need your signature--
TOMMY: Stop.
This dinner was never about
getting to know Laurel...
...it was about this.
You haven't changed
and you never will.
It's about time that I learn that
and stop letting you disappoint me.
We're leaving.
- This clinic was his mother's.
MALCOLM: Yes.
And his mother taught him a lesson...
...that the world is a harsh
and unforgiving place.
When did she teach him that?
When she was lying dead in the street
with a bullet in her head.
Good night.
GAYNOR: Management keeps things
running smooth, which is nice.
Better than going to war
with the army you got, right?
Heh. Indeed. Indeed.
So, Ted, are you the reason
Knox is working for Blackhawk?
Look, I know you don't like the guy.
I wasn't his biggest fan either.
But jobs are hard to come by
for everybody these days.
And guys like us?
When all anyone thinks you're qualified for
is shooting at people?
If I hadn't gotten Knox this job...
...chances are he'd be out knocking over
liquor stores or robbing banks.
[PHONE RINGING]
- What'd you get?
FELICITY: Your friend's bodyguard...
-...gave him the wrong fob.
- Why?
Well, once I got past Blackhawk's
authentication system...
...there wasn't anything
about a scavenger hunt.
Just a directory and...
Well, I think you've stumbled onto
or gotten me to stumble onto...
-...something pretty illegal.
- Define illegal.
Oh, you know, robbing an armored car
with grenade launchers and tear gas.
- What?
- Someone at Blackhawk...
...was using their system
to store schedules...
...for the city's
seven major armored car carriers.
Including the three that have been hit. We
should provide this information to police.
They should be able
to predict the next heist.
Hold on, Felicity.
I don't wanna get you in trouble.
Do me a favor.
Forward that directory on to me
and I'll get it to the police personally.
Thank you.
So no wine then?
[MAN GRUNTS]
[GUNFIRE]
[GROANING]
Blake? Blake? Come on, man, come on.
[GRUNTS]
- Blake is hit. He's hit!
- Come on, come on!
Go. Drive, drive, drive.
[TIRES SCREECH]
[DANCE MUSIC PLAYING
OVER SPEAKERS]
[CROWD CHEERING]
Oh, God, check it out. Check it out.
- Convertible. Oh, my God.
- You must be so surprised.
Isn't everything absolutely perfect?
Except for if Dad were here.
If Dad were here,
he'd say you look beautiful.
- Oh, excuse me a sec.
OLIVER: Mm-hm.
DIGGLE: I heard the Hood foiled
an armored car heist earlier.
Gaynor wasn't running
the rocket launcher.
I was with him the whole time.
Looks like you were right.
If someone at Blackhawk is involved,
I'd put my money on Knox.
He started right before the heists began.
He has training.
Okay, I injured one of them.
He was bleeding badly
when they made off in their van.
If any of Knox's blood is in one
of the motor pool vans...
-...we'll know.
- I'm going with you.
No, listen, you have this party
and I told you I would handle this.
- Any problems, you're a phone call away.
- Hey.
Head on a swivel.
That's the way I was born, man.
- Happy birthday.
- Oh, thank you.
We have a special birthday gift for you.
It's called Vertigo.
Supposed to make you feel all floaty.
Ah, heh, if my morn caught me with this,
I wouldn't make it to 19.
I'm gonna go put it upstairs
and then I'll be right back down.
Moira, I have a little something for you.
MOIRA:
Walter.
I did as you asked.
Now it's your turn to do as I asked.
MOIRA: I'll take care of it.
- Thank you, Moira.
- At my party. Right here in front of me?
- No, Thea, you don't understand.
Walter hasn't been gone two months
and you're already cheating on him.
- Just like you cheated on Dad--
- No, I never cheated--
- Like I would believe anything you say.
- Thea. Thea.
I wish it had been you
that was on that boat.
[GUNS COCK]
KNOX:
I had a feeling you'd show up.
DIGGLE:
Yeah? Why is that, Knox?
KNOX: Right after Gaynor got you hired,
someone hacked our system.
First person to ever make it through.
- You wanna tell me how you did it?
- Not really sure.
- He didn't think you'd be very cooperative.
- Who?
Hey, John.
- Ted, you're part of this?
GAYNOR: No, not part of.
My men. My mission.
Mission?
- This isn't Afghanistan.
- Oh, don't I know that.
Over there, we were trusted with millions
of dollars in weapons and personnel.
We were conquerors.
And now? We're nannies with Tasers.
[SCOFFS]
So that gives you the right to steal?
- To kill innocent civilians?
- I'm not gonna convince you I'm right.
- I am gonna convince you to join the team.
- Heh. Yeah, now I know you're crazy.
Tonight was supposed to be our last score.
Because of the Hood...
...we struck out.
Now we're down a man. Good thing
you're qualified to take his place.
[SCOFFS]
I think your convincing
is gonna have to be a lot more convincing.
Copy that. Cavanaugh.
[DOOR OPENS]
[CARLY GRUNTING]
DIGGLE:
Carly.
You son of a bitch.
- No, don't. Don't. Wait. Don't.
- Knox.
[MUFFLED SCREAMS]
You both can die tonight, John.
Or once we do this, we're on a plane
and she can go home to your nephew.
[OVER COMM]
It's your call.
[HORN HONKS]
Oh.
Come on, let's go. Ugh.
KNOX:
Oh, you shouldn't have done that, Dig.
Now you gotta watch us
kill your girlfriend.
- No, please don't.
DIGGLE: You're forgetting one thing, guys.
Oh, yeah? What's that?
I'm the one with the grenade launcher.
Carly, get out of there.
[GRUNTS]
[PANTS]
DIGGLE: Freeze!
- Oh.
[GASPS]
DIGGLE:
Drop it, Ted.
Or I swear...
Don't posture.
You're not gonna do it.
You can't. I can see it in your eyes.
- You're late.
- You knew I was coming?
DIGGLE: Next time you plant a bug
on someone, be more subtle about it.
- I wish you'd trusted me though.
- I trusted you.
But them, never.
[POLICE SIREN WAILING]
You should get out of here.
John.
Carly, are you okay?
OFFICER: Turn around
and put your hands where I can see them.
[CLUB MUSIC PLAYING ON RADIO]
[TIRES SCREECH]
[GLASS SHATTERS]
[WOMAN SPEAKING
INDISTINCTLY OVER PA]
Oh, Thea.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, yeah, I'm fine.
Just headachey, really.
- The car, is it...?
- The car isn't important right now.
[SIGHS]
Do you remember what happened,
sweetheart?
[SCOFFS]
Just go away.
- Thea, please.
- I said, I'm fine.
[PHONE RINGING]
[MAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY
ON TELEVISION]
Your father's even beginning
to call me now.
Don't waste your minutes.
[SIGHS]
Your father's a jerk,
but he's still your father.
I think, in his own way...
I think he sees himself
as protecting you somehow.
Yeah, he is really good
at using my dead mother...
...for an excuse for being a jerk.
You never talk about your mother.
I was only 8. I don't remember much
about what happened.
But after?
My father completely shut me out.
And then he went away.
He was gone for a year, maybe two.
I was 8 and he left me.
That is who my father is.
He only cares about himself.
- Cops give you a hard time?
DIGGLE: No.
I explained them that me and Gaynor were
old war buddies. He tried to rope me in...
[SIGHS]
When I refused, he kidnapped Carly,
everything else happened under duress.
[OLIVER SIGHS]
I screwed up, Oliver.
Obviously Gaynor wasn't
who I thought he was.
I was wrong.
Yeah, but you were right too.
When you told me that I trusted the list
more than I trusted you.
Diggle, the truth is,
after what happened to me on the island...
...it's difficult for me to trust anything.
But you do.
And that reminded me
why I chose you as my partner.
It's because you see the best in people.
I learned something too.
Until you tell me, I don't ever wanna know
what other names are in this book.
OLIVER:
She promised she's not cheating on Walter.
THEA: Like I would trust
anything that woman says.
OFFICER:
Miss Queen? Thea Queen?
- There a problem?
- We received a call from your doctor.
In the event of a vehicular accident,
they report the results of the tox-screen.
Ms. Queen tested positive
for a narcotic called Vertigo.
[SIGHS]
The drug they're using in the Glades?
OFFICER: Thea Queen, you are under arrest
for driving under the influence of narcotics.
Do you know why my men
wear balaclavas, Mr. Queen?
Because it masks everything
but the eyes.
And in a man's eyes,
one can always find the truth.
You risked everything
to save your friend.
Someone I warned you about...
...and yet you trusted him.
But that trust was misplaced.
[English - US - SDH]