If we don't get home soon,
the sitter's gonna charge us
an extra hour.
We should have taken the car.
Sitter's what, another 15 bucks
for half an hour?
It's a bargain at twice the price.
Lyla.
Dear God.
-Alan.
-Sorry to crash your evening.
Then don't. Just call like normal people.
I don't have a normal job.
And I've been compromised.
I'm not A.R.G.U.S. anymore.
Which makes you the only person
I can trust.
I need you to tell Waller...
-Get down!
-(GUNFIRE)
You're hit.
No!
Alan!
(GUNSHOTS)
-(GROANS)
-Johnnie!
Are you okay?
You were right.
We should've taken the car.
Just be careful. Slow down, slow down.
Careful, careful, careful...
Do you want me to be careful?
Oh, this is more Oliver 2.0, isn't it?
You think being cute
is going to distract me?
Mission accomplished.
(SIGHS) You don't have to wait on me
hand and foot.
Though I wouldn't say no to a blanket.
The doctor says
stick with the two tablets,
keep with your current
pain management regimen.
You know, I really appreciate
what you're doing,
but you have a city to save,
a mayoral campaign,
a freaky super-bad
who can move things with his mind.
None of which are nearly as important
as your recovery. Thank you.
(CHUCKLES) I think the people in the city
that Darhk wants to destroy
might disagree.
Well, those people should know
that I stand no chance
of stopping Damien Darhk
without your help.
Well, you might have to.
I have a spinal cord injury.
I might never make a full recovery ever.
That is worst case scenario.
And either way, you're still
a vital member of the team.
Your superpower is right there.
Maybe my new codename could be Hot Wheels.
Keep pitching on that.
All jokes aside, like you said,
what I do bring to the team is my mind
and there's a lot on it.
So talk to me.
I just don't think I'm ready
to come back yet,
and the last thing you need
in a life or limb situation is me.
Wow. We are going to agree to
disagree on that one for the moment.
-(PHONE RINGS)
-(CLEARS THROAT)
What's going on?
John and Lyla were attacked.
Oh, my God, are they okay?
John was shot. Flesh wound.
I should go see them.
We should go see them.
Nice try.
Dinner is in the fridge.
Reheat in the oven at 425 degrees.
I love you.
I love you, too.
And they just left you there?
Yeah, but not before
leaving me with this.
We are sure that this wasn't HIVE?
These men looked military.
Right. But you said
that Chang said he was compromised
and he specifically told you
to go and speak with Waller.
Knowing her, she had Alan
working on something off the books.
-I need to call the sitter.
-Okay.
We need to find Chang before this
kidnapping becomes something worse.
Yeah, well, the van didn't have
any plates on it.
And Chang's phone is A.R.G.U.S.-issued,
which means it'll be untraceable.
We could really use Felicity's help
right now.
Yeah, she's not up for it yet.
I can have SCPD see if John's bullet
is connected to any open cases.
Yeah.
I can go check the crime scene
for any leftover evidence.
You should go to Starling General
and have that looked at.
-I'll be fine.
-Why?
Because eating a cheeseburger
is a better option?
This isn't for me.
It's for Andy.
(GRUNTS)
Mmm. Mmm-hmm.
Hey, what happened to your arm?
Nothing. It's occupational hazard.
Right. I never pegged you
for the masked vigilante type.
Yeah, well, I guess
we're both full of surprises, Andy.
You know what?
You keep coming down here
asking me all these questions,
but I never get to ask them back.
-What do you wanna know?
-All right.
How do you end up working
out of a basement or wherever we are,
and fighting crime with a guy
who wears a green hoodie?
Well, he's a good man.
And we're not fighting crime, Andy.
We're taking a city that's holding
itself together and we are helping.
Don't you remember
when that was your mission?
Appreciate you two volunteering
for this mission.
A chance to ride with my little brother?
Wouldn't miss it.
Yeah, Taliban's not ready
for the Diggle brothers.
HQ's got eyes on a primo opium shipment
that's been funding the local arms trade.
We cut them off,
the terrorists will be left with nothing
but rocks and sticks to fight us.
Copy that, sir. You ready for this?
Incoming. Stay frosty, boys.
Copy that.
RPG!
-Perimeter!
-Go!
-(GUNFIRE)
-(GROANS)
Go, go! Move, move, move!
We're screwed if they come around
from the other side.
I'll see if I can buy us some time.
Move, move, move.
I can draw them to it.
Got your back.
Come on. Come on. Come on!
It's in.
Screw this! (GRUNTS)
Andy!
Hey!
Andy.
Talk to me, man. You okay?
Did we get them?
You got 'em, brother. Let's go.
WOMAN: Aww, why didn't I get invited
to this pity party?
Hello?
At least you found the right party favors.
Three pills is a bit much,
but who am I to judge?
Okay, whoever you are,
you picked the wrong woman
on the wrong night to mess with.
Please. We both know
you're in no position to do anything.
If you did you'd be back out in
the world instead of holed up here.
Oh, my God. What is going on? (EXHALES)
What is going on? Oh, my God. (LAUGHING)
Oh, my God, I am losing it.
I am completely and utterly losing it. Oh!
Now I am talking to myself.
Not exactly.
Laurel Lance, District Attorney's Office.
What do we have here?
Deceased male. Around 35. Asian.
Multiple lacerations, contusions
and blunt force trauma.
You canvass the area yet?
There could be a witness
who saw something.
I don't need an ADA
to tell me how to do my job.
Well, I'm sure
there's a murderer out there
who appreciates your lack of initiative.
Go ahead.
Private security found him
at the start of the graveyard shift.
That's Chang.
Whoever did this took their time.
Multiple lacerations to the knees,
a broken arm,
at least three pulled fingernails.
They were torturing him for something.
Information wasn't the only thing
they wanted.
I told you, what Agent Chang
was working on is none of your concern.
It's even less of yours.
Thought that would change
once you found out
that Chang was mutilated,
tortured and killed.
I'm afraid you've over-extended
your welcome, Mr. Diggle.
Which is A.R.G.U.S.-speak
for "get the hell out of here."
You always were a quick study.
I mean this with all sincerity,
your presence has truly been missed.
Even if I don't show it, I am deeply
regretful for Mr. Chang's death.
Hopefully we'll meet again
under happier circumstances.
Of course.
Hey, what was that look all about?
"Ketorolac. Possible side effects
include swelling of hands and feet,
"increased appetite, risk of infection..."
Oh. Good, good, good. "Hallucinations."
I really thought I was smarter than this.
You are not me
and you're definitely not real.
I used to be you. Or you used to be me.
Strong, confident, brunette.
But you wasted all that away
to go play super-hero.
And look where that got you.
Okay, so wait, this Waller person said
that she couldn't tell you anything
and then gave you that flash drive?
A.R.G.U.S. has 24/7 internal surveillance.
She didn't want anyone to know
she was giving me what she was giving me.
The question is, what did she give you?
I've seen that symbol before.
LYLA: It's a logo, actually.
Shadowspire is a US Army
Special Forces unit.
A.R.G.U.S. took them down three years ago
when they were exposed as war profiteers.
In an op run by Alan Chang.
What about those other two guys?
LYLA: They've been reported missing
for two days.
If those were the missing agents
that were part of Shadowspire...
Then the rest of Shadowspire's
gonna be on a payback mission.
We need to find the other two agents
before they end up like Alan.
Hey, I think I found something.
That logo that was on the flash drive
that Waller gave you.
Shadowspire.
Thought I recognized that from some place.
I ran into a lot of those guys
back in the 'Stan.
I need to talk to my brother again.
You wouldn't think the reward
for confiscating an opium shipment
would be additional duty guarding it.
What'd you expect?
A kiss from the President?
How are my two conquering heroes?
-Wet and tired.
-We are good, sir.
-You gentlemen did good today.
-Thank you, sir.
You ever think of your future
beyond working in this hell hole?
I don't know.
Personal security, body guarding maybe?
You boys are meant for better things.
The three of us could make bank if a few
bricks of that sweet Afghani powder
happened to go AWOL before the morning.
You know, I'm gonna have to decline, sir.
My mama taught me
never to trust dirty war profiteers.
You should probably watch your tone.
You might end up in worse shape
than those Talis yesterday.
As you were.
-Well, look at you.
-What you talking about?
Back in Starling,
you would have jumped at any opportunity
to earn a little extra scratch.
This place has been good for you.
Proud of you, Andy.
So exactly how many evil organizations
are you associated with?
I'm beginning to lose count.
What are you talking about?
Shadowspire. Your old army buddies
are in Starling City.
They tortured and killed an A.R.G.U.S.
agent and abducted two others.
Look, I have nothing to do
with them anymore.
After I get discharged, they cut ties.
They only want enlisted men.
How the hell could I not see this?
You were with me the entire time!
Because you saw what you wanted to see!
Look, you wanted to believe
that the Army had straightened me out.
Look, I'm your brother,
but I'm not built like you.
I didn't take to the military
like you did.
You saw the world
as something to be fixed.
I only saw it as broken.
So I made sure
I had enough to survive in it.
So you pretended to be
a completely different person
around your own brother?
Spare me the look
that's on your face right now.
But maybe some good
could come out of this.
Andy.
What are you talking about?
Two missing agents.
You still think they're alive?
-I can hope.
-And I can help.
Look, I know how Shadowspire operates.
If they're consistent,
they'll use the nearest free port
as a base of operations.
The best place to hide illicit things
is right next to legitimate ones.
SPARTAN: It's called a free port.
Holds commodities while they're in transit
between international destinations.
Pretty low-end.
Looks like somebody
upgraded their security system.
Motion sensors, laser trip wires,
digital locks.
I think I know somebody who can help.
(PHONE RINGS)
Not gonna get that? Smart move.
Oliver?
GREEN ARROW:
I'm out in the field, actually.
We've come up against some tech.
The kind that you typically eat
for breakfast.
Now, I know that you said you're not
ready to get back in the saddle,
but we could really use your help.
You're not really falling for that again,
are you?
Where are you?
Pacific Freeport, it's a...
Security's down.
That was amazing.
All you need to do
is to get back in the game.
I thought "vomiting inside my mouth"
was just an expression.
I'm inside their security system.
I got eyes on seven
very menacing-looking fellows
guarding a bunch of holding containers.
Reading infrared in one of the containers.
I'm working on opening that lock.
Go for the hostages.
We'll take care of Shadowspire.
Container's open.
Should be 10 feet in front of you,
second container on your right.
Got it.
(GROANS)
BLACK CANARY:
We found the two A.R.G.U.S. agents.
They're both dead.
-Get out of here then.
-What about you and Spartan?
We got this! Go!
Felicity, what's going on?
I don't know. I...
I must have tripped some sort of failsafe.
The system's overloaded
with too many requests.
(CHUCKLES) Oopsie.
You hear so much about these vigilantes,
but I've never seen one in person.
Wish I could say the same
about a cold-blooded murderer.
Have we met before?
Let's go.
I've got Spartan. We're good.
No thanks to you.
Hey.
You okay?
That depends. Is John okay?
John's fine.
But you seem to think that
what happened tonight is your fault.
Well, I'm pretty sure I was the one
who couldn't stop the security doors
from closing.
And I'm the one who pushed you
to get involved
when you signaled pretty hard
that you weren't ready.
I wasn't signaling
that hard.
I'm sorry that I pushed.
I just thought
that if you got behind a keyboard again,
that things would just start
to feel normal.
I love how playing super-hero
is what we consider normal.
(CHUCKLES) Yeah.
But there is no going back to normal.
-You know what I mean.
-I know what you mean.
What I mean is that
I can no longer be a part of the team.
Because of your injury?
You can't let that stop you.
Except it has.
Look at me, Oliver.
I've spent the last week and a half
stuck in this loft.
I can't move, I can't drive, I can't walk
down the street and get a cup of coffee.
And if tonight is any indication,
I can't do the one thing
that I'm supposed to still be able to do.
You just need to give it time.
Hey, talk to me.
Go ahead, tell him.
Tell him you're hallucinating.
That should go over like gangbusters.
I'm not going to pretend
that I understand...
Come on, Felicity, tell him.
...what you're going through.
Tell him that you're no good
for the team anymore.
That in addition
to having legs that don't work,
you've got a full on case of the crazies.
-We don't stand a chance to take down...
-Hearing voices, seeing visions...
Would you just shut up!
-I didn't mean that.
-I didn't mean to upset you.
No, no, no, it's not you, it's not you.
Can I just be alone for a little while?
You know, I guessed I hoped
by giving you intel on Shadowspire,
you would let me out of my cell.
But this isn't what I had in mind.
Hey, Lyla. It's been a while.
Andy.
Mr. Diggle. I'm the director of A.R.G.U.S.
Those three dead men were my agents.
I wanna debrief you
on your relationship to Shadowspire.
Which is interesting
because you couldn't even
say "Shadowspire" last time we met.
I was taking an understandable precaution
in light of a potential security breach.
The two agents you found tonight
were assigned
to safeguard a shipment
of confiscated railguns.
(ANDY SNICKERS)
But that was a completely
black assignment.
So I'd be very interested to know
how Shadowspire knew about it.
Amanda, you don't see
the bigger problem here?
Those things fire off
electromagnetic projectiles.
Just one of them
could take down a building.
Your point?
My point is that if Shadowspire's
looking for that type of ordnance...
I'm far more concerned
with a catastrophic security breach
in my organization, Mr. Diggle.
ANDY: It doesn't matter.
Shadowspire's not after railguns.
And what if you're wrong, Andy?
We thought you weren't hooked up
with Shadowspire anymore.
I'm not. But I know the way they work.
Shadowspire is all about misdirection.
An elite military unit?
A cover for a criminal organization.
A heist of a shipment of railguns?
No. Distraction.
They're after something else.
(GRUNTS)
You wanna talk about it?
What is there to talk about?
Felicity's upset,
I don't know how to help her,
it seems entirely straightforward.
As the only other person here
who's had the privilege of dating you,
a piece of advice?
Okay.
Don't be so hard on yourself.
Everything that's happening is my fault.
I knew you were gonna say that.
Last month, when we went up
against Vandal Savage,
Barry traveled through time
and changed things.
-What?
-Barry can travel through time.
And he warned me
that when you change the past,
the past fights back.
So for the past month,
I have been tortured by the idea
that what happened to Felicity
might have happened
because I wouldn't listen to him.
The only person who is responsible
for what happened to Felicity
is Damien Darhk.
-(PHONE VIBRATES)
-(SIGHS)
John. We're on it.
John thinks Shadowspire's going after
a shipment of railguns.
-Can you call Thea?
-Got it.
Hey, Oliver.
Felicity, she makes her own choices,
you know.
And I'm sure that's one of the reasons
why you love her so much.
Wow. The Shining.
Not sure if I should be flattered,
or insulted.
Oh, my God! God, just go away already.
Since I'm you,
that could be a little difficult,
don't you think?
Fine. I'm here. You're here.
So why are we here?
Do you have anything
the least bit interesting to say to me
besides these little jabs you keep making?
Well, those jabs
were just to get your attention.
So what do you wanna tell me?
I'm not here to tell you anything.
I'm here to show you.
The last time we looked like this,
Cooper had just fake died.
What does this have to do
with my ex-boyfriend?
The day we thought he died,
you broke out the hair dye,
ditched the contacts and decided
you weren't gonna rely on anyone else
for help ever again.
It was just going to be you
against the world,
and that was going to be your armor.
Guess I should've chosen Kevlar.
Stop it. Stop feeling sorry for yourself!
And stop pretending!
-Pretending?
-Pretending that this is the real you.
The blonde hair, glasses,
sensible fashion.
People wear masks for a reason.
To hide who they are.
Just like you have been doing
for the past five years.
First you decided to sign up for being
the world's most overqualified IT girl,
and then you decide to try being a hero.
And look what it got you.
A ringside seat to the rest of your life.
You thought you were such a badass.
So Waller says the shipment of railguns
is in the back of that truck.
Moving out in less than an hour.
What does Shadowspire want
with a whole shipment of railguns?
Absolutely nothing good.
It's nice to have you back,
Agent Michaels.
Feels like old times.
What feels like old times
is you keeping secrets
that get good people killed.
Did it ever occur to you that Alan and
the other two agents might still be alive
if you hadn't tried to keep your
anti-Shadowspire operations off the books?
Of course it has.
But the ugly side of our business
is that sometimes
security has to be paid for in blood.
Thank you. I was wondering why I'd left.
I don't know
what you're worried about, man.
Your team's not seeing action tonight.
Yeah, and I'm not with them
because I'm here babysitting you.
Where are they?
Something's wrong.
There's no movement on the railgun...
-(GUNFIRE)
-(GLASS SHATTERING)
Put your hands up! On your head now!
Don't do it!
Amanda. It's been ages.
Lieutenant Joyner.
Wish I could say it was a pleasure.
C'mon, man, stop moving.
You are making me dizzy.
Oh, my God.
I told you, John.
The railguns were a distraction.
A.R.G.U.S. is the endgame.
If this is retribution for the work Agent
Chang and I did crippling Shadowspire,
clearly it didn't take.
Vengeance and retribution
are useless pursuits.
For one thing, they don't pay.
I'm here for Rubicon.
And you, you're gonna give me
the codes to access it.
You know I can't do that.
I do.
That's why I kept all these people alive.
-(GUNSHOTS)
-(GROANS)
I'm gonna give you 20 minutes.
And then,
I'm gonna ask you again.
Damn it. They must have jammers in here.
No cell or Wi-Fi service.
Uh, would you like to share
with the rest of the class?
These monitors work just like TVs.
Receiving broadcast signals
from the 700 MHz band.
I have a friend who's into
this kind of stuff.
Occasionally, I listen to her.
If I can just switch the chipset
into transmitting mode,
I should be able to contact my team.
Oh, man, Lyla does not have time to wait
on your team. We've gotta do something.
Yeah, well,
you're not doing anything, Andy.
Look, man, your wife is in there!
Now is not the time to not trust me!
Come on, come on, come on.
Son of a bitch.
Hey.
What, you just putting on
a little show for me, huh?
Get your hands off of me, man.
What's wrong with you?
I see you buddying it up with Joyner.
Talking to him thick as thieves.
Would you relax?
We were talking about blackjack.
I was telling him about the card counting
technique you taught me.
-Really, Andy?
-Yeah, really.
Okay, man.
'Cause I can't have you backsliding,
all right?
Man, I agreed to go through
this whole army thing.
And I kept my end of the bargain.
Now I need you to keep yours.
And I need you to start treating me
like a brother and not like a criminal.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
You're right.
John, Shadowspire never made a move
on the shipment,
so whatever their next move is, it...
It's not railguns.
Just call me when you get something
new from your brother. All right.
Oh.
I am so glad
our new lair has elevator access.
Hi.
Curtis has anointed himself
my personal chauffeur.
Fancy. It's a good thing
he didn't ask too many questions
about coming to your campaign office
in the middle of the night.
What are you doing here?
Well, I was at home
feeling more self-pity than I have
in my entire life when it hit me.
This is who I am.
I wanted to come along
on your awesome superhero adventure
because I wanted to help people.
And the old me was so angry at the world.
That anger never accomplished anything,
it just created more anger.
And some seriously bad
personal style choices.
I wanted to do some good in the world.
(CHUCKLES)
-Ow.
-That was a good speech.
Thought you'd be a little more impressed.
It was a good speech. But...
But... How did it go again?
I know you, and I do,
you're probably thinking
what happened was your fault.
I'm here to tell you that it's not.
And that it's not mine either.
It's the fault of only one man
and he has an extremely on-the-nose
and alliterative name.
And we're going to stop him.
Not out of guilt or vengeance or regret.
We are going to stop him
because it's what we do.
It's who we are.
-That was a good speech.
-Yeah?
I'm very happy to hear it.
We're gonna need to get some ramps.
A.R.G.U.S. has been compromised.
And Lyla's being held hostage.
Found this in your office.
Hope you don't mind.
Lieutenant, we've picked up
an unauthorized comm
out of the detention area.
Take someone and look into it.
Yes, sir.
Go on.
You might not get the chance
to enjoy it again.
It's been 20 minutes.
I'm gonna have to downsize
your organization yet again?
Apparently.
Well, that's rather cold blooded.
You really don't know her
that well at all, do you?
Ms. Michaels was one
of my most trusted agents.
She knows better than anyone
that I'm perfectly capable
of watching you execute
every person in this room,
and I'll still never give you
the Rubicon access codes.
Is that right, Ms. Michaels?
It's right. It's why I left.
Amanda Waller doesn't make decisions
based on the value of human life.
Pity.
No!
Well, Ms. Michaels, most trusted agent,
looks like you now have 20 minutes.
John.
My God, no.
Wait, wait a minute. John. John. John.
John, please! He's going to kill her.
You can't afford not to trust me.
-Overwatch, we're onsite.
-Excuse me?
Well, I thought that it was time
you got a codename. What do you think?
It's perfect.
I was gonna go with Oracle,
but it's taken.
Shadowspire's got the entire area
around C-and-C in lockdown.
You guys are the only game in town.
Can you get us inside?
Like that, you mean?
Well, it's about time
you guys came looking.
Who the hell are you supposed to be?
Sergeant Andrew Diggle,
52nd Regiment, 5th Battalion.
-What are you doing locked up here?
-It's a long story.
Shorter version being my brother's a jerk.
Lucky for me, though,
your CO and I go way back.
If you're serious about Lyla Michaels
giving up the Rubicon codes,
you will get on the radio
and tell Lieutenant Joyner
the guy that taught him how to count cards
is here and wants to help him out.
Andy Diggle.
You look pretty good for a dead man.
And here, I thought I'd put on weight.
What are you doing at A.R.G.U.S.,
much less alive?
Amanda Waller brought me in because
of my former association with you guys,
but, small world, though.
Your friend, Ms. Michaels?
She's my sister-in-law.
-Andy...
-Point being,
her husband is crawling around
these ventilation shafts right now.
If you put a gun on him,
she'll tell you whatever you need to know.
You son of a...
Turning on your own brother,
that's ice cold.
Now, you know better than most.
John and I never saw eye to eye.
Gentlemen, check the facility's
ventilation shafts.
Overwatch?
FELICITY: C-and-C three floors down.
Northeast corner.
That'll give us a few minutes.
(ALL GRUNTING)
(DIGGLE GRUNTING)
The other Diggle brother.
Isn't this quaint?
I get out of these cuffs and you'll see
how quaint you think I can be.
It's a shame you can't be
more like the little Diggle.
His pragmatism has proven to be
quite the asset.
Now, if your brother's right,
you should be able to convince your wife
to give me what I want.
Johnnie, if Rubicon ever got out
in the open...
Ms. Michaels, in five seconds,
it's your husband's brains
that will be out in the open.
Four, three, two...
Do it. Do it, Lyla.
It's all right.
Excellent.
If you've run out of guys to punch,
Spartan needs an assist.
Two assists, actually.
Tell us what to do.
Shadowspire's getting the access codes
for a secure vault in the sub-level.
I'm trying to stop the codes from working,
but I'm going to need Canary and Speedy
as my insurance policies.
Where do you want me?
This is taking too long.
Something's wrong.
Someone's locking me out of the system.
Go away. I'm not you anymore.
I haven't been for a long time.
(SIGHS)
I can't get in. I have all the right codes
but someone on the outside is preventing
me from entering the sub-level vault.
That's extremely unfortunate.
-You okay?
-Yeah.
-Yeah, we're fine.
Good job.
Yeah, it was like you said,
it was the only way
to get us both in here.
Just remember whose idea this was.
What were you expecting,
a kiss from the President?
To Amanda Waller.
You remember that time that she tried
to take down the city with a drone strike?
Good times.
Hey, thanks for the assist tonight.
I was just glad to be useful.
Good job jury-rigging
the security system, though.
Just trying to make you proud, Felicity.
You did.
What are you gonna do about Andy?
Still haven't made a decision on that.
You mean even though
he just saved your life?
Yeah, well, you guys had a whole lot
to do with that.
But, you're right,
this is the first time in eight years
I've seen shades of my old brother.
You wanted to see me, sir?
I already got my cut.
Yeah, it's a token of appreciation
from the boss.
He traded the opium for something else.
Like what?
Ask him yourself.
Thank you for your assistance, Mr. Diggle.
Lieutenant Joyner sings your praises.
Happy to help.
What did you get for the opium?
Legend speaks
of a place of immeasurable power.
Many have disappeared searching for it.
So much so that the locals
simply refer to it by one word.
Purgatory.
I thought we were totally unpacked.
Just humor me.
What am I getting?
Uh, yes, that white box. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You ready?
-Wow!
-(LAUGHING)
When you said that you made
some bad personal style choices,
you weren't kidding.
This is the old me.
A rebellious, brunette hacker who didn't
listen to anyone else's rules but her own.
You're not that person anymore?
Nope.
What you did last night was amazing.
I was really badass.
Yeah.
Though the old me probably would have
stolen the plans for Rubicon
and released them
as some sort of political statement.
The old me
would have snapped Joyner's neck.
Yeah.
We've both grown.
Thank you for always being on my side.
No place I'd rather be.
Hand me that garbage can and this lighter.
(CLEARS THROAT)
How much medication are you on?
Absolutely none.
Okay.
I just wanna make sure
that my past stays the past, you know?
Goodbye.
-One more thing from me.
-What?
The doctor said
your condition is permanent.
And I don't think that it's healthy
or productive for either of us
to live in denial.
But I have seen people speed
and shrink and fly.
We watched a friend of ours
come back from the dead.
That is the world that we live in now.
And I will not stop searching it
until we find a way
to make you walk again.
Hey.
Are you sure about this? 'Cause I'm not.
Better than being in that cage, right?
You might wanna wait outside,
I have it from here.
Make yourself comfortable.
Lyla's cooking something.
Hey.
If this is about reconnecting
with Carly and Andy as well, I, um...
I get it, Andy. Step by step, right?
-Andy.
-Hey.
I'm making pork roast.
Johnnie said it's your favorite.
Yeah. Yeah, it is.
We've got another surprise for you, man.
Just a second.
-Hey, Lyla, I...
-Not a word.
John and I both agreed to this.
She's excited to meet you.
This is your niece.
Hey.
Sara. And that's your uncle Andy.
-(WHIMPERS)
-Yeah.
She's got Mom's eyes.
Welcome home, man.