My name is Oliver Queen.
For five years, I was stranded
on an island with only one goal:
- Survive.
- Oliver Queen is alive.
Now I will fulfill
my father's dying wish...
...to use the list of names he left me...
...and bring down those
who are poisoning my city.
To do this, I must become someone else.
I must become something else.
Previously on Arrow:
- Mom?
- What are you doing here?
- I believe Sara's still alive.
- You don't actually have any proof.
I have proof.
Doesn't it look just like Sara?
I did manage to find one thing.
I want to get out.
Malcolm Merlyn.
I want you to kill him for me.
If we have a traitor in our midst,
he just made his last mistake.
Lawyers for John Nickel
spoke to the press today.
They say they're pleased the DA declined
to indict their client on charges...
...stemming from the recent fire
in one of Nickel's buildings.
Nickel is one of the wealthiest
real estate developers in Starling City.
He's also one of the dirtiest.
That building that burnt down last night,
the wiring was not up to code.
- Maybe he didn't know.
- He didn't know about the seven people...
...who have frozen to death
in his other buildings.
Yeah, he's a real man of the people.
Not for long.
The DA ignores this
and the police can't do anything...
...because all these
slums are in the Glades.
So tonight, Felicity,
we cross Mr. Nickel's name off the list.
You okay with that?
The scene outside of
the courtroom where Nickel was released...
- ...was, not surprisingly, tense.
- One hundred percent.
- He was just gone?
- No, not gone. Taken.
Looks like Nickel was on
somebody else's list.
After the fire last night,
it's not entirely surprising.
Felicity, get everything
that you can on Nickel.
Focus on his tenants, anyone who might have
filed a formal complaint against him...
- ...or people that lost something in the fire.
- It's gonna be some list.
Slumlords aren't generally known
for their popularity. Plus...
- What?
- Nothing. It's just...
You went over there to be all,
"Grr, stop being bad or I'll arrow you."
Now you want to rescue him?
I don't like the idea
that somebody dangerous is out there.
Somebody else.
Because typically...
...they don't show my level of restraint.
- So you're gonna cross Nickel off anyway?
- No.
I'm finding somebody else
who needs a talking-to.
You're going out there again, Oliver?
- Go be with your family.
- That's when the work is done.
- Okay, I'll take you out to dinner.
- I'm not hungry.
I'm not asking.
Simple exchange.
You get us off the island,
we'll give you the circuit board...
...so your missile launcher
isn't just furniture.
You've grown up quite a bit, Mr. Queen.
I'll give you that.
I can get you a boat.
But I need time.
You got an hour,
Fyers, and then you're never...
What?
It might take you longer
than an hour to get a boat.
What we mean is you need
to move with some dispatch.
Oh, Wilson, still in command there, eh?
I thought your little pet
had staged a coup d'e'tat.
Just get us the damn boat.
I got a fatal heart
I'm tied to the living
Got a tortured soul
I can't give it away
Gonna find a line
- Oh, now you wanna stop?
- Well, we don't all have butlers.
Some of us actually
have to answer our own doors.
Oh, the horror.
You look familiar.
I see you on TV or something?
- Probably. I'm Thea Queen.
- Heh. Yeah, right.
Did you get it?
Tomorrow night.
Joe wants us there at 11 p.m.
He said to be on time, Harper.
I'd say I told you so
But I know you never listen
What's happening tomorrow at 11?
I'm actually focused on
what's happening right now.
- Oh, okay.
- Yeah.
No, no, Thea, don't.
- No.
- Why do you have a gun?
Because I'm no good with knives.
Look, it's just a liquor store. The guy's a creep.
Trust me, he deserves it.
Look, if it'll make you feel any better...
...I won't be armed.
The owner won't know that but...
I got you a job at my brother's club.
You have choices.
You don't have to be a criminal.
I'm not talking about phone bills.
I owe people.
People with much bigger guns than this.
Look, here in the Glades...
...this is pretty much the only solution.
No, lots of people in the Glades
live honest lives.
Obviously not you.
- You're just a waste.
- Thea. Thea.
- Let me make sure you get home okay.
- Don't bother.
Yeah. Mm-hm.
Yeah.
- Yeah.
- Hey, honey.
Here you go.
What's all this?
Well, you asked me to look
into your mother's leads on Sara...
...so I made some calls.
It looks like you did a lot more than that.
You're the one that said
we should do this, Laurel.
If there's a chance your sister...
- Yeah, but...
- Thank you.
Hi, sweetheart, I'm sorry about the mess.
Quentin, I just got off the phone
with the consulate in Phuket.
The secretary there's gonna run
Sara's photo against their database...
- ...see if there's a match.
- That's good work.
What?
Well, I guess I just thought deep down that
you were going to help Mom accept things.
Things you and I accepted.
Um...
Yeah, but you got to admit...
- ...this girl, she looks a lot like Sara.
- Sara had that same cap.
The Starling City Rockets.
Your dad bought it, remember?
Yeah, I remember.
- Stranger things have happened.
- Yeah. I can see that.
Hungrier than I thought.
Are you waiting for me to finish
before giving me the lecture?
You've been spending a lot of time
under that hood.
Keeps my ears warm.
And you've made this decision
to avoid entanglements?
For their protection.
The people who get close to me get hurt.
What's the problem?
Do you think I'm losing my grip?
No, it's just the opposite, really.
You seem calm.
Scary calm.
Things didn't end well with Helena,
with McKenna...
With Laurel.
With Sara.
- The list goes on.
- Yeah. But what do you do?
You hood up, you go home, you repeat.
Not much of a life.
The life that I'm leading for myself
doesn't leave much room for an actual life.
- And I don't need one.
- Wow.
That's a pretty bleak future
you plan on spending with no one.
- I'm used to isolation.
- And that is exactly what worries me.
You've been home for eight months, Oliver,
but I don't think you left that island yet.
What the hell is going on?
- Yeah?
- I found Nickel. Click the link I sent you.
This came up on every screen with
an IP address originating from the Glades.
If you make the Glades your home...
you know who this man is. John Nickel.
He owns your tenements,
manages your slums.
He provides the leaking roofs
over your heads...
...the lead in your pipes,
the asbestos in your walls.
Basically, he makes money
off of our suffering.
But the police aren't
interested in helping us.
They may have let us down, but I won't.
John, I want to give you the chance
to state your case.
Why shouldn't you be punished?
I knew there was bad stuff in my buildings.
Track him, Felicity.
- I'm looking.
- Okay, yes, I made a little profit.
At least they had a place to live.
Without me, people like that
would end up on the street.
"People like that."
That's all we are to guys like this.
John...
...I find you guilty.
There are plenty more people who need
to answer for their crimes against us.
So who's next?
Anything new?
This guy's got more than
a subscription to Wired.
His website's protected
by serious encryption.
Use that air magnet thing.
Oliver, no offense, but do I tell you
how to sharpen your arrows?
Spoke to my friend at the NSA.
The website code matches
a cyber crusader on their radar.
He hacks into fringe sites
under the user name The Savior.
He's a former resident of the Glades.
- Former?
- Yeah, a year ago...
...he hacked himself right off the radar.
Erased all traces of his existence.
- So, what happened a year ago?
- We're back.
I have with me Assistant District Attorney
Gavin Carnahan.
Now, DAs are supposed to go after bad guys.
But this one can't even be bothered
to bring them to trial.
Like the ones who killed my wife
in a bodega.
- Felicity?
- I'm on it.
You said there wasn't enough evidence.
You think evidence would have turned up
if she'd been killed...
...in one of Starling City's
nicer neighborhoods?
Emma Falk. Husband is Joseph Falk.
- What do we have on him?
- Not much, 42, former city worker.
Department of Transportation,
computer technician.
Left his job when she was killed.
One year ago today.
- No current phone, no current address.
- Gavin, you're a lawyer.
You're used to making a case. So go ahead.
I'm gonna give you 10 minutes to deliver
the closing argument of your life.
- Come on.
- Trying to get a lock on his signal.
Ten minutes to convince me
not to blow you away.
What did Malcolm want with you
at the hospital?
A target for reprisal.
He wants justice and he's not going to stop
until he gets it.
Besides, this is good.
I think your definition of good
requires an adjustment.
No, he came to me.
Which means he doesn't know that we're
responsible for the attempt on his life.
Yet.
What are the chances
of Malcolm discovering...
...who paid the Triad to assassinate him?
I was discreet. I wired the money...
...through a shell corporation I own
from an offshore account.
Offshore. Good. That's good.
I'm sending Amanda to London
for a few weeks. Just as a precaution.
Perhaps you should do
the same for your family.
There's nothing I wouldn't do
to protect my children, Frank.
Can I talk to you about something?
Almost-woman to woman?
I'm really busy right now.
Okay.
Thea.
Sorry. What's up?
I could use some advice.
I'm sort of dating this guy who could
definitely be described as a bad boy.
And I figured, as someone who's dated
like a gajillion of them...
I haven't dated a gajillion.
All right, guilty as charged.
You want my advice?
- Run. As fast as you possibly can.
- Yeah. That was my first instinct too, but...
Laurel? The Chinese embassy's on line two.
I'm transferring them over.
- Chinese embassy?
- It's just this case that I'm working on.
But we are definitely continuing
this conversation later.
Thank you so much for getting back to me.
I'm trying to track down the woman
in the photo that I e-mailed you.
You did.
Really?
And you're sure
that she's in the States now?
Do you happen to have an address on her?
- I got him!
- Shut it down.
Can't. He has a firewall.
He's working off an IPX at 23rd and Mira.
- You gonna hood up?
- It's the middle of the day.
Look! Listen! Listen to me, okay?
I have 53 cases on my desk right now.
- I don't always have time...
- You should have made time.
- How's Carnahan?
- Not making a persuasive argument.
I'm almost there.
- See anything?
- I'm only on the first floor.
- Just six more to go.
- There aren't resources.
I tried. Sorry! I'm sorry.
Oliver, hurry.
Can't find him!
- He's not here, Felicity.
- What?
I searched every office on every floor!
He's not here. Is this the right place?
- Are you sure?
- Yeah, I...
- Oh, crap.
- What?
How is this possible?
This can't happen. He's...
- Talk to me!
- Wait.
- He moved. Ocean and Grand.
- On my way!
I took on cases that were...
That I thought I could...
- Win.
- Yes.
I'm sorry.
Gavin Carnahan, I find you guilty
of crimes against the Glades.
- Don't do this! Don't do this!
- I sentence you to death.
I'm at Ocean and Grand,
and it's just a vacant lot.
How is this possible? He's...
- Find the right address now!
- He's...
He's...
Oliver, it's over. Carnahan is dead.
Where's Diggle?
I asked him to leave me alone.
In my loud voice.
This wasn't your fault.
I was the one who was supposed
to find Carnahan...
...and I was the one who sent you
to that bogus location.
I've never seen anybody die.
Hey, this is the thing with what we do.
Sometimes we lose.
Maybe it is better being alone.
I'm not seeing anyone currently...
...but if I were,
I don't know how I'd tell him about today.
Gentlemen. Welcome.
So happy we're able to reach an accord.
Oh, good. Small talk.
Are we gonna get on with this?
As you wish. Straight to business.
- Circuit board. Where is it?
- Somewhere safe.
So get us to the boat
and then we'll tell you where it is.
And, of course,
you'll be honest about its location.
Well, I wouldn't be.
But this one's got some strange hang-up
about principles and integrity.
Hmm. I always imagined as much.
Which is why I'd like to make
a counterproposal. Men!
No.
- No!
- Hey!
Deliver back to me the circuit board
or I will kill Yao Fei's daughter.
So I wouldn't leave.
I can't imagine you want the death of
an innocent young woman on your hands.
Not with your principles.
- Hey.
Hi.
I wanted to do some research
on my own...
...into the evidence
that you gathered on Sara...
...so I called my friend from law school
who works at the Chinese embassy and...
The photo of the girl.
- I found her.
- I'm sorry. Can I borrow your phone?
I promised my fiance
that I'd call him before dinner.
Jenn, these are my parents.
Hi. Nice to meet you.
Yeah, you too.
I told Jenn about this photograph
that popped up in this case...
...that I'm working on.
- That's you in the picture?
- Yeah.
I spent six months
on an island off the coast of China.
That was taken in a small fishing village
named Zhengjiu.
- It's Mandarin for...
- Salvation.
- Are you all right, Mrs. Lance?
- Yes, I...
It's just, uh, you look like someone
I used to know.
Wow.
I was waiting for this.
Waiting for what?
For the whole "you can change,
I see the real you" speech.
Look around, Thea.
This is home sweet home for me.
You starve or do things
that mean you're lucky to make it to 21.
- I can't accept that.
- No, you can't accept me.
- Roy Harper?
- Yeah?
- Unh!
- Roy!
More on the story out of the Glades.
The kidnapper seems to have another victim
and is broadcasting the feed to his website.
A warning to viewers, this is live footage,
so we 're not sure what we're about to see.
Meet Roy Harper.
Arrests, larceny, robbery,
aggravated assault.
Yet you're out on the street.
Another gangbanger
in the Glades running free...
...like the ones who killed my wife.
I grew up in the Glades too,
and it didn't turn me into a criminal.
- I know that kid.
- How?
- Ollie?
- Tommy?
Oh, God, no.
I didn't know where else to go.
- You know him?
- Roy. He's my friend.
We were in a fight and some guy...
...just attacked us.
He doesn't deserve to die.
I promise you he's gonna be okay.
You stay here with Tommy, all right?
- Hello?
- It's Malcolm.
I've learned a high-ranking member
of the Triad was arrested.
- I should have a word with him.
- I already have.
He's agreed to find out who hired
his organization...
...to assassinate me
in return for a reduced prison sentence.
Tonight we should know the name or names
of the people who tried to kill me.
Good.
- What are you doing?
- So it's not Sara in the photo.
But she's still out there, Quentin,
and I'm going to find her.
Look, I understand now
that neither of you have the stomach...
...to continue looking for her.
And that's fine.
I'm sorry I involved you both.
You know that I would cross to hell
and back to bring her home.
But I can't! Because she's gone, Di.
- No.
- You gotta let go of this now.
No. I can't. I won't.
How did you know Sara had her hat
with her when she went on the boat?
You were so sure
that the girl in the photo was Sara...
...not because she was American
but because of her hat.
Her Starling City Rockets hat
that Dad bought her.
Mom...
...how did you know...
...she took her hat with her
on the Queen's Gambit with Oliver?
I saw her.
- What do you mean?
- I came home early that day...
...and I saw her.
Sara.
I saw her put the hat in a bag.
- She was packing.
- You knew she was going with him?
I told her not to. I told her not to do this.
Not to you, Laurel.
But she said she was in love
and she had to follow her heart.
Even if nobody else thought it was right.
Just like I had told her...
Just like I told her I once did.
So I let her go.
I killed her.
I killed my daughter.
I killed her. I'm so sorry, Quentin.
I'm so sorry, Quentin. I killed our baby.
- Anything?
- I've been going through the video...
...to see if there's anything
that'll tell us where this guy is.
I got nothing except a sound.
Buried in the ambient noise.
Almost rhythmic. I've isolated it.
What is that? Sounds like a car
driving over lane markers.
It has to be bigger than a car.
- Bigger than a car? What, a bus?
- No.
I know this.
I know it.
Come on, guys.
Felicity, show me a map.
Sites of the abductions
and where we've seen the signal so far.
Right there, right there.
23rd and Mira, Locksley and Adams...
...Wells Street down by CNRI.
- Those are all subway stops.
- Starling City doesn't have a subway.
They used to. My dad used to take me
to the Rockets game by subway.
I'd lean against the window
feeling the rhythm of the train.
- That's how he did it.
- What?
He was at 23rd and Mira,
but he was underground.
He used to work
for the Department of Transportation.
That's why he knows all the subway stops.
That's why I couldn't trace the signal.
- Where is he now?
- He's on the old crosstown line.
He'll be at the Spring Street stop
in 15 minutes.
Let the girl go.
No deal? Very well.
- Kill her.
- No!
Well, that was unexpected.
Slade!
Come on! Come on!
Get her to safety. Now!
I will only slow you down. Go!
- Papa.
- Go! You've got to go!
Go!
It's happening-
I'll give you 10 minutes
to state your case, Roy.
So tell us, why do you get to live?
I shouldn't. Just do it.
Kill me.
Go on! Kill me!
You really don't care if you live or die?
No one's gonna miss me.
I'm just a waste.
Well, then, we agree on something.
This world will be better
off without you in it.
We seem to have lost the feed.
We will stay on the story and keep you
up to date on any developments.
Let the kid go.
If you kill this kid,
he'll never get an opportunity to change.
You can give him a second chance.
We're the only ones who can save this city.
- We can't stop now.
- We're not the same!
You've killed people
for this city. So have I.
What's the difference between you and me?
Emma never got a second chance.
You have no idea how lonely it is.
Joseph. Joseph!
I understand being alone.
But it doesn't give you the right
to kill people in cold blood.
He deserves it.
Just like the gangbangers who gunned
her down. He's no different.
- And now I get to gun him down.
- Don't do it!
I better get going to the airport.
That red-eye to Central City.
I should be home in a flash.
Mom.
Call me sometime.
I'd really like that.
- You would?
- Of course I would.
You're my mother.
- I love you so much.
- I love you too.
It's a fine day
People open windows
- I thought you were gonna die.
- That makes two of us.
I probably look like a mess.
I'm gonna go to the bathroom
and freshen way, way up.
Okay.
It's a fine day
People open windows
Ollie?
Hi.
Hey. I heard Thea's friend was okay.
Yeah, that worked out okay.
This Roy is more than
just a friend, isn't he?
Bad boys.
- They hook you ever time.
- Yeah.
Oh, I think Tommy actually went home
for the night.
Oh.
You all right?
You seem like you're something
other than all right.
My mom.
She showed up in town this week,
and she's been...
What?
She had this crazy idea
that Sara was still alive.
She was so sure of it
that she kind of had me believing it also.
- But Sara's gone.
- Yeah.
I can't believe she sucked me in like that.
- You miss her.
- I miss them both.
- Thanks for listening.
- Of course.
Laurel?
You wanna have a dinner or coffee?
I don't know.
Why?
I don't want to be on an island anymore.
Sure.
- Good night.
Slade. The circuit board's gone.
Damn. Fyers played us.
While he was screwing us around,
his men were combing the woods for it.
Now his missile launcher
is fully operational.
He was never gonna let us off the island.
Of course he wasn't gonna help you.
He couldn't chance
you warning the mainland.
She speaks English. Yeah, well, guess what.
Neither one of us have any idea
what his plans are.
I do.
Thank you for coming, Frank.
Meeting like this is dangerous, Moira.
Particularly now.
Yes, I know.
- Malcolm knows.
- What?
I had no choice but to turn over
what I discovered.
The evidence of the wire transfers.
Money that you paid to assassinate him.
The money I... Ah!
Moira.
Mr. Merlyn thanks you
for your loyalty. You've done well.
- Now Chen's family will share his fate.
- Chen betrayed us...
...but his daughter didn't.
Tell Mr. Merlyn I want her to live.
Amanda nearly lost her life.
Now she's lost her father.
I think she's suffered enough.
- We must send a message.
- We have.
- Very well.
- Thank you.
- Thea's friend is upstairs.
- I saw.
You probably saw they were very happy
to see each other, if you know what I mean.
Which you probably don't wanna talk about,
because she's your baby sister.
You Okay?
Getting there. Thank you.
Psst.
By the way, if you ever need
to tell someone about your day...
...you can tell me.
Thanks.
- What's that?
- Felicity pulled that up.
It's an old map
of the decommissioned subway line.
Runs underneath
the low-rent district of the city.
I've seen that map before.
It was right in front of our faces
the entire time.
My father, the other
archer, the Undertaking.
Whatever the plan is,
it's all connected to the Glades.