My name is Oliver Queen.
For 5 years, I was stranded
on an island
with only one goal--
survive.
Oliver Queen is alive.
Now I will fulfill
my father's dying wish...
Make it home.
Right my wrongs.
No!
To use the list of names
he left me
and bring down those
who are poisoning my city.
To do this, I must
become someone else.
I must become...
something else.
As Kanye says,
get 'em high!
- Get Down!
Everybody keep down!
Nobody lifts their head,
nobody gets hurt.
- Get down!
- Stay down!
Get on the floor
right now!
You can't jackhammer
into the safe.
It's too thick.
Shut up!
We're through!
3 minutes.
Make it 2!
Are you
trying to get us killed?
Don't worry.
I'm a cop.
Please don't do anything.
I don't want to die.
Please!
What the hell's going on?
He was a freakin' cop.
Enough throwing shots.
you hear that?
Someone triggered the alarm!
Don't!
That's it. Let's go.
Starling City
police department.
Lay down your weapons
and come out with your hands up.
Repeat: Lay down your weapons and
come out with your hands up.
Hold your fire.
These are hostages.
Mills, contain the hostages.
All units, move in!
Move in!
Come here. You shot a cop.
This is not how
we do things.
Me getting killed isn't how
we do things, either, is it?
- Is it?
- Get in the van!
Anchor the rear hand,
Diggle. Come on.
Hey.
Uhh! Uhh!
Variable acceleration.
Most fighters work
at the same pace.
You switch it up, you throw
your opponent off his game.
That was nice.
Where'd you learn that?
His name's Yao Fei.
He give you those scars?
One of them.
And the others?
You know, one of these days
you're gonna be straight with me
about what really
happened on that island.
Absolutely.
Uhh!
But not today.
Still some pretty
sweet moves.
Yep. Tonight I'm gonna
use them on him.
Scott Morgan runs
water and power in the Glades.
Jacks up the prices
when people can't pay,
shuts them down even
in the dead of winter.
Which is at least
a month away.
Look at this.
These guys started
at Keystone 3 years ago,
then began moving west,
hitting banks along the way.
This morning they hit
Starling City Trust.
Shot an off-duty cop.
He's in a coma
and the doctors are saying
it's a coin toss whether he'll make it.
If he's a cop, SCPD
will be all over it.
Overwhelmed? Underfunded?
Listen, these guys
don't hit one time.
They hit 2 or 3 banks
per city,
which means right now
they're planning their next job.
I think you have
the wrong impression
about what it is I do.
You take out bad guys
with a bow and arrow.
I don't fight street crime.
That's a symptom
of what's wrong with this city.
I'm trying to cure
the disease.
CEOs and crooked
entrepreneurs. I get it.
Listen, Oliver,
I'm just saying,
maybe you can
make a difference
if you think beyond
the scope of those pages.
I'm sure your father
wouldn't mind.
No, you don't get it.
My father died
so that I could live.
Live and make a difference
by fixing the city
that he and the people
in this book ruined.
Every name
that I cross off this list
honors that sacrifice.
There's more than one way
to save this city.
Not for me.
Crime happens
in this city every day.
What do you want me
to do, stop all of it?
It sounds like you have
a narrow definition of being a hero.
I'm not a hero.
Dad?
1x06
Legacies
Original Air Date on November 14, 2012
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Please tell me
that this is a nightmare
and I'm about to wake up.
How can Stagg Industries
pull out completely?
They're our largest donor.
It's like they say--
"It's the economy, stupid."
No, it's the stupid
economy.
Ok, without Stagg, how long
can CNRI keep the doors open?
It depends.
What time you got?
I have fiesta time.
Or is it siesta time?
Which one means a party
and which one means a nap?
Tommy, as much
as I would love to relive
intro to Spanish with you,
today is not a good day.
Of course not. Working in this tiny
brick office is intolerable.
Now, you know where is
a spectacular place
to spend the day?
Coast City. Here's what
I am thinking.
Sunset flight
on my private plane,
dinner at Broome's,
I'll have you home by midnight.
Or maybe in the morning.
What is this?
This is what
we talked about.
This is you getting to know
the real me.
Tommy, so you don't
misunderstand,
CNRI just lost
its largest single donor.
Which means all of the hard work
and sacrifices
that I have made to help
this legal clinic survive,
it may have been for nothing.
Maybe another time.
Yeah?
I mean, haven't you noticed
she's been acting a little down lately?
What am I saying?
Of course you haven't.
Well, who are you
to judge?
Since when do you
pay attention to how mom's feeling?
Since our stepfather suddenly
decided to take a business trip
halfway across the world.
I think when someone at Walter's
pay grade takes a business trip,
it's always sudden, Thea.
I wouldn't worry.
Ah, guess who I just
hung up with.
Janice Bowen.
Carter's mother.
Oh.
Carter Bowen.
The perfect son.
Is he perfect?
According to you.
Carter Bowen just won
the national chess championship.
Carter Bowen is anchoring
the debate team.
I'm sure I didn't
make that big of a fuss.
Oliver, Carter
just got accepted
into Harvard and Princeton.
Well, that's because Carter
got a perfect score on his SATs.
Now, how did he manage
to study and cure cancer?
All right, all right,
all right. I get it. I get it.
Well, they're coming for brunch
and I expect you to be there.
I have plans.
That's fine.
Brunch is tomorrow.
Hmm. Inches from
a clean getaway.
Well, you, too, Thea.
Snap.
Nobody says that anymore.
What? Mom.
Hmm?
I can't actually go.
I haven't seen
the Bowens in years.
So whatever it is
that you have planned,
I'm sure the two of you can make
the sacrifice just this once.
We'll be there.
I hate you.
Yeah.
You know your friend
Scott Morgan from your father's list?
He tried to kill himself.
Maybe he was afraid
of getting a visit from you.
How fast can you make it
to Starling General?
On my way.
Hey, just the man
I wanted to see.
I just picked up
a new sports car,
and I'm thinking
we can open her up,
pick up a few
speeding tickets--
that sounds great, but something's
come up. I gotta jet.
Oh. Uh, okay.
Nice talk. Thanks.
He moves fast, doesn't he?
It's ironic, really,
since you're the one
we call speedy.
Oh, please.
For the love of God.
But if you need somebody to talk to,
I'm here.
You know,
maybe you could help.
There's this girl
that I'm interested in.
And I am really not sure
how to pursue it.
Have you tried using
your usual lines?
Hi, my name is Tommy Merlyn
and I'm a billionaire,
but I don't look like
Warren Buffet.
Yeah. She is aware
of that,
and she doesn't care.
You know, money really
isn't a big deal to her.
Why don't you just
tell her how you feel?
Well, I've--I--
I've known her
for a long time,
and I'm not sure the direct approach
is really the right way to go.
Maybe you just
have to figure out
what's a big deal to her
and make it a big deal to you.
Thea.
You are amazing.
Love you.
You sure?
Scott Morgan doesn't
seem like the type
who would try
to kill himself.
True, but it's the best lie
I could come up with on short notice.
Mr. Diggle,
I can't thank you enough
for arranging to move my husband
from County Ward
to Starling General.
Now I know he's getting
the best care available.
You really should be
thanking this man,
Oliver Queen.
He's paying the bill.
Jana's husband Stan
is a police officer,
who happened to have
been making a deposit
at Starling Trust Bank.
The bank that was robbed.
I was so sorry
to hear about your husband.
Is he gonna be okay?
The doctors say
the next 24 hours are crucial.
He should have just
kept his head down, you know?
I've known a few police
officers in my day.
Always willing
to help others
even if that means
putting themselves at risk.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
You lied to me.
You asked me to work
with you, not for you.
And when you did,
you said it was because
you understand
the kind of man I am.
Well, Oliver, I'm the kind of man
who doesn't walk away
when there's a chance
to make a difference.
And neither does
Stan Washington.
Oliver, I'm not finished talking.
Where are you going?
To go make a difference.
Let's catch
some bank robbers.
See that guy right there?
He's got a temper.
And he shot
Officer Washington.
That's right.
College ring.
Or high school,
more likely.
That ring will get us
an I.D.
Yeah, but even with
photo enhancement,
you're gonna have a problem
getting a clear shot of that ring.
No, but it left an impression the police
would have photographed.
It'll be in evidence
lockup.
Please tell me you're not going
where I think you're going.
Diggle,
why do you even ask?
Are you kidding me?
I don't want to hear this.
Don't tell me about
red tape.
One of our own's been shot.
Tell them to find themselves
a pair of scissors.
So, where are you
gonna take me today?
Monte Carlo?
Actually, I was just
telling Jo here
that the Merlyn Global Group
is looking to expand
its local philanthropy,
and I thought
that we could start
by sponsoring a benefit
for CNRI.
Thank you, Tommy,
but I think we can manage
without your family's
finances.
Laurel, a word?
Come on.
What are you doing?
He's not interested
in throwing us a fundraiser.
What he wants to have
is the first annual attempt
to get back
into my pants gala.
Who cares why he's doing it?
We need the money.
Not like that we don't.
We really do. So you're gonna
listen to your best friend's advice.
You are gonna go over there
and say, "Thank you, Tommy,
we'd be honored if you'd
throw us a fundraiser." Hmm?
Thank you, Tommy.
We would be honored
for you to throw us
a fundraiser.
The bank manager
Ace punched,
his ring left a mark.
Larchmont High.
High school.
I cross-referenced
his height and relative age
with a list of students
and alumni.
Still, that's
a pretty long list.
It was. I dug a little deeper
and found Kyle Reston.
Right before Kyle's
senior year,
not only did he drop out,
he dropped off the grid.
Along with his family--
father, mother,
younger brother.
There are two other guys
involved in this robbery.
And a woman.
Aside from Stan Washington,
there were 22 customers
and employees
that came out of the bank.
9 men, 13 women.
Inside the bank,
9 men, 14 women.
They put a ringer in.
The mom. The police
are looking for a crew,
we're gonna look for a family.
Speaking of which,
I'm incredibly late
for mine.
Well, I'm sorry Walter
couldn't join us.
Oh, yes, well, the Australian trip
came up suddenly.
He sends his apologies.
Where's Oliver?
He's not out of town, too, is he?
Oh, I'm sure he's just--
Stuck in traffic.
One of the things
I didn't miss on the island--
Sunday drivers.
Sorry I'm late.
Thank God you're here.
It is so good to see you.
Mm. We all thought
you were--
oh, well, we are
just happy he's home.
Hmm. And returning
a celebrity, too.
How do you mean?
Billionaire scion,
castaway for 5 years.
You know,
there is a bidding war
for the rights
to your life story.
At least that's what
my agent says.
Agent? I thought you were
a neurosurgeon, Carter.
I know.
It's crazy, right?
One minute I'm
publishing this book
on how long-term
potentiation
initiates the creation
of a slow-moving
protein synthesis,
and the next,
there's an agent
trying to make me
the next Dr. Oz.
Why would he want
you to be a wizard?
Oh, Oliver.
For all our sakes,
start ready "Us Weekly."
Well, the truth is,
I just feel it's our duty
as Starling City's more fortunate
to help those most in need.
Oh, of course.
Wouldn't you agree,
Oliver?
You're the hero, Carter.
Quick and clean,
and try not to shoot anybody.
So now that you're back,
what are your plans?
Will you be taking a job
with Queen Consolidated?
I'm opening a night club.
Sir, your liquor
distributor's on the line.
First Bank of Starling
was hit two minutes ago.
Sorry. Business.
If the rest of their M.O. holds,
they made their escape underground.
First Bank of Starling is located
right above the water treatment tunnels.
The entrance is located here.
Oliver.
Where are you going?
Something's come up.
I'm really sorry.
SCPD! Don't move!
Enough! What are you doing?!
Let's get out of here!
- The cash!
- Forget it!
Let's go!
All right, let's move!
It's vigilante.
Who the hell was that guy?
The local vigilante.
Usually goes after
rich guys.
Well, clearly
he's branching out.
Things have gone sideways
for us lately.
That hood guy showing up,
Kyle shooting a cop.
You were the one
who warned me he was a cop.
So you would take his gun,
not shoot him.
Your mother has a point.
Maybe this is a sign
we need to hang it up.
Head for Mexico, retire.
We don't have enough.
We always said
that we wouldn't quit
until we had enough
to set ourselves up.
The kid's right.
We need to hit another.
- We can make do with what we've got.
- We'll be okay.
I didn't spend 5 years
risking my life and my freedom
to just be okay.
No. Set for life.
That was our deal.
Ok.
One more.
And then we're out.
I should add "personal Internet
researcher for Oliver Queen"
to my job title.
Happily, I mean.
His name is Derek Reston.
We were close before
I... went away.
And I want to
get back in touch.
I guess you didn't have
Facebook on that island.
Nope. Not even
a MySpace account.
It was a very dark time.
Well, there's not much here
that's recent.
No credit activity.
No utility bills.
Well, I guess you guys
must have met at the factory.
Wait.
What--what factory?
The Queen Steel Factory.
Derek Reston worked there
for 15 years
until it shut down in '07.
Derek Reston
worked for my father?
You weren't really
close friends, huh?
It looks like Derek
was the factory Foreman
until your dad outsourced
production to China.
About 1,500 employees
got laid off.
Looks like the finance guys
even found a loophole
in the union contract,
so, they didn't have to pay
severance packages
and pensions to their employees.
They all pretty much
lost their homes.
Including your friend.
You died.
I asked you,
I begged you to survive.
But I don't think you can.
There's still one bullet left.
But, Oliver,
my death is made
meaningless by yours.
I'm starving.
I'm gonna die anyway,
and I just want it
to be quick.
I want it to be quick,
like yours was.
You can survive this.
No, I can't.
I'm not as strong
as you think I am.
And I'm sorry.
The Restons just got home
after 5 years of being away.
Those factory guys hung out
at a bar after work.
I'm going down there.
Hopefully Derek Reston
wants to take a stroll
down memory lane.
And if by some miracle
Reston's there?
I'm gonna give him
the chance to do the right thing.
Oliver, he already had his chance
to do the right thing.
It's called
not being a criminal.
This is happening
because of my father.
Because of my family.
No. You're worried
about the wrong thing.
It's not your fault.
The Restons aren't the victims.
My family
stole from this city.
They hurt the people in it.
And I am hell-bent
on making that right.
For Derek Reston, that
means giving him the chance
to make it right.
Hey, don't fade on me now.
We have about 10,000
more decisions to make.
Now, cake--
chocolate or mocha?
Mm... Carrot.
Are you sure about that?
Because Bugs Bunny hasn't RSVP'd yet.
Tell me,
why the full-court press?
Asking me to coast city,
the fundraiser--
why now?
You know, I was in a bar
last week,
and I was talking
to this girl,
and things were progressing,
if you know what I mean.
No. You're too subtle.
Anyway, we finally
go back to her place,
and I realize all of a sudden--
That I'd been there before.
Been with her before.
Two years ago.
Just... didn't remember.
So I left.
You know, I remember
some of the mornings
when you and I
were together
and I made you omelets.
And I'd be in your kitchen
and I would think to myself,
this isn't just fun.
This is more than fun.
This is...
this is different.
I never felt that way
with anybody else.
And I miss it.
Not mocha. Carrot.
Carrot.
♪ ...my imagination
Ok, fellas.
Thanks for playing.
Ahem. Mind if I sit in?
Oliver Queen.
The prodigal son returns.
I didn't figure you
for someone who would
hang out in the Glades.
My father used to bring me here
after we visited the factory.
There was a Pac-man machine
in the back.
I had the high score
for two months.
The last time
I saw your dad,
he was making a speech,
telling my crew not to believe
all the gossip,
that there was no way
Queen Consolidated
was moving production
to China.
A week later,
they closed the doors.
I didn't even get the two weeks
vacation pay due to me.
My father made mistakes.
He hurt people.
When people are hurt,
people are in trouble,
they tend to make
the wrong choices.
Right, Derek?
But those choices
don't have to define you,
they don't have to define
who your family will be,
because there's always
one moment
when you can turn it
all around.
If my father
had another chance...
♪ ...imagination
I think he'd do things
differently.
But...
time ran out for him.
How poetic.
That doesn't help me
get my house back, now, does it?
No, it doesn't.
No, all I can offer you
is an apology and a job.
Queen Consolidated has
subsidiaries all over the country.
I make one phone call,
you start next week.
So what do you say?
How about I still have
some pride left?
I don't need charity
from the son of the man
who screwed me over.
Ok.
If you change your mind...
You and I have
one thing in common.
We're both dealing
with the consequences
of our fathers' actions.
What he did then,
that's on him.
What we do now,
that's on us.
I've been thinking, baby,
maybe you were right.
Maybe it's time
to hang it up, retire.
But Kyle says
we do one more
or he'll go out
on his own.
Well, if that's what he wants to do,
that's his right,
but you and me
and Teddy, we're out.
I want to quit, too,
but I am not leaving without Kyle.
What's this?
I dropped a bug
in Derek Reston's jacket.
I thought you were going
to give the man a second chance.
That's what I believe in.
I also believe in covering
all my bases.
Derek, we can't abandon our son.
After all this time,
we wants to end up a winner.
Set for life.
Otherwise what was the point?
All right.
One more.
Now what?
We take them down.
♪ You and I go hard
at each other ♪
♪ like we...
Monitor the Restons
with this.
When you get a line
on their plans, we move.
And you're gonna do
another abrupt exit?
I'm getting better at it
with practice.
Honey, keep the alcohol
flowing.
I can't--wow.
You look just
really lovely.
Lovely.
Well, it's nice that you've
extended your vocabulary
from words like
hot and mega hot.
You can just say
thank you, you know.
Thank you.
You know?
You're welcome.
♪ Well, I cross my heart
and I hope to die... ♪
Tommy.
This is wonderful.
It means the world to us.
Oh, God. Excuse me,
just for a second.
Excuse me.
So?
You were right.
Thank you for coming.
Thank you for inviting me.
Well, I figured the entire
Queen family
and their checkbooks
should be present.
Oh, right. And how is that
going for you so far?
It is going amazing.
And all thanks to you.
Thea Queen, the unlikely
voice of reason.
Little old me?
What did I do?
You gave me
that great advice.
I thought about what
the girl was interested in,
and, uh...
And you did this
for Laurel.
And it's working.
Thanks again, sweetie.
Yeah.
Anytime.
♪ So I cross my heart
and I hope to die ♪
♪ yeah
♪ then I'll only stay
with you one more night ♪
Oh, Tommy, do you remember
Carter Bowen from high school?
Oh, yeah, sure I do.
So glad you could make it.
It's so great to see you.
You look amazing.
I gotta say I'm so
impressed with the work
that you and CNRI
are doing.
Thanks, Carter.
You know, I've actually
been thinking
about starting a free clinic
down here in the Glades.
Really?
Can we grab
a couple drinks
and I'll tell you
what I'm thinking.
That sounds great.
♪ But I'll only stay with you
one more night ♪
Hi.
Excuse me.
Well. I'm surprised
you made it tonight,
given your hectic schedule.
Mom, I messed up
with the Bowens yesterday.
I made you a promise.
I couldn't keep it.
Well, it's nothing new
for you, Oliver.
I know you and I
have had our difficulties,
but despite all my many
mistakes,
I always thought that you and I
had a connection.
So can you imagine...
Just imagine, after being
granted the miracle
of having my child
returned to me...
That you seem to have
little or no interest
in being with me
or telling me the truth.
Ma'am.
Redwood United Bank.
Gonna try a nighttime hit.
I have to go.
I'm sorry.
No, don't bother apologizing.
Honestly, Oliver,
there are times when I wonder
why you bother
coming home at all.
3 minutes.
Ok.
You hear that?
I'll check it out.
Alright.
Kyle Reston.
I came prepared.
Uhh!
It's okay.
It's gonna be okay.
No, hey, I got this.
Drop your weapon!
- Now!
- No!
Call an ambulance. Now!
Kyle! Kyle.
He's okay.
He's just knocked out.
It wasn't his fault.
I turned my son into this.
Of course it doesn't work.
I'm hallucinating.
Or I'm dreaming.
But if you weren't...
You betrayed me, Oliver.
I died so that you could live,
and you threw that gift away.
You made that sacrifice empty.
I'm not you.
I'm not.
I'm not strong like you.
I never was.
I told you, I'm not
the man you think I am.
The things I've done.
What I was about to do.
Dad... Dad.
What does that mean?
Please?
I don't know
what that means.
I told you.
I begged you.
Right my wrongs!
This is your responsibility now.
How?
How do I do this?
I can't even
get off this island.
I'm sorry I didn't tell you
the truth about me.
But I hope...
I hope that you know
that I love you.
Did you know
that as a doctor,
I was able
to diagnose myself
as a giant tool?
How about a dance,
handsome?
Hey, uh, I thought
that we agreed
that you were going
to call me before
you did something stupid.
You're no fun.
I'm going to show
you how to have some fun.
Whoa, whoa,
what are you doing?
You said I was amazing.
Yeah, you are amazing,
but you're also like my sister.
My baby sister.
Well, I'm not
a baby anymore.
Thank you for noticing.
Laurel
doesn't even like you.
She doesn't
understand you.
I do.
Why can't you
just see that?
Thea. Thea,
it was a mistake
to talk to you
about girls and stuff.
It was inappropriate, and I think
it may have confused you.
Yeah, the rejection?
It is pretty clear.
Even if it wasn't,
between my mom and Oliver
and everybody
in my entire life,
I'm pretty much used to it
by now, so...
Whoa, whoa.
Ok, let's go,
let's go, come on.
- Tommy?
- Yep.
Is Thea okay?
Oh, yeah, she just ate
some bad crab cakes.
Are you sure it wasn't
something she drank?
Ahem. Don't worry.
I got this.
You can go back inside.
Keep having fun.
Looked like you were having a nice
little do-si-do with the good doctor.
Tommy, I'm going to let you in
on a little-known secret
about Dr. Carter Bowen.
The man is a gigantic ass.
And the only reason
why I danced with him
is because he wrote
a massive check to CNRI.
Why would you think
anything else?
I guess when it comes
to you, I tend not to think straight.
Can you call me a cab?
Absolutely not.
I am taking you home.
Get in.
I apologize
for making such a scene.
Just feel better, okay?
Hey, Tommy.
I owe you a dance.
Yeah?
You earned it.
Please don't hate me.
No, no.
Never.
What went down
wasn't your fault.
I didn't say it was.
Oliver, it wasn't
your fault, man.
You gave Reston a chance.
That was more
than he deserved.
I'm not so sure
about that.
Well, listen,
I'll tell you this much.
You say going after
the guys on that list
is the way you honored
your dad?
Well, if your dad
could have seen you this week,
the way you cared
about the people he had hurt,
the way you stepped up
to try to help them,
I'd say he'd be
pretty damn honored.
So maybe there is more
than one way to save this city?
Maybe.
By the way,
Stan Washington woke up.
He's going to be fine.
My responsibility.
I promise, Dad.
I promise.
Nightcap?
Well, I thought
it might help me.
I--I don't
sleep well alone.
I'm sorry about
what I said tonight.
No.
You were being honest.
No, not entirely.
The truth is, with Walter
being gone, I'm...
I'm lonely.
You know, you and I
used to talk.
I used to know what
you were thinking.
But now, even when
you're home,
you're somewhere
else. I...
I guess I just
miss my son.
I miss you, too.
And I wish that...
Are you hungry?
Thank you.
All right.
Mmm. Mom--
It's okay to get your hands
dirty every once in a while.
For me. Please.
All right.
- Mmm.
- Mm-hmm.
- Yeah.
That is a great burger.
- Thank you for this.
- Anytime.
You know, I'll bet
Carter Bowen
doesn't know where to find
the best burger joint
in Starling City.
So I have one thing on him.
No.
You have
everything on him.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==