OLIVER, VOICE-OVER:
MY NAME IS OLIVER QUEEN.
AFTER 5 YEARS IN HELL,
I RETURNED HOME
WITH ONLY ONE GOAL...
TO SAVE MY CITY.
TODAY I FIGHT THAT WAR
ON TWO FRONTS.
BY DAY, I LEAD STAR CITY
AS ITS MAYOR,
BUT BY NIGHT,
I AM SOMEONE ELSE.
I AM...SOMETHING ELSE.
I AM THE GREEN ARROW.
PREVIOUSLY ON "ARROW"...
HUH!
GREGOR: YOU ARE NOT
GOING TO BEBRATVA CAPTAIN
FOR MUCH LONGER.
THEA: SUSAN WILLIAMS
IS SUSPECTING
THAT OLIVER'S
THE GREEN ARROW.
WHAT ARE WE
GONNA DO?
HACK INTO
HER COMPUTER
AND FIND OUT WHAT'S
THERE.
-SHE HAS...
-EVERYTHING.
APPARENTLY, I'VE BEEN
PLAGIARIZING MY STORIES
FOR THE PAST YEARS,
AND MY LAPTOP
IS FILLED WITH
INCRIMINATING EVIDENCE,
BUT NOW I'VE BEEN
THOROUGHLY DISCREDITED.
DID YOU HACK
SUSAN WILLIAMS'
COMPUTER?
THEA ASKED ME TO PUT A FEW
THINGS ON SUSAN'S COMPUTER.
WAIT. WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
THEA ASKED YOU?
BETHANY, ON TV: THE MAYOR'S
OFFICE ORDERED THE FALSIFICATION
OF AUTOPSY REPORTS
TO PROTECT THE IDENTITY
OF DETECTIVE MALONE'S KILLER.
IF ANY OF THESE ALLEGATIONS
PROVE TRUE,
IT WOULD LIKELY TRIGGER
IMPEACHMENT PROCEEDINGS.
THIS MIGHT BE THE END
OF MY ADMINISTRATION.
[REPORTERS CLAMORING]
WHEN DID YOU LEARN
THE GREEN ARROW
KILLED
DETECTIVE MALONE?
WHY DID YOU PROTECT
THE GREEN ARROW?
QUENTIN: THERE'S NO COMMENT
AT THIS TIME,
BUT WE WILL HAVE SOMETHING
FOR YOU SHORTLY. THANKS.
I'VE CALLED IN EVERY
FAVOR I COULD.
I STILL DON'T KNOW
HOW THIS GOT LEAKED.
WE KNOW HOW
IT GOT LEAKED.
IT'S PROMETHEUS.
HE SENT THE ACU AFTER ME
AS THE GREEN ARROW,
AND NOW HE'S COMING
AFTER ME AS THE MAYOR.
SOMETHING HE SET YOU UP
FOR IN THE FIRST PLACE.
NOBODY'S SAYING
THE GUY ISN'T SMART.
WE'RE JUST GONNA
HAVE TO BE SMARTER.
WHAT'S THE PLAN, BOSS?
WE DON'T HAVE
A PLAN YET,
BUT IF WE LOSE THIS OFFICE,
THEN PROMETHEUS WINS.
I JUST REALIZED,
AM I ALLOWED TO BE IN HERE?
USUALLY, THE DETAIL
STANDS OUTSIDE.
-BETTER GO BLEND IN.
-OK.
WELL, ON
THE POLITICAL FRONT,
I THINK THE PLAN
SHOULD BE TO DENY,
DEFLECT, OBFUSCATE.
THAT'S JUST GONNA
CONFUSE PEOPLE.
YEAH, BUT THAT'S
THE POINT.
WHAT IF WE
TELL THE TRUTH,
A VERSION
OF THE TRUTH...
THE GREEN ARROW
IS A GOOD GUY,
AND I GAVE HIM
THE BENEFIT OF THE DOUBT?
YOU KNOW WHAT?
IT WORKED ON PIKE.
I'LL TELL
THE VULTURES
YOU'RE GONNA BE
MAKING A STATEMENT.
OK. DO YOU WANT ME
TO WRITE YOU A DRAFT?
NO. I'LL WRITE IT.
I NEED YOU TO HANDLE
SOMETHING FOR ME.
OK.
YOU NEED TO MAKE THINGS
RIGHT WITH SUSAN.
OLLIE...
YOU GOT HER FIRED UNDER
FALSE PRETENSES, THEA.
ONLY BECAUSE I WAS
TRYING TO PROTECT YOU,
WHICH IS WHAT
I AM DOING NOW.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
YES, ADRIAN?
MR. MAYOR.
WHAT'S THIS?
MY LETTER OF RESIGNATION
IN WHICH I TAKE
SOLE RESPONSIBILITY
FOR THE COVER-UP.
NO.
THE COVER-UP
WAS MY IDEA.
I APPROVED IT.
I'M THE MAYOR.
AND IF THIS IMPEACHMENT
PROCEEDING GOES THE WAY
THAT I THINK IT WILL,
NOT FOR LONG.
THE COUNCIL
HAS BROAD POWERS
TO RUN IMPEACHMENT
HEARINGS
AS IT SEES FIT,
CALLS ITS OWN
WITNESSES,
ENTERS ITS
OWN EVIDENCE.
THEY TAKE A VOTE.
MAJORITY RULES.
BUT OLIVER CAN'T
DEFEND HIMSELF?
IT'S NOT
A CRIMINAL TRIAL.
THE COUNCIL NEEDS
A POUND OF FLESH,
AND I'M
VOLUNTEERING.
-AND I'VE ALREADY SAID NO.
-YEAH. I'M PERSISTENT.
I HAVE A BETTER IDEA.
BE MY LAWYER AT THE HEARINGS.
MR. MAYOR...
IT'S OLIVER, AND I'M
NOT YOUR BOSS ANYMORE.
I'M YOUR CLIENT.
[GUN COCKS]
I HAVE MANY REASONS
FOR KILLING ANATOLY.
BIGGEST IS HIS POISONING
BRATVA WITH AMERICAN SCUM.
[APPROACHING FOOTSTEPS]
[SPEAKING RUSSIAN]
SPROSS DOPROSS.
FINE.
WHAT?
TAKE THEM.
WHAT DID YOU DO?
EXTEND OUR LIVES BY
LENGTH OF GOOD MOVIE.
AH.
OHH...
ALL RIGHT, LADY.
DO YOU THING.
[BEEP]
THAT WAS NOT YOUR THING.
BOSS IS GETTING
IMPEACHED,
AND YOU'RE DOWN HERE
PLAYING MARBLES?
ACTUALLY, THIS
WAS YOUR IDEA.
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO
ENCOURAGED ME TO LEAN
INTO THE STRENGTHS
OF MY TECH. REMEMBER?
-UH-UH, UH-UH.
-YOU SAID THAT. WE WERE WALKING
DOWN THE ALLEY,
YOU WERE LIKE, "LEAN
INTO YOUR STRENGTHS."
YOU LITERALLY SAID THAT.
ANYWAY, THESE ARE
TWO INVENTIONS OF MINE...
TWO AUTONOMOUS
MINI DRONES,
ONE WITH OFFENSIVE
AND THE OTHER
WITH DEFENSIVE
CAPABILITIES.
SO, WHAT, YOU CAN'T HANDLE
YOURSELF ON THE FIELD.
YOU GOT TO GIVE YOURSELF
A PAIR OF BALLS?
THAT WAS...THAT WAS
TOO HARSH, WASN'T IT?
YOU THINK? YEAH.
IT WAS, UM,
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU RECOGNIZED IT.
YEAH, BECAUSE
I'M...I'M...
-I'M TRYING TO WORK ON IT.
-THAT'S PROGRESS.
ANYWAY, PAUL'S BIG PROBLEM
WITH ME BEING MR. TERRIFIC
WAS THE FACT THAT
HE WAS WORRIED,
BUT NOW HE DOESN'T
HAVE TO WORRY
WITH THESE BAD BOYS
IN MY ARSENAL.
SOUNDS LIKE YOU GOT
THE EMOTIONAL LOGIC
ALL FIGURED OUT.
I DO.
NOW IF I CAN JUST GET
THESE DAMN THINGS TO WORK.
BETHANY: NEWS OF THE COVER-UP
SENT SHOCKWAVES
THROUGH CITY HALL,
FORCING COUNCILMEMBERS
INTO ENACTING A RARELY USED
IMPEACHMENT CLAUSE.
MAYOR OLIVER QUEEN'S
ADMINISTRATION MIGHT BE OVER.
THAT WOMAN NEVER
REPORTS GOOD NEWS.
IT'LL WORK OUT.
JUST WAITING
FOR MY OPENING.
THERE'S THAT
OPTIMISM AGAIN.
CHASE IS
REPRESENTING ME,
SO I'M GONNA
BEAT THIS.
HOW ARE WE DOING
WITH THE DATA PULL
FROM PROMETHEUS'
MOTHER'S HOUSE?
THE SNIFFER PULLED ABOUT
A PETABYTE WORTH OF DATA.
IT'S LIKE LOOKING FOR
A NEEDLE IN A HAYSTACK,
BUT I AM
WORKING ON IT.
GOOD. UH, THERE'S
SOMETHING ELSE
THAT I COULD USE
YOUR HELP WITH.
-OK.
-SUSAN WILLIAMS.
-OH.
-SHE'S NOT RETURNING MY CALLS.
AM I REALLY
THE BEST PERSON
TO COME TO
FOR LOVE-LIFE ADVICE?
WELL, SHE'S NOT
RETURNING MY CALLS
SINCE YOU AND THEA
GOT HER FIRED.
WELL, IN MY DEFENSE,
I DIDN'T KNOW
THAT WAS GONNA BE
THEA'S PLAY.
I KNOW, BUT I STILL
NEED YOUR HELP
BECAUSE THEA
IS NOT BUDGING.
LOOK. I KNOW HOW
SEVERELY PROBLEMATIC
WHAT I'M ABOUT
TO SAY IS,
BUT SUSAN IS
YOUR GIRLFRIEND,
SO IF ANYONE
IS GOING TO FIX IT,
I THINK
IT HAS TO BE YOU.
I'M TRYING,
BUT, LIKE I SAID,
SHE'S NOT
RETURNING MY CALLS,
AND YOU MAY HAVE
NOTICED I'M SORT OF
FACING AN IMPEACHMENT
THIS WEEK.
OK. YEAH.
I'LL DO MY BEST.
-THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
-MM-HMM.
UM, FOR WHAT
IT'S WORTH...
AND EVERYTHING I KNOW
ABOUT POLITICS I GOT
FROM "KEEPIN' IT 1600,"
BUT I DO THINK YOU'RE
GONNA BEAT THIS THING.
WHAT MAKES YOU
SO SURE?
TO STAR CITY, MAYOR
OLIVER QUEEN IS A HERO.
BANG.
THIS MARKS
ONLY THE SECOND TIME
IN THE 140-YEAR
HISTORY OF THIS CITY
THAT A MAYOR HAS
FACED IMPEACHMENT.
IN 1898, MAYOR PRESCOTT
WAS REMOVED FROM OFFICE.
WE'LL SEE WHAT FATE
AWAITS OLIVER QUEEN,
WHO'S STEPPING
INTO THE BUILDING NOW.
HEY, I'LL CATCH YOU
UP THERE, ALL RIGHT?
-HI, SUSAN.
-SORRY.
BUSY REPORTING
FOR MY NEW BLOG.
I'M SORRY.
I'VE BEEN TRY...
MY FIRST ENTRY WILL BE
HOW YOU NEVER TOOK
THIS JOB SERIOUSLY.
AS MAYOR, YOU
JUST PHONED IT IN.
YOU'LL ONLY EVER BE
THAT OTHER GUY,
BUT, OF COURSE,
I CAN'T WRITE THAT
BECAUSE NO ONE
WILL BELIEVE ME
NOW THAT YOU TRASHED
MY CREDIBILITY.
I HAD NOTHING TO DO
WITH THAT,
BUT I AM WORKING
TO MAKE IT RIGHT.
WHATEVER.
YOU DESERVE TODAY.
SO WHAT DO YOU THINK
OLIVER'S CHANCES ARE?
[GAVEL BANGS]
COME
TO ORDER.
WE'RE ABOUT
TO FIND OUT.
WE RECENTLY LEARNED
THAT DETECTIVE WILLIAM MALONE
WAS MURDERED
BY THE VIGILANTE
KNOWN AS THE GREEN ARROW.
IT APPEARS THAT THE MAYOR
KNEW SOME TIME AGO
AND ACTIVELY WORKED
TO HIDE THE FACT,
EVEN FROM THE SCPD.
TODAY THE COUNCIL CONSIDERS
TWO GRAVE QUESTIONS...
DID OLIVER QUEEN'S ACTIONS
VIOLATE THE OATH
HE TOOK FAITHFULLY
TO SERVE STAR CITY,
AND SHOULD HE THEREFORE
BE REMOVED AS MAYOR?
-HELL TO THE NO.
-WHAT HE SAID.
[CELL PHONE RINGS]
IT'S PAUL.
SHOULD I TAKE IT?
I'M NOT GONNA TAKE IT.
MAYBE I SHOULD TAKE IT.
NO. NO. OK.
I'LL TAKE IT. HEY..
THIS IS SO
COMPLETELY
UNFAIR.
YEAH. THAT SEEMS TO BE
GOING AROUND LATELY.
SO YOU GOT OLIVER'S
GIRLFRIEND FIRED?
HE TOLD YOU?
OF COURSE HE TOLD YOU.
WELL, DID HE ALSO TELL
YOU IT WAS A MISTAKE,
-I MEAN, ON MY PART, AT LEAST?
-FELICITY...
I'M PUTTING THE TOOTHPASTE
BACK IN THE TUBE, OK?
-AND HOW IS THAT GOING?
-WELL...
FELICITY, WHAT'S GOING
ON WITH YOU?
-WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
-THIS WEEK, IT WAS
OLIVER'S GIRLFRIEND.
LAST MONTH, HE TELLS ME
YOU'RE GETTING INVOLVED
IN SOME STUFF
-YOU SHOULDN'T BE INVOLVED IN.
-WELL, THAT IS A MATTER
OF PERSPECTIVE,
CONSIDERING THAT THAT "STUFF"
HELPED GET YOU OUT OF PRISON
AND GENERAL WALKER'S
GUN SIGHTS.
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
-PANDORA?
-IT'S A DATA CACHE COMPILED
BY A GROUP OF HACKTIVISTS
CALLED HELIX.
THEY COLLECTED
ELECTRONIC DIRT
ON LITERALLY BILLIONS
OF PEOPLE,
INCLUDING GENERAL WALKER,
SO WHEN I ASKED FOR IT
TO GET YOU OFF, THEY...
IT'S A BAD CHOICE OF WORDS...
THEY...THEY GAVE ME
THE WHOLE PACKAGE.
AND YOU'RE STILL IN BED
WITH THESE PEOPLE?
WHAT? YOU MAKE IT SOUND
LIKE IT'S A BAD THING.
I MEAN, PANDORA'S
JUST A TOOL.
SOUNDS TO ME LIKE
THIS COULD BE A WEAPON.
OK, AND IS THERE
A PROBLEM IF IT IS?
-IT DEPENDS, FELICITY.
-ON WHAT?
ON HOW YOU USE IT.
MY AUTOPSY SHOWED
THAT MORTAL INJURY
ON THE DECEASED
WAS CONSISTENT
WITH THE EDGING
OF THE ARROW HEADS
USED BY
THE GREEN ARROW.
I HAVE HERE YOUR ORIGINAL
CAUSE-OF-DEATH REPORT,
IN WHICH YOU CONCLUDE THAT
THE GREEN ARROW KILLED MALONE,
BUT THIS REPORT,
IT WAS NEVER INCLUDED
IN THE CASE FILE.
WHY IS THAT?
THE D.A.
CAME TO ME, AND...
YOU'RE REFERRING
TO ADRIAN CHASE?
THAT'S CORRECT.
HE INSTRUCTED ME
TO REVISE THE REPORT
TO INDICATE THAT
THE THROWING STAR KILLER
WAS RESPONSIBLE.
THIS REPORT, AND YOU
WENT AHEAD AND SIGNED IT,
EVEN THOUGH YOU KNEW
IT WAS FAKE
AND THEN PASSED IT ALONG
TO THE POLICE.
-IS THAT THE CASE?
-YES.
WHY? DID MR. CHASE
THREATEN YOU?
HE DIDN'T HAVE TO.
HE SAID THE REQUEST
CAME FROM THE MAYOR HIMSELF.
[PEOPLE MURMUR]
-THE MAYOR?
-YES.
HE TOLD ME THE GREEN ARROW
KILLED DETECTIVE MALONE.
DID MAYOR QUEEN
SAY WHY?
HE SAID
THE THROWING STAR KILLER,
A MAN WE'D BEEN
CALLING PROMETHEUS,
MANIPULATED HIM.
POLLARD: DID HE SAY
WHY THIS PROMETHEUS
WOULD WANT TO ORCHESTRATE
DETECTIVE MALONE'S MURDER?
NO.
STANDING HERE TODAY,
DO YOU BELIEVE
WHAT MR. QUEEN
HAS TOLD YOU?
[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS]
HONESTLY, I'M NOT SURE.
HE'S CLEARLY
BEEN DETERMINED
TO PROTECT THE GREEN ARROW
FOR HIS OWN PURPOSES.
I THINK THE QUESTION
HERE IS WHY.
[REPORTERS CLAMORING]
WHO'S MOST
IN OUR CORNER?
POLLARD,
BELIEVE IT OR NOT.
THAT'S NOT SURPRISING.
SHE CAN'T CALL
IN THE MARKER I OWE HER
FOR HELPING WITH GUN REFORM
IF I'M IMPEACHED.
I'LL TOUCH BASE
WITH HER,
SEE IF I CAN GET HER
TO CALL YOU
TO TESTIFY IN YOUR
OWN DEFENSE, OK?
UH, OK.
WELL, I...
I HAVE A VERY
POLITICAL IDEA.
I'M LISTENING.
THEA: LIKE ADRIAN SAID,
THE COUNCIL NEEDS
SOMEBODY THROWN
TO THE WOLVES,
AND I THINK IT
SHOULD BE MALONE.
-THEA.
-WHAT?
HALF THE SCPD
IS CORRUPT,
SO IT'S NOT
HARD TO BELIEVE,
AND HE'S
NO LONGER WITH US,
SO HE WOULDN'T
REALLY MIND.
THAT WAY, THE COVER-UP
IS NO LONGER
ABOUT THE GREEN ARROW.
IT BECOMES
ABOUT PROTECTING
MALONE'S REPUTATION FOR
THE SAKE OF HIS FAMILY.
NOW YOU'RE GONNA DESTROY
HIS REPUTATION. NO.
-BUT, OLIIE...
-THEA, IT'S NOT EVEN A QUESTION.
OK.
HOW DO WE THINK
THE COUNCIL'S GONNA VOTE?
IT'S, UH...IT'S
A PRETTY EVEN SPLIT
WITH KULLENS AS
THE SWING VOTE.
HOLD ON!
[CRASH]
MY TARGET'S THE MAYOR
AND HIS CORRUPTION.
HE SURRENDERS, I'LL LET
THE REST OF YOU LIVE.
GOOD MAN.
[CANARY CRY]
OH! UH!
GOOD WOMAN.
HEY, HEY,
GET TO SAFETY.
QUENTIN, THE DRIVER.
YEAH. YEAH, YEAH.
I'M ON IT.
UHH...
UNH!
[APPROACHING SIRENS]
YOU WANT ME?
COME ON!
[TIRES SCREECH]
LUCKY YOU.
YOU GET ONE MORE DAY.
[POLICE RADIO CHATTER]
AHEM.
OK. ALL RIGHT. LOOK.
I APPRECIATE WHAT YOU'RE
DOING, BUT I'M FINE.
MR. MAYOR, ALL DUE RESPECT,
YOUR HEAD'S BLEEDING,
AND OUR CONCUSSION
PROTOCOL'S
EVEN STRICTER
THAN THE NFL'S.
WELL, I'M THE MAYOR,
SO I'M SUSPENDING IT.
THE, UH...THE DRIVER,
HE'S OK.
HE TOOK A HIT
ON THE SHOULDER,
AND HE'S GOT A BUMP
ON THE HEAD, BUT HE'S FINE,
AND BEFORE YOU ASK,
HE DIDN'T SEE YOU
TURN ALL BRUCE LEE
BACK THERE.
WHERE'S DINAH?
SHE'S DOING HER JOB,
WORKING THE SCENE.
ALL RIGHT. I GOT TO
GET TO THE BUNKER.
-I...OH, BOY.
-EASY, ALL RIGHT?
HE KNOWS THE CONCUSSION
PROTOCOL, RIGHT?
YEAH, SO I'VE HEARD.
-THIS WAS VIGILANTE.
-YEAH.
APPARENTLY BECAUSE OF
THE IMPEACHMENT HEARING,
I'M A CRIMINAL.
YOU OK?
OH, NEVER FELT BETTER.
HEY, SO I MADE SURE
THE UNIS KEEP
ALL THE PRESS
BEHIND THE CORDON.
TRUST ME, YOU DON'T
WANT THEM SNAPPING SHOTS
OF YOU
IN AN AMBULANCE.
YEAH, NO AMBULANCE, BUT
I'M TOUGHER THAN I LOOK.
I'M GONNA GET
BACK TO THE OFFICE.
WHERE HAVE I HEARD
THAT BEFORE? HEY, LOOK.
WHILE UNDER THE THREAT
OF THE IMPEACHMENT,
YOU CAN'T EXACTLY
AMEND BYLAWS,
SO THAT CONCUSSION PROTOCOL,
YEAH, IT'S A THING.
THEA: IT'S...
IT'S OK, OLLIE.
I CAN...I CAN GO
BACK TO THE OFFICE
AND TELL EVERYONE WE'RE
GONNA BE WORKING OVERTIME,
PLUS I'M NEVER GETTING
INTO A LIMO WITH YOU AGAIN.
OLIVER IS ON HIS WAY
TO STARLING GENERAL,
BUT...DON'T WORRY...
HE'LL BE FINE.
WE HEARD SHOTS WERE
FIRED ON THE MOTORCADE.
YEAH, FLIPPED
OUR LIMO IN THE AIR.
-COOL.
-NOT COOL.
MORE LIKE OW, AND OLIVER
MIGHT BE CONCUSSED,
BUT IN THE MEANTIME,
THERE'S STILL THE
VIGILANTE OUT THERE.
OK. RENE AND I
ARE GONNA HIT THE STREET,
SEE IF WE CAN'T MUSCLE
THE VIGILANTE'S WHEREABOUTS
OUT OF SOME PEOPLE.
CURTIS, LET'S CHECK
THE KEYHOLE SATELLITE
AND CC THERMAL CAMS.
ACTUALLY, HOLD ON.
I...I NEED A FAVOR.
IF THIS IS ABOUT
SUSAN WILLIAMS,
I'M ALREADY ON IT.
NO. IT'S...IT'S ABOUT
THE IMPEACHMENT.
YOU SAID THAT
PANDORA HAS DIRT
ON A LOT OF PEOPLE,
RIGHT?
WELL, YEAH, IF BY A LOT
OF PEOPLE,
YOU MEAN EVERYBODY,
THEN YEAH.
WHAT ABOUT
COUNCILMAN KULLENS?
LAST TIME I CHECKED,
HE'S PART OF EVERYBODY. WHY?
-YOU KNOW WHY.
-OH. OH!
YOU WANT TO
BLACKMAIL HIM?
OH, IT'S NOT
BLACKMAIL.
IT'S POLITICS.
COME HERE.
BETHANY: IN THE WAKE OF
THE ATTACK, COUNCILMAN KULLENS
HAS CALLED A BRIEF RECESS
TO THE IMPEACHMENT HEARINGS.
IF THE MAYOR
IS MEDICALLY CLEARED,
THE COUNCIL
WILL VOTE TOMORROW.
OK.
OH, SOUNDS LIKE
YOU NEED A NOTE
FROM YOUR DOCTOR,
MR. MAYOR.
THIS IS RIDICULOUS.
I KNOW WHAT A REAL
INJURY FEELS LIKE.
I CAN ONLY IMAGINE,
GIVEN YOUR OTHER JOB,
AND...YOU'RE RIGHT...
YOUR CAT SCAN IS CLEAR.
-GOOD.
-AH, AH, AH, NOT SO FAST.
LOOK. I CAN'T
DISCHARGE YOU
WITHOUT A FEW MORE HOURS
OF OBSERVATION.
DR. SCHWARTZ...
PEOPLE CAN WITHSTAND
ONLY SO MUCH STRAIN,
AND BEING BOTH
MAYOR AND HIM,
IT'S UNSUSTAINABLE.
I ASSURE YOU, MY BODY
CAN HANDLE IT.
I'M NOT TALKING ABOUT
YOUR BODY, MR. QUEEN.
I'M TALKING
ABOUT THIS.
THE MIND NEEDS REST
OR AT LEAST SOMEONE
TO TAKE YOUR THOUGHTS
OFF ALL THE EVIL
YOU FACE EACH DAY.
DR. SCHWARTZ, ARE YOU
PRESCRIBING ME A GIRLFRIEND?
OR JUST A FRIEND.
[PHONE LINE RINGING]
SUSAN: YOU'VE REACHED SUSAN.
CAN'T COME TO THE...
"SPROSS DOPROSS"?
"DEMAND AN EXAM"?
YEAH. IT RHYME
BETTER IN RUSSIAN.
SPROSS DOPROSS ISBRATVA
WAY TO CALLPAKHAN
TO ACCOUNT FOR ACTIONS.
CAPTAINS WILL LISTEN.
MAYBEPAKHAN WILL
LOSE POSITION.
THAT'S GOOD NEWS.
THAT'S G...
THAT MEANS WE CAN OVERTHROW
GREGOR WITHOUT S FIGHT.
UH-UH. NO.
EVERYBODY KNOWS ABOUT
GREGOR'S DEAL WITH KOVAR.
NO. WE STILL
END UP DEAD.
MEN WHO CALL VOTE
ARE KILLED
IFPAKHAN
KEEPS POSITION.
ANATOLY, WHY BOTHER?
I DID NOT WANT TO DIE
IN HOSPITAL BASEMENT.
THAT'S...FAIR. LOOK.
ALL WE HAVE TO DO
IS FIND EVIDENCE
THAT GREGOR'S DEAL
WITH KOVAR BENEFITS HIM
AND NOT THEBRATVA.
YES, BUT WHERE ARE WE
GOING TO FIND THAT?
I HAVE TO GO.
CODE SAYS YOU HAVE
ONE HOUR TO FINALIZE
PERSONAL AFFAIRS
BEFORESPROSS DOPROSS...
I CAN DO THAT.
BUT YOU MUST HAVE CAPTAIN
WITH YOU WHO IS NOT ME.
I'LL LOSE HIM.
REALLY GOOD
AT LOSING PEOPLE.
[DISTANT SIREN]
I GOT BULLET FRAGMENTS
AND CASES COMING
OUT OF MY ASS
BUT NOTHING NEW.
ALL RIGHT.
I'LL CATCH YOU
BACK DOWNTOWN.
[POLICE RADIO CHATTER]
-ANYTHING?
-NADA.
PEEPS ON THE STREET
ARE ACTUALLY
MORE AFRAID OF THE
VIGILANTE THAN US.
WHAT ABOUT YOU?
VIGILANTE CHANGES
ARTILLERY SUPPLIER EVERY WEEK.
EVERY LEAD GOES COLD.
COULD REALLY USE A BREAK
RIGHT ABOUT NOW.
[BEEP BEEP]
DINAH: I THINK
I'VE GOT SOMETHING.
YES. I TOTALLY MANIFESTED THAT.
WHAT DO YOU GOT?
WHEN MY SONIC CRY
HIT VIGILANTE,
IT KNOCKED OFF A SMALL
PIECE OF HIS VISOR.
LOOKS LIKE IT'S LINED WITH
SOME KIND OF CIRCUITRY.
WELL, THAT MEANS,
IT'S MANUFACTURED.
MAYBE I CAN LINK IT BACK
TO WHERE HE BOUGHT IT FROM.
I THINK I CAN DO
YOU ONE BETTER.
MY T-SPHERES CAN
ACTUALLY TRACK
THE TECH TO THE
INDIVIDUAL USER.
EXCEPT IT WON'T BE READY
TILL THE IPHONE 16 IS RELEASED.
YE OF LITTLE
FAITH.
-WHAT'S A T-SPHERE?
-CURTIS' BALLS.
CURTIS: THEY'RE SOMETHING
REALLY FASCINATING
OF MY OWN PERSONAL
INVENTION.
I REALIZED THAT
QUANTUM COMPUTATION
COULD BE USED
TO HARNESS THE...
OK. LOOK.
FORGET I ASKED.
DINAH: I'LL BRING YOU GUYS
THE VISOR, OK?
COPY THAT. WE'RE HERE.
CURTIS, THIS IS ON YOU NOW.
CHALLENGE ACCEPTED.
HEY, SERIOUSLY, MAN,
WHAT'S UP WITH YOUR BALLS?
I MEAN, YOU WERE
LITERALLY GONNA
THROW THOSE THINGS
IN THE TRASH.
PAUL CALLED,
ASKED ME TO DINNER,
LIKE A DATE,
LIKE I'M GONNA GET
MY MAN BACK.
I TOLD YOU, HOSS,
SOME PIECE OF TECH
AIN'T GONNA...
LOOK. I KNOW PAUL.
HE WOULDN'T BE ASKING ME
TO GO OUT TO DINNER
IF HE WASN'T READY
TO RECONCILE.
PERSONAL CALL?
UH, YEAH. I HAD A...
A FAMILY EMERGENCY.
-I'M SORRY.
-DON'T BE. FAMILY'S IMPORTANT.
HEY, UH, WHY DON'T I
LOG THAT IN FOR YOU
SO YOU CAN HANDLE
YOUR EMERGENCY?
-UH...
-DON'T WORRY.
I'LL TAKE
GOOD CARE OF THIS,
AND, UH, I HOPE EVERYTHING
IS OK WITH YOUR FAMILY.
[PANTING]
[WHOOSH]
OLIVER QUEEN IS MINE.
NOT IF I KILL
HIM FIRST.
[WHOOSH]
AAH!
YES.
I'D LIKE TO REPORT
A SIGHTING OF VIGILANTE.
THIS IS DISTRICT ATTORNEY CHASE.
[BEEP BEEP]
[TYPING]
JOHN: HEY, OLIVER'S
OUT OF THE HOSPITAL,
HEADED TO CITY HALL.
ANY WORD FROM DINAH?
UM, SHE'S AT THE PRECINCT
TRYING TO RECOVER
THAT PIECE
OF VIGILANTE'S VISOR.
WHAT ABOUT YOU,
FELICITY?
AND DON'T TELL ME THAT
IT'S TRAFFIC CAMS.
WE BOTH KNOW THEY'RE
ON AUTO PILOT.
I SENT THEA SOMETHING
TO SWAY COUNCILMAN KULLENS.
APPARENTLY, HE'S THE SWING VOTE
ON OLIVER'S IMPEACHMENT.
PANDORA.
OFFICIALLY, HIS WIFE
DIED IN A CAR CRASH.
UNOFFICIALLY, SHE
CRASHED THE CAR ON PURPOSE.
SUICIDE.
HE USED HIS CLOUT
TO COVER IT UP,
SO I'M GUESSING HE'S NOT
GONNA WANT IT UNCOVERED.
AND YOU ARE OK
WITH THIS, RIGHT?
I THINK THE CITY NEEDS OLIVER
TO KEEP BEING MAYOR.
FELICITY, KULLENS
IS NOT A CRIMINAL.
-HE'S A HUMAN BEING...
-HE'S A POLITICIAN.
IT'S HARDLY
THE SAME THING.
A HUMAN BEING
THAT WENT THROUGH
A VERY TRAGIC ACCIDENT,
A VERY PRIVATE ONE.
COME ON.
THIS ISN'T YOU.
WELL, IT
PRETTY MUCH IS.
OK. DO YOU KNOW WHAT
YOUR SUPER POWER IS?
COMPUTERS?
EMPATHY...BIG, REFLEXIVE,
PURE EMPATHY.
WELL, MAYBE
I'M FRESH OUT.
BECAUSE OF BILLY.
IT'S A DARK WORLD,
AND FOR THE PAST
4 YEARS,
I HAVE WATCHED YOU
AND OLIVER
AND LAUREL AND THEA
AND ROY.
I HAVE WATCHED
ALL OF YOU USE
A LITTLE DARKNESS
TO FIGHT IT.
THAT'S TRUE.
SOMETIMES WE DO
FIGHT FIRE WITH FIRE,
BUT EVERY TIME
WE DO, FELICITY,
EVERY SINGLE TIME,
WE RISK BEING BURNED.
SOME DAYS, I CAN'T
HELP BUT FEEL AS IF
THE CITY WANTS TO
COLLAPSE IN ON ITSELF
AND ALL WE'RE DOING IS
DELAYING THE INEVITABLE.
NO. WE'RE
PREVENTING IT.
WE'RE THE GOOD GUYS.
DON'T YOU
FORGET THAT, PIKE.
IT'S WHAC-A-MOLE.
WE GOT PROMETHEUS,
THE VIGILANTE,
AND THE ONE WILD CARD
I THOUGHT MAYBE
MIGHT BE ON OUR SIDE
JUST MURDERED A COP.
NAH. THE GREEN ARROW
GOT PLAYED.
I DON'T KNOW.
WHAT I DO KNOW IS,
THE NEXT MAYOR
OWES ME A RAISE.
YEAH. I'LL PUT IN A WORD
WITH MAYOR QUEEN.
HE'S NOT IMPEACHED YET.
[TYPING]
PLEASE TELL ME
YOU DIDN'T SEND IT.
[SIGHS]
THIS THING WITH
KULLENS' WIFE,
HE DOESN'T
DESERVE THAT.
FELICITY TOLD YOU,
DIDN'T SHE?
THEA.
I HAVEN'T SENT
THE E-MAIL, OK?
OLLIE, DON'T LOOK
AT ME LIKE THAT.
IT'S POLITICS.
THERE'S ABOUT
TO BE A VOTE,
SO IT'S TIME
TO PLAY HARDBALL.
THIS ISN'T HARDBALL.
THIS IS CRUEL.
WHAT WOULD BE CRUEL
IS THE PEOPLE
OF THE CITY NOT HAVING
YOU AS THE MAYOR.
THE ANTI-CRIME UNIT,
LOW-INCOME HOUSING,
COMMON-SENSE
GUN LEGISLATION...
OLLIE, IN THE SHORT
AMOUNT OF TIME
YOU'VE
BEEN DOING THIS,
YOU'VE DONE
A REMARKABLE JOB.
PLEASE JUST LET ME
DO WHAT I HAVE TO DO
TO HELP YOU KEEP
DOING THAT.
FELICITY TOLD ME
ABOUT THIS KULLENS THING
BECAUSE OF SOMETHING
THAT JOHN SAID TO HER.
THEA, WHEN YOU FIGHT
FIRE WITH FIRE,
YOU ARE PROBABLY
GONNA GET BURNED.
I WON'T.
IT'LL BE FINE.
LIKE IT WAS
WITH SUSAN?
YOU DESTROYED
HER CAREER.
NOW YOU'VE GRADUATED
TO BLACKMAIL.
WHERE DOES IT STOP?
[ALARM SIREN]
[SPEAKING RUSSIAN]
[BEEPING]
MAGIC HANDS.
THE MAGNETIC
RESONANCE FREQUENCIES
WITHIN VIGILANTE'S TECH
ARE NOW COMMUNICATING
WITH MY T-SPHERES.
JOHN: GREAT,
SO WHAT DOES IT MEAN?
CAN WE CATCH
THE VIGILANTE OR NOT?
WELL, CROSS
YOUR FINGERS AND YOUR TOES.
FELICITY: IT'S WORKING.
THE T-SPHERE IS PICKING UP
ON THE SIGNAL FROM
THE PIECE OF VISOR.
YEAH, BUT THE OTHER
ONE IS STILL WONKY.
CURTIS: NO, NO.
IT...IT'S NOT.
IT'S ACTUALLY TRACKING
THE REST OF THE VISOR.
SO LET'S TAKE DOWN
THIS S.O.B.
WITHOUT OLIVER?
IF VIGILANTE GETS TO HIM,
WE'LL BE DOING THIS
WITHOUT OLIVER
PERMANENTLY.
-LET'S SUIT UP.
-SUIT UP. OH, SORRY.
I THOUGHT, UM...
I THOUGHT SINCE OLIVER'S GONE,
I WOULD PROBABLY...BUT IT MAKES
MORE SENSE PROBABLY FOR YOU...
I'LL MAKE SURE I WORK
ON THE TIMING OF THAT, PROMISE.
-BALLS.
-OH, MY T-SPHERE...
OH, DON'T CALL THEM BALLS.
YOU SPEAK
WITH POLLARD?
SHE WON'T CALL YOU
TO TESTIFY
WITHOUT
KULLENS' BLESSING...
WE'RE NOT
GONNA GET THAT.
AND THE COUNCIL HEARING
DIRECTLY FROM YOU
IS ONLY ONE OF TWO
WAYS I CAN SEE US
WINNING THIS THING.
-WHAT'S THE SECOND WAY?
-YOU WON'T LIKE IT.
DOES IT INVOLVE OFFERING UP
A SACRIFICIAL LAMB?
EITHER ME OR
DETECTIVE MALONE.
OLIVER,
THIS IMPEACHMENT
IS ABOUT
PUNISHING SOMEONE,
AND IF YOU DON'T
OFFER UP A NAME,
THIS WILL BE
THE LAST TIME
YOU'RE LOOKING OUT
THAT WINDOW.
IF THE COUNCIL'S NOT
GONNA LET ME TESTIFY
AT THE HEARING,
THEN I NEED
TO TAKE MY CASE
DIRECTLY TO THE PUBLIC.
-A PRESS CONFERENCE?
-YEAH.
MIND FILLING ME IN
ON WHO
YOU'RE THROWING
UNDER THE BUS?
THE GREEN ARROW.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[TIRES SCREECH]
RIGHT HERE...
AND...STOP.
-WE...WE GOT HIM?
-UH, THINK SO.
-OH, THIS IS BAD.
-WHY'S THAT?
THE BUILDING THAT YOU
JUST STOPPED IN FRONT OF,
WELL, CITY HALL IS LOCATED
DIRECTLY BEHIND IT,
OFFERING PERFECT
LINE OF SIGHT
TO WHERE OLIVER'S
GIVING HIS SPEECH.
IT'S THE VIGILANTE'S
BOOK DEPOSITORY.
FELICITY, WE NEED YOU
TO CHECK THE BLUEPRINTS.
FELICITY: YEAH,
ALREADY ON IT. OK.
THE SIXTH FLOOR
IS UNDER RENOVATION.
-DOLLARS TO DOUGHNUTS...
-THAT'S WHERE HE'LL BE.
[WHOOSH]
UNH!
[CELL PHONE RINGS]
YEP? I'M LISTENING.
ALL RIGHT. COPY THAT.
VIGILANTE IS ACROSS
THE STREET, SIXTH FLOOR.
HE'S GONNA TAKE YOU OUT
AS SOON AS YOU WALK
OUTSIDE
INTO THE OPEN.
IS THE TEAM ON SITE?
YEAH.
THEN IT'LL BE FINE.
[BEEPING]
EVENING, EVERYONE.
I'D LIKE TO THANK
THE CITY COUNCIL
FOR CONDUCTING THESE HEARINGS
WITH HONESTY AND INTEGRITY.
SIMPLY WISH THAT I
COULD HAVE DONE THE SAME
WITH REGARDS
TO THE GREEN ARROW'S MURDER
OF DETECTIVE WILLIAM MALONE.
-TERRIFIC, WHERE IS HE?
-THIS WAY, THIS WAY.
[GUN COCKS]
GET DOWN!
-HA HA HA!
-WHAT'S SO FUNNY?
THINK I JUST FOUND A NEW
USE FOR MY T-SPHERE.
YOUR WHAT? AGH!
WHEN I TOOK THE OATH OF OFFICE,
I PROMISED TO BE HONEST
AND FORTHRIGHT.
I NEVER WANTED TO BE
A POLITICIAN
WHO RELIED ON DIRTY POLITICS
OR UNDERHANDED TACTICS.
RENE: OH, NOW THAT'S
WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT
OH, NO.
[MACHINE GUN FIRE]
AND IN THE SPIRIT
OF THAT TRANSPARENCY,
I THINK I OWE EVERYONE
AN EXPLANATION
AS TO WHY I COVERED UP
WHAT THE GREEN ARROW DID.
[BULLETS RICOCHETING]
AGH!
I DID IT IN A MISGUIDED ATTEMPT
TO PROTECT EVERYONE
FROM THE TRAGIC NEWS
THAT THE GREEN ARROW
HAD BECOME A COP KILLER,
THAT A MAN WE HAD PUT OUR FAITH
IN HAD FAILED THIS CITY,
AND I DIDN'T THINK WE COULD
AFFORD TO LOSE ANOTHER HERO.
CURTIS: HEY, VIGILANTE,
I'VE GOT TWO OF THESE.
NICE AIM.
THAT'S THE THING.
THEY AIM THEMSELVES.
RENE: HOSS.
HOSS.
AAGH!
YO, HOSS,
THAT WAS BADASS.
THAT MEAN NO MORE
BALL JOKES?
HELL, NO. UH!
AH! AH!
REMIND ME TO THANK CISCO
FOR THAT UPGRADED KEVLAR.
YOU GUYS
ALL RIGHT?
YEAH, BUT WHAT
ABOUT OLIVER?
BUT THE TRUTH
IS MORE IMPORTANT,
AND THE TRUTH IS THAT
THE GREEN ARROW HAS GONE ROGUE.
WE MUST DISAVOW HIM.
WE MUST HUNT HIM AND PUNISH HIM
FOR WHAT HE HAS DONE.
GREEN ARROW'S NOT A HERO.
HE IS WHAT'S KEEPING
STAR CITY
FROM BEING THE BEST
THAT IT CAN BE.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
THEY'RE STILL
DELIBERATING.
OH, THAT'S TAKING
LONGER THAN I THOUGHT.
YEAH. WELL, YOU GAVE THEM
PLENTY TO THINK ABOUT.
SO HOW'S IT FEEL, HUH,
MAKING YOURSELF INTO
A VILLAIN LIKE THAT?
SUSAN WILLIAMS IS HERE.
-YOU WANT ME TO SAY YOU'RE BUSY?
-NO. NO.
I'D LIKE TO TELL
THE TRUTH
FOR THE REST OF THE DAY
IF AT ALL POSSIBLE.
-PLEASE SEND HER IN.
-ALL RIGHT.
SUSAN,
PLEASE COME IN.
GLAD YOU'RE HERE.
SUSAN, I'M VERY SORRY.
I GOT MY JOB BACK.
AN ANONYMOUS HACKER
CONFESSED
THAT THE PLAGIARISM
STORY WAS FAKE,
SAID THEY WERE JUST
MESSING WITH US.
-MY BOSS APOLOGIZED.
-WELL, THAT'S GOOD NEWS.
STILL, THOUGH,
I'M REALLY SORRY.
ARE YOU?
WHAT I MEAN IS,
YOU DIDN'T KNOW
ABOUT THIS
BEFOREHAND, DID YOU?
NO. I HAD NO IDEA.
ONCE YOU DID,
YOU MADE THEM
MAKE IT RIGHT,
RIGHT?
-ARE WE OFF THE RECORD?
-YES.
-YEAH.
-THANK YOU.
SO WHAT HAPPENS NEXT?
YOU MEAN, UH, WHAT DO
I DO WITH YOUR SECRET?
I KEEP IT.
I CARE ABOUT
THE CITY, AND...
AND YOU'RE WORKING
DOUBLE TIME
TO MAKE IT
A BETTER PLACE.
I DO APPRECIATE THAT,
BUT I MEANT
WHAT HAPPENS NEXT
WITH US?
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
UH, SORRY TO INTERRUPT,
BUT I THINK
YOU'LL BE HAPPY
THAT WE DID.
COUNCIL VOTED
AGAINST
IMPEACHMENT.
HEH. HEH.
THANK YOU
SO MUCH, ADRIAN.
I COULD NOT HAVE
DONE THIS WITHOUT YOU.
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
NO THANKS NEEDED.
YOU'RE NOT JUST
MY BOSS, OLIVER.
YOU'RE MY FRIEND.
I'M GONNA GO GIVE
THEA THE GOOD NEWS.
-I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
-OK.
OLIVER: HEY...
[KNOCKS ON DOOR]
NO NEED TO PACK UP.
WE WON, BOTH GET
TO KEEP OUR JOBS.
YEAH, NOT...
NOT BOTH OF US.
LOOK, OLLIE.
YOU...YOU WERE RIGHT.
I...I AM GETTING
DEEPER AND DEEPER
INTO THE MUCK LATELY,
AND IT'S LIKE
MY BLOODLUST LAST YEAR,
EXCEPT INSTEAD OF ARROWS
AND SWORDS, I'VE REPLACED
IT WITH POLITICS
AND SLANDER,
SO I'M...
THAT DOESN'T MEAN THAT
YOU HAVE TO QUIT, THEA.
-I NEED YOU HERE.
-OLLIE, PLEASE.
PLEASE DON'T ASK ME
TO STAY BECAUSE I WILL.
I WILL FOR YOU,
BUT I AM BROKEN, OK?
I...I NEED YOU
TO LET ME GO.
LET ME GO SO I CAN
TRY TO FIX MYSELF.
WELL, UH...
YOUR RESIGNATION'S
ACCEPTED.
THANK YOU.
[SIGHS]
MY RESIGNATION LETTER'S
ON THE DESK.
WHEN I SIGNAL,
YOU MUST ALIGN WITH ANATOLY,
WHO CALLSSPROSS DOPROSS,
OR GREGOR OUR INCUMBENTPAKHAN.
NOW, LET'S GET THIS
OVER WITH QUICKLY.
HEY, STOP.
MR. QUEEN,
YOU DO NOT HAVE FLOOR.
JUST GIVE ME
10 SECONDS.
LISTEN TO WHAT
I HAVE TO SAY.
IF YOU DON'T
LIKE IT, SHOOT ME.
AS YOU WISH.
[CLICK]
THIS LAPTOP CONTAINS
80 MILLION RUBLES
IN TRANSFERS FROM
KOVAR'S ACCOUNTS
INTO ACCOUNTS THAT
GREGOR CONTROLS.
YES. WE KNOW THIS,
TO SPREAD AMONG
BRATVA CAPTAINS.
IT ALSO CONTAINS
40 MILLION RUBLES
WORTH OF BANK
TRANSFERS FROM KOVAR
THAT GREGOR
HASN'T DISCLOSED.
OPEN IT. ASK HIM
IF IT'S TRUE.
IS THIS TRUE,
GREGOR?
[TYPING]
40 MILLION RUBLES.
SO IT'S TRUE.
IF ANYBODY WISHES
TO CAST A NEW VOTE,
PLEASE DO SO NOW.
IT SEEMS THAT YOU ARE
DECIDING VOTE, VIKTOR.
WHAT SAY YOU,
MY FRIEND?
WE HAVE
A NEWPAKHAN.
THIS IS MOST
DISAPPOINTING.
I LIKED MANY OF YOU.
COUNCIL ISN'T IMPEACHING,
STILL THE MAYOR.
RENE: YET THE GREEN ARROW
IS PUBLIC ENEMY NUMBER ONE.
JOHN: WE'VE DEALT
WITH THE POLICE
ON OUR BACKS BEFORE.
DINAH: NOT LIKE THIS.
ONE OF THEIR OWN IS DEAD.
NO. DINAH'S RIGHT,
AND NOW WE KNOW
JUST HOW MUCH THE
POLICE CAN INTERFERE
WITH OUR WORK HERE.
CURTIS: UM, CAN I GO?
KIND OF GETTING BACK
TOGETHER WITH PAUL.
IT'S A BIG DEAL.
UH, CAN I LEAVE? CAN I...
YES. YES. OF COURSE.
GO. HAVE FUN.
EVERYONE SHOULD
HAVE FUN TONIGHT.
UH, JUST QUICKLY,
THOUGH...
MIGHT HAVE BURIED
THE HEADLINE HERE...
YOU ALL SAVED
MY LIFE,
AND 5 MONTHS AGO,
I NEVER WOULD HAVE
THOUGHT THAT
WAS POSSIBLE.
THANK YOU FOR
WORKING HARD.
THANK YOU
FOR BANDING TOGETHER.
-THANK YOU FOR...
-SORRY. I...
I MEAN, THANK YOU
FOR SAYING THANK YOU...
WOW, MAN TO MAN,
THAT MEANS A LOT...
BUT I'M REALLY LATE
TO SEE PAUL, SO...
-GIVE PAUL MY BEST.
-THANK YOU.
-GOOD LUCK.
THANK YOU.
I'M SORRY. SORRY.
WE WERE STOPPING
AN ASSASSINATION.
CAN YOU BELIEVE I
STOPPED AN ASSASSINATION?
HA! WOW. HA!
SO, UM, ON THE WAY
OVER HERE,
I REHEARSED WHAT
I WOULD SAY TO YOU...
HEH...HOW I WOULD
WIN YOU BACK,
TELL YOU I LOVE YOU,
AND ALL I JUST STARTED WITH
WAS DEFINITELY NOT
HOW I PLANNED ON OPENING.
CAN I START AGAIN?
I'M GONNA START AGAIN.
-WHEN I CAME OVER...
-IT'S NICE TO SEE YOU, CURTIS.
I MEAN THAT,
AS MUCH AS YOU'RE GOING
TO THINK THAT I DON'T.
WHAT?
ARE YOU DIVORCING ME?
I'M SORRY.
I REALLY AM.
[DISTANT SIREN]
-FELICITY, HI.
-G'AH! HI.
I AM SO GLAD
YOU GOT IN TOUCH,
THOUGH I AM
A LITTLE SURPRISED.
YEAH. ME, TOO.
WELL, "SURPRISED" ISN'T
EXACTLY THE RIGHT WORD
TO DESCRIBE HOW
I'M, UM, FEELING.
WHAT'S
THE RIGHT WORD?
READY.
A GOOD FRIEND OF MINE
TOLD ME THAT IF YOU'RE
GOING TO TRY TO FIGHT
FIRE WITH FIRE,
YOU'RE GONNA GET BURNED,
BUT THEN ANOTHER FRIEND
OF MINE CAME THROUGH
SOMETHING PRETTY SCARY
TONIGHT BECAUSE
HE HAD BACKUP, A TEAM.
YOU'RE ACCEPTING THE
INVITATION TO JOIN HELIX.
YES, FULL THROTTLE.
HA HA!
[BEEP BEEP]
-SUSAN.
-OH, HEY.
I THOUGHT
WE COULD TALK.
-ABOUT?
-AN EXCLUSIVE.
CAN WE SET UP
THE MEETING TOMORROW.
I'M LATE FOR A DINNER.
THE THING IS
IS THAT THIS STORY,
IT'S IMPORTANT.
YOU COULD CALL IT
LIFE OR DEATH.
MAN: GREG, MOVE YOUR HEAD.