OLIVER:
My name is Oliver Queen.
For five years, I was stranded on an island
with only one goal.
Survive.
Oliver Queen is alive.
OLIVER:
Now I will fulfill my father's dying wish...
...to use the list of names he left me...
...and bring down those
who are poisoning my city.
To do this, I must become someone else.
I must become something else.
Previously on Arrow:
Company Mrs. Queen invested in
doesn't exist.
Tempest purchased a warehouse
in Starling City.
Could never tell if the playboy thing
was all an act.
But I guess after a while,
it doesn't really matter.
He is a vigilante. He's a damn criminal.
Here's the security footage.
What do you want me to look for?
Anything out of the ordinary.
What is that? Play that again.
You're under arrest on suspicion...
- What is going on?
-...of assault--
- Are you out of your mind?
- And murder.
- Dinner.
- Come-- Hey, I've got an idea.
Why don't you let me shoot that thing...
...and you can go pick up the bloody, dead,
disgusting animal?
- What?
- Try.
Breathe. Everything breathe.
Breathe. Aim.
- Fire.
- Yeah.
Aim that tree.
Breathe.
[SPEAKS IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
- What does that mean?
-"You will die badly."
Get.
[OLIVER GROANING]
Wait. Wait. You can't leave me here.
Don't do this to me. Please.
[SCREAMS]
Please! I didn't do anything!
POLICEMAN 1: Stay back.
OLIVER: The police think they know who I am.
They think I'm the vigilante.
The man in the hood,
terrorizing the city's criminals.
They also think they have me trapped.
That I have no way out.
They're only half-right.
OLIVER: This is a mistake.
- I'll be asking you a few questions.
Standard stuff for the report.
Have you been arrested before?
It's okay, I know the answer to that one.
Plenty of times.
- Like I said, this is a mistake.
- As far as I can tell, the mistake I made...
...was not shooting you down at the docks
when I had the chance.
- I am not who you think I am.
- Oh, you're exactly who I think you are.
You're a menace
who doesn't care about who he hurts.
You're doing it with bows and arrows
instead of trust funds and yachts.
Detective, you hate me. I get it.
But that doesn't make me a vigilante.
No, the security camera footage of you...
...from the Unidac Auction
with the green hood does that.
Again, I ran into the stairwell
once I heard shooting.
I saw a dufﬂe I thought maybe belonged
to the shooter, looked inside and saw...
-...a hood.
- You took it home?
We can't find it.
What about harassing Adam Hunt?
Happened to take place
across the street...
-...from your little bash.
- Coincidences.
No. When they pile up like that,
it becomes evidence.
- Parents are here.
- Tell them to wait.
- I wanna see my son.
LANCE: I'm in the middle of an interrogation.
Detective, I know you hate my family,
but I had no idea you'd go so far...
...to arrest my son without any grounds.
I have solid grounds,
and I have evidence.
Which you can present
to Queen's attorney when he gets here.
Until then, this interrogation
is over, detective.
Sure. You have 15 minutes.
Detective Lance appears to be
on some personal vendetta.
He is.
He blames me
for the death of his daughter.
He also thinks
that I dress up in a green hood...
...and shoot people with arrows.
-Important thing is not to say anything...
-...until your attorney gets here.
- Fine. I want Laurel.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
Oliver, I don't think your ex-girlfriend
can be counted on to be objective here.
She knows me better than anyone.
She knows that I could never be this guy.
- Walter, you say Lance has a vendetta?
- Yes.
I think Laurel can get him off of it.
He raised her to do the right thing.
That includes representing
an innocent man.
So, Morn...
...please.
REPORTER: Oliver Queen was arrested today
on suspicion of being the vigilante...
...that has been targeting the wealthy
and corrupt.
Laurel.
- Mrs. Queen, what--?
-It's Oliver. Something's happened.
It's been all over the news.
[SCOFFS]
- These charges are ludicrous.
- I know.
- Can I ask you, who's representing him?
- Well, that's why I'm here.
He wants you to represent him.
- Me?
- Yes. I told him it was a bad idea.
But, to be frank, I am desperate.
He says if you don't represent him,
he doesn't want any attorney.
Mrs. Queen,
my father is the arresting officer.
- Yes.
- I don't think it's a good idea...
...for me to represent someone
I've been involved with.
Listen, I am sorry for what your family
is going through--
No. No apologies.
Your idealism, I think, is why my son,
for all his mistakes, is so smitten with you.
Regardless,
it was a bad idea on his part...
...and I am sorry
if I made you feel uncomfortable.
Docket ending 1-9-4-1,
People v. Oliver Queen.
Murder, aggravated assault...
...assault with intent,
menacing and trespassing.
- Where's your attorney, Mr. Queen?
- I'm representing myself, judge.
I'm not sure that's the wisest course,
Mr. Queen.
I think it is.
- I'm innocent.
- Then we'll consider that your plea.
- Thank you.
- Now, as to bail.
Your Honor, Mr. Queen's family
owns a pair of private jets.
While on the subject of their wealth,
there is virtually no bail amount...
...that could guarantee his presence
at trial.
So then I guess it's a good thing
that the people's case is so circumstantial.
Dinah Laurel Lance. I'd like to file my
appearance on behalf of the defendant.
Mr. Queen's wealth should not deprive him
of the right to be released on bail...
-...under the presumption of innocence.
- He is a flight risk.
Then minimize the risk.
The defendant is willing submit to home
confinement and electronic monitoring...
...through the wearing of a UKG-45
administrated ankle device.
- No, he wouldn't.
- Sold.
- Your Honor--
- Bail is set at $15 million...
...5 million dollars bond.
Defendant to see Probation
for the fitting of a GPS device.
I knew you couldn't resist saving my ass.
- Gonna make me regret this, aren't you?
- No. It's gonna be like old times.
Fortunately, with the legal case,
there's no way that you're this vigilante.
- I agree.
- He's actually trying to make a difference.
We both know that's not really your style.
Mom, it's not that bad.
Okay, this device has a direct line
into the precinct.
You stay on the property, you're golden.
Any questions?
I'm having a sizable get-together
here tomorrow evening...
...and there is a likely chance
it spills into the outdoor pool.
Pool deck's fine. Step on the grass, they're
sending a team to forcibly subdue you.
WALTER: Thank you, officer.
OFFICER: Of course.
- A sizable get together?
- I am confined for the foreseeable future.
I might as well make the most of it.
Party is gonna be themed.
I'm thinking prison.
Burning Man meets
Shawshank Redemption.
The invite says,
"Come before Oliver Queen gets off."
Maybe a party's not in the best of taste,
considering the circumstances.
Tommy, the circumstances are why
we're having the party in the first place.
I want people to know I'm not worried
about any of this.
Well, that makes one of us.
LAUREL: Before you start yelling--
- Why yell?
You're defending the man
that killed your sister.
Oliver did not kill Sara.
She wouldn't have been on that boat.
Have you considered the possibility that
that's the reason...
-...you're trying to make him this menace?
- It is the videotape, the suspicious timing.
- That is the reason.
- This is Oliver Queen we're talking about.
He wrecks fancy cars and he dates models.
He doesn't kill people.
No, he just uses them. Like he used Sara.
And like he used you.
He's only asked you to be his lawyer
to get at me.
No, he asked me to be his lawyer
to get through to you.
You hate the hood and you hate Oliver
and you want them to be the same person.
But Oliver isn't the reason why Sara died
or the reason Mom left.
I don't have to listen to this.
And by the way...
...you're not the only one
who misses them.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Yeah?
Thank you for coming. Shut the door.
Just a matter of time
before the police caught up with you.
- Except they didn't.
- Oliver, they got you on video.
I knew the camera was there,
I knew the police...
...would review the footage and arrest me.
All part of the plan.
So you wanted to get arrested?
I returned to Starling City
and a few days later the vigilante appears.
Somebody
was gonna make the connection.
What part of serving yourself
to the cops...
...will help you avoid going to prison?
- There's more to it.
- There better be...
...because your family is freaking out.
Oliver, your mother and your sister
just got you back...
...and now you're gonna put them
through a trial?
- Don't you care?
- Of course I care.
The mission comes first.
Who is he?
Leo Mueller.
German arms dealer, suspected in the theft
of 100 M2-49 squad automatic weapons.
- Okay.
- Last night he arrived in Starling City...
...to sell the guns.
Don't you imagine there's enough trouble
you're in than to go after this guy?
I imagine what would happen if a gang
got military hardware.
I imagine our city's streets
turned into a war zone.
But you're under house arrest, Oliver,
which means you can't go after this guy.
Look. For now, I would just like you
to shadow Mueller.
I would like you to track his movements.
I wanna know where the buy
is happening.
Okay.
- And how am I supposed to track him?
- Well, you know us billionaire vigilantes.
We do love our toys.
[ELECTRICITY HUMMING]
Wow.
Ow.
Whoo.
[BEEPING]
Oh, that's sweet.
- You wanted to see me, sir?
- No, I didn't.
In fact, this meeting isn't taking place.
How long have you been head of Security
at Queen Consolidated, Josiah?
- Going on seven years now, sir.
- Sounds about right.
But what I'm about to tell you
will test the bounds of your discretion.
You're aware of the Queen's Gambit?
Robert Queen's ill-fated yacht?
I found it.
Sir, the boat went down
in the North China Sea five years ago.
Which is why my discovery
of its remains in a warehouse downtown...
...was unexpected, to say the least.
I want you to transfer those remains
to a secure location.
Can I count on you?
[CHUCKLES]
What's going on, sir?
That's very much
what I'm trying to determine.
Thank you both for coming.
Thank you.
It's nice to get out of the house.
I'll cut right to it. Detective Lance arrested
your client without consulting my office.
So, congratulations,
I am willing to consider a plea in this case.
Absolutely not.
SPENCER:
Mr. Queen spent five years in seclusion...
...on a deserted island,
cut off from civilization.
It is quite possible he's suffering
from some form of post-traumatic stress.
Given that,
we would support a plea of insanity...
...conditional on a period of indeterminate
incarceration at a psychiatric facility.
- No, thank you. I'm not crazy.
- Finally something we agree on.
- He's not a nut. He's a killing machine.
- I'm neither.
There is nothing you can say
that I would believe.
I'll take a polygraph.
- Polygraphs are inadmissible.
- In front of a jury.
I'll talk a polygraph in front of him.
He's the one I need to convince.
I'm gonna need a minute.
You're looking at life in prison.
What Spencerjust offered you is a gift.
I'm not crazy. I am innocent.
I kind of wanna take the polygraph...
...and if I take it and I fail,
then I will consider making a deal.
Fine.
I'll set up the poly. And I will tell Spencer
that we're not pleading out.
But, Oliver? You have a family. Friends.
People who actually care about you.
So don't for one second think you're the
only person with something to lose here.
I'll be right back.
[GROANS]
Please. Sit. You're making me feel rude.
I do apologize
for my men's treatment of you.
They're...
They're trained to view any stranger
as hostile.
I'm Edward Fyers, by the way.
And you are?
I'm Oliver Queen.
I was shipwrecked here.
I don't know for how long.
My family has money, lots of money.
You would be--
You'd be really well compensated
for my rescue.
Well, I look forward to that.
But for the moment, let's just talk.
About what?
Well, for instance...
...this gentleman.
Do you know him?
- No.
- No?
- No. Who's he?
- You're a poor liar.
I've been polite.
I'll offer you one more chance
before my manners leave me.
Hey. Hey. I don't know this guy.
L-- I thought I was on this island
all by myself.
Do you know what this island is named?
We're on Lian Yu.
Mandarin for "purgatory."
But I can make it feel like hell.
I don't know why you're protecting him.
You're young. Foolish.
Perhaps you don't know why either.
Think on that
when you're begging for death.
He's yours now.
Hey, Speedy. One of the workers left a keg
too far from the bar.
Can you ask them to move it? Please?
I got the ankle thingy.
I don't want to set off a SWAT invasion.
Hey, all this stuff, it's gonna be fine.
I promise.
Yeah, well, when you and Dad left
on the yacht...
...you promised me I'd see you
in a few days, which didn't happen.
This is different than that.
I didn't do any of this stuff.
You know that. Right?
You're out all the time.
You have those scars, and since you've
been back, you've been acting really weird.
None of this makes me
some Robin Hood wannabe.
And you gave me this.
I mean, it's an arrowhead.
Oh, man.
Thea, I bought that in the gift shop
of the Beijing Airport.
Now I'm sort of happy I didn't buy you
the shot glass with the panda on it...
...because then you'd be worried
I was Panda Man.
You know,
I knew you couldn't be this person.
I just-- I can't lose you again.
Deal.
Moira, thank you for coming
on such short notice.
Yes. Could you please make this quick.
I'm in the midst of a family emergency.
Yes, of course.
It's all over the local news.
Possibly even national.
- Well, I know what you're thinking.
- Do you?
My son is not the man targeting the list.
The charges are preposterous.
Not according to the district attorney,
assistant attorney...
...the investigating detective
and the police that filed charges.
- That detective has a vendetta.
- Why?
Is there something untoward
about your family?
If so, something really needs
to be done about that.
LANCE:
ls your name Oliver Queen?
You don't know who I am, detective?
The questions calibrate the polygraph.
- Is your name Oliver Queen?
- Yes.
Were you born in Starling City,
May 16th, 1985?
Yes.
- Is your hair blue?
- No.
Ever been to Iron Heights prison?
No.
Are you the man in this picture?
Where can I find the man in this picture?
No.
- You steal $40 million off Adam Hunt?
- No, I didn't.
Were you marooned on an island
for five years?
- Yes.
- Is that relevant?
Since you asked, whatever happened
to your client on that island...
...turned him into a cold-blooded killer.
[SCREAMING]
The physician reported that 20 percent
of your body is covered in scar tissue.
[SCREAMING]
The machine won't work
unless you ask a question.
Did that happen to you there?
Yes.
When you came back, you told everyone
that you were alone on that island.
Are you claiming that your scars
were self-inflicted?
No.
I wasn't alone. I didn't wanna talk
about what happened on the island.
- Why not?
- The people that were there tortured me.
Have you killed anyone?
Yes.
When I asked your daughter Sara
to come on my father's yacht with me.
I killed your daughter.
I'd have to study the data,
but just eyeballing it, he's telling the truth.
Hmm.
Can I assume you'll be recommending
Ms. Spencer...
...to drop all charges against my client?
No. I know a guilty man when I see one.
He is guilty.
Whether you can see it or not.
[3OH!3'S "YOU'RE GONNA LOVE THIS"
PLAYING FROM SPEAKER]
[MUSIC STOPS]
- Hi, everybody.
ALL: Hey.
I'm very touched that you came to celebrate
with me before I am sent up the river.
Closest neighbors are 6 miles away,
so don't worry about the noise.
Actually, on second thought...
...let's wake those losers up!
[MUSIC RESUMES PLAYING]
[ALL CHEERING]
If you think this is what prison's like,
you are in for a rude awakening.
Mueller's car's been in the warehouse
district of the Glades for 45 minutes.
Yeah, it's a good place for an arms deal.
Okay, since it's going down tonight,
what do we do?
- Drop a dime on Mueller with the cops?
- No. The man in the hood...
...he's gonna stop them.
Oliver, you can't leave the house.
It doesn't have to be me in the hood.
That's why you threw
this ridiculous party?
A hundred witnesses placing you
at the house...
...while I'm across town
dressed as a vigilante?
I thought it was gonna be enough
just for you to be seen in the hood.
I didn't count on Mueller showing up,
and the possibility that the Glades...
...could be flooded with machine guns.
Look...
...I promise, it was never my intention
to put you in harm's way.
Oliver, I didn't think joining your crusade
was ever gonna be risk-free.
I just don't like being played.
You have gotten used to lying
to everyone else...
...but I'm the one guy you don't lie to.
You're right.
I'm sorry.
So am I going to jail?
No, man.
I gotta stop an arms deal.
[PHONE RINGING]
- Hello?
VOGEL: Mr. Steele.
I'm sorry to bother you, sir.
This is Mike Vogel down in Security.
I have some sad news for you.
The company's head of Security,
Josiah Hudson...
...was in a car accident tonight.
He's dead, sir.
[DANCE MUSIC PLAYING FROM SPEAKER]
OLIVER:
Hello.
Do we have a legal meeting or something?
Because I have friends over.
Do you think maybe
you can tear yourself away...
...from this inappropriately themed rave
for a couple minutes?
LAUREL:
Wow.
I can't remember the last time
that I've been in this room.
I can. Halloween 2005.
We were getting ready for Tommy's party.
Ah. Yes, I wore those horrible fishnets.
I thought you looked good.
Listen...
...I just wanted to come by
and apologize...
...for my father's behavior today
during the polygraph.
You don't have to apologize for him.
He has a right to feel any way that he wants.
It wasn't just Sara, Ollie.
What do you mean?
After Sara died,
my father threw himself into his work.
I think that's part of the reason
I'm an attorney.
He ran to the law and I followed.
But my mother couldn't.
So she left him.
Left us.
Look, I'm not trying to tell you this
to make you feel bad or worse.
I just-- I really want you
to understand him.
Why don't you hate me?
You should.
I did.
For so long, I did, Ollie.
But after today, I realized...
...I was so focused
on what happened to my family...
...that I didn't even stop and wonder
what could have happened to you.
I didn't know about the torture
or your scars.
What happened to you on that island
was far more than you deserved.
And I was wrong
that I didn't ask you before.
But I'm asking you now.
I need to know. I need to see.
Are you sure?
Yes.
How did you survive this?
There were times when I wanted to die.
In the end...
...there was something I wanted more.
You don't-- Laurel, you don't have to go.
Amazing. You have resolve
I didn't credit you for.
Or perhaps
he truly doesn't know anything.
Yes.
You should put him out of his misery.
[MUELLER SPEAKS IN GERMAN]
MUELLER:
The M249 machine gun.
Gas-powered, air-cooled,
fires up to 800 rounds per minute.
[WHISTLES]
We need to move. Now.
[YELLS IN GERMAN]
Go. Come on.
Let's go.
Well, I'm not accustomed
to being summoned to the office...
...in the middle of the night.
Well, what was it that was so important
that I had to race down here?
I found the Queen's Gambit, Moira.
I know you secretly
had the boat salvaged.
I wanted to move it to a secure location
before confronting you about it.
In fact, I sent Josiah Hudson to
the warehouse for precisely that purpose...
...but he died mysteriously
in a car accident.
I hope you now have a better understanding
of why it is I've been so distant of late.
It's very disconcerting to discover the
person with whom you share your home...
...your bed and your heart,
has been lying to you so convincingly.
I would be a fool not to consider
all the things you have told me were lies.
- Walter, you're my husband.
- Yes, I am.
Walter, please.
You've got to stop looking into this.
It's not safe.
You'll be-- You'll be upsetting people.
People with influence.
You are very far out of your depth.
[PHONE RINGS]
DIGGLE:
Man in the hood, 1. Gang bangers, zero.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Hang on. Yeah?
Mr. Queen, if you're entertaining guests
upstairs...
...should I have drinks sent up?
OLIVER: No, it's just me here...
...and I'm on my way back down.
Good job. Now get back here.
LANCE:
Yeah. Yeah.
How did you know I was in trouble?
When the guy was fighting you,
he broke the ankle monitor.
MOIRA: Are you all right?
- I'm fine.
- Oliver.
- Mom, I promise.
This is on you. By accusing my son
publicly, you've made him a target.
WALTER: Do you have any idea
who attacked Oliver?
We haven't identified him. It must be
someone with a grudge against the hood.
- What are you doing?
- Just got a call from my lieutenant.
An arms dealer was attacked
across town tonight.
By the vigilante.
Multiple witnesses put him there.
In light of that, all charges against your son
are dropped.
I'm truly sorry for what's happened
to your family, Quentin.
But would you kindly get the hell out
of my house?
OLIVER:
Mr. Lance?
Thank you.
Moira. Did we have an appointment?
No. But I decided to screw propriety
after you tried to have my son killed.
I'm sure you understand
I was justified in suspecting your son...
...of being the vigilante
targeting our associates.
I had to take steps.
And now that you know
your steps were taken in error?
That Oliver is not your enemy?
[CHUCKLES]
I offer my sincerest apologies.
I know you found out
I had the yacht salvaged.
Just as I know
you had Josiah Hudson killed.
Well, accidents tend to befall people
who are too curious.
I've been the good soldier.
I've done everything you asked.
But if any member of my family
so much as gets a paper cut...
...I will burn your entire world to ashes.
[GROANING]
I tell you, island dangerous.
But you not tell them where to find me.
You stronger than I thought.
Take it. I lead them off. You stay.
Remember, everything breathe.
You breathe, you survive here longer.
I'm coming with you.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
- Rough party.
- My father told me what happened.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
These are your polygraph results.
My father asked you
if you'd ever been to Iron Heights.
It's the prison where the vigilante saved me
last week.
It's also where you and I went
on our eighth-grade field trip.
When you said
that you had never been there...
...I thought maybe you were just nervous,
or that you'd forgotten.
But then I looked at your results...
...and there is a slight flutter in your answer
to that question.
And if you lied on one,
you could have lied on others.
What happened to me being too selfish
to be a masked crusader?
Oliver, I saw your scars.
Do you wanna know why I don't talk
about what happened to me there?
Because, if people knew...
...if you knew...
...you'd see me differently.
And not as some vigilante guy.
As damaged.
I don't sleep.
I barely eat.
I can barely sign my name...
...let alone aim a bow and arrow.
After last night...
...clearly we're still attracted
to one another.
Oliver...
...nothing can ever happen between us.
I know.
DIGGLE:
So you lied to her.
Or maybe you just gave her
a version of the truth.
I told her what she needed to hear.
She was too close.
DIGGLE:
The sad thing is...
...I think you actually believe that.
I think things didn't go down exactly
as you planned.
You didn't count on so many people
having questions.
Doubting you.
You didn't think about what happens
when you lie.
- Thank you, Chris.
- Walter?
DIGGLE:
Especially when you lie to ones you love most.
What is this?
Business trip.
I decided it's long overdue for me
to inspect our holdings in Melbourne.
And how long will you be?
I don't know.
DIGGLE:
When you were stuck on that island...
...plotting your grand plan to save the city...
...I don't think you stopped
to consider the effect...
...it would have on the people in your life.
Let's go.
LANCE: It's fine.
LAUREL: Come on. You're okay.
No, no, no. Put it--
Or how it might hurt them.
You're wrong.
I think about it all the time.
And just to be clear,
not being able to tell my family the truth...
...it doesn't hurt anyone worse
than it hurts me.
- Where you going?
- Mueller still has guns. I have to stop him.
- Oliver.
- He had his chance.
MUELLER: Twenty-eight crates, four guns
in each crate, $250,000 cash.
Take it or leave it.
That's the deal.
MAN:
Yeah, okay.
[GRUNTS]
[SPEAKS IN GERMAN]
Leo Mueller, you have failed this city.
[MUELLER SCREAMS]
[English - US - SDH]