Previously on "Arrow"...
You would be
remiss in forgetting
the thermobaric
explosive
that remains
in my possession.
What...Do you want?
Vengeance for my son.
What did you find?
Video of his
son's murder.
This is fabricated.
It didn't happen.
Whoever planned this
knew exactly how
Cayden would react.
Which means that person
has to be close to Cayden.
Do you trust me?
I need you here
for a rather
important assignment.
- What's that?
- Rooting out a traitor.
D--don't.
Baby,
please wake up.
He's gone, D.
We're clear.
All right. Keep moving.
I guess Cayden James
and friends knew
we were coming.
Oh, yes.
Once I learned of
Mr. Sobel's treachery,
I had to assume this
location was compromised.
Speaking of which,
I didn't appreciate
your alliance with him.
Made me think we no longer
have an understanding.
You need to know something.
Many things, I'm sure.
But I doubt very much
that you're the man
to teach them to me.
We almost have proof that
I didn't kill your son.
A desperate gambit.
Cayden, give me
more time.
Time, I'm afraid,
is a commodity
you and your city
have run out of.
Mr. Sobel's betrayal
convinced me
that there's little good
in delaying matters further.
Accordingly,
I will be detonating
the thermobaric bomb
over Star City at midnight.
My son will find justice
in the ashes of your
beloved city.
♪ Arrow 6x13 ♪
The Devil's Greatest Trick
Original Air Date on February 8, 2018
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Cayden is going to detonate
the bomb in 4 hours.
Where are we with the video?
Well, we're running
our photographic analysis algorithm
to reveal the original
footage.
How long will
that take?
As long as it takes.
The algorithm Felicity and Curtis wrote
works wonders
on a still image,
but this is 24 fps video we're talking
about here, so...
Right. Cayden just told us
that we are running out of time.
There's something
you should consider.
You're putting
all of your chips down
on a bet that he'll spare
the city if he thinks
you're not responsible
for his son's death.
That's because
it's the only play we have, Alena.
I'm just saying you
might be trying to reason with a man
who's beyond reason.
As you are well aware,
Arclight is now in its
final phase.
And now it's time for us
to take our leave.
Words much appreciated,
but how are we to get
out of city?
Stay close to your phones.
You will be airlifted
from the city
before the bomb goes off.
After it does, your individual shares
of the ransom
will be wired
into offshore accounts
that have been set up
for each of you.
Sounds fair...
Lucrative.
Indeed.
Thank you for helping to see
this project to fruition.
I don't think
I need to stress
how...personally important
this has been for me.
Thank you
for all you've done
to get justice for my boy.
Mr. James.
Just as Alexander
rained destruction
on Persepolis,
so do I now
on Averwood
Pharmaceuticals.
$50 million for illegal
black market drug deals
and I just made
it all...
Disappear.
You must be our
new recruit.
Kojo Sledgehammer,
if I recall.
Yeah, I am--I am so stoked
to be here, Mr. James.
This is just--you're
an absolute legend.
It's been a pleasure
meeting you.
I'm sure we'll all do
great things together.
Owen.
See you guys
tomorrow.
Hi, Dad.
Hey, that was quite
a game.
Please don't lie, ok?
I could see you weren't
in the stands.
Mom told me you didn't show.
Where's your mother now?
She and Jim went
to have dinner
at some fancy
French restaurant.
Jim got a promotion and said
he wanted to treat her.
That's considerate
of him.
So sorry I missed
the game, Owen.
I got delayed
at work.
Is that what we're
supposed to call
your weirdo hacker group?
The work we do is
important.
It benefits people
all over the world.
Yeah, work you won't
even tell me about.
As I've said, that's
for your protection.
Look, I know I'm not
the easiest person
in the world to
talk to...
But I do want to be
a bigger part
of your life.
I truly do.
Well, you can't have it
both ways, Dad.
You can't say you want
to be a part of my life
and keep me out of yours.
When are the finals?
Tomorrow night.
I will be there.
I can't share with
you all the details of my work,
but I vow to do
a better job of sharing your life,
and that begins
tomorrow.
Yes! Yes, exactly. Please.
Listen, we need SCPD radios linked
with emergency services
right now, ok? Now!
Where the hell
are you?
Did you get my message?
Yeah. Ok. We
rallied the troops,
and everyone's
panicking a little.
Gather a list of essential
personnel, clergymen,
doctors, as many people
as you can mobilize.
Wait. How--how are
we gonna explain
how you have access
to the Arrow's bunker?
We have bigger problems
right now, Speedy.
Besides, this is the
only place in the city
I can think of that could possibly
withstand that blast.
You have eyes on--
William. Of course.
I got it.
Thank you.
Do you have to keep
doing that?
It keeps me calm.
Do not worry.
Cayden James will not
let his friends die with the city.
You're damn right,
but I'm not gonna stick
around to find out.
Where are you going?
Someplace
I won't get blown up.
The two of you
haven't noticed?
The airlift
that Cayden promised,
it's more
than a little late.
I hate to say it,
but I think he's right.
I noticed that Dinah didn't show
up for work today.
Well, after what happened
to Sobel,
you really
expecting her to?
No. I just--from what
Oliver told me, I...
I don't really think that
she's exactly just grieving.
You think Oliver would
just what,
let Dinah kill her?
No. I--I just
don't think that
that's what's
on his mind right now.
Right. Well, you know,
if it comes down
to Laurel against Dinah,
then Laurel's
not the one
I'm worried about.
Tell me where I can
find Black Siren,
or the next bone I break
is your neck.
Lady, if any of these
people told me
where they were going,
I'd be with them.
I guess that's
one way
to not
get information.
What are you two doing here?
Looking for you. SCPD says
you weren't in today.
We were wondering
if you were gonna do something stupid.
Guess we were wrong.
I am looking for her
to get justice for
Vincent.
Why do you say, "justice," like
it's cold-blooded murder?
I know you're hurting, D.,
but Felicity called.
We've got till midnight
before James
lets his bomb do its thing.
As much as we feel for you,
that seems
like the priority.
He's right. Now is not the time
to go off the deep end.
I can't
let this go.
I'm sorry.
D.
I love you both, but stay
the hell out of my way.
We need to consider the
A.R.G.U.S. airlift option.
Oliver, we've already
talked about this.
James will see it coming.
We need to consider
something.
- Got it!
- What?
I've seen
this. It's bogus.
You said you had
something?
Yeah, the whole thing
was a massive deception.
Owen was never
collateral damage,
like Cayden was made
to think.
He was the real target
the whole time.
Who is that?
Facial recognition just
picked him up
as Karl Iscove,
paid assassin.
With a bow and arrow?
A bow and arrow's not
his usual M.O.
I'm guessing it was
a special request
by whoever hired him
to kill Cayden's son.
All to set you up.
We need to have a conversation
with this Iscove,
find out who hired him.
He's dead.
What?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
The assassin was assassinated
not long after Owen Post.
We need to know where
Cayden James is right now.
Got him.
Well, I'm
guessing Cayden doesn't care
about people knowing
his location
now that his bomb is
about to go off.
He's almost on the I-86.
He's psycho, but he's
smart, meaning he
doesn't want to be
anywhere near the boom
when the boom goes
boom.
We'll never catch him.
I have an idea.
We need to talk.
Questionable
judgment, Mr. Queen.
If you wanted
the bomb to go off
before midnight,
you'd be hard pressed
to come up
with a better way
than taking me
into custody.
Watch this.
Would that be
the proof that you
alluded to earlier?
Just play the video.
No, I'm not
watching this again.
No, Cayden, you're not.
Now we're watching
the real video
for the very first time.
Oliver didn't kill your son,
which means
someone else did.
The assassin's
name is Karl Iscove.
He was instructed to use
a bow and arrow
so the video could be
manipulated,
and they could make it
look like me.
It's the same tech used
to out Oliver as
the Green Arrow 4 months ago.
Someone's gone through
a lot of work to put
you two
on a collision course.
Oh, yes.
Someone within
my organization.
How do you know?
The metadata on
the forged video file
confirms it is the work
of the same person
who manipulated
that photo in October.
You lost a man a month ago.
Killed by the traitorous
Mr. Sobel,
but I highly doubt
it was Mr. Sheck.
That leaves
Laurel, Diaz.
And Anatoly.
I'd like to speak
to my former
colleagues.
And that's where the
two of you come in.
No! We're not rounding
them up to be executed.
No. I just want
a pointed conversation.
Bring them to me,
all 3 alive.
Otherwise I'll have
no choice
but to stay the course.
I still have a very
powerful bomb,
and I'd be
perfectly happy
to take out Star City
right along
with whoever orchestrated
the death of my son.
You got to be kidding me.
Please tell me you're kidding me.
The only way to stop James
from destroying the city is
by delivering him
his people.
Lead them to the
slaughter, you mean.
I won't let that happen.
Right now,
that's our only option.
You don't even know for sure
that one of them did it.
I mean, none of them were working
for Cayden when he received the video.
But they were working
for him when he received
the doctored photo.
It has to be one of
those people, Alena.
It is either Diaz,
Anatoly, or Black Siren.
You hope.
What if Cayden is lying?
Well, we got bigger
problems than that.
I mean, what makes
you think that we
can find Cayden's
BFFs if he can't?
If they're smart, they're
out of the city by now.
They're smart,
but so is he.
He grouped them
together by promising
to fly them out
before the blast.
Thank goodness
for small favors
and gullible
bad guys.
But now they're worried
that James
might not make good
on that promise.
Raisa wanted to go to
one of the city shelters,
so she could be
with her family.
What's going on?
Why did we have to
leave the safe house?
We'll talk about it
later, buddy.
You promised you
wouldn't lie to me anymore.
Cayden James is threatening
to detonate a large bomb
in Star City, and this is
the safest place for you.
That is the truth.
Alena.
Yeah, we're running
facial recog,
and Cayden gave us back
satellite control, but--
our usual tricks
aren't working.
Oliver, we need
the rest of the team.
Agreed.
Where are you going?
I need to go look
for a few people.
Let me come with you.
I need you to stay here.
I want to stay with you.
It is too dangerous
out there,
bottom line.
I'll be back as
soon as I can be.
You have any luck?
You think I would?
She was pretty clear
about where she stood, Hoss.
So basically the city's
gonna get destroyed
and our friend's gonna
commit murder,
and there's not a damn thing we can
do about either?
About time, D.
Different kind of D., Hoss.
Sorry, John.
We've gotten someplace
with Cayden James.
He won't detonate his bomb
if we bring back Anatoly,
Diaz, and Laurel alive.
So no honor amongst
thieves?
Well, let's just say he has
a good reason to think
at least one of
them's responsible
for his son's death.
We could use your help
finding them.
Well, if we do it, we should
go after Laurel first.
Dinah's after her.
And if she gets to her
before we do--
D.'s gonna kill her.
And if she does that,
she might be killing
the whole city.
Vince told me you had
a to-go bag stashed.
It took me a little while to
figure out where.
- Hyah! Hyah! Hyah...
- Hyah...
You can't stop me.
This ends tonight.
You end tonight.
No!
You stay out of this.
I can't let you
hurt her.
Hi, Daddy.
I missed you.
I told you,
this ends tonight.
Ah--
I wouldn't do that
if I were you.
What are you doing?!
I had her.
I'm saving the city.
I cannot believe you are
working with Cayden James.
Not like that, D.
He wants Anatoly,
Diaz, and Laurel alive.
Or boom goes the city.
Just saying that's
a pretty good reason
to not kill her besides,
you know,
all the other good reasons,
like killing is bad.
I can hold off for
a little while.
Dinah, we do not
just execute people.
No. You just let
them die.
Can we continue
this later?
Anatoly and Diaz are
still in the wind.
Correction. Ricardo Diaz
was in the wind.
Cayden's satellite just
picked him up headed south.
Our team can take down Diaz.
Ok, sending you
the GPS coordinates now.
I'm staying here.
I'm not letting her
out of my sight.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
So what, we're letting
the foxes guard
the henhouses now?
Quentin, Canary, you
keep eyes on Black Siren.
Wild Dog, Terrific,
you go after Diaz.
Overwatch, let us know when
you have eyes on Anatoly,
and Spartan and I will be
ready to move.
Put me through to Cayden.
Mr. Queen, have you
fulfilled my request?
We have Black Siren.
Where do we take her?
The last time I checked, it
took more than one songbird
to make up a trio.
Cayden, we don't
have time for games.
Then I suggest you find
my former compatriots
as soon as you can.
Owen, before this night
is over,
I promise you we will
render our judgment.
Ah.
You heading out, Cayden?
Yes, Alena.
Prior engagement.
Must attend.
Well, are you sure
that's a good idea?
What ever do you mean?
Oh, uh, I'm s--I'm sorry.
I just assumed somebody
would have told you.
I--I picked up
some chatter
on your hacked A.R.G.U.S.
responder a few minutes ago
about your takedown of
Averwood Pharmaceuticals.
My point being, it's just
if A.R.G.U.S. has your scent,
maybe going out right now
isn't the best idea.
Probably not, but I'll
take precautions.
I can't afford
to break this date.
Where do you think
you're going, buddy?
You like that?
We got this off another
pair of doppelgangers.
You know, I have to say,
I was surprised.
Your boyfriend
and his little magical
healing abilities,
you know, I thought
it would be harder
to take him down,
but it wasn't.
What's going on?
I'm counting down
the minutes.
What, before you try and
kill my daughter again?
That is not
your daughter.
That is a monster.
You gave your monster
a second chance.
After he worked his
ass off
to redeem himself
and after
he gave his life
to stop
Cayden James,
so if you seriously
want to compare
Vince to Laurel,
I sugg--
I know. I know
what she's done.
I'm not an idiot.
But no one deserves
to die, not even her.
You're wrong.
And once this is
all over
if Cayden James
doesn't kill her,
I sure as hell am
gonna take my shot.
Where's my dad? He said
he'd be right back.
Um, yeah. I--I know.
And he will.
It's just
that things
didn't really go as
he planned tonight,
the way any of us
have planned.
So it's taking
a long time.
He's gonna be ok, ok?
Ok.
I've got eyes on Anatoly
and a few of his friends.
Looks like they got
themselves a helicopter.
Next I come back to city,
I hope it is ash.
Kapiushon! Show yourself.
Aah! Agh.
City is
about to become crater.
You want to put me
in prison? Fine.
Just out of town, please.
The bomb's not
going off, Anatoly,
because I'm going
to deliver Cayden James
the truth--you.
You have
finally snapped.
Took a few more years
longer than I expected.
You set me up.
The photo,
the doctored video.
I already told you,
that was not me.
Well, forgive me
if I don't want
to take you at your word.
Overwatch, we got him.
Curtis and Rene got
Ricardo Diaz.
That makes us 3 for 3.
William, give
that to me.
Call James.
I was beginning
to think you'd forgotten about me.
We have all 3.
Where do you want them?
Meet me at the abandoned
theater on Jefferson Avenue.
I'm on it.
I'll call Curtis and Rene.
Ok, I got
Quentin.
I'll keep an eye on Cayden.
Prodigious timing,
gentlemen.
It's almost midnight.
We're not here
to play games, Cayden.
And yet
here you are.
And what of Mr. Diaz
and Ms. Lance?
They'll be here.
And what of this
young man?
I don't believe your
son was invited, Oliver.
What are you doing here?
I want to be with you.
I'm scared.
William, just
listen to me--
It's just like
on the island,
just like when my mom died.
I don't want
to lose you, too.
Please. I want to stay
with you.
Come here. Come here.
It's all right.
You stay over here.
This started
with my son.
Yours should be
here for the end.
It's a beautiful
symmetry,
don't you think?
He has nothing
to do with this.
I don't disagree,
but it appears your
son has other plans.
Hello, William.
My name is
Cayden James.
You're the guy who wants
to blow up the city.
I suppose.
It's a long story.
And it concerns
my own son.
Where is he?
Passed away, I'm afraid.
Cayden James?
I was told to expect you.
Warned, in fact.
Mr. James, we're here to
remand you into custody
for multiple violations
of federal law.
I strongly advise you
not to resist.
My only son is playing
in this game.
Could I perhaps watch it
before you take me in?
That's not
how it works.
I'm just asking
for a few moments,
a little compassion here.
I strongly suggest
surrendering peacefully
to avoid a scene.
There's no need for that.
All right. I'm gonna get
the lay of the land.
She'd better be here
when I get back.
I don't think she likes me.
Well, you haven't
given her
much reason to,
have you?
Fair.
She's right, you know.
Ahem. About what?
I'm not like Sobel.
I'm not gonna change.
I'm not gonna
just wake up one day
and be your Laurel.
No, no.
You'll always be you.
But you can be better.
Why would I?
We live in an ugly world,
and the only way
to survive it is--
is to be ugly right back.
You're wrong, ok?
Hey, has it ever occurred
to you that I like who I am,
that when I killed Sobel,
I actually enjoyed it?
And all those pictures
that you showed me of your daughter--
this--this--this woman
that I don't even recognize.
They made me sick.
She was soft and naive,
and that's why she's
the one who's dead.
Why are you telling
me this?
Because I don't ever
want to find myself
enjoying killing you.
Perimeter's secure.
Let's move.
Yeah.
Quite a brave young fellow
you have here, Mr. Queen.
Brave and foolish,
much like his father.
What--what's he
doing here?
None of your concern,
Mr. Lance.
Ah! And the rest of our
guests have arrived.
These two freaks say
that you think
one of us killed
your boy?
In point of fact, Mr. Diaz,
I know that one of you
killed my boy.
I intend to find out who.
You believe people
in masks
over people you do
business with?
I'm with the Russian.
I think these guys
would do anything
to save their
precious city.
I don't trust anyone's
word, Mr. Diaz.
I put my faith
in data, information.
Ones and zeroes never lie.
Here's digital proof that one
of you has betrayed me.
Oh, William, please
just get out of there.
None of you know...
What it feels like
to lose a son.
A piece of yourself
gone.
It's like a phantom limb.
No, it's worse than that.
It's like a piece
of your soul lost
as if it had never been there.
Lost. No, stop. I keep
reminding myself that
I have not lost my son.
He's been taken from me.
Hey...
You're losing it.
Your grief,
it's making you crazy.
What if it has?
Just look at him.
He wants to kill
everyone in this room.
Just be ready to move.
Ok, screw this.
It was me!
I did it.
Surprise.
I'm the one who did it.
I killed your stupid kid.
- Oh, my God.
- What?
For the past 3 minutes,
Cayden's detonator
has been emitting
a 76-gigahertz field.
Now it's spiking.
What does this mean?
It means there's something
wrong with the bomb.
It's a shame, really.
He was very cute.
The signal's fritzing again.
The closer Cayden gets
to Laurel,
the bigger the frequency
spikes on the detonator.
No. It's not
the detonator.
Aren't you gonna ask me
why I did it?
No. I know
you're lying.
You're not
nearly as callous
as you portray
yourself to be.
I saw, Ms. Lance.
When I ordered you
to execute Mr. Sobel,
I saw you hesitate.
You didn't want
to do it.
Oliver, you need
to get Laurel away from Cayden
right now.
His detonator is interfering
with her power-dampening collar.
Well, well, well.
Now, this is interesting.
Grr! Laurel!
Guys, are you ok?
Do you copy?
Overwatch, we're fine.
Ok, thermal imaging reads
everyone's still inside,
but they've gone in
different directions.
I'm good.
Find Anatoly!
I've got Diaz! Go!
Sure thing, Hoss.
I knew this would
happen.
Why?
We work with Oliver,
we get in trouble.
The guy's a walking
death trap.
Who do you think taught him
about traps?
Stop!
God, you're persistent.
It's annoying.
The son of a bitch.
Dinah, no!
No!
Laurel. Laurel.
William. William,
back away, son.
Come here, come here,
William.
Your son wouldn't want
you to do this.
The person responsible for
his death is in the vicinity,
and I intend to drag them
to hell with me.
I owe it to my son.
Come here. Come here.
You don't have to be
afraid, all right?
I'm right here
with you.
And I love you
very much.
William...
I had an obligation
to protect my son.
It's a father's job--
protect your child...
But I failed.
I failed him utterly.
All this time...
The man responsible
for his death...
was me.
Don't you move.
I can't believe he was ready
to blow up the whole city.
Yeah.
He lost his boy.
I don't even want
to imag--well.
Yeah.
What you did was
very dangerous.
I know. And I'm sorry.
I am never gonna let
anything happen to you, William,
ever.
And I am promising you
that I will do
everything that
I can to make sure
nothing happens to me.
You can't make that
promise.
I can make that promise.
I just did.
I am right now.
Kiddo, I've been doing
this a long time.
So trust me.
Ok?
Ok.
Thank you.
I got to go talk
to the others, all right?
Ok.
Where are we?
If by we you mean
Anatoly, Diaz, and Laurel...
Completely in the wind.
- Again?
- Again.
Again.
Ok, well, Quentin's walking
Cayden James through booking right now.
Look. I know what
you're gonna say,
but I think finding
Laurel needs to be our first priority.
Don't make this
personal, Dinah.
Or, you know,
more personal. Heh.
You heard her.
She is the one who had
Cayden James' son killed.
She is the one who set
all of this into motion.
- You don't know that.
- She confessed.
She was pushing James'
buttons, D.
How did she manage to
blind all of you this much?
You're the one that's
not seeing clearly,
if you ask me, Dinah.
I didn't.
Hey, hey.
You're better than this.
I guess we're leaving now.
Yeah, we're leaving now.
Just to be clear,
whatever happened
doesn't change anything.
Yeah, we're glad that we
took down Cayden James,
but we're still doing
our own thing.
Please try and keep
Dinah in line.
No promises, Hoss.
In case you haven't noticed,
we're not having a lot of
luck with that right now.
Well, we saved
the city again
and got Cayden James.
Yeah. Why doesn't it
feel like we won?
I must say this visit
is somewhat predictable.
Well, I needed to look
you in the eyes, Cayden.
I need to know that
this surrender of yours...
Isn't some sort of ploy.
I've had bad luck
with that tactic.
You prevented me from
doing the unspeakable
last night.
I'm sure Owen would
have been ashamed of me,
but then he always was.
These are my best
guesses
as to where you might
find my former allies
along with
the account number
to a bank
in Corto Maltese
where I placed
all the money
I embezzled
from the city.
Thank you.
I would ask one thing
in return.
Permission to visit
my son's grave.
I can arrange that.
Be a better father
than I was, Oliver.
If this is another
feeble attempt
to extract
information from me,
I--I warn you I will
continue to invoke
my fifth amendment
protections.
I'm very sorry to have
to tell you this, Mr. James,
but...
Your son Owen was found
murdered last night.
No. He's...He's 18.
N--no.
Who would want
to hurt my boy?
I'm afraid we don't know.
I am truly
very sorry, Cayden.
Hey, what's the story,
morning glory?
I used to say
that to you
when you were a little
girl, you know?
The other you.
I already told you.
I know what you
told me.
What you told me
was a lie.
But it's--James
said it:
You hesitated when
you killed Sobel.
So what if I did?
It means
there's a piece--
maybe just a small
piece, but it means
that there is
a piece of my daughter
in you somewhere.
And I'm gonna get it
out whatever it takes.
SCPD custody.
Didn't think we'd
end up here.
You know, I saw this
playing out a lot of ways.
I got to tell you...
I wasn't expecting this.
I assume it would be
foolish to think
that this is
a rescue operation.
You were always the smartest
guy in the room.
You thought you always
had everybody pegged.
You put everyone
in your little boxes.
You always understood
what they were thinking,
how they'd react,
but you're realizing now
you didn't really know
anything, did you?
I'm afraid I don't
take your meaning,
Mr. Diaz.
Is that so?
You're supposed to be
the smart one.
You made some moves.
Then I made some moves.
Queen is under
indictment now.
His team is fractured
in a million pieces.
And this city--
oh, this city--
it's primed for a takeover.
You see, guys like you never
understand these things.
Why destroy a city
when you could take it over?
I suppose this accounts
for your presence here.
Mm-hmm.
The new police captain--
she's on my payroll,
along with a few other
city officials.
Arclight was
a big help
in thinning
the herd for me.
I suspect you're not
done thinning the herd.
Well, you were
always talking about
how much you
miss your son.
In case you
didn't know,
I'm the one who
had him killed.
Tell your boy...
I said hello.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man