PREVIOUSLY
ON "ARROW" AND "FLASH"...
FLASH: GUYS, THIS
ISN'T A METEOR.
LYLA: WE'VE BEEN CALLING
THEM THE DOMINATORS.
WE LEARNED THEY WERE
ABDUCTING HUMANS
TO GATHER INTEL
ABOUT US.
IF THEY DECIDE
TO ATTACK,
NO MILITARY
CAN STOP THEM.
YOU CAN'T DO
THIS ALONE.
I DON'T PLAN TO.
BARRY: GUYS, THANKS
FOR COMING.
BARRY, I THOUGHT YOU
WERE BRINGING AN ALIEN.
THIS IS MY FRIEND
KARA DANVERS...
SUPERGIRL.
CALL LYLA, TELL HER
THESE DOMINATORS AREN'T
HERE PEACEFULLY.
[OLIVER PANTING]
WOMAN: SO...
HOW WAS YOUR RUN?
YOU KNOW HOW IT WAS
I TOLD YOU ABOUT IN THE SHOWER.
HERE YOU GO.
HOW COULD I FORGET?
DINAH LAUREL LANCE...
WILL YOU MARRY ME?
I THINK I ALREADY
ANSWERED THAT QUESTION.
RIGHT.
OK. TIME TO GET READY.
MY SISTER
WILL BE HERE SOON.
ANY WORD FROM FELICITY?
ONLY THAT OLIVER,
JOHN, AND THEA HAVE BEEN
ABDUCTED BY ALIENS.
SHE ACTUALLY MADE
THAT SOUND NORMAL.
I'VE GOT EVERY TRAFFIC CAM
FROM HERE TO CENTRAL CITY
LOOKING FOR THEM.
YEAH, LIKE
TRAFFIC CAMS
ARE GONNA HELP
AGAINST ALIEN
INVADERS.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
IT'LL PROBABLY HELP
THAN YOU TRYING TO PRETEND
TO BE OLIVER QUEEN.
NOTHING TO
PRETEND ABOUT.
GOT TO KEEP IN SHAPE
SO WHEN THESE E.T.s
SHOW UP
I CAN KICK THEIR
COLLECTIVE ASSES.
YEAH. YOU'LL HAVE BETTER
LUCK ON THE SALMON LADDER.
MY WHOLE LIFE, I'VE WAITED
TO SEE A SIGN
OF INTELLIGENT LIFE.
NOW THAT I'M SEEING IT,
THEY'RE NOT
INTELLIGENT AT ALL.
THEY'RE JUST MEAN.
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
FELICITY: TRY TO START.
GUYS, THIS IS
CISCO RAMON OF STAR LABS.
CURTIS. BIG FAN.
-RENE RAMIREZ.
-RORY REGAN.
OK. CURTIS,
YOU'RE TALL.
RENE AND RORY.
THAT'S TWO RORYS
I KNOW NOW.
THE OTHER ONE,
HE'S A DOUCHE, THOUGH.
-YOU'RE NOT A DOUCHE, ARE YOU?
-NO.
OK. GOOD. I JUST HAD
TO MAKE SURE, RIGHT?
GUYS, WE HAVE TO FIND
OLIVER AND COMPANY,
AND I'M NOT TALKING
ABOUT THE CHERISHED
DISNEY ANIMATED FILM
STARRING BILLY JOEL, OK?
I'M TALKING...I GOT
TO VIBE, ALL RIGHT?
I NEED SOMETHING TO
VIBE OFF OF,
SOMETHING PERSONAL.
I GOT ONE OF HIS
OLD BOWS HERE SOMEWHERE.
[SCOTTISH ACCENT]
THAT'LL DO.
CURTIS: UM, FOR THOSE
OF US WHO DON'T KNOW
YOU AS WELL...NOT ME
BECAUSE I FEEL LIKE
WE'RE BEST FRIENDS,
WE'VE KNOWN EACH OTHER
FOR A LONG TIME...
UH, WHAT ARE YOU
GOING TO DO EXACTLY?
OH, RIGHT. UH,
I'M ABOUT TO VIBE.
IT'S THIS THING I DO
WHERE, UH, I TOUCH SOMETHING.
I...I CAN NOT ONLY
SEE THE PAST.
I CAN SEE THE FUTURE,
BUT MOST IMPORTANTLY,
I CAN SEE
WHERE PEOPLE ARE.
RENE: SO YOU'RE
ONE OF THEM...
METAHUMAN?
YEAH. DON'T SOUND
TOO EXCITED ABOUT IT.
OK. SO THIS IS IT.
JUST...JUST PLEASE
DON'T BREAK IT
ANY MORE THAN IT IS
ALREADY BROKEN.
OK. COOL.
[EXHALES]
I SAW THEM.
THEY'RE IN SOME KIND
OF STASIS,
LIKE A SHIP.
IT'S, UH,
A LITTLE "ALIEN,"
A LITTLE "STAR TREK"...
J.J. ABRAMS STYLE...
AND A WHOLE LOT
OF TECH.
-YOU SAID TECH!
-YES, I SAID TECH.
IT'S AN ALIEN
SPACESHIP, FELICITY.
-THESE GUYS AREN'T AMATEURS.
-YEAH, BUT...BUT...
CURTIS: I THINK
WHERE SHE'S GOING IS
IF WE HAD SOME
WE MIGHT BE ABLE
TO DOWNLOAD SOME
INTEL OFF IT,
LIKE, INCLUDING
EVERYONE'S LOCATION.
-YES.
-HOLD, PLEASE.
YES. THAT'S
WHAT I MEANT.
-THANK YOU.
-OF COURSE.
-ALWAYS GOT MY BACK.
-OF COURSE I DO.
WHAT ABOUT THIS?
I TOOK IT OFF
THE DOMINATOR SHIP
THAT CRASHED
IN CENTRAL CITY.
YOU WHAT?!
WE'RE GONNA HACK
ALIEN TECH.
THIS IS SERIOUSLY
THE BEST DAY OF MY
ENTIRE LIFE!
OLIVER: YOU DIDN'T HAVE
TO GET ME A GIFT, SPEEDY.
IT'S JUST A LITTLE
PREREHEARSAL DINNER GESTURE.
WELL, LITTLE IS RIGHT.
IT'S CALLED A HOZEN.
IT SYMBOLIZES
RECONNECTING,
LIKE YOU DID
WITH LAUREL.
THEA, IT'S A ROCK.
IT'S A VERY
THOUGHTFUL GESTURE
FROM YOUR AMAZINGLY
LOVING SISTER.
-THANK YOU.
-YEAH. THAT'S BETTER.
WELL, WHAT'S
GOING ON HERE?
THEA GAVE ME
A ROCK.
-OH.
-HA HA HA!
LET'S GO, CHAMP.
YOU GOT A 6:00 APPOINTMENT
AT THE TAILOR'S,
GOT TO FIGHT TRAFFIC.
OH, DAD, YOU KNOW I'M
NOT MUCH OF A FIGHTER.
THEA: TELL THAT
TO THE PAPARAZZI
YOU PUNCHED.
-10 YEARS AGO.
-STILL.
MOIRA: MIGHT AS WELL
BE A LIFETIME.
YOU'RE PRACTICALLY
A COMPLETELY
DIFFERENT PERSON.
YOU BOTH ARE.
DON'T START CRYING
AGAIN, MAMA.
JUST SAVE ALL THE TEARS
FOR THE ACTUAL WEDDING.
I THINK WHAT YOUR
MOTHER'S TRYING TO SAY
IS THAT BOTH OF US
FEEL BLESSED
TO HAVE WATCHED
THE TWO OF YOU GROW UP.
WHOA! SWEET REFLEXES.
LAUREL: GOD.
HOW MUCH LUGGAGE
DID YOU BRING?
THANK YOU.
WHAT, DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE MOVING IN?
OH! I WISH.
HA HA HA!
I MISS YOU.
I MISS YOU, TOO.
THIS IS BEAUTIFUL.
THANKS.
OLLIE GOT IT
FOR ME.
-IS IT A BIRD?
-IT'S A CANARY.
SARA?
IT'S JUST THAT
I MISSED YOU.
ROBERT: THE TUX IS
A GOOD LOOK ON YOU.
NEVER REALLY FELT
LIKE MY THING.
MAYBE YOU'D BE
MORE COMFORTABLE
IN A SUIT AND TIE.
DAD, COME ON.
I GET SWORN IN
AS MAYOR IN LESS
THAN TWO MONTHS.
I DON'T HAVE TIME TO
FIND A REPLACEMENT CEO
FOR QUEEN CONSOLIDATED.
WHAT ABOUT, UM,
WALTER STEELE?
THE BOARD
WON'T BACK HIM.
BESIDES, QC IS
A FAMILY COMPANY.
IT SHOULD STAY
IN THE FAMILY.
DAD, I WANT TO...
I WANT TO MAKE MY OWN NAME.
I DON'T JUST WANT TO
RELY ON YOURS.
OLIVER, IF YOU DON'T
DO IT, THE BOARD'S
GONNA PUSH
TO ACCEPT RAY PALMER'S
BUYOUT OFFER.
-I...
-WHAT?
I DON'T KNOW.
EXCUSE ME.
EXCUSE YOURSELF.
WATCHES, WALLETS,
PHONES.
WHAT, ARE YOU DEAF,
TRYING TO CATCH A BULLET?
TAKE IT EASY.
I'LL SHOOT YOUR ASS
RIGHT HERE.
HEY!
GET AWAY FROM HIM.
YOU WANT A PIECE
OF THIS?
OHH!
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
[COUGHS]
UH, YEAH, YEAH.
YOU COULD HAVE
BEEN KILLED.
WHY WOULD DO A THING
LIKE THAT?
THEA: WOW. MOM IS
TOTALLY GONNA
FREAK OUT.
THAT'S PROBABLY WHY
SHE DOESN'T NEED TO KNOW.
YEAH. SHE PROBABLY
WOULDN'T BELIEVE
THE PART ABOUT THE GUY
IN THE HOOD ANYWAY, SO...
ACTUALLY, YOUR BROTHER
WAS THE ONE WHO CAME
TO MY RESCUE FIRST.
YOU'RE QUITE
THE HERO, SON.
[GUNSHOT]
LAUREL: OH, MY GOD!
I HEARD WHAT HAPPENED.
ARE YOU OK?
YEAH. HEY.
HEY, HEY.
I'M FINE, I'M FINE.
OLIVER?
OLIVER, ARE YOU OK?
NO. I'M FINE.
I'M...PROBABLY
JUST NEED SOME AIR.
I'M GONNA...
I'LL SEE YOU AT
THE RESTAURANT.
[SIGHS]
I'M SO CONFLICTED.
YOU KNOW,
ON THE ONE HAND,
I GET TO HACK ACTUAL
EXTRATERRESTRIAL TECHNOLOGY,
BUT ON THE OTHER HAND,
E.T.s ARE REAL,
BUT UNFORTUNATELY,
THEY'RE DICKWADS WHO
ARE GONNA KILL US.
DON'T WORRY.
IT'S GONNA WORK OUT.
YOU'RE NOT GONNA TELL ME
GOD HAS A PLAN, ARE YOU?
WELL...
LOOK. I RESPECT YOUR
RELIGION AND ALL.
I JUST FIND IT
A LITTLE HARD TO BELIEVE
THAT THERE'S SOME
DIVINE PLAN TO THE UNIVERSE
WHICH ALSO INCLUDES
SPACE MONSTERS.
-WHAT'S THAT?
-I LIKE TO CALL IT
MY 3PO PROCESSOR.
[AS C-3PO]
I AM FLUENT IN OVER
6 MILLION FORMS
OF COMMUNICATION.
AND IT SPEAKS DOMINATOR?
I DIDN'T SPECIFICALLY
PROGRAM IT FOR THAT,
BUT IN MY DEFENSE,
I DIDN'T KNOW
THE DOMINATORS EVEN EXISTED.
LET'S SEE IF IT WORKS.
[PULSING]
I FEEL LIKE ELLIOT
IN "E.T."
"IT'S WORKING,
IT'S WORKING!"
YOUR TECH GUY QUOTES
MOVIES, HUH?
-YEAH.
-REAL ORIGINAL.
[BEEPING]
-OH, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO!
-NO, NO, NO NO!
RENE: WHAT HAPPENED?
WE MADE AN IDIOT MOVE.
THAT'S WHAT HAPPENED.
HSS! AGH!
WE TRIED TO PLUG
HUMAN TECH INTO
A DOMINATOR
POWER SOURCE.
OF COURSE IT
OVERLOADED!
WE NEED
A REGULATOR, OK,
SOMETHING THAT CAN
HANDLE THE DOMINATOR JUICE.
VAN HORN INDUSTRIES
WAS WORKING ON
A PROTOTYPE
FOR NASA OVER
A YEAR AGO.
MAYBE THEY PERFECTED
IT BY NOW.
OH, YEAH.
THEY PERFECTED IT ALL RIGHT,
SO MUCH SO SOMEBODY'S
ALREADY STOLEN IT.
ACCORDING TO SCPD REPORTS,
IT'S DOCTOR
NAMED LAURA WASHINGTON.
DOCTOR? THAT DOESN'T
MAKE ANY SENSE.
IT DOES IF SHE'S BEEN
ARTIFICIALLY AUGMENTING
HERSELF WITH STOLEN
TECHNOLOGY
BECAUSE WHY WOULD
THE UNIVERSE MAKE
ANYTHING EASY?
IT SAYS HERE
IMPLANTS GIVE HER
ENHANCED STRENGTH,
STAMINA,
AND ELECTRICITY-BASED
POWERS.
WELL, THAT'S NOTHING
WE CAN'T HANDLE.
THAT'S EVERYTHING
COME ON, FELICITY.
I MEAN, THIS MIGHT
BE OUR ONLY CHANCE
TO FIND OLIVER
AND EVERYONE ELSE.
THAT'S WHY I'M CALLING
IN REINFORCEMENTS.
[SIREN]
[QUENTIN WHISTLING]
OH, HEY!
CAPTAIN LANCE.
HEY. I WAS JUST
ON MY WAY OUT.
UH, DO YOU HAVE
A MINUTE FOR ME?
YEAH, ACTUALLY,
I SHOULD HAVE CALLED
YOU EARLIER.
DETECTIVE HILTON TOLD ME
ABOUT WHAT HAPPENED TONIGHT.
-YOU OK?
-OH, YEAH.
MY...MY DAD AND I
ARE FINE.
GOOD, GOOD. WELL, WE GOT
THE GUY IN CUSTODY.
BECAUSE OF THE GUY
WITH THE BOW AND ARROW?
YEAH, YEAH. WE'VE BEEN
CALLING HIM THE HOOD.
SOME KIND
OF VIGILANTE.
UH, IF I'VE GOT
THE TIME RIGHT,
YOUR REHEARSAL DINNER IS
PRACTICALLY NOW.
FREEZE!
OLIVER?
DO YOU HAVE ANY
LEADS ON WHO THE...
HOOD...
MIGHT BE OR...
THIS IS THE LAST THING
YOU SHOULD BE THINKING ABOUT
THE NIGHT
BEFORE YOUR WEDDING,
OR IS THAT WHAT'S
GOING ON HERE?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
YOU GETTING COLD FEET?
NO, NOT AT ALL,
I PROMISE.
GOOD BECAUSE I WOULD
HATE TO HAVE TO SHOOT YOU
FOR BREAKING
MY GIRL'S HEART, RIGHT?
THE PAPERWORK
WOULD BE HELL.
IN TRUTH, I'M PROBABLY
A LITTLE BIT MORE...
SHAKEN UP BY
THE WHOLE MUGGING
THAN MAYBE I THOUGHT.
WELL, YOU KNOW, I GOT
JUST THE THING TO FIX THAT.
A FEW DRINKS AT YOUR
REHEARSAL DINNER.
-I'M BUYING. COME ON.
-YEAH, ACTUALLY...
UH, CAPTAIN LANCE,
I'LL...I'LL MEET
YOU THERE.
-YOU SURE?
-YEAH. I'LL SEE YOU THERE.
ACTUALLY, UH,
OLIVER, SOMETHING...
SOMETHING...SOMETHING
I WANT TO SAY.
YOU KNOW, UM, WHEN
YOU AND LAUREL
WERE, UH, KIDS,
YOU KNOW, TEENAGERS,
I...WELL, LET'S
FACE IT.
I DIDN'T LIKE
YOU MUCH.
HEH. I THOUGHT
YOU WERE A RICH,
ENTITLED PUNK.
I WAS.
BUT SINCE THEN,
OLIVER,
YOU HAVE GROWN INTO
A HELL OF A MAN,
THE KIND OF GUY
I'M PROUD TO HAVE
AS MY SON-IN-LAW.
THANK YOU, CAPTAIN LANCE.
-ALL RIGHT.
-SEE YOU AT THAT DINNER.
-I'LL SEE YOU THERE.
-ALL RIGHT.
[APPLAUSE]
LAUREL:
HE'S NOT COMING.
SARA: DON'T WORRY.
HE'LL BE HERE.
-I DON'T KNOW.
-YOU KNOW OLLIE'S NEVER BEEN
ON TIME FOR ANYTHING
IN HIS ENTIRE LIFE.
YOU DIDN'T SEE HIM
EARLIER.
HE HAD THIS LOOK
ON HIS FACE LIKE...
LIKE HE WAS
BACKING OUT.
NO WAY. HE LOVES YOU.
HE JUST...HE LOOKED LIKE
EVERYTHING THAT HE KNEW
WAS WRONG.
I'M PRETTY SURE
THAT EVERY GUY
HAS THAT LOOK
THE NIGHT BEFORE
THEIR WEDDING.
HEH.
YOU KNOW, THERE WAS
A TIME WHEN I THOUGHT
THE TWO OF YOU WOULD...
WOULD ACTUALLY HOOK UP.
YOU KNOW I
PREFER GIRLS.
HEH.
HEY.
AH. MS. LANCE.
HI. I'M RAY PALMER,
A BUSINESS ASSOCIATE
OF OLIVER'S FATHER.
I JUST WANTED TO SAY
CONGRATULATIONS.
LAUREL: THANK YOU.
IT'S REALLY NICE
TO MEET YOU.
UH, THIS IS...
THIS IS MY SISTER SARA.
HAVE WE MET BEFORE?
SARA: RAY!
NO. I THINK
I'D REMEMBER.
YOU JUST...SEEM
VERY FAMILIAR.
EXCUSE US.
YEAH.
ARE YOU SURE
YOU PREFER GIRLS?
HE WAS HOT.
OH, WOW.
WHAT THE HELL?!
UH...HI.
WE HAVE AN UNAUTHORIZED ENTRY!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
[GASPS]
HOW DID YOU FIND
THIS PLACE?
MY NAME IS OLIVER QUEEN.
I KNOW WHO YOU ARE!
EVERYBODY KNOWS
WHO YOU ARE.
HOW DID YOU FIND
THIS PLACE?
BETTER QUESTION IS WHY.
HE'S GETTING MARRIED
TOMORROW.
-GET OUT.
-WAIT.
GET OUT!
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
NO ONE CAN KNOW
MY SECRET.
YOUR NAME IS JOHN.
WHAT'D YOU SAY?
YOUR NAME...
IS JOHN DIGGLE.
OLIVER: HA HA HA!
JOHN, VOICE-OVER:
MY BROTHER NEEDED ME.
ERR!
[WHEEZING]
[COUGHS]
NO. NO.
NO! NO! NO, NO, NO!
BAD IDEA.
HOW DO YOU KNOW
ALL THIS?
I THINK...I THINK
WE'VE MET BEFORE
WHEN YOU WERE
MY BODYGUARD.
HEH. AND YOU THINK
I'M FUNNY.
YOU'RE THINKING
OF MY BROTHER ANDY.
HE'S IN PERSONAL SECURITY.
YOU WERE
IN THE MILITARY.
105TH AIRBORNE
OUT OF KANDAHAR.
DID A LOT OF THINGS
BACK THEN I'M NOT PROUD OF.
I CAME BACK HERE TO...
ATONE, I GUESS.
UH, JOHN,
STRANGER DANGER.
MIGHT WANT TO EASE UP
ON THE INFO DUMP.
FELICITY SMOAK?
FELICITY.
THIS ISN'T RIGHT.
I DON'T THINK THAT
ANY OF...
OF THIS IS RIGHT.
I DON'T THINK
THAT YOU'RE
THE GREEN ARROW...
AND I DON'T THINK
ANDY'S ALIVE.
JOHN, I THINK
YOU KILLED HIM.
ERRR!
FELICITY: OH, I HATE
BEING RIGHT ALL THE TIME.
LISTEN TO ME.
YOU'RE HAVING
SOME KIND
OF PSYCHOTIC BREAK.
GO BACK TO YOUR FAMILY,
YOUR FIANCÉE,
AND YOUR FANCY HOUSE!
AND YOU'RE GONNA FORGET
ABOUT ALL OF THIS!
AGH!
FELICITY'S RIGHT.
YOU'VE GOT EVERYTHING,
EVERYTHING, MAN!
STOP TRYING TO THROW
IT ALL AWAY.
YOU SHOULD HAVE
TAKEN HIM UP
ON HIS OFFER
TO CARRY YOU.
IT WAS AWESOME.
RENE: NOBODY'S CARRYING
ME ANYWHERE.
RORY: IT'S SO COOL
FELICITY REACHED OUT.
IT'S AWESOME
TO MEET YOU.
YEAH. WELL, WAIT
TILL YOU MEET HER.
KARA: HI, EVERYONE!
OH, I HAD ENOUGH
OF THIS.
BARRY: YO. YOU WANT
SOME COMPANY?
NOT REALLY.
OK. UM, SO WHAT
EXACTLY IS IT YOU'VE
HAD ENOUGH OF?
NOTHING. I JUST
DIDN'T KNOW THERE WERE
FLYING METAHUMANS NOW.
KARA: NO SIGN
OF WASHINGTON.
YEAH. UH, SUPERGIRL'S
NOT A META.
SHE'S AN ALIEN.
OH, I'M ONE
OF THE GOOD ONES.
THERE ARE
NO GOOD ONES.
HEY. WHAT'S
YOUR DAMAGE, MAN?
MY DAMAGE IS THAT
PEOPLE LIKE YOU TWO
HAVE THE POWER
OF GODS,
YET YOU THINK YOU
CAN MAKE THE WORLD
A BETTER PLACE
JUST BY PUTTING ON
A FANCY COSTUME.
NO. WE...WE THINK
WE MAKE THE WORLD
A BETTER PLACE
-BECAUSE W...WELL, WE DO.
-YEAH.
LOOK AROUND.
MOMENT HE SHOWED UP,
METAS START
APPEARING EVERYWHERE.
NOW YOU SHOW UP,
AND WE GET ALIENS.
SUPERPOWERS ARE
EVIL, MAN,
AND I DON'T WANT
ANYTHING TO DO
WITH THEM
OR WITH EITHER
OF YOU.
[ENERGY BUZZING]
[ELECTRICITY
CRACKLES]
MOIRA: THEA,
YOU HAVE GROWN
INTO THE MOST
BEAUTIFUL YOUNG WOMAN.
IT'S JUST
A BRIDESMAID'S DRESS, MOM.
NO ONE ACTUALLY
LOOKS GOOD IN ONE.
WELL, YOU DO.
YOU LOOK FULFILLED.
YEAH. I DON'T KNOW
ABOUT THAT ONE, MOM,
BUT I...I DO KNOW I HAVE
NEVER BEEN HAPPIER.
-GOOD.
-AND I LOVE YOU, MOM.
-OH.
-HEH HEH.
MY BABY GIRL. MMM.
HEH HEH HEH.
OK. WE'RE GONNA
WRINKLE THE DRESS.
-WELL, I REALLY DON'T CARE.
-OH. HA HA!
HA HA HA!
THEA: NO! OH, OH!
THEA?
ARE YOU OK?
Y-YEAH.
LAUREL, I...
DON'T YOU KNOW IT'S
BAD LUCK TO SEE THE BRIDE
BEFORE THE WEDDING?
OR SKIP OUT
ON THE REHEARSAL DINNER?
I...I KNOW.
I SAID I WAS SORRY.
IN A TEXT.
SARA, CAN YOU
GIVE US A FEW
MINUTES, PLEASE?
[SIGHS]
YOU'RE LUCKY I'M NOT
A TRAINED ASSASSIN
OR ANYTHING.
I...
OH, WOW.
YOU, UM...
YOU LOOK BEAUTIFUL.
I CALLED YOU
OVER 20 TIMES LAST NIGHT.
I CAN'T EXPLAIN
LAST NIGHT.
I JUST...
TODAY...TODAY, I WANT
TO MARRY YOU.
WELL, THAT'S GOOD
BECAUSE THERE ARE
GUESTS HERE.
NO, NOT WITH GUESTS,
NOT IN A FEW HOURS.
NOW. LAUREL, I
NEED TO...I NEED TO
GET OUT OF HERE.
-I...WE CAN ELOPE.
-OLIVER.
I'M BEING SERIOUS.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S
GOING ON WITH ME
RIGHT NOW.
I JUST KNOW THAT
I WANT TO BE
WITH YOU
AS QUICKLY AS
HUMANLY POSSIBLE.
WHAT IS GOING
ON WITH YOU?
I...LAST NIGHT,
SOMEBODY REMINDED ME
THAT I HAVE
EVERYTHING...
AND I DON'T WANT
TO GIVE IT UP.
I'M AFRAID THAT I'M
GONNA GIVE IT UP.
WELL, THAT'S
VERY SWEET OF YOU,
BUT WE HAVE
OVER 200 GUESTS COMING,
AND YOUR PARENTS,
THEY'VE SPENT A FORTUNE
ON THIS WEDDING.
I KNOW, AND I'M...
I'M SORRY IF THIS
IS CONFUSING
OR IF I'M SCARING YOU,
BUT THE ONLY THING
IN THE WORLD THAT MAKES
SENSE TO ME RIGHT NOW
IS THAT I LOVE YOU,
AND I'M GONNA
TAKE THAT JOB
AT QUEEN CONSOLIDATED,
AND I SWEAR TO GOD
I'M GONNA WORK
EVERY SINGLE DAY
TO BE THE MAN
YOU FELL IN LOVE WITH.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
SORRY ABOUT
THE INTERRUPTION.
THE RUSSIAN LADY
DOWNSTAIRS TOLD ME
TO COME RIGHT UP.
YOU GOT A MINUTE
TO TALK?
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
OLIVER: NOW WHAT HAPPENED
TO I SHOULD JUST GO
BACK TO MY LIFE?
LOOK. HAVE YOU BEEN
GETTING OUT INTO
THE CITY LATELY,
SEEING MAYBE
A PARTICULAR BUILDING
THAT SHOULDN'T BE THERE?
-SMOAK TECHNOLOGIES.
-YEAH.
YEAH, WHEN I WAS
WITH MY DAD,
I...I SAW IT,
AND IT FELT, UH...
-IT FELT WRONG.
-RIGHT.
FELICITY SMOAK
SAYS SHE NEVER
OWNED A BUILDING
OR A COMPANY.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S
GOING ON HERE,
BUT WHEN YOU LEFT,
I STARTED HAVING
THESE, UH...
VISIONS, RIGHT?
LIKE, UM...
UH, MEMORY FLASHES.
I'M GETTING THEM, TOO.
JOHN, WHAT IS
HAPPENING TO US?
I HAVE NO IDEA.
I'VE SEEN SOME
WEIRD THINGS
IN THE STAN,
EVEN STRANGER THINGS
AS THE HOOD, BUT THIS...
LOOK. WHEN YOU LEFT,
I TRIED TO DRAW ONE
OF THESE, UH,
MEMORY FLASHES,
AS YOU CALL THEM.
NEVER BEEN MUCH
OF AN ARTIST,
BUT THIS IS WHAT
I CAME UP WITH.
-WHAT THE HELL?
-I DON'T KNOW.
BEEN REMEMBERING THINGS.
IT'S LIKE THEY'RE DREAMS
BUT THEY'RE NOT, JOHN.
I DON'T THINK THAT
ANY OF THIS IS REAL.
WE'RE REAL,
BUT WHATEVER'S
PLAYING THESE
HEAD GAMES WITH US,
I DON'T THINK IT'S
FULLY WORKING.
ARE YOU SURE?
BECAUSE THE QUEEN'S GAMBIT...
THEY'VE PUT ME INTO A WORLD
WHERE I NEVER
GOT ON MY FATHER'S BOAT.
OLIVER, I DON'T KNOW
IF THESE ARE MEMORIES
OR FEELINGS, BUT I
THINK YOU'RE A HERO,
AND I DON'T THINK
IT'S BECAUSE OF ANY BOAT.
THESE HEAD GAMES
AREN'T OVER.
THEY ARE GONNA PUSH BACK
AGAINST WHATEVER WE DO.
PUSH BACK?
LIKE HOW?
LIKE THAT.
[CRACK]
HOW DID I DO THAT?
ALL RIGHT. THIS IS
HARD TO EXPLAIN.
WELL, START TRYING.
WE THINK...WE THINK
WE'RE IN SOME SORT
OF SHARED HALLUCINATION.
WHAT? THAT'S CRAZY.
I MEAN, NOT AS CRAZY
AS ME KNOWING KUNG FU,
BUT IT IS DEFINITELY
UP THERE.
THAT WASN'T KUNG FU.
THAT WAS JETE KUNE DO,
AND I THINK THAT
YOU LEARNED IT
IN A SPOT CALLED
NANDA PARBAT.
NOTHING YOU ARE SAYING
IS MAKING SENSE.
NONE OF THIS MAKES SENSE.
ALL RIGHT, SARA.
WHAT IS THE LAST
THING YOU REMEMBER?
-I DON'T KNOW.
-I MEAN, BEFORE YOU
CAME HERE YESTERDAY.
WHAT IS THE LAST
THING THAT YOU REMEMBER?
YOU REMEMBERED SOMETHING.
COME ON.
SARA, COME ON,
CONCENTRATE...
[ECHOING]
CONCENTRATE.
THERE WAS A FIGHT.
IT WAS 5 OF US,
AND THEN...
AND THEN WE WERE TAKEN.
JOHN:
TAKEN WHERE?
I DON'T KNOW.
WELL, ALL RIGHT.
THERE WERE 5 OF US.
WHO WERE
THE OTHER TWO?
RAY PALMER
AND...AND THEA.
I MEAN, IF THIS IS
SOME KIND OF DREAM
OR SHARED
HALLUCINATION,
THEN HOW DO WE WAKE UP?
BY GETTING OUT
OF HERE.
THE SMOAK TECHNOLOGIES
BUILDING.
MAYBE THE REASON
WHY THAT PLACE
SEEMS SO STRANGE
IS BECAUSE THAT'S
THE WAY WE GET
OUT OF HERE...
WHEREVER HERE IS.
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
YOU STOLE SOMETHING
FROM VAN HORN INDUSTRIES.
YOU MEAN THIS?
YEAH. HAND IT OVER.
OR WHAT?
I'LL TAKE IT
FROM YOU.
I DOUBT THAT.
YOU WANT TO GIVE UP?
I'M JUST
GETTING STARTED.
SO AM I.
RORY:
THAT WAS AWESOME.
THERE'S THE REGULATOR.
SHE SEEMS PRETTY
ATTACHED TO IT. HEH HEH.
MAYBE JUST REMOVE IT.
AHEM.
RENE: THANKS
FOR THE SAVE.
IS THAT ALL YOU
HAVE TO SAY?
I DON'T DO
APOLOGIES,
SWEETHEART...
BUT IF SUPERPOWERS
ARE A THING,
IT'S GOOD THERE ARE
GUYS LIKE YOU TO
HELP THE WORLD.
YOU KNOW, THE GREEN
GUY WOULD HAVE
KICKED MY ASS
IF I TALKED TO HIM
LIKE THAT.
OH, YEAH. YEAH.
WE KNOW. YEP.
THEA: IT'S TOO BAD
TOMMY COULDN'T
MAKE IT, THOUGH.
WELL, THEY'VE GOT HIM
WORKING TRIPLE SHIFTS
AT THE HOSPITAL
THESE DAYS.
BESIDES, CHICAGO
ISN'T EXACTLY
NEXT DOOR.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
HE'S A DOCTOR NOW.
WELL, HE SAYS THE SAME
THING ABOUT YOU,
MISS ENTREPRENEUR.
YEAH, I DON'T THINK
RUNNING VERDANT
MAKES ME
AN ENTREPRENEUR.
NO, BUT IT MAKES YOU
SUCCESSFUL.
YOUR FATHER SHOULD BE
VERY PROUD
OF THE WOMAN
YOU'VE GROWN INTO.
RAY, I NEED TO
TALK TO YOU.
SARA...RIGHT? H-HI.
UM, THIS IS
MY FIANCÉE FELICITY SMOAK.
HI. NICE TO MEET YOU.
OH, YOU'RE LAUREL'S
SISTER, RIGHT?
YEAH. CAN I STEAL
HIM FOR A SECOND?
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH. OK.
RAY, DOESN'T THIS
ALL FEEL WEIRD
TO YOU?
A LITTLE.
I NEED YOU TO THINK.
SHE'S NOT MY FIANCÉE.
MY FIANCÉE'S NAME
IS ANNA...OR WAS.
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
YOU'RE REMEMBERING.
OLIVER: HEY.
ROBERT: SON,
DON'T YOU THINK
YOU SHOULD BE GETTING
YOUR TUXEDO ON?
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT,
OLIVER?
I JUST NEED TO SPEAK
WITH THEA.
ROBERT: I THINK I SAW HER
TALKING TO MALCOLM
OVER BY
THE ICE SCULPTURE.
YEAH.
SON...I THINK YOU
NEED TO CLAM DOWN.
WE BOTH DO.
YOU'RE ACTING
TERRIBLY STRANGE.
YOUR MOTHER AND I
ARE CONCERNED
THAT IF YOU KEEP UP
THIS UNSTABLE BEHAVIOR
THAT IS NOT
GOING TO FINISH WELL.
THAT IS NOT GOING TO
FINISH WELL.
-WHAT?
-I'M JUST SAYING.
LAUREL, THE COMPANY.
THIS IS YOUR LIFE NOW.
NO, IT ISN'T.
OLIVER.
I'M SO...I'M SORRY.
ROBERT: OLLIE, OLLIE.
-SPEEDY.
-SHE KNOWS, OLLIE.
SHE KNOWS, AND SHE
DOESN'T WANT TO GO.
THE BETTER QUESTION IS
WHY WOULD YOU WANT TO?
BECAUSE NONE OF THIS
IS REAL.
IT'S REAL ENOUGH, OK?
IT'S...IT'S BETTER
THAN OUR REAL LIVES.
IN...IN THIS LIFE,
LAUREL IS ALIVE,
MY PARENTS ARE ALIVE.
BUT THOSE ARE NOT
YOUR PARENTS.
THEY REMEMBER THE ONLY
LULLABY THAT WOULD
ACTUALLY WORK
TO PUT ME TO SLEEP.
THEY REMEMBER
EVERY DAY OF MY LIFE, OK?
THEY EVEN SMELL
LIKE THEM, OLLIE...
THEY'RE NOT THEM,
THEA.
I WANT THEM TO BE,
BUT...
BUT THEY'RE NOT.
WHERE ARE JOHN AND RAY?
THEY'RE WAITING OUTSIDE.
GIVE US
A FEW MINUTES.
WE CAN'T STAY HERE,
SPEEDY, NO MATTER
HOW MUCH WE WANT TO.
WE CAN'T.
WHY NOT?
WHAT IS WAITING
FOR US,
WHEREVER WE ARE
RIGHT NOW?
NOTHING. NOTHING
BUT PAIN
AND S-SUFFERING.
THEA, WE HAVE
RESPONSIBILITIES.
WE HAVE PEOPLE
WHO COUNT ON US.
THERE'S FLASH
AND...AND SUPERGIRL
AND...AND PEOPLE
WITH ACTUAL POWERS NOW.
WHATEVER NEEDS TO BE DONE,
THEY CAN HANDLE IT.
WE...WE FINALLY HAVE
A CHANCE TO BE HAPPY.
I MEAN, WHY...WHY CAN'T
YOU JUST FOR A SECOND ACCEPT
THAT MAYBE THIS IS
YOUR REWARD
FOR ALL OF THE SACRIFICES
YOU HAVE MADE?
I DIDN'T MAKE
THOSE SACRIFICES
FOR A REWARD, THEA.
I DID WHAT I DID
BECAUSE I THOUGHT
IT WAS RIGHT...
AND SEEING ALL THIS,
IT HAS JUST...
IT HAS SHOWN ME THAT
THERE IS STILL SO MUCH
MORE TO DO,
SO PLEASE, I'M BEGGING
YOU TO COME WITH ME
BECAUSE I CANNOT
DO IT ALONE.
BUT...
I CAN'T LOSE
THEM AGAIN.
I CAN'T LOSE MY FAMILY.
OK. OK. ALL RIGHT.
I WANT YOU TO BE WELL,
I WANT YOU TO BE HAPPY.
I LOVE YOU, THEA.
[THUNDER]
JOHN: WHERE'S THEA?
THEA'S STAYING.
HAVE YOU EXPLAINED
TO RAY WHAT WE
HAVE TO DO?
YEAH. APPARENTLY,
WE HAVE TO GET TO
AN OFFICE TOWER THAT MY
NON-FIANCEE DOESN'T OWN.
WHICH IS
A LITTLE STRANGE.
ALL THAT
COMING FROM A GUY
WHO'S BEEN
HAVING MEMORIES
THAT HE'S ABLE
TO SHRINK.
WELL, WHATEVER
WE'RE DOING, WE
HAVE TO DO IT FAST
BECAUSE WHATEVER
THE DOMINATORS HAVE
DONE TO US,
THEY WOULD HAVE
BUILT IN SAFEGUARDS.
THEY'RE PROBABLY
MANIFESTATIONS
FROM OUR MEMORIES
DESIGNED TO
KEEP US HERE.
OHH! AGH!
AGH! UNH!
THEY'RE NOT REAL.
THEA: THEY CERTAINLY
LOOK REAL.
LET'S NOT GET
INTO THAT RIGHT NOW.
SPEEDY?
YEAH. I HAD A CHANGE
OF HEART, OK?
LIKE I SAID,
I CAN'T LOSE
MY FAMILY AGAIN.
MALCOLM: YOUR FATHER'S
STILL ALIVE, THEA.
YOUR REAL FATHER
AT LEAST.
UNFORTUNATELY, THIS IS
GONNA BE A LITTLE LESS
SATISFYING FOR ME
THAN KILLING YOUR SISTER.
AGH!
OLLIE!
[THUNDER]
LAUREL: OLLIE?
SARA, SARA, WHAT'S
GOING ON HERE?
LAUREL, LOOK.
I CAN'T EXPLAIN,
BUT I HAVE TO GO.
WE HAVE TO GO.
WHAT? NO. NO.
WHATEVER IT IS,
WE CAN FIX IT.
LOOK. WE CAN'T.
SOME THINGS YOU
JUST CAN'T FIX.
OLLIE, OLLIE, OLLIE,
WHAT'S HAPPENING.
I'M SORRY.
THE PERSON YOU
FELL IN LOVE WITH...
THAT'S NOT ME,
AND I NEVER DESERVED
THAT LOVE...
AND YOU ALWAYS
DESERVED BETTER.
PLEASE.
I LOVE YOU.
DON'T...DON'T GO!
[CRYING]
OK, JOHN. WHAT NOW?
GUYS, I DON'T THINK
THAT BELONGS THERE.
OK. THAT'S EITHER
THE WAY OUT OF HERE,
OR WE GOT TO CLICK
OUR HEELS TOGETHER
3 TIMES AND SAY,
"THERE'S NO PLACE
LIKE HOME."
AND IF THAT DOESN'T WORK?
IT HAS TO WORK.
HE'S RUNNING
OUT OF TIME.
COME ON.
MOIRA, VOICE-OVER:
YOU'RE NEVER WITHOUT ME,
MY BEAUTIFUL BOY.
THERE'S NOTHING ELSE
TO SAY EXCEPT
I COULD NOT BE
MORE PROUD OF YOU.
BECOME SOMEONE ELSE.
BECOME SOMETHING ELSE.
FELICITY, VOICE-OVER:
YOU HONOR THE DEAD BY FIGHTING,
AND YOU ARE NOT DONE
FIGHTING!
TOMMY, VOICE-OVER:
I KNOW I CALLED
YOU A MURDERER,
BUT YOU ARE NOT.
YOU ARE A HERO.
ROY, VOICE-OVER:
YOU SAVED MY LIFE.
YOU GAVE ME PURPOSE.
THIS TIME, WE HAD TO
SAVE YOU.
LAUREL, VOICE-OVER:
I KNOW WHO YOU ARE
IN YOUR BONES, OLIVER,
AND THAT PERSON
DOESN'T GIVE UP!
ROBERT, VOICE-OVER: THIS IS
YOUR RESPONSIBILITY NOW.
THEA: OHH. OH, GOD.
WHERE ARE WE?
YOU ALL RIGHT?
YEAH. IT MAY NOT
BE REAL,
BUT IT
STILL HURTS LIKE
A SON OF A BITCH.
RAY: UH, GUYS.
THERE'S SOMETHING YOU
REALLY NEED TO SEE.
RORY: ANY LUCK
WITH THE REGULATOR WE
TOOK OFF CYBER-WOMAN?
PHEW. CYBER-WOMAN?
I THINK I'M STARTING
TO LIKE YOU GUYS.
THE REGULATOR WORKED,
BUT MY TRANSLATOR DID NOT.
THE ONLY THING I GOT BACK
FROM THE DOMINATOR TECH
WAS SOUP.
FELICITY: WHAT?
WELL, NO, NO, NO.
THIS...NO. THIS JUST
LOOKS RANDOM.
IT'S NOT.
IT'S GEMATRIA.
GEMATRIA IS
THE NUMEROLOGY OF...
OF THE TORAH.
HOW DID I NOT SEE THAT?
FOR THE GENTILES
AND THOSE OF US
WHO ACTUALLY HAD
SOCIAL LIVES
IN HIGH SCHOOL,
WHAT THE HELL ARE
YOU TALKING ABOUT?
IN HEBREW, EACH LETTER
POSSESSES A NUMERICAL VALUE.
GEMATRIA IS THE CALCULATION
OF THE NUMERICAL EQUIVALENTS
OF LETTERS, WORDS,
OR PHRASES.
YOU MEAN, THE DOMINATORS'
LANGUAGE IS
BASED OFF
THE OLD TESTAMENT?
OR SHARES COMMONALITIES
AT LEAST.
YOU WANTED PROOF
OF A DIVINE PLAN
TO THE UNIVERSE, RIGHT?
FELICITY: GUYS,
I'M GETTING REFERENCES
TO 5 TERRAN CAPTIVES
HERE, OK?
THE SIGNAL'S COMING
FROM...THAT'S NOT POSSIBLE.
-3.127 LATITUDE,
-23.7987 LONGITUDE.
THAT DOESN'T
MAKE ANY SENSE.
GEOGRAPHICAL COORDINATES
DON'T HAVE
ANY NEGATIVE NUMBERS.
I MEAN, THEY DO.
ONLY WHEN...
OH, MY GOD. I THINK
I KNOW WHERE THEY ARE.
KLIC-CLAC-TO NICK-LAVA
SHACK-TOO.
NICK-LAVA SHOO-LA.
THEA: OK. SO HOW DO WE FIND
OUR WAY OUT
OF AN ALIEN SPACECRAFT?
THIS WAY.
EVEN THOUGH IT'S
AN ALIEN TECHNOLOGY,
CERTAIN PRINCIPLES
OF DESIGN ARE
UNIVERSAL.
OR NOT.
RAY'S RIGHT.
CERTAIN PRINCIPLES
OF DESIGN ARE UNIVERSAL.
JOHN: YOU THINK YOU CAN
FLY ONE OF THESE THINGS?
I'M HOPING THAT
BETWEEN YOU, ME,
RAY, AND SARA
SOMEONE CAN FLY
ONE OF THESE THINGS.
OK. NOW WHAT?
OLIVER: RAY?
UM, NOW MIGHT BE
A GOOD TIME TO FIND
THE OWNER'S MANUAL.
[COMPUTERS BEEPING]
AND MOM SAID I WOULDN'T
AMOUNT TO ANYTHING
IF I DIDN'T GO
TO COLLEGE.
UH, I REALLY HOPE YOU
HIT AUTOPILOT
BECAUSE I DON'T SEE ANY
CONTROLS ON THIS THING.
HOLD ON!
WE GOT INCOMING!
SARA: HOW DO YOU KNOW?
[BOOM]
LUCKY GUESS?
WE NEED TO FIND A WAY
TO STEER THIS THING,
OR WE'RE NOT GONNA
LAST VERY LONG!
OLIVER...
NICE CLOTHES.
SHOPPING AT ALIEN GAP?
NOT FUNNY.
WELL, LUCKY
FOR YOU GUYS,
THE WAVERIDER HAS
A MACHINE THAT
REPLICATES OLD CLOTHES
AND WEAPONS.
-HI. I'M NATE HEYWOOD.
-HI. THEA,
AND...AND THIS IS
EXACTLY TWICE AS MANY
SPACESHIPS AS I EVER
THOUGHT I'D BE ON.
WELL, ACTUALLY,
IT'S A TIME SHIP.
-HOW'D YOU FIND US?
-I DIDN'T.
YOUR NERD ARMY
BACK ON EARTH DID.
SARA: I'M GONNA TAKE
DIG TO THE MED BAY,
HAVE GIDEON FIX HIM UP.
JOHN: WHOEVER
GIDEON IS.
THEA: OH...GET...OUT!
OLIVER:
THANKS FOR THE SAVE.
NATE: NO PROBLEM.
RAY: EXCEPT FOR
ALL OF OUR OTHER
PROBLEMS.
OLIVER: LIKE WHAT, RAY?
RAY: AFTER WE
WOKE UP,
I GOT A LOOK
AT THE TECH
THE DOMINATORS WERE
USING TO KEEP
US UNDER.
THEY'RE USING
A NEUROMORPHIC INTERFACE
SIMILAR TO HOW I MANIPULATE
THE ATOM SUIT.
THEA: AND...AND WAIT.
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
I...I THINK THE SHARED
HALLUCINATION
WAS TO KEEP OUR MINDS
OCCUPIED WHILE
THE DOMINATORS...
OLIVER: WHILE
THE DOMINATORS WHAT?
WELL, WHILE THEY
PROBED OUR SUBCONSCIOUS.
I'M GUESSING LOOKING
FOR INTEL.
WAIT. MAYBE THEY DIDN'T
CHOOSE US AT RANDOM.
MAYBE THEY CHOSE US
BECAUSE WE COULDN'T
FIGHT BACK.
BECAUSE NONE OF YOU
ARE METAHUMANS.
BIGGER QUESTION...
WHAT INTEL WERE
THEY AFTER?
WHAT IS THEIR PLAN?
"KLIC-CLAC-TO NICK-LAVA
SHACK-TOO."
GESUNDHEIT.
IT'S WHAT ONE
OF THE DOMINATORS
SAID TO ANOTHER.
HEH. SOUNDS LIKE
THE BEGINNING OF
A NOT-SO-FUNNY JOKE,
BUT, GIDEON.
GIDEON: TRANSLATING.
THEA: DID YOU EVER
THINK THAT OUR LIVES
WOULD REALLY GET
THIS WEIRD?
GIDEON: THE PHRASE LOOSELY
TRANSLATES TO
"WE ARE NEARING COMPLETION
OF THE WEAPON."
WHAT WEAPON?
I'M AFRAID I HAVE
NO IDEA,
BUT I'M TRACKING
THE DOMINATOR MOTHERSHIP
YOU ESCAPED FROM,
AND IT APPEARS TO BE
ON A DIRECT COURSE FOR EARTH.