My name is Oliver Queen.
After 6 months in hell,
I have been released from prison
and returned home with only one goal...
To save my city,
but things have changed.
Instead of operating outside the law,
I am now working alongside the police.
I am no longer inmate 4587.
I am once more the Green Arrow.
Previously on "Arrow"...
Ricardo Diaz is dead.
Whoever's been running around
dressed up as the Green Arrow,
that's your murderer.
Does she have any
reason to blame my family
for her mother's death?
Y'all did become Starling City royalty
while she and her mom were
left to struggle in The Glades.
What our father did to
you was unforgivable.
I see now you are different from him.
You and Oliver Queen are
getting along quite well.
He trusts me now.
It's time for you to come home.
Archer is active.
I think that's more than a
security system you're working on.
I think you're on to something big.
You're lying about who you really are.
What makes you think they will believe
a word you say,
Black Siren?
Where are we supposed to go?
I don't know. I'm sorry.
Sorry? This is our home, Robert,
one that you used to be a part of.
You don't understand.
If I let you stay, she
will take everything...
My company, my money, my children.
What about our child?
The movers will be
here tomorrow afternoon.
Tell Emiko I'm sorry.
- Emiko.
- Where are we going, Dad?
You and your mom are going to live
someplace else, someplace better.
But I want to stay here!
I know you do, kiddo,
but life isn't fair.
We don't always get what we want.
I'm sorry.
Dad, please don't leave.
You okay?
Are you?
Where'd you learn that?
I'll tell you if you tell me
where you learned taekwondo.
I learned taekwondo
from a woman named Talia in Russia.
Your past gets more
mysterious every day.
Could say the same thing about you.
Your turn.
It's complicated.
I had a good teacher. He, um,
showed me how to protect myself.
He taught you well.
Nice trick.
The key is to watch your opponent
and not the stick.
What are you smiling about?
- I kicked your ass.
- Oh, no.
You most certainly did not.
Thea and I used to spar like this.
She always wanted a sister.
So did I.
Rematch?
If you think you can handle it.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
Oh, come on, Smoak. You got this.
You know you can be pregnant
and be CEO of a company
and a deputized vigilante by night.
Women really can have it all.
I'm talking to myself.
DNA match complete.
Identity confirmed. Alena Whitlock.
Well, that is ingenious.
Was not expecting an entrance
or that you knew my last name.
- Alena, hi.
- Hi.
Hi! Oh, it's been so
long. How have you been?
When you're the known associate
of the evil and murder
genius Cayden James,
good to keep a low profile,
so I'm working at Tech Village.
Oh, no. Oh. I have been there literally.
I know your pain. The... the vests.
So, um, how did you find me, actually?
It's part of a new project
I have been working on.
It started off as, like, a
home-based security system,
and now it's turned into, like,
a DNA-tracking-based
surveillance system.
- Meet Archer.
- Sorry. So you located me
using my DNA?
When did you collect my DNA? Heh.
- I know it's a little creepy.
- It's more than a little,
but it's also impressive.
I've been using it for
Team Arrow, but I think
if we scaled it up, it could
be so much more than that.
I mean, we could find missing
persons, we could track terrorists,
we could do crowd control,
we could do anything!
Just, I can't do it alone.
I mean, whatever you need, I am game.
I am so done telling customers to use
the chip in their card
when they insist on swiping.
Great! How does CTO of
Smoak Technologies sound?
Oh! Oh! Oh!
Oh! You're not even
gonna ask about benefits?
I don't care about the benefits
as long as there's no
crappy vest requirement.
- I am in!
- No vest. Huge benefit.
Music to my ears.
D.A. Laurel Lance is at the front door.
Allow access.
Access granted.
It's open.
- Hey.
- Is your wife around?
No. She went out. What's up?
Uh, nothing. I'll just...
I'll come find Felicity later.
Your bandage is bleeding through.
Sit down. We'll get you cleaned up.
Fine.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
Looks like an arrow wound.
Because it is an arrow wound.
Where'd it come from?
Your sister's bow.
- What?
- Look. I don't mean to
blindside you with this,
which is why I wanted
to talk to Felicity...
You know, empathy and all that...
But your sister is not
the hero you think she is.
What are you talking about?
Ben Turner saw her at Slabside
the night Diaz was murdered.
It wasn't another
inmate that killed Diaz.
It was Emiko.
Heh heh heh.
That makes no sense.
Well, I figured you'd say that,
so I did more digging,
and there are no records
of her that exist past the age of 15,
no fingerprints.
And when I followed her
last night to find out more,
she tried skewering me with an arrow.
Okay. I've seen her skills up close.
She doesn't miss.
If she wanted you dead, you'd be dead.
Oh. Maybe I should be thankful, then.
Once upon a time, I actually
shot Roy Harper and Barry Allen.
It was to illustrate a point.
My guess is that her point is
she doesn't want to be stalked anymore.
Or maybe sister has brother wrapped
around her little finger.
You know, the Oliver I knew, he had
a blind spot for family,
and I'm guessing you do, too.
It's called loyalty.
I know that's a concept you
don't totally understand.
I have nothing to gain here.
I am only trying to do what's right.
Why can you not see that?
There has to be more to this,
and I will look into it
if you will promise to stay out of it.
I already wish I would have.
Good luck.
If I give this to you,
my family's safe, right?
I can guarantee it.
If it's all there.
All that we'll need.
I believe we're done here.
What the hell is that?
Uh!
Help!
Someone...
Please.
Hey. It's okay. It's okay.
I got you, I got you. I got you.
Forget about me.
You need to stop them.
Who? Who? Stop who?
The Ninth Circle.
The Ninth what?
- Circle.
- Dante's a part of it.
Turns out he's not just a banker
for terrorists and cartels.
Okay. Lyla and I have been
hunting Dante for months.
Why are we just hearing this name?
Because the Ninth Circle
is practically invisible.
I mean, I combed the entire
dark web and came up with nada,
but then I remembered
this photo you sent me
from the Ghost Initiative's last ride.
Right. That symbol was on
all the weapons that
Virgil's goons used.
The symbol also pops up on
artifacts dating all the way back
to 14th-century Italy,
the real Dante's era.
The insignia is mostly
commonly found on ephemera
that is connected to times
of historical upheaval...
The Russian Revolution, the
colonization of the Americas,
the War of Roses.
So you're saying Dante
runs a secret society
responsible for centuries
of worldwide regime change?
Right, but if that's true,
the Ninth Circle's clearly way bigger
than just Dante.
Okay. Well, how did you run
into Dante last night, Oliver,
and why didn't you call for backup?
Laurel came to speak
with you and found me.
Suggested that...
Emiko has been hiding
certain parts of her past
and said that she killed Diaz.
She killed Diaz?
Which doesn't mean she's bad.
I followed Emiko,
and it led me to Dante.
Okay. Well, all we
really know about Emiko
is what she's told us, which isn't much.
She's a vigilante. For all we know,
she's gathering intel on the
Ninth Circle to take them down.
Also, why are we taking
Laurel's word about anything?
Hey. Laurel has changed a lot.
I mean, she's been a
really good friend to me...
Not to say that your sister's
evil, but she's changed a lot.
Be that as it may, the Ninth
Circle is clearly a threat,
and we need to follow up
every lead that we have.
Well, we know that they
stole 8 military-grade drones,
which they could literally be
planning to do anything with.
Okay. Can you use Archer to
pinpoint Dante's location?
Not without his DNA.
Okay. Well, I'll talk to Lyla,
take this new intel back there,
and see if we can use
A.R.G.U.S.'s databases.
Yeah. We should be able
to use SCPD resources, too.
I'll get D up to speed.
I'm gonna go speak with my sister.
She deserves a chance
to explain herself.
And I... I will...
I'll be here.
What is so important that
couldn't be handled over the phone?
Do you remember our conversation
about playing by the rules,
about doing things the right
way is usually the hard way?
Why do I feel a lecture coming on?
The Halcones' Kingpin, Ramiro Gonzalez,
we had a witness
who was ready to nail him
for criminal conspiracy
until we found out his
confession was coerced by the D.A.
You wanted the city cleaned up, right?
I'm cleaning.
You are an officer of the law.
You have to play by it.
You know, with Team Arrow
working alongside the SCPD,
this city has a real chance
of turning things around,
and it's never gonna happen
if our D.A. is a criminal.
All of those guys are guilty.
You'd rather see them kicked than me
bend a couple of... of little rules
to make sure their charges stick?
Yes, because if anyone finds
out what you've been up to,
they're all gonna get
off on technicalities,
and you're gonna get fired.
Fine, but I'm sure there's a reason
you brought this up in the first place.
You have a second chance.
SWAT brought in one of Ramirez's
lieutenants last night...
Gustavo Hernandez.
He's looking to deal,
and I want you to put
that Kingpin behind bars.
Just need you to do it the right way.
You really know how to take
the fun out of everything.
Uh, we don't have a training
session until next week.
I don't think family
needs a reason to stop by.
Going somewhere?
I, uh, was just heading
out for a bite to eat.
- What some company?
- Hmm. Not really.
Because you're meeting someone?
What's with the interrogation?
That teacher that you
were telling me about,
how long did you train with him?
Since I was 11.
Where'd you meet?
It doesn't matter. It
was a long time ago.
Yeah. I mean, if I was
working with a known terrorist,
I'd want to keep that quiet, too.
What are you talking about?
I saw you last night with Dante
outside Palmer Technologies.
You were following me.
Mm-hmm.
So now you, uh...
You think I'm some kind of criminal?
Trying to give you the
benefit of the doubt,
but... this guy Dante is...
He's a monster.
I know who Dante is,
but I... I didn't back then.
I was 11 when your father
walked out on me and my mother.
He chose your family over mine,
and he left us with nothing...
No home, no money.
Dante took me under his wing,
and he... he trained me.
He taught me how to survive.
By the time I knew who he
really was, it was too late.
You know, I owed him,
and I still do now.
I can help you.
You have no idea
what kind of power he holds.
The organization he runs...
The Ninth Circle?
Then you know there's no way out.
On your own,
but if you're being backed up
by a team...
Just, I can... I can help you,
but you have to let me.
You can't, and, trust me,
you will only make things worse
for the both of us if you try.
Delivery from Frank Bertinelli.
I didn't know the Bertinellis
employed child labor.
Pays better than a lemonade stand,
and the cops don't hassle a kid.
That'll be all.
I'll take my watch back.
Do you know who I am?
Dante. It says on the package.
The suspense is killing me.
- Emiko.
- Well, Emiko,
taking my watch is a pretty risky move.
Well, I need money,
and it looks like you have enough.
I earn it.
How'd you do that thing with the knife?
Pretty simple, actually.
I can teach you if you want.
Come back tomorrow.
That was a good lift.
Steal from me again,
and I'll slit your throat.
Good news!
Lyla got a DNA sample from
the dagger used by Dante
to kill Director Bell.
Guess who now has said sample.
John Diggle, you give the best gifts.
Now that we have Dante's DNA,
will Archer be able to find him?
Well, with all the money I'm spending
on this program, that is the hope.
How's Emiko? Did you find anything more
- about her being...
- Being on the wrong side.
She admitted to being in very deep
with Dante and the Ninth Circle.
Sounds like she could
be in some real trouble.
Boom. I got him.
Looks like he's at the Star City branch
of Szrek Chemicals.
If we surprise Dante now,
we could still take him down.
And get my sister out of trouble.
Let's suit up.
Hey, Jerry. We still
on for beers tonight?
Maybe we should try Nelson's.
Better service.
I'm afraid Jerry's not gonna make it.
Please don't kill me.
Of course not.
Unh!
Those.
- You told him we were here!
- I didn't.
Your allegiance has shifted.
Now!
D, go! We got you covered.
Agh!
Let's get out of here.
Grab her.
Let me go!
- You okay?
- Uh-huh.
I shouldn't be here. Dante will find me.
It's just a matter of time,
and you will all be targets.
Yeah? Well, it won't be the first time.
Think about it like this.
It'll be a hell of a
lot easier to stop Dante
with all of us working
together than you by yourself.
Okay, as long as I get to be
the one who takes him down.
That sounds fair to me.
Well, yeah, except
there's just one problem.
Archer just crashed, which
means I lost Dante's location.
Fine. We'll just have to find
Dante the old-fashioned way.
Easier said than done.
Now that he knows I'm working with you,
we should consider all Ninth
Circle locations burned.
But that op we just interrupted,
I mean, Dante didn't get
what he was looking for.
You must know what he was after.
Enriched uranium.
I told you he was dangerous.
We need to figure out
where else in the city
he can get his hands on that uranium.
Yeah. I'm on it.
Archer may have crashed,
but computers will never replace people.
Do you have any idea what
he was planning on doing
with the drones and uranium?
I wish I had more intel,
but it was always on
a need-to-know basis.
That's how the Ninth Circle works.
- Hey. You hurt?
- Not badly.
- You guys have some ice?
- Yeah.
This could not be worse timing,
but I have to run to the SCPD.
Go ahead, Captain. We'll
handle it from here.
Hey. What's wrong?
Just be careful with her, Oliver.
Okay. I will.
Hey, guys. Think I got something.
- That was fast.
- One point for the humans.
If Emiko is right and
he's after uranium,
there's only two places in
Star City that have it...
Dunkirk Power and Global Energy.
Sounds like a divide
and conquer situation.
My thoughts exactly.
So are you just gonna
not ask me about it?
You have nothing to say about the fact
that I've been secretly
working for the Ninth Circle?
I know you well enough not to pry,
and you did try to keep
me out of your mission
when we first met.
I didn't want you to
get mixed up with them,
but I... I should
have told you the truth
so you'd know what you
were really getting into
working with me.
I bet you wish you'd listened
when I told you to stay away.
If you think I regret
teaming up with you, I don't.
We're still partners, Emiko,
no matter who we're up against.
You haven't practiced.
This is much harder than last week.
No. You're just not prepared.
I was busy. I was working on something.
Oh, yes. Your plan to impress Daddy.
Being a father means
more than just blood.
I know, but he is still my father.
So you would choose a
man who abandoned you
over the Ninth Circle?
Why can't I have both?
The Ninth Circle is not a
place of split loyalties.
Once you join, it is
a lifetime commitment.
There is nothing else.
I can't give up on my family.
The Ninth Circle is your family now...
And that is their gift to you.
You really want a deal
for this smug bastard?
Are you sure?
Bigger picture, Laurel.
Mr. Hernandez, do you know who I am?
You're the D.A. who
used to be a vigilante.
Yeah, I know you.
Good because I know you, too...
Drug trafficking,
embezzlement, manslaughter.
Murder?
So this is the part
where you offer me a deal
to make it all go away, right?
Hmm. If it were up to me,
I'd let you rot or worse,
but, luckily for you, it's
your boss who we're after...
Ramiro Gonzalez.
And you think that a plea
deal's enough to flip me?
Hey. I've got enough evidence here
to convict you of 3 felonies,
one using a deadly weapon,
and that was in a day.
Imagine what I could do in a week.
You know, your dad thought he
could convict me, too, right?
Must be a family defect.
I would be really careful if I were you
because we're not a family
that plays very nice.
How's that going for you?
Captain Lance... He's
dead now, isn't he?
Say his name one more
time, and you will be, too.
Aw. Girl's got a soft
spot for Daddy. Aw.
That's enough, D.A. Lance.
We're done here.
Global Energy was a bust.
No sign of Dante or the uranium.
Ah. You still came back looking
like a prizefighter, though.
We ran into a couple
thugs on the way back.
Ooh. Cute. A little brother-sister
crime-fighting duo time.
- I like it.
- Any word from John and Rene?
They struck out, too.
Global Energy and Dunkirk Power are
two spots in Star City
that manufacture uranium.
- Archer's still not working.
- Right.
I'm just about to go down
into the deepest, darkest,
most dungeony part of this bunker
and give it a full system reboot.
Then hopefully then, you know,
Archer can be back online,
we can find Dante, and all my dreams
of Smoak Tech saving the
world don't have to die.
I'm gonna clean this up.
Think I found the problem.
Some kind of jammer.
Wonder how that got there.
So you were never under duress.
Sorry to disappoint you,
but that's what family does, right?
This is the reason that
Archer isn't working?
I couldn't let you and your
team get in the way again.
We don't give up that easily.
You've been lying this entire time,
everything about our father,
your debt to Dante?
It was all true, but I never needed you
to put me back together.
I just knew you'd try.
Can't resist playing the hero, can you?
Unh!
You went looking for a family,
and you chose the Ninth Circle?
Better than living as a Queen.
Always watch your opponent.
You don't have to be a part of this.
You have a choice!
I've made it!
Bye, Brother.
I was married to a junkie.
You'd think I'd know when
someone was lying to me.
At least now we know what
side Emiko's really on.
It doesn't matter. The... the
Ninth Circle are still out there,
and they are a threat.
You can take a minute to
process this if you need to.
I need to know where she is.
How soon can you have
Archer back up and running?
Not as soon as I would like.
Emiko's little device didn't
just jam up the system.
It wiped the entire
memory card, which means
I have to rebuild the
entire infrastructure.
Looks like we have another problem.
There's been a break-in at the
waste treatment site at Orchard Bay.
I thought the only spots
that manufactured uranium
were the two sites we just canvassed.
Well, that's true, but
how much do you want to bet
that Dante and his pals
aren't actually after uranium?
- More of Emiko's lies.
- What'd they get?
All the ingredients to make
a big batch of sarin gas.
That plus the drones
that they just stole
makes one hell of a murder party.
We have to know where the Ninth Circle
is planning on sending these drones.
- Oliver, we're on it.
- You might want to take 5.
I'm going to Emiko's hideout,
see if she left behind
a clue or something.
Yeah, or you could do
exactly the opposite
of what your wife recommends.
I'll go with him.
Are you here to give
me another lecture or...
The Halcones' Lieutenant,
Gustavo Hernandez,
was found dead an hour ago.
Really?
Am I supposed to be sad
about that or something?
Well, we had him in
custody to prevent that.
That is, of course, until your
office said we had to turn him loose.
Well, he made bail.
You're the one that said I
had to do things the right way,
so I let him loose,
and here we are back to square one.
Well, actually, we're not.
Hernandez's death
spooked one of Gonzalez's
other lieutenants,
and, uh, he's gonna testify.
Isn't that convenient?
You think I did this.
I'm not exactly hearing a denial.
I shouldn't have to give you one.
I think I've done more than enough
to have earned the benefit
of the doubt from you.
I saw how you looked at that man,
and it was the same
look that you gave Vinnie
right before you executed him.
I have busted my ass being a good D.A.,
trying to play by the rules,
but no matter what I do, you
always just see me as the Black Siren.
You're right. You're right,
and I am sorry, but I don't know
who you really are, Laurel.
I don't, and I don't
think that you do either.
I think that's what scares me the most.
Didn't hurt you too
bad back there, did I?
No. It was a convincing performance.
Did you, uh, make any
progress on who hired
Andrew Thorn... ton?
You know I'm a man of my word.
Once you've found and taken
care of your mother's killer,
you can go back to
focusing on the mission.
A deal is a deal.
This is really impressive.
Did you come up with this yourself?
Yeah, I did.
Um, and Queen Materials,
Inc., could be profitable
in as little as 6 months.
If you look at page 7,
after an initial startup fee,
its projected growth rate is at 14%.
I wish Oliver showed this kind
of interest in the business.
I inherited your business sense.
Let me start Queen
Materials, and I'll show you.
Well, I... I can't approve this.
Why not?
Queen Consolidated is for Oliver.
He's going to inherit it,
and if anyone were to find
out that you're my daughter...
I need this.
Okay. Otherwise, I am gonna have to find
the money somewhere else,
and I need it to help Mom,
- something you never did.
- Emiko.
Do you ever even think about us?
All the time,
and I wish things were different.
I really do.
Since the day you left,
I kept holding out, thinking
one day you'd do the right thing
and become the father I deserved.
It's never gonna happen, is it?
I have to go.
I have a trip planned to China
on the "Queen's Gambit."
And I'm sorry.
Is there something else you'd
like to talk to me about?
No. Have a good trip.
You want to talk?
Not even to the guy who found out
his long lost sibling was secretly
an evil double agent?
Being reminded that
this has happened before
is not really making things better.
I get that, but I also know
that despite what Emiko's done,
you're not quite ready
to give up on her.
That obvious, huh?
Only to someone who knows you
and who's been there.
All I wanted was to bring
Andy back over to the light.
I don't have to remind you what
having that blind spot cost us.
No, you don't.
But please, John,
trust me when I tell you
that I am seeing Emiko more
clearly than I ever have.
Oliver, you're still trying to save her.
John, my family is to blame
for her current situation.
My... my father a-abandoned
her and her mother.
She was 11!
She was 11 years old,
and no one's gonna convince me that...
That her life wouldn't be different now
if that had never happened.
Andy tried to convince
me that I was the reason
for his bad choices, too.
He made me feel so
guilty that I was willing
to trust him again even after knowing
he worked for Damien Darhk.
I held out hope, Oliver, so much hope
that I put you, my family,
my team at risk.
John, if I abandon her now...
I'm no better than my father.
If I can help redeem her,
selfishly I feel like I... I
help redeem my family just...
A little.
Felicity got a hit on the Ninth Circle.
Drones are at an abandoned
airfield north of the city.
And Emiko?
She's there.
Let's get the team. Let's go.
All right. They're still
prepping the drones.
Good news is we're not too late.
Bad news is we're outnumbered 5:1.
Those are my kind of odds.
- Got eyes on Dante.
- And Emiko.
Once the drones are primed,
we can begin the demonstration.
Eight stolen drones, which
means 8 potential targets,
and each one runs on a separate signal.
It's gonna take some time to
hack into the guidance system.
Oliver, that means that you
need to stop those things
before they take off.
You draw them out, I'll get the drones.
- Copy that.
- Let's go!
Unh!
It's your brother.
I'll deal with him.
Pack up the demonstration.
No! The demonstration goes as planned.
Protect the drones.
Unh!
Dante!
Drive.
Damn it!
Emiko.
Get out of here.
Bad news, guys. Those
drones are airborne,
which means you need to
incinerate them mid-air
or else that's a lot of sarin
gas raining down on the city.
Overwatch, it would be very
helpful if I could see them.
Okay. I'm working on
decloaking them now.
I'm in.
There's still one drone left.
I'm working on it.
Emiko, it's not too late.
Whatever you owe Dante...
I owe Dante everything.
Dante taught me how
to take care of myself,
to cut the ties that bind
us, that hold us back,
which is why it's time
for us to say good-bye...
Brother!
Kill him!
Please tell me you got that last drone.
By the time I locked on, the
gas had already been deployed.
Sorry, Oliver.
- How many casualties?
- None.
The target was an abandoned building.
What about the other targets?
Well, that's the even weirder thing.
All of the other buildings
targeted were also empty.
Who goes to the trouble
of bombing empty buildings?
Seemed like some sort of weapons test.
Well, imagine what would
happen if all the drones worked
instead of just one.
They'd be able to take out
multiple targets simultaneously.
If we couldn't stop this test,
how are we gonna stop the real thing?
Reacting to the shocking allegations
about District Attorney Laurel Lance,
new photos show her with
notorious criminal Ricardo Diaz.
Could the city's highest prosecutor
actually be a wanted criminal herself?
Looks like you've got a problem.
- You.
- Knocked off that Halcone?
I did.
Media's gonna have a field day.
- You're a psycho.
- And you make me sad,
trying so hard to become
someone you're not,
and for what?
So that the city will take
you seriously as a hero.
That is almost as ridiculous
as you wanting to be one.
Get the hell out of my office. Now!
I thought I was punishing
you for following me.
Maybe I just set you free.
Oh, hey. Good. You're still here.
I'm sorry. It's been a day.
I assume that's always the case.
Honestly, going over
Archer has made me happier
than I've been in months.
The algorithms you programmed are like
this beautifully composed Rondo-Finale.
A Rondo what, now?
Not into opera. Got it.
Hey. So question for version two.
- Mm-hmm?
- What happens when we
don't have the DNA of the
person that we are looking for?
- What do we do then?
- Well, that's a little trickier.
We could reprogram the
algorithm to highlight
any individuals whose DNA we don't have,
but unless we hack into a
medical or criminal database
and collect all of
their DNA profiles first,
all we'd really be doing
is taking a couple pieces
of straw out of the
haystack we're looking in.
Ah. Guess we'd better get to work then.
Okay.
Felicity couldn't find her,
but you think you can, huh?
I just... I don't want to give up.
Still trying to redeem her?
Trying to stop her
before it's too late.
You disobeyed a direct order.
I gave you that dagger.
The weapons test failed
because of your brother's involvement.
Any more mistakes, and the rest
of the Ninth Circle will mutiny.
- I am their Leader.
- Then lead.
Where is your focus
at this critical time?
The family you swore to give up
to be part of the Ninth Circle.
Your absence has been noted.
Thanks to my time with Oliver,
I found something even better.
The Archer Program,
cutting-edge surveillance technology.
We can't stake our future on technology
we haven't even seen.
I need you to trust my vision,
okay, trust that you
have taught me well,
but if you question my authority again,
I'll kill you.
The "Queen's Gambit" sent
a mayday transmission late last night
and has not been heard from since.
Casualties of the
"Queen's Gambit" include
Starling City billionaire Robert Queen
and his son Oliver.
While rescue teams
continue to comb the seas
in search of passengers...
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
Greg, move your head.