This season on Arrow...
The only way I know how to fight
the darkness is to be darkness.
And I don't wanna be
that type of person anymore.
I'm running for mayor.
And I promise you that I will never
stop fighting to save this city.
So, you're all fretting
about this city dying.
I'm here on behalf of an organization
that wants you to let it die.
I'm Damien Darhk.
The type of magic he's using,
I've seen it take good people
and turn them dark.
If I don't make it off this island,
you will go to Russia and find my parents.
If Darhk wins,
Laurel died for nothing.
If you can channel light and hope,
you will be able to repel Darhk's magic.
- Do you remember what I promised you?
- A new beginning.
Darhk plans to burn the world
in a nuclear fire.
I'm assuming you know what Rubicon is.
And I'm assuming
it's under Mr. Darhk's control.
Every NATO ally, Rubicon has control
over all their nuclear systems.
You mean HIVE does.
If even one of those nukes hits...
He'll be unstoppable.
- I think it worked.
- It worked.
Rubicon's offline.
"DARHK". Do you need a moment?
No? Good.
'Cause I need you to do me a favor.
Go to hell.
Why bother?
I'm going to bring it to us.
- Get the hell out of here.
- Mom. Stop.
- Oh, my God!
- Mom, get back!
This is your mother? Oh, goodie.
On!
Persuading you to help me is
gonna be easier than I thought.
Helping you do what?
Your underground city's
already been destroyed.
I'm still going forward.
So, what, you kill my mother
if I don't help you destroy the world?
Newsflash, my mother lives in the world.
Dying instantaneously in nuclear fire,
rather painless.
And then there's having your life-force
slowly sucked out like this...
9h, my God! Mom!
What's it gonna be, Ms. Smoak?
Look, I know you don't live here anymore,
but those were nice windows.
So unoriginal.
I'm now powered by the deaths
of tens of thousands of souls.
There is nothing you can do to stop me.
Or should I say, us.
Stop!
You let them go, or I kill your daughter.
You think I'm bluffing?
(%GRUNTS) %GROANS)
Let my daughter go.
It's okay, sweetheart.
Everything's gonna be all right.
You okay?
When did this become your life?
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, it's gone.
He took it. It's gone.
- What's gone?
- The laptop with the anti-Rubicon program.
If Darhk has that...
He can launch all of
the world's nuclear missiles.
Looks like internal bleeding.
And possible broken ribs.
Hemothorax.
We have to relieve the pressure. Thea.
Felicity, we need you at your station.
We have to stop Rubicon.
Is he gonna be okay?
Put the gun down, Reiter.
Ahh!
You think you can kill me, Ms. Venediktov?
I'm going to kill you!
You'll only kill yourself in the attempt.
Without these runes, the idol's power
would overwhelm my mind.
I don't care. It's worth it to stop you.
You see that, Reiter?
That plane filled with all of those people
you were keeping prisoner?
They're getting away. This is over.
It's not all of them, Mr. Queen.
The plane is too small, and it's not over.
All those deaths.
They give me power. And her...
Only madness.
How is he?
Well, he's stable. John said the next
30 minutes should tell us...
- Whether or not he'll make it.
- Yeah.
Hey, can I ask you something?
I know it might not be the best time.
Back at our place... My place, the...
The place, the loft...
Yeah?
Darhk's magic, it worked on you.
I thought...
You thought I found a way to stop it?
But that was before he grew so powerful.
It was the...
The hope you had in me
was able to counteract his magic.
And now my hope's not enough?
So, where are we?
Um, good news, bad news time.
Uh, good news is, is that Darhk
hasn't launched the nukes yet.
I think his hacker is still trying to
break our fail-safes.
Okay. And the bad news?
Well, the bad news is
that, with Rubicon offline,
- there is nothing for me to hack into.
- Right.
- But your laptop has to have a GPS...
- Yeah.
I'm sure that you've already
started to try and do that.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
I thought you had shut Rubicon down.
Yeah, Felicity is working on
locating the laptop.
- Where's Sara?
- She's fine.
She's in an A.R.G.U.S. bunker
in Coast City.
With Darhk's anti-nuke bunker destroyed,
why is he moving forward with Genesis?
Machin killed his wife.
Well, his daughter still lives
in this world. He must know that.
He knows. He just, he doesn't care.
He's lost all hope.
Yeah, just like all of us.
But I thought he was the cynic.
It's not like John doesn't
have a point, Thea.
We are not finished yet.
Kewvord being "yet."
I got a 20 on the laptop.
Downtown, abandoned office building.
Let's move.
Oven/vatch, there's no one here.
That's impossible.
You're right on top of the GPS signal.
She's right.
Oh, my God.
- Oven/vatch.
- I see it.
Just over 15,000 ballistic missiles,
and they all just launched.
How much time do we have?
Two hours. Maybe less.
Confirmed. 15,434 birds in the air.
We need to set Defense Condition One
and get the President down to the PEOC.
Felicity?
He's got me completely locked out.
Okay, how many missiles are there?
D.O.D.'s working on it,
but the targets are worldwide.
- You said that we have two hours.
- The world has two hours.
But I'm tracking a Minuteman ICBM
heading straight for Star City.
It just launched out of
Warren Air Force Base in Colorado.
Okay. Well, that's close.
Which means we only have 45 minutes.
- Taiana.
- I'm okay.
I think
I'm okay.
Taiana?
All right, where's the fire?
- What's this?
- The safest place within 100 miles
to survive a nuclear attack,
based on wind patterns and...
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. Slow down.
What are you talking about?
The world is gonna end in two hours.
I need you to take my mother there.
Can you do that?
Yeah, I will.
"SARA". Bye, Daddy. Bye, Mama.
- We'll see you soon, sweetie.
- I love you, baby girl.
A.R.G.U.S. has a chopper
waiting to take us to Coast City.
So, at least we'll all be together,
if we can't stop the...
The end of the world.
In these situations,
you're usually the one offering hope.
I'm fresh out, Lyla.
Because of what happened with Andy?
It was self-defense, John.
It was a clean kill.
Lyla, are you having A.R.G.U.S.
move on City Hall?
John told me
the source of Darhk's power is there,
that he might be looking to harness
the deaths from the nuclear attacks.
No, he's already done that
with the first attack.
He will decimate your team.
You should pull them back.
And what if his hacker's
down there with him?
Cooper Seldon is not gonna be anywhere
that we think to look.
He'll be in a secure location.
If your team goes down there,
they will all die.
It's not your call, Oliver, it's mine.
I don't like this place. It's scary.
It's just a little bit longer, sweetheart.
I miss Mommy.
I do, too.
But we're gonna see her soon.
Assault Team
Sledgehammer has engaged target.
Switching you to their feed now.
Turn it off.
With those missiles hitting, he's gonna
become even stronger, isn't he?
He already is with the souls of
all of those A.R.G.U.S. agents
that he just killed.
Wait. I'm in.
I'm through Cooper's firewalls.
- Well, shut it down.
- That's what I'm trying to...
Look at me, listen to me.
Don't let it control your mind.
You are a murderer!
You killed my brother! You are darkness!
Yes, lam...
But you don't have to be.
I am sorry.
It's okay.
I can feel it burning my mind.
Taiana, we will find a way
to work around this.
There is only one way.
You have to kill me, Oliver.
With Mayor Adams
missing and presumed dead,
Deputy Mayor Remz called for calm
in the wake of unconfirmed reports
that a nuclear attack on our city
is imminent.
Newly installed
Police Captain Frank Pike...
As if things couldn't get any worse.
Is everyone all right?
I think "all right" is a relative term.
How much time do we have?
I think, 27 minutes.
It's kind of hard to tell now.
I wonder what Laurel
would have thought of all this.
Well, she probably would've said
something about finding a solution,
no matter what.
Yeah. She was always stubborn like that.
Too bad she would've been wrong this time.
Hey, come on,
we can't just lose all hope here.
You have.
I can see it in your eyes.
I just can't believe that I thought
that I'd be the one to unite this city
while Damien Darhk was trying to kill it.
That was arrogant.
The same arrogance that made me feel like
I could be the Green Arrow
without descending into darkness.
Bottom line, it was foolish.
- You don't believe that.
- I didn't believe that,
until Laurel died.
I thought you weren't blaming yourself
for her death anymore.
We made a decision to come back here.
I tried to do things differently.
And, for a time, I did.
And now I am left here to wonder,
if I hadn't,
would Laurel still be alive?
Curtis. You shouldn't be up.
Tell me about it.
But someone's gotta provide
a little optimism.
It doesn't seem like anyone around here
is in the head-space to do it.
You know we've lost the city.
No, I know that you're running out of time
to get it back.
Look, living in Star City requires
a special kind of tenacity.
A sane person wouldn't live here.
It's a fact that Paul
likes to remind me of weekly.
We were this close
to leaving Star City last October.
After three terrorist attacks,
we were done.
But then,
the night before
we were gonna start packin',
the Green Arrow popped up on our TV,
and he reminded me
that this city is worth saving.
That my home...
That my home was worth fighting for.
That guy gave me inspiration.
He gave me hope.
And if he could give me hope then,
why can't he give it to others now?
Hey! Calm down! Stop!
Please! I know
what you're feeling right now.
I'm feeling it, too.
The sense of helplessness.
Of hopelessness.
I don't know how we even begin to process
what might happen to us right now.
But there are a few things that I do know.
I know that this city has been through
tough times before,
and we have pulled through.
We survived the Undertaking,
we survived the siege,
we survived the outbreak,
and somehow, someway we will survive this.
A friend of mine told me
that living in Star City
takes a special kind of tenacity.
But we do live here
because this is our home.
This is our home.
It is our friends. Our family. Our lives.
And we will not, we will not
throw those precious gifts away
by descending into chaos.
We will look to each other for hope.
We will cling to each other for strength.
If we do that, no matter what happens,
then we can all stand here united.
Oh, my God, it's here.
"BURNS". That's terrifying.
And also kind of great.
I think you got hit on the head
harder than you realize.
No. No, he's right.
I can't hack this system.
But if the nuke gets close enough,
which it is...
We could use the line-of-sight attack
on the missile itself and disarm it.
I'm still not getting a signal.
Are you sure
you're pointing that thing at the nuke?
It's pretty hard to miss, Felicity.
Okay, okay, okay! I'm just going...
Uh. Whatever you changed,
don't change it again, it's working.
I got the signal.
I didn't change anything.
Nukes are designed to detonate
100 feet above their actual target.
I'm uploading a GPS spoof
so it thinks it's already detonated.
Great! But, um,
it is still headed straight for us.
Just keep pointing
the IR receiver at the thingy.
I have perfect confidence
in your abilities.
- Thank you.
- But, just in case,
working with you and the rest of the team
has been the highlight of
my professional career and my entire life,
and I can't think of any better way
for it to end...
Curtis. As sweet as this is,
the talking is really not helping.
Oh, my God. it worked.
Oh, my God, it worked!
Whatever you guys just did was incredible.
We only took down one nuke.
We still have 15,433 to go, give or take.
The code to the line-of-sight hack.
Can you distro it to everybody?
I'm on it.
All right, that's one, one nuke in 15,000.
The chances of us getting 'em all is...
One in 375 million.
Well, we need to find Darhk's hacker
and shut down Rubicon at the source.
When we disarmed the nuke,
we gained access to its on board computer
and cloned its hard drive remotely.
Then, we ran a backtrace to determine
the source of the initial launch signal.
He's holed up in a warehouse on
the corner of Cheswold and Crombie.
Let's get after him.
That was quite a speech, Oliver.
Made me long for a voting booth.
You and Thea need to
back up Curtis and Felicity
while they deal with Seldon.
- Okay, what are you gonna do?
- I'm going to City Hall.
Oliver, you yourself said going
after Darhk is a suicide mission.
Well, John, I'm not gonna die tonight.
Well, let me go with you, back you up.
If things go bad,
I need you to back the city up.
Oliver, things aren't gonna go bad.
Your speech
inspired all of us, too.
Let's move.
TAIANAI Do it, Oliver.
Please do it quickly.
Taiana, I'm not gonna kill you.
- Then I will kill you!
- Hey!
Don't you understand?
Please!
Before I kill
whoever is left on this island.
Before I become worse than Reiter, please.
Please don't ask me to do this.
If you ever cared for me,
then you would do this.
Okay.
Don't forget your promise.
I won't.
Taiana, I'm sorry.
You killed her!
I thought you were staying behind.
Yeah. It doesn't mean
I shouldn't be prepared.
I'm not gonna ask if you're all right.
I think I know the answer.
Lyla, this isn't the right time
for this conversation.
When the Ghosts attacked, you froze.
I've never seen you do that before.
- Lyla, I can't talk about this.
- Was it Andy?
He was a Ghost.
- Lyla...
- If the world's going to end,
then let's at least go out
being honest with each other.
Yes. it was Andy.
But not like I said.
And not like you think.
Earlier you said it was a good kill.
It wasn't, Lyla.
I said it was self-defense. it wasn't.
You must think I'm a monster.
Fog of war, Johnnie.
You did what you had to do.
It's that simple.
Lyla, there's nothing simple about this.
Darhk!
What does a guy have to do
to end the world in peace?
"NORA". Why is he here, Daddy?
Oh, he came here to die, sweetheart.
Clearly.
Fifteen minutes till the end of the world,
and you want to spend them with me.
I am touched.
Thea, look out ahead of you.
Thanks, unless you were aiming at me.
At this point, I honestly can't tell.
"DARHK". Even if you stop me,
even if you could,
those missiles are finding their targets.
This is a mercy killing
on a global scale.
I'm sparing my daughter the pain
of growing up without her mother.
Or Mr. Lance living without Laurel.
And don't get me started on your pain.
Let him go!
Get out.
For real?
- Get out of here.
- Get out!
Get out of our town!
We don't want you here!
Get out of this town!
- Get out!
- "Get out."
Get out of here!
This heartwarming display
would mean a whole lot more
had I not just seen you all tearing
yourselves and your city apart.
That is why I did this.
Humanity is feckless.
And I wanted to cleanse it
of a millennia worth
of rot it has been infected by,
and I will do it.
No, you won't.
Okay,
just for fun, how are you gonna stop me?
Because it won't be just me
who's gonna stop you.
It's not so easy without the magic, is it?
Oh, I don't need magic.
I'm a former member
of the League of Assassins.
Or have you forgotten that?
Remind me.
- Oh, my God.
- Cooper?
Hey, Felicity. How you doing?
Who shot you?
Guess.
He's moving the bullet
closer and closer to my spine.
Said it'd hurt so bad
I'd do anything to make him stop.
Like blow up the planet.
Sorry, I'm a selfish bastard.
But she knew that already.
I need a moment alone with him.
- Felicity, I don't think right...
- Now!
I'm sorry, Felicity.
I know I should be strong enough
to pull myself away from this keyboard,
but I think we both know that I'm not.
You are.
He's powerful. He's so powerful.
And if I stop Rubicon, he'll know.
And he'll kill me
in the most painful way possible.
You're better than this, Cooper.
You're stronger than this.
You can still do the right thing.
You can still be the man that I loved.
I haven't been that guy in a long time.
Remember what we wanted to do
seven years ago
in that cockroach-infested dorm room?
Save the world.
Now's your chance.
Mr. Seldon, you weak-willed dust mite.
I'm sorry, Coop.
Ah! You brought friends.
That's okay. So did I.
- What the hell happened?
- Darhk!
We have three minutes
to take down 15,000 nukes.
Why isn't this a simple matter
of flicking off a switch?
Rubicon has safeguards for their
safeguards. I can't disarm a warhead.
Then don't.
I don't think you understand
how this works.
It's not the warheads, it's the missiles.
If we invert their horizons...
They'll explode in space.
Now you know how it feels.
- Wait, I thought you and Donna...
- Don't worry. She's safe.
But I had to come back
to stand with my city.
'Cause this Oliver Queen guy
gives a hell of a speech.
You two were supposed to stay as backup.
I already lost one brother.
You two put down the Ghosts.
You keep people safe.
- What about Darhk?
- Darhk's mine.
What are you gonna do now, Oliver?
Stop posturing.
We both know you can't do it.
You spared the life of the man
who killed your own mother.
You killed a friend of mine.
You've killed tens of thousands
of innocent people.
With Slade Wilson, I had a choice.
This time, I don't.
It's gonna take forever
to clean this place up.
Well, I wish you guys
the best of luck with that.
You going home to my mama?
Uh, yeah, and to pack.
We're leaving town for a while.
Wait, why?
LAB reached out.
My suspension is no longer a suspension.
But, uh, it's funny, you know,
'cause being a cop is all I ever wanted,
but when I got that call,
I didn't feel a thing.
All I could think about was Laurel.
You know?
But you got herjustice, Oliver,
and you got me some closure.
And I'm never gonna forget that.
Well, it's gonna make me feel
like I'm piling on...
What do you mean?
Well, l...
I jumped straight out of the Lazarus Pit
right into this and to...
To Speedy.
But, um, I've just been wondering
if this is even who I really am?
And then I threatened
to kill a little girl, and I, uh...
I realized I'm my father's daughter.
So, I...
I thought about Laurel and...
And what she'd say to me if she were here.
I think she'd tell me to get out.
Before I lost too much of myself.
- I'm sorry, Ollie.
- Hey. Come here.
You don't have
to apologize to me, ever.
Well, it looks like
it's just the three of us.
Team Arrow. The original gangsters.
Up top?
You Okay?
Not really.
I told Lyla the truth about Andy.
What did she say?
She's a soldier, she understood.
But I don't,
and I don't think I ever will.
What are you gonna do?
Take some time away from this team,
away from the city.
Figure out where I went off track
and how to get back on.
John, I have never done this without you.
You're the one who keeps me in line.
Oliver, I don't know
if you've watching lately,
but it's been the other way around, man.
She begged me to do it.
So, I know that this is not gonna
make a ton of sense,
but all of this has to do with that.
It is darkness!
And Taiana had...
She was succumbing to that darkness.
They destroyed the plane.
That was Reiter.
There's another way off the island.
And here I thought
you'd never use the comm gear I gave you
to radio for a trip home.
Well, I lost it for a while.
- And the job wasn't done.
- And now it is.
I sent you here
to break up Reiter's operation
and free his prisoners. You did both.
- You saved a lot of lives.
- And took some, too.
Do you remember what I told you?
That the only way out is through?
Well, I'm not out, Amanda.
I'm still filled with darkness.
This was never about
expunging your darkness, Mr. Queen.
That darkness
will always be a part of you.
- Then what was the point?
- To show you
that sometimes killing
is the only path to justice.
Director Waller,
what do you wanna do with the artifact?
Have it transported to The Slab.
Yes, ma'am.
That's it?
Just gonna bag and tag everything
and pretend like nothing ever happened?
You've seen what that idol can do.
How large the world truly is.
Speaking of...
What am I gonna do with this?
Our business here is concluded, Mr. Queen.
Unless it's not.
As I said, justice requires killing.
A man of your talents could be useful
in hot spots across the globe.
Or you could just go back
to playing vigilante.
Neither.
I have a promise to keep.
I know you wouldn't approve of what I did.
I mean, I know that it's not
what you would have wanted.
Me killing Darhk.
But you were always
better than me, Laurel.
That is what I loved most about you.
You okay?
No.
It's Thea and John. It's...
Them leaving has to be a blow.
And they're leaving
because of their own personal darkness.
I just can't help but think that
maybe they were infected by mine.
Maybe.
Like you said,
maybe you can't become a hero
without succumbing to the darkness,
even a little bit.
But you were able to defeat Darhk
by giving the city its hope back.
You're saying it's not black and white?
I'm saying that there is a man
who killed Darhk in cold blood.
And that same man stood on top of a car
and gave the city its hope back.
What you're feeling isn't darkness,
it's a schism.
You're at war with two sides of yourself.
Hello?
Mr. Queen, this is Thomas Kemp.
I chair the City Council.
Yes, of course, Councilman.
What can I help you with?
That impromptu speech you gave
during the city's latest crisis
got a lot of people's attention.
And there's something
I'd like to talk to you about.
It's only an interim appointment.
A proper election will be held in August.
But given that you got 48% of the vote
before as a write-in candidate,
- well, I think that's just a formality.
- I appreciate the optimism.
Are you sure about this?
You look, well, conflicted.
Well, someone very close to me
recently told me that I am.
- But I am ready for this.
- Good.
Shall we?
Put your left hand on the Bible.
Raise your right hand and recite the oath.
I, Oliver Queen, do solemnly swear
to support the charter
and laws of Star City,
and to faithfully and impartially perform
and discharge the duties
of the office of mayor,
according to the law
and to the very best of my ability.
Congratulations.
I didn't know you'd be here.
You thought I was leaving, too?
Not a chance.
English - SDH