My name is Oliver Queen.
After five years
on a hellish island,
I have come home
with only one goal--
to save my city.
But to do so, I can't be
the killer I once was.
To honor my friend's memory,
I must be someone else.
I must be something else.
Previously on "Arrow"...
When I was in Afghanistan,
my unit was tasked
with protecting Gholem Qadir.
How is it you think
your brother ended up dead?
You shot at a client,
you missed.
I don't miss.
You murdered Shado.
Yes, I pulled the trigger,
but you, you aimed the gun.
What are you
doing here?
Five years ago,
I made you a promise.
You cannot die until you have known
complete despair.
And you will.
I promise.
Sara.
Sara?
Murderer.
Mne nuzhno
vstretit'sya svami.
Aleksi. Kak Ty, moy drug?
What can I
do for you?
There's no gulags here
in Starling City.
Anatoly talks too much.
Eto verno.
I need you
to find a man for me.
His name is Slade Wilson.
He's rich, Australian,
and he's missing an eye.
I need to know
where he sleeps.
First, I need your assistance
with my business.
There is a man who owes me
a substantial amount of money.
I am not here to trade.
You know how our
brotherhood works.
I do a favor for you
and you do one for me.
Put it on my tab, Aleksi.
I don't have time
for these games.
Make time.
My services are
of no use to you
unless yours
are use to me.
I know exactly
how this brotherhood works,
and right now,
it works for me.
U nas yest' ponimaniye?
♪ Arrow 2x16 ♪
Suicide Squad
Original Air Date on March 19, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
I woke up
and you were gone.
Yeah. I wasn't tired.
You should be.
When's the last time
you actually slept?
Right before I found out
that Slade Wilson
is still alive.
Do you want to talk?
I mean...
I know neither one of us are very
good about sharing our feelings,
but...I mean, I get it.
Slade, and...
And it's a lot,
and, you know,
it's ok if you're scared.
I am, too.
I'm not scared.
Slade came back
to Starling City
with an agenda.
First, he tries to mass produce
the Mirakuru.
Then he shows up...
at my mother's
house.
So he wants
a fight, fine.
I'll give him a fight.
And this time,
when I kill him,
I will make damn sure
that he stays dead.
I just need
to find him.
Ooh, coffee?
Hot cocoa.
Hmm.
What, no
marshmallows?
I'm out.
What are you doing here, Dig?
Keeping an eye
on things.
Ok. And by things,
you mean my neck.
The one you think Slade Wilson's
going to break in my sleep.
Yeah, something
like that.
Look, I have extra
security details
on Oliver's mother.
Roy's keeping
an eye on Thea,
Sara's staying
close to Laurel.
So I get you sitting
outside of my house
like that lacrosse player
my freshman year of college.
What?
You know, I had a life
before you and Oliver, yeah?
Right. I just want to make sure
you're ok, Felicity.
And I love you for it.
But if Slade wants
to kill me, he can.
There's nothing you can do
to stop him.
So go home. Ok?
Hey.
Nice jammies.
What took you so long?
What is all this?
A little early for champagne,
don't you think?
Not for me.
I just got back
from a mission in Pyongyang.
Well, damn.
That was you?
I'm sorry.
That's classified information.
But I missed my ex-husband,
new boyfriend.
And A.R.G.U.S. has
a standing reservation
at this hotel
for very important assets.
Mm-hmm.
Can you stay?
Um, well, Oliver
and I kind of have
a...situation.
Everything all right?
Yeah, yeah,
we're handling it.
So you can stay.
Mmm.
Hey.
Is there a problem,
Michaels?
We need to rest.
These women are tired.
We're all tired.
It's a long hike back to camp.
Keep going.
Shall I go explain to the ladies
why they want to get back before dark?
They're not allowed
to talk to you.
Why, 'cause I'm an American?
Because you're a man.
Five minutes.
Girls in the military.
Can't keep up,
don't join up, right?
Whoa, whoa, hey,
what's going on here?
What's going on?
You recognize that face?
You should. He's on the U.S. military's
high value target list.
Gholem Qadir.
Opium drug lord
and arms dealer.
Wanted alive.
What were you saying
about women in the military?
Why didn't we do fun stuff like this
when we were married?
And take time out from our busy schedule
of driving each other crazy?
Amanda.
Don't look so worried,
agent Michaels.
We've all
availed ourselves
of the Ostrander suite at some point
in our careers.
Something's come up,
I'll need you to come with me.
Duty calls.
Yeah, guess so.
Actually...
I meant both of you.
What are we
looking at here?
Hydroxy-cyclosarin.
It's a nerve agent.
The apocalypse in the form
of a chemical weapon.
And it's about to hit
the open market.
A.R.G.U.S. agents
uncovered
a manufacturing plant
in Kahndaq.
All samples were accounted for,
except for one.
Two weeks later,
this footage
was captured in a remote village
in southern Qurac.
One milliliter has a kill radius
of ten miles.
It only took half that amount
to produce these results.
Our sources have traced the sample
through Europe to an estate in Markovia.
So send in the army.
We send in the army, we risk
an international spectacle
our government
can't afford.
This has to be off-book.
If you need me to draw up
the smash and grab, done.
But John isn't a field agent.
He's not qualified.
Judging from how he and Oliver Queen
spend their free time,
I'd say
his credits transfer.
Hey, look, I don't want this thing out
in the open any more than you do,
but I'm not sending my boss in
on another one of your business trips.
I have no intention
of involving the Arrow.
I need you.
What for?
Gholem Qadir.
We caught him.
D.O.D. turned Qadir
loose a few years ago.
Who thought
that was a good idea?
It's a complicated
world, Johnny.
The nerve agent's
not the only WMD
Qadir's tried getting
his scummy fingers on.
Last month, he tried
to buy Malcolm Merlyn's
prototype
earthquake machine.
Thank you for stopping that,
by the way.
Fortunately, he doesn't know about
your involvement in that.
He remembers you as the man
who tried to save his life.
The nerve agent's
under lock and key
at his estate in Markovia.
He's scheduled to host
a fundraiser there shortly.
The two of us haven't
exactly kept in touch.
We've got that covered,
but our window is rapidly closing.
Ok.
So I infiltrate the fundraiser,
come out with the package.
Sounds simple enough.
Nothing in this
business is simple.
You know that,
Mr. Diggle.
Follow me.
I don't need you
to get the nerve agent out.
I need you to get your team in.
My team?
They're designated
"Task Force X."
Give me a break.
This ain't no task force.
Let's call it like it is--
Welcome
to the Suicide Squad.
"It's not only prisoners
who grow course and hardened
"from corporal punishment,
but those as well
who perpetrate the act or who are
present to witness it."
Oh, please stop
giving him books.
So this
is your unit, huh, Waller?
What, OJ and Charles Manson
weren't available?
This is a dangerous operation.
And these men
have useful skills.
Should the mission be
compromised...
You'll just
write them off.
The Suicide Squad.
Yeah, like he would
ever make the sacrifice.
Lyla, I can't believe
you're on board with this.
Those men are murderers!
And what's
the number of bodies
between Oliver Queen
and Sara Lance?
What they do, what I do,
is completely different.
Not really, John.
Don't you see that?
What I see is you letting
the man who killed my brother
roam completely free.
It's not freedom.
It's work.
It's wrong.
Do you cuties
need some counseling?
I'm a trained therapist.
"Do you have previous
experience in retail?"
Does shopping count?
Sara?
I've seen that look before.
On my face in the mirror when
Ollie goes into distant mode.
Hang in there.
He'll open up to you
when he's ready.
Yeah.
You'd think so.
I started by tracing the donation
Mr. Wilson made to Moira's campaign.
All of the money was routed through
a series of offshore accounts.
None of which link back
to a local address,
so I looked into
credit card transactions
and car rental agreements.
What?
He's got to get around somehow,
just not by rental car.
Slade's former ASIS.
He knows how
to be a ghost.
Robbery in progress.
5th and Giffen.
We're still in the crime fighting
business, right?
Harbinger has eyes
on the target.
Light the torches.
Deadshot is a go.
Shrapnel's a go.
Tiger's a go.
This is Mockingbird.
Harbinger,
you have a green light.
Freelancer, you're a go.
Deadshot?
Got Freelancer
in my sights.
What's stopping you
from shooting me right now?
Honor.
Can I trouble you
for a cigarette, my friend?
I don't smoke,
and I'm not your friend.
You know who I am?
What it is I do?
You're dealing drugs,
weapons and children.
Play both sides
of the conflict.
Make money while
your country burns.
I do not have
to be the only one.
Let me go,
I make you rich.
You trying to bribe
my men, Qadir?
If we wanted to make a buck,
this is the last place we'd be, moron.
Get down!
Sorry, I wasn't
looking where I was--
Gholem Qadir.
I do know what is less likely--
that John Diggle
would be clumsy,
or I would find him here,
of all places.
You like art, my friend?
I know a good
investment when I see one.
Out of the military, then?
And in a more
lucrative line of work.
What kind of work is that?
The kind you don't
get to ask about.
It's good seeing
you, Gholem.
Everything all right
here, Mr. Diggle?
Yes, he's with me.
So the soldier now has
his own security.
In my line of work, when I do a
good job, I tend to make enemies.
A good man turns bad.
Bad man turns good.
You changed my life, you know.
Trust me, that was
never my intention.
The intelligence
I provided your government,
it saved many lives.
Now as a free man,
I give back when I can.
Of course.
Get down!
It's all clear.
Deja vu, my friend.
Mr. Qadir!
I am fine.
I do not believe
I was the target.
Like I said, when I do my job right,
I tend to make enemies.
We should go.
Good job, Deadshot.
You're a go for exfil.
Already in motion.
Except, uh,
I'm not the only one.
Shrapnel just bolted.
Find him.
Picking him up,
headed east.
Shrapnel.
Stand down and return
to the rally point.
I won't be conscripted
into your moral army.
Stand down!
Final warning.
Especially not while in a country
without an extradition treaty.
Very well.
What the hell's
going on?
Shrapnel just fouled
out of the game.
What the hell
was that?
We're going to want
popcorn for this.
You said it yourself,
John. They're murderers.
Criminals.
They need an incentive
to follow orders.
So you rigged
their heads with explosives?
There's no danger as long
as they play by the rules.
Scheffer didn't.
It's like I don't
even know you anymore, Lyla.
Where are we at with Qadir?
Save a man's life once,
get a silver star.
Save it twice?
Rent a tux.
I'll await further
instructions, sir.
Vashi lyudi
nezhnyye.
So is my patience.
This is Starling City
bank account number
for your Mr. Wilson.
To be clear...
Take this envelope
and we are through.
I do not care
who your friends are.
U nas yest' ponimaniye?
Relax, it's just me.
What's going on, Ollie?
Hey! Talk to me.
Now is not the time.
Then when is the time?
The Bratva, Ollie?
You're losing your grip.
Ok? Slade's getting
in your head.
I need this to stop.
And for it to stop,
I need to find him.
Yeah, and until then,
how long do you think
you can keep
this up for?
You're not eating,
you're barely sleeping.
And when you do,
you have nightmares.
They're about her,
aren't they?
Hey, look at me.
You did what
you had to do, ok?
Ivo was going to shoot Shado,
or me, or both of us.
It was an
impossible choice.
I made it, anyway.
But if you had
chosen differently,
then it would be me
haunting you at night.
It still could be, Sara.
That's why we have to stop.
What are you saying?
He's going to use you
to hurt me.
Or he's going to hurt you...
Stay away from me.
Seeing as how you haven't
brought it up,
I'm guessing you
haven't got very far
with that H.I.V.E.
lead I gave you.
Just make this quick.
You're usually
so chatty, John.
These problems with your girl,
they got you down, huh?
And what about
your girl?
The one you have
a shrine to in that cell of yours?
Zoe.
Does your daughter
know what you do for a living?
She is why I do what I do.
Really?
Yeah.
How many enemies can
a little girl have?
I wouldn't know.
Everything I make
beyond expenses
goes in a blind trust.
A girl needs
her father.
Nah, not this father.
Best thing I can do
for her life...
Not be in it.
Is it ready?
We're almost there.
You know, we went through all
that trouble to get Johnny here
invited to this little shindig.
Seems like an awful waste
not to use that invitation.
You're using it.
Once you have hands
on the nerve agent,
pocket it,
walk right on out.
Copy that.
Thank you very much.
Your generosity is much appreciated.
That's not exactly
army camo.
But have you given any thought to
what would happen
if Qadir recognizes
you anyway?
Mr. Diggle.
Who is this vision?
His new bodyguard.
Mmm. You will have to refer me
to your security company.
I'm glad you could
come tonight.
It's the least I could do after
you saved my life.
Again.
I will see you
inside, my friend.
Gholem.
It would seem
I didn't have time
to get credentials
for my associate.
Come. This way.
Gosh, I'm so sorry.
I forgot those
were in there.
Enjoy the benefit,
Mr. Diggle.
Deadshot and his gear
are in position.
Tiger's got
the overwatch.
Harbinger to all,
fire in the hole.
Shooter at my ten!
I got you covered!
Bounding!
All clear!
It's just a kid.
And don't you look
lovely tonight?
Oh, I think you owe
your bodyguard a dance.
I insist.
Deadshot en route
to package.
The fate of the world
resting in the hands
of Floyd Lawton.
It helps to focus
on the mission.
Is that what
you tell yourself?
I tell myself to see
the world how it is,
not how I want to see it.
We both operate
in the grey.
The only difference
is, is I'm willing to admit it.
That's not the only
difference between us.
That's true.
I don't judge other people for it.
Lyla, I'm the same man
I've always been.
And I'm who
You're rigid, John.
You're blind to any viewpoint
that isn't yours.
These past few months
have been amazing.
But we've done more
playing than talking.
Because when we talk,
we tend to get divorced.
Don't worry.
It's virgin.
Ugh. Which is why
it tastes terrible.
True.
So.
It looks like things with you
and Sara are going well.
I'm not sure
you're the best person
to talk to with all this.
And why is that?
Is it because of the whole cheating,
shipwreck, drowning,
not drowning, you're
back, she's back thing?
Sorry.
It's brutal AA
honesty talking.
I think I preferred it when
we were all lying to each other.
No, you just
thought you did.
I know you better
than almost anyone, Ollie.
I know that you think that you don't
deserve to be happy,
but you're wrong.
You may think
that keeping her at arm's length,
you're protecting
her, but you're not.
You're only
protecting yourself.
It's more complicated than that.
It always is.
I got the address for that account
number you gave me.
I'll call Roy and Sara.
No. I'm not giving Slade
any more targets.
You can't go out
there by yourself, it's suicide.
This started
with the two of us.
That's how it ends.
Deadshot's on target.
Bingo.
I don't know what to do.
He's too far ahead.
I mean, he spent years
planning this,
and he knows
everything about me.
I can't, I...
I don't know
how to stop him.
Well, you start
by letting people help you.
But he's going
to come after you.
You're alive...
Because Shado isn't.
And when he does,
do you think it'll make a difference
whether or not
we're together?
Let him come.
I'm not the girl he
knew on the island.
I'm not that easy
to kill.
Together?
Together.
I'm in.
I'll have the nerve agent
in my pocket in 30 seconds.
Harbinger...
We've got what I would describe
as a little bit of a situation here.
Explain.
Well, I got eyes
on the nerve agent,
and I'm not going to be
able to move it,
much less pocket it.
Stand by, Deadshot.
I need to talk to Waller.
Go for Mockingbird.
We have a situation.
The package is much bigger
than our pre-op briefing
indicated.
Stand by.
Deadshot's on target; I need
to see what he does.
Activate the camera
in his eye piece.
Multi spectrum
from Lawton's rig
coming in...now.
It's a match.
Tiger, move
for extraction.
Deadshot,
remain in position.
Harbinger and Freelancer, evac
and head to the rally point.
Deadshot still isn't
topside with the package.
I only needed eyes on.
Fall back to the rally point.
Wait...You knew
that the nerve agent
was too large
to be extracted?
Fall back
to the rally point.
Nine is inbound
and hot.
Mockingbird out.
What the hell
are nines?
MQ-9s. Predators.
Waller's called in
a drone strike.
Everyone here is dead
inside of ten minutes.
The nines carry
the Hellfire missile.
Just one of them
can level this whole building.
And your boss doesn't care
who's here when it does.
Lyla, we have to get
these people out of here.
Maybe there's a house alarm
we can trigger.
John, we have
to move now.
I have a better idea.
Excuse me.
Can I have your
attention, please?
In honor of our host.
Gholem Qadir excels at everything
he puts his mind to,
be it business,
philanthropy...
or terrorism.
Yeah, I guess you could say Gholem
is somewhat of a renaissance man.
He dabbles in a little
bit of everything.
Arms trading--
did I mention the sex trafficking?
Or the deadly nerve
agent that he's holding
just 30 feet beneath
this very dance floor.
These are lies!
This man is a mercenary!
Lawton!
He's not answering.
I have to go help him.
I can't believe
I just said that.
You! You were
in Afghanistan five years ago.
You and that Judas have been deceiving
me from the start.
Good timing.
Got tired of waiting
for my invitation.
Tsk, tsk.
Disobeying orders, John.
Behind you.
That's two
you owe me, junior.
We have to go.
Waller told me
to stay here.
There's an incoming
drone strike.
How contemporary.
Get your team clear.
You are on my team.
And it's time for you to go.
Yeah, that's right.
It is time.
And this
is my way to go.
Suicide Squad,
remember?
I'm expendable,
John.
Even got the damn bomb
in my head to prove it.
This way, at least I get to go out
doing something honorable.
You don't get to die
that easy, Lawton.
Really?
Why don't you give
me even just
one good reason
why not, huh?
Zoe.
What about the nerve gas?
Believe me--
Waller's already
got that covered.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
The drone shifted course.
It's following us.
Do you find that funny?
The wall.
What a woman.
How do you think she knew where
to send the drone, huh?
And I mean,
the precise coordinates.
The implants.
Bomb and GPS.
Pretty clever,
right? The drone
ain't targeting
Gholem's house.
It's targeting me.
Whoa, hang on, do I
get a say in this?
Turn around.
What are you doing?
Look, I think
I'd rather get blown up!
Hold still.
This is going to hurt.
The Markovian government
is threatening retaliation
following an unprovoked
drone attack over a no-fly zone.
Just the attention we wanted
to avoid. Well done.
I'm not the one
who sent that drone.
It was cloaked.
An explosion atop
a chemical weapons cache
is easy to explain.
Instead, there were
witnesses and we had
to send in a SEAL team
to clean out the estate.
I guess you'll think
twice before dragging me
in to do your dirty
work, Waller.
Somehow I don't think
it will be an issue.
Good day, Mr. Diggle.
Kind of uncanny.
How Diggle knew exactly
where Lawton's implant was.
Still,
it exposed an obvious
design flaw.
We'll be putting in the implants
in their spinal vertebrae now.
Have Lawton and the others
prepped for surgery.
Waller said in a few years,
you might even get a pardon.
Don't worry, John.
We both know I'm not
going to be around that long.
You still employed?
People with my security clearance
aren't that easy
to get rid of.
Right.
What about us, Johnny?
Last night, the man who
killed my brother
showed more character than
the woman charged
with protecting
the world.
Good and bad is not
so clear to me.
One thing
I do know for sure,
black and white...
Is that I can't ever
lose you again.
Finally.
Something we agree on.
Well, there goes another
terrorist-turned-ally.
By the way, I put you in
for a commendation
for saving Qadir's ass.
You owe me a beer.
Congratulations.
Yeah, well, kill a kid,
get a medal, right?
When someone's shooting
a Kalishnikov at you,
he's not a kid.
I see things
differently.
It's a complicated world,
Johnny.
Is it ok if I call you Johnny?
I don't think I caught your first
name, Michaels.
Lyla.
It's really good
to meet you, Lyla.
In international news,
a United Nations inspections team
was called to a chemical weapons
manufacturing facility
hidden beneath
the Markovian estate
of humanitarian
Gholem Qadir.
Closer to home, mayoral
candidate Moira Queen
stumped
for an initiative
to revive inner city
after school swim programs.
Oh, I remember how
much my children
enjoyed swimming
when they were young.
I couldn't get them out
of the pool.
We need--
I thought
you hated swimming.
I detest swimming.
So does Thea.
My mother sometimes--ahem--
enjoys a casual relationship
with the truth.
Anyway.
Thank you
for being there for me.
You mean for not
letting you push me away?
I'm going to stop doing that.
Yeah? Good.
You'll be wasting
your time, anyways.
It looks like
you took my advice.
Thank you.
Helping me
with Sara,
I know that that...
can't be easy.
Helping two people
I care about?
There's nothing easier.
I came by to take Sara
to dinner.
Would you care to join?
I'd love to, but I need
to go see an old friend.
Ok.
Hello, Oliver.
Hello, Amanda.
Still mad at me?
Lucky for you,
you've been pushed
down that list.
Really? Who do you want
to kill more than me?
Slade Wilson is alive.
You killed him.
It's not possible.
Everything is possible
where Slade is concerned.
And I need
your help to find him.
I might have something.
What?
There's a new player
we've been tracking--
mercenary.
He's left a trail of bodies
from Macau
to Istanbul to Lisbon.
A trail that leads
right here to Starling.
We've been
calling him Deathstroke.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man