(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
Now I know that it's not my fault.
It's my responsibility.
Responsibility to do what?
To end it.
I'm gonna kill him.
(CHATTERING)
Where is Damien Darhk?
(GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
(DOCTORS CHATTERING)
Where's Darhk? Where is Darhk?
(GRUNTS)
Any luck?
Just more Ghosts
who would rather die than talk.
Nobody, nobody is gonna give up Darhk.
John, we gotta talk to Andy again.
I don't think Andy
is in a very cooperative place.
Darhk has gone to ground.
Right now, unless things change,
Andy is our best chance of catching him.
Felicity's going in for another surgery.
If we hurry, we might be able to see her
before she goes into prep.
No, no. Darhk's in the wind.
The longer he's there,
the harder he's gonna be to catch.
I'm going to stay here,
find something useful from the tip line.
It's what Felicity would want me to do.
Can't lie your way out of this one, pal.
Reiter might've bought your BS before,
but now, between these maps
and ol' Miss Ukraine over here
still being alive,
it's game over.
(PANTING AND GRUNTING)
He needs to rest for a moment.
Don't care. Keep moving.
And when he passes out,
do you plan on carrying him?
Fine. Quick.
(WINCES)
Hey. You need to make a run for it.
I'll distract Conklin.
By doing what? Bleeding on him?
Well, isn't this touching.
All right, come on, let's go.
Don't get too attached to him, sweetheart.
His prospects for a long life
don't look too good.
Hey.
How you feeling?
I have never been more ready
to have a bunch of guys
poking around inside me.
Doctors. (GROANS)
Doing doctor things.
They, um... (SIGHS)
They think the last surgery
will fix the nerve damage, so...
Mmm-hmm.
These are from Oliver.
Well, that's really nice
of him to stop by.
Yeah, it's okay.
I know he's doing everything he can
to track down the, uh, flowers.
-(CHUCKLES)
-Which is much more important.
Plus I got all the support
I need right here.
-NURSE: Felicity?
-Mmm?
I'm here to prep you for surgery.
-I'm gonna be fine.
-(SIGHS)
Yeah.
ANDY: Aren't you tired of this?
Same dead-end conversation.
I'm not talking. I'm not helping.
So how about you stop wasting
both our time?
The Green Arrow told me to have
a conversation with you about Darhk.
(GRUNTING)
(PANTING)
I'm surprised, John.
I didn't think you had it in you.
-I didn't.
-What changed?
Her name is Felicity.
(GROANS)
(BEEPING)
Yeah, listen. I know, I know, all right?
(STUTTERS) Just do...
Listen, I gotta call you back,
call you back.
How's she doing?
She's in surgery again.
(SIGHS) Then what are you doing here?
Looking for Damien Darhk.
There's a card
that we haven't turned over yet.
And we haven't turned it over
because when we do,
he will know that you are working with us.
You want to know where
I've been meeting with Darhk.
Yeah.
You won't be able to go home.
Luckily, we have space in the bunker.
There are living quarters.
-What about Laurel?
-She can take care of herself.
(CHUCKLES) Yeah, I've seen that.
All right. Office building,
832 6th Street, 30th floor.
But with Felicity in the hospital,
me and Laurel watching our backs,
your team gets mighty small.
None of it matters
once Darhk is off the board.
So you're back to dropping bodies?
Just this one.
(BEEPING)
Lonnie Machin.
The symbol that I found at Darhk's lair
is consistent with the symbol
that Machin left near the bodies
of two paramedics a few months ago.
Okay. But why is Machin
still targeting Ghosts?
When he kidnapped Danforth's daughter,
Darhk was the one
who gave up his location.
This is payback.
Darhk cleared out before Machin got there.
Darhk is one step ahead of Machin,
but Machin is one step ahead of us.
Yeah. And I'll keep chipping away
at my stone wall.
Wait. How did you suddenly
find Darhk's base of operations?
Finally had an interrogation
that went somewhere.
I'm gonna bring up
everything I can on Machin.
I'll ask my dad if SCPD found
any leads at the crime scene.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Mr. Conklin,
I trust there is a reason for this?
It's like I've been telling you.
Queen's a liar.
He told me he'd killed this one.
It turns out he's just been
keeping her stowed away.
What you and your men do
to satisfy your needs outside of camp
is no interest of mine.
Yeah, I thought you might say that.
That's why I made sure
to bring these with me.
I found these two coming up
from a shipwrecked freighter.
Must've found them inside.
If he's been on this island
the whole time like he says,
how'd he know where they were?
I got those for you.
(SIGHS) For whatever it is
you're doing here.
And yet you waited all this time.
With someone you claimed to kill.
I've defended you, Mr. Queen.
At the cost of my credibility with my men.
No more.
You can kill him now if you like.
No. I got something else in mind.
TAIANA: (SOBS) You can't do this!
You can't do this!
(SCREAMS)
(SCREAMING CONTINUES)
How's Felicity?
She's in surgery. It's a long procedure.
I'm gonna go to the hospital in a bit,
but I needed to come here
and get something first.
What?
I'd hate to see the other guy.
The other guy's Andy.
(SIGHS) We had to
get information on Darhk.
I thought that was Oliver's vendetta.
Oliver does have a vendetta.
I'm just trying to keep my friends safe.
You feel betrayed.
I do feel betrayed, Lyla.
He was my brother. My family.
-I think that's your problem.
-(SIGHS)
Ever since you heard about
what Andy did back in Afghanistan,
Andy stopped being Andy to you.
He became a traitor. The enemy.
Yeah. And then he doubled down
and became one of Darhk's Ghosts.
And you've been treating him
like a Ghost ever since.
How's that working out for you?
What's your point, Lyla?
If you're not getting through
to Andy as a Ghost,
maybe you should try
reaching him as your brother.
No. No.
I can't do that.
Sure you can.
I've seen the love you have
for your brother, Johnnie.
The strength of it. It's iron.
Before you give up on Andy,
just make sure he sees what I do.
A man who'd go to the ends of the Earth
for the ones he loves.
And if it helps,
consider it an order, soldier.
-Are you doing okay?
-(SIGHS)
You mean now that Machin's back?
I'm sure he's not after you.
Why would he be?
I only burned his face off
in a fiery fit of Lazarus rage.
Thea.
Look, you know those crime scene photos
that Ollie showed us,
with paramedics
and the writing symbols in blood?
Whoever is out there now
is a complete monster.
A monster that we're going to catch.
I don't know anymore.
And lately,
I can't seem to win for losing.
What do you mean?
When we got John's brother outta HIVE,
I ran into Damien Darhk.
And he tried to use his
creepy magic mojo on me,
but after that, my bloodlust was better.
It was almost completely gone.
I don't know. I really just thought
I was starting to get on
the other side of this.
Hey. Sounds like you already are.
Except now, Machin's out there
and he has a bloodlust of his own.
And it's completely my fault.
No, Thea. You can't think that way.
It's a little too late for that.
(QUENTIN AND DONNA WHISPERING)
Dad.
-(GASPS)
-(CLEARS THROAT)
What are you...
I had no idea that Felicity's friend
was Quentin's daughter.
(CHUCKLES)
It's such a small world. (CHUCKLES)
Microscopic.
Um, Thea, I've been trying to get, um,
Donna to eat something at the cafeteria.
But maybe you'd have better luck.
Uh...
Yeah. Yeah. Sure, sure. Come on.
-Yeah, okay.
-All right, sweetheart. All right.
I was gonna say something, but then,
with everything with Felicity and...
Dad, Dad. It's fine.
Really?
I want you to be happy.
(CHUCKLES)
Okay, so, Oliver found
Darhk's base of operations,
and I'm guessing that's thanks to you?
Well, there's no use being on the inside
if I can't provide inside intel, right?
Darhk's going to realize
that you're helping the Green Arrow.
I think that ship's
probably already sailed.
Don't worry. I can look after myself.
I'm more worried about you.
I thought we already worked past this.
There's no working past a father
caring about his daughter.
(CELL PHONE CHIMING)
Mmm. Text from your new girlfriend?
Easy. Get outta here.
Crime lab. I had the handful of CSI's
I got working on the HIVE crime scene.
I doubt they'll find anything.
The Ghosts have their DNA scrambled.
Which makes this particularly strange.
The blood Machin used for his graffiti
didn't come from the Ghosts.
How do you know?
The CSU got a match.
Two of them, actually.
Michael and Crystal Olguin.
Machin's foster parents.
Kidnapped three days ago.
Machin's settling old scores.
He planted their blood at HIVE,
so clearly Darhk is next on his list.
But Machin's gotta be laying low
somewhere, right?
You think his former home?
Well, I mean, it's vacant now.
Yeah. Maybe they have
a security system we can hack into.
I got it.
(KEYS CLACKING)
(BEEPS)
-Or not.
-Here, let me try.
Okay, wait, who's that?
It's him.
Suit up.
Whoa. That's not at all creepy.
-(DEVICE BEEPS)
-The front's clear.
Same. Except for trash, flies
and some bad graffiti.
Wait. I think we might have something.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER ON TELEVISION)
I was expecting Mr. Darhk's friends,
but you guys are a pleasant surprise.
Especially you, dear.
GREEN ARROW: Hey! Don't move.
Funny. I was gonna tell you
the same thing.
It's on a motion sensor.
Good.
Oh, did you think I was going to kill you?
(PANTING)
Why would I do such a thing?
You're the one who saved me from myself.
Come on, then. Hit me with your best shot.
(SCREECHING)
Oh, that's pretty.
You take voice lessons?
No, Speedy! Stay away from her!
Oh, I would never hurt her.
You, on the other hand...
(GRUNTS)
Speedy, you okay?
Now what?
GREEN ARROW: We find out what he knows.
Aren't we risking some crazy
Bond villain stupidity here?
I mean, this guy needs to be put away.
Far, far away.
Machin found Darhk's base of operations
without any help.
I need to know how,
I need to know where Darhk is right now,
and the cops can have him
when I'm done with him.
Machin is about
10 different kinds of deranged.
Why would you believe
anything he tells you?
'Cause I don't have any other choice.
Now, I am done talking about this.
Give me the room.
Thought we'd moved past this.
Sorry to disappoint. Wake up.
Where's Damien Darhk?
(CHUCKLES)
He went home. (CLEARS THROAT)
I was planning, you know, a party for him
when you interrupted my...
(GROANS)
Tell me where he is.
Or what?
Look at me.
What can you possibly do
that I haven't already enjoyed?
-Hey!
-Get out.
No. Look, there's something
you need to hear.
What?
Felicity is out of surgery.
Donna just texted me.
Didn't say what was wrong,
but I don't think it's good.
You need to go there.
Hmm. Back for more?
Does beating up on your little brother
give you a little thrill?
I'm not proud of what I did, Andy.
In fact, I'm ashamed of it.
You, John? Mr. High and Mighty?
Do you remember the last time
you beat on me until your knuckles bled?
Yeah, I do. Ten years ago.
When I found out you were dealing.
Yeah. You convinced me to enlist.
To go the straight and narrow
like my big bro.
And I tried. Honestly, I tried, man.
Enough to fool you.
That's just not who I was.
'Cause it's always been about you, John.
Because I'm such an embarrassment,
my bad deeds look bad on you.
No, Andy, no. That's not true.
I did what I did because I love you, man.
No, I do, Andy. Then, now.
Andy, you're still my little brother,
who I stayed up late playing cards with.
You going through this, that's on me.
But do you really think Damien Darhk
gives a damn about you?
He believes that the world needs a reset.
And honestly, John, after
what we witnessed in Afghanistan,
can you tell me otherwise?
Okay. All right, so you and Darhk
are burning the village
in order to save it.
I get that.
Malcolm Merlyn was talking the same tune.
But, Andy, Darhk hurt a friend of mine.
A close friend.
A woman better than you
and me put together.
It doesn't matter if Darhk
wants to save the world.
He crossed a line!
So I'm asking you, Andy,
begging you, man,
brother to brother,
where can I find Darhk?
He, uh,
likes to talk about Stonehaven.
About how the leaves look there in autumn.
Thanks, Andy.
Don't thank me.
You're ashamed?
Now we're even.
Speedy. (CHUCKLES)
That is what the blonde
with the black leather
and the big mouth called you, right?
Hard to look at me, I know.
Your doing. I owe you a thank you.
Baptism by fire. It's transcendent.
You burnt away my weakness,
like a phoenix rising from the ashes.
If you thought burning your face off
was fun, keep talking.
Put an arrow through your eye.
So why hold back?
I know you want to kill me.
Because I can control myself.
No, you can't.
You think you can, you say you can,
but I can see it in your eyes.
The hunger to deliver death.
Ah, delicious.
(GASPS)
-(POLICE SIRENS WAILING)
-Told you.
Bye, dear.
REPORTER: Coming to you live now
from downtown Star City, where the SCPD
has apprehended a fugitive wanted
for murder and kidnapping charges...
-Hi, Donna.
-Where have you been?
I... I should have been here.
Thea said that Felicity is out of surgery.
Yeah, yeah. She's, uh, well,
she's got a new diagnosis.
-What?
-(SIGHS)
They can't...
They can't fix her.
What do you mean, they can't fix her?
The damage to her spinal cord, it's...
Oliver, it's permanent.
She's never gonna walk again.
No. No. No. We'll talk to another doctor.
No, no, no. See, you don't...
This...
This is the other doctor, okay?
This is the doctor that came
all the way from Central City.
This is...This is the doctor.
-Where is she? I need to see her.
-(SOBBING)
She's in recovery.
REPORTER:
In a special report, Lonnie Machin
has just been apprehended
by the Star City Police Department.
D.A. Laurel Lance was onsite
to oversee his containment.
(SCREAMS)
(SOBS)
Stop!
What?
Stop.
You said he was mine
to do whatever I want with.
That was before I saw the signs.
On his abdomen.
Mmm.
Well, you can look at it
all you want after he's dead.
But I have need of him.
-(GRUNTS)
-No! No! No! Everyone stay back!
Well, I count five guns.
You got one.
What you gonna do? You can't run.
I'm not running.
(BOW TWANGS)
Ah, long time no see.
We didn't finish our conversation.
And, what, I'm supposed to be so grateful,
I'm just gonna give up what I know
about where Darhk is?
Not likely.
You make sure he's dead.
LAUREL: Have you
completely lost your mind?
I don't have time for a debate.
Good, because there's nothing to debate.
What you did is...
What I did?
I did what I had to do,
after you made it necessary.
Machin was only arrested by the SCPD
because you gave him up.
You were holding a man prisoner
as some sort of personal vendetta.
Do you have any idea
how many people Damien Darhk
and HIVE have killed
over the past six months?
This might be a vendetta,
but it's not personal.
I don't know what's worse.
You actually believe that
or you expect me to.
I put a tracker on Machin.
He will lead us to Darhk,
and then we will take both of them down.
And when your master plan doesn't work,
you just sent a murdering psychotic
back on the streets.
Like you did with Sara?
That's not fair.
What's going on?
Oliver broke Machin out of custody.
-What?
-I'm using Machin to get to Darhk.
Period.
If either of you has a problem with it,
you know where the door is.
Laurel, give us a second.
I don't have time for a lecture, John.
There's no lecture here, Oliver.
But you should know that
Andy gave me a lead on Darhk.
-And I've been working on it.
-Good. What have you found?
Unfortunately, it was a dead end.
-But you should also...
-But nothing. But nothing.
Oliver, I know you're hurting, man.
But you should know
that whatever your play is,
-I got your back.
-But?
But you've come so far, Oliver.
You've recovered a humanity
that you'd lost when I first met you.
I know you want payback
for what Darhk did to Felicity,
and you should.
But don't lose what made her
fall in love with you in the first place.
Oh. Hey.
What are you doing here?
I came by to tell you, um...
I can't do this.
(SIGHS)
My "anger management issues,"
they are less manageable than I thought.
Look, I called what's going on with you
"anger management" because
I don't know what else to call it.
All I know is that there's something
that's really bothering you.
And if I know what it is,
maybe I can help.
You can't.
This... This can't really be helped.
I don't believe that.
I don't believe that for a second.
Thea, you've lived through more tragedies
than a person has any right to,
but instead of crumbling, here you are,
every single day,
working to rebuild your home.
-You've got steel inside of you, Thea.
-Huh.
That's what drew me to you
in the first place.
Thank you. I'm... (SIGHS)
Just not ready.
Well, hey, when you are, I'll be here.
Hmm.
Okay.
(SIGHS)
Oh, boy. What did I miss?
Well, it's a long story.
Short version, Machin's gotten loose,
he's after Darhk, and we're tracking him.
Wait. What? What happens
if he gets out and starts hurting people?
-That's exactly my point.
-It doesn't matter.
You sound like him.
No, I mean the tracker's gone dark.
I mean, we just lost his signal.
He must have found the tracker.
We lost him.
(SCOFFS)
Okay, so what do we do now?
I don't know.
That was the whole plan.
Oliver, go see Felicity.
Not right now, John. Not when we're...
DIGGLE: Then when? Then when, Oliver?
She needs you.
(SIGHS) And right now,
I think you need her too.
We will find Machin.
Look, they are right, okay?
We are going to figure this out.
But right now,
you need to go and be with her.
Hey, stranger.
Sorry I didn't come by sooner. It's...
It's unforgivable.
Only if you were in Bali or something.
Were you in Bali?
No, I was, uh...
Beating the streets?
Probably a lot of people
looking for Darhk.
I didn't want to come see you
until Darhk was off the board.
Any luck?
We're working some leads.
Tell me you haven't gone off the rails.
Well...
It's just...
I can't help but think that
the reason that Darhk is winning
is because I haven't been willing
to go far enough.
And that if I was, if I had,
maybe you wouldn't be in here right now.
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
And I don't know what the point of
what I'm doing as Green Arrow is
if I can't protect the people
that are closest to me.
What was the point of doing it
if you lose yourself in the process?
Yeah.
There's something else
we need to talk about.
The doctors,
they say that I'm... Uh...
I know.
My point being is
we didn't really exchange any vows,
so the whole "for better, for worse"
thing doesn't really apply here.
What are you talking about?
That maybe the real reason
you haven't been here is because...
Felicity.
The nurse, she took this
off of you in the ER.
How dare she.
(SNIFFLING)
For better or for worse.
Yeah.
He's bluffing.
Reiter, I can help you find what you need,
on one condition.
What do you want?
I want Taiana's safety.
So long as she is alive, I'll cooperate.
He's manipulating you.
What do you think he's been doing
this whole time?
You give him what he wants,
he's gonna turn on you.
Do we have a deal or not?
Take them both to prison.
(COUGHS)
You can't trust him!
Remember, Conklin,
there's no part of my plan
which requires you to be alive.
When we go out every night,
suiting up, risking our lives,
fighting assassins and meta-humans,
and all the worst kinds of people,
she's stronger than all of us.
You won't get an argument from me.
Oliver, we might have something.
John's brother said Darhk could be found
at a place called "Stonehaven."
Dig said that lead was a dead end.
That was before we cross-referenced
the tracker's location
and came back with a residential address.
Machin's going after Darhk where he lives.
We're gonna roll out.
I thought you might want to tag along.
Thank you.
Let's go.
All righty. I just spoke with Mr. Darhk.
He's on his way.
Traffic's a bitch. (CHUCKLES)
Could take a while.
I really don't see why we can't have
some fun in the meanwhile.
(SHUDDERING)
Just so you know, this isn't your fault.
You see, Daddy done me wrong.
There needs to be recompense for that.
He's not responsible for what
happened to my face.
Not directly. But incidentally.
And isn't that what anarchy is?
The intersection of seemingly
unconnected events?
(MUFFLED SOBS)
Who owns the house?
It's owned by a dummy corporation.
Couldn't work through
all the layers without Felicity.
(SIGHS) And we're sure
that Machin's inside?
Oh, yeah.
We're sure.
Hey.
Get on the ground!
First, you catch me,
then you break me out,
now you wanna catch me again.
Make up your mind!
Stick him.
(GRUNTING)
(CLANGING)
Get them out of here!
You're gonna be okay. Just come with us.
(GRUNTING)
-Split up.
-Okay.
(YELLS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(GROANING AND PANTING)
There it is.
Shut up.
A little piece of me inside of you
just begging to come out and play.
(YELLS)
(SCREAMS)
Where's my family?
I saved them.
I want to be clear about something.
I have shown you repeatedly
that you cannot beat me.
You saved my family.
So I'll give you a few weeks
to spend with yours.
Enjoy your time.
What's left of it.
You missed.
On purpose.
I'm disappointed in you.
(GRUNTS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(PANTING)
OLIVER: Are Darhk's wife
and daughter in police custody?
DIGGLE: They told police
they weren't his wife and daughter.
Had fake ID and everything.
Speedy,
you okay?
Yeah.
I'm just sorry I let Machin get away.
I'm just glad that you're all right.
I'm gonna go see Felicity.
-Chinese used this island as a prison.
-(COUGHS)
Bet you didn't know that.
They said being sentenced here
was worse than any hell.
Guess I'll just have to see if I can give
those Chinese a run for their money.
Reiter's gonna get through
with you eventually.
Then you and me'll have
a little uninterrupted time.
(GROANS)
You've lost a lot of blood.
You shouldn't let these wounds
sit open like that.
Thank you.
You saved my life again.
Nearly at the expense of your own.
No.
You didn't deserve to die.
You're a good man.
My brother would have liked you.
(SIGHS)
I already told you
everything I know, John.
(SIGHS) I'm not here
to ask any questions, Andy.
Thank you for coming.
Yeah. I'm glad I did.
And glad you called.
(CHUCKLES)
You know, this is
a little bit confusing. Uh...
Yeah. (CHUCKLES)
First we're on, then we're off,
now we're...
-Drinking wine.
-Drinking wine. (CHUCKLES)
Look, um,
something happened earlier today,
and I guess I just wanted to say
that you were right.
I am stronger than I think I am.
Well, uh, here's to being stronger, huh?
Mmm.
How you feeling?
How long you been sitting there?
Not long enough.
Sorry I went away.
I think you apologized already.
Nowhere near done apologizing.
(CHUCKLES)
You know, I think I wanna go to Bali.
Yeah.
Wanna come with me?
I'd go anywhere with you.
Yeah.
Just one question.
Mmm-hmm?
What's Damien Darhk doing in Bali?
I only ask 'cause if he's still here,
we have some work to do.
How did you get to be so strong?
(CHUCKLES)
I take my lead from you.
Shh.
I've bought out the Fairmont
for the month.
You'll be safe there
until we find a new home.
And what about the man that attacked us?
Lonnie Machin?
He'll never hurt you again.
Those vigilantes saved us.
(SCOFFS) My dearest Ruvé, do I detect
a note of criticism in your voice?
Yes, but not the one you think.
You should have killed
the Green Arrow tonight.
As you said, he saved your life.
It would be bad form to take him out now.
Genesis is almost ready.
We're much too close to play games.
Do you remember what I promised you?
A new beginning.
And you will have it.
Once we've brought this world to its end.
(CHUCKLES)
Are you okay?
Are you?
(SIGHS)
No.
You know what you have to do, right?
You have to kill the son of a bitch.
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)