Previously,
on "Arrow"...
If I only knew how
you were spending your nights.
Why should I trust you?!
Oliver.
I thought it was past time we talked.
About what?
You being
a serial killer?
Let's start with Laurel,
since you're still in love with her.
So are you.
Lord knows that I am guilty
of a lot of things
between us, but not you
and her. She chose you.
My name is Moira Dearden Queen.
I'm the CEO
of Queen Consolidated.
I have been complicit
in an undertaking
with one horrible purpose--
to destroy the Glades
and everyone in it.
But you need to know that
the architect of this nightmare
is Malcolm Merlyn.
You can't
beat me, Oliver,
'cause you don't
know in your heart
what you're
fighting for.
Is Laurel safe?
Yeah, you saved her.
No. Tommy...
It should
have been me.
Felicity,
if you're so scared,
why did you insist
on sitting up front?
This is the only seat
with a seatbelt.
Which will come in handy
when we hit the water
at 180 miles an hour.
Which will not happen.
I think that means
we're here.
Lian Yu.
But...You said the parachutes
were just in case!
Yeah, just in case
we made it here.
Come on.
No!
All right,
Felicity, on 3!
I can't, I'm scared! I can't--
1!
Thanks for waiting
until we touched down.
My pleasure.
Let's move.
What is it?
Thought I heard something.
Dig!
Don't move.
It's a landmine.
I'm going to try to disarm it.
You can't!
Diggle! Walk away.
Felicity, don't move.
God, you're--
you're really sweaty.
You're a hard man to find.
You shouldn't have
come here.
Would have emailed,
but this isn't exactly a WiFi hotspot.
Is this where you lived when
you were here?
I mean, the first time
you were here.
For some of it.
Could you at least pretend
like you're glad to see us?
Dig and I spent weeks
tracking you down.
We've traveled
halfway across the world.
And this morning
we flew in a plane so old,
I'm pretty sure I was safer once
I jumped out of it.
You could...at least
offer us a water.
Or...
A coconut.
Fresh out of coconuts.
I am happy to see you.
But I know why you're here.
I'm not coming back
to Starling City.
I can't. My mission,
my father's list,
it was a fool's crusade.
And I failed.
Malcolm Merlyn
destroyed the Glades.
Tommy died.
And the Hood couldn't stop it.
So don't ask me
to put it on again.
Ever.
This isn't about you
being the Vigilante.
This is about you
being Oliver Queen.
Your mother's
in prison, Oliver.
Her trial's
coming up.
Thea's out
on her own.
Your family
needs you.
So does the family business.
All the bad press
after the Undertaking
left Queen Consolidated
ripe for a hostile takeover
by Stellmoor International.
They've gutted every company
they've taken over.
Once they gobble up
Queen Consolidated,
30,000 employees are going
to be out of a job.
Including one very blond
I.T. expert.
Listen, I get why you
had to leave, Oliver,
probably better
than anybody else.
I've been there.
And after what happened,
nobody can blame you for leaving.
But it's time
to come home.
You're not the first man
to learn the hard way--
women are a distraction.
You've come very far
in a few months.
Don't beat yourself up.
Ah, apparently that's his job.
And I love my job.
Not that I wouldn't trade it
for a way off this island.
While you two were playing
with each other, I was hunting.
Well, there's nothing more attractive
than a woman who can hunt.
When I was marooned here,
my first meal was a pheasant.
Your father cooked it for me.
He was an awful cook.
Yeah.
But a great father.
I'm looking at the proof.
Let's eat.
What's that?
That's Fyers'
proximity detector.
We salvaged it from the wreckage
of the soldier's camp.
Picks up anything moving
outside our safe zone.
It's been five months
since we stopped Fyers.
He and all of his men
were dead.
So maybe it's an animal.
There's an imaging
interface.
Those are not animals.
And we're not alone
on this island.
♪ Arrow 2x01 ♪
City of Heroes
Original Air Date on October 9, 2013
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Who's blood?
An alderman from the Glades
trying to save the city.
Fill your shoes.
Here's everything
on Stellmoor International.
The vice president
of acquisitions
is a woman named Isabel Rochev.
She looks angry
in every photo.
So where to?
Office?
Home. I want
to check in on Thea.
Uh, she's not
at your house, Oliver.
Where is she?
I only have a second.
That's ok, my boss has been
all over my ass today.
You should hear what
she sounds like when--
Ow!
You have got to be kidding me!
Come on! I don't
want to fight.
Clearly you do,
since you keep on taking
every street corner drug dealer
that you can get your fists on.
It's not like that.
The Glades are worse than ever.
I know, but you already
saved a busload of people
and managed not to get
buried alive.
I mean, how much more
of a hero do you need to be?
It's like you have
a death wish.
And guess what--
it's going to come true.
Yeah, well, someone
has to do something.
And stand up for what's
right, like he did.
The Vigilante.
Who hasn't been seen
since the earthquake,
which means he did get
buried alive and isn't coming back.
I'm back.
Ollie!
Ah, you remember
my friend Roy.
Still here?
Always.
So how was Europe?
You never texted,
no postcards.
Almost like you're
on the island all over again.
Yeah, sorry,
I was kind of distracted.
With snow skiing,
waterskiing.
A lot of skiing.
I hear rumors that my club
is under new management.
Ah, actually,
it's my club now,
and you're not
getting it back.
You're not old enough to drink.
But I am old enough
to run a bar.
Have you made it
to Iron Heights?
To visit the woman
who dropped a city
on 500 innocent people?
No, thank you.
Thea...That's not what mom did.
Right.
She had no choice.
But guess what?
She did.
A choice not to be
a mass murderer.
And I have
a choice, too.
So I choose not
to be her daughter.
But I am so happy
you are home.
Honestly, I need to deal
with our liquor distributor
who shorted me
on yesterday's delivery,
and one of my bartenders
called in sick, so...
What?
Nothing. It's--
it's nice to see you
like this.
Like what?
Together.
The representative
from Central City
says construction on the
Star Labs particle accelerator
should be completed
by Christmas.
And in local news,
billionaire Oliver Queen
has returned once again
to Starling City.
With his mother's upcoming
trial and his father's
company in freefall,
analysts are asking what
the Queen family scion
has planned next.
Wasn't our country  founded
on a brand of vigilantism, Mr. Donner?
The revolutionaries
in the Boston Tea Party
were certainly choosing
justice over law.
I'd hardly compare our founding fathers
to the Hood, Mr. Mayor,
or these twisted copycats
who have risen in his wake.
Ms. Lance.
What do you think
about vigilantes?
I'd be foolish to disagree
with my new boss.
I knew I was smart
to hire you.
I'd heard you joined
the district attorney's office.
It was time for a change.
Still, I'm sorry that
you and your colleagues
at CNRI won't be opening
your doors again.
There were no doors left
to be reopened.
They're playing
my song.
Good evening.
It has been a very difficult
year for Starling City.
Our losses have been
incalculable,
our grief unimaginable.
But with the generous donations
you people are making tonight,
we will come back
from this tragedy.
You have failed
this city, Mr. Mayor!
The Glades descended
into hell on your watch!
You swore to protect
all the citizens of Starling,
not just the wealthy!
We're sorry
about this, folks.
We'll have this sorted
out in just a minute.
We are the Hoods.
And what was taken from us,
we will take back.
Laurel!
Dad, I'm fine.
You've got one
very brave daughter there, sir.
Yeah, one daughter's right,
and I can't stand to lose another.
Well, I still can't believe
this happened.
The hoods attacks
have strictly been limited
to people
in the financial sector
trying to redistribute
wealth in the Glades at gunpoint.
Yeah, well, clearly
that's not getting the result
they're looking for,
is it?
Did you get a good look
at any of them?
It was hard to focus
on anything other
than the gun barrel
pointed at my face.
No tattoos,
distinguishing marks?
What do you think
you're doing?
Interviewing the witness
is the job of the Detective.
Officer Lance.
This is my daughter.
She was nearly killed tonight.
Well, as a parent,
you're welcome to stay.
But as a beat cop,
you're more than free to go.
You know, that's one
of the downsides of being demoted--
I don't get to witness
his sunny disposition on a daily basis.
Dad, give me a sec.
Yeah.
I didn't know
you were back in town.
I just got back
a little while ago,
and I was going to call,
but then I...
Saw you on TV,
so I thought
that I would come
and make sure you were safe.
Just four hooded gunmen.
Nothing a few self-defense
classes couldn't handle.
Take a walk?
Yeah.
Sorry I left.
Believe me, I get it.
After the funeral,
I think we both needed time
to figure things out.
On our own.
I didn't get
very far on my own.
Did you?
Figure anything out?
That I made a mistake...
when I slept with you.
I know it wasn't
exactly cheating,
because Tommy
had broken up with me,
but he only did that
because he thought
that you and I...
should be together.
All I know is that I feel
like I betrayed him.
And now he's gone.
And there's nothing I can do
to make it right.
I know how that feels.
When I brought your sister on
"the Queen's Gambit,"
I betrayed you
and your father.
There's no forgiveness
for what I led
Sara into.
I would give
anything to...
To go back.
Yeah.
But we can't go back.
Diggle!
I don't like
being played.
I'm not sure
what you mean.
That's why you came
to the island
and brought me back
to Starling City--
these hood copycats.
Well, what if it was?
They're just doing
what you did last year,
terrorizing one-percenters
into cleaning up their act.
Except they don't have
your restraint, Oliver.
Or your honor.
I'm done being
the Vigilante.
Maybe this town
still needs a vigilante.
Now there's four of them.
How's that working?
Please take me home.
Got a big day at
the office tomorrow
trying to save
my family's company.
Absolutely.
Mr. Queen.
And in local news,
billionaire Oliver Queen
has returned once again
to Starling City.
Unbelievable.
We off the mayor
on live TV,
and what's the local
news keep showing?
Oliver Queen. Why?
Guess he's taking over
the family business.
We've been going
about this wrong.
What do you mean?
If we want real payback,
we got to take the fight
to the name that did this to us.
Queen?
Yeah.
He's some useless brat.
The applied sciences
division of Queen Consolidated
built the earthquake generator.
If we want real justice...
Then that family has
to pay for the suffering
it's caused us.
In full.
Hello, earth to Queen.
What, did you drop a Vertigo
when I wasn't looking?
I was
just distracted.
About what your brother said,
about your mom?
Eavesdrop much?
Ah, what I lack in height,
I make up
for in wicked good hearing.
Well,
don't keep me
in suspense, Harper.
What's your take on the matter?
Though, keep in mind,
I do control your paycheck
and your sex life.
Well,
both my parents weren't worth
a damn, either of them.
You never talk about them.
You got nothing nice
to say, right?
Still, I--
I'd be glad to see
them and talk to them if I could.
But...
Look, you already
lost your dad.
Your mom,
she's still here,
and I'm sure she'd
love to see you.
I'm sure she's dying to.
Just like a lot of mothers
in the Glades
who won't ever get to see
their kids again...
Because my mother
helped kill them.
I'm not going to that prison.
It's the only way
I know how to hurt her.
You might want to consider
how much it's hurting you.
They're in the conference
room. Just fyi,
no one is eating the bagels.
Isabel Rochev.
Oliver Queen.
Sorry I'm late.
For this meeting
or a career in business?
I didn't realize
hostile takeovers
were filled with
so much hostility.
Not at all. I'm actually
in quite a good mood.
Really?
So destroying companies
agrees with you?
Winning agrees with me.
You haven't won yet.
Since you majored
in dropping out of college,
let me put this in terms
that are easy for you to understand.
You control 45%
of Queen Consolidated stock.
I control 45%,
leaving 10% outstanding.
But, in two days the board
will release the final 10%.
And I'll buy it
before you do.
With what money?
I doubt your trust fund
is that large,
and no angel investor
will go near the company
that build the machine
that destroyed half the city.
Companies rise and fall,
Mr. Queen.
Your company has fallen.
Oliver Queen!
You failed this city.
Pull back!
Oliver, go!
Go, go, go, go!
Careful. Go, go.
Quick! They're getting away.
Go! Move!
Ms. Rochev,
I'm sorry about this.
'Cause they were
after you?
Because what happens
in this building is my responsibility.
Only for the next
48 hours.
I still can't get used to you
in that uniform, Detective Lance.
It's "Officer" now.
And I'm just glad
it still fits.
They hurt you?
I'm ok.
You, uh, heard anything from
our mutual friend lately?
Nope.
In fact...I keep
waiting for him to show up.
You could have
stopped those guys.
Not without
giving Isabel Rochev
and the hoods a pretty good
idea of what I'm capable of.
I think what
Felicity's wondering
is whether you avoided
taking those hoods on.
And, Oliver, she's not
the only one wondering.
I told you, I did not come back
to Starling City
to be the Vigilante.
But they came
after you, Oliver.
You could have
taken them out.
No, I couldn't,
Diggle.
Look, there's a part
of being the Hood
that neither
one of you are considering.
The body count.
And excuse me
for saying this,
but so what?
Since when do you care?
Since Tommy.
After he found out my secret,
you know what Tommy called me?
A murderer.
He was right.
My best friend
died thinking
that I was a murderer,
and anyone that I kill
dishonors his memory.
So don't.
It's not like you've killed
every guy you've faced.
I could have.
Because when I
put on the hood,
it's kill or be killed.
That is what
kept me alive.
That's why I should have
stayed on the island.
Is that where
you're going now?
The two of you won't help me
save my family's company,
I'm going to talk
to somebody who will.
Well, someone's
definitely out there.
They're moving closer.
Where do you think
you're going?
Flanking position.
They get the drop on you,
you'll want some back-up.
She's teaching you
Chinese. How sweet.
I'm sure she'd be happy
to teach you, too--
Shado!
Hey.
I'm sorry I didn't
make it here sooner.
Oh, no, no, no.
Please, Oliver.
There are going to
be enough apologies
with me apologizing
to you for the rest of my life.
You don't have to.
You saved hundreds of lives.
And killed
hundreds more.
Including Tommy.
That was Malcolm.
Your sister doesn't
see it that way.
And, you know,
my attorney is thrilled.
If my own daughter
can't forgive me,
she's not too
optimistic about
12 strangers
in a jury box.
All right,
enough of that.
How has it been going
at Queen Consolidated?
Yes, we do get the news
in here, Oliver.
Right.
You know,
if I'd known the key
to you taking
your rightful place
at the company
was its demise,
I would have declared
bankruptcy a year ago.
I don't know if I'll get
to run it for long.
Stellmoor.
Their VP
is coming after us hard.
Isabel Rochev.
Yes.
Do not trust that woman, Oliver.
She is dangerous.
Well, mom, everywhere
I look, there are no good options.
I don't know what to do.
You don't have
to do it yourself.
This is a family
business.
I love Thea.
I don't think that she wants
anything to do with it.
I wasn't talking
about Thea.
Table seven
needs bottle service,
and I need a round
of Martinis on the three top.
You go see
your mom yet?
I thought
about what you said.
And?
And...I'll go see her
when you stop going out at night
looking to clean up the streets.
What does one thing have
to do with the other?
I guess they're both things
that are never going to happen.
We're looking
for Oliver Queen!
He's back in town.
He owns this dump.
Where can we find him?
Ok, then plan "B,"
I'm going to start shooting people
until Mr. Queen...
Grows a pair.
Roy!
Aaah!
Aah!
Drop off, hero.
I'm just as happy to kill this
Queen as her brother. Let's go!
One of the guys
was missing a hand.
What's going on here?
Mostly, anyway.
He still had sutures.
Excuse me. It was
the hoods, again.
They came here looking for you,
they took Thea instead.
Where?
I'm sorry.
I really tried
to stop them, but I--
Queen.
Queen!
We'll get your sister back.
I was going to check
something downstairs.
I've made a few
improvements down here.
Just in case, you know...
You decided to come back.
We need to find these guys.
I've been trying,
ever since you got back.
I figured you'd come
around eventually.
I kept that.
I liked
watching you do that.
Thea's boyfriend said one of
them was missing part of his hand.
Maybe a veteran?
Check hospital records,
any males that have had
surgical amputations
on their extremities.
Cross-checking
by race and age.
Got one--Jeff Deveau.
Caucasian, late thirties.
What else can
you get on him?
Ex-Marine.
Would explain how he can
handle himself.
Did he lose
his hand overseas?
No. In the earthquake.
Says here he and his wife
were trying to make it
across the 52nd Street bridge
when it collapsed.
She didn't make it.
Phone records, please.
I want to know he's in contact with.
He's made a lot of calls
to a church in the Glades.
Something called
Standing Strong.
It's a support group for those
who lost loved ones in the quake.
Great place to meet
three other guys as angry as you,
looking
for a little payback.
Get me an address,
please.
You're going to need this.
I had it custom made.
How'd I do?
It's perfect.
You were right.
Once I signed on,
I stopped thinking
about all the bodies
you dropped.
Because I knew
that being the Hood
meant occasionally
being a killer.
Maybe there's
another way.
They have my sister.
What other way is there?
What are you doing?
We need to save her.
Listen, kid.
You are not the only one
who cares for her.
But there's a lot of them.
Wait for my signal.
Where
are the graves?
Where are the graves?
I don't know
what you're talking about.
Uhh! Uhh!
Tell me.
Oliver, no!
Oliver!
So...
What do you want
to do with her?
We could knock her out,
drop her off somewhere.
Come on. Why don't you
just buy her
a new pair of Pradas
while you're at it?
She's seen our faces.
Look, offing Oliver Queen's
one thing, but his sister?
She's not much older
than my sister was
when she was killed
in the earthquake.
Your sister wasn't killed,
she was murdered.
By her mother.
What we're doing here is justice,
which makes us the heroes.
She didn't kill anybody.
My mother didn't kill anyone.
Malcolm Merlyn
destroyed the Glades.
With mommy's help.
Merlyn killed my father.
She thought he'd kill
my brother, too.
She was afraid of him.
She must have been so afraid.
Just like my wife...
When our house
collapsed on top of her.
Ow!
Get away from her!
Let's go.
Please!
Move!
Go, move!
Please!
Let...
Her...
Go.
You want to save her?
There was no justice
for people
like the Queens
till you showed us
how to get it.
You showed us.
Go!
You shoot me, we both die.
You'll drop me
anyway.
I know you.
You're a killer.
Keep it under 40 next time.
Have a good evening.
Do you know who they are?
I think the hoods gives
me a pretty good idea.
Bring them in.
Where you been?
Typically when I bring in guys
that you've gone after,
they're a little more dead.
I'm trying another way.
I didn't mean
to disturb you.
I didn't know
that you were here.
I was just...
I come here a lot.
I can go.
No, it's...
You don't have to.
It's, uh...
Laurel, I understand.
After everything
that's happened, I...
Understand why
we can't be together.
But I still need you
in my life.
We've been through too much
for it to be any other way.
I feel like
I betrayed him, too.
Before the Hood,
we didn't have things
like earthquake machines
or copycat vigilantes--
Laurel.
Malcolm killed Tommy.
He was killed in the crossfire
between two archers.
And now that
Malcolm's dead,
there's only
one archer left.
And I'm going to help
my boss catch him.
That outfit,
with your coloring--
isn't that cruel and unusual
punishment or something?
I've done my best
to avoid mirrors in here.
So, I--
How have you been?
Don't worry about me.
I want to hear about you.
How are you doing?
Are you still
seeing, uh--
Roy was his name,
wasn't it?
Sweetheart,
I'm fine, really.
It's not that.
I...
I almost died last night.
What?
Thea, what happened?
It doesn't matter.
But when I thought
it was over,
I kept thinking that if...
If I died,
you would spend the rest
of your life thinking that...
I hated you.
And I want to hate you.
I really tried to.
But I can't.
I can't, Mom.
However long I am
in this place,
you have freed me.
If I hug you,
are they going to shoot us?
I'm willing
to risk it if you are.
Oh, shh, shh.
You can't win this.
I now own 50% of the stock.
By tomorrow, I'll have
the outstanding five percent
and I will control your company.
Any attempt to fight me
will lead to litigation
and leave you penniless.
And trust me, poverty
isn't as glamorous
as Charles Dickens
made it look.
What if I found someone
to invest new equity capital?
A White Night?
With all due respect,
your last name is now
associated with mass murder.
Even you don't have
that good a friend.
You're right.
I have family.
Mr. Steel. It was
my understanding
that you had
resigned as CEO.
I did. I'm now Chief
Financial Officer
of Starling National Bank.
And my institution
has committed
rescue financing
to Mr. Queen.
We bought up the remaining
shares of Queen Consolidated
when they were
released this morning.
Now I know I majored
in dropping out,
but I'm pretty sure that makes
us partners going forward.
So I guess...
We will be seeing
a lot of each other.
You aren't at all
what people say about you.
Most people fail
to see the real me.
Thank you, Walter.
Thank you,
for reaching out to me.
Whatever's happened
between your mother and me,
I'm gratified that you know
you can still count on me.
Your father would have
been very proud of you, Oliver.
Ms. Smoak.
Mr. Steel.
You did it.
Not bad for someone who got
a "D" in tenth grade Algebra.
If it's online,
I can find it.
Yeah.
Well, it was just
like a good friend once told me...
I had to find another way.
We're not alone.
The question is,
where did they come from?
Hey, what's up?
Just came back
from visiting my mom.
Really?
Good for you.
So what do you say?
You ready to start spending
your nights safe with me?
Absolutely.
Hey, I'm going to pick us up
some big belly burger right now.
I'll see you later.
Ok.
We just want
to be friendly.
What, we scare you
or something?
Yeah.
I think you do.
Me, though,
not so much.
Run.
Where the hell
did you come from?
Well, it looks like
Starling is back down
to only one man
in a hood.
And the three of us
are back in the archery business?
No.
I spent the past year
trying to avenge my father.
If we're going to do...this,
it has to be about
honoring Tommy.
I need to become the man
he hoped I could be.
You two have helped me
take the first step.
So what's step two?
I'm game for anything as long as
it doesn't involve skydiving.
And I'm pretty down
on landmines now, too.
The city still
needs saving.
But not by the Hood.
And not
by some vigilante
who's just crossing
names off a list.
It needs...
Something more.
It needs a hero, Oliver.
It's too bad the hoods kind of
ruined your nickname.
No, it's good. I never...
I don't want to be called
the Hood anymore.
Ok.
So what do you want
to be called?
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man