My name is Oliver Queen.
After five years in hell, I have come home
with only one goal:
To save my city.
Now others have joined my crusade.
To them, I'm Oliver Queen.
To the rest of Starling City,
lam someone else.
I am something else.
Previously on Arrow and Flash:
- Hello?
- It's Barry. Barry Allen.
I woke up. I could use some advice.
I don't think that bolt of lightning
struck you. I think it chose you.
You can inspire people.
In a way that I never could.
- What are you doing in Central City?
- Working a case.
Suspicious homicide in Starling
where the murder weapon...
...is a boomerang.
- Partners?
- Partners.
Barry has superpowers.
Oliver has a bow and arrow.
If I had a DNA sample I was unable
to breakdown, think you could...
...isolate genetic markers?
What's the sample from?
The Canary's murder.
In position?
In position.
Neighborhood's clear.
I probably should have
brought this up before...
...but if this doesn't belong to the killer
you chased to Central City and back...
...we're gonna have a lot of explaining.
It's his.
Why? The residue S.T.A.R. Labs found
on the boomerang says so?
Because the whole place is rigged.
I can see tripwire connected
to pressurized gas.
Front door will be the same.
Our new friend doesn't want
any surprise visitors.
Well, he's gonna get a surprise.
Looks like we interrupted his dinner.
We just missed him.
Drop your guns.
Sure thing. Right when you learn
how to count.
You're outnumbered, jerkwad.
You're not S.C.P.D.
Unless police uniforms have gotten
interesting, neither are you.
A.R.G.U.S.
Your flanking patterns haven't changed
in years.
Why is A.R.G.U.S. in on this?
The man who was killed by the boomerang,
he was an A.R.G.U.S. agent?
Which makes this an A.R.G.U.S. matter.
Bug out. Target's not here.
Let this go.
Are we gonna let this go?
What do you think?
What about this A.R.G.U.S. angle?
A.R.G.U.S. wiped all evidence
of their agent's death...
...after he was killed,
or they thought they did.
Our boomerang victim, Kai Wu.
Man's profile is so clean,
I should have known it was a cover.
Now that we know Wu was A.R.G.U.S.,
maybe Lyla can get us a lead.
If this is A.R.G.U.S.,
Lyla's gonna want it to stay that way.
Tell her to stop letting people get killed
in my city.
You really don't care about my marriage,
do you?
Well, I Would...
...if you and Lyla were still married.
Thank you for coming.
Like I had a choice.
- I see you made a new friend.
- This is Katsu Cheng.
Mr. Cheng fancies himself something
of a munitions specialist.
According to H.K.P.F., Cheng planted
an explosive device somewhere in Hong Kong.
I need you to talk to him,
find out the bomb's location.
I'm just gonna talk to him,
he's gonna give me information?
It won't be easy.
That's why I brought you your tools.
What tools?
We recovered these from the freighter
when we recovered you.
You're welcome.
You want to torture this guy
to find out where the bomb is?
I want you to find out where the bomb is.
How you do so is of little interest to me.
Almost done here, Gerry.
- You should have gone home hours ago.
- Who's Gerry?
- This place is bigger than my apartment.
- What are you guys doing here?
You asked us to analyze the DNA
of the arrow that killed Sara.
I was just gonna mail you the sample.
- We had some vacation days coming...
- We wanna see the Arrow Cave.
We don't call it that.
Even
But I want to see the toys.
I need to see the toys.
Do you guys have an Arrowmobile?
Don't touch that.
Or that.
It's a jettisoning arrow.
It uses compressed...
Compressed CO2 to jettison
high-tensile strength polymer cables.
Yup.
Since when did we start selling admission
to the Arrow Cave?
It's...
You see what you've done?
Incredible.
I have so many ideas for improvements.
And this.
Oh. Oh, man.
This is the bomb. And I mean, red is
so much cooler than green. Am I right?
I'm really starting to like this guy.
Hey, what's that for?
Distracting me from work.
So where's Mr. Diggle?
He's running down a lead.
- We have this handled, Johnnie.
- I told Oliver that already.
- Seriously, it's an internal A.R.G.U.S. matter.
- I told him that too.
Listen, sweetie.
A guy who kills with boomerangs?
That's outside you guys' wheelhouse...
...while exotic killers are more...
...our thing.
You only call me sweetie
when you want something.
Is it working?
Hang on a second.
Is there a problem?
Something strange with your ID.
I'm gonna have to detain you.
Hmm. If that's a problem,
I really don't care.
You know, you should be careful
how to treat people, my friend.
After all...
...what goes around comes around.
I appreciate the offer, Johnnie.
But really, we have it handled.
Is that your "we have it handled" alarm?
We have a breach.
Initiate lockdown protocols.
Diggle.
We have a situation here.
Our man's at A.R.G.U.S., Lyla's here.
And Oliver, this guy is the real deal.
Our target is storming A.R.G.U.S.
and Lyla is there.
Mm-hm. Badass.
- So cool.
- It'll be over by the time they get there.
Clear.
Eyes up.
Sweetie.
You only call me sweetie
when you want something.
Get down!
Uh... Chase, just because we kissed,
it doesn't mean anything, okay?
- Are you sure you're okay?
- What was that?
Who attacked you?
And don't tell him
it was an internal A.R.G.U.S. matter.
His name is Digger
Harkness, former A.S.l.S.
His specialty is weapons and technology
before he went rogue.
Started selling his services
to the highest bidder.
We caught him three years ago.
- Well, looks like he escaped.
- Not exactly.
Harkness' skills made him an ideal recruit
for Task Force X.
You mean, the Suicide Squad.
They had an op in Tanzania.
The assassination of a local warlord.
But the warlord had bigger guns,
the mission went south...
...and the team had to be sanitized.
You mean killed, Lyla.
Waller couldn't be reached. It was my call.
The microbomb in Harkness' neck
must have malfunctioned.
We need to consider that
every A.R.G.U.S. facility is compromised.
There's only one place
we can keep you safe.
How often does Oliver do this?
At least every Wednesday.
There's a lot of sweating.
I don't see what's so hard about that.
I'm not sure she should have called you.
Oliver doesn't play well with others.
Come on.
Barry and Oliver kicked ass last week.
- Yeah.
- They were in, like, a league of their own.
Yeah, that was, like, a one-time thing.
The dude was tossing around
exploding boomerangs. They needed backup.
And I need some dinner. That salmon
ladder made me hungry for sushi.
And I need to
get some paperweights down here.
- Should have warned you about that.
- Yup.
Are you okay?
You can't work for A.R.G.U.S.
without making enemies.
I'm sorry to involve all of you in this.
- Is that A.R.G.U.S. property?
- It's evidence.
Hey. Secret identity?
- They're married.
- We're not married.
Or together. Whatever.
He told her about me.
- You didn't?
- I keep secrets for a living, man.
- Ah. My bad.
- You're... You're...
The Flash. Sushi?
We need a location on the man who's after
Lyla. His name is Digger Harkness.
The first step is to work the evidence...
Barry, can I speak to you
for a moment, please?
I appreciate your help back at A.R.G.U.S.,
but we have this handled.
- You don't wanna team up again?
- Things work differently here.
Starling City is meaner.
I remember helping you pretty
good last year, without powers.
I've been practicing everything
you taught me.
I'm casing new environments,
I'm not running in blind.
- We do this my way.
- Yes! This is gonna be awesome.
- What's our first move?
- We need to reassemble the evidence.
It will take some time, but it'll...
But it'll be Worth it.
Rad! These are a bit more teched out than
the one you guys brought to Central City.
3D printed polymer with a circuitry weave.
Some of Harkness' boomerangs exploded.
Yeah. There are grooves
that could pack a C4 charge.
Maybe if we figure out where Harkness
got the supplies, we can track him.
- These weren't made by Ka-Boom-Boomerang.
- Ka-Boom-Boomerang?
Yeah, you know, he has exploding
boomerangs.
- Is that your best?
- Really? It makes perfect...
Cisco. If Harkness didn't make them,
we need to find out who did.
- And who he made the buy off of.
- Markos.
You see this collapsible-node design?
Dead giveaway. That's his signature.
- We need a location on this...?
- Klaus Markos.
No known home address
or place of employment for Markos.
But he was arrested last year
by an Officer Quentin Lance.
Dad, I understand...
...but my boss wants answers about the
rash of B-and-E's on the Southside.
Tell him I got a whole squad in there,
but they can only move so fast.
Hey, Laurel. Detective. Captain.
Captain. Sorry.
- Don't worry. It's been a while.
- Everything okay?
Oh, it's fine. This is, uh...
Bart Allen, right? Got hit by a bus?
Barry. Uh, it was lightning.
- Huh. We worked together on a case last year.
- Barry's a friend.
He's in town with the
Central City Police Department.
I was hoping you could help him.
- He'll explain.
- Sure.
- Oliver, can I talk to you for a moment?
- Yeah.
- The Arrow was in Central City.
- This is a follow-up.
Kind of.
I'm looking to track down a suspect
you apprehended last year. Klaus Markos?
You know where we might find him?
None of his last-knowns are checking out.
Well, I don't really keep up
on the skels I busted, you know.
- I'm not real sentimental that way.
- Okay.
What did you arrest him for?
Uh... Identity theft.
He was using some gizmo to steal credit-card
numbers for the Bratva, Russian mob.
Okay.
I cannot believe
you're a member of the Russian mob.
Former member, probably.
We had a falling out last year.
This is where they run
their cyber-crime operation.
Hey, nice outfit, by the way.
This place looks like a fortress.
Kalashnikovs everywhere.
Roy, take the southeast corner.
Barry, scan the perimeter.
_Digg__
I got northwest.
Are you going to be okay?
You think I'll lose it
because Harkness is after Lyla?
I'm good.
I had eight seconds to kill.
Was that wrong?
What?
My friend wants to have a conversation
with you.
You made this for Digger Harkness.
- I wanna know where he is.
- Go to hell.
The only thing that hurts worse than an
arrow going in is an arrow coming out.
- Hey, what are you doing?
- Getting information.
- Where is he?
- I don't know!
- But he said he doesn't know!
- He's lying.
If you wanna be able to raise your
arm again, tell me where he is!
Here. Harkness gave it to me.
It's encrypted.
I had an order ready for him.
I called, he came.
I don't know where he is, I swear. I swear!
Felicity can crack the encryption.
Use this to track down Harkness.
You tortured that guy.
I interrogated him.
My friend said
your tactics made you a criminal.
I defended you
because I thought you were a hero.
I thought we were supposed to be
better than them.
Barry...
...you live in Central City...
...where it's sunny all the time
and your enemies get cute nicknames.
- You're not in Central City.
- Yeah.
I live in a city
where my best friend was murdered.
Where a woman that I loved was shot full
of arrows and sent tumbling off a rooftop.
Where my mother was murdered
right in front of me, so before...
My mother was murdered in front of me too.
But I don't use my personal tragedies as an
excuse to torture whoever pisses me off.
I'm sorry, Barry.
I'm not as emotionally healthy as you are.
- What's wrong with you?
- When we agreed you were staying...
...we decided that it would be on my terms.
If that is proving too difficult for you,
you know your way back to Central City.
Everything all right between
you and Speedy?
What? Roy? Yeah, we're fine.
I meant him.
Oh. We had a difference of opinion
about the way the world works.
Yup. I know what that's like.
Sometimes they don't see it.
There are people in the world
who deal only in extremes.
And it would be naive to think that anything
less than extreme measures will stop them.
Sometimes bravery isn't enough.
Sometimes the world requires us to be bold.
Whatever the personal cost.
I got him. He's in a warehouse
at the corner of lnfantino and Adams.
- Is that...?
- A.R.G.U.S. by satellite, yeah. Maybe.
- Thermographic imaging shows 10 bodies.
- Harkness knows we're coming.
I can track his cell phone's position.
Cisco, you're with Diggle and Roy.
I'll race you there.
Where's the bomb?
My Chinese sucks.
But that doesn't sound like a location.
Last chance.
Your hands are shaking.
I knew.
You don't have it in you.
You've killed, but torture is different.
For those with a conscience, inflicting pain
is more difficult than inflicting death.
- I'll figure it out.
- No, you won't.
- You don't have the stomach for it.
- I do.
To save all those people, I do.
Where's the bomb?
You Okay?
My daughter's mother tried to detonate a bomb in
a man's head, and now he's trying to kill her.
- So that would be a no.
- Look, you don't know me that well.
I'm the type of guy who's only thought about one
thing, how do I keep the people I love safe.
You seem to me to be pretty good at that.
Maybe before.
I remember a world where people didn't kill
each other with boomerangs.
- Or walk on water?
- Barry can walk on water?
You guys, Harkness has been around
long before people like Barry.
I mean, this world was crazy before all
these metahumans and superpowers, right?
What's your point?
Well, maybe metahumans and superpowers
were given to us to deal with the crazy.
You mean, by God?
No. By a dark matter wave released from
a failed particle accelerator reaction.
Either way, I think people like Barry...
...are the hope for saving people like us,
people like your wife and daughter.
- She's not my wife.
- She's not his wife.
Okay.
Anyway, you see my point, right?
Plus, you gotta admit...
...it's all pretty freaking cool, right?
You're late.
I knew he was there.
He's not dead, right?
Tranq arrow.
Same thing I used on you in Central City.
- Cisco has the van running.
- You've met Harkness' hired muscle.
Harkness isn't here.
Hey! Where's Digger Harkness?
Never met him.
But he paid us 10 G's to give you this.
Ten'll get you 2O that belongs to Harkness.
- What does that mean?
- That Harkness played you.
- I swore I turned that off.
- What?
Markos' phone.
I shut it down after I decrypted it.
- Could someone turn it back on remotely?
- And back-trace the trace?
We have to get out of here now!
Hello, Lyla.
It's been a long time.
- Guns!
- Third drawer!
Know what I like most
about boomerangs, Lyla?
They're proof that things can come back
to haunt you.
You had a bomb for the back of my head.
I have a little something special
for the back of yours.
Lyla, get down!
No!
Caitlin! Caitlin!
Stop the bleeding. I need lidocaine.
- We have epinephrine.
- That will work.
- Hey, stay with me.
- Hey.
Just try and keep her awake.
Can you hear me, Lyla?
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Lyla? She's not breathing!
Lyla?
Lyla.
She's not moving.
I've got her stabilized,
but I can't operate on her here.
- Barry?
- Starling General's at 8th and Wilcott.
H.K.P.F. lD'd her as Sumilu Kang.
She was a student
at the University of Hong Kong.
Biology textbook in her backpack.
She was studying to become a veterinarian.
He would have told me.
I just needed more time.
No, Mr. Queen,
what you needed was conviction.
The men who do things like this have it.
You didn't.
- I thought I could...
- You thought what?
You could reason with him?
Look around you, Mr. Queen.
Look around and tell me that the men who
do this type of thing understand reason.
There are people in this world
who deal only in extremes.
It's naive to think that anything
less than extreme measures will stop them.
The bomber was Katsu Cheng,
but make no mistake...
...this blood is on your hands.
Cheng said I didn't have the stomach
for torture. He was right.
Because you need to practice.
Torture is an art form.
It's a skill one must cultivate.
- Why would I do that?
- I think Cheng was wrong.
I think you not only have the stomach
for this work, you have the talent.
This feels wrong.
Being here, it feels wrong.
Oliver needed to be alone.
He made that clear.
Three doubles, straight up.
- Are you guys okay?
- We're just having a tough night.
- Anything I can do to help?
- No, we're good.
But thanks for the night off.
Yo, who was that hottie?
- Oliver's sister.
- My ex-girlfriend.
- So stay away, that's what you're saying.
- Yeah.
She's in surgery. Mr. Diggle is with her.
- Is she gonna be okay?
- I hope so. She's strong.
How do you guys do it?
How do you guys live like this...
...where anyone you care about
could be struck down?
We haven't been taking this seriously.
It's all been a game.
We give the bad guys code names.
I think the fact that we go up against
metahumans made it all kind of clean.
Like, the fact that they've got these
powers makes what they're doing less...
Real.
This is all my fault.
It's really not.
I tortured Markos to give up that phone.
None of this would have happened
if it wasn't for me.
I get the feeling you don't say that often.
To do what I do, Barry, takes conviction.
But...
...more often than not,
it's the will to do what's ugly.
Every time I do that, I'm...
I'm trading away little...
...pieces of myself, so...
You asked what's wrong with me,
that's what's wrong.
Because the part that I'm trading away...
...is Oliver Queen.
And lately I've been
feeling like there is...
...nothing left except the Arrow.
I think you're full of crap.
Look, you've convinced yourself...
...that everything you've been through
took away your humanity.
I think it's because of your humanity
that you made it through.
You wouldn't have survived,
much less come out the other end a hero...
...somebody who wants to do good,
if you didn't have a light inside of you.
I'm sorry if I'm interrupting.
I ran facial recognition on Harkness,
and I have a match.
Where is he?
Get on the ground!
Now, why would I wanna do that?
You hurt a friend of mine.
You really think there's anywhere in the
world you could run and we won't find you?
Hmm. Probably not...
...which is why I have
a contingency in place.
Five bombs planted throughout Starling.
You can stop me,
or you can stop the bombs...
...but you can't do both.
Bombs are armed.
In 90 seconds, this city will be on fire.
Go.
Guys, Harkness just triggered five bombs
throughout the city. We don't know where.
- To blanket the entire city, you'd have to use...
- Radio-controlled lED's.
- But if we key into the detonator frequency...
- We can pinpoint the location of the bombs.
I need a location! I need five locations.
The five receivers.
Nearest one is behind a restaurant
at Faith and Flower.
Okay. Guys, I found it.
- I'm gonna run it out of the city.
- Barry, wait.
- That's not an option.
- The bombs might be linked.
What?
Press the emblem on your suit.
I installed a mini-cam there.
Okay. You see the secondary trigger?
It's not just a receiver.
- It's a transmitter.
- If you try to defuse the bomb...
...the trigger will transmit a signal and
the rest of the bombs are gonna explode.
- We're running out of time.
- Defuse all the bombs at the same time.
You're thinking of multiplex.
I can't be in five places at once.
But I don't have to be.
- Stop the countdown.
- Go to hell.
- Last chance.
- Or what?
You'll inflict pain?
You've done it before,
so let me ask you this...
...why are you hesitating?
Yaah, uh, whoa!
Ten more seconds,
and we should be able to see at least...
...ah, three explosions from here.
Okay.
Everyone has to cut their wires
exactly on three.
One...
...two...
...three.
Oh, screw you, Captain Boomerang.
You think
you've accomplished something here?
You think you not killing me
makes you strong?
It just means...
...you're weak.
It means I have some humanity left.
You just couldn't resist, could you?
Hey, sweetie.
You only call me sweetie
when you want something.
I do.
I want you to marry me.
I can't believe I waited this long to ask.
I need you, Lyla.
Now, forever, official.
- I need you...
- Will you please stop talking...
...so I can say yes?
Some of the STR markers on the DNA sample
have degraded...
...but I've got a computer
that I think will help fill in the gaps.
- Thank you, Caitlin.
- I'll let you know as soon as I have the results.
I'll call this time.
- It's cool. You guys are fun.
- So are you guys.
Well, you could be if you realized
you were working under a nightclub.
Oh, hey, you guys take care of business?
Digger Harkness is now cellmates
with one Slade Wilson.
We've got a pipeline,
he's got a gorgeous tropical island.
- With the landmines. Hm, hm.
- What?
It's a long story.
What's this?
Oliver had me put that in
while you guys were at the hospital.
- Wait, this is for me?
- For the next time you're in town.
- There'll be a next time?
- I'm still calling the shots.
- We'll talk about that.
- Yes, we will.
And then I'll call the shots.
We got a gift for you too, Oliver.
Early Christmas present.
Turns out S.T.A.R. Labs' industrial
fabricator's based out of Starling, so...
Polymer Kevlar weave.
It's 25 percent lighter
and can carry 15 percent more gear.
I got designs I'm working up
that I'm really excited by.
It's, uh, subtle.
I wanted to replace the hood,
but Felicity said it had sentimental value.
- Thank you.
- Anytime.
You guys headed back?
It's possible that Dr. Wells didn't
sign off on us leaving town.
Hey, do you still, like, take the train?
Yeah, sure, if I feel like taking a nap.
But Oliver and I have some
unfinished business to take care of first.
You guys aren't gonna punch each other,
are you?
Why'd you summon me here?
To make me feel worse?
No, I summoned you here
to give you a second chance.
- Is this a joke?
- No.
This is Li Khuan Hui.
That name should sound familiar to you.
- You work for China White.
- Chien Na Wei.
Yes, Mr. Hui is on her payroll.
He's Chinese triad,
and he knows her agenda here in Hong Kong.
Fortunately, Mr. Hui has been
less than forthcoming with the details.
Fortunately?
You get a stab at redemption.
You could have invited everybody.
They'd like this.
No, they would love this,
but this is just for the two of us.
You mean the one of you.
This was your idea.
You can't expect me to believe that
you don't wanna know once and for all...
...who would win, me or you.
- If you don't shoot me in the back.
- Get over that.
Okay, I have superpowers,
you have arrows that run out.
I have strategy and tactical awareness.
When I'm fighting you,
it's literally like you're standing still.
- Tough talk. You ready to back it up?
- Oh, yeah.
Hey, by the way...
- Yeah?
- ...you were wrong.
When you told me I could inspire people,
you said you couldn't.
But you were wrong.
You can inspire.
Not as the Arrow, that guy's a douche...
...but as Oliver Queen.
Thank you.
Since we're sharing, you were wrong too.
- When?
- Right now.
Because you think you can kick my ass.
I can tell.
Well, if you think you can kick mine,
you better do it fast.
I get it, Barry, I get it. You're fast.
Ready.
Set.