Previously on "Arrow"...
Dinah: This is a plan
to level all of Star City.
Felicity wouldn't do
something like this.
Maybe she had
a change of heart,
tried to back out
last second.
It'd explain why
someone would want
her dead, right?
Last call out
was to someone named...
Blackstar.
What's this?
Something I
lifted off Byrd
before he
went into custody.
It's a painting?
All right, looks like someone
doesn't want
us to see this.
Bethany Snow: Ricardo Diaz
is behind bars tonight,
thanks to the unidentified
Green Arrow.
Felicity put a gun
right to my face.
I don't believe you.
I made a deal
with the feds.
Oliver will be
a free man again.
Woman and man: ♪ When I go ♪
♪ Into the ground ♪
♪ Oh, they got to bury me ♪
♪ Bury me face down ♪
Man: ♪ From the rubble ♪
♪ What do I see? ♪
♪ There's a whole damn army ♪
♪ Thinkin' that they're
gonna harm me ♪
♪ Say good night,
I'll never get free ♪
♪ When I go ♪
♪ Into that ground ♪
♪ Oh, they got to bury me ♪
♪ Bury me face down ♪
♪ Bury me
face down ♪
♪ Oh, they got to bury me ♪
♪ Bury me face down ♪
Bethany Snow: After keeping
a low profile
since his release last week,
Oliver Queen will make
his first public appearance
tonight
at a gala supporting
prison reform.
But will Star City welcome back
its former vigilante
with open arms?
Or has public opinion soured
against the Green Arrow
now that we know who's under
that hood?
Aah!
Hey. It's just me.
Hey. I'm sorry about
earlier.
I didn't mean
to freak you out.
No. I'm just, um,
getting used
to being home.
[Pulls zipper up]
Mm. I missed that.
Having someone
to zip your dress?
Well, that, and you.
And I really miss
William.
Yeah. Christmas vacation
feels like
it's 20 years from now.
So why aren't you
dressed?
I'm gonna sit this one out.
[Chuckling]
Oh, no, no, no.
I don't think that's
how this works,
especially
when you're the one
being honored.
Besides, you've been
spending more time
in the shadows
recently
than when you were
the Green Arrow.
The last time I faced
the city, I was in cuffs.
A lot of people are
mad at me, Felicity.
I lied to them.
They have a right to be
mad at me.
Which is exactly why
this event is
so important.
They want to publicly
recognize you as a hero.
And after all the lives
you saved at Slabside,
let them see you
for who you really are,
without a mask.
I mean, you're
probably right.
Oh, I'm always right.
You will always be
the best part of me
for the rest of my life.
You remember.
Of course I remember.
Happy anniversary.
[People cheering]
This used to be the
nicest club in town
20 years ago.
You can practically
smell the money.
Zoe: Yeah. Definitely
not smelling that.
I can't believe Roy's
missing out on all the fun.
[Chuckles weakly]
If he got recognized here,
we'd have big trouble.
And you're sure
Blackstar's here?
Dinah: The Canary network
couldn't find much,
but they did learn
Blackstar likes to
frequent this club.
I seriously question
this person's choice
of friends.
Dinah: That's why we need
to keep our heads down.
Blackstar was the last one
to talk to Felicity.
Whoever this is could have
either been helping her or...
Or they're the one
who killed her.
[Punch lands, crowd cheers]
And you were worried this
was going to be dangerous.
Dinah: Hey, we're looking
for someone named Blackstar.
You know who that is?
Yeah.
She's right there.
Uh!
Spectators: Blackstar!
Blackstar! Blackstar! Blackstar!
Blackstar! Blackstar!
Blackstar! Blackstar...
Well, she seems
easy to talk to.
[Piano music]
We didn't get this
treatment after we
put Diaz behind bars.
Envy is not
a good look on you.
Neither is
the crab cake
on your face.
Rene: This event is
messed up.
Rich folk and politicians
fronting
like they actually care
about prison reform.
If everybody in here
actually gave a crap,
they'd use that money
to help people
in hard-up neighborhoods
who end up in the system
because they don't
have anything else.
What?
You ever think about
running for office?
Woman: Oliver, what's it
like to be out of prison?
How does it feel to be
back home
with everyone knowing
you're the Green Arrow?
Man: Are you gonna
put on the hood now
that you're back?
My husband
is very grateful
to be home with
his family. Thank you.
[Indistinct chatter]
Excuse me. Queen!
Max Fuller.
Hey, man, I know we've
had some bad history.
You, uh, had
your bodyguards
kick the crap out of me
and Tommy at your club.
Right. Well, you slept
with my wife.
Well, now my ex-wife.
Dude, all that is in
the past, OK?
You're the freaking
Green Arrow.
Well, I'm Felicity.
I am the wife of
the freaking Green Arrow.
That sounded a little less
strange in my head.
Impressed.
You see, he didn't used
to be the marriage type.
-Ah. Hmm.
-Yeah.
But, hey, people
change, right?
Felicity: Yes, they do.
And we are just gonna say hi
to some friends
if you'll excuse us.
Yeah, please.
Is it just me,
or is that guy
the absolute worst?
Uh...
[Laughter]
I never got to ask you.
what was your first meal
when you got back?
Felicity: Double Double
at Big Belly Burger.
That's what I'm
talking about.
John: Taking a while to get
those sea legs back, huh?
Rene: Speaking of,
you thinking about
getting back out there,
trying that old suit
on for size?
Shh, shh. No, no, no.
He's absolutely not
just like we don't
do that anymore.
Dinah's right.
I'm very much enjoying not
being in prison.
So what now?
I don't know.
Find a different way
to help the city,
way you guys did.
What about you, Felicity?
Well, I'm developing a new
security system.
Laurel: Well, then I'm sure
it's the best one in town.
We're friends
with her now?
It's more like frenemies.
It's a long story.
Relax. I'm just here
keeping up appearances.
D.A., remember?
Actually, we should all
really be thanking Laurel.
I mean, she is the one
who did the trade
to get Oliver out of prison.
Oliver: That's true.
I'm very grateful.
I know that I haven't
always given you
the benefit
of the doubt, so...
Well, it was
really Felicity
who was willing
to do anything
to stop Diaz.
She's ruthless.
[Applause]
Pollard: Welcome.
Thank you all
for attending this evening.
I would like to introduce
this evening's honoree,
Mr. Oliver Queen.
[Applause]
Thank you,
Mayor Pollard.
[Clears throat]
I used to believe
that justice was
as simple as putting
criminals behind bars...
but then I spent
some time in prison,
and I realized that
the truth is
nowhere near
that black and white.
The truth is that
our institutions have
a long way to go
before they achieve
true justice.
[Arrow flies]
[Circuits blowing]
[Attendees shouting
and screaming]
The attack perpetrated by
the Green Arrow this evening
is further proof
why we, as a city,
cannot trust men
that hide behind masks.
There is a reason why the
anti-vigilante law exists.
Thank you.
Rene: Look, I know
how this looks,
but this wasn't
the new Green Arrow.
He hasn't murdered
anyone.
That
you know of.
Has anyone actually seen
who's behind the mask?
Well, no. But whoever it is
has been helping the city.
And helped us
take down Diaz.
This was
cold-blooded murder.
Now, I appreciate how
all of you feel as though
the new Green Arrow
is an ally,
but I would like to be sure.
And how are you
gonna do that
if you're a no-go
on the Arrow?
Is there a law against
me consulting?
You mean an investigative
consultant, like
"The Mentalist"?
I love that show.
I can't think of
a better way to investigate
a copycat Green Arrow than
with the original.
Rene: I can.
With my help,
because I'm not
sitting this one out.
I appreciate it,
but there's nothing left
to be done tonight,
so go home.
Let my guys work the scene.
And if I need help, I'll
call you tomorrow.
Rene: This is everything
Dinah's compiled
on the vigilante...
every sighting, targets.
It's all there.
It says here
the SCPD
nearly arrested him
last month.
But he had
an accomplice?
Uh, yeah, that...
that was me.
I, uh,
I didn't want Dinah
to lock him up.
Oh, I bet she really
appreciated that.
She threw my ass in jail.
I'm really sad
I missed that.
What else do we
know?
Rene: Uh, he's definitely
not a rookie. I know that.
I mean, the guy's efficient,
disciplined, precise.
I mean,
he works the bow and arrow
about as well as you do.
That takes
a very specific
type of training.
Dinah: Hey. Sorry I'm late.
Pollard's on the warpath.
That's OK. Forensics
pull anything
from the scene?
Well, nothing we didn't
already suspect.
Arrows are consistent
with the vigilante.
Here. Take a look.
Thank you.
Oliver: Well, they're both
handmade.
The materials in the arrowhead
seem to match.
This would be difficult
to replicate.
But not impossible,
right?
The security camera
footage?
Yeah, but you're
not gonna find much.
The killer was
off-camera.
His arrows weren't.
If this guy is as precise
with a bow and arrow
as Rene says, then he
would've had a target.
Based on the trajectory,
that guy.
Oh, wait a minute. That's...
that's Clayton Ford.
He's a rich dude who
actually helped the Glades.
He funded a clinic.
This makes no sense.
The vigilante's only
targeted people
who've hurt the Glades.
Ford helped it.
Then what the hell's
the motive?
Sure would help
if we could ask
directly.
[Scoffs]
Wait. Hang on.
You're...you're in contact?
That was one time,
all right?
And count me out
if we're gonna roll up
and arrest him.
Dinah: I'm not
talking about
the SCPD.
Just us. We just
need to talk to
the new Green Arrow.
Oliver: You think he's
innocent. So we'll be fine.
And what if we aren't?
Then we deal
with him.
You should make
the call.
John: Hey.
Got to say,
I never appreciated
how tightly you run
this ship
until you were gone
with the brass.
It is so good to see
you behind that desk
again, Lyla.
Flatterer.
Shut the door.
What's going on?
I had my contact look
into the image
that Curtis decrypted
from the Malcolm Byrd op.
The "Dante" painting.
It's being used
as some sort of
highly advanced
identification protocol
within terrorist circles.
Kobra, Basilisk,
the Third World
Liberation Army...
they're all using the name
Dante like it's a contact.
For what? Or for who?
I don't know, but I might
know how to find out.
When I cross-referenced
the terrorist groups
with the financials that
we obtained in Geneva,
I found a common account.
Could you trace it?
No. Come here.
Look at this.
[Laptop beeps]
John: Five transactions
in the past 7 months
between Dante
and a consulting firm
called Rubrum,
Silentium, and Ursa.
That's Latin for
"red," "silent," and "bear,"
the Longbow Hunters.
Look.
You got to be
kidding me.
[Sirens in distance]
This is definitely
the place.
Oliver: Then where is he?
Maybe he got
held up.
[beeping]
Oliver:
Rene, stop.
What are you talking about?
There are
motion detectors.
We've been made.
[Distorted voice]
I said, Come alone.
These are my friends.
You already met
Captain Drake.
You can trust them.
We only want
to talk.
I'll pass.
A piece of advice
from one Green Arrow
to another:
cooperate.
Because right now,
most of the people
in this city think
you're a killer.
Are you?
-Cut him off!
-On it.
[Engine starts]
Mr. Queen. Mr. Queen,
Mr. Queen,
do you know who
the new Green Arrow is?
Are you helping with
this investigation?
I have no comment, guys.
Dinah: Hey, whoa, whoa,
whoa. What the hell is this?
You all know the precinct
is off-limits.
Captain Drake,
care to comment?
The SCPD does not comment
on ongoing investigations.
But I do. The vigilante
didn't do it.
OK. Can somebody please
get these guys out of here?
Not helping.
Hey. Why does
the mayor have to
have all the fun?
Oliver: Maybe meeting
at the precinct
wasn't the best idea.
Yeah. Well, I thought
the jig was up
after you were spotted
last night.
Oh, and speaking
of last night,
turns out we were
right about your
Green Arrow clone.
He is innocent.
How do we know?
Remember our second
suspected target,
Clayton Ford?
-Mm-hmm.
-My guys found him dead
across town at
the same time
we were chasing
the vigilante.
-We're his alibi.
-OK.
What do we know about
the Ford murder?
Dinah: Emerald arrow,
center...chest,
same as Hutchinson.
Rene: Someone's going
through a lot of trouble
to pin this on
the new Green Arrow.
We really need to come up
with a better name for him.
He's making everyone,
including Pollard,
look away.
The question is from what?
Well, Ford
may have known.
He was trying to skip
town when he was killed.
He found him with bags
packed and ready to go,
clothes and cash.
Yeah, he knew he was
the target.
What the hell is going on?
Last time I checked,
Mr. Queen and Mr. Ramirez
were not employed by
the SCPD.
Well, they're just here
giving statements.
That the vigilante didn't
do it. Yeah, I heard.
You know,
it's no big surprise
that the old Green Arrow
would be supporting
the new one,
but I expected more from
my police captain.
You telling me how to
conduct my investigation,
Ms. Mayor?
Because last I checked,
I was still in control
of this precinct.
I hired you to restore
the city's faith
in this department.
That means bringing that
vigilante to justice.
And if you can't do that,
I will find someone else
who can.
Rene: She may be
the tiniest,
most unpleasant person
I've ever met.
You have to listen
to her, but I don't.
What are you thinking?
It says here both
victims were
members of the same
society at Yale.
I know a guy. Max Fuller,
he was a member, too.
I could go see him,
gather some intel.
I'll be in touch if I
learn anything, all right?
Excuse me,
Ms., uh, Blackstar?
Can we talk to you?
I'm kind of busy.
Clearly.
We only need 5 minutes.
Not interested.
Like I said,
I'd love to talk.
So this whole
fight club thing,
you just beat people
up for what? Fun?
Stress release.
[Chuckles]
Do you really want to
spend your 5 minutes
talking about
my hobbies?
Zoe: How do you know
Felicity Smoak?
I don't.
Well, that's strange,
because you were
the last person she called
before she was killed.
Felicity's dead?
Oh, so you do know her.
We worked together
sometimes.
What kind of work was that?
The kind that's none
of your business.
So, illegal.
Well, you're one
to talk, Canary.
You're not
as smart as you
think you are.
But you want
to come in here
and judge me?
At least I'm not
lying to everyone,
pretending to be
some kind of hero.
At least I'm not
a vigilante.
You don't know what you're
talking about, kid.
You know, you're part of
the reason Star City is
in the shape it's
in right now.
Really? 'Cause I
could've sworn,
the story goes,
it's because of you.
Hey, just tell us why
Felicity called you.
Then we'll leave you alone.
I work as a broker.
I help people find
certain items.
Felicity asked me to
find her
an electrical
firing circuit
and a couple
transmitters.
Those are mechanisms for
triggering a bomb.
Blackstar: I don't know
why she needed 'em.
I didn't ask.
As long as I get paid,
you can ask for
whatever you want.
Sounds like you two had
a lot in common.
If that's it, I have
my next fight coming up,
and I really
should stretch.
Yeah. I'm done here anyway.
Word of advice.
Asking questions
about Felicity Smoak
will not end well
for anyone.
Max: Five
fully-stocked bars,
3 private lounges,
and the sound system is
the best...
outside of Europe.
A.I. adjusts
the acoustic environment
based on capacity.
Right this way here.
That's a ton of security
you got down there, Max.
It must be costing
you a fortune.
Heh! Not when you pay
for them with crypto
you mine yourself.
All it costs me is
the little USB drive
I put it on. Scotch?
It's a 25-year.
Why not?
We can toast your new club.
Hey. Toast to
your new prison- and
Green Arrow-free life.
It's really got to piss
you off, though, huh?
Seeing some lame copycat
screw up
everything you
sacrificed for.
I wanted to speak with you
about that.
The last two murders
weren't connected
to the vigilante.
So the rumors are true.
You are helping the cops
investigate this.
How can I help?
You were a member of
the Scroll and Key
back at Yale.
Allegedly.
It is a secret society.
Fair point.
How well did you
know Clayton Ford
and Sam Hutchinson?
Clay and Hutch.
Well enough to mourn them.
Mm-hmm.
But we'd sort of fallen
out of touch.
Ford looked like he was
trying to skip town
before he died,
like he knew the hit
was coming,
but we just...we
don't know how.
You're looking for
skeletons.
And are we gonna
find any?
I know you're not supposed
to talk ill of the dead
or whatever, but, you know,
there were always rumors
that they had shady
business dealings going on
with the Triad, I believe.
So who knows? Maybe they got
in over their heads.
Probably.
I won't take up any
more of your time.
Thank you, Max.
You mind if I ask you
a question?
They sent you to prison
for helping this city.
Why the hell should you
care about any of this?
Old habits.
I guess some people
don't change
that much after all.
[Chuckles softly]
Hey.
Sorry I'm late.
That's OK.
I'm still
getting used to you
coming home at all.
How did things go
with Fuller?
Max Fuller is
hiding something.
Do you mind looking
into it?
Of course.
Hey, you just came in
the front door,
and none of my security
measures triggered.
You sure?
[Typing]
Felicity!
Who are you?
My husband asked you
a question.
Where'd you get that?
We'll talk about it later.
Stay down!
Hey, hey.
Dinah: All right. As soon
as the doc gives the OK,
we'll take him into
the station for questioning.
In the meantime, we'll go
through his effects,
see what we can find out.
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
Oh, hey, and just
a bit of advice.
Yeah.
You probably shouldn't
be shooting people
your first week
out of prison.
-That's a good tip.
-Yeah.
He must've somehow
countered my alarm
by sonically hacking
into the sensors.
Felicity.
That is a design flaw
that could take
weeks to fix.
-We need to talk about this.
-No. We need to be safe.
This security system
was supposed to bring
peace of mind.
-You mean like owning a gun?
-Yeah.
Where'd you even get a gun?
Your best new friend
Laurel?
Of course not.
I got it from your
ex-best friend, Anatoly.
You what?
I've barely been gone
7 months,
and you've aligned yourself
with two of the most immoral
people we know?
Oliver, you don't
get to judge me.
You just shot a man in
our living room.
Something you've done
a million times.
Hey, this isn't you.
You don't obsess over
security.
You certainly
don't carry a gun.
This is me, Oliver,
not because I was
influenced by Laurel
or Anatoly.
This is me
because of you.
You were the one
that decided
all on your own that
you were going to
sacrifice yourself,
leaving your son
and your wife
alone at home as
sitting ducks for Diaz.
And the best part about
the whole thing is that
you didn't even
ask us about how we
felt about it.
I've already apologized
for this.
I don't know how many times
you need me to apologize.
What am I supposed to do
with an apology, Oliver?
I'm just supposed
to move on?
While you were gone,
I had to figure out
how to survive.
And I am glad that
I did
because the old me,
she was weak.
How could you possibly
think that?
The old you was the person
I fell in love with.
Well...
she's gone.
And she's not
coming back.
[Laughter in distance]
I thought you didn't drink.
Yeah, well, it's been
a tough week.
I know the feeling.
You know, Roy told me
this would only
bring me pain,
and he was right.
[Chuckles softly]
I'm going home.
Just like that, huh,
without any answers?
Felicity is dead.
And before that,
she had a plan to blow
up an entire city.
So I'm not sure exactly
why I'm supposed to care
about what happened
to her.
I'm just sorry I dragged
you all into this.
You need to see something.
It's called
the mark of four.
Your dad came up with it.
I don't remember that.
You were already gone.
It was right before
everything.
It symbolizes the 4 pillars
of heroism...
courage, compassion,
selflessness, and loyalty.
We all got them as
a reminder that
no matter what happened,
if one of us was in trouble,
the other ones would
be there.
That's why Roy came with
you back to Star City.
He saw the symbol
written on the inside
of your father's bow.
So that's why you're
helping us?
I didn't know what to
make of you at first.
[Scoffs]
Trust doesn't come
so easily to me.
Yeah? So what changed?
I started seeing the best
parts of your dad in you...
the strength that
made him a hero.
I am not that.
You sure about that?
'Cause your dad,
he had this way of
looking into things,
of seeing beyond
the evidence.
So what does your gut
tell you about Blackstar?
That she isn't telling
us the whole story.
Good. Let's find out
what she's hiding.
Hey, hey.
Who's hungry?
Ohh. You're a life saver.
It's not often I get to buy
the police captain dinner.
Yeah?
Well, you'd better get
your fill in now
because I probably
won't have this job
much longer.
Why? You don't think this
will blow over with Pollard?
Well...
I don't know.
You know,
maybe it shouldn't.
How can I really
be effective here
if she's just gonna
undercut me
the whole way?
I'd be better off
as Black Canary.
Whew. You don't know
how long
I've been waiting for you
to say that.
But you're the best damn
person for this job, D.
This city needs you here.
[Knock on door]
Hey. How's it going
with the hit man?
Good. He's still
recovering,
but we got an ID
thanks to A.R.G.U.S.
Frank Cassaday, otherwise
known as "the Mirror."
Specializes in kills
via mimicked m.o.
Proof the vigilante
didn't do it,
but who ordered the hits?
Where'd you find that?
I found that on Cassaday.
Why? You recognize that?
[Exhales]
Fuller. He used those
to pay his muscle
in the club.
This was Fuller.
He ordered the hit on
Hutchinson
and then Ford
and then me
once I got too close.
Why? I mean,
he's a rich douche bag,
but I didn't peg him
to be a killer.
Felicity ran
background on Fuller.
He had secret
business dealings
with both
Hutchinson and Ford.
If they were gonna
cut him out,
this was payback.
All right. Well, the hit
on you failed,
so that means Fuller's gonna
know something's up soon
if he doesn't
already, right?
I'm gonna send S.W.A.T. in
while we still have
the element of surprise.
It's not
that simple.
Fuller's in there
right now with at
least 12 hired guns,
and the club is
at capacity.
So it could get
really messy.
Guys.
It won't get messy
if the Green Arrow
goes in...
the O.G. one.
No. I...I can't risk being
separated from my family,
Rene, I can't do it.
I might know a way you can.
Even if you did,
Pollard would never
stand for it.
Pollard wanted me
to restore
the city's faith in
this department,
and that is never
gonna happen if we
keep treating our heroes
like criminals.
It's time the mayor
realizes that.
Dinah, I trust you,
but you have to be sure.
Half this city believes
in the vigilante
because they were hoping
it was you.
Now they don't have
to hope anymore.
OK.
I need to make
a pit stop.
The bunker has seen
better days.
Yes, it has.
It didn't seem right
coming back here
after the team
disbanded.
Thanks for bringing this.
The FBI still has mine.
It's a good thing
you made another one.
Yeah.
Does that mean you
changed your mind
about breaking
the cycle of violence?
No.
[Clasps snap]
I cannot burden William
with this.
But it's not
just about breaking
the cycle of violence.
It's about accountability.
What does that mean
to you?
If Star City wants
to hate the Green Arrow,
that's fine.
They'll have
to hate me, too.
You want some backup
out there?
Thank you, but this time,
I got to go solo.
Hey.
Yeah.
Don't you need this?
No.
[Clang]
[Dance music playing]
Woman: ♪ Uh, do it
till they feel it... ♪
Cassaday,
you were supposed
to check in here
when the job
was done.
Where the hell
are you?
Listen, I want everyone
on high alert, OK?
No one gets in here.
Go!
Woman: ♪ Do your thing ♪
♪ Do your thing, do your thing ♪
♪ Just make it happen ♪
[Comms beep]
I'm in.
Copy that.
We're ready.
Keep your men
in position and wait
for my word.
I don't want
to tip our hand
or panic the crowd.
Let's hope
you're not rusty.
All units, stand by.
Queen?
[Machine gun firing]
Aah! Uh! Uh...
[Fires pistol]
[Pistol thuds along floor]
Aah! Uh! Uh...
Man: ♪ You don't hate me ♪
♪ You hate you ♪
♪ If you're looking for me,
I'm right here... ♪
Dinah: Oliver,
do you have Fuller?
I'm about to.
Man: ♪ I'm right here,
I'm right ♪
♪ I'm right here, I'm right ♪
♪ I'm right here! ♪
[People screaming]
Stay back!
Drop the gun, Max.
-I'll shoot.
-Hiring killers is easy.
[Clang]
Taking the shot
yourself isn't.
Oh. You're a vigilante.
You don't have the authority
to arrest me.
She does.
Max Fuller, you are
under arrest
for the murder
of Clayton Ford
and Sam Hutchinson.
[Smartphone cameras snapping
photos]
Take Mr. Fuller into
booking.
Should I give you two
a minute?
We do this together.
Ms. Mayor, to what do
I owe the pleasure?
You've got
some nerve.
I want Mr. Queen booked
in violation of
the anti-vigilante law.
Hmm. Afraid I
can't do that.
Then I want
your resignation.
I think that would be
a mistake.
Oh, that's rich,
coming from the man
who stared this city
in the face and lied.
You made a mockery
of city hall.
I'm gonna show you
that no one
is above the law.
I could not
agree with you more,
which is why, as of
today, Mr. Queen
is officially working
for the SCPD.
He's no longer
a vigilante.
I'll get that tossed
by this time tomorrow.
Well, you can try, but
I have a strong feeling
the district attorney is
going to side with me
on this one.
This isn't over,
not even close.
This should be fun.
Got to warn you,
this one's a handful.
We know.
You sure you're
good with this?
Hiding the truth from
Oliver and Felicity? No.
But this is the strongest
lead we've got.
If we don't exploit it now,
who knows how many people
will be hurt later?
Lyla: Open it.
[Door buzzes open]
We'll take it from here.
Hello, Mr. Diaz.
Remember me?
I'm sure you remember
my husband.
What do you want?
We need your help.
Man. And I thought
I was messy.
How are we supposed to find
anything in this place?
[Grunts]
Guys!
These are the bomb
schematics we found
in Felicity's
hideout.
Blackstar knew about
her plan to blow up
Star City.
Maybe she didn't just
know about it.
Maybe she was part of it.
Huh. If Felicity
got cold feet,
that's one hell of a motive
to kill her.
OK. But why
hang on to these?
I mean, why not
destroy the evidence?
Because she's still
planning on using them.
OK, we have got to
go to the cops.
The SCPD are a joke.
They'd love to watch
Star City go up in flames.
Well, there is
another option.
We go to the Glades.
I thought we weren't
welcome there.
Well, we're not,
but she is.
No. No way.
Zoe, we don't know
when or where
this is going
to happen, right?
And by the time we find out,
it could be too late.
I don't love the idea
either,
but we need resources.
[Heavy sigh]
I guess it's time to
pay my dad a visit.
Snow: With the successful
arrest of Max Fuller assisted
by Oliver Queen, the Green Arrow
will officially be working
on the side of the law
hand in hand with the SCPD,
marking a new era
for Star City.
[Shuts off TV]
Well...
it looks like
you're famous again.
Could you have
imagined 7 years ago
that you'd be
working unmasked
and alongside the cops?
[Chuckles]
A lot has changed.
Yeah.
All those months
at Slabside,
there wasn't a day that
went by...
there wasn't an hour
that went by I didn't think
about you and William and...
getting our life back.
Me, too.
[Clears throat]
OK.
So what's changed?
I think time apart
forced us to move
in different
directions.
OK. But how do we...
start pushing in the same
direction again?
I want to.
Mm-hmm.
But you're right.
You know,
I've changed...
more than you know.
I almost killed Diaz,
and I would've
killed him
if Laurel
hadn't stopped me.
And I know that you're
gonna want
to talk me down to
the old Felicity,
the one that you met
chewing that red pen.
While you were gone,
I had to learn how
to protect myself.
I put you in the position
where you had to do that,
and I'm sorry.
No. This isn't on you.
Well...OK.
I love you more than
a human being
should love another
human being.
I just don't know
if what's best for me
right now is
the same thing
as what's best for us.
Hey, Dad, turns out Oliver
is more like you
than I thought,
more like me, too.
But I'm not giving up,
not ever.
[Explosions]
You failed.
Why are you doing this?
You did this
to yourself.
And now all of you
will perish.
Man: Greg, move your head.