MY NAME IS OLIVER QUEEN.
AFTER 6 YEARS
OF BEING A VIGILANTE,
THE ONLY WAY TO ACHIEVE MY GOAL
AND SAVE MY CITY WAS TO CONFESS
TO BEING THE GREEN ARROW.
NOW MY FAMILY AND FRIENDS MUST
CARRY ON MY MISSION WITHOUT ME.
I AM NO LONGER A HERO.
NOW I AM INMATE 4587.
PREVIOUSLY ON "ARROW"...
OLIVER: YOU HIRED
THOSE PRISONERS
TO ATTACK ME
IN THE SHOWER FOR DIAZ.
SO WHY DON'T YOU TELL ME
HOW I CAN FIND HIM?
YOU GOT TO PROVE
YOURSELF WORTHY
OF MY FRIENDSHIP.
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
I WANT HIM GONE.
[GROANS, SHIV FALLS TO FLOOR]
OLIVER: YOU STABBED ME.
-I DIDN'T STAB YOU.
-GET AWAY FROM HIM.
THE VIDEO! THAT GUARD
STABBED ME. HE STABBED ME!
YORKE: I DIDN'T!
I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING!
FELICITY: YOU MADE A DEAL
WITH MY HUSBAND.
AND HE'S IN PRISON
BECAUSE OF IT.
NOW IT'S YOUR TURN TO HOLD UP
YOUR SIDE OF THE BARGAIN.
WE'RE GONNA TAKE DOWN
RICARDO DIAZ TOGETHER.
[INDISTINCT SHOUTING]
YOU PROMISED THE FBI WOULD
STAY IN STAR CITY
UNTIL DIAZ WAS
OFF THE BOARD.
AND AS YOU CAN SEE,
WE'RE STILL HERE.
YEAH, BUT YOU
HAVEN'T CAUGHT HIM.
APPREHENDING DIAZ IS
STILL A PRIORITY,
BUT HE'S NOT THE ONLY
CRIMINAL ON OUR LIST.
-LET ME HELP.
-EXCUSE ME?
YOU'VE SEEN WHAT I CAN
DO WITH THE TCK, TCK.
HEH. WE HAVE OUR OWN
EXPERTS, MS. SMOAK.
BUT NOT AS EXPERT AS ME.
I KNOW EVERYTHING THERE IS
TO KNOW ABOUT DIAZ
AND THE LONGBOW HUNTERS.
YEAH! THEY'RE HERE, TOO.
DIAZ BROUGHT IN
THE BAD GUY BIG GUNS,
WHICH MEANS YOU DON'T HAVE
ANY MORE TIME TO WASTE.
SO GIVE ME A COMPUTER
AND PUT ME TO WORK.
MY AGREEMENT WITH
YOUR HUSBAND,
IT GIVES YOU IMMUNITY.
IT DOESN'T MAKE US
ALLIES.
DIAZ ATTACKED ME WHILE
I WAS IN PROTECTIVE CUSTODY.
MY HUSBAND IS IN PRISON.
I HAD TO SEND MY SON AWAY.
YOUR DEAL WITH OLIVER
RUINED MY LIFE AND THE CITY'S.
ALL I'M ASKING OF YOU
IS TO HOLD UP
YOUR SIDE OF THE BARGAIN.
I'M SORRY
YOU WERE ATTACKED,
BUT IT'S NOT MY FAULT
YOUR HUSBAND'S IN PRISON.
IT WAS HIS CHOICE
TO PUT ON THAT HOOD,
AND IT WAS HIS CHOICE
TO TURN HIMSELF IN.
GO HOME.
ENJOY YOUR FREEDOM.
LEAVE THE CRIME
FIGHTING TO ME.
MY HUSBAND SPENT
THE LAST 6 YEARS
FIGHTING FOR
THE PEOPLE OF THIS CITY,
RISKING EVERYTHING,
AND NOW HE SITS IN PRISON,
HIS LIFE ON THE LINE,
WHILE THIS MONSTER
GETS TO WALK FREE.
THAT ISN'T JUSTICE.
WOW. I STILL CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU STABBED YOURSELF.
DID YOU HIT
ANYTHING BIG,
LIKE YOUR LIVER
OR SOMETHING?
RIGHT. YOU PROBABLY
DON'T EVEN HAVE A LIVER,
JUST MUSCLE.
YOU THINK I HAD
ANY OTHER CHOICE?
I DID WHAT YOU ASKED.
NOW TELL ME WHAT YOU
KNOW ABOUT DIAZ.
THAT WASN'T EXACTLY
WHAT I MEANT
BY GETTING RID OF YORKE.
WELL, I FOUND
A BETTER WAY.
HEH! HE STILL THINKS
HE'S A HERO.
YOU'RE A BIGGER IDIOT
THAN I THOUGHT.
BRICK: EASY, GENTS.
A DEAL'S A DEAL.
GETTING YORKE OFF OUR BACK
MEANS WE'RE IN BUSINESS.
THANKS TO QUEEN HERE,
WE'RE GONNA HAVE
ONE HELL OF A NIGHT.
WHERE IS DIAZ?
I DON'T KNOW,
BUT I DO KNOW WHO DOES.
THERE'S AN INFORMANT
HERE AT SLABSIDE.
ANYTHING THAT GOES ON HERE
GOES THROUGH THE DEMON FIRST.
-THE DEMON?
-YEAH.
THE PERSON WHO ARRANGED
THE HIT ON YOU
AND WHO'S THE DIRECT
CONNECTION TO DIAZ.
ALL I DID WAS HANDLE
THE TRANSACTION,
BUT SEEING AS HOW I'M
A MAN OF MY WORD,
I WILL ARRANGE THE MEETING.
YOU REALLY EXPECT ME
TO TRUST YOU?
YOU DON'T HAVE
MUCH CHOICE, NOW, DO YOU?
WHEN?
TONIGHT, CELL 3-B
AFTER LIGHTS OUT.
AND YOU WILL KNOW WHEN.
STALL ALL YOU WANT.
EVENTUALLY YOU'RE
GONNA BREAK.
AND WHEN YOU DO,
I'LL BE RIGHT HERE.
LAST CHANCE
BEFORE I BRING HER IN.
DID YOU OR DID YOU
NOT EAT THIS ENTIRE
BOX OF COOKIES?
IT'S OK, HONEY.
YOU JUST GOT A LITTLE
HUNGRY, DIDN'T YOU?
NOW YOU HAVE A TUMMY-ACHE.
WELL, NOW WE KNOW WHAT
HAPPENS WHEN WE
EAT TOO MUCH
SUGAR, RIGHT?
COME ON.
LET'S GO SAY HI TO ELLA.
SHE HAS LOTS OF
FUN STUFF PLANNED
WHILE DAD AND I
ARE OUT OF TOWN.
I WAS WORKING ON HIM
FOR 20 MINUTES.
YOU GET HIM TO
CONFESS IN 15 SECONDS?
I'M HIS MOTHER
AND YOUR BOSS.
WE LEAVE IN 5.
YEAH, PACKED AND READY.
OH. YOU DON'T SOUND
TOO HAPPY ABOUT THAT.
I JUST WISH WE
WOULD'VE CAUGHT DIAZ
BEFORE HEADING
ABROAD.
-WE WILL.
-YEAH.
AND FELICITY WILL
BE FINE, I PROMISE.
I THINK YOU COULD USE
A CHANGE OF SCENERY.
IT'LL BE LIKE
A SECOND HONEYMOON.
[IN MONOTONE]
YAY, WITH CURTIS.
[LAUGHTER]
WELL, DEADSHOT AND CUPID
CAME WITH US ON OUR FIRST.
NO, THAT IS NOT OUR
FIRST HONEYMOON.
OUR FIRST HONEYMOON
WAS IN HAWAII, REMEMBER?
THE HAMMOCKS
BY THE BEACH.
-HAWAII WAS NICE.
-HAWAII WAS REALLY NICE.
YOU KNOW, I THOUGHT IT'D
BE A LOT MORE DIFFICULT
WORKING WITH YOU.
BEING TOGETHER 24/7?
BUT ADVENTURE WAS
ALWAYS WHAT KEPT
US STRONG.
-DANGEROUS OPS.
-ROMANCE ON THE FRONT LINE.
-WE MAKE A GOOD TEAM.
-WE MAKE THE BEST TEAM.
RICARDO DIAZ TOOK OVER
A WHOLE CITY.
THEN WE DISMANTLED
HIS INFRASTRUCTURE.
HE'S NOT
AN IMMINENT THREAT.
HE'S GOT NEW ALLIES.
ONE OF THEM HACKED
INTO THE CDC's SECURE
NETWORK,
SPECIFICALLY THEIR
SECURITY PROTOCOLS.
THEY'RE PLANNING
SOMETHING.
YOU DEDUCED THAT
FROM THIS PHOTOGRAPH
AND ONE
UNSUBSTANTIATED HACK?
IT'S THE ONLY LEAD
WE GOT IN MONTHS,
AND YOU KNOW IT.
WE CAN'T LET THAT
SLIP AWAY.
THEN BRING ME SOMETHING
CONCRETE I CAN ACT ON.
CDC's SECURITY SYSTEM
IS AIRTIGHT.
NO ONE GETS IN
WITHOUT A LEVEL 5
SECURITY CLEARANCE.
I CAN'T WASTE
VALUABLE RESOURCES
ON SOMETHING
THIS CIRCUMSTANTIAL.
YOU MEAN SOMEONE WHO
DROPPED TO NUMBER 27
ON OUR
MOST WANTED LIST.
THAT, TOO.
TELL THE CDC THEY'VE
BEEN HACKED.
THEY CAN HANDLE IT
AS THEY SEE FIT.
I NEED YOUR FOCUS
ELSEWHERE, AGENT.
I GUESS HER HEART
ISN'T COMPLETELY
MADE OUT OF STONE.
BUGGING THE FBI...
MAYBE NOT THE BEST MOVE
FOR OUR IMMUNITY DEAL.
I'M GOING WITH
THE ASK FOR FORGIVENESS
INSTEAD OF
PERMISSION TYPE THING.
WHEN YOU SAID YOU WERE DONE
WITH THE A.R.G.U.S. WAY,
YOU WEREN'T JOKING.
JOHN HAS PRIORITIES OTHER
THAN CATCHING DIAZ. I DON'T.
I REALLY APPRECIATE YOU
WANTING TO HELP
AND LETTING ME SLEEP
ON YOUR COUCH,
WHICH IS A LOT MORE
COMFORTABLE THAN IT LOOKS.
I'VE BEEN DYING TO GET
THE BAND BACK TOGETHER
AND GET THAT
SON OF A BITCH DIAZ.
WHAT'S HE WANT
AT THE CDC?
FINDING THAT OUT IS
THE EASY PART.
WHAT'S THE HARD PART?
GETTING INTO THE CDC.
YOU HEARD THE BOSS MAN.
THE ONLY WAY WE GET IN THERE
IS WITH FEDERAL CLEARANCE.
[THUNDER]
[BUZZER SOUNDS]
[PRISONERS CHEERING]
WHERE ARE ALL THE GUARDS?
WHAT THE HELL IS HAPPENING?
NO IDEA.
BRICK HAS SOMETHING PLANNED.
JUST STAY HERE.
WHERE YOU GOING?
I NEED TO FIND SOMEONE.
I'M GONNA COME.
HEY, YOUR CELL IS
THE SAFEST SPOT
FOR YOU RIGHT NOW.
WITH ALL THESE MURDERY
GUYS ON THE LOOSE,
I'M STICKING
RIGHT BY YOUR SIDE.
FINE.
[TYPING ON KEYBOARD]
JOHN: THAT'S A LOT OF
FIREPOWER FOR A BANK.
THEY NEED IT. HALF OF
EUROPE'S CRIMINAL UNDERWORLD
FUNNELS THEIR MONEY
THROUGH HERE.
GUESSING
THAT'S A SHOOT FIRST,
ASK QUESTIONS NEVER
KIND OF BANK?
WHICH IS WHY THEY
CAN'T FIND OUT THAT
WE'RE WITH A.R.G.U.S.
OH. WHICH
THEY WON'T BECAUSE OF...
THIS.
I PRINTED IT TO BE
COMPLETELY IDENTICAL
TO THE REAL ONE,
EXCEPT FOR
THE NANOTECH-LACED PAINT
WHICH ALLOWS US
TO ACCESS THE BANK'S
FINANCIAL TRANSACTIONS.
HEH HEH. THAT'S
A CURTIS HOLT ORIGINAL.
I MEAN, COME ON.
THAT'S PRETTY COOL, RIGHT?
WELL, HOPEFULLY,
IT'S ENOUGH TO FOOL 'EM.
CURTIS: WELL, IT ONLY
NEEDS TO FOOL HIM...
PETER TIETJEN.
HE IS THE BANK MANAGER.
I HAVE YOU AN APPOINTMENT
SET UP WITH HIM ALREADY.
YOU GET THAT PAINTING
WITHIN 5 FEET
OF HIS COMPUTER
AND IT IS DINNER PARTY
DOWNLOAD TIME AT A.R.G.U.S.
I'M TALKING
AN ALL-YOU-CAN-EAT BUFFET
OF EVERY NAME, ACCOUNT,
SHADY BUSINESS TRANSACTION
THAT THAT BANK
HAS EVER CONDUCTED.
OOH! OOH! OOH! WHILE
YOU GUYS ARE IN THERE,
CAN YOU GET ME
A FREE TOASTER?
MR. AND MRS. ANDREWS,
THANK YOU FOR COMING IN.
MAY I SEE YOUR
REFERENCE LETTER,
PLEASE?
[UNZIPS BRIEFCASE]
THIS IS OUR
REFERENCE LETTER.
WE NEED A SAFE PLACE
TO STORE IT.
WE WERE TOLD YOU
COULD HANDLE THIS...
DISCREETLY,
OF COURSE.
I THINK YOU WILL
FIND OUR TERMS
MORE THAN
REASONABLE.
THAT'S IT!
SHOW ME THE MONEY.
[BEEPING]
WE HAVE UPLINK.
PETER: AFTER SIGNING
THE REQUISITE FORMS,
ALL WE REQUIRE IS
AN APPROVAL FROM
OUR IN-HOUSE APPRAISER.
IF YOU'LL EXCUSE ME.
TICK-TOCK, CURTIS.
WHAT'S OUR STATUS?
ZURICH, WE HAVE A PROBLEM.
I'M GETTING
EXTERNAL INTERFERENCE,
AND IT'S SLOWING DOWN
THE TRANSFER.
THIS IS SOFIE,
OUR APPRAISER.
IS THIS REALLY NECESSARY?
WE MUST AUTHENTICATE
THE ITEM
FOR INSURANCE
PURPOSES.
YOU UNDERSTAND?
MR. TIETJEN, THIS IS
A PRICELESS FAMILY HEIRLOOM.
I NEED TO DISCUSS
THE SECURITY OF YOUR VAULT.
CERTAINLY.
WE ARE VERY
EXPERIENCED
WITH THESE TYPES
OF SITUATIONS.
I'M SHUTTING DOWN COMS TO
OPEN BANDWIDTH. HANG TIGHT.
MR. TIETJEN...
[SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
COME ON.
DONE! GET THE HELL
OUT OF THERE.
THIS IS OUTRAGEOUS.
WE'RE TAKING OUR
BUSINESS ELSEWHERE.
MISSION ACCOMPLISHED.
IF THIS IS ILLEGAL, I DON'T
WANT TO KNOW ABOUT IT.
AW, D., WHY YOU ALWAYS
GOT TO EXPECT THE WORST?
WATSON: YOU MAKE IT
EASY, MR. RAMIREZ.
DINAH: OK, OK, WHAT THE
HELL IS GOING ON HERE?
WE KNOW HOW
TO GET DIAZ,
AND WE NEED
YOUR HELP.
I THOUGHT I MADE MYSELF
CLEAR, MS. SMOAK.
YOU DID. AND THEN
I FIGURED OUT
HOW TO SET A TRAP
AT THE CDC.
-HOW DID YOU KNOW ABOUT THIS...
-I BUGGED YOUR OFFICE.
-SEE... -I KNOW. I KNOW.
BUT HOLD THE LECTURE.
WE'RE ON
A TIME CRUNCH HERE.
I BACKTRACED
THE SILENCER'S HACK.
WAIT. WE'RE CALLING HER
THE SILENCER NOW?
-IT'S BETTER THAN THE BELT LADY.
-NOTED.
SHE'S BEEN CHECKING
INVENTORY
ON GLUTATHIONE
HYDRATE.
IT'S A BIOCOMPOUND
THAT HELPS PROTECT
RED BLOOD CELLS
AGAINST DISEASES
LIKE EBOLA
AND THE LASSA FEVER.
I MEAN, GOD KNOWS
WHAT CREEPY THING
DIAZ HAS PLANNED
FOR THAT,
AND THE ONLY PLACE
HE CAN GET IT IS
THE CDC.
YOU DO REALIZE THE CDC IS
A SECURE GOVERNMENT FACILITY.
THEY HAVE STRICT
PROTOCOLS, PROCE...
WHICH MAKES IT
THE PERFECT PLACE,
YOU KNOW,
TO SET A TRAP.
THE COMPOUND
IS BEING STORED
IN A BIOCONTAINMENT LAB.
DIAZ WALKS IN THERE,
I SEAL THE DOORS...
[SNAPS FINGERS]
HE'S LOCKED IN.
LIKE THAT ZOMBIE MOVIE...
OR ANY ZOMBIE MOVIE.
-AND WHEN IS THIS HAPPENING?
-TONIGHT.
A SHIPMENT
JUST CAME IN
FROM CENTRAL CITY.
WELL, I'LL PUT
A TEAM TOGETHER.
IF DIAZ GOES NEAR
THAT BUILDING, THE SCPD
WILL BE THERE WAITING.
IF DIAZ EVEN GETS
A WHIFF OF THE POLICE,
IT'LL SPOOK HIM.
[CHUCKLING]
OH, RIGHT. YOU WANT
TO DO IT THE VIGILANTE WAY.
WELL, YOU PROBABLY SHOULDN'T
HAVE INVITED HER.
RENE: NO CANARY,
NO WILD DOG. JUST US.
IT TECHNICALLY
WOULDN'T BE
OFF THE BOOKS
IF AGENT WATSON
COMES WITH US.
AND GO AGAINST MY BOSS'
DIRECT ORDER
TO STAY AWAY FROM THE CDC?
YOUR BOSS IS WRONG,
AND YOU KNOW IT.
BESIDES, SOMETHING
TELLS ME IF YOU
BROUGHT DIAZ IN,
ALL WOULD BE
FORGIVEN.
THAT'S A BIG "IF."
DIAZ HAS BEEN
A PLAGUE ON THIS CITY
AND ON OUR LIVES
FOR TOO LONG.
AND NOW WE HAVE
A CHANCE TO BRING
HIM DOWN.
WE HAVE TO TAKE IT.
IT'S BEEN 5 MONTHS.
THE SCPD HASN'T
CAUGHT HIM,
NEITHER HAS THE FBI,
NEITHER HAS A.R.G.U.S.
IT'S TIME TO TRY
ANOTHER WAY.
FINE.
BUT THIS IS A ONE-TIME
THING, UNDERSTAND?
AND IF ANYTHING FEELS OFF,
I PULL THE PLUG.
WHAT DO YOU SAY, D.?
[EXHALES]
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GO CATCH US
A DRAGON.
STANLEY: THIS IS LIKE
A HORROR MOVIE.
IT'S SO QUIET,
I CAN HEAR MY HEARTBEAT.
I'M GONNA BE
THE FIRST ONE TAKEN OUT.
IT WOULD NEVER BE YOU.
ALL RIGHT. IF YOU'RE
GONNA TAG ALONG,
DO IT A LITTLE MORE QUIETLY.
RIGHT. OK.
THERE'S 3-B.
NOT HERE!
SO WHAT DO WE DO,
JUST WAIT?
TURNER:
IT'LL BE A LONG WAIT.
WHERE'S THE DEMON?
HELL IF I KNOW.
[CHUCKLING]
YOU ACTUALLY THOUGHT BRICK
WAS GONNA HELP YOU?
WELL, BRICK GOT
WHAT HE WANTED,
AND NOW HE WANTS YOU DEAD.
YOU'RE NOT GOING ANYWHERE
UNTIL I GET SOME ANSWERS.
WE HAD A DEAL!
A DEAL THAT MEANS
NOTHING
NOW THAT BRICK
GOT WHAT HE WANTED.
WITH YORKE GONE,
WE'RE FINALLY FREE
TO HAVE SOME FUN.
BRICK'S GOT A GAME GOING ON
RIGHT NOW IN THE MESS HALL,
ALL THANKS TO YOU.
FIRST RULE
OF PRISON...
TRUST NO ONE.
AH, THE KID'S RIGHT.
NOW, HOW DID HE MANAGE
TO FIGURE THAT OUT
BEFORE YOU DID?
ALL RIGHT. SO BRICK WAS
LYING. THERE'S NO DEMON.
OH, THERE IS, BUT YOU
DON'T SUMMON THE DEMON.
THE DEMON SUMMONS YOU.
I THINK I'LL TAKE
MY CHANCES.
YOU'RE NOT GETTING THIS.
THE ONLY WAY TO THE
DEMON IS THROUGH BRICK.
THERE'S A SYSTEM.
THAT'S HOW
THIS PLACE WORKS.
WELL, LOOKS LIKE
I'M GONNA FORCE BRICK
TO MAKE GOOD ON HIS DEAL.
HMM. GOOD LUCK.
HIS PARTY'S
INVITE ONLY,
AND, UH, YOU'RE NOT
ON THE LIST.
I'M GUESSING YOU ARE.
GOOD EVENING.
SAMANDA WATSON, FBI.
I'M HERE TO PICK UP
SOME SECURITY ABSTRACTS.
YOU'RE WORKING LATE.
DAY GOT AWAY FROM ME.
YOU KNOW HOW IT IS.
DOOR TO THE RIGHT.
I'LL BUZZ YOU IN.
[BUZZER SOUNDS]
THE BIOCONTAINMENT LAB
SHOULD BE RIGHT HERE.
THIS IS IT.
SO ALL WE GOT TO DO
IS TRAP THEM INSIDE?
FELICITY: THAT'S THE IDEA.
WATSON: THERE'S A SERVER
ROOM DOWN THE HALL.
FELICITY AND I WILL
SET UP THERE.
FELICITY:
THE CAMERA'S ON A LOOP.
AS FAR AS DIAZ CAN TELL,
THE PLACE WILL BE EMPTY.
WE'LL COVER THE EXITS.
THIS IS QUITE
THE SET-UP.
WELL, THE CDC TAKES
THEIR SECURITY
A LOT MORE
SERIOUSLY THAN THE FBI.
NO OFFENSE.
NONE TAKEN. YOU THOUGHT
ABOUT GETTING INTO
CYBERSECURITY LEGALLY?
I HAVEN'T DONE LEGALLY
IN A VERY LONG TIME.
WHAT SCARED YOU OFF?
ALL THAT NASTY
DUE PROCESS?
YOU MEAN THE ROLLS
AND ROLLS OF RED TAPE?
NO, I JUST PREFER
TO SPEND MY TIME ACTUALLY
CATCHING CRIMINALS.
I KNOW THE LAW
ISN'T PERFECT.
IF IT WERE, DIAZ
WOULD BE IN PRISON,
WILLIAM WOULD BE AT HOME,
AND I WOULDN'T
JUMP 5 FEET
EVERY TIME I HEAR A
DOOR SLAM, BUT HERE WE ARE.
JUST BECAUSE
THE SYSTEM IS FLAWED
DOESN'T MEAN
IT SHOULDN'T EXIST.
EVEN SOMEONE LIKE
RICARDO DIAZ
NEEDS A LAWYER,
A FAIR TRIAL.
WE PROTECT THE
RIGHTS OF PEOPLE WHO
DON'T DESERVE THEM
BECAUSE IT'S THE
ONLY WAY TO PROTECT
THEM FOR EVERYONE.
AND YET HERE YOU ARE
TONIGHT GOING OFF-BOOK.
WELL, IT'S LIKE YOU
SAID BEFORE:
AS LONG AS I CUFF
A BAD GUY,
ALL IS FORGIVEN,
RIGHT?
AND THEN WE
GO GET JUSTICE THE
OLD-FASHIONED WAY...
IN COURT.
LET'S HOPE.
HEY, IS LYLA HERE?
NO. SHE STEPPED OUT.
WHAT'S UP?
UH, NOTHING. WELL,
OK. SOMETHING.
WELL, NOT
SOMETHING-SOMETHING
NECESSARILY
BUT PROBABLY...
SWISS CHOCOLATE?
HEH! CHOCOLATE
PRALINES.
I MEAN, THERE'S
NOTHING BETTER.
-CURTIS.
-OK.
REMEMBER
THAT INTERFERENCE
THAT HAPPENED
DURING OUR DOWNLOAD?
DON'T TELL ME YOU
LOST THE DATA.
DEPUTY DIRECTOR BELL'S
GONNA BE PISSED.
NO. THE OPPOSITE.
I THINK SOMEONE
DUPLICATED THE FILE
SIMULTANEOUSLY
AS WE DOWNLOADED IT.
THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
THE ONLY ONES WHO KNEW
ABOUT THIS OP WERE
ME, YOU, AND LYLA.
YEAH. AND JUDGING FROM
YOUR FACE, IT WASN'T YOU.
IT DEFINITELY WASN'T ME.
SO THAT ONLY LEAVES...?
WHY WOULD LYLA MAKE
A COPY OF THAT DATA?
MAYBE IT'S NOT
AS SHADY AS IT SEEMS.
WHY WOULD SHE HIDE
THIS FROM ME?
SOMETIMES SECRETS ARE
GOOD IN A MARRIAGE.
YOU KNOW, IT KEEPS
THE SPICE ALIVE.
ACTUALLY, DON'T
QUOTE ME ON THAT.
I'M ACTUALLY DIVORCED.
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?
FIND OUT WHY MY WIFE
IS LYING TO ME.
WHERE DO YOU
THINK THEY KEEP
THE DEAD RATS?
SO INHUMANE.
I GOT EYES ON DIAZ,
AND HE BROUGHT
TWO PSYCHOS WITH HIM.
ANY CHANCE THEY LEFT
THE THIRD ONE AT HOME?
IT'S DOUBTFUL. THE SILENCER
WOULDN'T WANT TO MISS THIS.
THEY'VE REACHED THE LAB.
[LOCK DISENGAGES]
HOLD UP. THE ZOMBIES
JUST WALKED RIGHT IN,
NO KEY CARD OR NOTHING.
THAT DOESN'T
MAKE ANY SENSE.
IT DOESN'T MATTER.
JUST LOCK THE DOORS.
[BUZZING]
FRAK. FRAK. FRAK. FRAK.
RENE: MAKE BETTER
SOUNDS, FELICITY.
WHATEVER'S OPENING
THAT DOOR IS JAMMING MY
ACCESS FREQUENCIES.
IT'S SOME SORT OF
SONIC DISRUPTION.
RENE: THE COMS ARE
STILL WORKING.
WELL, HOW ABOUT
I SAVE THE DETAILS
OF ACOUSTIC-INJECTION
CYBERATTACKS
FOR POST-MISSION
HAPPY HOUR?
THE SILENCER. SHE MUST'VE
BROUGHT A NEW TOY.
CAN YOU
TURN IT OFF?
I CAN'T HACK IT,
BUT I CAN TRACK IT.
SHE'S IN
THE NORTHEAST CORRIDOR,
HEADED TOWARDS
THE MECHANICAL ROOM.
I'M ON IT.
BUT ONCE I CATCH UP TO HER,
IT'LL BE RADIO SILENCE,
LITERALLY.
WHAT MY DARTS COULD DO
WITH ALL THIS STUFF!
YEAH, IF IT DOESN'T
KILL YOU FIRST.
I FOUND IT.
DIAZ IS PACKING UP.
WE GOT TO HURRY.
-TIME FOR PLAN "B."
-NO, NO, NO.
THAT'S A BIG OLD NEGATIVE.
MANUAL OVERRIDES ARE
IN THE BASEMENT.
AND, AGAIN,
NO LOCKS, NO ENTRY.
-I CAN'T LET DIAZ ESCAPE.
-WHAT ARE YOU, CRAZY?
YOU CAN'T BEAT THEM.
I DON'T HAVE TO.
I JUST GOT TO KEEP
THEM IN THAT ROOM
LONG ENOUGH
FOR YOU
TO LOCK THOSE DOORS.
I'M IN THE MECHANICAL ROOM.
[TANKS HISSING,
DEVICES CLANKING]
[SILENCE]
[MUFFLED GUNSHOTS]
FELICITY: UH, GUYS, JUST FYI:
A LOT OF THINGS IN THAT LAB
DON'T REACT NICELY TO GUNFIRE.
SO ONE STRAY BULLET,
AND THE WHOLE PLACE GOES BOOM.
FBI.
STOP RIGHT THERE.
AGENT WATSON,
I SEE YOU'RE REUNITED
WITH SOME OLD FRIENDS.
STEP AWAY
FROM THE COOLER, DIAZ,
AND PUT YOUR HANDS
IN THE AIR...
SLOWLY.
CAN YOU PLEASE
HANDLE THIS?
HYAH!
[SILENCE]
HYAH! HYAH! HYAH...
DIAZ: PLAY TIME'S OVER.
[GUNSHOTS]
LET'S GO!
THE SILENCER'S STILL HERE
IN THE MECHANICAL ROOM.
I'LL TAKE DIAZ.
YOU HELP DINAH.
[DISARMS SILENCER DEVICE]
THIS IS GONNA BE FUN.
[GRUNTS]
D.
I'M FINE.
GO! GO GET HER. GO!
DIAZ GOT AWAY.
-RENE, CAN YOU HEAR ME?
-YEAH, I HEAR YOU.
THE SILENCER'S THE ONLY
LEAD WE HAVE ON DIAZ.
WE CAN'T LET HER ESCAPE.
THE SILENCER GOT AWAY.
ON A SCALE OF
ONE TO UNEMPLOYMENT,
HOW MUCH TROUBLE IS SHE IN?
WELL, SHE WASN'T SUPPOSED TO
BE HERE IN THE FIRST PLACE;
DIAZ ESCAPED
WITH THE COMPOUND;
AND WE HAVE NO IDEA
WHERE OR HOW HE'S
PLANNING ON USING IT.
SO A LOT?
HEY, RENE SURE GOT OUT
OF HERE IN A HURRY.
WELL, CAN YOU BLAME HIM?
I MEAN, THE FBI AND HIM
DON'T EXACTLY
HAVE A LOVE-LOVE
RELATIONSHIP.
HOW BAD IS IT?
WHAT DO
YOU THINK?
I MEAN, THE SILENCER
WAS RIGHT THERE.
I DON'T
UNDERSTAND HOW HE
MANAGED TO LET
HER SLIP PAST US.
RENE MUST HAVE MISSED
HER BY SECONDS.
I HAVE TO GO. MY
BOSS IS WAITING FOR
ME AT THE OFFICE.
AGENT WATSON...
THANK YOU FOR TRYING.
BRICK'S GONNA BE
EXTRA PISSED TO SEE YOU.
HE THINKS YOU'RE DEAD.
OLIVER: WELL, HE'S
IN FOR A SURPRISE.
COME ON.
WHAT ARE WE
WALKING INTO?
BRICK WILL PROBABLY
HAVE PRISONERS POSTED
OUTSIDE THE MESS HALL.
YOU TALK US
PAST THEM.
AND IF YOU SAY
ONE WRONG WORD...
YEAH, SLASH GOES THE ARTERY.
YEAH, I GET IT.
YOU KNOW, IT'S NICE TO KNOW
THAT YOU'D SHIV YOURSELF
TO SAVE SOME HARDASS GUARD
BUT YOU HAVE NO PROBLEM
SHIVVING ME.
OLIVER:
WELL, YOU AMBUSHED ME.
YOU THINK I HAD
A CHOICE IN THAT?
BRICK CALLS
THE SHOTS.
IF I DON'T TRY
TO KILL YOU,
THEN BRICK KILLS ME.
EVERY MAN HERE IS
OUT FOR NUMBER ONE,
INCLUDING YOU.
EVERYTHING I DO IS
FOR MY FAMILY.
YOU'RE JUST OUT
FOR YOURSELF.
YOU THINK YOU
KNOW ME SO WELL.
YOU KNOW NOTHING
ABOUT ME.
I KNOW YOU MADE A DEAL
WITH CHINA WHITE
TO HAVE ME KILLED,
AND I KNOW YOU HELPED
STEAL A WEAPON
THAT BLEW UP
HALF THE GLADES.
WHAT ABOUT
MARKOVIA, 2014?
A KNOWN TERRORIST
NAMED GHOLEM QADIR.
OR DID YOU FORGET
I WAS PART OF
THE MISSION
THAT HELPED BRING
HIM DOWN?
A.R.G.U.S. PUT AN EXPLOSIVE
IN THE BACK OF YOUR NECK.
YOU DIDN'T HAVE A CHOICE.
OH, BUT I DID HAVE
A CHOICE
TO SAVE
YOUR FRIEND'S LIFE.
YEAH. LYLA
AND I WERE ALONE
WHEN QADIR TRIED TO
SLIT HER THROAT,
AND I DROVE MY BLADE
RIGHT THROUGH
HIS BACK.
JOHN NEVER TOLD ME IT WAS
YOU WHO SAVED HER LIFE.
YEAH, WHY WOULD HE?
YOU AND YOUR TEAM ONLY
SAW ME AS ONE THING...
THE ENEMY.
[SCOFFS]
BUT NOW LOOK AT US,
BOTH IN PRISON.
SO I GUESS WE'RE NOT
THAT DIFFERENT
AFTER ALL.
[SIGHS]
YOU FOLLOWED ME.
WELL, I WOULDN'T
HAVE HAD TO
IF YOU HAD TOLD ME
THE REAL REASON
WHY WE'RE
IN ZURICH, LYLA.
-IT'S NOT WHAT IT LOOKS LIKE.
-REALLY? THAT'S GOOD.
THAT'S GOOD, BECAUSE
IT LOOKS LIKE YOU
JUST HANDED OVER
SENSITIVE
A.R.G.U.S. INTEL
TO A CRIMINAL.
I THOUGHT YOU'D
HAVE A LITTLE
MORE FAITH
IN ME THAN THAT.
I DID UNTIL THIS
VERY MOMENT.
LYLA, JUST TELL ME
WHAT'S GOING ON...
THE TRUTH.
I CAUGHT WIND OF SOMETHING...
MONEY CHANGING HANDS
THAT'S...
THAT'S BIGGER THAN ANYTHING
WE'VE BEEN UP AGAINST.
I RAN IT UP THE CHAIN
BUT KEPT GETTING
STYMIED BY THE BRASS.
NOT ENOUGH EVIDENCE.
WHAT, SO YOU'RE GOING
BEHIND A.R.G.U.S.'s BACK?
I DIDN'T EXPECT JUDGMENT
FROM SOMEONE
WHO'S SPENT SO MUCH TIME
DELIVERING JUSTICE
IN THE SHADOWS.
OH, LYLA, THAT'S NOT
WHAT I'M SAYING.
LISTEN TO ME,
I JUST...I JUST
CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU WOULD HIDE
THIS FROM ME.
AFTER EVERYTHING
WE'VE BEEN THROUGH,
I THOUGHT THE ONE THING
WE AGREED ON IS THAT
THERE WILL BE NO MORE
SECRETS BETWEEN US.
I WAS TRYING
TO PROTECT YOU.
I WASN'T KEEPING SECRETS.
YOU DIDN'T WANT TO TAKE UP
OLIVER'S MANTLE,
AND I RESPECT THAT,
BUT BEING THE DIRECTOR
OF A.R.G.U.S. HAS SHOWN ME
THAT THERE IS FAR MORE EVIL
IN THE WORLD THAN PEOPLE
WILLING TO FIGHT IT.
AND I CAN'T STAND AROUND
ANYMORE AND JUST WATCH.
JOHNNY, SOMETIMES YOU
HAVE TO CROSS THE LINE
FOR THE GREATER GOOD.
I WOULD EXPECT YOU
TO UNDERSTAND THAT.
TWO PRISONERS GUARDING
THE MESS HALL DOOR,
JUST LIKE TURNER SAID.
YOU'RE UP.
GET ME IN THERE OR ELSE.
[RIPS CLOTH]
STEP ASIDE, FELLAS.
GREEN ARROW'S JOINING
OUR LITTLE GAME.
YOU KIDDING?
WE CAN'T LET
QUEEN IN HERE.
YOU'D BETTER. HE'S VIP.
THE HIGH ROLLERS WILL BE
VERY HAPPY TO SEE HIM.
[KNOCK KNOCK]
[KNOCK]
YOU'RE COMING IN THERE
WITH ME.
GOOD. I'D HATE
TO MISS ALL THE FUN.
[PRISONERS CHEERING]
-WHOO!
-YEAH!
BRICK: GENTLEMEN, GENTLEMEN,
IT SEEMS WE HAVE AN UNEXPECTED
TREAT FOR YOU THIS EVENING...
AN EPIC, ONCE-IN-A-LIFETIME
MATCH-UP:
OUR CHAMPION, SAMPSON,
VERSUS THE GREEN ARROW!
[CHEERING]
I KIND OF WISH WE
STAYED OUTSIDE.
NO. I DON'T HAVE
TIME FOR THIS.
WHERE YOU GOING,
ARROW?
OH, YOU'RE WAY TOUGHER
THAN THIS GUY.
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
TIME FOR A REMATCH?
LAST TIME DIDN'T END
SO WELL FOR YOU.
THIS TIME,
I'M GONNA KILL YOU.
BRICK: GENTLEMEN,
PLACE YOUR BETS.
THIS IS GONNA BE A HELL
OF A PAY DAY.
-YEAH!
[MEN SPEAKING EXCITEDLY]
OW! UH!
THAT'S IT, SAMPSON. HIT HIM.
YOU GOT THIS, OLIVER!
YES!
[GROANS]
[BONES CRACK]
YIELD!
NEVER.
[BONES CRACK]
[SPECTATORS GROANING]
THAT WAS AWESOME.
BRICK: WHAT A PERFORMANCE.
I'LL LET YOU IN ON A SECRET,
QUEEN.
MY MONEY WAS ON YOU.
YOU'RE A HARD MAN TO KILL.
[PRISONERS CHEERING]
[RIFLES ARE ARMED]
STAND DOWN!
NO MORE GAMES.
TELL ME WHERE
TO FIND THE DEMON.
BRICK...
DON'T MAKE ME ASK
YOU AGAIN.
[CHUCKLES]
I'VE HAD YOU RUNNING AROUND,
PLAYING FETCH FOR ME
LIKE MY GRANDMOTHER'S
SPRINGER SPANIEL.
AND YOU KNOW THE BEST PART?
YOU'LL NEVER GET
TO THE DEMON,
'CAUSE YOU'RE ON
THE WRONG LEVEL.
THE DEMON IS ON LEVEL 2,
THE PLACE FOR THE WORST
OF THE WORST.
AND THAT JUST ISN'T YOU NOW.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT, ARROW?
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
OLIVER, YOU GOT
A PLAN, RIGHT?
STOP WORRYING ABOUT ME.
JUST TRY TO KEEP
YOUR HEAD DOWN.
MAYBE LEVEL 2 ISN'T AS BAD
AS EVERYONE SAYS.
AS LONG AS IT GIVES ME
WHAT I WANT,
I DON'T CARE.
[EXHALES]
YOU WERE NEVER GONNA BE
ABLE TO STAY A HERO...
NOT IN THIS PLACE.
[KNOCK KNOCK]
THANKS FOR COMING.
I'M GUESSING YOU DIDN'T
CALL ME IN TO TELL ME
YOU'RE GETTING PROMOTED.
HA HA. I'VE BEEN
REASSIGNED.
DESK JOCKEY JOB
BACK IN D.C.
AND I'M GUESSING THAT NEW
GIG TAKES YOU FAR AWAY
FROM THE DIAZ INVESTIGATION.
THAT'S THE IDEA.
I HOPE YOU'RE NOT
EXPECTING ME TO APOLOGIZE.
I'M NOT. I KNEW
I WAS PUTTING MY
CAREER ON THE LINE
WHEN I AGREED
TO WORK WITH YOU
AND YOUR TEAM.
I BELIEVE THAT GOOD
LAW ENFORCEMENT
DOES MAKE UP FOR
THE BAD,
AND I ALWAYS WILL.
BUT GOING OFF THE BOOKS
TO CATCH DIAZ?
THAT WAS THE RIGHT
THING TO DO.
YOU DON'T DESERVE
TO LIVE WITHOUT
YOUR FAMILY.
YOU'RE A GOOD PERSON,
FELICITY.
HMM.
I NEVER THOUGHT I'D HEAR
MYSELF SAY THIS,
BUT I'M VERY SORRY TO SEE
YOU GO, AGENT WATSON.
I'M SORRY DIAZ
AND HIS CREW GOT AWAY.
I MEAN, THINGS WOULD'VE
TURNED OUT DIFFERENT
IF WE'D GOTTEN
AT LEAST SOMETHING ON
THAT SON OF A BITCH.
I KNOW. I KNOW.
I'M WITH YOU.
SQUARE ONE SUCKS.
YOU READY?
TO GET HOME TO J.J. AND OUT
OF THIS HOTEL ROOM? YES.
CAN WE TALK FIRST?
-TALK OR LECTURE?
-LYLA, I'M SORRY.
I WAS WRONG.
I SHOULD'VE GIVEN
YOU THE CHANCE
TO EXPLAIN YOURSELF
BEFORE ACCUSING YOU
OF BEING SOMETHING
THAT YOU ARE NOT.
I KNOW THINGS HAVE
BEEN HARD FOR YOU
WITH OLIVER GONE, BUT
YOU HAVE TO TRUST ME.
I DO TRUST YOU,
BUT, LYLA,
ALL OF THIS,
IT'S SO DANGEROUS.
I THINK OF J.J.
SO DO I, WHICH IS WHY I
CAN'T TURN MY BACK ON THIS.
YOU WERE RIGHT.
[INHALES AND EXHALES]
SOMETIMES YOU DO HAVE
TO CROSS THE LINE.
JUST PROMISE ME,
NEXT TIME
SOMETHING LIKE THIS
HAPPENS...
LET ME IN.
I PROMISE.
RENE: THIS WAS
A BAD IDEA.
FELICITY: WE DIDN'T
HAVE A CHOICE.
LISTEN, I'M NOT
A SUPER FAN OF
AGENT WATSON,
BUT WE GOT HER
IN TROUBLE.
WE DIDN'T MAKE HER
DO ANYTHING.
WE'VE BEEN SITTING
AND WAITING
FOR THE LAW TO CATCH
DIAZ FOR MONTHS.
I AM TIRED OF WAITING.
I GET THAT, BUT...
ISN'T THIS KIND OF
WHAT WE'VE BEEN
DOING THE WHOLE TIME,
STEPPING IN WHEN
THE SYSTEM FAILS?
ISN'T THAT SORT OF
A VIGILANTE M.O.?
SOMETIMES YOU HAVE TO
CROSS THE LINE FOR THAT.
LISTEN, NOBODY BELIEVES
IN THAT MORE THAN ME.
I'M JUST NOT SURE THAT'S
WHAT THIS IS.
[BEEPING]
THEY GOT HONOR.
SHE'S A BIG GIRL.
SHE CAN TAKE CARE
OF HERSELF.
EVER SINCE I WAS BLOWN
OFF THAT ROOF...
ALL I'VE FELT IS PAIN...
[CAP DROPS TO DESK]
DIAZ: THE PAIN OF BETRAYAL,
THE PAIN OF HAVING EVERY
BONE IN MY BODY SHATTERED...
WHEN I HIT THE WATER.
BUT I DIDN'T PANIC.
I WAS PATIENT.
[TAPS SYRINGE]
AND THAT PATIENCE
HELPED ME TO FIND A WAY
TO TRANSFORM THAT PAIN...
INTO SOMETHING ELSE.
[SYRINGE DROPS TO DESK]
AHA! HUH!
STRENGTH.
[BUZZER]
LET'S GO, 4587.
YOU'RE GOING
DOWNSTAIRS.
BRICK: HAVE FUN DOWN THERE.
I HEAR THE ONLY WAY OUT OF
LEVEL 2 IS THROUGH THE MORGUE.
MAN: GREG, MOVE YOUR HEAD!