Hello, Oliver. Nice timing.
I think you're going to need
much bigger arrows.
Wow.
Cool.
You know, I didn't even mean to do that.
I turn steel arrows into dust,
and you thought lead would do the trick?
He's not human anymore.
Oh, I'm still human. Just better.
Doesn't give you the right
to remake the world.
Why not? It's been done before.
Noah and the flood.
People even worship the responsible party.
(GRUNTS)
(BOTH GROANING)
This might smart, though.
(RUMBLING)
I'm pulling the oxygen out of your bodies,
molecule by molecule,
but here's the good news.
I'm not going to kill you.
Well, not right now, at least.
Instead, I'm going to
regain control of Rubicon.
That way, when the whole world
goes all Dr. Strangelove,
you can feel your skin
melt from Armageddon.
(GROANING)
Oliver, let's go!
Come on! We gotta go, now!
(MUTTERING) Come on.
What happened here?
Too bad. I liked him for you.
Where's Machin?
I... I don't know.
He disappeared, okay?
I wasn't paying attention.
Why do I have trouble believing you?
(GRUNTS)
THEA: Let go of me!
Not to sound too much like your father,
but I really think you need a timeout.
Government officials
couldn't confirm the death toll.
However, various reports
place the number in the tens of thousands.
Evacuation efforts
of the surrounding areas continue...
(TURNS OFF TV)
What are you doing?
We can't afford to get caught up
in grief right now.
Now, I've bought us 24 hours
by sending Rubicon's launch algorithms
into an infinite loop,
but if we can't find a more permanent...
God, what am I doing? (SNIFFLES)
-It's okay, sweetheart.
-Don't "sweetheart" me.
You don't get to do that,
but you're right.
I can't get wrapped up in this.
(KNOCKING)
(SIGHS)
Have you been watching the news?
I can't stop.
Ironically, last week my mom was giving me
a hard time about living in Star City.
Between the earthquakes,
the viral attacks,
the homicidal super soldiers,
why would anyone want to live here?
It turns out we live in
only the second worst place in America.
Curtis.
Oh. I'm sorry.
I didn't realize you had company.
This is my father. Noah Kuttler.
Noah Kuttler. Huh.
You know, it's funny
because there's this super hacker
who's wanted by the FBI
whose name is also Noah Kuttler.
He's kind of a big deal
on the Dark Web. (CHUCKLES)
Honestly, I thought they could have used
a more flattering photo
for the wanted poster.
Wait, you...
You're the Noah Kuttler? (GASPS)
And, if you're Felicity's dad,
you were married to Donna...
And you make so much more sense now.
Yup.
This is... It was a big mystery.
I was trying to figure out,
like, how Felic...
-FELICITY: Yeah.
-Yeah.
We have work to do.
HIVE was behind the Havenrock explosion.
They stole a cyberweapon called Rubicon
and now are using it
to commandeer the world's nukes.
So, we have less than 24 hours to stop it,
or the world is going to
experience the sequel to WarGames.
Actually, there was
a direct-to-DVD sequel in 2008,
but it was a bomb, too,
so, that reference still holds.
(CELL PHONE CHIMES)
I have to go.
Don't worry.
Me and your fugitive dad have got this.
He says, just realizing
he said that out loud.
Today was supposed to be Christmas,
and I woke up to a lump of coal.
Is it because I've been
naughty this year? (CHUCKLES)
It's because Kuttler and his daughter
are wrestling us for Rubicon.
DARHK: Which is why
I felt the need to up our game.
Mr. Seldon, pleasure to see you.
Do you know what the best part
about leading a prison break is?
A long list of criminals that owe you.
Amar, Brickwell, and now Mr. Seldon.
-It's like one-stop shopping for thugs.
-I'm a hacker, not a thug.
Ohh. Turns out he and Ms. Smoak
have a history.
Just your typical boy meets girl,
boy falls in love with girl,
boy goes to jail for girl.
Boy tries to kill girl for money.
Speaking of thugs,
we have a new problem at Tevat Noah.
Not this guy again.
Don't worry, darling.
I'm dealing with him.
Give Mr. Machin my love, my love.
It's beginning to look
a lot like Christmas.
A long-range ballistic KN-08 missile
was responsible
for the nuclear blast at Havenrock.
The Pentagon has not further commented.
What's going on?
What the hell happened in Havenrock?
Darhk happened.
This city is starting to panic.
Are they right to?
Felicity's got it under control,
but, my wife
and her top secret government agency's
looking for a more permanent solution.
I cannot get in touch with Thea!
-It's okay. She got a hold of me.
-All right.
Thanks for not being dead.
Aren't we all going to be
if you're away from your computer?
Curtis and Kuttler are
dealing with Rubicon.
What did Thea say?
Do you know where she is?
-It's not good news. HIVE has her.
-(OLIVER GROANS)
-Do you have a location?
-I'm tracing a signal.
I should have taken more processors
from Palmer Tech on my way out.
They made a mistake letting you go.
They'll see it.
And if they don't,
I'm taking revenge plan suggestions.
Got it. Thea's message came from
the intersection of Berkeley and Childers
right in the heart of the Glades.
I thought you said
Thea and her boyfriend went out of town.
I thought they did.
Let's go.
-I'm coming with you.
-I want you to stay here.
If this gets worse, the city's going to
need someone to listen to
that they can trust.
(PANTING) What is it? Say something.
Your eyes were glowing.
Like Reiter?
(SOFTLY) Oh, my God.
-Oliver, what's happening to me?
-It doesn't matter.
We will figure it out,
but for now we have to keep moving.
All right? Come on.
(SCREAMS)
Oliver!
(BREATHING DEEPLY)
It's incredible.
I know now why Reiter sought this power.
When you furrow your brow like that,
you look just like Moira.
Don't you dare talk about my mother.
Fine. Let's talk about the future instead.
Genesis is coming.
With Machin running around,
we can't have
another X-factor on the loose.
"We"? Not your HIVE overlords?
Point being, I need your word
that you won't cause any trouble.
Or what?
Or I will have to do something
to assure your compliance
that I really don't want to do.
Well, when there's
something I don't want to do,
I just get it over with.
This will make everything better.
(RADIO BEEPS)
GREEN ARROW: Overwatch,
are you sure this is the spot?
There's nothing here.
FELICITY: That's impossible.
Okay, not impossible,
but my backtrace on Thea's message
has a 99.9999% accuracy rate,
so, unless this is part
of the .0001 percentile...
GREEN ARROW: It's just an empty street.
Just look for anything
out of place, all right?
Whatever HIVE has built
is probably recent, you know, new.
Is there supposed to be
sewer access on the street?
FELICITY: Not according to city plans.
Stand by.
RUVÉ: Help me with something, Malcolm.
How is it again that
this juvenile annoyance, Lonnie Machin,
is still a problem for us?
-Machin is exactly what we...
-Actually, I've changed my mind.
I'm not interested in excuses,
just results.
(WALKIE-TALKIE BEEPING)
Yes?
WOMAN: Two hostiles have
breached the southeast entrance,
one in green, the other in black.
(SIGHS) Send a squad
and secure the entrance.
Green and black.
Oliver's come for his baby sister,
most likely.
Mmm. And, since she's only here
because of you,
I believe that makes
Mr. Queen your problem.
You have a lot on your plate, Malcolm.
I suggest you get started.
Come on, sweetie.
SPARTAN: How did HIVE build all this
without anyone knowing?
GREEN ARROW: Well,
doesn't hurt having someone
controlling the city's infrastructure.
Can't find any public blueprints on file
for an underground lair
with a creepy sewer entrance.
GREEN ARROW: Believe me,
there are no public blueprints for this.
Unbelievable.
SPARTAN: Just like Mount Weather.
Continuity of government facility
built by FEMA during the Cold War,
in case of a nuclear attack.
I think that we found the ark
that HIVE's been building.
(COMPUTER BEEPING)
-What?
-I lost their signal.
Well, get it back.
(CELL PHONE CHIMES)
I have to get back to Curtis and Kuttler.
(SIGHS) All right. I'll cover comms.
I hear anything, I'll patch you in.
What's the emergency?
Is Rubicon still stabilized?
Where is Kuttler? Did he do something?
Did he... Are you drinking a beer?
I knew that being
a child of divorce was hard,
but what I did not have any idea about
was all the yelling,
the name-calling, the loudness.
-You poor thing.
-Uh... Oh.
-What are you talking about?
-Oh, God, do you even listen?
So, I'm here to take her away from you?
DONNA: My God, you just...
Yada, yada. My brain...
-Honestly, my brain is numb.
-Can we not with her here? She's here.
This really is the end of the world.
It actually does the opposite.
Baby, I've been so worried about you.
Oh, my God.
Do you know I have called?
I have called you a million times, baby.
I have been calling and calling.
-Are you okay?
-Mom, I'm fine.
Just been a little distracted.
With your father?
Thanks for telling me.
I don't know.
Everything just happened so fast.
What has?
Sit down.
What? What?
I have to tell you something.
(GASPS)
I'm going to be a grandma!
-I'm going to be a grandma! (SQUEALS)
-No, no, no. No, you're not.
I knew you had more than
a bad burrito the other day.
-I knew it was more than that.
-(DONNA AND CURTIS LAUGH)
-Okay. No...
-Baby! Baby!
I am not pregnant.
Is that the only news
that a woman can have?
The world is under attack,
and I need my fa...
I need Noah to help me stop it.
Honey, what happened
in Havenrock is horrible,
but, that doesn't mean
the world is going to end.
-She's telling the truth.
-You know, I know...
Which she clearly gets
from my side of the family, thank you.
You know, I know
when my daughter is lying, okay?
There were plenty of times
when she was a teenager,
not that you would know.
Here we go.
For once, this isn't about you, Dee.
Oh, you're calling me "Dee"?
-There are nuclear missiles...
-Are you calling me "Dee"?
Somebody stick something sharp in my eye.
It is going to happen to the entire world.
Unless we stop it, which we will.
Sweetie, why do you even think
this is something that you can...
Because I work with the Green Arrow, Mom.
-For how long?
-Three years.
And you've been keeping this from me?
Yes.
Wow, I guess you and your father
are more alike than I thought.
-Mom.
-We can talk about it later, hon,
after you save the world.
NOAH: Get in here.
FELICITY: Oh!
NOAH: Yeah.
The world's two best hackers side by side.
This is history. (CHUCKLES)
I mean, it's... It's no biggie.
What just happened?
Oh, my God.
SPARTAN: It's crazy. Take away
the psychos in the smocks...
GREEN ARROW: ...might as well be Ivy Town.
Everyone looks so happy.
Happy's when you're mindless
on some little yellow pill.
Let's just assume
we weren't invited over for casserole.
What's our play?
We split up and find Thea.
Scope the houses on the north.
I'll head south.
Good afternoon.
Today is a brisk and sunny 75 degrees.
It is a lovely day to be outside.
As we all enjoy Tevat Noah, I want to
take this moment to express my gratitude.
And, I want to thank each and every one...
I've got eyes on Thea.
Fourth house down.
There are two hostiles with her.
(GROANS)
Speedy, let's get you out of here.
Are you all right?
(GRUNTS)
I have the intruder.
Move, and I will kill you.
-Thea...
-Don't move.
Listen to me.
You're not thinking clearly.
In her defense,
she's a little drugged at the moment.
I should have taken your head.
That's always been your problem.
An inability to do what is necessary.
Laurel is dead because of you.
What are you going to do?
We've already established
you're not going to kill me.
(GUN FIRING)
(GROANS)
-What the hell?
-It's the yellow pills.
Son of a bitch.
(HIVE SOLDIERS SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
We got to go. Let's move!
(GUNFIRE)
(GROANS)
(GUNFIRE CONTINUES)
Not that it's not scintillating
to watch you type,
but when exactly will I have Rubicon back?
Hacking isn't as easy as waving your hand.
Ah. Point taken.
So, you and Felicity Smoak.
I just don't see it.
She used to be a lot different.
All clear. Looks like
we bought ourselves a few minutes.
John, this place is enormous.
I don't know how we're going to find Thea.
Just have to make sure
that the Ghosts don't find us.
So much for clear.
We're not going to hurt you.
Then what are the weapons for?
There's a woman
being held against her will.
We're just here to bring her home.
Citizens of Tevat Noah,
I have disturbing news.
We are under attack
from a man in a green hood
and another in a black helmet.
Do not let them disrupt Genesis.
These individuals
are not only an affront to our home,
but to our future
and the futures of our children.
Find them and kill them.
OLIVER: Oh, no.
It's okay, Oliver. (BREATHING DEEPLY)
I know what to do now.
I finally understand
what Reiter was after.
OLIVER: Taiana, Reiter was insane.
TAIANA: Why?
He said after his village was destroyed,
he would never be powerless again.
I have a village, too, Krasnoyarsk,
run by a government strongman named Kovar.
Taiana...
Now I know
why fate has led me to this place.
To give me the strength to free my home.
Okay. All right.
You'll go back to Russia,
and you can take on this Kovar.
But right now there are people here
that need our help.
What would Vlad want you to do?
What would your brother expect you to do?
Find these hostiles at once.
Nothing can be permitted
to stand in the way of Genesis.
Thank you.
I'm not sure murdering vigilantes is what
your loyal supporters signed up for.
Well, you better hope that
they don't find Mr. Queen and Mr. Diggle
before you do, Malcolm,
or I'll be forced to seriously question
what your purpose here is.
Every time I knock down a firewall,
five more pop back up.
It would seem that Mr. Darhk
has a counter-hacker in his employ.
-And he's good.
-Yeah.
Okay. I might have something.
Now, until the FBI gets their way,
smartphones are protected by encryption.
If you don't enter your passcode
after enough times,
then the device bricks itself, right?
Curtis, I don't even have the time
to tell you that I don't have the time.
You just did. But, here's the point.
Instead of trying
to break Rubicon's encryption...
We make it stop working
in the first place.
You're suggesting
as it is with a smartphone.
We overload Rubicon
with too many access requests.
And it shuts itself down.
Unfortunately, I doubt very much
that A.R.G.U.S.
would leave Rubicon so vulnerable
to such a brute force attack.
Let them try.
You're always such a stick in the mud.
Yes!
Let's all take hacking advice
from a woman whose only use
for her smartphone is as a mirror.
(DONNA LAUGHS SARCASTICALLY)
So funny. Not.
Felicity may have gotten
her brains from you,
but she got her creativity from moi.
Matching lipstick
to lip liner isn't creativity.
And, while I may
not be father of the year...
Oh, try the past two decades.
I recently took a bullet for our daughter.
Not metaphorically, either.
-By the way, a metaphor, it's a...
-Oh, I know what a metaphor means,
just like I know what abandoning
your family looks like.
Really? Because I remember
not having much of a choice in the matter.
(COMPUTER BEEPS)
CURTIS: Uh... Felicity?
COOPER: Hello, Felicity.
-Remember me?
-Cooper.
Your system is now under my control,
just like Rubicon will be
in the next five minutes.
Once again, you lose.
-Oh, frak.
-Frak.
Who is this guy, again?
Cooper Seldon, her ex-boyfriend.
How could I forget?
I thought he was dead,
and he just came back evil.
Oliver, Dr. Palmer, this guy.
You really have
a complicated romantic history.
Not the best time, Curtis.
Be honest, Felicity, hacker to hacker.
You prefer it this way, don't you?
As it was meant to be?
Once more unto the breach.
Is he seriously going
full Star Trek VI on you?
He shut our system down with a virus.
-It's an X-axis binumeric algorithm.
-I know.
I created it in college. Wait.
How did you know?
Just because I wasn't in your life
doesn't mean
I wasn't keeping tabs on my daughter.
He's sending electrical surges
to all our previous IPs!
(DONNA SCREAMING)
Whatever it is, it's working.
It is, but it's pinging back
to his location.
You thinking what I'm thinking?
We hitch our own code onto the back trace.
Curtis, your Rubicon lockout...
How long till you can get me
an executable?
-Uh... Twenty seconds.
-Great.
(DONNA WHIMPERING)
If this works, it will send the latest
surge back to its point of origin,
triggering Rubicon to lock itself out.
I have no idea what you're talking about.
Just get the son of a bitch.
Locked and loaded.
Got you.
(RUMBLING)
-Oh, no.
-What is it?
To be, or not to be...
(ALARM BLARING)
CURTIS: Did it work?
-I think it worked.
-It worked.
Well, the power's still on.
That's... That's good, right?
Rubicon's offline.
(ALL LAUGHING)
He's going to need more
than some third-rate hacker
to get it back up again,
all because of you, sweetheart.
Thanks, Dad.
Mom?
Streets are filled.
Ruvé's mobilized the entire ark
looking for us.
They're in here! (GROANS)
Quiet.
You can't win. You can't stop Genesis.
Well, what are you going to do when you're
not here to enjoy your brave new world?
Spartan.
Easy.
He almost got us killed.
They're like Thea.
They're not in their right minds.
MAN: You mean the pills?
We haven't taken any. Not even one.
None of us have.
We're here because we believe.
Because we know
the world is evil and darkness.
It's beyond saving.
How can you believe that?
Because we've lived it. Every day.
(SCOFFS)
So many promises
were made to save the city.
But it all just fell apart,
and we were the ones left in the rubble.
Damien Darhk has given us hope.
Can you with your masks and your guns
actually say the same?
(SCREAMS)
(GUNFIRE)
(GROANS)
There's a plane due east.
Stay here. We'll hold off Reiter's men.
Taiana, help me with this guy. He's alive.
Hey. He's alive. Help me with him.
He's too bad.
He'll only slow us,
help us from keeping the others.
We're not just going to leave him here.
You're right.
-Hey, hey, hey, hey! What are you doing?
-His death is inevitable.
Why waste his life
when it can make me stronger?
What are you doing with my clothes?
When I get stressed, I... I like to fold.
Yeah.
I know. When you two were married,
it was like living at the Gap.
Hey, what did Noah mean when he said
that he didn't have much choice
in the matter when he left?
(EXHALES)
I always just assumed he disappeared.
(SIGHS) He didn't disappear, hon.
I did.
We did.
I had a seven-year-old daughter,
and I know all about gambling,
and I wasn't willing to take the bet
that your father could possibly change.
You let me believe that he abandoned us.
Well, I don't...
(SIGHS)
I don't know what to say about that, hon.
I mean, I think...
I think he just didn't
want you to lose your mom, too.
Hey, look at me.
I didn't lose you.
Did I?
Never.
I'm sorry.
(OLIVER SIGHS)
Do you ever think
that maybe Darhk has a point?
No, Darhk is psychotic.
Everyone down here is.
Are they?
He's not wrong.
The world is coming apart
just like Star City.
I mean, it is worse than it has ever been.
That's because Darhk's been
spending the past year trying to kill it.
Then why is he giving these people
more hope than we ever could?
(KNOCKING)
Go! Go to the bedroom! Take cover!
Go! Move, move, move!
I'll hold them off. Go find Thea. Go, now!
Thea.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
This isn't you, Thea.
They are trying to control you.
But you are stronger than that.
You can fight through it.
I can't.
Yes, you can!
Every day, we stand side by side
to protect this city,
and no matter how dark or how hopeless,
you always keep fighting,
you never give up!
I refuse to believe
that you're going to give up now.
So, fight!
Drug me again,
and I will kill you, you son of a bitch.
Hi, everyone.
Uncle Lonnie here.
See, I just absolutely adore
your little community.
It's so welcoming to outsiders.
But it's so structured.
Going to have to fix that.
Mr. Darhk, remember me?
The loyal servant you rejected, betrayed?
In 20 minutes, I'm going to kill someone.
It can be your wife...
But, Damien, you're my first choice.
Ball's in your court, buddy.
Oh, and be quick about it,
because in 21 minutes,
I'm going to blow your
little underground world into next week.
Okay?
SPARTAN: So, Machin is down here?
An ongoing pest we've yet to exterminate.
Yeah, he killed Alex, who brought me here
because Ruvé drugged him
just like you did to me.
We can discuss
my parenting philosophy later.
Mr. Machin is the immediate threat.
To Darhk and his wife,
and I still don't understand
why we should care.
Because he has already tried once
to kill everyone down here.
GREEN ARROW: Malcolm's right.
We're not letting anyone else die.
This place isn't safe.
I need you to get your family out of here
in order to protect them.
Please.
Now, you know the way out.
So, if we can't stop Machin,
then you are going to lead the evacuation.
I don't recall volunteering.
And even if I did,
where exactly would I evacuate them to?
Everything above our heads
is going to be under a mushroom cloud.
I refuse to believe that.
Because you're a fool.
Because I have hope.
Let's go.
Taiana... (GRUNTS)
I am not just going to
let you kill this man.
I'm the only one who can stop Reiter.
This is how.
I need that man's power.
Listen to yourself. This isn't you.
Whatever that idol is doing,
it is warping your mind!
No. I've never been clearer.
Now, get out of my way!
(GROANS)
No, don't!
(NECK SNAPPING)
(SIGHS)
Déjà vu all over again.
You as the bait,
me waiting to kill your husband.
You know, I really hope
I get it right this time.
You have no idea
the power that you're up against.
Look at you.
No longer the whimpering victim.
Mommy's so strong and impressive.
Isn't she?
You do realize
that you're planning to destroy
the last safe place
left on the entire planet, right?
I'm sorry.
Did I leave you with the impression
that I was a rational guy?
(ARROW WHIZZING)
(GROANS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
That's my mommy.
Isn't she pretty?
Oh, and she brought her friends.
This is over.
LONNIE: More like under.
I tinkered with the engineering here.
This whole place is powered
by a dwarf star alloy.
Very powerful, but a little touchy.
So, you might want to
be careful where you aim
because a stray shot
could blow this whole place.
We're not letting you out of here.
Oh.
Well, in that case...
(GASPS)
(ALL GRUNTING)
Unless you want to die, let's go! Go!
Let's go!
Bye, Mommy.
I got you. Come on. Come on.
There's no time.
Save my daughter.
Please.
Promise me.
I promise.
We need to get out of here,
like, right now.
Finally, Electric Boogaloo awakes.
Sir, there's something
happening at Tevat Noah.
Well, it looks like the real estate value
of the Glades just went up.
It is called gallows humor.
What about everybody else?
(SIGHS) I saw Merlyn
leading some evacuations.
There must be other access points.
Or Malcolm's underneath all that.
What about her?
Is anyone there?
Green Arrow, Spartan, Speedy?
Hell, I'd take Malcolm Merlyn
at this point.
We're all safe.
Where are you with Rubicon?
HIVE is locked out. We're good.
The city is safe...
You sound like
there's a "but" to that sentence.
People still need saving.
They still need hope.
Give it back!
Taiana, if you want it back,
you're going to have to kill me.
And I'm betting you won't.
And what about me, Mr. Queen?
And after killing you,
I'll kill her.
Tell me.
It was Machin. He's...
Ruvé?
I'm sorry.
My daughter?
We're still getting reports of survivors.
We're locked out of Rubicon.
Momentarily.
I know someone who can get us back online.
Damien...
Tevat Noah is gone.
It's buried under miles of ash.
Even if you could
regain control of Rubicon,
there'd be no place on Earth that is safe.
If there's no place left on Earth
that's safe,
let it all burn.
All right, I'm listening.
Though, if you could
keep the lecture short...
-No lecture.
-I'd appreciate it.
-Just a request.
-Uh-huh.
Leave, and this time,
don't come back.
-What?
-You helped Felicity tonight.
Maybe it was because you'd be nuked, too.
Maybe it was a broken clock
being right for once.
Either way, we both know it wasn't you.
-Dee...
-You know who you are.
Are you really going to stand here
(CHUCKLES)
and tell me that you've changed?
You're every bit as dangerous
to our daughter
as the day I took her from you.
If you care about her,
you will walk away.
After everything that's happened,
she'll be crushed.
She'll survive.
She's strong. She's my daughter.
You can lie to her,
but can you lie to yourself?
Can you really believe
that leaving isn't the best thing for her?
CURTIS: What do you think
your parents are talking about?
FELICITY: I'm trying
not to think about it.
Maybe they're discussing that thing
that Noah said before
about not having much of a choice.
That's exactly what
I'm trying not to think about.
-Felicity, I helped you save the world.
-Mmm-hmm?
The least you can do
is give me a little gossip.
Okay, fine.
So, apparently...
My dad didn't leave.
My mom kicked him out.
Did she tell you why?
I think she didn't want
to risk him hurting me.
I mean, he could promise
whatever he wanted,
but he was a criminal, is a criminal.
So, he inevitably would have
gone back to his old habits.
Mmm-hmm.
What does that mean?
It just sounds familiar, that's all.
The criminal
who you don't think can change,
the slightly overactive
but understandable breakup.
Just saying.
You and Oliver,
Donna and Noah.
(DOOR OPENS)
Where is Noah?
He's going away for a little while.
That's what you told me when I was seven.
DARHK: Boo-hoo!
Are you getting all weepy?
Do you need a moment?
No? Good.
'Cause I need you to do me a favor.
Go to hell.
(DARHK EXHALES DEEPLY)
Why bother?
I'm going to bring it to us.