My name is Oliver Queen.
For 7 years, I have fought
with only one goal...
to save my city,
but now a new threat has emerged,
a danger so severe, it has forced me
to leave my family in order to face it,
and it won't be enough for
me to just be the Green Arrow.
To prevent the crisis that's coming,
I am going to have to
become someone else.
become... something else.
Previously on "Arrow"...
Turns out Connor
doesn't know his brother
as well as he thinks.
We're all still alive, aren't we?
Which means what exactly,
that your brother's not such a bad guy?
What did you do?
You are not gonna touch me.
- Oh, my God.
- Because if you do,
the men who are storming
your bunker right now
will kill your brother.
I ignored the orders of a cosmic being,
and as a result, I watched
an entire world disappear.
We're facing the
destruction of everything?
That's the very definition
of all hands on deck.
A lot of people have died already
for the sake of this mission.
I owe it to all of them to find out who
the Monitor really is.
So what's the plan?
I'm going to Nanda Parbat.
_
Ollie?
Hi, Speedy.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
Well, I'm guessing Mia's for Mom
and not my Corto Maltese alias.
Good guess.
She's beautiful, Ollie.
Where'd you get that?
Athena.
I wasn't expecting to
find you here alone.
Where's Nyssa?
Thailand, I think. I don't know.
After we destroyed the Lazarus pits,
she said she had some League
business to take care of.
You destroyed the pits.
Why didn't you come home?
Pits may be gone, but
the Thanatos Guild isn't.
I have to take them down
after what they did to Roy.
That's fair. Have you seen him?
He came back here after Star City.
He told me what happened,
how he killed those men and...
He's dealing with his own demons.
He'll be back.
I missed you.
I missed you, too.
But I'm pretty sure I'm not
the reason why you came here.
Last year, I made a deal
with a cosmic being named Mar Novu.
Recently, he came to collect his debt.
He asked me to help him,
but he's not very good
at sharing information
with the people he's working with.
Sounds like somebody else I know.
I need to be 100% sure
that I can trust him.
I know it's a long
shot, but I was hoping
that Nyssa could tell
me what, if anything,
the League knows about him.
Okay. What are you not telling me?
He's seen the future.
He's seen me die.
It's soon, Speedy.
And?
Take as much time as
you need to be upset.
Ollie, come on. You've cheated death
more than any of us have by this point.
This is fundamentally
different than anything
that we've ever dealt with before.
Okay.
Well, let's try to figure
out what we're dealing with,
but like I said, Nyssa's not here.
Sara hasn't been able to help either.
We've kind of killed off every
League member, haven't we?
I can think of one more.
William?
Frak!
William!
Where is he?
- Aah?
- Oh. It's you.
I'm here. I'm okay.
I remembered how Mom hardwired
the bunker's power
grid through the floor.
Gave those guys the
shock of their lives.
Guys.
This is why JJ was going after William.
He's targeting all the members
of the Star City unification movement.
The ones that are still alive anyway.
This was a city-wide assault.
There's 10 confirmed dead.
And now that JJ knows who they all are,
it's only a matter of time before
he wipes out the entire movement.
Unless we trap him first.
All we really need is the right... lure.
You want to use yourself as bait?
No way. It is too dangerous.
Look. I know you don't
want to hear this,
but the Deathstrokes have
been 5 steps ahead of us
this whole time.
We need to gain the upper hand.
Which is why we are going
to bring the fight to them,
take them out in one fell swoop.
How? It's not like we're gonna waltz
back into their headquarters.
Unless that's your plan.
Mia, that didn't work out
too well for us last time.
Right, but we've been there before.
We know the layout.
We can use that to our advantage.
I think this is a mistake.
I'll remember that.
Get ready to move out.
_
Something wrong with the uplink?
No, no. It's our timing that's off.
JJ already went to sleep.
Well, we can call him back, wake him up.
No. Little man's gone
through enough already.
Besides, I need to know
what mission was so important
that you wanted me here
instead of Nanda Parbat.
Ben Turner is currently
on a deep cover op,
so I've been keeping
an eye on his family.
Sandra Hawke has
never missed a check-in
until yesterday.
So you think something
happened to Sandra and Connor?
I know it.
These pictures were taken
at an airfield in Kasnia.
Kasnia? That's far from home.
Any chance Sandra and Connor
are meeting up with Turner?
Kasnia's nowhere close to
any of Turner's missions
past, present, or future,
and then there's this man.
Abdul Nardoc. He owns that plane.
Nardoc bills himself
as a philanthropist,
but intel suggests that he
has ties to local terrorists.
- Hmm.
- He's throwing a fundraiser
tomorrow at his home.
Odds are good that Sandra and
Connor are being held on site.
We need to infiltrate
and get eyes on them.
Why not just take an
A.R.G.U.S. recon team?
I've spent the past few months
trying to untangle the web
of corruption at A.R.G.U.S.
Until I eliminate it, I
can't trust this with anyone.
I need you with me, John.
Hmm. Must be really important
if you call me John.
Guess I need a suit.
I already picked one out.
Hmm.
I thought you guys were friends now.
Well... not exactly.
Okay. Well, this place
isn't the least bit creepy.
Hold!
Leave us.
Your students used to
ask questions first.
I have learned
that hesitation often proves fatal.
You should not have come to this place.
You owe me a debt.
I'm here to collect.
You come here at great peril.
Especially you.
Word of your exploits has traveled far.
How is my sister?
She's great. Vacationing,
working on a tan.
I see you survived prison.
Mm-hmm. Dr. Parker didn't.
Heard he was killed with a sword.
He received the justice he deserved.
So now you're back to your old exploits?
With the League gone, the
region has become quite unstable.
And you think training
a bunch of assassins
in a place like this
is gonna stabilize it?
I think it a wiser course of action
than declaring a one-woman war
on the Thanatos Guild.
Much as I would like
to have a debate, Talia,
I need to know whatever
the League might know
about Mar Novu.
That's an unusual name. I'd remember it.
If it helps, he's apparently
some kind of cosmic know-it-all.
Well, such beings
often go by many names.
If I help you,
I can consider my debt paid?
Yes.
If the League has any
information concerning this man,
it will be found
underneath the Karan Shah.
The League's stronghold.
It has since been destroyed,
but my father kept the League
records in the catacombs,
so with any luck, they're
still there waiting to be found.
We leave at nightfall.
She's still fun.
- You good?
- I'm fine.
I think I just... ack...
Got some dust in my mouth.
Ack! Was it this dusty last time?
It was worse.
Are you sure this is gonna work?
If I can tap into the
old Galaxy One cameras,
we should be able to see everything,
including JJ and his
Deathstroke maniacs.
Pstt. Hey.
Someone's coming.
Guys, there's an office
just up here I can use.
Okay. System's gonna need a minute
to reboot before I can access it.
Look. I know you think
this is a bad idea.
The 4 of us taking on all of JJ's forces
on their home turf?
Wasn't my first choice.
Thanks for coming anyway.
We're a team. I just...
I hope you're doing this
for the right reasons.
What do you mean?
I'm pissed that JJ tried
to kill William, too,
but we can't let fear
dictate our strategy.
I'm not afraid of JJ or his idiot goons.
I know, but you are afraid
of losing your brother.
Bad news, guys. System's in
worse shape than I thought.
I'm gonna need more time.
We should get into position.
I'll stay with William until he's done.
Let us know when you're up and running.
Yeah.
_
See a lot of unfriendly faces here.
How you looking?
Just waiting for the security feeds
to finish uploading.
Hmm. Dancing undercover's like déjà vu.
There's Nardoc.
What do you say we take a closer look,
find out who his friends are?
You've come a long
way since Afghanistan.
Heh heh heh.
Yeah. Well, sometimes, I wish
we were still on that tour.
Life was a lot less complicated.
But we wouldn't be married.
Hmm. That's true. Or divorced.
Or remarried, and we wouldn't
have our beautiful boy.
All the feeds are complete.
Copy that.
Sandra and Connor are here.
They're being held in a room
in the northeast corner.
Good. We'll exfil them out
before Nardoc knows what hit him.
I don't think it's gonna be that easy.
- Why?
- We just got a hit on one
of Nardoc's friends.
The man in the black
suit and blue tie...
Farzad Qadir.
Gholem Qadir's son.
- Who Ben Turner killed?
- To save me.
I doubt his family's
kidnapping is a coincidence.
Wow. Love what they
haven't done with the place.
Assuming the Karan Shah
hasn't been plundered,
we're likely to find
what we're looking for
in "The Chronicles of Al-Fatih."
He was the first Ra's al Ghul.
According to legend, he was
bestowed primordial knowledge
by one of the sky gods.
Now my father kept a secret room
with his most valued possessions,
including information on Al-Fatih.
Looks like we're too late.
Not necessarily.
Heh heh heh.
"The Chronicles of Al-Fatih."
So the looters just
happened to leave behind
the one thing we're looking for?
Because the thieves did not
consider it to be of value.
Right. What's it say?
"The Phoenix is reborn in the fire.
The path to your destiny follows me."
Speedy, you just read Arabic.
You speak Russian.
Yes, but what does it mean?
To join the League,
your old self must die
so that your new one may be reborn.
Oh.
We need to burn the scroll.
The scroll is centuries old.
Yeah.
Al-Fatih took great
pains to hide his secrets
lest he be betrayed.
I believe this leads to Al-Fatih's tomb.
It stands to reason
that he would attempt
to take his secrets with
him beyond the grave.
So it's a scavenger hunt.
It would appear so, yes.
Why can't everything just be easy?
Actually, your situation is
more difficult than you think.
- Athena.
- You have always been
treacherous, Talia,
but bringing outsiders
into our sacred heart is a betrayal
of the highest order.
I'll take that.
Relinquish it or perish.
As you wish.
Attack them!
Athena showing up right when
we did can't be an accident.
No, and neither was her
giving Athena the sphere.
If you're accusing me, I'd
like to point out two things.
First, Athena and I are blood enemies.
And second?
She was likely trailing you.
The woman who's declared war on her.
Still, I don't see why Athena would give
a crap about a rusty, old
scroll buried with Al-Fatih.
She wouldn't. She would give a crap
about what else is buried with him,
namely his sword
as revered as the ring of Ra's.
Whoever wields it
commands absolute devotion.
Clearly Athena wants
to use it to restart
the League of Assassins.
Yeah. Well, now she's got the
marble of destiny or whatever.
Actually, it's a map.
The markings on it were constellations
indicating the tomb's
location, but we don't need it.
I've memorized them.
What?
- You memorized them?
- You didn't?
Okay. Listen. I'm gonna
go head with Talia.
I'd like you to go back to
her camp and wait for us there.
You can't be serious.
I will give you two a moment.
Ollie, I thought we were way
past this overprotective brother thing.
It's not about that.
You came to me for help.
I came to you for answers.
I wasn't counting on
getting attacked by Athena.
Athena and I were fighting
long before you showed up here.
I can take care of myself.
I know you can take care of yourself.
If Athena is trying to restart
the League of Assassins,
that makes you her chief rival.
- I don't care.
- I care, Thea.
If you want to help me,
just... just let me handle this.
Qadir must be using Turner's
family to lure him out.
Okay. Then we have to
get out of here right now.
What? What are you talking about?
If Ben Turner's a
target, then so are we,
and every second we stay
here, we risk being made.
What about Sandra and Connor?
Call an A.R.G.U.S. team, Lyla.
- Exfil them.
- It would take a team
at least an hour to get here.
A lot can happen between now that then.
Okay, fine, but we can't
risk doing this alone.
- We have to do something.
- Then you leave.
I'll get Sandra and Connor myself.
Johnny...
What's really going on here?
You've never been one
to shy away from risk.
I'd never seen a world just
disintegrate in front of my face.
I know what we do requires risk.
I've always accepted that,
but this is different, Lyla.
Seeing a universe just disappearing,
I don't know, it's like...
like looking into the eye of God.
It changes you.
It changed me.
I can't risk losing you.
I can't risk that.
No one knows the future.
All we can do is enjoy the time we have
with the people we love
and make our choices
from a place of strength, not fear,
and if the world ends today,
there is no one I'd
rather have by my side.
How much further?
Patience. You realize
your sister is involved
in this whether you
want her to be or not?
She's a daughter of the demon.
She has a claim to the sword.
She's carried enough
of Malcolm's burdens.
Fate does not care what
we believe we're owed.
You're very familiar with that.
Isn't that why you're here?
What do you mean?
You carry yourself with a heaviness
I've not seen since Russia.
This is the place.
I've been here before.
Yes. When my father vanquished you.
Hopefully you have better luck
with the mountain this time.
Down!
The Phoenix up there,
triggering the spears.
Here's an idea.
The key to the Crypt of Ra's.
Looks like the entrance right there.
Yes.
Agh!
Wh... what are you doing?
I am sorry, Oliver.
I can't let Athena get to the sword,
but I can't let you get it either.
Looks like you're down
one evil companion.
Hmm.
I thought I told you
to stay at the camp.
You did. Looks like I didn't
ignore you soon enough.
Hey. I don't have time
for an I told you so.
All right.
So Talia will take the
trail to the summit.
It's safer, you conserve energy,
but going up the face of
the mountain is faster.
Thought you said it was harder.
Yeah. I've done it before.
Okay. If you can do it, I can do it.
- Thea.
- Ollie, just stop it.
Start walking.
Tell me you're almost
done hacking those cameras.
You ever hear that thing
about patience being a virtue?
Since when have I ever
cared about virtue?
All right. Seriously, how much longer?
Okay. I just activated the
northwest quadrant cameras.
I just need a few more minutes to
get the rest of them up and running.
How many is a few?
Look. I know what I'm doing, okay,
so just trust me.
I do.
I d... I just...
William, this has to work.
If we're gonna bring Star City
and The Glades back together,
we have to take out the
Deathstrokes for good this time.
Well, we could have if you'd
let the team use me as bait.
No. That is too risky, and you know it.
Well, how many times have you
risked yourself for this team?
How many times have you beaten
up a guy 10 times your size
to protect someone you care about?
- That's different.
- Why? Because I'm not a fighter?
No. Because you're my brother.
You are the only family I have left.
Mia... look.
I...
I appreciate you
looking out for me. I do,
but operating from a place of fear
is not the way to protect each other.
We need to trust each other.
It's the only way we'll survive.
Found them.
Oh, boy. That is a lot of Deathstrokes.
You sure about this?
- Connor, Zoe, we have eyes.
- Roger that.
- Get ready to move.
- On it.
Mia.
Be careful.
I will.
Oh, and if you tell anyone
about this conversation,
I will kill you myself.
Err!
Thought you said this was the hard part.
Don't get cocky.
Okay. What is going on with you, Ollie?
You were never this overprotective
when I left Star City.
Things have changed.
I left my family behind, Speedy,
and I miss them.
And every day, I wrestle
with whether or not
I made the right decision
because maybe I didn't,
and...
I saw an entire world
wiped out of existence,
a world that you weren't in, by the way,
because I wasn't around to protect you.
I'm sorry, Thea, but the
only way that I can bear this
is if I become 100% certain
that my sacrifice, that my death...
Will protect the people I love.
I need my family to be safe.
You know, I've been thinking a lot
about Mom and Dad lately,
wondering what they would think
about the lives we've chosen.
All the mistakes they made,
all the... lies they told
in their own very, very messed up way.
They thought they were protecting us.
They weren't. They didn't.
No, but... it did help us become
the people we are today.
They turned us into heroes.
We can't change the future, Ollie.
The past teaches us you might as well
not bother trying to.
Heh.
When you'd stop being my baby sister?
No. I never did.
I just grew up a little bit.
Now can we please get off this mountain?
Yeah.
We're not alone.
Apparently, this day
is not going the way
either of us have planned.
Surrender your weapons.
What do you want?
The route to Al-Fatih's
Crypt will be dangerous.
Always good to have a
few sacrificial lambs
to tell us where not to stray.
After you.
Underground in Nanda Parbat.
What could possibly go wrong?
Well, Indiana Jones made
this look way more fun.
"To survive death, you must embrace it."
Well, how do you embrace death?
The coffin. Come on.
Go on.
Okay.
I miss watching you kick ass.
This way.
Must be passcode-protected.
This should be able to crack it,
but it'll take a few minutes.
We may not have a few minutes.
If this is Qadir and his men,
he'll recognize us
the minute he sees us.
Maybe we can use that.
I was standing next to Gholem Qadir
the night that Turner killed him.
I can distract Farzad.
Lyla that's too dangerous.
It's our only option.
Hey. Just be careful.
Pardon me.
Wait.
You know, usually, I
detest party crashers,
but I'll make an exception for you...
Lyla Michaels.
Hey. Shh, shh, shh, shh. It's okay.
It's okay. My name is John Diggle.
I'm a friend of Lyla
Michaels and Ben Turner.
I'm here to help you. I
can get you out of here,
but you have to move quietly.
Come on, come on. Shh, shh shh.
Did you know I was there
the night my father died?
I was supposed to stay in my room,
but I wanted to hear the music.
Do you have any idea
what it's like to watch
your own father be murdered?
I was just a boy.
I'm sorry you had to see that,
but your father was a criminal.
So he deserved to die?
I will have my vengeance.
You all right?
I've got Sandra and Connor.
Let's go home.
Prisoners first.
Watch your step.
Ollie, a Phoenix.
All right. Crypt must be through there.
Okay.
Thea!
Thank you.
Yeah.
"All beings burn,
but a Phoenix rises from the ashes."
Okay. I think we need
to use the Phoenix tiles
to get across.
You hold them off. I'll get Talia.
- Thea!
- Just trust me.
Talia?
You're too late.
As heir to the demon, I have the right
to challenge you to combat.
You wish to fight me?
Very well. I accept.
I hope you prove to
be a worthy opponent.
Your brother trained you well.
Pity the tools you learned
from him he learned from me.
Less talk, more fighting.
You were a fool to think
you could defeat me.
Actually...
You're right where I want you.
Unh!
Do you yield?
I yield.
Ahem. What's it say?
It says Al-Fatih was visited by a god
who possessed the power to see
all that is and all that will be.
He believed that if he
failed to keep the balance
between good and evil this god would
bring forth the end of times,
the annihilation of all things.
Ollie, if that's true,
this means that...
It means Mar Novu is
not trying to prevent
what's going to happen
because he's gonna be what causes it.
You're leaving?
I have betrayed my honor
and the sacred traditions of the League.
The sword was destined to
be yours, daughter of Merlyn.
I am sorry for the pain
I've caused you both.
What about your students?
I've released them.
They will follow you if
that is what you wish.
It's not.
You're their teacher.
They need someone to follow.
If I was meant to lead them,
I would wield Al-Fatih's sword,
but you do,
so the honor and the burden are yours.
Yeah. Hard pass.
It is your destiny.
Yeah, but, see, about that.
I don't really believe in
the whole fate, destiny thing.
We can all make our own choices.
Meaning?
Meaning I don't think the world needs
another League of Assassins.
It could use League of Heroes.
It wouldn't be a one-woman job.
You'd extend me that honor
despite my betrayals?
You made a mistake.
We've all made mistakes.
Not one but two women to
wield my father's sword?
He would be aghast.
Heh.
I accept.
New phone, better encryption,
and a one-way ticket home via Hong Kong.
No one will be expecting that.
I can't thank you
enough for all your help.
I mean, without you two I'd...
No, no. It's the least
we could have done,
and you were very brave.
Your father would be proud of you.
Thanks, Mr. Diggles.
Call me Dig.
Let's go get our things.
Hey. They're gonna be okay.
Yeah... and so are we.
The world's gonna keep coming for us.
There's nothing I can do to stop it.
Neither can you, but you were right.
We just hold on to each
other, we'll be fine
like Sandra and Connor.
What? What is it?
Johnny, promise me that
no matter what happens
you'll always remember the good times.
I won't have to because
I'm not going anywhere,
and neither are you.
I love you, Lyla Michaels.
I love you.
I love you, too.
Always have, always will.
I'm sorry you didn't get the
answers you were looking for.
Got to see you.
- Here's what I don't get.
- Okay.
If Mar Novu causes
whatever's gonna happen,
why does he bring you
in in the first place?
I don't know.
Look. I just... I know that if he
ends up being on the
wrong side of this...
I'm gonna stop him.
If you're gonna take on a god, Ollie,
you're gonna need all
the help you can get.
Pretty good on help actually.
I have John, I have
Laurel... believe it or not.
Seems to me you have your hands full
rebuilding the League of Assassins
into a League of Heroes.
Yeah.
I can't believe I'm saying
good-bye to you again.
Well, you're not. Think of it as a...
"See you later,
and please don't die."
One of us is gonna have to let go first.
- Same time?
- Mm-hmm.
No hozen this time?
Uh, Felicity gave it to William.
I'm gonna miss you.
Every day, I miss you.
Good-bye, Speedy.
Bye, Ollie.
Tonight is the night that
we have all been waiting for,
the night that we destroy
the unification movement.
The city will be ours,
and there is nothing
anyone can do to stop it.
Actually, I think there is.
You just don't know when to quit.
Damn. What an entrance.
Mia!
You know, the human
body holds an average
of 5 liters of blood.
Let's see how much you have, huh?
Hyah!
Are you okay?
Thanks.
Zoe!
Zoe.
JJ!
Stay with me. We're
gonna get you out of here.
Tell... tell my dad...
Just tell... tell him that...
I'm sorry about everything.
That I love him.
Hey. Hey. You're gonna
tell him yourself, okay?
You are because we are...
We're gonna get you safe.
Okay? I got you.
Zoe, I got you.
Zoe?
No. No, no, no, no.
No. Zoe.
Aah!
You don't have the guts, do you, huh?
You're wrong.
What is this?
Oliver?
What's going on?
That's a very good question.
Dad?
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --