[ALL SCREAMING]
ACE:
Get down. Everybody keep down.
Nobody lift their head,
nobody gets hurt.
KING: Get down!
ACE: Down.
KING: Get on the floor right now!
MAN: Go.
You can't jackhammer into the safe.
It's too thick.
[GRUNTS]
ACE:
Shut up.
KING: Move. Move. Go.
JACK: We're through.
KING;
Three minutes.
Are you trying to get us killed?
Don't worry. I'm a cop.
WOMAN:
Please don't do anything, okay?
I don't wanna die. Please.
[ALL SCREAMING]
KING:
What hell's going on?
ACE:
He was a freaking cop.
KING:
Enough throwing shots.
[SIRENS WAILING]
ACE:
You hear that?
Someone triggered the alarm.
KING:
Don't. That's it. Let's go.
HILTON:
Starling City Police Department.
Lay down your weapons
and come out with your hands up.
Repeat, lay down your weapons
Hold your fire.
[ALL SCREAMING]
Move those hostages.
Mills, contain the hostages.
All other units, move in, move in.
[ACE GRUNTS]
KING: Come here. You shot a cop.
This is not how we do things.
ACE: Me getting killed
isn't how we do things.
KING:
Get in the van. Get in the van!
Go.
[TIRES SCREECH]
[METAL CLANKING]
Anchor the rear hand, Diggle.
Come on.
DIGGLE:
Okay.
[DIGGLE GRUNTS]
Variable acceleration.
Fighters work at the same pace.
You switch it up,
throw your opponent off his game.
[GRUNTS]
That was nice.
Where'd you learn that?
His name was Yao Fei.
-Did he give you those scars?
-One of them.
And the others?
One day you're gonna be straight
with me about what happened.
Absolutely.
[DIGGLE GRUNTS]
But not today.
Still, some pretty sweet moves.
Yup. Tonight I'm gonna use
some on him.
Scott Morgan runs Water &amp; Power
in the Glades.
Jacks up the prices
when people can't pay...
...shuts them down
even in the dead of winter.
Which is at least a month away.
Look at this.
These guys started in Keystone
three years ago.
Began moving west,
hitting banks along the way.
This morning,
they hit Starling City Trust.
Shot an off-duty cop. He's in a coma.
Doctors say it's a coin-toss
whether he'll make it.
If he's a cop, S.C.P.D. will be over it.
Overwhelmed, underfunded.
These guys don't hit one time,
they hit two or three per city.
Right now they're planning
their next job.
You have the wrong impression
about what I do.
-Take out bad guys with a bow and arrow.
-I don't fight street crime.
That's a symptom of this city.
I'm trying to cure the disease.
CEOs and crooked entrepreneurs.
I get it.
Listen, Oliver, I'm just saying...
...you can make a difference if you think
beyond the scope of those pages.
-I'm sure your father wouldn't mind.
-No, you don't get it.
My father died so that I could live.
Make a difference by fixing the city that
he and the people in this book ruined.
Every name I cross off this list
honors that sacrifice.
There's more than one way
to save this city.
Not for me.
Crime happens in this city every day.
What do you want me to do?
Stop all of it?
It sounds like you have
a narrow definition of being a hero.
I'm not a hero.
Dad?
Tell me that this is a nightmare
and I'm about to wake up.
How can Stagg Industries pull out?
They're our largest donor.
It's like they say,
"It's the economy, stupid."
No, it's the stupid economy.
Okay, without Stagg, how long can CNRI
keep their doors open?
Uh, depends. What time you got?
TOMMY:
I have fiesta time.
Or is it siesta time?
Which one means a party
and which one means a nap?
Tommy, as much as I would love to relive
Intro to Spanish, today is not good day.
Well, of course not, working in
this tiny brick office. It's intolerable.
Now, you know where's
a spectacular place to spend the day?
Coast City.
Here's what I am thinking.
Sunset flight on my private plane,
dinner at Broome's...
...I'll have you home by midnight.
Or maybe in the morning. Hmm?
-What is this?
-This is what we talked about.
This is you getting to know
the real me.
Tommy, so you don't misunderstand,
CNRI just lost its largest single donor.
All of the hard work and sacrifices
that I have made to help...
...this legal clinic survive,
it may have been for nothing.
[SIGHS]
Maybe another time.
Yeah?
I mean, haven't you noticed
she's been acting a little down lately?
Heh, what am I saying?
Of course you haven't.
Since when do you pay attention
to how Mom's feeling?
Since our step-father decided to take a
business trip halfway around the world.
When someone at Walter's pay
takes a trip, it's always sudden.
I wouldn't worry.
Ah. Guess who I just hung up with?
Janice Bowen.
-Carter's mother.
THEA: Oh.
OLIVER:
Oh, heh.
Carter Bowen. The perfect son.
-Is he perfect?
OLIVER: According to you.
Carter Bowen just won
the national chess championship.
Carter Bowen is anchoring
the debate team.
I didn't make that big a fuss.
Oliver, Carter just got accepted
into Harvard and Princeton.
Because Carter got a perfect score
on his SATs.
Now, how did he manage to study
and cure cancer?
All right, all right. I get it, I get it.
Well, they're coming for brunch
and I expect you to be there.
-I have plans.
-That's fine. Brunch is tomorrow.
-Heh, inches from a clean getaway.
-Well, you too, Thea.
[SNAPS FINGERS]
-Snap.
-Nobody says that anymore.
-What? Mom?
-Hmm.
I can't actually go.
I haven't seen the Bowens in years.
Whatever it is that you have planned...
...I'm sure the two of you
can make the sacrifice just this once.
We'll be there.
-I hate you.
-Mm-hm.
[PHONE RINGING]
-Yeah?
-Scott Morgan from your father's list?
[OVER PHONE] He tried to kill himself.
Maybe afraid of getting a visit from you.
-Can you make it to Starling General?
-On my way.
Hey, just the man I wanted to see.
I just picked up a new sports car.
I'm thinking, we can open her up,
pick up a few speeding tickets...
That sounds great
but something's come up. I gotta jet.
Oh, uh, okay.
Nice talk. Thanks.
He moves fast, doesn't he?
It's ironic since you're the one
we call Speedy.
Ah, "Called," please.
For the love of God.
But if you need somebody to talk to,
I'm here.
You know, maybe you could help.
There's this girl that I'm interested in.
And I am really not sure
how to pursue it.
Have you tried using
your usual lines?
"My name is Tommy Merlyn, billionaire,
but I don't look like Warren Buffett."
Yeah, she is aware of that
and she doesn't care.
You know, money really isn't
a big deal to her.
Why don't you just tell her
how you feel?
Well, I've...
I've known her for a long time.
And I'm not sure the direct approach
is the right way to go.
Maybe you have to figure out
what's a big deal to her...
...and make it a big deal to you.
Thea, you are amazing, heh.
Love you.
You sure?
Scott Morgan doesn't seem
like the type who'd try to kill himself.
True, but it's the best lie
I could come up with on short notice.
Mr. Diggle, I can't thank you enough...
...for arranging to move my husband
from county ward to Starling General.
Now I know he's getting the best care.
You should be thanking Oliver Queen.
He's paying the bill.
Jana's husband, Stan,
is a police officer.
He happened to have been making
a deposit at Starling Trust.
The bank that was robbed.
I was so sorry
to hear about your husband.
-Is he gonna be okay?
-The next 24 hours are crucial.
He should have just kept
his head down, you know?
I've known a few police officers
in my day.
Always willing to help others even
if that means putting themselves at risk.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
You lied to me.
And you asked me to work with you,
not for you.
You said it was because
you understand the man I am.
I'm the man who doesn't walk away when
there's a chance to make a difference.
And neither does Stan Washington.
Oliver, I'm not finished talking.
Where you going?
To go make a difference.
Let's catch some bank robbers.
See that guy there? He's got a temper.
-And he shot Officer Washington.
-That's right.
-College ring.
-Well, high school, more likely.
-That ring will get us an ID.
-But even with photo enhancement...
...you have a problem getting
a clear shot of that ring.
It left an impression
police will have photographed.
It'll be in evidence lockup.
You're not going
where I think you're going.
Diggle, why do you even ask?
[PHONE RINGING]
HILTON: Are you kidding me?
I don't wanna hear this.
Don't tell me about red tape.
One of our own's been shot.
Tell them to find themselves
a pair of scissors.
So where are you gonna take me today?
Monte Carlo?
Actually, uh, I was just telling Jo here...
...that the Merlyn Global Group
is looking to expand its philanthropy...
...and I thought that we could start
by sponsoring a benefit for CNRI.
Thank you, Tommy. But I think we can
manage without your family's finances.
Laurel, a word?
Heh, come on.
What are you doing?
He's not interested
in throwing us a fundraiser.
He wants the First Annual Attempt
to Get Back Into My Pants Gala.
Who cares why he's doing it?
We need the money.
-Not like that, we don't.
-We really do.
So you're gonna listen
to your best friend's advice.
You are gonna go over there and say,
"Thank you, Tommy.
We'd be honored
for you to throw us a fundraiser." Hmm?
Thank you, Tommy.
We would be honored
for you to throw us a fundraiser.
The bank manager Ace punched.
His ring left a mark.
Larchmont High.
High school.
I cross-referenced his height and age
with the students and alumni.
That's a pretty long list.
It was. I dug a little deeper
and found Kyle Reston.
Before Kyle's senior year,
not only did he drop out...
...he dropped off the grid,
along with his family.
Father, mother, younger brother.
There are two other guys involved
in this robbery.
And a woman.
Aside from Stan Washington...
...there were 22 customers
and employees that came.
Nine men, 13 women.
Inside the bank, nine men, 14 women.
-Heh, they put a ringer in.
-The mom.
The police look for a crew,
we look for family.
Speaking of which,
I'm incredibly late for mine.
-Well, I'm sorry Walter couldn't join us.
-Oh, yes.
Well, the Australian trip came up
suddenly.
He sends his apologies.
Where's Oliver?
He's not out of town too, is he?
-I'm sure he's...
-Stuck in traffic.
One of the things I didn't miss
on the island? Sunday drivers.
-Sorry I'm late.
-Mm-hm.
Thank God you're here.
It is so good to see you.
We all thought you were...
Oh, well, we are just happy he's home.
-Hmm, and returning as a celebrity too.
-How do you mean?
CARTER: Well, billionaire scion,
castaway for five years.
You know, there is a bidding war
for the rights to your life story.
-At least, that's what my agent says.
-Agent?
-I thought you were a neurosurgeon.
-I know. It's crazy, right?
One minute I'm publishing this book
on how long-term potentiation...
...initiates the creation
of a slow-moving protein synthesis...
...and then next, there's an agent
trying to make me the next Dr. Oz, heh.
Why would he want you
to be a wizard?
[ALL CHUCKLE]
-Oliver.
-For our sakes, start reading US Weekly.
Well, the truth is, I feel it's our duty
as Starling City's more fortunate...
-...to help those most in need.
-Oh, of course.
-Do you agree, Oliver?
-You're the hero, Carter.
Quick and clean.
And try not to shoot anybody.
Now that you're back,
what are your plans?
Will you be taking a job
with Queen Consolidated?
I'm opening a nightclub.
[THEA CHUCKLES]
DIGGLE: Sir, your liquor distributor's
on the line.
First Bank of Starling
was hit two minutes ago.
Sorry.
Business.
If their M.O. holds,
they made their escape underground.
First Bank of Starling is located
above water tunnels.
The entrance is located here.
Oliver, where are you going?
Something's come up. I'm really sorry.
[SIREN WAILING]
MAN:
Okay, go, go. Go.
I got it. Let's go.
HILTON:
S.C.P.D. Don't move!
KING:
Enough. What are you doing?
Move! Let's go!
[ACE GRUNTS]
KING:
Get out of here!
JACK: Our cash!
KING: Forget it!
Go. Go!
All right, let's move.
It's the vigilante.
ACE:
Come on.
JACK: Who the hell was that guy?
KING: The local vigilante.
-Goes after rich guys.
-Clearly, he's branching out.
Things have gone sideways lately.
That hood guy.
-Kyle shooting a cop.
-You warned me he was a cop.
-So you would take his gun.
KING: Your mother has a point.
Maybe this is a sign
we need to hang it up.
-Head for Mexico. Retire.
-We don't have enough.
We said that we wouldn't quit
until we had enough to set ourselves up.
We need to hit another.
-We can make do.
-We'll be okay.
I didn't spend five years risking my life
and my freedom to just be okay.
No, set for life.
That was our deal.
Okay.
One more.
And then we're out.
Should add "personal Internet researcher
for Oliver Queen" to my job title.
Happily, I mean.
His name is Derek Reston.
We were close before I went away...
...and I wanna get back in touch.
-Didn't have Facebook on that island.
DIGGLE: Nope.
Not even a Myspace account.
It was a very dark time.
There's not much here that's recent.
No credit activity, no utility bills.
I guess you guys
must have met at the factory.
Wait, what factory?
The Queen steel factory.
Derek Reston worked there for 15 years
until it shut down in '07.
Derek Reston worked for my father?
You weren't really close friends, huh?
Looks like Derek
was the factory foreman...
...until your dad outsourced production
to China.
About 1500 employees got laid off.
The finance guys found a loophole
in the union contracts...
...so they didn't have to pay
severance packages and pensions...
...to their employees.
They all pretty much lost their homes.
Including your friend.
You died.
I asked you, I begged you to survive.
But if you don't think you can...
...there's still one bullet left.
But, Oliver, my death is made
meaningless by yours.
I'm starving. I'm gonna die anyway.
And I just want it to be quick.
I want it to be quick like yours was.
You can survive this.
No, I can't.
I'm not as strong as you think I am.
And I'm sorry.
The Restons just got home
after five years away.
Those factory guys hung out
at a bar after work.
Hopefully, Derek Reston wants to take
a stroll down memory lane.
And if by some miracle
Reston's there?
Gonna give him the chance
to do the right thing.
He had his chance to do the right thing.
It's called not being a criminal.
This is happening because of my father,
because of my family.
No. You're worried about
the wrong thing.
It's not your fault.
The Restons aren't the victims.
My family stole from this city.
They hurt the people in it.
And I am hell-bent
on making that right.
For Derek Reston...
...that means giving him the chance
to make it right.
[LAUREL YAWNS]
Hey, don't fade on me now.
We have about 10,000 more decisions
to make.
Now, cake. Ahem, chocolate or mocha?
Mm, carrot.
Are you sure about that?
Because Bugs Bunny hasn't RSVP'd yet.
[CHUCKLES]
Tommy, why the full-court press?
Asking me to Coast City,
the fundraiser.
Why now?
You know, I was in a bar last week
and I was talking to this girl...
...and things were progressing,
if you know what I mean.
No, you're too subtle.
Anyway, we finally go back
to her place...
...and I realize, all of a sudden, ahem,
that I had been there before.
Been with her before.
Two years ago. I just didn't remember.
So I left.
You know...
...I remember...
...some of the mornings
when you and I were together...
...and I made you omelets.
And I'd be in your kitchen...
...and I would think to myself,
this isn't just fun.
This is more than fun. This is...
This is different.
I've never felt that way
with anybody else.
And I miss it.
Not mocha? Carrot.
-Carrot.
-Yeah.
[COUNTRY MUSIC
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
[LAUGHS]
MAN: All right.
-Heh, okay, fellas.
Thanks for playing.
[OLIVER CLEARS THROAT]
Mind if I sit in?
Oliver Queen.
The prodigal son returns.
Didn't figure you for someone
who would hang in the Glades.
My father used to bring me here.
There's a "Pac-Man" machine in the back.
I had the highest score
for two months.
The last time I saw your dad,
he was making a speech...
...telling my crew not to believe
all the gossip.
That there was no way
Queen Consolidated...
...was moving production to China.
A week later, they closed the doors.
I didn't get
the two-weeks vacation pay due me.
My father made mistakes.
He hurt people.
When people are hurt,
people are in trouble...
...they tend to make
the wrong choices.
Right, Derek?
Those choices
don't have to define you.
They don't have to define
who your family will be.
Because there's always one moment
when you can turn it all around.
If my father had another chance...
...I think he'd do things differently...
...but time ran out for him.
How poetic.
That doesn't help me
get my house back.
No, it doesn't.
No, all I can offer you
is an apology and a job.
Queen Consolidated has subsidiaries
all over the country.
I make one phone call,
you start next week.
So, what do you say?
How about,
I still have some pride left?
Now, I don't need charity from the son
of the man who screwed me over.
Okay.
You change your mind?
You and I have one thing in common.
We're both dealing with
the consequences of my father's actions.
What he did then, that's on him.
But what we do now...
...that's on us.
KING [OVER COM]:I've been thinking.
Maybe you were right.
Maybe it's time to hang it up, retire.
QUEEN [OVER COM]:But Kyle said
we do one more or he'll go out on his own.
KING: If that's what he wants, that's his
right. You and me and Teddy, we're out.
QUEEN: I wanna quit too
but I am not leaving without Kyle.
-What's this?
-I dropped a bug in Reston's jacket.
I thought you were gonna give
a second chance.
That's what I believe in.
I also believe in covering
all my bases.
QUEEN:
Derek, we can't abandon our son.
After all this time,
he wants to end up a winner.
Set for life.
Otherwise, what was the point?
KING:
All right.
One more.
Now what?
We take them down.
Monitor the Restons with this.
You get a line on their plans, we move.
And you're gonna do
another abrupt exit?
I'm getting better at it with practice.
[DIGGLE CHUCKLES]
[POP MUSIC PLAYING
OVER SPEAKERS]
Honey, keep the alcohol flowing.
I ca, heh...
Wow, you look just really lovely.
LAUREL: Lovely?
-Yeah.
It's nice you've extended
your vocabulary...
...from words like
"hot" and "mega-hot."
You could just say "thank you,"
you know.
Thank you...
...you know.
You're welcome.
Tommy, this is wonderful.
-It means the world to us.
-Thank you.
Oh, God. Excuse me, just for a second.
-So?
-You were right.
Thank you for coming.
Thank you for inviting me.
Well, I figure the entire Queen family
and their checkbooks should be present.
Right. How is that going for you
so far?
It is going amazing
and all thanks to you.
You know, Thea Queen,
the unlikely voice of reason.
-Oh, me? Well, what did I do?
-You gave me that great advice.
You know, I thought about what the girl
was interested in and, uh...
And you did this for Laurel?
And it's working.
Thanks again, Speedy.
Yeah.
Anytime.
Tommy, do you remember
Carter Bowen from high school?
Oh, yeah, sure I do.
So glad you could make it.
So great to see you.
You look amazing.
I gotta say, I'm so impressed with
the work you and CNRI are doing here.
-Thanks, Carter.
-Yeah.
I've been thinking about starting
a clinic in the Glades.
Really?
Maybe grab a couple drinks,
tell you what I'm thinking.
That sounds great.
It's a creative space. Gorgeous.
Hi.
MOIRA:
Excuse me.
Well, I'm surprised you made it tonight,
given your hectic schedule.
Mom, I messed up
with the Bowens yesterday.
I made you a promise.
-I couldn't keep it.
-Well, it's nothing new for you, Oliver.
I know you and I
have had our difficulties...
...but despite all my many mistakes...
...I always thought that you and I
had a connection.
So you can imagine...
...just imagine,
after being granted the miracle...
...of having my child returned to me...
...that you seem to have little
or no interest in being with me.
Or telling me the truth.
Ma'am.
Redwood United Bank.
They're gonna try a nighttime hit.
I have to go.
-I'm sorry...
-No, don't bother apologizing.
Honestly, Oliver,
there are times I wonder...
...why you bother coming home at all.
[GUN COCKS]
[GRUNTING]
[DETONATOR BEEPING]
-Three minutes.
-Okay.
[DOOR OPENS]
You hear that?
-I'll check it out.
-All right.
ARROW:
Kyle Reston.
ACE:
I came prepared.
[ACE GRUNTS]
It's okay. It's gonna be okay.
[ARROW AND ACE GRUNTING]
ARROW:
No! Hey, I got this.
MAN: Drop your weapons. Now!
KING: No!
[GRUNTS]
[KING GROANING]
ARROW:
He's bleeding out.
Call an ambulance. Now!
[KING GASPING]
Kyle?
He's okay. He's just knocked out.
Listen, it wasn't his fault.
I turned my son into this.
I'm...
Of course it doesn't work.
I'm hallucinating. Or I'm dreaming.
But if you weren't...
You betrayed me, Oliver.
I died so that you could live
and you threw that gift away.
You made that sacrifice empty.
I'm not you.
I'm not as... I'm not strong like you.
I never was.
I told you,
I'm not the man you think I am.
The things I've done.
What I was about to do.
Dad.
What does that mean, please?
I don't know what it means.
I told you, I begged you...
...right my wrongs!
This is your responsibility now.
How...?
How do I do this?
I can't even get off this island.
I'm sorry I didn't tell you
the truth about me...
...but I hope that you know
that I love you.
[SIRENS WAILING]
[POP MUSIC PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
Did you know that as a doctor...
...I was able to diagnose myself
as a giant tool?
How about a dance, handsome?
Hey, uh, I thought that we agreed
that you were going to call me...
...before you did something stupid.
See? You're no fun.
I'm gonna show you
how to have some fun.
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
what are you doing?
You said I was amazing.
You are amazing, but you're also
like my sister. My baby sister.
Well, I'm not a baby anymore.
Thank you for noticing.
Heh, Laurel doesn't even like you.
She doesn't understand you.
I do.
-Why can't you just see that?
-Thea.
Thea, it was a mistake to talk to you
about girls and stuff.
It was inappropriate
and I think it may have confused you.
Heh, no, the rejection is pretty clear.
Even if it wasn't,
between my mom and Oliver...
...and, heh, everybody in my entire life,
I'm pretty much used to it by now, so...
Whoa, whoa.
Hey, let's go, let's go. Come on.
It's all right.
[THEA RETCHING]
-Tommy?
-Yeah.
Is Thea okay?
Oh, yeah. She just ate
some bad crab cakes.
Are you sure
it wasn't something she drank?
Ahem, don't worry. I got this.
You can go back inside.
Keep having fun.
Looked like you were having
a nice do-si-do with the good doctor.
I'm gonna let you in on a little-known
secret about Dr. Carter Bowen.
The man is a gigantic ass.
[CHUCKLES]
And the only reason
why I danced with him...
...is because he wrote
a massive check to CNRI.
Why would you think anything else?
I guess when it comes to you,
I tend not to think straight.
Can you call me a cab?
Absolutely not. I am taking you home.
Get in.
I apologize for making such a scene.
Just feel better, okay?
Hey, Tommy. I owe you a dance.
Yeah?
You earned it.
Good night.
-Please don't hate me.
-Never.
Never.
-What went down wasn't your fault.
-I didn't say it was.
Oliver, it wasn't your fault, man.
You gave Reston a chance.
That was more than he deserved.
I'm not so sure about that.
Well, listen, I'll tell you this much.
You say going after the guys on that list
is the way you honored your dad?
Well, if your dad could have seen you
this week...
...the way you cared
about the people he had hurt...
...the way you stepped up
to try to help them...
...I say he'd be pretty damn honored.
So maybe there is more than one way
to save this city.
Maybe.
By the way, Stan Washington woke up.
He's gonna be fine.
[PANTING]
My responsibility.
I promise, Dad.
I promise.
Nightcap?
Well, I thought it would help me.
I don't sleep well alone.
I'm sorry about what I said tonight.
No.
You were being honest.
No, not entirely.
The truth is, with Walter being gone,
I'm...
I'm lonely.
You know, you and I used to talk.
I used to know what you were thinking.
But now, even when you're home,
you're somewhere else.
I guess I just miss my son.
I miss you too.
And I wish that...
Are you hungry?
OLIVER:
Thank you.
[POP MUSIC PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
[CHUCKLES]
All right.
Mm, Mom, heh.
It's okay to get your hands dirty
every once in a while. For me, please.
All right.
-Mm.
-Mm-hm.
-Yeah.
That is a great burger.
-Thank you for this.
-Anytime.
I'll bet Carter doesn't know where to find
the best burger joint in Starling City.
So I have one thing on him?
No.
You have everything on him, Oliver.