Previously on "Arrow"...
The Quadrant.
You know, I heard about these guys
when I was working undercover.
I never could get anyone
to confirm their existence.
Yeah, well, they are real.
High-end
cartel ruled by moneyed families
with ties to all
things black market.
We think Diaz may be
helping her with that operation.
You said you were
an honorable man.
Now, I think you
know Diaz isn't.
Help me stop him.
I'm moving on
to plan B--
killing
Oliver Queen
and everyone
he cares about.
Uh, Dad, there's a shell
in this one.
Uh, yes, there is.
Oh, isn't the pan hot?
Ow. It's immensely hot,
but when we are doing
breakfast for dinner
at Chez Queen,
we do it right.
Salt me, please,
Felicity.
What?
Could you pass the salt, please, quickly
when you get a chance?
I can not put salt
on this if it's
gonna put that
expression on your face.
It's not
about the salt, Oliver.
Ok.
Call me when dinner's ready.
Ok, well, you have
officially scared him away,
so, ahem, you want to tell
me what's going on with you?
Oliver, it's just you're
in here pretending
like you weren't almost put in prison
for the rest of your life.
Ok, we almost lost you.
And the man who tried
to put you there is
still out there
controlling the city,
and you're just in here
scrambling eggs, Oliver.
Yup. Ok, first,
I'm gonna stop him.
Second...
I am in here
scrambling eggs
because I just
wanted a night--
one night--
to remind myself
what I'm
fighting for.
Ok, I guess I can
compartmentalize that.
I can help you
with that.
Arm strength's back.
Motor function's
restored.
All signs of the nerve
damage you had are gone.
Do you mind telling me
how you did this?
Sorry, doc. NDA.
So if he's in the clear,
does that mean
no more checkups?
Well, you guys
are good to go.
- Enjoy date night.
- Thank you.
Thank you, doctor.
I'll take care
of the paperwork.
- Good.
- I think we still have time
to make
the Shabu Shabu place.
Good.
And over here is
the polyrase inhibitor.
Felicity and I had to
take out, like,
3 big loans just to buy
it, but it's great.
You know, when you asked me
to meet you at your work,
I, uh...
You thought that I had
a fantasy about
fooling around
in an office?
I thought it was your way
of milking another hour
out of work.
Well, I just thought
that you'd like to see
how I spend my days.
I mean, this is some pretty
cutting-edge tech.
Which is gonna make us
late for our reservation.
Ok, Mr. punctuality.
Let me just shut down
the rest of the equipment.
He shoots, he scores!
Nope. Off the post.
Ah, damn.
Ok, you know what?
When everything
settles down,
I'm getting us
the best seats in the house.
You do know it's like
400 bucks a ticket.
Then they will have
obstructed views.
Nah! Anything for
my baby, ok?
Dad, quiet.
At least wait for a whistle
if you want to talk.
Ok, ok.
I'll give you the courtesy
of putting that back in
before we start this.
Does it have to be
in that order?
Hyah!
- You work for Ricardo Diaz.
- Who?
You want to play that game?
Good. I need to blow off
some steam.
My mom and I used to eat
breakfast for dinner
all the time,
except it wasn't ironic,
because she worked
nights, so...
I mean, not like that!
At least I hope not.
Are you gonna get it, Dad?
No. That's one of the perks
of being impeached.
No interruptions.
Oliver, get
the phone.
Get the phone.
Ok.
Who was it?
Anatoly.
Get down!
When I move, get
William into the bedroom
and shut the door, ok?
Are you two ok?
Yeah.
Are--are they dead?
No, but they're down.
Oh.
- What?
- Trouble.
You know, you're gonna
wake up in a couple hours.
Your heads are
gonna be throbbing.
You're gonna regret
not talking.
Oh. You were just
the bait.
Lyla, behind you!
- I had him.
- I know you did, honey.
Look at me. Stay with me.
Stay with me.
Don't look.
One bullet,
back of the head.
You won't even feel it.
You know the cool thing
about sound waves?
They bounce.
Mr. Oliver?
Ohh. I'm glad you are
all right.
Thank you for coming
so quickly.
I was close.
Where are the men?
I tied them up.
They're unconscious.
Hey, I just spoke
to Rene, Dinah, and John.
They're ok.
Good. Wait.
What about Curtis?
He's ok.
His boyfriend isn't.
He has to go
into surgery.
Starling General
is not secure.
No, no. Lyla sent them to
the A.R.G.U.S. med-bay.
They're gonna be ok.
Quentin?
Quentin said that Diaz isn't gonna
attack the mayor.
He's too much in
the public eye.
But Laurel's
in the wind.
What about us?
That's why I
called Raisa, ok?
We're gonna put you into
A.R.G.U.S. custody.
They're
gonna keep you safe.
You're not coming, are you?
No. I have to stay here.
I have to finish this.
You're gonna go
with Raisa and Felicity.
Oh, actually,
buddy,
I'm not
coming either.
I would like you
far away
from here and safe.
Oliver, this is my fight
as much as it is yours.
I'm not going anywhere.
As the Green Arrow,
I have gone up against
some terrible people
who have tried to do
terrible things.
Hey, look at me.
And I'm still here.
That doesn't mean you
always will be.
You're right.
William, I just started
being your dad, ok?
I love being your dad.
And nothing is gonna
take me away from you,
especially not
Ricardo Diaz.
Kick his ass.
John and Lyla
are on their way?
Yeah. But why are you
having them come here?
Because our bunker
is not secure.
Yeah. Why would
Diaz do all of this now?
He could've moved on us
months ago.
Diaz wanted me in prison
to avoid making a martyr
of the Green Arrow.
With me out of the picture,
he would've come after you.
It didn't go that way.
Well, I'm not
liking his plan B.
This is the feed
from our surveillance cameras.
Son of a bitch.
What are we doing
just watching?
Let's go there now.
There's no time, Rene.
Diaz has numbers, which means
he has tactical advantage.
John's right.
Bunkers and equipment
can be replaced.
We need to look at
the big picture.
Are our families on the way
to the safe house?
Better. NORAD bunker
in Colorado.
Oh, no, no. Not the--
Should've done this
months ago.
Torch it.
We leave now,
we could snag a couple,
send a message.
Don't worry. You'll
get your chance.
Just have
patience, Rene.
Dinah's right.
Diaz is making his move.
We will make ours
carefully and precisely.
End this tonight.
♪ Arrow 6x22 ♪
The Ties That Bind
Original Air Date on May 10, 2018
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
How much support can we
expect from A.R.G.U.S.?
I had to stretch
the rules to get
what little resources
John has now.
As big a problem as Diaz is
for Star City--
For A.R.G.U.S.,
he's small potatoes.
What John means is
A.R.G.U.S. isn't chartered
for law enforcement.
It looks like it's
just up to us, then.
Curtis.
How's Nick?
He's resting,
post-op.
It was pretty bad,
but he's gonna be ok.
We got lucky.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
He took those
bullets for me.
Don't worry. We'll give him
payback times 10.
Where do we start?
Well, we've got to get a direct Intel
on Diaz's location.
I'm working
on that.
All right. And we need
some major-league ordnance.
That A.R.G.U.S.
can help with.
Bennet and I, we're
a force multiplier.
You know,
if we keep going this way,
we're going to die
out there.
It doesn't matter how much
weaponry Lyla provides,
how angry we are, how much
adrenaline we have.
If we just--if we just
press ahead like this,
we're all gonna die
out there.
We haven't worked
together in months.
You know, Diaz is not
expecting that at least.
He's planned
for everything.
Us getting back together,
working as a team--
it's a start,
but this guy's got an army.
He has the city officials;
He's got the police.
He's got everything.
Please tell me
there's a "but"
coming out the end
of this pep talk.
Anatoly Knyazev.
I thought he hated
your guts.
I think we've come to
an understanding.
I also think that
he might be
the one move Diaz
does not see coming.
Oliver, if that's our
tactical advantage,
we need to press it.
Let me set a meet with him, ok?
Let us make a move off
of his Intel.
But until we have it,
I want you guys to stand down,
and I...I'm asking you
to trust me.
I know that that trust
does not come easy
after everything that's
happened.
Let's put all of that aside
and get this done.
My family's alive
thanks to you.
Please save gratitude
for when I'm sipping on
umbrella straw on the beach,
safe and sound in Maldives.
I don't know how long
family's safety
going to last.
SCPD has instructions:
"Kill on sight."
Diaz's base of operations
is too secure.
We can't move on it
without losing people.
Agreed. Best bet
to get him on move--
in transit, so to speak.
Well, but he's gonna
expect us to hit back.
I'd expect him to stay
where he's secure.
Perhaps I can think of
something to motivate him.
I'm asking a lot of you.
I appreciate it.
You cannot wage revolution
in white gloves.
Lenin had many faults,
but he was right about that.
You want to stop pacing?
You're giving me a headache.
Funny. I was going to
say the same to you.
Your pitch to
the Quadrant was that
you controlled
this city.
And I do.
Then why have you turned
it into a war zone tonight?
I thought we couldn't
let the vigilantes
be turned into martyrs.
The judge kicked the case
and let Oliver Queen walk.
So you've switched gears
from careful and precise
to loud and messy?
Your attitude
is what I find...
To be unwanted.
Be careful, Ricardo.
You've already given
us the city.
Hey...
Are you suggesting that
I'm replaceable?
I'm suggesting
no such thing.
Ms. Cassamento does not
appear to be pleased.
What happened tonight?
You underestimate
your enemy.
They are strong
and motivated.
They got lucky.
Luck, strength.
What does it matter?
You did not kill bees.
You merely poked
the HIVE.
The bees will be
agitated.
You think they're gonna
come here. That's fine.
Let them bring it on.
Bring them here, hmm?
This place--lovely
but not secure,
at least not enough
for what
you know they're
going to come
after you with.
Anatoly did it.
Diaz will be on his way
to the SCPD in an hour.
A.R.G.U.S. doesn't have
authority to arrest Diaz.
So once you have him in custody,
what's the next step?
Yeah, Lyla's right. We can't just
hand him over to the police.
And, no offense, but
your Lian Yu supermax
is kind of blown up.
One problem at a time.
Now, we need to end this.
And that means solving
our first problem,
getting Diaz.
Can I say it
for old time's sake?
Suit up.
In Russia, we travel
in nicer cars.
This girl ain't pretty,
but she's bulletproof.
What's that?
Construction?
Hold up, guys. We got
to move this forklift.
Get this under control now!
Did you forget your gun?
Uh! Uh!
Curtis, don't!
You hurt someone I care
about! Want some more?
Do you?
Uh! Uh!
Quadrant reinforcements with
SCPD and more on the way.
We got to pull out now.
We almost got
that son of a bitch.
How's Curtis?
He's resting with Nick.
One inch either way,
he would've bled out.
He got lucky.
- It wasn't just luck.
- What do you mean?
Diaz could've killed Curtis,
but he went for some
sort of necklace instead.
That must be one damn important
piece of jewelry.
More like a piece
of tech. Look.
It's a GRV-567,
solid state drive,
military grade,
dynamic encryption.
Whatever's on it, Diaz has
gone to some major trouble
to keep it secure
and close, though.
This looks like something we
should have our hands on.
Wait.
How do we know?
There could be
nothing on it.
You just said so
yourself.
I mean, Diaz went after this instead
of going after Curtis.
Your digital sniffer, can it
read the drive?
Yeah. If you get me close
enough, for sure.
But Diaz is headed to SCPD.
I'm sure he's gonna let us
stroll right in.
They'll let me.
What do you mean?
Diaz knows that A.R.G.U.S.
is working against him.
The police still
have to keep up appearances.
Wouldn't look good
if they decline
a visit from the head
of a federal agency.
And if things go south,
I've got you to back me up.
I think that
this is a big gamble
for an unknown payoff.
It probably is,
Oliver,
but it might be
our only shot.
So we're
all onboard here?
Yeah.
Double
perimeter security.
Next time I see
Oliver Queen,
I want his head
on a spike!
You got it, boss.
Where's
the tech kid?
Crosby's over there.
Oh. Mr. Diaz.
I need to know if
what's on this is
still intact
without you looking
at the data.
Can you do that?
Your grandma's life
depends on it.
Yes, sir.
Close the door.
They knew!
Who? Knew what?
That I was moving,
that my men were coming
for them tonight!
Laurel--she's
buttoned up, right?
Who could've told them?
I do not know.
Hmm. You and Queen,
you go way back.
Yes, which is why his
betrayal hurt so much.
If it wasn't you...
Then who, hmm?
Who brought men and police
to help us tonight?
Cassamento.
How did she know
we'd be attacked?
I did not ask
for backup. Did you?
Why would she tip off Queen
and then drag our asses...
Out of the fire?
That doesn't make sense.
Yes, it does,
if she wants
leverage over you
to make you grovel.
Truth be telling,
I do many times before
in Bratva.
I don't grovel.
How's it going
with the sniffer?
Oh, just snifferific.
I am reprogramming it
to specifically couple
with the digital signature
of Diaz's drive.
I'll have to do some
on-the-fly programming
just to cut out the noise,
but totally
in my wheelhouse.
Does this absolutely have
to be done on site?
It absolutely does
if you
would absolutely
like it to work. Why?
Oliver, you do know
I have been on
the field before, right?
Russia, twice.
Nanda Parbat,
Merlyn Global.
That all happened before
you were a parent.
Well, if it will make
you feel any better,
I will not be the one infiltrating
the precinct.
That'll be Lyla,
the same Lyla who's
also a parent
and whose husband
didn't blink twice
when she volunteered
to go into Diaz's dragon den.
Lyla's a soldier.
Yeah, which is why she's
the one infiltrating
and I'm the one
hacking remotely.
I'm not gonna do
anything stupid.
Do we have
a problem here?
No. Ready when you are.
All I have to do is position that
someplace central?
Yes, if Diaz's drive is in that building,
sniffer will find it.
I can monitor
the transfer from here,
but I need this back
for full pull.
How much time do you
need for the transfer?
A couple minutes, Max.
Copy that.
Everybody in position?
In position.
First hint anything's wrong,
signal us.
Copy.
We move in 5.
Everything ok?
Yeah. It's just--
it's so nice to see
how you and John, you know,
work when you're out in the field,
because you're so in sync.
How do you do it?
You're asking
for marital advice? Now?
Sorry. Yeah,
totally terrible timing.
It's just that, like, Oliver
doesn't even want me here.
So I just thought maybe
a tip or two would work.
We always knew our lives
would be high risk.
Eventually we got
to a point
where worrying
about that
seemed less important
than enjoying the time
we have together,
even if that was
on a battlefield.
Oh, that's so sweet.
Also, getting divorced
helps.
Can I help you
with something?
Lyla Michaels.
Where can I find
your captain?
We're kind of
between captains
since our ex-mayor fired
the last one.
What's A.R.G.U.S.
doing here?
Investigating
Ricardo Diaz.
Never heard of him.
Well, be that as it may,
I'm gonna need to see your compstat
reports over the last 6 months.
Oh.
You do not want to make me
come back with a warrant.
Wait here.
You're on, Felicity.
All right. Locked on.
Give it a few minutes.
Data all seems intact,
Mr. Diaz.
We got a problem?
I'm not sure.
You better get sure.
Yes, sir.
Guys, the encryption array,
it's Corto Maltesian
in origin.
What does that mean?
I mean, I don't know,
but if I was betting, financial records.
What if these are
all of Diaz's books,
everyone he has
on his payroll?
We could liberate
the city,
take down
his whole operation.
The data is being copied--
cloned, actually.
What?
It's happening onsite
somehow.
Some bitch from A.R.G.U.S.
is here.
She wants to look at our
compstat reports.
No, she doesn't.
Lyla, we're done.
Grab the sniffer.
Agent Michaels, talk
to you for a minute?
They're on to us.
Forget the device.
Just get out of there!
Director Michaels,
I heard you're
interested in me.
Honey...
You better get
in here.
Oh, frak it.
Hey.
Sorry, not sorry!
- Quick! Hurry.
- Ok.
That was an all-out
fight with the SCPD.
Totally nuts,
even by my standards.
Yeah, but it was
the only option.
I mean, this was
too important not to get.
How would you even know?
This is supposed to be encrypted.
Well, you can just call me an optimist
because I'm thinking
in 2-3 hours, all of us are
gonna be extremely happy.
Can you gather information
as it decrypts?
It'd be nice to get
a jump on things.
Oh, no, no, no.
No, no, no.
This is an all-or-nothing
type deal, ok?
We go in mid-decryption,
and the whole drive wipes.
Nothing.
Felicity, may I speak
with you?
Yes.
I'm gonna just take
a wild guess and say
that this isn't one of
those conversations
that starts with, like,
"I love you. You were brave.
You go. That was awesome."
No. This is
a conversation
that happens
because I love you.
Ok.
You promised me you
would stay put.
Well, I didn't exactly
promise.
Fine. You promised
me you wouldn't do anything stupid.
You charged into
a firefight.
Which was a calculated risk.
Did you calculate how
close Ricardo Diaz came
to shooting you in
the back of the head?
We got what we wanted.
That's not--
And if I'm right,
what we wanted has
the list of everyone in
the city that Diaz controls.
This could help us get our
home back from Diaz, Oliver.
We could actually save
our city this time around.
I think that's a little bit
more important
than what ifs.
This is why I started
working alone again.
Yeah. You know what?
I tried convincing myself
that that was the right move, too,
but it's not because
we're married
and we're supposed to be
each other's strength.
So there is no alone
for us anymore.
It's not that simple,
and you know it.
God. I'm really gonna
start needing you to see it that way.
Hey. What the hell are
you doing here?
I heard Felicity might've got a hold
of Diaz's payroll,
so I hitched a ride
back with John.
I can help
with the decryption. Unh.
Whoa, whoa, Curtis.
Hey, are you crazy?
You are in no shape
to be up and about.
A deranged madman
attacked everyone
I hold dear
and near to me.
I'll nap later.
He also made you
almost bleed out,
so I need you to stop, ok?
Curtis...
How is me resting gonna
help anything, Dinah?
Ok, but being reckless isn't
gonna help anything either.
He almost killed my man.
What do you expect
my reaction to be?
Exactly the same as mine.
I'm sorry. I...
I wasn't thinking
about Vincent.
I'm so sorry, Dinah.
Because you--you shouldn't
be thinking about Vincent.
You need to be thinking
about Nick.
Just please
don't go about this
the same way that I did,
Curtis, blind with rage.
Remember how you had
to talk me down?
I remember my advice
not really taking.
Yeah. But you're a lot
smarter than me.
Look, Nick is lying
in a hospital bed right now.
If you don't take it easy,
you're gonna end up
right back in one.
We got this.
Go be with him.
That's absurd.
Why would I tip off
the Green Arrow
only to save you from him?
You tell me.
You're delusional.
You ought to be thanking me.
I hacked, and I
hacked, and I...
I--I back-traced where
Felicity Smoak took your cloned data.
We can get there
before she decrypts it.
Good work.
Call everyone.
We're going to war.
War? You've already
shot up two apartments
and a hospital to say
nothing about what happened
in your own police station.
Your point?
You're out of control
and out of your depth,
Ricardo.
We accepted you into
the Quadrant because--
So sorry.
I couldn't hear you.
You have something
stuck in your throat.
Clean this up.
Felicity says that
the decryption is
only at about 40%.
I'm sure she's working
as fast as she can.
I'm quite sure she is,
but maybe we need to come up
with a backup plan
just in case this doesn't
pan out the way we think.
I agree, and I'm open
to suggestions.
The first thing
is figuring out
what's going on
in your head.
Yeah? What else
you guys talk about?
I may have
prodded her a bit.
But, Oliver,
I really didn't need to.
Everyone could see
the tension between the two of you.
Well, John, I asked her
not to go into the field.
And she did.
And I'm sorry that she
thinks I'm changing the rules for her,
but I am changing
the rules for her
because things
have changed.
William.
Well, Diaz's people
attacked us in our home,
sitting down for a meal
in our home,
so don't ask me to sit here and
pretend like things aren't different.
And you--you told me
that I had spread myself too thin,
and I listened
to what you said.
And I took it to heart,
and I made some changes.
She went into
the field tonight,
she split my focus,
and it could've gotten
both of us killed.
- But it didn't.
- Well, it--
truth is you were there
for her tonight
the same way she's been
there for you as Overwatch.
And, look, when
I said that your focus was split,
I didn't mean throwing
away everything and everyone
that gives you strength.
Diaz is here
with an army.
Oliver Queen doesn't
make it out alive!
- Tricelic gas is filling the building.
- This is Diaz.
His men breached the northeast entry.
Between that and the gas,
- we don't have a lot of time.
- Are there any other ways
- out of here?
- South corridor.
There's a secret stairwell
that leads to street level.
If anything goes sideways,
Curtis rigged
the whole place
to go boom.
Let's hope it doesn't  come to that,
all right? We got to go--
- not yet.
- Felicity, we have to go now.
The decryption is not done.
I'm not leaving until it's done.
Do not fight me on this.
Everyone else has to go.
We will catch up.
I'll cover you! Go!
Whoa!
Get out of here!
Go! Get out of here!
Get back!
Uh!
I had him, honey.
Let's go.
How much time
do we have?
5 minutes.
We don't have
5 minutes, Felicity.
You have to get out of here.
No chance.
Once this decryption's done,
I'm gonna email it to you
and basically
the entire world.
Hey, you ok?
This is our
last chance, Oliver.
This could be
our only chance to stop him.
Let me try.
William needs you.
William needs us.
I'm gonna find
another way.
Come on.
How many flights
are there?
A lot.
Where's Oliver
and Felicity?
All right. We're almost
there, Felicity.
You can do this. Hey.
I got you. Up, up.
I was just
coming to kill you.
Looks like you met
me halfway.
What hurts more,
do you think,
killing her in front of you
or you in front of her?
Hyah!
You'll do anything to keep
her safe, won't you?
Love--
that's the real
king killer!
Click it.
Come on, Felicity.
Felicity, Oliver.
Let's get them out of here.
I'm so sorry about
your men, Lyla.
Bennet was a good soldier.
They all were.
We should go back.
I want to see
Diaz's body.
I sent in
a forensics team.
He wasn't
there.
Son of a bitch
has 9 lives.
I'm sorry.
Did Felicity finish
the decryption?
No.
No. She had to leave it.
Where does that put us?
Absolutely nowhere.
I know, buddy.
We miss you, too.
Well, it's gonna be
a few more days,
but we're...
We're safe, ok?
We're both safe.
Hey, we love you, William.
Bye, kiddo.
Is he ok? How's he doing?
He's ok.
He's scared,
but, you know,
he's safe and...
Just wants
all this to be over.
Yeah.
Don't we all?
Hey, I'm, uh...
I shouldn't have
pushed you away.
I should have trusted you
to keep yourself safe,
and I should have
trusted my abilities
to help keep you safe.
Thank you.
Yeah.
It's good to know
after all these years
that you can still
learn something.
Nah, I still have
a ways to go.
That's true.
So what now?
I have an idea.
Thank you for coming.
I asked you here
because we lost another
Quadrant member last night.
See, I don't
mind partners...
When they're loyal.
Turns out
Ms. Cassamento wasn't.
So what I have to decide
right now is
whether you two fall
into that same category.
You wanted
into Quadrant.
You are in.
This doesn't have to
be adversarial.
See, that's the thing--
me wanting in.
I always thought that
I wanted that,
and I realized...
It's just not enough.
You don't want
a partnership.
You want
a controlling stake.
Guilty.
Let's try this again. May I?
We have the Quadrant's
resources.
We got its muscle,
its connections.
All I need...
Is loyalty.
The Quadrant's running
out of members.
Do I have it?
So far Ricardo Diaz
has been unstoppable.
He has aligned himself
with the most powerful
criminal organization
in the country.
He controls Star City's
government,
its infrastructure,
and its police force.
I can't stop him
on my own.
And when you say you
can't stop him,
are you speaking as
the former mayor
or as someone else?
You want my help? I'm gonna
need two things from you.
The first is I'm gonna
need you to say the words.
I am the Green Arrow.
And the truth
shall set you free.
What's the second thing?
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man