PREVIOUSLY ON "ARROW"...
YOU KILL BECAUSE YOU
LIKE IT.
THAT'S NOT TRUE,
ANATOLY.
SOMEDAY IS GOING
TO FALL APART,
AND WHEN IT DOES, YOU'RE
NOT GOING TO LIKE
THE MAN YOU SEE UNDERNEATH.
YOU DON'T HAVE
TO DO THIS.
YES, I DO.
UNH!
YOU HELPED ME
DISCOVER WHO I AM.
THAT'S WHAT I'M GONNA
HELP YOU DO, OLIVER.
YOU DON'T KILL BECAUSE
YOU HAVE TO. SO WHY?
I WANTED TO!
AND I LIKED IT!
JOHN: WE'RE GONNA GET
THIS SON OF A BITCH
FOR WHATEVER HE DID TO YOU.
OLIVER: I DON'T WANT
TO DO THIS ANYMORE.
I'M SHUTTING
EVERYTHING DOWN.
[CLEARS THROAT]
JOHN: OLIVER,
WHAT HAPPENED?
YEAH. WHAT DID YOU MEAN BY
"SHUTTING THIS ALL DOWN"?
OLIVER, I REALLY THINK THAT
YOU SHOULD BE CHECKED OUT
BY AN ACTUAL DOCTOR.
THE ONLY THING I NEED
IS FOR ALL OF YOU
TO GO HOME.
OLIVER, WE'RE NOT
GOING ANYWHERE.
NOT A SUGGESTION, JOHN.
DON'T YOU THINK YOU AT LEAST
OWE US AN EXPLANATION?
THE EXPLANATION IS SIMPLE.
CHASE IS RIGHT.
EVERYONE THAT IS, UH,
DOWN HERE, AROUND ME...
WELL, THEY EITHER SUFFER
OR THEY DIE.
OLIVER, I CAN'T IMAGINE
WHAT YOU'VE JUST
BEEN PUT THROUGH,
BUT YOU HAVE TO KNOW
THAT CHASE IS WRONG.
I DON'T THINK
THAT HE IS.
AND I CAN'T...
WOULD YOU JUST GO,
PLEASE?
CAN, UH, THE TWO OF YOU
GIVE US THE ROOM?
IT'S JUST YOU AND ME NOW,
OLIVER.
AND YOU DON'T HAVE TO TALK
TO ME IF YOU DON'T WANT TO,
BUT I DON'T THINK YOU
SHOULD BE ALONE.
I THINK I SHOULD.
JOHN, I WANT YOU
TO LEAVE.
RENE: HE SAID
ALL THAT?
FELICITY: I'VE NEVER
SEEN HIM SO BROKEN,
AND I'VE SEEN HIM
AT HIS LOWEST.
DID HE SAY WHAT CHASE
DID TO HIM?
CURTIS: NOPE.
DON'T WANT TO KNOW.
I ALREADY HAVE
MORE THAN ENOUGH
NIGHTMARE FUEL
FROM THIS JOB
TO LAST ME
A WHILE, SO...
L...LE...LET'S BACK UP
A SECOND.
HE SAID THE TEAM'S OVER?
LIKE, WE'RE SUPPOSED
TO JUST SIT BACK
AND LET CHASE RUN WILD?
NOBODY'S
SITTING AROUND, RENE.
LOOK, OLIVER'S
IN A BAD PLACE RIGHT NOW,
BUT HE WILL GET IT TOGETHER.
I DON'T HAVE TO REMIND ANY
OF YOU OF HOW STRONG HE IS.
-WHAT DID THEA SAY?
-SHE AGREED.
HE JUST NEEDS TIME
TO GET HIS HEAD RIGHT.
SHE SAYS SHE'LL CONTACT
HIM ONCE WE UPDATE HER.
I DON'T KNOW. THIS TIME,
IT JUST SEEMS DIFFERENT.
HE WILL BOUNCE BACK,
FELICITY. HE WILL.
UNTIL THEN, WE ARE THIS
CITY'S LAST LINE OF DEFENSE.
EXCEPT OUR GEAR'S
BACK AT THE BUNKER.
OLIVER REPROGRAMMED ALL
THE SECURITY PROTOCOLS.
LYLA WILL LOAN US GEAR
FROM ARGUS.
AND WHAT ABOUT CHASE?
HE'S STILL OUT THERE.
JOHN: WE JUST HAVE
TO REMAIN ALERT.
WE'RE NOT JUST THE
ANTI-PROMETHEUS TEAM.
THERE ARE A LOT OF
PEOPLE IN THIS CITY
WHO NEED SAVING.
I'M ON CHASE.
YOU GUYS JUST FOCUS
ON PROTECTING THE CITY.
FEEL FREE TO USE
MY APARTMENT
AS YOUR NEW SECRET LAIR.
WHERE IS SHE GOING?
NO PLACE GOOD.
[HEAVY SIGH]
WELL, THE CITY COUNCIL
BOUGHT MY STORY
ABOUT YOUR, UH,
SPIRITUAL RETREAT.
AND IT TURNS OUT
COUNCILWOMAN POLLARD IS
A BIG FAN OF ALL THAT
STUFF.
YOU KNOW,
THE WOO-WOO ZEN STUFF.
[CLEARS THROAT]
LOOK, EH, I'M NOT ASKING
WHAT HE DID TO YOU,
ALL RIGHT?
ALL I GOT TO KNOW IS
WHAT WE'RE GONNA
DO TO HIM.
I MEAN, NOTHING.
IT'S OVER.
WELL, HOW DO YOU
FIGURE THAT?
CHASE DOESN'T GIVE
UP EASY.
HE DOESN'T NEED TO DO
ANYTHING.
HE'S ALREADY WON.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
MR. MAYOR, YOUR
11:00 IS HERE.
THANK YOU FOR YOUR
COMPASSION
IN GRANTING ME
BEREAVEMENT LEAVE,
MR. MAYOR. UH...
DORIS' DEATH HAS
BEEN VERY DIFFICULT.
YEAH? WELL,
MAYBE YOU SHOULDN'T
HAVE KILLED HER, THEN.
I'D LIKE TO SPEAK TO
THE MAYOR IN PRIVATE.
THAT'S NOT GONNA HAPPEN.
QUENTIN, PLEASE JUST...
[SCOFFS]
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
YOU WON. IT'S OVER.
WHAT DID I EVER SAY
THAT GAVE YOU
THAT IMPRESSION?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
PROVING A POINT,
SO TO SPEAK.
YOU THINK I'M GONNA STAB
THE DISTRICT ATTORNEY
IN THE MIDDLE
OF CITY HALL?
YOU'RE AN ANIMAL
WHO ENJOYS MURDER.
THERE'S NO TELLING
WHAT YOU'LL DO.
AND IT'S NOT LIKE YOUR
ALTER EGO CAN KILL ME,
NOT SINCE THE SCPD PUT
ME IN PROTECTIVE CUSTODY
SINCE THE GREEN ARROW
SLAUGHTERED MY WIFE.
SO YOU KILL ME IN
BROAD DAYLIGHT,
OR YOU LET ME LIVE
KNOWING THAT THERE'S
NOTHING YOU CAN DO.
DISAPPOINTING.
YOU CAN KEEP THAT KNIFE.
IDEA OF RETURNING
TO LIAN YU
MAKES ME WEEP LIKE
TINY BABY,
BUT OLIVER QUEEN,
HE PLAN VACATION THERE.
IT'S NOT A VACATION,
ANATOLY.
PEOPLE ARE GONNA WANT
TO KNOW WHERE I'VE BEEN
FOR THE PAST,
NEARLY, 5 YEARS.
LIAN YU IS
THE SIMPLEST ANSWER.
IT'S GOOD TO SEE YOU
THINKING ABOUT THE FUTURE.
I ONLY WISH I HAD MORE
TIME TO SPEND
WITH THIS OLIVER QUEEN.
YOU HAVE 48 HOURS.
I KNOW JUST HOW
TO SPEND THEM.
IN OLD DAYS, BRATVA USED
TO WORK ON BEHALF
OF RUSSIAN PEOPLE.
THEN SELFISH LEADERS LIKE
GREGOR CORRUPTED OUR CAUSE.
SO THE NEW PAKHAN WANTS
TO BRING THE BRATVA
BACK TO ITS ROOTS.
THE NEW PAKHAN
NEEDS YOUR HELP.
I FEAR I CANNOT REBUILD
BROTHERHOOD
WITHOUT YOU, OLIVER.
LIKE I SAID,
YOU HAVE 48 HOURS.
HEY. I FINISHED THAT WORM.
I WOULD'VE BEEN A LOT
FASTER IF I KNEW
WHAT KIND OF SYSTEM
I WAS EMBEDDING
A BACKDOOR INTO, BUT...
YOUR TIMING IS PERFECT.
I JUST FINISHED
THE COMPILATION.
THIS IS ALL THAT WE
FOUND ON YOUR TARGET
FROM ALL AVAILABLE
VIDEO SOURCES...
CELL PHONES, TRAFFIC
CAMS, SECURITY FOOTAGE.
PLEASE PROMISE ME YOU'RE
NEVER GONNA MAKE
A FELICITY VERSION OF THIS.
THE WORLD DOESN'T
NEED TO KNOW
HOW OFTEN I'M
AT THE WINE SHOP.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
I GUESS IT'S TOO MUCH
TO HOPE THAT CHASE TOOK
OFF HIS MASK ON CAMERA.
ACTUALLY, HE DID.
YEAH, I FIGURED HE
WOULDN'T. WAIT. WHAT?
WHY IS HIS FACE
ALL PIXILATED?
WE'RE ASSUMING THE USE
OF OPTICS SCRAMBLING.
HE'S GOT TECH
THAT PREVENTS A CAMERA
FROM CAPTURING HIS IMAGE?
LIKE THOSE SCARVES
THAT CELEBRITIES USE
TO FRUSTRATE PAPARAZZI.
OH, YEAH.
BUT HERE'S THE THING, IF
HE'S USING A PIECE OF TECH...
BOTH:
WE CAN REVERSE ENGINEER IT.
IF WE CAN PRODUCE VIDEO
THAT CHASE IS PROMETHEUS,
THAT'S GAME OVER FOR HIM.
LET'S GET STARTED.
HEY.
THEY TOLD ME YOU
WERE BACK.
I HAD TO SEE YOU.
OH. I'M SO SORRY.
THIS WASN'T YOU,
OLIVER.
IT WAS HIM.
WELL, I...I CREATED HIM.
AND I KNOW THAT
THAT MIGHT SOUND WEIRD,
BUT, UH, THIS HAPPENED
TO YOU BECAUSE OF ME.
DON'T LET HIM
DO THIS TO YOU.
DON'T LET THAT BASTARD
INSIDE YOUR HEAD.
I GAVE THE POLICE
A STATEMENT ABOUT HIM.
BUT THEY DIDN'T BELIEVE YOU
BECAUSE HE PROBABLY HAD
AN IRONCLAD ALIBI, RIGHT?
YES. BUT IF YOU
CORROBORATE MY STATEMENT...
I CAN'T.
I KNOW. IT...IT WOULD
PROBABLY MEAN OUTING
YOURSELF AS
THE GREEN ARROW, BUT...
IT HAS NOTHING TO DO
WITH THAT.
IT HAS TO DO WITH
THE FACT THAT CHASE
WOULD HAVE PLANNED FOR THAT
JUST LIKE HE HAS PLANNED
FOR EVERYTHING ELSE.
MY ONLY CHANCE IS...WELL,
I HAVE TO DO SOMETHING
THAT HE HASN'T PLANNED FOR.
WELL, LIKE WHAT?
LISTEN, SUSAN,
I KNOW THAT...
W...WE NEVER GOT A CHANCE
TO RESOLVE THINGS.
I CAN'T BE WITH YOU.
MY APOLOGIES
IF THAT'S PRESUMPTUOUS.
O...OLIVER...
THIS IS NOT HOW...
THIS IS NOT HOW I WANTED
MY LIFE TO...TO TOUCH YOURS.
I SHOULD HAVE KNOWN BETTER,
AND FOR THAT, I REALLY,
TRULY AM SORRY.
THANK YOU FOR BEING HERE
ON SUCH SHORT NOTICE.
I UNDERSTAND THAT AFTER
LAST TIME,
I HAVE RUN OUT OF FAVORS.
BUT THIS IS AN IMPOSSIBLE
SITUATION,
AND YOU'RE MY ONLY OPTION.
OBVIOUSLY.
LAST TIME YOU MADE
VERY CLEAR
YOU DID NOT WANT
BRATVA IN CITY.
CIRCUMSTANCES
HAVE CHANGED.
I NEED YOU TO KILL
ADRIAN CHASE.
ANATOLY: INTERESTING.
I NEVER THOUGHT YOU
WOULD GIVE UP THE HOOD.
WELL, YOU WERE THE ONE
WHO TOLD ME IT WAS SILLY
TO THINK THAT A...
A PIECE OF CLOTH COULD
CONTAIN
THE MONSTER
INSIDE OF ME FOREVER.
YOU WERE RIGHT.
SUCH A BURDEN,
ALWAYS BEING RIGHT.
LIFE HAS NO SECRETS.
I SHOULD'VE LISTENED
TO YOU BACK THEN.
AT LEAST NOW YOU
SEE SELF CLEARLY.
MAN MUST KNOW WHO HE IS
IN ORDER TO BE HAPPY.
YOU THINK I DESERVE
TO BE HAPPY?
WHY NOT?
I AM HAPPY.
[CHUCKLES]
MY OLD FRIEND HAS FINALLY
REMEMBERED HIS OATH
AND IS ABOUT TO MAKE
HIS BROTHERS VERY RICH.
YOU SHOULD BE
HAPPY, TOO.
I JUST WANT TO SEE
ADRIAN CHASE IN THE GROUND.
YOU'LL BE PLEASED
TO KNOW I'VE GOT
ONLY THE BEST
MEN WITH ME.
I'LL GET YOU CHASE'S
SCHEDULE
AND KNOWN LOCATIONS.
OTLICHNO.
THERE IS ONLY SMALL MATTER
OF MY DOWN PAYMENT.
THERE'S NO DOWN PAYMENT,
ANATOLY.
I WANT CHASE DEAD
IMMEDIATELY.
AFTER LAST TIME, I NEED
SMALL GESTURE
OF GOODWILL
SO MY MEN CAN SEE THAT
YOU ARE SERIOUS.
IT'S LIKE YOU AMERICANS
SAY, "LET'S MAKE DEAL."
YOU SAID THAT YOUR FEE
HAS TWO PARTS, YES?
DA.
I WILL MAKE SURE THAT YOU
ACQUIRE THE FIRST TONIGHT.
YOU GET THE SECOND
WHEN YOU TAKE CHASE OUT.
SEE? I KNEW WE COULD
BOTH BE REASONABLE.
[CHUCKLES]
LET'S TOAST.
PLEASE TELL ME YOU DID
NOT PUT AWAY THE VODKA.
FELICITY: ADRIAN CHASE,
WINTER IS HERE.
IT'S SPRING.
WE'RE GONNA TALK ABOUT
YOU NOT WATCHING
"GAME OF THRONES,"
BUT FIRST, LOOK AT THIS.
THE PIXILATION PATTERN
WAS CONSISTENT
WITH THAT
OF AN OPTICS SCRAMBLER
THAT KORD INDUSTRIES
IS PLANNING
ON BRINGING TO MARKET
IN THE NEXT 6 MONTHS.
HOW DOES IT WORK?
IT INTERFERES WITH
THE CAMERA'S DIGITAL
CONVERSION CIRCUIT.
THAT'S GOOD! THAT MEANS
WE CAN USE AN ALGORITHM
TO REMOVE THE DISTORTION
FROM THE EXISTING IMAGE.
YES, BUT TO DO THAT,
I WOULD NEED PHYSICAL ACCESS
TO CHASE'S SCRAMBLER.
OH, I'M SURE HE'D BE
HAPPY TO HELP.
SOUNDS LIKE
A SUPER-ACCOMMODATING GUY.
GREAT.
RENE: I'VE SEEN MORE
FIREPOWER IN THE STANDS
AT A DOGS GAME.
LYLA CAN ONLY
AUTHORIZE HARDWARE THAT
WOULDN'T BE MISSED.
HEY. HAVE YOU HEARD
FROM FELICITY?
IT'D BE NICE FOR HER
TO HAVE OUR BACKS
WHEN WE HIT THE STREETS.
RADIO SILENCE SINCE SHE
LEFT FOR HELIX,
BUT WITHOUT OUR COMS, I'M
NOT SURE SHE'D BE MUCH HELP.
WE HAVE THESE.
[COMPUTER BUZZING]
WE HAVE A BREAK-IN
AT BATOON MEDICAL
RESEARCH LABORATORIES.
LET'S MOVE OUT.
TALK TO ME, CURTIS.
WITHOUT THE INFRARED
FROM OUR BODY CAMS,
WE WON'T BE ABLE TO PULL
HEAT SIGNATURES.
SO WE WON'T REALLY
KNOW HOW MANY HOSTILES
WE'RE UP AGAINST.
ALSO, THIS MASK IS REALLY
MAKING MY FACE ITCH.
PERIMETER SWEEP HAS TWO
TANGOS AT THE BACK ENTRANCE.
NO OTHERS.
I KNOW WE DON'T HAVE
OUR TRANQ AMMO,
BUT I NEED THIS DONE AS
CLEAN AND BLOODLESS
AS POSSIBLE.
NOT A PROBLEM.
I'M ALL FOR BLOOD,
BUT LOOK AT THE LABEL
ON THOSE CRATES...OPLIMID.
THAT'S A DIABETES DRUG.
[MAN GROANS]
BACK ENTRANCE IS CLEAR.
SPARTAN AND WILD DOG
MOVING IN.
JOHN: HANDS UP. HANDS UP.
HANDS UP. HANDS UP.
HANDS UP. HANDS UP!
HE DOESN'T LIKE
REPEATING HIMSELF.
[SPEAKING RUSSIAN]
CURTIS: THAT SOUNDS
LIKE RUSSIAN.
BROS'TE ORUZHIYE.
ANATOLY: LOOK,
THIS ONE'S ACCENT
HAS NOT IMPROVED.
STILL SOUNDS HORRIBLE.
ANATOLY.
JOHN DIGGLE,
MY FAVORITE AMERICAN.
RENE: WE KNOW THIS GUY?
JOHN: WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU
DOING IN STAR CITY?
ISN'T IT OBVIOUS?
[SPEAKING RUSSIAN]
ANATOLY, I CAN'T LET YOU
STEAL THESE DRUGS.
IT'S NOT MATTER OF "LET."
I HAVE INVITATION
TO BE HERE.
INVITATION? FROM WHOM?
OLIVER, HAVE YOU BROUGHT
ANATOLY KNYAZEV TO STAR CITY?
YES, I DID.
AND HE JUST TOLD ME
THAT HIS OPERATION
WAS NEARLY COMPROMISED
BY MY TEAM.
WELL, I SAID,
"THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
THE TEAM NO LONGER
EXISTS."
THE HELL IT DOESN'T!
WHEN I TOLD YOU TO STAND
DOWN, I MEANT IT.
ANATOLY IS HERE
FOR A REASON.
TO STEAL DRUGS.
I HAD TO GIVE HIM THAT
TO GET WHAT I WANTED.
HE'S HERE TO KILL
ADRIAN CHASE.
OLIVER.
WE DON'T HIRE CRIMINALS
AND PAY THEM
WITH DIABETES DRUGS.
CHASE HAS KILLED
INNOCENT PEOPLE
IN THIS WHOLE SICK GAME
HE'S BEEN PLAYING,
TRYING TO GET TO ME.
STAR CITY WILL NOT
BE SAFE
UNTIL HE IS
IN THE GROUND,
AND THERE IS NO PRICE
I WILL NOT PAY
TO SEE THAT HAPPEN.
EVEN SELLING YOUR SOUL?
BETTER MY SOUL
THAN YOURS
OR FELICITY'S OR CURTIS'
OR ANYONE ON THE TEAM.
SO YOU GOT ANATOLY
TO KILL CHASE
SO WE WOULDN'T HAVE TO.
I CREATED PROMETHEUS,
JOHN.
I CREATED
THIS WHOLE THING.
CHASE'S DEATH SHOULD BE
ON MY CONSCIENCE,
NOT YOURS.
WHAT THE HELL DID CHASE
DO TO YOU, MAN,
TO CONVINCE YOU TO THINK
THAT ANY OF THIS IS OK?
THIS IS A MISTAKE, OLIVER,
A MISTAKE THAT YOU WILL NOT
BE ABLE TO COME BACK FROM.
AND I'M NOT
GONNA LET YOU MAKE IT.
WELL, I'M NOT GONNA
LET YOU GET HURT.
AND SO HERE WE ARE.
FELICITY WAS RIGHT.
PROMETHEUS TRYING TO
CONVINCE YOU THAT YOU ARE
RESPONSIBLE
FOR EVERYTHING BAD
THAT'S HAPPENED TO PEOPLE,
OLIVER, I SWEAR THAT'S
JUST A BUNCH OF CRAP.
TELL THAT TO LAUREL.
TELL THAT TO...TOMMY.
TELL THAT
TO MY MOTHER.
TO BILLY MALONE.
MAYBE TELL IT TO THEA.
SHE'S SO DAMAGED THAT
SHE HAD TO LEAVE TOWN.
THIS IS NOT
POST-TRAUMATIC
STRESS, JOHN.
THIS IS A TRUTH THAT I
WAS KEEPING MYSELF
FROM SEEING, AND I AM
NO LONGER DOING THAT.
ANATOLY AND HIS MEN WILL
KILL ADRIAN CHASE.
THAT IS THE SOLUTION.
THE TEAM IS DONE.
SO I'M TELLING YOU.
I'M NOT ASKING YOU.
I'M TELLING YOU...
FOR THE LAST TIME,
STAND DOWN.
I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
REALLY? I MEAN, OLIVER
CAN'T GO AFTER CHASE HIMSELF,
SO HE FINDS GUYS WHO CAN?
HE LET THEM STEAL
FROM A COMPANY
THAT WAS BARELY HANGING ON.
OLIVER PUT HUNDREDS
OF JOBS ON THE LINE.
AND I KNOW HE KNOWS
THAT 'CAUSE I WAS
IN THE SAME BRIEFING.
YEAH. SPEAKING
OF WHICH,
WHY HAVEN'T YOU GONE
BACK INTO CITY HALL?
JOHN: BECAUSE LANCE
BANNED HIM TILL CHASE
IS TAKEN OFF THE BOARD.
SOMETHING TO DO WITH RENE
THREATENING TO "POP A CAP
IN HIS ASS."
WHAT ABOUT BREAKING
UP THE TEAM?
[SIGHS]
PROMETHEUS IS IN OLIVER'S
HEAD, CURTIS,
LIKE I'VE NEVER SEEN BEFORE.
HEY. CAN WE
TALK IN PRIVATE?
UM...YEAH.
YEAH.
HEY.
YOU AND I NEED TO
TALK SOME SENSE
INTO OLIVER BEFORE
HE DOES SOMETHING
THAT HE'S GONNA
REGRET.
I'M NOT STOPPING YOU.
WELL, FELICITY, I KNOW
YOU'RE FULL THROTTLE
WITH THIS HELIX,
BUT IT HAS TO BE
THE BOTH OF US.
WE HAVE TO PRESENT
A UNITED FRONT
SO WE HAVE
THE BEST CHANCE OF
GETTING THROUGH TO HIM.
-WELL, MAYBE WE SHOULDN'T.
-WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
THE TEAM HAS BEEN AFTER
CHASE FOR MONTHS,
AND HE'S ALWAYS BEEN
ONE STEP AHEAD OF US.
IF OLIVER THINKS THAT THE
BRATVA IS OUR BEST CHANCE
AT GETTING TO HIM,
THEN MAYBE WE SHOULD STAY
OUT OF HIS WAY.
AND WHEN CHEMICALS
FROM BOTH
MEDICINES BIND,
IT CREATES
POWERFUL OPIOID.
IT'S MORE ADDICTIVE
THAN HEROIN.
JUST WHAT
THE WORLD NEEDS.
REVENUE IS
WHAT BRATVA NEEDS.
IT'S GOTTEN BAD, OLIVER.
I'M UNDER MUCH PRESSURE.
TH...THIS DRUG
WILL HELP SECURE
MY POSITION AS PAKHAN.
SO THAT'S WHY YOU NEED
THE MEDICINE.
TO MANUFACTURE
A STREET DRUG.
YOU SHOULDN'T
BE HERE, JOHN.
YOU SHOULD'VE KNOWN
THAT CURTIS WOULD HACK
THE LOCKS, OLIVER.
I DIDN'T THINK I COULD BE
MORE DISAPPOINTED.
I GUESS I WAS WRONG.
I'LL LET YOU HAVE ROOM.
I'M NOT GONNA KEEP
HAVING
THE SAME
CONVERSATION.
THAT'S TOO BAD 'CAUSE I
DEDICATED 5 YEARS OF MY LIFE
TO YOUR CRUSADE.
SO I'M THE ONE THAT GETS
TO SAY IF I NEED PROTECTING,
NOT YOU.
I'M NOT GONNA HAVE
YOUR DEATH
ON MY CONSCIENCE.
OLIVER, DON'T TALK TO ME
ABOUT YOUR CONSCIENCE,
NOT WHEN YOU GET BACK
IN BED WITH THE BRATVA.
THIS ISN'T YOU, MAN.
THE OLIVER I KNOW
WOULD NEVER LET
A GROUP OF DANGEROUS
CRIMINALS
CRAWL INTO HIS CITY,
LET THEM STEAL MEDICINE.
YOU DON'T KNOW
WHAT KIND OF MAN I AM.
WHAT?!
WHAT THE HELL DID CHASE
DO TO YOU, OLIVER?
WHATEVER IT WAS, HE M...HE
MESSED WITH YOUR HEAD
IN A WAY I DIDN'T THINK
WAS POSSIBLE.
LOOK AT ME, MAN.
I COULD HELP YOU.
I'M YOUR BROTHER.
YOU DON'T WANT ME
AS A BROTHER.
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
CHASE SHOWED ME
THE TRUTH ABOUT MYSELF.
YOU SIGNED ON
FOR A CRUSADE
THAT TURNED OUT TO BE
AN OUTLET.
IT WAS AN EXCUSE
FOR ME TO MURDER
PEOPLE.
OLIVER, PLEASE.
I PUT ON A HOOD,
AND I CREATED A PERSONA
BECAUSE, JOHN,
SOMEWHERE ALONG THE WAY,
SOMETHING IN ME BROKE.
SOMETHING IS SICK
INSIDE OF ME.
THE CRUSADE...
ALL OF THIS...
THE FOUNDATION
OF IT IS A LIE.
SO I DISBANDED
THE TEAM
BECAUSE I WON'T
SIT BY
AND WATCH ALL OF YOU
PARTICIPATE
IN MY MURDER SPREE.
I AM
BEYOND REDEMPTION.
YOU AND THE TEAM
WILL BE FINE
IF...YOU STAY AWAY
FROM ME,
YOU STAY AWAY
FROM THIS,
FROM CHASE,
AND YOU ALLOW
THE BRATVA
TO DO THEIR JOB.
LET MY CRUSADE DIE.
NO? HA HA!
THAT KID WON'T LAST A MONTH.
THEY HAVE
TUBERCULOSIS?
MMM. THE DISEASE COMES
FROM PRISON.
SUPER RESISTANT STRAIN.
WELL, I...I MEAN, IS IT
IN ANY WAY TREATABLE?
MM, YEAH, WITH RIGHT
MEDICINE, YES,
BUT EVEN BRATVA CANNOT
BUY FOR THEM,
NOT IN QUANTITIES NEEDED.
ALL WE CAN DO IS
PAY FOR FUNERALS.
ANATOLY, IS THIS HOW
WE'RE PLANNING
ON SPENDING MY LAST
TWO DAYS IN RUSSIA?
I THOUGHT, WHAT BETTER WAY
TO CAP OFF YOUR TIME HERE
THAN A GOOD
OLD-FASHIONED HEIST?
IF DIGGLE'S THE NEW OLIVER
AND I'M, OBVIOUSLY, THE NEW
FELICITY...DON'T HATE...
WHICH ONE OF YOU GUYS
IS THE NEW DIGGLE?
BOTH: I AM.
SERIOUSLY?
YOU'VE BEEN HERE, LIKE,
WHAT, 10 MINUTES?
YOU DON'T EVEN HAVE
A CODE NAME.
FINE. YOU'RE THE NEW DIG.
THE FACT THAT SHE WAS
NOT PETTY AND...
I MEAN, THAT'S EXTREMELY
DIG-LIKE.
YOU...YOU SEE THAT, RIGHT?
SHE'S THE NEW...
YEAH. OK. YOU'RE
THE NEW DIG.
BUT AS THE ONLY
RENE RAMIREZ,
I GOT TO ASK, SHOULDN'T
WE BE COOL WITH LETTING
THE BRATVA
KILL ADRIAN CHASE?
NO, WE SHOULDN'T.
LOOK, GUYS, IF OLIVER
LETS THE BRATVA KILL CHASE,
HE'S JUST GOING RIGHT BACK
INTO HIS OLD HABITS,
AND HE'S WILLING TO MAKE
THAT SACRIFICE RIGHT NOW,
BUT I THINK ONCE OLIVER'S
THINKING CLEARLY,
HE'S GONNA REGRET THIS.
SO WE'RE JUST SUPPOSED
TO LET CHASE LIVE
TO KILL ANOTHER DAY?
NO. WE'RE GONNA BRING CHASE
TO JUSTICE THE RIGHT WAY.
THIS ISN'T
ABOUT SAVING CHASE.
IT'S ABOUT SAVING
OLIVER'S SOUL.
[COMPUTER BEEPS]
DINAH: CURTIS, THE HACK YOU
PUT ON THE D.A.'S OFFICE
JUST PULLED UP CHASE'S
SCHEDULE.
HE'S ABOUT TO LEAVE
CITY HALL.
TRIP TO THE SAFE HOUSE
SCPD'S KEEPING CHASE IN
IS THE PERFECT TIME
FOR THE RUSSIANS
TO DO THEIR THING.
JOHN: WE CAN'T LET THE
BRATVA GET A HOLD OF CHASE.
I CAN PULL UP HIS
ROUTE REMOTELY,
AND I SAW SOMETHING ON
FELICITY'S COMPUTER THAT
MIGHT HELP US GET CHASE.
JOHN: GOOD. DO THAT.
LET'S SUIT UP.
SUIT UP.
WAIT. WE DON'T HAVE SUITS.
OH, YOU
MEANT FIGURATIVELY SUIT UP.
SUIT UP, LIKE, "WE'RE STILL
IN THE LAIR. SUIT UP,"
LIKE, BUT WE'RE NOT
IN THE LAI...
BUT DO YOU SEE WHAT I'M SAYING?
QUITE AN ESCORT.
GREEN ARROW COULD BE
ANYWHERE.
WHO DO YOU THINK IS
UNDER THAT HOOD?
THE DEPARTMENT'S GOT
TO HAVE A THEORY.
OH, MY GOD!
MAKE SURE THAT KEVLAR
STAYS ON.
[CANARY CRY]
GO! RUN!
HEY!
WHY INTERFERE?
YOU WANT CHASE DEAD,
YES?
YES, BUT NOT LIKE THIS.
MR. HOLT.
HOW'S THAT HUSBAND OF YOURS?
[T-SPHERE WHIRRING]
[SIRENS]
CHASE!
I'M OVER HERE!
THE HITTERS ARE RETREATING.
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
I'M FINE. I'M FINE.
RENE AND DIGGLE?
DRIVING OFF ANATOLY'S
MEN. DID YOU GET IT?
-I GOT IT.
-GOOD MAN.
IT'S CLEAR
THE ATTACK OCCURRED
AFTER DETAILS OF
THE D.A.'S SCHEDULE
WERE COMPROMISED.
A LEAK?
MAN: UNTIL WE CAN CONFIRM
THE SOURCE, D.A. CHASE
WILL BE TRANSFERRED
INTO THE FEDERAL WITNESS
PROTECTION PROGRAM.
NO STAR CITY EMPLOYEE
WILL HAVE ACCESS
TO HIS FILE.
ADRIAN: I'M REALLY NOT SURE
ALL OF THIS IS NECESSARY.
OLIVER: ADRIAN, PLEASE.
YOUR SAFETY IS OF PARAMOUNT
IMPORTANCE TO THIS OFFICE.
DO IT.
YOU ACTUALLY TRIED
SOMETHING.
CONSIDER ME
IMPRESSED.
THIS ISN'T OVER.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
CHASE IS BEING TRANSFERRED
INTO FEDERAL PROTECTION,
WHICH MEANS THAT THE BRATVA
CAN'T GET TO HIM.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
HMM, FEEL BETTER?
NO.
WE'RE NOT DONE, OLIVER.
YOU AND ME, WE'RE NEVER
GONNA BE DONE.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND THAT?
LISTEN, MAN, YOU CAN
TELL ME
THAT YOU'RE
A SERIAL KILLER,
THAT YOU'RE CRAZY,
OR YOU'RE WHATEVER CHASE
HAS SHOVED INTO YOUR HEAD,
BUT I'M NOT BELIEVING ANY
OF THAT, EVEN IF YOU DO,
AND THAT'S BECAUSE I
KNOW THE KIND OF MAN
YOU ARE, OLIVER.
THE GOOD, THE BAD,
AND THE UGLY I KNOW,
AND YOU DON'T NEED TO
PUNISH YOURSELF
OR ISOLATE YOURSELF,
BUT WHAT YOU NEED TO DO
IS STOP PUSHING ME AWAY
BECAUSE I'M NOT GOING
ANYWHERE, OLIVER!
DO YOU GET THAT?
WHAT DO YOU WANT
ME TO DO, JOHN?
I'VE TOLD YOU WHAT I AM,
WHO I AM,
AND EVEN IF YOU DON'T
BELIEVE IT, I DO.
I DO.
SO I DON'T KNOW
WHERE THAT LEAVES US.
IT LEAVES US RIGHT
BACK AT LANGHAM, OLIVER.
DO YOU REMEMBER THAT?
I KILLED MY BROTHER,
OLIVER...
AND I WAS GONNA LET
MYSELF ROT IN PRISON
FOR WHAT I DID...
BUT YOU TOLD ME TO ATONE
FOR WHAT I DID AS SPARTAN.
AND IF THAT'S TRUE
FOR ME,
IT IT 100 TIMES TRUER
FOR THE GREEN ARROW.
YOU DON'T GET TO JUST
WALK AWAY FROM THIS, MAN.
THE HOOD IS WHO YOU ARE.
YOU DON'T THINK YOU
DESERVE IT? FINE.
WORK TO BECOME THE MAN
WHO DOES.
I...I DON'T KNOW HOW.
YOU JUST ASK FOR HELP.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO DO
THIS ALONE, OLIVER.
I HAVE AN IDEA.
WE HACK WITSEC.
OK, WE FIND OUT WHAT TOWN
CHASE IS GOING INTO,
AND THEN WE GET HIRED
AS WAITRESSES
AT THE INEVITABLY
FOLKSY DINER.
WE DRUG HIS COFFEE.
WE STEAL HIS SCRAMBLER.
YOU KNOW HOW I KNOW
I'M EXHAUSTED?
MM-HMM.
THAT PLAN ACTUALLY
SOUNDS PLAUSIBLE.
FREE PIE FOR LIFE. THAT'S
ALL I'M SAYING. FREE PIE.
-FELICITY.
-YEAH.
DO YOU KNOW THIS GUY?
CURTIS?
YOU TOLD HIM ABOUT
OUR OPERATION?
FELICITY: NO. I TURNED
OFF THE GPS ON MY PHONE.
HOW DID YOU...
YOU SON OF A BITCH.
THOSE DAMN...
TRACKING NANITES. YUP.
BLUEBERRIES WEREN'T
THE ONLY SURPRISE
IN THOSE PANCAKES.
I KNEW THEY WERE FUNKY.
UM, CAN WE TALK IN PRIVATE?
-UH, NO.
-FINE.
THEN YOU DON'T GET TO ASK
ME ANY QUESTIONS
ABOUT HOW I GOT THIS.
IS THAT...
CHASE'S OPTICS SCRAMBLER.
SURE IS.
HOW DID YOU KNOW WE
WERE LOOKING FOR IT?
I MIGHT HAVE TAKEN A PEEK
AT YOUR IRC WINDOW.
I GUESS YOU COULD SAY THAT
I HACKED THE HACKERS. WHOA.
[TYPING ON KEYBOARD]
CURTIS: WHAT?
THE PIXILATION ALGORITHM
IS ENCRYPTED.
I SHOULD'VE KNOWN IT
WOULD BE ENCRYPTED,
BUT IT'S ENCRYPTED.
WELL, HOW LONG WILL
IT TAKE YOU TO BREAK
THE ENCRYPTION?
IF MY MATH IS RIGHT,
(3.1610^18)(E^6)(75 TERAFLOPS)...
13 MONTHS.
[SCOFFS]
WELL, I KNOW SOMEONE
WHO CAN BREAK IT
FASTER.
KORD INDUSTRIES.
I MEAN, THEY SET
THE ENCRYPTION.
THEY CAN BREAK IT.
CURTIS: I DON'T THINK
THAT KORD IS GONNA HELP US
HACK THEIR STOLEN TECH.
THAT'S WHY YOU'LL
HAVE TO BREAK IN.
IT SHOULDN'T BE TOO HARD FOR
OVERWATCH AND MR. TERRIFIC,
WHO COULD PULL OFF
A HEIST AT KORD.
YOU TOLD THEM
ABOUT OUR OPERATION?
I DIDN'T.
-HOW DID YOU...
-OH, COME ON, FELICITY.
YOU REALLY THINK WE
DIDN'T KNOW?
IT TOOK ME 8 MINUTES,
3 FOR THIS GUY.
THESE HACKERS ARE MEAN.
WELL, DEAL WITH IT.
WE HAVE TO DEAL
WITH THIS.
THANKS FOR MEETING.
I'M ONLY HERE
FOR YOU TO EXPLAIN
WHY TEAM YOU DISBANDED
KEEPS INTERFERING
WITH BUSINESS.
BECAUSE THEY DON'T
GIVE UP.
THEY CONVINCED ME
NOT TO.
ANATOLY, I'M SORRY,
BUT YOU
NEED TO TELL
YOUR MEN TO STAND DOWN.
OUR DEAL'S OFF.
NO.
EXCUSE ME?
YOU WANT CHASE
TO KEEP BREATHING? FINE.
BUT I'M NOT LEAVING
STAR CITY,
NOT TILL I GET
WHAT I CAME FOR.
YOU KNOW AS WELL AS I DO
ONCE THERE IS DEAL,
IT IS FOREVER.
I UNDERSTAND HOW THE
BRATVA WORKS. I...
I AM ASKING YOU THIS
AS A FRIEND.
YES. AND I AM TELLING YOU
AS FRIEND,
IF YOU INTERFERE
WITH MY OPERATION,
NO FAVOR EXISTS THAT CAN
REPAIR BREAK
BETWEEN YOU AND I.
YOU EITHER BRATVA BROTHER
OR YOU BRATVA ENEMY.
WE ARE IN POSITION.
OLIVER: I'LL MEET YOU
BY THE SIDE ENTRANCE.
[FIRES PISTOL]
[NECK SNAPS]
THE BRATVA AREN'T BACKING DOWN,
WHICH MEANS I HAVE
TO STOP THEM.
JOHN HAS CONVINCED ME NOT
TO DO IT ALONE.
I WANTED TO SHUT
ALL OF THIS DOWN
BECAUSE I WAS AFRAID.
I WAS AFRAID THAT ASKING
YOU TO KILL CHASE
WOULD CORRUPT YOU
MORE THAN...
MORE THAN
I ALREADY HAVE.
TO ME, THE...THE...
THE BRATVA WAS
THE BEST OPTION,
BUT JOHN INSISTS THAT
AS A TEAM,
WE CAN FIND ANOTHER WAY
TO BRING CHASE TO JUSTICE.
YOU'VE PUT YOUR FAITH IN ME,
AND I'M PUTTING MY FAITH
IN YOU NOW.
BECAUSE ONCE...ONCE
WE HANDLE THE BRATVA, I...
I NEED YOUR HELP TO PROVE
THAT JOHN IS RIGHT
AND CHASE IS WRONG.
IT SHOULD BE EASY
CONSIDERING PROMETHEUS
IS ALL THE WAY WRONG,
HOSS.
DINAH: I THINK WHAT RENE
IS TRYING TO SAY IS
THAT IT'S NOT ALL
ON YOUR SHOULDERS.
WE'RE HERE FOR YOU, OLIVER.
OK.
SUIT UP.
ALARMS HAVEN'T BEEN
TRIGGERED ALL NIGHT.
NO BREAK-INS.
YEAH, EXCEPT US.
ANATOLY NEEDS REVLEXTRA
TO MANUFACTURE HIS DRUG.
THE BRATVA
WILL DEFINITELY BE HERE.
OLIVER:
SPARTAN'S RIGHT.
ANATOLY WON'T
BACK OFF NOW.
THEY COULD BE ANYWHERE.
THIS PLACE IS HUGE.
FELICITY AND CURTIS PICKED
A HELL OF A NIGHT
TO TAKE OFF.
OK. I'M IN.
CCTV IS COMPROMISED.
GOT ANYTHING?
WEST WING IS CLEAR.
SO IS THE EAST.
I WAS HOPING I WOULDN'T
HAVE TO PUNCH ANYBODY.
ALL RIGHT. I JUST TOOK OUT
A SENTRY. THEY CAN'T BE FAR.
JOHN: THEY'RE NOT.
BETTER GET
OVER HERE FAST.
NOPE.
[SYRINGE HISSES]
-THAT WORKED.
-WHOA!
YOU CAN'T WIN.
IS THAT YOU BEHIND MASK?
WHAT HAPPENED TO HOOD?
IT'S OVER, ANATOLY.
LEAVE THE MEDICINE
AND GO.
I HAD FEELING
YOU WOULD SAY THIS,
SO I PREPARED
INSURANCE PLAN.
[WOMAN WHIMPERS]
YOU HAVE CHOSEN WHERE YOU
STAND WITH BRATVA.
NOW YOU MUST MAKE
ONE MORE CHOICE.
SAVE PILLS OR SAVE HOSTAGES.
SPARTAN, WILD DOG,
GET THE HOSTAGES.
I'LL HANDLE THE BRATVA.
KILL THEM.
IN RUSSIA, YOU
WOULD HAVE KILLED HIM.
AND YOU WOULD HAVE
STOPPED HIM.
LOOKS LIKE WE'RE NOT
IN RUSSIA ANYMORE.
[WOMAN WHIMPERING]
YOU ALL RIGHT?
CURTIS DIDN'T LEAVE US
COMPLETELY HANGING.
HAND ME
YOUR TABLET.
YOU BROUGHT
THE SCRAMBLER HERE?
I WASN'T GONNA WAIT TO
SEE IF WE
COULD BREAK
THE ENCRYPTION.
GO AHEAD, OLIVER.
YOU WANT TO KILL OLD LIFE?
START BY KILLING ME.
[GUNSHOT, ALARM SOUNDS]
VERY STUPID!
NOW YOU HAVE TO RUN.
SO DO YOU.
-DID YOU GET IT?
-OH, YEAH.
OLIVER:
THAT IS WHAT WE NEEDED...
SOMETHING THAT HE COULDN'T
PLAN FOR...
YOU.
DINAH: PLEASE LET ME BE THE ONE
TO WALK THIS INTO SCPD.
KNOCK YOURSELF OUT.
YEAH, AND THEN I'M GONNA
THROW IT UP ON YOUTUBE.
THERE WON'T BE ANYWHERE
THAT SON OF A BITCH CAN RUN.
DOES THIS MEAN THAT
WE'RE OFFICIALLY
BACK IN BUSINESS?
ASIDE FROM A FEW MINOR
CHANGES, YEAH.
THE NEW LINEUP
COULD USE A LITTLE
MORE GREEN, HOSS.
I'M NOT QUITE THERE YET.
I'M THINKING THAT
WITH THIS TEAM BEHIND ME,
IT'LL BE SOONER RATHER
THAN LATER.
OLIVER: HOW DOES IT FEEL
TO BE ROBIN HOOD?
YOU TELL ME.
YOU'RE THE ONE
WITH BOW AND ARROW.
I KNOW I SAID
THAT RUSSIA'S NOT
GOOD FOR YOU, OLIVER.
BUT YOU THOUGHT THAT
THIS HEIST
AND HELPING THESE PEOPLE
WOULD CONVINCE ME
TO CHANGE MY MIND
ABOUT LEAVING.
DA.
LIKE I SAID, I NEED
YOUR HELP.
RUSSIA IS YOUR HOME,
ANATOLY.
LET ME GO SAVE MINE.
YOU CAN DO THIS WITHOUT ME.
I AM NOT WORRIED
ABOUT WHAT BRATVA WILL
BECOME WITHOUT YOU.
I WORRY ABOUT
WHAT I BECOME.
BUT MORE IMPORTANT
QUESTION...
HOW DRUNK CAN WE GET
BEFORE DROPPING YOU OFF
AT LIAN YU?
[CHUCKLES]
YOU HAVE TWO MINUTES, AND
THEN I'M CALLING THE SCPD.
OLIVER QUEEN AFRAID TO BE
ALONE WITH BRATVA GANGSTER?
HOW FAR YOU HAVE FALLEN.
ANATOLY, YOU DIDN'T BRING
ME HERE TO INSULT ME.
NO. I GIVE YOU
FRIENDLY TIP.
I GO BACK TO RUSSIA TONIGHT
BUT LEAVE STAR CITY
A LITTLE PRESENT...
MY BEST MEN.
YOUR BEST MEN WERE
ARRESTED.
ALREADY OUT ON BAIL.
I HEAR THEY CANNOT WAIT
TO GET REVENGE
ON VIGILANTES
THAT PUT THEM AWAY.
THIS IS BETWEEN YOU
AND ME, NO ONE ELSE.
"NO ONE ELSE"?
YOU BETRAYED EVERY MAN
IN BRATVA.
YOU BETRAYED RUSSIAN
COMMUNITY.
YOU EVEN WORKED
AGAINST OLD TEAM.
WHEN I SEE THIS, I THINK
I STILL TRUST HIM ANYWAY.
WHAT A FOOL I WAS.
NO. I'M THE FOOL.
BECAUSE I THOUGHT THAT
OUR FRIENDSHIP...
EVERYTHING THAT WE HAVE
BEEN THROUGH TOGETHER...
ACTUALLY MEANT
SOMETHING TO YOU.
THE PERSON THAT I KNEW
WOULD NEVER BETRAY
A FRIEND,
WOULD NEVER THREATEN
INNOCENT PEOPLE
OVER WHAT?
A PAYDAY.
WHEN I LEFT RUSSIA,
I WAS CONVINCED
THAT YOU COULD LEAD
THE BRATVA,
THAT YOU COULD SET THEM
ON A BETTER PATH,
AND NOW LOOK AT YOU.
YOU'RE NO BETTER
THAN GREGOR.
I TOLD YOU, I WAS WORRIED
ABOUT WHAT I WOULD BECOME
WITHOUT YOUR HELP.
I DID WHAT I HAD TO DO
TO KEEP BRATVA TOGETHER
AND TO STAY ALIVE.
I BECAME WHAT I HAD
TO BECOME.
YOU ASKED WHY I CHANGED.
THAT IS IT.
THIS VIDEO HAS BEEN
AUTHENTICATED
BY 3 DIFFERENT EXPERTS.
AND IT HASN'T BEEN
DOCTORED OR ALTERED
IN ANY WAY.
THAT IS RAW FOOTAGE.
CHASE IS IN
THE PROTECTIVE CUSTODY
OF THE U.S. MARSHALS.
YEAH. WELL, SOMEBODY
BETTER GIVE THEM A CALL
AND PLACE THAT SON OF
A BITCH UNDER ARREST.
[CELL PHONE VIBRATING]
UNH!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
NO. UNH!
UNH! UNH!
[SIRENS]
THE RASCALS:
♪ IT'S A BEAUTIFUL MORNING ♪
♪ AH ♪
♪ I THINK I'LL GO OUTSIDE
FOR A WHILE ♪
♪ AND JUST SMILE ♪
♪ JUST TAKE IN SOME CLEAN,
FRESH AIR, BOY ♪
♪ AIN'T NO SENSE IN STAYIN'
INSIDE... ♪
MAN: GREG, MOVE YOUR HEAD.