Need a hand, John?
DIGGLE: I'm good.
Varsity track, all-state, 100 meters.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Dig?
Felicity, you know where
that son of a bitch went?
He vanished.
We call them Ghosts for a reason.
But I got air support
coming in on Number Two.
ARROW: I got him.
Oliver?
-Oliver?
-DIGGLE: He's all right, Felicity.
We need eyes back on our target.
I'll give you one better than that.
(ENGINE STARTING)
(WHIRRING)
Twenty feet ahead,
I got one gift wrapped for you.
Feels like old times, the three of us.
The OGs, the original gangstas.
-(DIGGLE GRUNTING)
-(GROANING)
You're not checking out
without answering a few questions first.
Where can I find H.I.V.E.?
Who's behind the Ghosts?
-Answer me!
-(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
(GROANING)
Dig?
Now, he's gone.
Damn it!
We needed
more boots on the ground, Oliver.
Thea and Laurel
picked a fine day for a spa treatment.
I don't think Thea would be much help
in the state of mind she's in.
Where the hell did they go anyway?
(GRUNTING)
I really enjoy sparring with you, Nyssa.
-I'm not sparring.
-I know.
That's what makes it so much fun.
You know I would show you no mercy
if given the opportunity.
That's why I take great care
not to give you the opportunity.
Next time, I'll take your head off.
(CHUCKLING)
My liege, two foreigners are here.
One of them claims to be
the daughter of Ra's al Ghul.
No. I am his daughter.
What a pleasant surprise.
Sister-in-law.
What brings you to Nanda Parbat?
They have a coffin with them, my liege.
A coffin?
I want you
to bring my sister back to life.
No.
You took her life away from her.
It is your obligation to bring her back.
I have no obligations in this house.
You don't get to waltz in here and
demand a cup of tea, let alone this.
Thea wasn't dead.
-Sara is.
-Thanks to you.
What you are asking for
hasn't been done in ages past.
Even then, only in legend.
Which is why I did not ask my father to
use the Pit to save Sara after she fell.
Even if Sara went into the Pit,
even if it worked,
who, what came out of the Pit
would not be Sara.
Laurel, I am sorry, truly sorry.
But, of course, my answer is no.
Okay, I know that was kind of a bust,
but wasn't it fun having the original
"Team Arrow" back together?
-You shouldn't have.
-Got that off one of the Ghosts.
It's where they hide
their cyanide capsules.
Looks like an upper left bicuspid.
There was a very brief time
where I envisioned a future for myself
as a dental hygienist.
The best lead we've gotten
in the last three months.
It'll take the DNA sequencer
a little bit of time,
so I was thinking margaritas
while we wait.
You remember that place we went
after we took down the Dodger?
Oh. What do you say?
It's been a while
since it was just the three of us.
I got a family to get back to.
I guess he just needs more time.
Time hasn't been doing anything.
Apologies haven't.
What're you saying?
I'm saying that
I'm done waiting for him to come around.
(MAN COUGHING)
Work faster!
Like a fish to water.
What did you say?
People gossip.
They say that you're a rich kid
who got shipwrecked here.
Bossing people around, giving orders.
It must feel just like home to you.
We got a runner!
Hey, watch your field.
(GRUNTS)
Hey! Come on, man.
Let's do this the easy way.
Yeah! That's the way.
Well, what are you gonna do?
Talk him into surrendering?
That's how you do it.
(GRUNTING)
Who are you?
Definitely not someone
who deserves to be shot.
Your wife and kid are out, by the way.
Who are you?
Relax.
I'm a friendly.
You're A.R.G.U.S.?
He can read. Lyla sent me.
My wife left the agency seven months ago.
She couldn't have sent you anywhere.
She asked back
when she was still with the agency.
Took me a while because, well, favors
aren't exactly
at the top of my to-do list.
Here, ID on whoever hired Floyd Lawton
to do a hit back in '09.
"Mina Fayad"?
Where can I find her?
Well, that's the best part.
TSA flagged her coming in last night.
Flew in from Markovia.
I'll contact you with her location.
Ah. Ms. Fayad. You brought a guest.
As instructed.
Not by me.
The vigilante problem in this city
is greater than anticipated.
Your partners in H.I.V.E.
asked me to take steps.
You don't exactly look like
a problem solver. What do you do?
I play cards, mostly.
Perhaps a demonstration.
Funny you should mention.
I happen to have just the problem.
My operatives are under orders
to choose death before capture.
This gentleman chose wrongly.
They got to me before I could take
the countermeasure.
He's also prone to excuses,
which I find tiresome.
(LAUGHING)
That was good.
Ooh.
JEREMY: That one was free.
Taking out the Green Arrow
and his friends,
that'll cost.
Deal.
I'm not giving up.
I'm never giving up.
Because you're thinking only of yourself.
I expected your support.
I was counting on it.
Then you never really knew me at all.
The Pit gave my father a long life.
Longer than what was natural
and much longer than he deserved.
But he paid a dark price for it.
A price Thea is no doubt paying now.
I wouldn't wish it on my most
bitter enemy, let alone my beloved.
I don't know if the Pit
can bring her back.
And Malcolm's right.
I don't know
what Sara will be like if it does.
But what I do know is that I have to try.
To what end?
To have your sister
returned to you a monster?
Her spirit, the part that we both love,
that's the part that I have to believe
will come back.
You're not doing this out of love,
you're doing this out of grief.
I miss Sara, too.
But she is gone, Laurel.
Forever.
I have accepted it.
I think it's time you did, too.
Still wishing you were a dental hygienist?
More like a molecular biologist.
You see this?
No.
In my defense, I flunked biology.
Well, I got an A-plus,
and I still have no idea
what the hell is going on here.
This DNA has half of the genetic
markers that it should have, half.
How's that possible?
It's not. This guy should be nothing more
than a pile of goo.
(ALARM BEEPING)
What now?
Robbery at a parts store, Litchfield Ave.
-Call Dig. Tell him I'll meet him there.
-Ah!
Hold ups are a little below
your pay grade.
You sure you don't want
the S.C.P.D. to handle this one?
How effective have the police been
in solving the city's problems recently?
That's a good point.
John's still not answering his phone.
I'll be fine.
Still, I don't like you going out there
without backup.
I'm not. I have you.
That restraint you showed back there,
-bury it.
-Here.
Violence is the only thing
these losers understand.
The guys out here who can't handle that,
they either wash out
or end up doing the product,
both of which are fast-tracks
to a bullet in the head.
The product.
Reiter hasn't told me a lot about it.
He calls it Slam,
genetically modified hybrid,
one part heroin poppy, one part coca leaf.
Get you higher than the Empire State.
MAN: Conklin.
We got a problem.
Some Slam's missing, a whole cake.
The runner was just a distraction.
Any idea who did it?
All right then, round them up!
What are you gonna do?
I told you, only one thing
these losers respond to.
Get on the ground.
Thanks for coming, by the way.
Ms. Fayad wasn't sure it would work,
but I knew you couldn't turn down
a good old fashioned robbery.
(GRUNTING)
Are you ready to call this yet?
Now you can call it.
Game's not over yet.
Are you all right?
Aside from the fact
that you won't help my friends?
I wouldn't be helping Sara,
as you know more than anyone.
What gave me away?
When I was cautioning Laurel
about the effects of the Pit,
I saw the look on your face.
You're feeling it, aren't you?
The blood lust.
What's happening to me?
The Pit contains traces of the souls
of all the men and women
who have bathed in its waters.
And what those waters restore
they can also take. Life for life.
What are you saying?
That you need to feed this impulse.
Give in to it.
Once you do, it will subside for a time.
Okay.
I'll just go on a killing spree.
Thank you for the fatherly advice.
Can you just, for a second,
pretend to be a normal father?
Can you do that, Dad?
Do you have anything remotely normal
to offer me?
All right.
There is something,
high in the mountains, a man.
Some call him a sage.
He has a way
with the ancient arts of healing.
He may be able to help you with this,
though I am not sure.
Does that qualify as being normal?
Normal enough.
Get some rest.
We'll start at first light.
-This hurt?
-Yeah, it stings.
Good. That's what you get for trying
to take on a meta all by yourself.
-A meta?
-Yeah!
Turns out, Central City is missing one.
A Jeremy Tell. Cisco says
we should call him "Double Down."
Which doesn't exactly make sense,
since he was getting a tattoo
when the dark matter wave hit.
You missed quite a show, tonight.
Sorry I couldn't help out.
It's a long story.
Oh, my God. It is not a long story.
It is the shortest story in history.
Two guys go take on criminals
without asking for backup
and nearly get killed in the process.
You know,
I haven't said anything up till now,
because I was hoping that the two of you
would remove your heads
from your own asses
without assistance.
Turns out, I was wrong.
Hey, Felicity...
No, no, no. This is the part where I talk
and you two listen.
The both of you nearly got killed
out there tonight
because you didn't have
each other's backs.
That was a one-time deal, Felicity.
It won't happen again.
I absolutely agree.
Because the two of you
are going to sit down here
until you have resolved your issues.
Do we have an understanding?
-Hey...
-Do we have an understanding?
Yeah.
I'm gonna take this
to a guy at Palmer Tech
to find out how some lunatic meta
turns tattoos into lethal weapons.
If you two haven't figured out
your issues by the time I get back,
I'm gonna find a bunch of Mirakuru
soldiers to knock some sense into you.
It's been months, man.
And I don't know how many apologies...
I mean, John, you're a forgiving person.
Oliver, this isn't about forgiveness, man.
I don't know how
to move forward with this, us.
Doing what we do.
-We've worked fine since I got back.
-We've got lucky.
Oliver, there was a time
I would've taken a bullet for you.
And I don't know if I would do that now.
Which means that even when we're
out there, we are not out there together.
You crossed a line, man.
And the fact that you could do that again
sits in the back of my head somewhere.
I get it! I get it.
I understand that I crossed a line.
I understand that I lost your trust.
What I do not understand is why you
won't give me a chance to earn it back.
You think this meta tonight
is connected to Darhk?
I don't know. Uh...
He mentioned a new player, a woman.
Fayad.
We need to go.
Where?
Some place where I'm gonna try
to trust you again.
I like to think of all of us as a team.
Teammates need to trust each other.
Right now,
I'm having a little difficulty doing that.
I want y'all to tell me
who stole the product,
or else this man right here
is gonna eat a bullet.
Nobody?
Let's try this again.
Hey, wait. Wait, wait, wait.
You said that violence is the only thing
these people respond to.
Doesn't seem to be working.
Well, what do you have in mind,
harsh language?
I've been on this island three years.
I've learned some things.
About what?
Pain.
(CLEARING THROAT)
-Uh-oh.
-"Uh-oh"?
Those aren't the words you wanna say
when your CEO walks into a room.
Well, technically, "uh" and "oh"
aren't words, they're interjections...
Please tell me these are the prototypes
for our new world-changing technology.
Since I'm inventing them,
wouldn't that make them my...
What is this?
CURTIS: Contact lenses
with built-in HD displays.
FELICITY: Ooh, That's impressive and fast.
-How much would they sell for?
-100,000.
-$100,000?
-Per lens.
(PHONE VIBRATES)
Hmm.
Everything okay?
Yeah, my phone just keeps acting up.
Need to restart it.
-Ooh!
-(WHIRRING)
Ah!
This is an autonomous
communications device.
Which is great, except for the fact
that it spontaneously explodes.
Okay, maybe you need something
to get your mind off all this.
Like a little side project,
clear your head.
Like gambling?
I need a full workup.
It's possible it's made out of
some sort of bio-organic material.
I need to know everything
that you can find out about it.
Strange. These edges.
It doesn't look mass manufactured.
Where'd you find it?
Casino.
-You gamble?
-Oh, yeah! All the time. Poker's my jam.
It ruined an outside flush for me.
I think my opponent was cheating.
So, you want me to check it
for evidence of marking or something?
Yeah, anything strange,
out of the ordinary.
Like you playing poker?
I will check back in on you later.
-Oh, and, uh, Ms. Smoak?
-Mmm?
There's no such thing
as an "outside flush" in poker.
That's probably why I lost.
You remember Russia?
Two years ago,
when we got Lyla out of that prison?
Of course.
That night, Lawton told me that my brother
was not collateral damage
in a hit gone bad.
That he was the target.
And that Lawton was hired
by an organization called HIVE.
The other week you reacted
when I said that Ra's called Darhk's men
a "hive" of operatives.
Mmm-hmm.
Could be a coincidence.
I don't think so.
Last page.
That woman hired Lawton
to kill my brother.
And I'm betting she hired that meta
that tried to take you out.
-Based on what?
-Her name is Mina Fayad.
Two years and you didn't tell me.
We have more in common than you think.
Oliver, that's my first legitimate lead.
I have to find her.
Ms. Fayad hired you for one job, one.
Against my objections
and only because my associates
are anxious to progress to Phase Three.
We shouldn't talk about Genesis...
Don't lecture me about secrecy.
Particularly on the same night
that you were just compromised.
I...
In the same night that I lost good men
in the name of protecting you.
-Damien.
-Mr. Darhk!
I think I require another demonstration.
(SCOFFING) You want me to kill her now?
Show me.
Try to kill me.
I kill you, I still get paid?
Do it.
(GASPS SOFTLY)
What are you?
Ms. Fayad,
many members of HIVE,
they consider me to be a charlatan.
That this, this is a parlor trick,
sleight of hand.
(GRUNTS)
This demonstration was for you, Mr. Tell.
Just in case you have any doubt
as to how I process disappointment.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(GASPING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
How do you feel?
How do...
How do I feel?
Oh, my God.
There is no sage.
There is no cure.
There never was.
I'm sorry.
You will be compelled to kill until
you've slain the one who hurt you.
But I can't. Okay, Ra's is already dead.
Then the only way to cope
is to indulge the blood lust on others.
So you...
You set your men up to be slaughtered?
You will not feel the hunger
to kill again for weeks.
No need to thank me.
There is nothing I wouldn't do
to help my daughter.
I hope we learned a lesson of the benefits
of trusting our friends with our problems.
You mean, like your boyfriend?
You're supposed to be
more evolved than him.
-Hmm?
-Sorry, but he is.
-Can we find her?
-FELICITY: No.
She's not coming up on any
of our traffic or security cams.
But I think I have the next best thing,
her cell phone. Or at least
the one that followed her through airport
security on the way to Star City.
Where's her phone now?
Redmond and 8th.
-(CRACKING)
-(SCREAMING IN PAIN)
So, which fancy private school
you pick this up in?
Learned it here.
Three years on this island, and I have
been hurt every way you can imagine.
I know what kills,
I know what cripples,
and what just hurts.
-(SCREAMING)
-Stop! Stop.
He didn't take the drugs.
I did.
You're working us too hard,
and some of the other prisoners are hurt.
I wanted to give them
something for the pain.
And where's the Slam now?
It's all used up.
And I'm not going to tell you by who,
so if you're going to kill me,
just get on with it.
Suit yourself.
Wait, wait, wait.
You've already executed
one prisoner today.
How's Reiter gonna feel about
you exterminating his work force?
Oh, I think he'll make an exception
for a thief.
Or I just make her disappear.
Take her someplace.
They'll never find the body.
All right, take her.
Keep them company.
-Wake up. Wake up, we need to go.
-What?
It was a mistake to come here.
-Thea.
-Stay the hell away from me.
Thea, what's wrong?
He's not gonna help Sara,
and he's not gonna help me.
-Thea!
-Don't talk to me.
-I was only trying to help you...
-Help me?
Yeah, that's funny
on more than a few levels.
My favorite is you are the reason
why I am like this in the first place.
I know.
I will not kill people.
I won't.
Just stay out of my life
and the hell away from me.
MALCOLM: We are bound together, forever.
You and me, father and daughter.
Let me prove it to you.
How?
I am responsible for Sara's death.
Yet, I have the means to make it right,
or at least try to.
Do you think, after knowing
what that Pit has done to me,
that I would let that happen to Sara?
I think if you are truly sincere
in fighting your blood lust,
you would offer the same to Sara.
What are you saying?
That I am willing to heal
my daughter's conscience
by restoring your sister's life.
That we should prepare Sara's body
for the ceremony.
I'm still getting a ping
off Ms. Fayad's cell phone.
Ten feet ahead.
John.
DIGGLE: It was my first chance
for answers.
My last chance.
-I'm sorry.
-Don't be, Oliver.
This isn't your fault. It's mine.
I should've trusted you.
Told you about this forever ago.
If I had, she wouldn't have gotten
away from me earlier.
Would be alive enough now
for some answers.
We're gonna get answers.
Oliver, I haven't been able to get answers
for more than two years now.
For more than two years,
you've been doing this alone.
You want me to take a look
at your phone for you, Ms. Smoak?
I think we've reached the point
in our working relationship
where you can call me Felicity.
Have you ever considered
how ironic your name is?
"Felicity" refers to the ability to find
appropriate expression for one's thoughts,
which is not exactly something
you're particularly good at.
Yeah. You're right.
Let's stick with Ms. Smoak.
Any luck on our playing card?
Yeah, it's actually right there, Felic...
Uh, Ms. Smoak.
-Mmm-hmm.
-Except it's not a playing card at all.
Now, in my experience,
playing cards don't contain
motor proteins and proprioceptors
and a neural net.
The responsible thing to do
would be to get this back
to its rightful owner.
Is there any way to track him down?
Well, if you tell me the truth
about where you got it from,
that could speed along the process.
I did tell you the truth.
I did. Now, tracking the owner?
You see this ink here,
for lack of a better word?
It's magnetite, which is
the key component to tattoo ink.
-You don't say.
-I do.
I also say that magnetite happens to
guide the internal compass of birds,
specifically homing pigeons.
So is it possible to use the magnetite
in the card to get a location on our, um,
poker player?
Theoretically. Though, if your
hypothetical poker opponent
has a deck full of these cards,
he'll probably be able to find you faster.
Curtis, we have to...
JEREMY: I'm gonna make you two a deal.
The first one to tell me
where you can find the Green Arrow
gets to live.
-Green Arrow?
-I have a better idea.
Run!
(CLANGING)
Ms. Smoak, I really need to know
what's going on here.
Does the board of directors know
there's a secret elevator in the building?
(GRUNTING)
(GASPING)
-Since when are you such a bad ass?
-Since always.
-Okay, I have multiple questions.
-Okay.
Obviously, there's
a very long explanation to this.
The short version is that
I work with the Green Arrow.
This man is trying to kill me,
well, us, sorry.
And I'm taking us down to the
only place that we're gonna be safe.
-The lobby?
-Not exactly.
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
You have a hidden floor.
We should be safe here, but just in case.
I think I know
where I can find the Green Arrow.
Which means that offer
about not killing you is off the table.
Stay here, do not move.
-You know how to use that thing?
-No.
Curtis? Curtis?
-OLIVER: Felicity?
-I'm here. I'm here. I'm okay.
What happened?
Your meta came back
to retrieve his ace of spades.
And you fended him off?
Don't sound so surprised.
Okay, I had a little bit of help
from a co-worker, but to be honest,
-he was more freaked out than I was.
-Is he all right?
Yes, he's fine.
I sent him to Starling General.
And he only knows about my secret,
not yours.
If he can trace the cards back here,
can we use the cards to trace back to him?
That is exactly what Curtis,
my freaked-out co-worker,
was doing when...
I got something.
He's headed for the Star City expressway.
Probably hightailing his way
back to Central City.
Too bad he's not gonna make it.
(INDISTINCT CHANTING)
I will see you all dead
before I let you do this.
Laurel, please. Don't.
Are you sure you wanna do this?
Just keep going.
Wait, what's wrong?
I told you.
The Pit has never been used for...
No, wait.
Look.
Sara?
(PANTING)
Hold her!
Sara! Sara!
Sara, it's okay.
You're gonna be okay.
It's okay. It's okay.
(GROANS)
You guys are a special kind of stupid.
I was gonna blow town, call it a draw.
Not until you tell us about your employer.
Where's HIVE?
Who's behind the Ghosts? Tell me!
You know what your problem is?
You don't scare me
half as much as he does.
Look out!
(GRUNTING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(GROANING)
-You okay?
-Yeah. Kevlar held.
(GRUNTING)
You took a bullet for me.
They were meta-human tattoo playing cards.
Still counts, Oliver. Still counts.
To OTA.
Original Team Arrow.
Sorry. I know you hate it
when I call us that.
It's growing on me.
Cisco has our meta in lockup
at Iron Heights.
Yeah. We still can't get any intel.
He's too afraid of Damien Darhk.
So am I.
What are the odds that Double Down
told Darhk about Lair 2.0?
Enough that we should start
thinking about Lair 3.0.
I've been working on something.
-Really?
-Yeah.
Thought you would've learned your lesson
about keeping secrets from friends.
It's not a secret.
It's a surprise.
You enjoyed that, didn't you?
Torturing that man.
You don't even know what his name is.
-Walk faster.
-Elias.
That was his name, Elias.
-Faster.
-I'm in no rush to get to my death.
I'm trying to put some distance
between us.
-Between us and Richards?
-No. Between us and...
Between us and the landmine.
Listen to me. I am not going to kill you.
But you need to trust me,
or we're both dead. Do you understand?
-Yes.
-Okay.
Hey.
You okay?
Well, the only thing wounded
is my workspace.
Oh, and if Mr. Dennis asks,
please just tell him
that all this happened
because an experiment I was running
had an unforeseen outcome.
Thank you for not letting him know
that there is a secret lair
in the basement.
I'm a full service employee.
You seem pretty calm for a guy
who nearly got killed by a meta-human.
Ms. Smoak, I came to Palmer Tech
so I can help make this city
a better place.
Can you even imagine how excited I am
to know that my boss
is doing exactly that?
Well, you really helped out, Curtis.
The Green Arrow...
We couldn't have done it without you.
(CELLPHONE VIBRATING)
Ms. Smoak, is everything okay?
I don't know.
It's okay.
Everything's gonna be okay.
Dad's not gonna believe it.
He's gonna be so happy when he sees you.
(GRUNTING)
-Laurel?
-It's fine.
The same thing happened to you
when you first came out of the Pit.
She's just taking longer.
-It's probably because she was...
-Laurel, we are in uncharted waters here.
I suggest you prepare yourself
for the worst.
My liege, something has happened.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
What have you done?
My father was not a trusting man.
He devised means to destroy the Pit
should its powers
fall into the wrong hands.
Like yours.
Nyssa, why would you
do something like this?
How can you even look at your sister
and ask me that?
One day, I will have my moment,
and I will kill you.
And now when I do,
there will be no coming back.
Take her!
I warned you, Laurel. I begged you.
What happened to Sara last year
was on Malcolm's hands.
But what's happening to her now
is on yours.