Previously on "Arrow"...
This place looks exactly
like it did when I was 13.
We had planned to come
back here with both of you.
Yeah. That didn't
really work out.
Because I died.
Have you come to doubt
your commitment.
To this mission?
It might help if I
actually knew why.
The recovery of your universe.
Will require a single task.
You must betray Oliver queen.
If saving it means going back.
To the person that I used to be,
the what the hell is the point?
I'm sorry.
Passes it quickly over to the right.
Tark drives the Lane.
Kicks it to aldrich
in the corner for 3.
Bingo! Count it and the foul!
That's an 8-0 run by the comets,
who have stormed
all the way back.
To tie it up here
in the fourth quarter.
No way. It tastes the same.
I'm telling you this big
belly burger's just better.
I think he's right.
This is pre-gwespin
foods merger.
Dad, what are you
still doing here?
How did we get here?
What do you mean?
Uh, I was on a roof
with John and Laurel,
and we were tranqed.
Yeah. By Lyla.
Dad said it was all just
a big misunderstanding.
Ahem. What did we do with
burov's plan for the weapon?
You said we didn't
need it anymore.
Why? The monitor's
still out there.
He's still a threat.
Dad, are you ok?
You... you look like you
don't remember any of this.
I...
I need to talk to John.
That should be easy.
He's waiting for you at
that fancy fundraiser.
What fundraiser?
The one you're very late for.
I mean, you do remember
you're Oliver queen, right?
Hey, queen,
what's the difference.
Between a cop
and the green arrow?
A cop doesn't need to play
dress-up to do his job.
Ha. Yeah, sure. Whoa!
- I'm so sorry, Mr. Queen.
- It's fine, it's fine.
There you are, man.
The party started
an hour ago, Oliver.
Do you remember getting
tranqed last night?
Yeah.
Uh, Lyla feels awful about that.
By the way,
that wasn't last night.
- That was two days ago.
- What? No.
No, no. That...
John, that is the last thing.
That I remember
before waking up.
In my apartment earlier tonight.
You ok, man?
No. This is... this...
Is this the...
This is the monitor.
- Oliver.
- Your wife is working.
With the monitor, John. What...
I thought we
already settled this.
I have been working with the
monitor but as a double agent,
which I told you on the roof.
I don't... I don't remember that.
I'm not remembering anything.
Oliver, look.
Just maybe you should go home, man,
get a little sleep, ok?
Oliver, there you are.
Mayor's looking for you. Come on.
What?
- What happened there?
- Oh.
Can't give a speech
with a stained shirt.
Give a s... what speech?
I'm giving a speech?
Very funny.
Your joint remarks with the mayor.
Rene, um, serious question.
When did Palmer tech
get rebuilt?
You really need to drop
this amnesia routine quick.
This fundraiser is
our only chance to take.
The scpd vigilante
pilot program global.
The mayor needs you
to be on point.
- He's waiting for you.
- He who?
Isn't... isn't pollard the mayor?
In her dreams maybe.
What's the matter, Oliver?
You look like you seen a ghost.
Resync from kool3ds
- RDSop -
So listen. I was
thinking about making.
A few changes to the speech,
so I figured I should
run it by you first.
This is not possible. This is...
What? Don't tell me
you're scared.
Of a little last-minute
memorization, Oliver.
It's been a while
since I've seen you.
Couple of days maybe.
You're looking at me
like it's been years.
No. You're right. A couple days.
Right. So listen.
I was thinking.
About adding a line
about, you know,
me telling you it was
a bad idea to unmask,
but, you know, maybe
a joke about how.
You'd rather take it
to supermax.
Than take my advice.
Heh. You know?
What do you think?
You know that I went
to slabside?
Uh... yeah. What's that,
your way of saying I should
have come visit more often?
Quentin, right before
I turned myself in...
Diaz shot you, right?
Oh. Yeah.
That son of a bitch
almost killed me.
Almost died in the O.R.
you don't remember?
I remember it differently.
Well, the doctors
called it a miracle.
I was without oxygen
for so long,
I should have been 6 feet under.
Felt like I escaped
my fate or something.
Hey. There's
something you need to see.
So... there's
a hostage situation.
At the scpd.
The leader's demanding
to meet with the mayor.
No. No. You can't go down there.
We'll call in
a special-ops team.
I'm the mayor. Nobody
does my dirty work for me.
Give my apologies to the guests.
I'm... I'm gonna come with you.
Ok, but you might want
to bring a change of clothes.
Because something tells me
we're gonna need the green guy.
Get the feds on the line.
Tell them I need backup.
Here now, right now.
What's the situation, captain?
Armed mercs stormed my precinct,
took a dozen of my guys hostage.
How'd they get by your men?
It's a long story that I
don't have time to tell.
The only demand was to
speak to the mayor.
All right. Well, I'll
go talk to them.
I appreciate that,
but there is no way
I'm sending you in there.
Listen. I wore the blues
a long time.
Before I wore
this monkey suit, ok?
- I can hold my own.
- I know, sir.
It's not the point.
She's right. It's too risky.
Says the man who risks
his life every day.
For this city?
Give me a vest.
I'll go in there,
I'll distract
the son of a bitch,
and in the meantime,
you sneak around the back.
And do your thing, ok?
The longer this drags on,
the worse it gets.
Let me do this.
I'll have his back.
I want you on comms
the whole time.
Sure.
This is mayor Quentin Lance.
I'm unarmed. I'm coming in.
- That's far enough.
- All right.
Just... just take it easy, ok?
Take it easy.
- I'm in position.
- Keep him talking.
You asked for me. Here I am.
What do you want to
talk about with me?
You're the mayor. You're a guy.
Who can make things happen.
Why don't you let a few of
these guys go while we talk?
So I can get stormed
by the cops?
No, thanks. I'm not stupid.
But it would show that you
don't want anybody to get hurt.
Because if anybody gets hurt,
you're in real trouble.
Actually,
I think you're already in trouble.
I'm the one holding the gun.
Not for long. Put it down.
Agh. Err.
This... is... over.
This isn't over until you stop
it, Oliver.
That's the only way out.
What are you talking about?
- No!
- Quentin!
Ahh!
Tark drives the Lane.
Kicks it to aldrich
in the corner for 3.
Bingo! Count it and the foul!
That's an 8-0 run by the comets,
who have stormed
all the way back.
To tie it up here
in the fourth quarter.
88 apiece. What a comeback
for the comets,
and there's a timeout...
No way. It tastes the same.
I'm telling you this big
belly burger's just better.
I think he's right.
This is pre-gwespin
foods merger.
Ooh, dad. What are you
still doing here?
I'm late for a fundraiser.
Yeah. Really late.
You want a burger?
Those things never have good food.
Did something happen
at the scpd headquarters?
Like what?
Never mind.
Hey, queen.
What's the difference.
Between a cop
and the green arrow?
A cop doesn't need to play
dress-up to do his job.
Ha ha ha!
- Ooh! Nice reflexes, Mr. Queen.
- Thank you.
There you are. You know the
party started an hour ago, right?
I need to speak with you.
Uh, this is gonna sound crazy.
Um... I have been here before.
So have you.
What are you talking about?
About the monitor dropping
me into some sort.
Of alternate reality
t-t-time loop or something,
where everything is different,
where Lance is still alive.
Oliver, Lance has
always been alive.
No, he hasn't.
You just don't remember.
Because the monitor has done
something to people's memories,
but I... I think I know
the way out of this,
but I... I need to stop
a bomb at the scpd.
Oliver, will you just
calm down, man?
If there was a bomb,
we would know about it.
Lyla would know about it.
Lyla's a part of this.
Part of what?
Oliver seems to
think that he's caught.
In some sort of time loop.
If we're traveling back in time,
I'd like to revisit my 20s.
I... I need to speak
with Quentin.
They mayor's waiting for me.
Yeah. How'd you know?
Mr. Mayor.
Oh. Hey, Oliver. Listen.
I, uh... I made a few last-minute
changes to the speech, so...
- We need to talk.
- Sure. Let's.
Uh, yeah. I wanted to run
these changes by you anyway.
You want to add
a joke about slabside,
about how I would
rather spend time.
In a supermax
than take your advice.
You steal a copy of my
speech or something?
We've had this
exact conversation already.
What are you talking about?
Fully aware of how
this is going to sound.
Quentin, I'm trapped in some sort of...
Time loop,
where the same events just
keep repeating themselves.
Like "groundhog day."
Sure except this one
ends a lot of people dead,
including the two of us.
Ok. How can I help?
Do you actually believe me?
Oliver, I've seen
one daughter die.
And come back to life twice.
I've seen another come
from some other earth.
I've seen a guy in red run
so fast he can reverse time.
This is not exactly
outside the norm, is it?
Also, I'm done learning my
lesson about doubting you.
Because that always
bites me in the ass. Heh.
What happens now?
Very shortly, we are
gonna learn that.
There is a hostage situation
at the scpd.
They're going to insist that
they talk to you and only you.
And how does it go south?
There's a hidden
explosive device.
That I didn't know about
the first time through,
and judging from the blast,
it's underneath the building.
Ok. So you find it,
you keep us from going boom.
- What then?
- I break out of the loop.
Great. Out of the loop.
Here you are.
There's something you need to see.
Get the feds on the line.
Tell them I need backup now.
What's the situation, captain?
Armed mercs stormed
the precinct,
took a dozen of my guys hostage.
They have a bomb.
We already did a sweep
of the entire building.
It's not in the building.
It's underneath it.
How could you
possibly know that?
I trust him. Instinct thing.
So what do you want to do?
This is mayor Quentin Lance.
I'm unarmed. I'm coming in.
Stop right there.
Oh. It's you. Would you relax?
We are both here
for the same thing.
Hey. How did you know
to come down here?
I may have learned
about the existence.
Of this place as a part
of a former career.
How did you know about the bomb?
You wouldn't believe me
if I told you.
Well, actually,
since you're not going to remember anyway,
there is a crazy space god who
has me trapped in a time loop.
Yeah? Me, too.
It's my second time through.
Same. I wake up in the bunker.
I wake up in my apartment,
so clearly,
the monitor is doing this.
- You mean punishing us?
- Yeah.
We are the two people who have
royally pissed him off the most.
In Russia, I disobeyed him,
and you... you tried to
destroy him.
At least we're in it
together now.
I think disarming that
is the way out of here.
How long do you think
until this thing goes boom?
Oh. Your guess is
as good as mine.
Quentin's upstairs
buying us some time.
- Quentin... he's here?
- Yeah.
I think we just activated
some kind of failsafe.
Look. We need more time
with the next loop, Laurel.
It would probably help if we
found each other faster next time.
There's a party at the
Palmer tech building.
- Meet me there.
- Are we talking formal wear or...
Tark drives the Lane.
Kicks it to aldrich
in the corner for 3.
Bingo!
No way. It's the same.
I'm telling you.
This big belly burger is just better.
Guess you realized you're late.
Something like that.
Hey, queen.
What's the difference.
Between a cop
and the green arrow?
Cop doesn't need to play
dress-up to do his job.
Sorry.
Mr. Mayor.
Hey, Oliver. Listen.
I made a few last-minute changes.
To the speech.
And you figured you should
run them by me first.
Yeah, exactly.
Hey, baby girl.
I didn't think you
were gonna make it.
Me either.
You ok, honey?
I'm just really
happy to see you.
Oh. I'm happy to see you, too.
Though I got to say
I'm glad you left.
The black lipstick
at home tonight.
You know that I'm
earth-2 Laurel.
Who else would you be?
Look. I'm really sorry
to interrupt,
but you and I need to go.
You're coming with us.
We need your help.
What do you mean there's a bomb?
I know how to stop it,
but you have to trust me.
I'm gonna need a vest.
Not this time, Quentin.
This is mayor Quentin Lance.
You wanted to talk. Let's talk.
The detonator operates
on an oscillating frequency.
If we can find the right one,
we should be able to disrupt it.
Vincent, listen to me.
I know you don't
really want to do this.
And I know that
if you don't get in here.
These men are gonna die.
I have an idea.
We did it.
Ok. Fine. You did it.
We stopped the bomb.
What the hell are we still doing here?
I don't... I...
We must have missed something.
- No!
No! No!
Tark drives the Lane.
Kicks it to aldrich
in the corner for 3.
Bingo!
All right.
Quentin's death is the reset point,
which means that.
Saving him must be the key.
What kind of sick game
is the monitor playing?
I don't know.
We need to find out.
Who is behind this
hostage situation.
If it's just about killing
Quentin, then why plant a bomb?
It seems like a lot
of extra work.
Maybe whoever is
behind this wants.
Their involvement kept a secret.
Do you really think there's
a larger conspiracy here?
Those were mercenaries, Laurel,
which means that somebody
had to hire them.
Great, and I'm sure they're gonna
be really easy to find, too.
Any idea where to start?
Let's get Quentin out of here.
Why don't you take
him to the bunker?
What about you?
I'm gonna go take
a look at that bomb.
Laurel, I didn't think
you'd make it tonight.
I am really not in the
mood for small talk.
With the monitor's bestie.
- Excuse me.
- It turns out tranq darts,
they don't feel so good.
I told you that was
a big misunderstanding.
Well, understand this.
The second I get out.
Of this sadistic "edge
of tomorrow" reboot,
I am going to make sure
to tell everyone.
Exactly what kind of
traitor you really are.
Laurel, I truly have no idea
what you're talking about,
but whatever it is
you're feeling toward me,
that's on you.
Thank you for
the advice, Dr. Phil,
and now here's some for you.
The next time you decide
to double-cross someone,
don't pick a woman who
specializes in revenge.
You're threatening me.
Yes. Yes, I am, but don't worry.
You won't remember anyway,
and by the way, I pull off.
The short hair way
better than you do.
What are you doing here?
Well, word came down that the green
arrow called in a bomb threat,
so I thought to myself,
"how did he know about that,
and why didn't he call me?"
Because the monitor has
me trapped in a time loop.
Already told you that.
Ok. Definitely not the
answer I was expecting,
but if the monitor's involved,
anything is possible.
Any idea how to break out?
I have to save Quentin's life.
I thought that this
was the key to it,
but I'm not finding anything.
Well, has to be something.
No case is unsolvable.
This might be impossible.
Well, you'll figure it out.
I do wish I was
as sure as you are.
You want to know what
makes me so sure? You.
You, Oliver.
You always figure it out.
You never stop fighting.
You never give up.
You always keep at it.
Why should this be
any different?
Whatever version this is of you,
you still give the best advice.
- Yeah. I'm flattered.
- Well, a.R.G.U.S. Has.
Some more sophisticated
analytical equipment.
Any chance you can
get me in there?
Yeah. I bet I can make
a few calls.
So you're telling
me we're in some kind.
Of a alternate reality based on
the plot of a bill Murray movie?
Well, I was gonna go with a
Tom Cruise flick but basically.
Also just really glad
that you believe me.
Well, it's not the craziest
thing you ever told me.
I mean, I'm just
glad this monitor guy.
Just kept me as mayor, you know?
What? What's that look?
It... it's just that, uh,
in my world.
Or in the real world, uh,
you're not mayor anymore.
Really? Ohh. Pollard.
She always had it
in for me. Heh.
There something else?
Laurel. Sweetheart,
I always know when you're.
Hiding something from me.
Please tell me. What is it?
It... it's a year and a half ago.
When Diaz... when he shot you.
In... in the real reality
or whatever,
you... you didn't exactly, um...
I didn't recover.
No. No. You died to save me.
Best way I could have gone.
What?! I'm sorry.
I basically just.
Told you you're a ghost,
and you're completely ok with that?
It doesn't... it doesn't faze you?
You're completely calm?
I always felt like I
cheated death with that one.
Guess that's because I didn't.
Fate's just tricky like that.
- It's Oliver.
- Yeah?
He figure out who wants me dead?
Not yet, but he did
figure out the location.
Of the mercs' hideout.
Ok. So we better go.
How'd you find this place?
Uh, we analyzed the bomb.
And traced the
chemical signature.
Back to this building.
Interesting.
What?
Your mouth but Felicity's words.
It still doesn't tell us
who hired these bozos.
Maybe this will help.
Bomb!
Ohh.
Lyla, what the hell
are you doing?
Helping you. You're missing
the point, Oliver.
- What?
- You can't fight this.
Lyla!
Passes it
quickly over to the right.
Tark drives the Lane.
Kicks it to aldrich
in the corner for 3.
Bingo! Count it and the foul!
No sign of Lyla anywhere. You?
John just told me
she got called away.
On a last-minute
a.R.G.U.S. Mission,
meaning she's never
even been here.
Maybe the monitor deleted
her for going rogue.
Heh. Wouldn't that
be so, so sad?
She's clearly helping him.
There's no reason for her.
To switch sides right now.
So why reveal her hand?
It makes no sense.
You spoke with her.
Was there anything,
anything at all.
In the conversation
that stood out?
She said how I feel
towards her was on me.
Like it's my fault that
I'm stuck here.
I told you the monitor's
punishing us.
I'm not so sure.
We've had to watch Quentin
die over and over again,
and we can't save him.
If I had to design hell,
this would be it.
But right before
Lyla disappeared,
she told me she was
trying to help me.
She also told you
you can't fight this.
It seems pretty clear to me
that we're not supposed to win.
The first time
that I met mar novu,
it felt... it felt the same.
It was like I was put in a situation
where there was no way out,
but it was a test, Laurel.
It was a test just like
I think that this is.
- A test of what?
- I don't know,
but there is a way out of here,
and I'm gonna find it.
- You just never give up, do you?
- No, I don't.
Are you with me?
Fine.
What's our play?
We go back
to the mercs' hideout.
We know where the danger
is this time,
so we can do things differently.
You grab Quentin,
and I'll meet you there.
Ok.
So you're telling
me we've been here once.
And still came back for more?
At least now we know
what not to do.
Ok.
That should disable the bomb.
Well, I certainly hope so
because I am getting.
Sick and tired
of getting blown up.
Ok. So now what?
We find out who hired
those mercs to kill you.
Money leads to a man
named Anderson white.
Never heard of him.
Looks like he's been accused.
Of not too many nice things...
Money laundering, racketeering.
Doesn't explain why
he'd want me dead.
Well, that's what we're
gonna find out.
Ceo of a company
named global solutions.
They have a warehouse
down by the docks.
Let's go.
We need to find white.
No! No! I got you.
Come on, come on.
I'll take care of the rest.
Err! Ugh.
Oh, I'm sorry, baby girl.
Looks like we lost this round.
No. No! I am not
letting you die again.
- It's too late.
- No.
It... it's... it's time
to say good-bye.
I'm not giving up
on you, Quentin.
Quentin, I am not
giving up on you.
You never gave up on me.
You believed in me
when nobody else did.
Well, that's what
dads do. They believe.
I want you to know that you.
Are the reason that I'm
trying to be a hero.
It's because of you.
Sweetheart... you are a hero.
You are.
Thank you.
I never had the chance to tell you.
How much you mean to me.
- Well...
- Thank you.
I think you just did.
I love you. I love you.
Good-bye.
Damn it.
All right. Ok.
All right, Laurel.
We fix this next time.
We'll fix it.
I can't do this again.
I'm done, Oliver.
All I have ever wanted
was a chance.
To say good-bye to Quentin.
Now I have.
Tark drives the Lane.
Kicks it to aldrich
in the corner for 3.
Bingo! Count it and the foul!
Laurel?
Laurel!
She's not here.
- Where is she?
- Gone.
What did you... what
did you do, Lyla?
I didn't do anything.
Laurel got what she needed from this.
I don't have time
for these games, Lyla,
so whatever this is,
get me out of here right now!
I can't do that, Oliver.
Mar novu needs you
to understand.
No good will come from struggle.
The only way to win is
to accept the inevitable.
I have no idea what that means.
Learn that, and this will end.
Lyla!
So if me dying is the problem,
maybe bringing me into the
lion's den isn't so smart.
Couldn't think of a better
way to keep you safe.
Yeah. That makes sense.
Huh!
Ah-ah-ah-ah.
Unless you want a hole for a head.
Are you Anderson white?
You really think
Mr. White would be here?
He ordered a hit
on my friend. Why?
I guess the clock's ticking.
Looks like a list of hits.
And clients.
Coded and anonymous.
White's just the middleman.
A ceo with a healthy
side business brokering.
Hits for wealthy asshats.
All right. We're back
to square one.
We have no idea how deep
this rabbit hole goes.
We got to get going.
Unh!
Get down! Get down!
Hey. You ok? You all right? Ok.
No time. Come on.
Come on.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Whoa!
Go, go, go, go, go, go!
Go, go, go.
Let's go.
Get down, get down!
Over there!
Ohh. Oh, it's the last one.
How many arrows you got left?
Not enough.
Oh, boy. Aren't we the couple?
We are gonna find
a way out of this.
There has to be a way to fix it,
and we are gonna
find it, Quentin.
It doesn't matter how many times.
We're gonna find it!
Heh heh. Yeah? Sure.
What's it gonna be,
60 times, 100 times?
It's gonna be however
many times it takes!
You know, getting
hunted like this.
In a space like this
is kind of like.
What I was doing to you
all those years ago.
Remember?
Ohh. Oof.
Sort of makes sense I'd go out
like this now, don't you think?
Would you please just
save your strength.
For what?
Oliver, you take care
of these guys,
there'll be more behind them,
there will be more behind them.
There is no saving me from this!
Ok? You ever think
that's the point?
Maybe you're not supposed to.
I'm not giving up...
And you're not giving up either.
Oh, no, no, no.
I'm not giving up.
Maybe I'm giving in.
You see, I've been outrunning
death for a while now.
The siege, the island,
but when Diaz shot me,
that felt different.
Like I was finally at the end,
and I made my peace with that.
And maybe it's time
you did, too.
It looks like fate's knocking.
Just... just...
You just get ready to move.
I'll see you
on the other side, Oliver.
Quentin.
Passes it
quickly over to the right.
Tark drives the Lane.
Kicks it to aldrich
in the corner for 3.
Bingo! Count it and the foul!
Drives down the Lane.
Beautiful pass
to the big man underneath.
Puts it up off the glass,
and it's in for two.
Inbound pass to the other p...
No way. It tastes the same.
Dad, what are you
still doing here?
Hey, guys.
I'm just heading out the door.
Wanted to let you know,
all of you know.
What a... just what a gift.
Getting to know
you all has been.
Dad, you're going
to a fundraiser.
It's not like you're
going into war.
Heh heh.
Although I guess I can
see the similarities.
I think he's talking
about crisis.
I'm just really proud
of all you guys.
I'm really proud.
I got to go.
Dad...
You're gonna be fine.
So are you.
All of you will be.
Whatever happens.
Hey, queen.
What's the difference.
Between a cop... hey!
Quentin, excuse me.
Yeah.
What's the matter, Oliver?
You look like you've
seen a ghost.
Maybe I did.
May I speak with you
for a second?
Sure.
Uh, yeah, you want to
go over the speech?
Because I was thinking
about adding a few lines.
I have a question for you.
Sure.
Back when I was running
around as the hood,
you were trying to arrest me.
- You remember that?
- Heh heh heh.
Ah. Yeah. The good, old days.
How could I ever forget?
The question is...
What made you decide
that I wasn't.
Your enemy anymore?
What changed your mind?
Heh. Oh, you know,
my daughters for one.
Because I didn't raise dummies,
and, uh, you know, if
they were ok with you,
then I figured I should be, too.
- Yeah.
- They trusted me,
and you trusted them.
Yeah. They got me to listen
to what I always knew.
In my gut, that we were
on the same side.
And fighting for the same goal,
and it just took me
a while to get there.
Sorry.
It's ok.
Oliver, is there
any particular reason.
For this trip down memory Lane?
Yeah.
God, I've been hanging
on to something.
Someone told me
just recently that,
uh... it's about time
I made peace with it.
Ok. Sounds like a smart someone.
Yeah.
Oh, I shouldn't have to
say good-bye to you again.
Good-bye?
Evening's just getting started.
Yeah.
Thank you, Quentin
for everything.
Mr. Mayor.
We're gonna see each other
again, Oliver.
Mr. Mayor!
Ahem.
I hope so.
Congratulations, Oliver.
Now you understand.
I couldn't change
Quentin's fate.
I can't change
mine either, can I?
No. I'm sorry.
Why did the monitor go to all.
Of this trouble just to...
Just to prove a point?
You've always been
a man who needed to.
See things for himself.
Telling you wouldn't
have been enough.
How long have you
worked for him?
A while.
You lied to us, Lyla.
You...
You lied to John.
Keeping this from John has been.
The hardest thing I've
ever had to do.
Then why do it?
The same reason you left
Felicity and Mia.
In that cabin...
To protect my family.
Do you honestly
believe that working.
With the monitor is the
best way to do that?
It's the only way.
The crisis is coming.
There is no stopping it.
All we can do is
try to survive it.
Ok. Help me out here, Lyla.
I don't even know what it is.
I know, but you will... soon.
What I can tell you.
Is there is an evil coming
that is greater.
Than anything we've
ever had to face.
Can we stop it?
I don't know...
But you are the only
chance we have.
So everything I've done.
From the moment
I left that cabin,
this has all been some...
Bigger part of a test?
He needed to be sure
you were ready.
He's just been sending
me on useless missions.
They weren't useless.
The dwarf star particles,
Dr. Wong,
even the antimatter weapon,
they all have a purpose,
just not the one
you were expecting.
Why did he involve my children?
Time is a gift.
What now?
You complete your final mission.
I'll see you there.
Ohh.
Where are we?
You ok?
I have a killer headache.
The last thing that I
remember is Quentin...
Dying in that warehouse.
I was wearing these on the roof.
When we got tranqed,
so does that mean that...
We got out.
How?
We learned our lessons.
I got out after I said good-bye.
Why would the monitor let me
see Quentin one last time?
It was a reward
for not betraying me.
Didn't really think
rewards were his brand.
No. We were wrong about him.
And Lyla was right?
That's annoying.
So why did you have to
learn to let Lance go?
Because deep down,
I still believed.
That I could fight my fate.
Now I know I can't.
Lyla said we had
one last thing to do,
one final mission.
I can't wait to find
out what that is.
Where that is.
We're not in star city anymore.
Dad.
You ok?
Where the hell are we?
We're on lian yu.
Resync from kool3ds
- RDSop -