SLADE:
Your mascara is running.
Thank you.
Are you all right?
I don't know.
It's my boyfriend.
Ex-boyfriend now.
He just, completely out of nowhere,
decides to end things.
Heartbreak is something I know all too well.
It's not an easy thing to recover from.
And sometimes you never do.
Um... We're not, uh...
This isn't my home.
You're not going home, Thea.
Get out.
Get out!
[GASPS]
Hello, Thea.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
About time.
You letting the bad guys stay alive this year
has filled the jails up to capacity.
Yep.
Ready?
Well, I've been working with Sara,
but I'm not exactly a natural.
Neither was I.
Okay, we have some work to do.
Sorry. I'm having a hard time keeping
my head in the game today.
-Thea?
-I just can't stop thinking...
...what's the worst that could happen
if I told her the truth.
I told a guy the truth
and he got struck by lightning.
To be fair,
probably won't happen again, statistically.
Telling Thea the truth won't make her safer,
just the opposite.
What we're doing, Roy, it's dangerous.
And anyone that is even in our orbit
can get hurt.
Try again.
This time...
...aim.
-What are those?
-Month's messages from Queen Consolidated.
-Toss them.
-That's what I did with last month's messages.
With Slade out there,
I don't have time for the company.
Well, you have to make time, Oliver,
at least three hours.
-The annual board meeting.
-Ugh.
There's absolutely zero way that the CEO
can avoid being there.
And I know it's been a while,
so in case you've forgotten, that's you.
Do you remember
where you put your business suit?
Or do you keep it in a cool glass case too?
[HENDRICK GROANS THEN YELLS]
I'm gonna kill all of you.
This is not personal.
Well, maybe a little.
It's not. This is about survival.
"Survival." What a noble word for murder.
Slade gave us no option.
Hendrick for Oliver.
What gives us the right to decide
one's life is more valuable than another?
He is tied up. We are not.
Once he gets the boat working,
Slade will have no more need for him.
So let's not kid ourselves. Doing this
is effectively sentencing Hendrick to death.
He would do the same thing to any of us
in heartbeat.
This is only option.
What if it's also an opportunity?
To do what?
Well, to kill Slade.
I know I haven't been here in a while, but you
don't look like the entire board of directors.
The meeting doesn't start
for another half-hour.
Really?
I routinely bump all appointments 30 minutes
in anticipation of you being late.
That's good policy.
But thank you for coming out of hibernation
for this.
Whether you recognize it or not,
it's your name on the building.
No matter how many meetings you miss...
-...you're still the public face of this company.
-Isabel, I realize I have been distracted.
Thank you for picking up the slack.
Ours is an unconventional partnership,
but it's a partnership.
And it's working.
Indeed, it is.
Oliver?
Your mother's here.
Family squabble?
And how is Miss Rochev these days?
Still angry that Dorothy dropped a house
on her sister?
What are you doing here?
-Have you heard from Thea?
-No.
You haven't returned any of my calls,
so I'm left to resort to checking in person...
...as to whether you're attending
the debate tonight.
I told you that I would publicly support
your campaign.
Anything else?
It would be embarrassing for us both if you
couldn't at least appear to be my son tonight.
I have gotten pretty good at pretending
to be someone I'm not.
I learned it from you.
Excuse me. Have you seen Thea Queen?
Okay.
[LINE RINGING]
Speedy, it's Ollie. I'm at the debate,
where I thought you would be.
Listen, I know that you're upset about Roy,
but Mom needs both of us here...
...so please just call me back.
You do not look happy.
Is everything all right?
Yes, my sister's just a little late.
I'm afraid that's my fault.
S.C.P.D. insisted that I arrive with a motorcade.
We tied up traffic all over the city.
I'm sure Thea's probably just fallen victim
to gridlock.
Well, I should probably try her again.
Good luck tonight, Sebastian.
Thank you, sir.
I thought backstage was supposed to be
restricted access.
The benefits of having
a district attorney's badge, I guess.
-You stopped by to wish Moira good luck?
-I did.
But I'm really glad I ran into you.
I owe you an apology.
I accused you of really terrible things.
You were going through a very difficult time.
I'm just happy you're on the mend.
Good luck tonight.
I'm not the one who's gonna need it.
Sebastian Blood is not the man
you think he is.
He's not going to revive this city
with social services.
He's going to bankrupt it
with unfunded mandates.
Mrs. Queen's problem with my proposals
is that they will be paid for by the 1 percent.
It's time the wealthiest people
stop avoiding their responsibility.
-It will limit their abilities to hire people.
MODERATOR: All right, that's time.
And I will remind the candidates
to please refrain from interrupting.
We have the next in our series of video
questions submitted by Starling City voters.
This one comes from...
..."Thea Queen"?
Okay, there must be some mistake.
[THEA WHIMPERING]
THEA [OVER SPEAKERS]:
Help. Help.
Somebody help me, please.
He's...
MOIRA:
Oh, my God.
We're gonna find her, Roy.
We're gonna get her back.
She's a tough girl.
Is she gonna be alive when we find her?
You can't think like that.
I can't stop thinking like that.
MAN 1: There he is.
MAN 2: Mr. Diggle.
[CROWD CLAMORING]
MAN 3:
Mr. Diggle. Sir, can we get a comment?
-I think I might have found something...
BLOOD: I am suspending my campaign...
...and devoting its resources
to the safe return of Thea Queen.
PIKE: The video referenced a demand
but no ransom...
...which means
this might not be about money.
We're gonna get her back, Moira.
I promise you. Thea's coming home.
Can you think of anyone who might wanna
get to you through Thea?
No one. Except for the families
of the 503 people that died last year.
This isn't about the quake.
-How can you be so sure?
-You just need to find the man in the mask.
We're working on it.
-We're running down every lead.
-What leads?
Oh, God. Oh, God,
how could I have let this happen?
[SHUDDERING]
Excuse me for a minute.
If I hear one more invasive press inquiry
being sent to Mr. Queen...
...or any member of the family,
I will hold you personally responsible.
You're very scary. Thank you.
My job's to take things off your plate,
now more than ever.
To that end, you remember how at today's
meeting the board nominated new officers?
Voting has to take place within 24 hours.
It cannot be suspended. It's an SEC thing.
-I can't think about this now.
-I'm sorry. You have to.
-You're CEO. You have responsibilities.
-Which you handle for me all the time.
A board vote is several orders of magnitude
different from covering a missed meeting.
You could appoint someone CEO pro tem.
-That's not a good idea.
-I'm appointing you.
What?
Congratulations, you are the temporary CEO.
I can't.
Please.
Thank you.
Have Thea thank me
when she's back safe at home.
Mr. Queen? I need to talk to you.
It's about Mr. Wilson.
Since Thea was last seen at Verdant,
I used credit-card receipts...
...compiled a list of customers,
pinged their phones and hacked their photos.
NSA's right. It's easy when you don't
need a warrant. I eyeballed every photo.
-Must've been thousands.
-It's Thea.
I found this.
Partial plate three blocks from the club.
Car is registered to a Slade Wilson,
and it has GPS.
Where is it right now?
Parked outside a defunct bar on Roosevelt.
Okay, this doesn't seem easy to you?
Slade using a car registered in his name?
Smells rotten.
Either Thea's there, or he is.
Either way, we have to go.
I figured you'd say that,
which is why I worked up these.
Tibetan pit-viper venom.
The League of Assassins' poison of choice.
And the most powerful sedative
I've worked with.
That'll give us an advantage.
You are gonna give us another.
-You sure you want me to go?
-Are you angry?
Use that rage.
-You're just always telling me to hold back.
-Not tonight.
Landmines?
What kind of island is this?
Can you remove the explosive?
Certainly.
Without it going off? Eh.
Less certain.
[SIGHS]
Ah, KGB...
...you taught me many, many things.
Russian bomb...
...Japanese bomb...
...they both go boom.
Congratulations, we are not dead.
Now what?
Slade takes Hendrick as we agreed.
And then once they're far enough away...
What?
You want to rig Hendrick into bomb?
Peter was right. Handing Hendrick over
to Slade is the same as killing him.
And you're right too, we don't have a choice.
At least this way, he takes Slade out,
and then we can take the ship.
-What?
-Just wondering...
When did you become so scary?
[SIREN WAILING IN DISTANCE]
Where is she, Slade?
ROY:
The man asked you a question.
Where is she?
What are you gonna do, kid? Kill me?
But then who would tell you...
...where your beloved Thea is?
Call Detective Lance.
-Tell him to come down here.
-What? Why?
To arrest Slade Wilson.
[MOANS]
Any idea what this son of a bitch
wants with Thea Queen?
No. We just need to make sure
Slade gives up where he's holding her.
Does Oliver know?
-That you're working with the Arrow on this.
-Oliver doesn't know anything about the Arrow.
Are you okay?
Yeah. It's just that look in Moira's eyes.
Terrified she's lost her daughter.
I couldn't go through that again, Sara.
Yeah.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Officer Lance? The Queen family's here.
-Mr. Lance, did he tell you where Thea is?
-Mrs. Queen, thank you for coming.
This doesn't make any sense.
Slade Wilson is a friend.
And he's been in Costa Rica
for the past 72 hours.
He can provide flight manifests,
phone records, even some videos...
...so he couldn't have taken your daughter.
-If he didn't, then why did you arrest him?
-We didn't.
He was apprehended by the vigilante...
...who then contacted Officer Lance.
-Lieutenant, I can explain...
-No, I got a pretty clear picture.
You're a special kind of stupid.
The reason you're wearing that uniform...
...instead of a detective's
is because you were working with the vigilante.
-A young girl's missing...
-Now you arrest someone on his say-so?
You'll be lucky if the next uniform
that puts you in isn't prison gray.
They're calling you Deathstroke.
It's a bit flamboyant. Heh.
I like it.
How'd you get off the island?
That is your first question?
You've made it pretty clear that you're not
gonna tell me where my sister is, so yeah...
...that's my first question.
I swam.
But it wasn't without its obstacles.
The rip current dragged me under.
The rocks and reef cut up my flesh
to the bone.
But the Mirakuru...
...it regenerated everything.
Except this.
You know, it's just the two of us in here...
...so why don't we try being honest.
Why are you doing this?
You know why.
It was five years ago.
It was yesterday.
Oh, I tried to let go of the island...
...but it's still got a hold on me.
And if that hood that you wear every night
is any indication...
...it's still got a hold of you, kid.
She never did anything to you. I did.
Shado is dead
because of a choice that I made.
So punish me, blame me, but...
Thea...
You want me to beg?
Is that what this is all about?
Because I'm begging.
You win.
Just please.
Please tell me where she is.
Hmm. That must've been hard for you to say.
Thea.
Well, Thea is...
Mr. Queen? Who the hell let you in here?
Mr. Wilson, you are free to go
with the department's deepest apologies.
SLADE:
No need, lieutenant.
An innocent girl's life hangs in the balance.
You need to follow every lead possible.
Still, you should know that Officer Lance
is facing some very serious charges.
Don't pursue them on my behalf.
I'm not one to hold a grudge.
MAN: Mr. Wilson. Mr. Wilson.
Are you involved with the case, Mr. Wilson?
I was in Costa Rica, but returned
as soon as I heard the terrible news.
WOMAN: What did you tell them
about Thea's disappearance?
I'm offering every resource at my disposal
plus a $5 million reward...
...for any information
that leads to Thea Queen's captors.
[CROWD CLAMORING]
This is Dig. I've got the follow.
FELICITY:
Tracker on his car is active.
Roy, he's coming up on your position.
Got him. He's turning up Warner.
FELICITY:
I see him. Heading north.
Damn it, I lost him.
It's all right. I still have eyes on him.
Sara, cut right onto Downey.
SARA:
Got it.
Negative. Negative, it's not him.
What?
Oh, my God.
He's cloned the tracker signal.
Roy, you've gotta move.
Roy, you gotta pick him up on Fuller.
[TIRES SQUEALING
AND HORNS HONKING]
Roy, do you still have eyes on him?
Roy? Roy?
Leave us.
I'm sorry I was gone for so long.
Screw you.
I saw Oliver and your mother.
They're all quite worried about you.
If you hurt them, I swear I...
Please, go on.
Finish that sentence.
I'm curious to know what kind of threat
a 19-year-old girl can make.
What do you want with me?
Well, that, Thea...
...is a very long story.
Looks like I've got time.
Not at all.
You're free to go.
What?
I had to make a point.
And I made it.
The door is unlocked,
so you can leave anytime you'd like.
Those guys who work for you
will shoot me the second I walk out.
SLADE:
No, they won't.
Their instructions were
to keep you here until I returned.
And I have. So...
...you're free to go.
But if you do...
...you may never know
about your brother's secret.
-What?
-Your brother has a secret, Thea.
Would you like to know what it is?
So...
...what now?
Wait for Oliver.
He'll figure out what our next move will be.
Wait for him to tell us, you mean. We can't do
anything without King Queen's permission.
-You're out of line, Roy.
-Let's just all calm down here.
Slade outplayed us. It happens.
It only happened
because the police let Slade go.
After we turned him in,
because Oliver told us to.
-What were we supposed to do?
-You're Special Forces.
She's an international assassin.
You'd think between the three of us...
...we could've gotten answers out of Slade
instead of turning him in.
Here's what's really sick.
We didn't even question him
because he said it was the right thing to do.
Like he said I needed to break up with Thea
one week after telling me...
-...it wasn't safe to leave her alone.
FELICITY: Wait.
You think it's Oliver's fault
that Slade took Thea?
I think it's his fault
I wasn't there to stop Slade.
And I think you're just blaming Oliver
because you lost Slade.
Well, of course you'd take his side.
You're screwing him.
Could you guys give us a minute, please?
You remember how she loved to color?
Your father would buy her boxes of crayons
by the truckload. She could never get enough.
She'd draw on the walls.
And I could never get angry
because it was just so adorable.
You should try to get some sleep.
MOIRA [SOFTLY]:
Is my baby still alive?
What?
[IN NORMAL VOICE]
Is my baby still alive?
Yes.
I woke up every day for five years,
the mother who lost her son. I...
I can't...
I can't endure it again.
And now you hate me.
And you have every justification.
-Now is not the time.
-Yes, it is.
It is exactly the time.
I've told you that these lies
were to keep our family safe.
To keep us all together.
But that was the biggest lie of all.
And I told it to you, to Thea...
...to myself.
Because I was too weak...
...to face any kind of truth.
What's happening now isn't your fault.
From the moment your children are born...
...you worry what the world
might do to them.
But you never stop to think
what you might do to them.
That we could be our own worst enemy.
[IVO COUGHING]
Ollie.
What did you do to him?
Not enough.
And what did you do to him?
We just knocked him out. It's better that way.
He wasn't exactly a fan of the arrangement.
I'd imagine.
Hendrick's all yours.
I know.
Wait.
It's an incredible thing, this Mirakuru.
Not only does it gives you strength,
it also heightens all of your senses.
TNT has a particular smell.
How long before it goes off?
Ninety seconds?
Sixty seconds?
You're thinking that the blast would kill me...
...but I disagree.
Not that I could say the same for you lot.
I'm tempted to see this blow you to pieces.
But then again, maybe I'll just shoot you
the same way that he shot Shado.
No.
SHADO:
Slade.
Hey, where you going?
-Sitting around here isn't helping Thea, is it?
-Neither is you running off half-cocked, Roy.
[SCOFFS]
ROY: I know that you think
that this is the Mirakuru,but it's not.
I'm right, and you know that I am.
So you better get the hell out of my way.
Roy, just calm down.
-That's what Thea would want us to do.
-She's right, Roy.
Come on, let's throttle back...
[DIGGLE GRUNTING]
Next one goes into your chest.
Let him go.
You'd honestly kill me because I dare
to criticize the almighty Oliver Queen?
No, I'd kill you
because you're hurting my friend.
Let him go.
OLIVER:
Let him go!
-What the hell's going on down here?
-I'm done.
That's what's going on.
Thea, she's out there, hurt or worse,
because of one person.
And that is not Slade Wilson.
Roy.
I believed in you.
There's nothing left for me here.
[COMPUTER BEEPS]
FELICITY:
Oh, my God. Oliver.
Now what?
Publicity has drafted
a rather compelling statement...
...and I will be doing the talk-show rounds
to control the spin.
I'm sorry, Miss Rochev, but he was very...
...insistent.
Can you give us the room, please?
-Isabel, what have you done?
-Me?
Very little.
You're the one who made this possible
when you made me CEO.
I know it was only temporary...
...but it gave me the authority I needed
to call an emergency board meeting.
As of 30 minutes ago...
...your company belongs to me.
The directors unanimously
made my appointment permanent.
I'd say they lost faith in your leadership,
but that would imply there was any.
Maybe you should've focused
a little less on your...
...evening activities.
Slade.
You're working for him.
With.
He knew planting me in your family's business
would draw you back to Starling City.
Truth be told, I was skeptical, but...
Why are you doing this?
I think it's sad you don't know.
"The sins of the father
are the sins of the son."
[BOTH GRUNTING]
You are gonna tell me where my sister is...
...or I am going to kill you.
Where is she?
He's holding her at a storage depot
just outside the city limits.
Tosca Cartage.
How do I know you're not lying?
[LAUGHS]
It's cute how you think this isn't all playing out
exactly how he wants it to.
And he wants you to come alone.
If he even smells your partners,
he will gut sweet little Thea like a trout.
It was a pleasure doing business with you,
Oliver.
-At least let us surround the perimeter.
-Isabel was very clear.
I come alone, or Thea dies.
Ollie, this is another one of Slade's games.
-And unless...
-No, what I can't do, Sara, is nothing.
What would you do if it were Laurel
or your father or your mother?
I will not get dragged into the same debate
over and over.
Go.
Go get Thea.
Stop Slade.
Do whatever it takes.
End this once and for all.
[ALL GRUNTING &amp; YELLING]
[SCREAMS]
Stop. Stop.
[BUS DOOR OPENS]
Halloween was six months ago, ass-hat.
Now, get off the road or get put down.
You hear me?
I have a proposal for you men.
[BLUETOOTH RINGING]
-Go.
-Oliver, are you okay?
-Yeah, I'm fine. But Thea's not here.
-You did it.
-Did what?
-Thea's fine. She's fine.
She walked into the precinct
five minutes ago.
Safe and sound.
Oliver, did you hear me?
-Thea?
-She's fine. No injuries. He didn't touch her.
-He wasn't there. He had men, hired guns.
-Because he was busy elsewhere.
DIGGLE: Iron Heights reopened a wing
damaged in the quake.
There was a prisoner transfer.
Slade hijacked it.
-Soldiers for his army.
-Abducting Thea was all a diversion.
Oliver.
-Oh, thank God.
MOIRA: Oh, my baby.
Oh, my baby.
What?
He told me.
Mr. Wilson...
...he told me your secret.
How you've been lying to me for years.
How could you not tell me
Malcolm Merlyn was my father?
I believed in you.
We were trying to keep you safe.
You have any idea who you sound like?
You sound like her.
Slade...
...death is too good for them.
This island should be their punishment.
Death is too good for you.
This island should be your punishment.
Their prison for the rest of their days.
Your prison for the rest of your days.
Get him out of here.
IVO:
Slade.
Get back.
I can help you.
You can live or you can die. You choose.
Would you like to send a message
to your family?
Because as soon as this boat is fixed,
I'm paying them a visit.
[SIREN WAILING]
Hell of a night.
Quentin Lance,
master of the understatement.
PIKE:
A word, officer?
Hold on, sweetheart.
Yeah.
I've spoken to DA Spencer
about your situation.
She doesn't wanna press charges...
...if you cooperate.
Tell us who the vigilante is.
Heh. I'd love to, but I don't know.
-Well, that's unfortunate.
-Yeah, it looks like.
Quentin Larry Lance...
...you are under arrest for conspiracy
and aiding multiple felonies.
What? Are you out of your mind?
What are you doing? Wilson did it.
I collared the right guy. What are you...?
-Pike.
-You have the right to remain silent.
-What are you doing?
PIKE: You have the right to an attorney.
Dad?
Riding what pundits are calling
a "sympathy bump"...
...Moira Queen pulled far ahead
of Sebastian Blood...
...in the latest polls conducted
in the last 24 hours by channel...
This whole thing just blew up in our face.
How the hell do I get elected now?
-I think you intended a different tone.
-You said I'd be mayor.
You just delivered this election
for Moira Queen. And for what?
What is this obsession you have
with the Queen family?
-You haven't told him? Heh.
-Shh.
You promised me.
I promised you this city.
I promised you an army with which to take it.
What is our status?
Queen Consolidated's Applied Sciences
Division is now fully dedicated...
...to replicating a serum
based on your blood sample.
You see?
Everything is proceeding as planned.
Where are you going now?
To service my obsession.
Oliver Queen needs one more distraction.
What are you two doing here?
Thought this is where you would go.
You're predictable. That,
and you've been sleeping on the cot at night.
What are you doing here?
Where else would we be?
Roy was right.
At every turn,
I have made the wrong decision.
With him. With...
...the company.
And with Thea.
I was so focused
on what Slade might do to me...
...that it never even occurred to me
what I could do to myself.
I am my own worst enemy.
That's Slade talking.
Don't let him in your head.
I can't keep him out of my head, Diggle.
I can't...
-I can't stop him from doing anything.
-Yes, you can.
What makes you so sure?
Because you're not alone, man.
Now what, boss?
Now we fight back.
Police have issued a warrant
for Slade Wilson...
...after Thea Queen named him as
the mastermind of her kidnapping yesterday.
This in the wake of Wilson's arrest
and subsequent release by the S.C.P.D...
...hours before Miss Queen was released.
In a statement to the press,
S.C.P.D. Lieutenant Franklin Pike...
...reiterated his support for his department
despite what appears to be a serious blunder.
He went on to say the S.C.P.D.
is committed...
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
...to making sure any arrest they make
is a legal one.
Don't worry.
I am not here to harm you.
Go to hell.
All in good time, I'm sure.
But before then...
...I have come to Starling City
to see Oliver Queen suffer.
Oliver...? What? Why?
Because he's not the man you think he is.
And how would you know that?
Because I know Oliver Queen is...
...the Arrow.
[GASPS]