Well, I'm... I'm conflicted
about this.
I'm not gonna lie to you.
I'm a police officer,
Duly Sworn.
I don't condone vigilantes
or vigilantism.
Once people start taking the law
into their own hands,
you're on the road to anarchy.
But there's worse things
out there than anarchy,
and sometimes, as much
as I hate to admit it,
the police aren't enough
to deal with it all.
[Man vocalizing on soundtrack]
Narrator:
Emerald Archer:
The hood and the rise of
vigilantism.
[Sirens]
[Indistinct shouting]
[Indistinct police radio
transmissions]
Thea: Look, Star City is
a very dangerous place.
If it wasn't, my brother Tommy
would still be alive,
my mother would still be alive.
If the police can't
protect the people,
then the people need to learn
how to protect themselves.
Diaz: Vigilantes?
No, they're... they're hypocrites.
They think that they're
upholding the law,
but they're breaking the law.
They're not heroes.
They're criminals.
The only difference
between me and them
is that I'm
smart enough to realize
that the only person
worth looking out for
is yourself.
I've lost a lot,
most recently my dad.
The world needs a protector,
someone to keep it safe.
And it doesn't matter
if someone's wearing a mask.
All that matters
is no one should
have to lose their family
or anyone they love.
Narrator: Villains
or vigilantes?
Criminals or heroes?
From Star City to Central City
to Gotham City,
Americans have debated
this question.
Do the ends justify the means?
Does the law have to be broken
to uphold it?
[Grunting]
Woman: Whoa. Did you get that?
Man: Go! Go! Go...
Dinah: Hey! Hey, you're
not supposed to be here!
Narrator: In December 2018,
the Star City police department
answered that question
definitively
when they officially deputized
Oliver Queen,
the vigilante known as
the Green Arrow.
Drop the gun, Max!
[Indistinct shouting]
Sin, Voice-Over: I knew them
back in the day.
Canary, the Arrow,
the whole crew.
Honestly, I don't know
where I'd be right now
without them.
They helped me out of
a couple pretty tight spots.
I owe them a lot.
But I, uh, I saw the toll
that it took on them.
Like, people like
to debate about the legalities,
but for the people
wearing the masks,
it's... It's not
philosophical, it's real.
[Camera shutter clicking]
And it takes everything
from them.
Oliver: It absolutely
takes a toll.
I have been doing this
in Star City
for a really long time,
you know?
Nearly... nearly 7 years,
but before that,
i... I was running
all around the world
with a hood on, trying to make
things right, and...
Now my life has...
it's never been better.
I'm... I'm...
I don't have to wear
a mask anymore.
And that really makes
all the difference.
I'm... I'm doing what I think
I'm supposed to be doing
in the light of day.
And if I could've, I would've
done it this way from the start.
[Door opens]
Felicity: Surprise.
Hey. One minute, please?
Hey. Hey. Come here.
Hey, buddy. Hey.
Kiddo,
how are you?
I think I've grown
out of "kiddo."
Yeah. OK.
All right.
Felicity: Well,
who gave you permission to grow so tall?
My god.
You must be so excited
to be done... midterms.
You finally come home
and relax, you know...
What's this?
Oh, right.
Uh, Ms. Pedowitz
is doing a documentary
on vigilantes,
and the SCPD
and I thought
it might be a way to, uh,
improve public opinion
on the work I'm doing.
Pedowitz: I've
been collecting
interviews for years
and, frankly,
I couldn't get the funding
I needed to finish it
until your dad
went public.
Well, the timing
is perfect.
I mean, what with
you working with the SCPD
and, you know, um, heh,
full transparency.
But this isn't gonna
be in the film, right?
We can...
we need all of
this edited out.
I don't want my
son on camera.
Pedowitz: Oh, uh, OK.
Guys, cut, please.
Man: OK. Mark.
Felicity: You know, I kind of
hate the word "vigilante."
It just feels like
such a... Disrespectful term.
Call them what they are... heroes.
What? Oliver Queen?
No, that's ridiculous.
Look, first of all, Oliver Queen
doesn't even know Adam Hunt.
And even if he did, what do you
think he did...
slip out of his own
welcome home party
to become Robin Hood?
[Crowd cheering]
I missed tequila!
John: Ha ha!
No, look,
you don't become successful
in my line of work
without being really good
at sizing people up.
Trust me.
Oliver Queen is no one's hero.
Obviously, this particular
comment didn't age too well.
[Indistinct conversation]
Truth is, Oliver is not
the same man he was 7 years ago.
He's changed, grown
not just as a hero
but as a person.
Quentin: You really expect me
to believe you're the Arrow?
I am the Arrow.
Oliver Queen
isn't the Arrow.
Quentin, Voice-Over:
Heh! OK, I'll bite. Why?
Because
Starling City needs
what you
can't give it...
Hope.
Dinah: Well,
he fights for justice,
and he cares about the city,
which is no different than
any other officer here,
as far as I'm concerned.
He just dresses in green leather
and runs around
with a bow and Arrow.
Which sounded a lot better
in my head.
Can we, uh, can we...
can we do that again?
There have been two murders in the
past week that strike me as odd.
Throats slit
on both of them.
We should cross-reference
the victimology
with any open cases.
Way ahead of you.
Uh, working for the police
is different.
I always thought I was
gonna work on my own,
or that was the plan...
"my crusade is my crusade."
But, you know, life doesn't
work out that way.
Next thing I know,
I'm leading a team.
[Sighs]
I'm not...
I'm not entirely sure
I'm meant to be a leader.
Made a lot of mistakes.
Man: Here they come.
Rolling.
Shots fired
at the parking garage
on nutter and winter.
Possible vigilante
sighting.
And vigilantes are still
illegal in Star City.
[Siren in distance]
Man: Captain Drake,
are we clear?
Clear. Establish
a perimeter.
Oliver:
Is this a false report?
I think it's more
that we're just too late.
[Man groaning]
Man: Go.
Oliver: Rene...
I need a bus at
nutter and winter!
Officer down!
They respond
faster that way.
Medics are on the way,
buddy. It's gonna be OK.
I'm fine.
I got a vest on.
Just got the wind knocked out of me.
But they took...
[coughing]
Who'd they take?
The new Green Arrow.
Man: Who's he talking about?
Pedowitz: I don't know.
Just stay on them.
Hey, turn that off...
I told you to turn
those cameras off.
You promised me
full access.
Hey! Keep rolling.
Follow him.
What do you think
you were doing out there?
Same thing
you do.
I'm doing good,
by the way.
Thank you
for asking.
I'm glad you're OK.
I'm glad the FBI made
your immunity permanent,
but being a vigilante
is illegal in Star City.
Well, that's easy
for you to say.
I mean, you have a cute,
shiny new badge.
Thought about giving
one to anyone else?
First step would probably
be not being so reckless.
- You or me?
- Try to guess.
I nearly lost my job
giving Oliver a badge,
and Pollard is still looking
for ways to take it from him.
Oliver: You said they took
the new Green Arrow.
What happened out there?
We were handling
a routine drug bust.
Dinah: I'm sorry, Rene.
Are you still working with
the new Green Arrow?
Because I'm pretty sure
we've been over this.
Not for nothing,
but crime stats
have skyrocketed
ever since
we've hung up
our masks,
and they've gone down
ever since nga showed up.
Oh, we need
to come up with
a better name immediately.
OK. Who was it who
attacked you guys?
Another mask,
some sort of exosuit.
Looked military.
Oliver: All right,
we need a full
forensics sweep
of the abduction point.
I need to know
where they could've gone.
On it.
Pollard:
What is this circus?
Public relations.
Oliver thought...
I don't mean them.
I mean what I've been hearing
about a vigilante being
abducted tonight.
I thought you didn't
care about vigilantes.
Believe me, captain Drake,
I'm anything but Sanguine,
but your little stunt of
deputizing Oliver Queen
has set off
a firestorm.
That's funny. I think that's
actually a different superhero.
You're doing your
damage control.
I'm doing mine.
I'm holding a town hall
on vigilantism.
In the hope
that firestorm
will burn Oliver,
get him to resign?
Your friend Oliver,
he's gonna have to stand in
front of the city he lied to,
a city that's afraid
of him, and justify
his continued existence
as the Green Arrow.
You can't force him to.
Oh, I'm the mayor.
I'm pretty sure I can.
You guys get all that?
[Typing on keyboard]
- Take it off.
- What?
The worm or virus
or trojan horse you
put on my tablet.
Take it off
right now.
I didn't put
anything on your...
I found
a firewall breach
with a Bluetooth
incursion.
It had to be you.
OK! Whoa.
I programmed a virus
so that it would infect anything
that tried to log on to our wifi
for security purposes.
It wasn't personal.
Take it off
right now.
OK. Whoa. What is
going on with you?
I haven't seen anybody
this unhappy to be home
since I had to go
back to Vegas
after my first year
of mit.
I'm just pissed
about my tablet.
You were pissed
a long time
before you found my virus,
which is for your protection, by the way.
Really good job
on finding it. I mean...
- Do you want to talk?
- No.
That wasn't so much
a suggestion
as it was more one of those
"mom" things where
if you don't talk now,
you're grounded. So...
Why didn't you let me come
home for Christmas break?
Oh, will...
Trust me, things here were
very complicated.
I was the only kid
left at school,
and then when
I come back here,
dad's in the middle
of making some movie.
It's a documentary. It's...
I'm sorry.
I thought you'd be happy to be home.
We're so happy
that you're home.
We missed you.
Then you shouldn't
have sent me away.
That is not fair.
Yeah. Neither is
getting shipped off
to boarding school.
[Door closes]
John.
Hey.
Felicity's having trouble
locating the new Green Arrow
using surveillance and
keyhole satellite technology,
but I think we both know
A.R.G.U.S. has satellites
off the books.
Oliver, you come in
here with guns blazing,
asking for satellite access
you shouldn't even know about!
I'm simply asking if I can
have your help on this one.
Well, Oliver, yes, but, look,
I need a little bit more information.
I'm quite sure you're
not this animated
because this missing
Green Arrow copied your hood.
She was abducted, John,
and I need to find her.
How do you know
he's a her?
[Sighs]
Because she's
my sister.
Thea?
I have another sister.
My mother wasn't the only
one who had an affair.
Who'd have known
that wearing a hood
and carrying a bow and Arrow
runs in a gene pool?
Look, will you... will you
please help me find her?
Of course I will.
But I have to ask...
how long have you
known about this?
- A month.
I didn't keep it
from you.
I don't
do that anymore.
I mean, you have to admit,
we haven't exactly been running
in the same
Circles lately.
Lately. Lately's been
nearly a year, Oliver.
But I get it.
We have not been looped in.
[Sighs]
But, look,
you should know something.
You rang, boss?
I did.
Oliver needs access
to the black watch
satellites.
Is he supposed to know about those?
You know about those?
You've met my wife,
right, Curtis?
Great point.
Uh, what are we
looking for?
Not what. Who.
John: Area's clear.
Oliver: You sure
this is the place?
It's been closed
over a year.
Curtis saw movement off
the black watch satellites
at the new Green Arrow's
last location.
Her name is Emiko.
Sounds like you two
have had a conversation.
It's not going
too well so far.
My father
abandoned her.
My mother didn't
help any.
Still, shows
a lot of respect
for her to put on
your hood and quiver.
Not quite sure why
she's done that.
Looks like someone's
been fixing up the place.
[Lock clicks]
[Door opens]
Oliver.
Looks like Rory Regan's...
And Rene's.
John, that's Helena's.
And this is Emiko's.
What the hell is
this guy doing?
He's hunting vigilantes.
I've been on more than
one side of the law.
I was a vigilante, and now
I'm the district attorney.
So, I think it's
pretty safe to say
that I'm qualified to talk about
whether vigilantes can operate
within the bounds of the law.
They can't.
They shouldn't.
I know that. And guess what?
They know it, too.
Because if what they were
doing was right,
they wouldn't hide
behind a mask.
Rory: Yeah, and I stopped
hiding behind a mask.
But I didn't
stop doing good because
people need help.
It's just that simple.
Is that all?
Rene: I keep going out there
because I love my city
and I'd do anything to help it.
To me, I'm risking more
sitting on my hands
doing nothing,
just letting the world
get worse.
Yeah, the mayor,
the politicians.
They might care about the city,
but they don't seem to give a
crap about the people in it.
So, are you really so surprised
when people decide
to do something about it?
[Curtis sighs]
Curtis: Um, Oliver's
a complicated person.
You know, we haven't always
seen eye to eye.
He's no Saint.
But he doesn't have to be
for what he does,
for what he is.
That's a hero.
So it looks like I'm
the director, right?
That's awesome.
I didn't just... I...
I messed it up? Sorry.
Oliver is
an interesting guy. Um...
Unbelievably damaged.
I hope he won't mind me
saying that.
I don't mean... well, all I meant
by that was just that he's...
He's lived through
a lot of darkness.
And all he really cares
about is trying to make sure
nobody else has to go
through what he's gone through.
No, no, no. I didn't know
he was the Green Arrow
until he turned himself in.
I mean, and...
[imitates explosion]
You know.
Whoa, obviously,
big surprise.
I mean, you think you
know a guy.
[Indistinct police radio
transmissions]
Curtis: And bingo
was his name-o.
I found chimera.
Chimera?
Yeah. Chimera. We gotta
call him something.
I thought "chimera"
sounded cool.
[Man sighs]
OK, do I look
like Cisco?
Uh, who are they?
John: Curtis!
I need you to focus.
How'd you find the target?
What? Oh, yeah,
uh, sorry.
I managed to track it
using the security footage
from that abandoned
athletic club.
After that, I was able
to pinpoint the trajectory
using the black watch
satellites,
which I never said,
because they don't exist.
Dinah: OK. Where was
he headed, Curtis?
101 federal street. It's an abandoned
building. Probably a secondary lair.
101 federal?
Yeah. Why?
It used to be
Adam Hunt's building.
Who's Adam Hunt?
You know,
either way, suit up!
They're already
suited up, though.
[Clears throat]
Pedowitz: Hurry up.
Get this, get this.
Man: OK, yeah. Huh!
Not anymore.
Dinah: It's a big building.
He could be anywhere.
John: Let's start from
the top, work our way down.
You really shouldn't
be in here with us.
Dinah: He's right.
The guy we're going
after is dangerous.
We knew what we were
getting ourselves into
when we agreed
to this.
Dinah: Suit yourself.
[Pedowitz and man scream]
Man: What the hell is that?
Get them
out of here!
Keep looking
for her!
John: Go, go, go! Get down,
get down, get down, get down!
Man: OK, just go.
Aah! Uh!
[Man groaning]
[Arrow flies]
Get out of here now!
[Rifle firing]
You all right?
Yeah. I knew
you had my back.
Dinah: Oliver!
Cameraman: Look...
She's hurt bad.
It's OK.
You're gonna be OK.
He's... he's coming.
He's coming
for you, Oliver.
Hey, hey. You hungry?
We've still got
half a pizza left,
and somebody's
gotta eat it.
- Thanks, dad.
- Of course.
[Knock on door]
Who's that?
It's probably your
aunt Dinah
coming here to lecture me
about something.
I swear, she treats me
like a kid or something.
Well, if you just
listen to her.
If you take her side,
I take back that pizza.
Hi. Is Zoe home?
Yeah. Yeah, she is.
I didn't know you
were back in town.
Just for a few days.
Your folks know
you're here?
I'm not 7.
Hey, will. Dad,
I totally forgot.
I texted will about
my geography homework.
He said he'd come
over to help.
Is it OK if we work
in the living room?
I didn't realize
that you two were...
ahem... you know.
Friends?
Yeah.
Felicity set up
an encryption scheme
so I could text Zoe
while I was away.
I didn't know that.
Why didn't I know that?
How come you didn't
tell me?
It's just texting, dad.
Yeah. Yeah, yeah,
yeah, sure, yeah.
Um, you guys can have
the living room.
I'll be in
the next room...
Cleaning my gun.
Don't worry about him.
How's it being back home?
Sucks.
Guys with cameras are following
my dad and Felicity everywhere.
And that's
what's bothering you?
We've only got
about 3 minutes
before my dad finds
an excuse to check on us.
What's wrong?
You tell some girl
you have a crush on her
and she didn't
like you back?
Sort of.
Cool. What's her name?
It's not that.
Then what is it?
I don't know.
I think you do know.
You just don't want
to tell me.
Maybe it's not
the worst thing.
My dad and aunt Dinah
fight instead of talk.
Promise me we'll
never be like that.
You got it.
Mind if I hang here
for a few hours?
I really do not
want to go back home.
OK. We should probably
open that geography book.
Yeah.
Get up. Go.
Curtis: What's that mean,
"he's coming for you"?
Well,
this chimera...
I'm really glad that
name's catching on.
Hey, he's
hunting vigilantes.
So he's like
an anti-vigilante vigilante.
John: More like a predator
or a lion trying
to take down the biggest
in the jungle.
Dinah: That's quite a leap.
Tell that to Rene,
who was nearly cut in half,
had it not been for the kevlar,
or Rory or Helena,
neither of which we can
get in contact with.
Oliver and I came across
this collection of masks
in chimera's
underground lair.
He had them all
on display,
almost like
trophies.
Any word?
Oliver: Best guess is that
she has a concussion
and a couple of
broken ribs.
They're having Dr. Schwartz
examine her discreetly.
Dinah: Did she give you
any intel on chimera?
Is that what
we're calling it?
I can only hope. I mean,
it'd be nice. Heh! Ahem.
No, she was
in too much pain to speak.
Oliver: Meanwhile.
John: Meanwhile...
You're next on
chimera's list.
So I can't think of
a worse idea
than going out as Green Arrow
during Pollard's town hall.
Except maybe showing up
in the first place.
Maybe you should tell Pollard
that you're not coming.
I think that's Dinah's job.
Great.
Schwartz: Excuse me.
Uh, where is she?
What?
Your green-hooded friend.
She's not in her room.
Oliver: Oh, for god's sakes.
Well, did we really expect
her to stick around?
[Whispering] No.
It's just me.
What are you doing here?
Captain Drake told me you
bailed at the hospital.
I just came to
check up on you.
- Let me help you with that.
- I can manage on my own.
You are so stubborn.
You sure you and
Oliver aren't related?
[Sighs]
Actually, we are.
He's my half-brother.
Ha ha! That's funny.
I'm not joking.
Robert Queen was my father.
So when you told me
about your mother,
you kind of left out a
pretty important detail.
Robert was out of
the picture long before.
I didn't want to
tell you
because I didn't want
to risk changing things.
Changing
what things?
You and me working together.
Why would it?
Oliver's got his thing,
and we've got our thing.
Right?
Yeah, we do.
All right. All right.
Thank you, Ms. Mayor...
For nothing.
[Hangs up]
We have a new problem.
Don't we always?
Dinah, before
we get to that,
there's something that I need
to speak with you about,
something I've been
keeping from you.
Well, that is par for
the course with you, Oliver.
That's a fair point.
In this instance,
I just... I needed
some time
to process
the information
before I shared it
with everyone.
What information?
The new Green Arrow
is my half-sister.
She's the product of an
affair that my father had.
Wow.
Ha ha!
I wasn't expecting that.
I really hope you
can appreciate
why I needed
some time with this.
Sure. Yeah.
I have lots of questions.
I have a lot of
questions, too.
I have been trying
to connect with her,
but she is
not very trusting
at the moment.
Sounds like
your sister, all right.
OK, what's
our new problem?
Right. Pollard is insisting you
go to the town hall tonight.
What? You explained
to her...
yeah, of course I did.
But she actually thinks
that we made up chimera
as an excuse to get you
to not face the city.
If I had a problem being scrutinized,
Dinah,
I wouldn't let a camera
crew follow me around.
I know. I explained
that to her.
But if you ask me,
she sees this town hall
as a chance to
publicly crucify you,
and she's not
gonna miss that.
I'm not exposing
hundreds of people
to what could potentially
become a war zone.
Pollard cannot
force me to.
- I will tell her.
- Thank you.
Mm-hmm. This should be fun.
Hey. You got a minute?
Of course.
I know you don't plan on doing this
town hall meeting thing, do you?
I just told Dinah to
tell Pollard that.
I'm thinking maybe
you should.
It might be our only shot
at catching chimera.
Curtis will
find him again.
Yeah, well, the trail's
gone cold.
But, Oliver, I have a plan.
I'm all ears.
So are they.
Sorry, guys.
Private party.
Cameraman: Ugh. Damn it.
I enjoyed that.
You know I know what
you're gonna say, right?
I do.
Best way to stop chimera
is by drawing him out?
Exactly.
Not with hundreds of
people there, John.
This guy's taken
down 4 vigilantes.
He is out of
the SCPD's league.
Yes, he is...
But not Team Arrow's.
What? No. No.
There's no world
in which Pollard
will allow Dinah to
deputize all of you.
And I'm certainly not going
to risk you going to prison
for violating
the anti-vigilante law.
Come on.
Even if I was willing to take that risk,
there is
no Team Arrow anymore.
But there is.
Oliver, there is.
It's just changed.
We may not have been Team Arrow
when you were in slabside,
but we had
each other's backs.
Just give us a chance,
man, to have yours.
You could
go to prison.
So?
You did it for us,
which never really
sat right with me.
And the reason why is because
it wasn't right, Oliver.
We have fights, disagreements,
recriminations,
but it doesn't matter
because we are a team.
And nothing's going
to change that.
John, I made a lot
of mistakes.
We all did.
That's why they're
called mistakes, Oliver.
You learn from them.
You move forward.
We...
We get better.
Announcer: Ladies
and gentlemen,
welcome to our town hall
discussion on vigilantism.
We're about to get started.
Please take your seats.
Pollard:
Thank you for coming.
You made it pretty clear
I didn't have a choice.
Well, it's my hope
that once the
pittson pavilion opens,
your services will
no longer be required.
The police can keep this
event and the city safe.
The SCPD
has been rebuilt
into a remarkable
police force,
but if they were
enough, the city
wouldn't need me,
now, would they?
It doesn't need you.
That's exactly the message
I intend to convey tonight.
[Applause]
Mayor Pollard.
All right, buckle up, kiddies,
because overwatch is back in the house.
Well, not actually
in the house.
I mean, I'm working at A.R.G.U.S. remotely,
but I'm on the comms, you know.
We know what
you meant, overwatch.
Cool, cool, cool.
So I am tapped
into the Venue's CCTV,
and I am very proud of this one,
The Documentary
Crew's wifi,
so everything
they see, I see.
Copy that. Standing by.
I swore I'd never
wear this suit again.
Come on. It's got to feel good
to be back in the saddle.
I just wish Dinah
was here with us.
She's doing
her thing with SCPD.
That anti-vigilante law's
crap, man.
No argument from me.
Let's do this!
Over the past 7 years,
Star City has suffered
through a weapon
of mass destruction,
an actual army of soldiers,
and nuclear weapons...
what happened 7 years
ago, I wonder.
Now, Mayor Pollard, I
fail to see your point.
7 years ago,
you started zip-lining
through the city.
Your activities as the hood
and then the Green Arrow
prompted the very same dangers that
you claim to have saved us from.
[Audience members gasp]
Everyone clear out of here!
[Woman screams]
Man on P.A.: All units,
all units, report to...
Dinah: Come on! Let's go!
Let's go. Let's go.
[Bullets ricocheting]
Hyah! Hyah! Hyah...
[Groans]
Too bad you don't wear
the mask anymore,
but I'll settle
for the hood.
You want a mask?
Here's 3.
[Gunfire]
[T-spheres whirring]
OK, I'm analyzing the armor.
It's Wayne enterprises,
military grade.
I'm just figuring out
how to disable it.
[Canary cry]
[Breathing heavily]
Get as many of these people
out of here as you can.
What about you?
He wants a vigilante?
I'm gonna give him one.
OK, good news, bad news
time, guys.
The suit is powered by
an exolithium cell.
He can't move without it.
The only problem is...
It's electromagnetic
shielded,
which means you can't
disable it remotely.
All good.
Oliver, Dinah,
team's in position.
We've got this.
Dinah: On your call.
Oliver: Now!
[Yells]
Uh!
Dinah!
[Canary cry]
Whoo!
Pedowitz: Please tell me
you got this.
Officer: Scpd! Don't move!
Freeze!
Rene:
What the hell is this?
Maybe you all were too
busy being unconscious,
but we just saved
everyone in here.
Pollard: Illegally.
The anti-vigilante
law stands.
My hands are tied.
Your honor...
I'm sorry.
The law is the law.
The mayor can't
make exceptions.
Take them into custody.
[Handcuffs lock]
Nick: His name's
Kevin Meltzer,
recently released from
roth psychiatric hospital.
Imagine that.
Apparently,
the hood saved his life 7 years ago,
and he's been obsessed with
vigilantes ever since.
Oliver:
So he just attacks them.
Says he just wanted
the masks.
Fans have a strange way of
showing their affection.
Where are the others?
Interrogation room.
We're not all
on board with this.
Yeah, that's cute.
Hey, get that camera
out of my face
before I give you
an enema with it.
Well, this is
another fine mess
you all have managed
to get yourselves into.
John: We were
aware of the risk.
All of us.
I think I know
the answer to this,
but is there any way
for us to avoid
sharing Oliver's old cell?
As the district attorney,
I can decline
to press charges.
Great.
But by going out
tonight,
we violated the avl.
Not so great.
We don't have a lot
of good options here.
I'm sorry.
I never should have let all of
you go out there with me tonight.
You didn't
let us do anything.
It was the right
thing to do.
In more ways
than one, Oliver.
It felt good.
It felt right,
like being heroes.
Being a team...
Even if it was
for the last time.
[Computer beeps, door opens]
Computer: Disarmed.
Hey, kiddo, what's up?
I saw what happened
on the news.
Where's dad?
Oh, he just came across
a very unexpected...
completely expected
setback.
But he will be fine.
It's actually... You
I'm worried about.
- I told you...
- that you've been lying to me.
I went to go check your
midterm results online,
and I came across
a very convincing
and very fake version
of your school's website.
Felicity...
and I didn't come across
any test results
because you didn't
take the exams.
Why?
Because I got
expelled.
[Footsteps approaching]
What's this?
My resignation.
I won't captain a department
that arrests my friends.
I made you captain because I believe in you,
Dinah.
And yesterday I learned you've
been lying to me all along.
Oh, it's a party.
To what do I owe
the pleasure, Mr. Queen?
After speaking with my family,
I'm here to turn myself in.
If you're gonna send
my friends to prison,
you're gonna have to
send me, too.
That's funny because
captain Drake
just stopped by
to offer her resignation.
Your team really
sticks together, huh?
Yes, we do.
I had no idea you
were one of them.
Black canary, huh?
That's right.
And I suppose because
you saved my life,
it's supposed to
melt my cold heart,
but I wouldn't go
that far, exactly.
Dinah: Well, how
far would you go?
The anti-vigilante law
is still in effect,
but the district attorney's office will
not be pressing charges on your friends.
And tomorrow,
you will issue one of these to each of them.
They'll each be deputized
like Mr. Queen.
So you're changing
your mind?
I am absolutely not.
Like I said,
I believe in you.
I respect results.
And as much as it
pains me to admit it,
we couldn't have made it
through yesterday
without the help
of vigilantes.
Consider this your chance
to prove me right.
Just watch your step,
please, guys.
There's still glass
on the ground.
Cameraman: That was awesome.
What happened here?
Ricardo Diaz and his crew
happened here.
They couldn't stop us.
We're coming back here.
We'll rebuild.
Gonna do it better
this time.
Pedowitz: Sounds like you have
regrets about how you did it before.
Too many to name.
A friend of mine
recently told me
that's why they're
called mistakes.
You learn from them,
move forward...
Be better.
[Turns TV off]
Where did you get that?
I stole it.
Yeah, Mia,
that much I figured,
but wasn't this
documentary banned?
I thought every copy
was destroyed years ago.
Not this one.
It's total
pro-vigilante garbage,
but even garbage
can be useful.
Useful for what?
A break-In?
You know what?
Actually, the less I know
about that, the better.
Trust me, Connor.
You are going to want to come with.
Connor: So you found this place
by watching that documentary?
[Coughs]
Oliver told them not
to reveal the location,
but there's always
clues.
[Coughs]
God. It's dusty down here.
Yeah, well,
that's what happens
when a place sits
empty for a while.
[Rain]
Whoa.
OK, this is actually
pretty amazing.
It almost feels haunted.
It probably is.
Vigilantes were
the death of Star City.
And they got exactly
what they deserved.
Man: Greg, move your head!