Previously, on "Arrow"...
That woman running around
in black leather tonight, that wasn't Sara.
Sure it was.
Who else would it be?
That's why
I'm talking to you.
Who are we running from?
His name
is Ra's al Ghul,
and he's marked me
and my family
for death.
I heard a rumor
you were leaving town.
Happy to say that those rumors
were false.
[Speaking Arabic]
Ra's is going
to come for me,
and he will learn the truth
about Sara.
Then he will come for Thea.
That's why I have
to kill him.
You couldn't before.
This time, I will have you
to train me.
[Groaning]
Dinah Laurel Lance...
Selfish bitch.
You're not a hero.
You're a liar.
A fraud.
And an addict.
[Grunting]
[Groaning and gasping]
Sara...
Sara, please, please.
I'm your sister.
Then why are you trying
to take my place?
♪ Arrow 3x13 ♪
Canaries
Original Air Date on February 11, 2015
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
What the hell
do you think you're doing?
Your job, apparently.
I told you that I didn't
want you out here.
And I told you that
it wasn't your call to make!
Will you think for a second about
what it would do
to your father if something
happened to you?
What you're doing
is selfish.
Fighting for your city
isn't selfish.
It's what a hero would do.
You're not a hero.
Maybe it's best if we stay
out of each other's way.
How did it go out there?
We ran into Laurel.
Again.
Diggle, how could you sign off
on her doing this?
Oliver,
you might not notice,
but she's not exactly
lobbying for anyone's permission.
She has yours.
Well, not at first, but she can definitely
hold her own out there.
You have
a visitor.
Or as I like to call him,
your new BFF.
I see things are still running
smoothly down here.
What do you want?
[Sighs] It's been weeks
since your return.
I thought it
past time we spoke.
Nanda Parbat is remote,
but I wouldn't delude
yourself into thinking
that Ra's al Ghul missed
your televised return
to Starling City.
Your point, Malcolm?
We can't merely wait
for Ra's to mobilize
his forces.
It's time to bring Thea
into the fold.
She's not ready
to know my secret.
I disagree.
But in any case,
if we have to protect Thea
and to defeat the League,
the three of us need
to join forces.
But I don't see
how we can do that
if she is still to believe
that her brother
is a reformed playboy
and failed businessman.
John: Oliver,
I told you before,
if Thea finds out you've been lying
to her all this time,
you will lose
her...forever.
Oliver:
How's Tatsu?
She'll be better
when we're far away from here.
Your bow. If you
want anything else,
take it quickly.
We're leaving in five minutes.
We're not
coming back.
Oh, we can't just run.
Waller knows I tried
to steal the virus
to get Tatsu back.
Even if she didn't,
Chen Na Wei knows
where we live.
We have to go.
Look, Maseo, we--
You stay, Waller will
torture you to find us.
Contact your family,
contact the press.
Once the world knows
Oliver Queen is still alive,
it will limit
A.R.G.U.S.'s options,
make it more difficult
for Waller to assassinate you.
Well, that's
reassuring.
What are you
going to do?
I'm going to take
Akio and Tatsu
on the ferry to Shanghai.
And from there,
we will disappear.
You saved us.
Now save yourself.
[Reporters
all talking at once]
Reaction to sentencing,
Mr. Zytle?
The Roman governor
Porcius Festus maintained
that the accused
has the right to face
their accuser.
Now, where is my accuser?
I speak, of course,
of the Arrow.
Excuse me, Mr. Zytle
has no further comments.
Ada Laurel Lance.
Take him to the van. Thank you.
[Growling]
Stay back!
[All screaming]
Alderman, stay back!
[Gasps] Where's Zytle?
Hey.
So you still
haven't told me--
what did you think
of my set last night?
Because fangirls on Vine
called it "epically epic."
More like epically
profitable.
It's kind of hot when
you talk business in numbers.
Chase. God, if you
ever really want to kiss me again,
you're going to have to work
on your game.
Later, Princess.
Ollie.
Hey, Speedy.
I'm so happy you're home.
What?
I have to show you
something.
Where are we going?
Basement.
I...thought that
you said that it was flooded.
I lied.
Ollie...
[Scoffs] What's going on?
You're kind of--
kind of making me nervous.
I know that this isn't
going to mean much.
I've given you no reason
to believe me when I say it.
But I lied all of this time
to protect you.
You're...
You're him.
Yeah.
That night with
the--the hoods, and...
that woman in black, that...
Was Ra's al Ghul's
daughter.
That was you.
All those times
I got so mad at you
for being...a flake,
or telling me
something I knew
that had to be a lie.
You were saving
someone's life.
[Sighs] Thank you.
Thank you, Ollie.
Thank you.
You know how many
times I've wished
that I could thank the Arrow
for things he's done for the city?
Probably as many times as I've wished
we could have this conversation.
Did mom know?
The night that she died,
she told me that...
she'd known for a while.
I was worried that
you'd be angry.
Only 'cause
you broke my window.
Although I did
kind of kick your ass.
You didn't.
But you did have
a good teacher.
You were looking for
Malcolm that night.
We know about each other.
Wait, Malcolm knows that
you're the Arrow?
I am amazed that
he didn't tell you.
Then why did you...
tell me?
Why now?
[Door opens]
Because Ra's al Ghul
is coming for us.
All of us.
And the only chance
that we have to survive
is to work together.
To trust each other.
He's right.
No.
No, no, he's not.
I turned my back
on everyone I know,
including
my own brother,
because you told me
there was nobody else I could trust.
I was only trying
to protect you.
Yeah, by driving a wedge
between me and Ollie?
You manipulated me.
Thea...
Let her go.
[Cell phone vibrating]
Yeah?
[Line ringing]
Moira, on answering machine:
You've reached Moira Queen.
Please leave a message.
[Beep]
Mom, it's me.
I'm alive.
I'm, uh, I'm in Hong Kong.
I know it sounds crazy,
but I'm alive,
I'm in Hong Kong,
and I need your help.
I want you
to call Ned Foster,
you tell him to issue
a press release.
Tell everyone.
And you tell Thea.
I'm coming home.
I love you--
[groaning]
What do we know?
Apparently the federal marshal
guarding Werner Zytle
just started shooting
while Zytle waltzed off in the panic.
This is my favorite part.
Roy: That's
pretty convenient.
Guy decides to wig out,
and Zytle takes advantage.
It's not convenient,
it's planned.
Those are the affects
of his vertigo.
Zytle was in a full set
of restraints.
How did he even manage
to dose a federal agent?
He didn't. One of
the reporters did.
What's wrong?
Was my form off?
She's right.
About the reporter.
We need a name--
a name and address
on our clumsy reporter.
I'm on it.
What do you think
you're doing?
I'm coming with you.
No, you're not.
I just gave you
your only lead!
Can I talk to you
for a second? Alone?
I know what
you're going to say,
but I risked my life
for this city while you were gone.
That should
earn me some respect.
This isn't
about respect,
and it's not about you
risking your life.
I understand
that you miss Sara.
And I understand that when you go
out there like this,
all of that pain
goes away.
It's the only time
it ever does.
And that relief
isn't real.
It's a drug.
If you're implying...
You are an addict.
And just like with
booze and pills,
that high that you're chasing
every night
is endangering
your life.
Go to hell, Oliver.
You don't get to play
that card with me.
Ever.
And if there is anyone
who is using adrenaline
to hide the pain of real
feelings and real life,
it's you.
Oliver, Felicity
tracked down
the reporter's work address.
Anthony Walker!
Where's Werner Zytle?
He's not--he's not here.
You helped him
escape today!
Zytle,
he threatened my wife.
Said he could get to her,
that he'd kill her
if I didn't do this, then--
Do what?
Kill you.
I'm so sorry.
Anthony...
Give me the detonator.
He'll kill my wife.
We can protect her.
I promise.
Now hand me
the detonator.
God forgive me.
I will weep for thee.
[Cell phone vibrating]
Thea: Ollie?
I'm sorry,
did I wake you?
Can't sleep.
Apparently insomnia
is a common
side effect
of finding out
your brother is a vigilante.
[Oliver chuckles]
You smell
like smoke.
Korean barbecue?
C4. Yeah.
It's nice that we
can tell each other this stuff now.
It is, actually.
You always had
the lamest excuses.
Lame excuses are sort of an
occupational hazard.
What was tonight's hazard?
Roy and I were
looking for the man
that escaped from the courthouse
earlier today.
Found a bomb
instead.
Yeah, I don't know
how you do it.
Just risk your life out there
for people every night.
It's my job.
It is my job
to keep the people
of this city safe.
And that includes
you, too, Speedy.
Listen to me.
I'm always going to hate
Malcolm Merlyn.
But right now, he is
a necessary evil.
We can take care
of ourselves--
Not against
Ra's al Ghul.
You have to trust me
on this.
I do.
But I don't trust him.
I can't.
And I won't.
[Oliver groaning]
[Gasping]
Amanda: Ten minutes.
I'm impressed.
I know special forces
who can't last longer than three.
Eventually, though,
everybody breaks.
[Coughing]
Tell me where the Yamashiros
are, and it will stop.
My family's going
to be looking for me.
Everyone is going
to be looking for me!
Because your mother
issued a press release?
We erased your message
before she could hear a word of it.
Be glad.
If she had heard it, your mother
would be dead right now.
You would never risk
the exposure.
Hmm, you're right.
Your mother's
too public a figure.
But your sister,
on the other hand.
What's her name? Thea?
Did you know she's
developed something
of a substance abuse problem
since you've been gone?
I guess the strain
of losing two family members
must have been too much
for her to bear.
One day, someone may just find her
in the back of a car,
dead with a needle
in her arm.
Poor Speedy.
You stay away
from my sister.
I will, if you answer
one question.
Where are the Yamashiros?
The ferry to Shanghai.
[Knock on door]
Knock knock.
Hey.
You know, half
the department
is still talking about
the way you clocked that marshal.
[Chuckles] Those boxing lessons
look like they're paying off.
Yeah, I guess so.
Uh, are those the cargo manifests
for the whole city?
Yeah, yeah.
Although, you know, I got to ask, what
do you need these for?
Just a RICO case that
I'm second chairing.
Right.
Dad?
Yeah, sorry.
I just...[Sighs]
Have you heard
from Sara lately?
No. Why?
I ran into her
a few weeks back.
And something just felt
a little...off.
Then I ran into
that friend of hers.
You know, the one
with the, uh, the boy hair?
Sin.
Yeah, Sin, that's it.
She said something strange.
She said that the woman
in black isn't Sara.
That doesn't
make any sense.
No.
I mean, look, I just
want to talk to her,
you know, Sara or not.
But look, don't worry,
I said I'd start taking it easy,
I meant it.
I'll get out of your hair.
Now I've been
wondering,
how do you decide between
the red hoodie
and the one
with the mask?
I'm glad you know.
I feel pretty lame
for not recognizing
my own brother
just because he's
wearing a hood.
I can't believe you
knew before I did.
He saved my life, Thea.
He saved a lot of
people's lives.
He thinks we need
Merlyn's help.
Hmm.
And what do you think?
I think I want
to get as far away
from Malcolm Merlyn
as I possibly can.
Well, there's your answer
right there.
Hey.
Sorry.
May I borrow him
for a second?
[Scoffs] Apparently,
he's been more yours
than mine lately, so...
What happened?
One of our trackers sent a signal from
the Starling City docks.
Except we don't have
any tracking devices in the field.
Unless we do.
It's Laurel.
You tagged Laurel
with a tracer?
If she's going to be reckless,
I need to know what she's doing.
Well, she's definitely
doing something.
I'm just not exactly sure how
reckless it is.
I ran the manifests on all these shipping
containers that you see here.
One of these leads back
to Zytle's old supplier.
Looks like Vertigo's
back in business.
[Sighs] She's going
to get herself killed.
Suit up.
Hey!
Werner: Wonderful
seeing you again.
Ooh, I fancy
the new outfit.
[Groaning]
[Gasping]
Feeling
my Vertigo, dear.
Wonderful.
Dinah Laurel Lance.
[Grunts]
Selfish bitch.
You're not a hero.
You're a liar.
A fraud.
And an addict.
Sara...
Sara, please, please.
I'm your sister.
Then why are you trying
to take my place?
Oliver: Get away from her!
You should be dead!
I salute
your persistence!
[All grunting]
Laurel: Help me!
Help!
Help me, please.
Need an IV.
Watch her.
You're going to be ok.
It's going to be ok.
Why did I have to die?
Sara?
If you wanted to be me,
you could have.
I didn't have to die.
I am so sorry!
Sara! I am so--
[Gasps]
Thea: Ollie?
I'm--I'm sorry,
I just wanted to talk.
You need to go
back upstairs.
Now!
Hey!
Don't talk to her like that.
You brought her in;
you don't have the right
to kick her out.
I'm not.
I'm protecting her.
By telling her what to do?
Work with Malcolm Merlyn,
let him get his hooks deeper--
Enough.
She's my sister.
She makes her own
choices, Oliver!
It's ok. I--
we can talk later.
I just--just,
is Laurel ok?
Is she a part
of this, too?
She's going to be fine.
I promise. Just...
Please go back upstairs.
What the hell
was that?
You think you're the only person who
can stand up to Thea?
I'm trying to figure
out why you're standing up to me!
All right, maybe we just
need to throttle back.
No. We need this.
Oliver, you were gone.
Dead. At least
we thought you were,
and we had to go on
with our lives.
And doing that meant
not doing things your way.
Fine! I'm back now.
That doesn't mean
that we can go back.
And you do not have
the right to come back here
and question
everyone's choices.
Just let me know if there's
any change in her condition.
Hey, how's it going?
[Thea sighs]
What's that for?
My life has been
really complicated lately,
so I--I just need
something simple.
So...
This seat taken?
It's a free country.
Apparently.
The first time that
we went after Zytle,
I told you that
this was my crusade.
Doesn't seem to be
the case anymore.
You're right. It isn't.
Diggle, I get that
I was gone for--
No, you weren't gone--
you were dead.
And all of us, including me,
we were ready to hang it up.
Why didn't you?
Because I realized
we weren't just fighting for you;
we were fighting
for ourselves, too.
And that includes Roy.
And, yes,
that includes Laurel.
[Sighs]
She's not a soldier.
Neither were you.
That's not the same thing,
and you know that.
[Exhales]
What I know, Oliver,
is that you started something.
Something strong enough
to live on past you.
The question is,
can you live
with what it's become?
[Footsteps on stairs]
Oliver.
Are you all right?
I told them
you were on the ferry.
I'm sorry.
They tortured you.
I sold you out.
No, you didn't.
Because we were
never going to Shanghai.
I lied.
A precaution just in case
you were captured.
Then how'd they find you?
They didn't.
When I found out you'd been taken,
I came back.
You're an idiot.
Maybe.
But I will not let you face Waller
alone for my actions.
So now we're both going
to get tortured, or worse.
Great plan.
I must speak
with Agent Waller.
Hey! Why did you--
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, hey.
Hey, hey.
Hey.
How are you feeling?
When Zytle hit me
with Vertigo, I--
I saw Sara.
She was alive.
And she was
calling me a fraud.
I was crazy to think
that I was fit
to wear Sara's jacket.
Much less follow
in her footsteps.
You're right.
I hope I'm not
out of line here,
but...
I think Sara wore her mask
just as much to hide her demons
as she did to help people.
And I don't see that with you.
You have a light
inside of you
that Sara never had.
So...
Maybe you should
stop trying to be Sara...
and just be yourself.
Thank you.
[Beeping]
What's that?
One of the chemical drums
Zytle stole tonight
just sent out a GPS signal.
Why?
'Cause he just opened it.
Ah. I dig
your place.
I'm sorry I interrupted
the tour.
[Laughs] Pretty sure
you saw everything you needed to.
Mmm.
You want a drink?
Sure.
This was nice.
I almost took it personally
when you said I was simple.
Well, I never said that
you were simple.
What?
Nothing. It...
It's just something
my father once said.
We were sitting in
this little taberna in Corto Maltese,
drinking this
amazing Carménère,
and he said that
for centuries,
noblemen have been
using the rich aroma of red wine
to cover up a very
different scent.
Cyanide.
Tell me who you are and what
he hell you think you're doing here!
Serving my master,
Ra's al Ghul.
[Both grunting]
Please!
Don't struggle. I can do this so
you won't feel a thing.
Get away from her.
If you beg forgiveness
for trying to harm my daughter,
I'll grant you
a quick death.
I'd never give you
the satisfaction, Al Sa-Her.
You're unarmed and you have
nowhere to run.
But there's some place
I can go where you won't dare to follow.
[Groaning]
Daggett Pharmaceuticals.
5th and Kingsley.
Looks like Zytle found
a place to change those chemicals
into some new Vertigo...
And he's got hostages.
Where's Roy?
I can't reach him.
Laurel.
Oliver.
There isn't anything that
you can say to me
that I don't
already know.
Actually, there is.
I must once again
thank you
for letting us use
your laboratory
this evening. And my
sincerest apologies
to your colleague here.
But mistakes will not
be tolerated.
Werner Zytle...
This ends now.
As you wish!
May I suggest
a grand finale--
chlorine triflouride.
Oliver, I'm registering
an enormous spike in thermal activity.
Oliver, the whole place
is going to blow.
You have to get
out of there!
Not yet.
Go! Run! Now!
Please! Help!
Help!
I'm surprised.
Usually women
don't return
for a second go.
Hi, sis.
You're not her.
You're...
You're not real.
Oh, I'm quite real.
[Both grunting]
You lied to me,
Laurel!
Straight to my face,
my own daughter!
Sara was my daughter,
I deserved to know! I had a right!
To grieve, to mourn!
Who do you think you are
to take that away from me?
Huh? Who do you think you are?!
I'm--I'm sorry!
I know you are.
She says she's sorry,
but she'll do it again.
You keep my own
daughter's death a secret
because you think I'm
too weak for the truth?!
You think you can
wear my mask?
You think you can be me?!
No.
And I'm done
trying to be.
[Gasping]
Felicity: Oliver,
are you there?
It's over.
No, it's not.
You have to get home.
It's Thea.
See? All good.
Hey.
Is everything ok?
Oh, yeah, just the usual
insurance policy
search and seizure.
Seems like
I'm a high risk case.
I wonder what
gave them that idea.
What's a matter? You ok?
Um...
There's, um...
There's something
that I have to tell you.
And I didn't tell you--
I didn't tell you
before, because I was
worried about
your health.
But...I realize that--
that you
deserve to know.
I already know it.
Sara's off God knows where,
and yet there's another blonde
in a mask running around
tuning up the bad guys,
and it's you, isn't it?
Sweetheart, come on.
It's all right. It's ok.
It's ok, honey.
I mean, look, I am
pissed as hell.
But, you know, we'll figure it out.
We figure out everything.
No. No, no,
daddy, that--
[crying]
That isn't what
I was going to tell you.
What I was going
to tell you
is about Sara.
No.
Dad...
Daddy, I'm sorry.
Not my baby, not again.
[Both sobbing]
I'm so sorry.
I can't do this.
Oh, God, please.
[Door opens]
Oliver: Thea?
It's ok. You're ok.
I thought that
I was stronger.
I thought that I could
keep myself safe.
Who was he?
Malcolm:
One of Ra's agents.
Roy...
Could you give us a minute?
Really hope you're not
expecting a thank you.
No parent needs gratitude for
saving their child.
I didn't ask
to be a part of this.
I didn't ask for any of this.
[Sighs] Maybe you're right.
Maybe we can't do this
without him.
But I am never going
to forget the things you've done.
Or the person that you are.
Understood.
But before
we can begin,
there's something
that only the two of you can do.
Ra's al Ghul preys
upon the fears of his enemies.
Conquer your own fear,
and you eliminate that
critical advantage.
For you, there is
only one place
on earth uniquely
suited to doing that.
So you're leaving again?
She's got a point, man.
You just got back.
It's just
for a few days.
Ordinarily,
I wouldn't do this.
But it's for Thea.
And if you've
shown me anything,
it's that the city
is more than safe in your hands.
All of your hands.
Thank you.
Ollie told you we're heading
out for a bit?
You cool with it all?
[Exhales]
After the whole chase thing,
I think it's going
to be a little while
before I'm cool
with anything.
[Chuckles]
What was that for?
Take your pick.
Saving my life,
or standing up to Oliver
about Malcolm.
I should get going.
[Exhales]
Oliver: Come on, Speedy,
we have four more miles
to make
before night fall.
Ah, God.
I get that Malcolm
wants to whip us into shape
so we can face the League,
but don't you think
it's a little bit excessive?
We've been here for two hours.
Are you complaining already?
I--I started thinking it
after the first ten minutes.
Well, give it time.
Eventually this place
will feel like home.
It does not look like home.
It was for me.
For other people,
this is Purgatory.
You're not dead,
if that's what you're wondering.
Once again, you have
the good fortune
of being uniquely
qualified to help me.
Me? Why?
Chen Na Wei has left Hong Kong.
We've tracked here here.
Here? Where are we--
Welcome home, Mr. Queen.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man