[Oliver] Previously onArrow...
The prosecution's smoking gun
is a witness who is willing to testify
that you are the Green Arrow.
It's someone on the team.
Dinah isn't the witness, Oliver, it's me.
You're off the team.
It's been real, y'all.
I'm out, too.
I'm done.
So we've got 'em fighting with each other
instead of fighting us.
This is only the beginning.
Mr. Bertinelli, I think you're gonna
like these numbers.
We need a name
for the Panam-X that's, uh, coming in.
Christening ships does make it seem
more legit if the IRS checks in.
How about The Huntress? After my cousin.
Very good.
Thank you, sir.
[door opens and closes]
Who the hell are you?
Someone important.
Real important.
You don't look it.
How'd you get past my men?
I blew them a kiss.
Jerry Bertinelli
of the eponymous crime family
and the last of his kind.
The rest of your family is either
dead or incarcerated.
You... You writing a book?
I have heard
that sometimes ships appear
on your docking manifest,
but never actually arrive.
Sometimes ships arrive
and never end up on the docking manifest.
Well, it's, uh, very profound.
If the price is right, maybe,
maybe we can facilitate a few things.
No, I'm afraid you misunderstand.
We want to buy you out.
I got a feeling you're not hearing me.
Port's not for sale.
Take a walk.
Oh, it sounds to me like
you want a kiss, too.
[Jerry chuckles]
[grunts]
[Jerry groaning]
You have 48 hours
to consider our proposal.
[groaning]
Don't you have a daughter
attending Columbia University?
I've always wanted to visit New York.
[footsteps approaching]
Hey, you.
Looks like you need this.
Oh, John Diggle, the savior of souls
and bringer of java.
-Thank you.
-I have been called.
I guess I have to find ways to be useful.
[breathes deeply]
You're working overtime
trying to find Cayden James,
and I'm still on the disabled list.
Well, not for long. Curtis is on his
way over and we will fix you.
We have the technology.
Ah, I'm not the Six Million Dollar Man.
Not yet, you're not.
And more like $2.24 million man,
because Curtis and I
are stretching pennies
-with Helix Dynamics as it is.
-[cell phone beeping]
Oh, speak of the devil,
that little psychic.
Oh. He's early. He'll be here soon.
-Who's early?
-[John] Curtis.
Shouldn't you be getting home?
Raisa must be making quadruple
overtime by now.
Raisa is doing just fine.
I mean, William loves her.
-William doesn't know you're here.
-I know.
And I don't like it, but...
We need to find Cayden James.
Are we making any progress on that front?
Despite my 21st consecutive
all-nighter, no.
He's either the first bad guy to ghost us,
or he's just biding time.
-Black Siren.
-Another strikeout.
I can't track her cry and Cayden must
have inserted some sort of Trojan
into the software, it's confusing
our facial recognition algorithms.
I cannot find her.
All right, we will continue
with the low-tech option.
I will go out up there again tonight.
Yeah, and every time you do,
you're playing Russian roulette,
considering you're being followed and all.
And the Anti-Vigilante Law.
I'm not worried. You should not be either.
The three of us,
we will solve this problem together.
Like your haircut. [chuckles] It's nice.
I didn't get a haircut. Curtis, it's fine.
I'm really appreciative
that you're helping John.
No hard feelings?
No.
That wasn't super awkward. [chuckles]
Ooh. Let's get to work.
-[knock at door]
-Yep?
-Hi.
-[chuckles] Hey, look who it is.
Ah, to what do I owe the pleasure?
Sit down.
Uh, well...
I heard you needed a new assistant.
Yeah.
Developed some trust issues
with the last one.
Yeah, Ollie told me you fired him.
Yeah, about that.
He also mentioned
that you wanted to, what?
Err on the side of forgiveness?
Yeah, I mean, look,
you know everyone makes mistakes.
And I totally get
why you did what you did.
But I just feel like
it might come across bad for optics.
It might look like you're retaliating
against a whistle-blower.
Yeah, I hear what you're saying.
But, Thea,
Oliver shouldn't have to work
shoulder to shoulder
with a guy who's testifying against him.
Doesn't mean you're not still down
an assistant.
Yeah. Well, actually, I hired
a replacement this morning.
Oh.
What I could really use
is a chief of staff.
-[beeping]
-[John sighs]
Almost there.
Just slipping past the radiocarpal.
Yeah.
Boom!
-Chip implanted.
-That's it?
-Seems simple.
-Yeah, for you,
I mean, making the chip.
That was the hard... [echoing]
What was that?
Some kind of electro-magnetic
frequency interference.
-From the chip?
-No, I doubt it, but...
[sighs] It's probably nothing.
All right, the moment of truth.
Can you make a fist without a tremor?
Round Two. El busto.
Why don't you just
stop pouring money into this? Into me.
You let us worry about the money,
okay? We're going to do this.
I can tinker with the design
some more when I get home.
-Or you could do it here.
-[scoffs]
Hard pass. After this morning's
awkwardness, I am good.
-See you, guys.
-See you.
Please tell me you can get Halo
on that thing.
If I have to go one more week
without shooting a bad guy,
I'm gonna bust.
Funny. I always pictured you
like a more Call of Duty...[echoing]
[sighs]
[echoing] What?
[cell phone chimes]
[Dinah Drake] Anastas.
Who collared this guy?
We've had a warrant on him for weeks.
Nobody. He just up and turned
himself in five minutes ago.
-Turned himself...
-It's crazy. Fifth one this week.
All of a sudden these bad guys
grew a conscience.
Did you like my presents?
-What are you doing here?
-Seeing you.
You know, anybody in this office
could arrest you.
-Hell, I could arrest you.
-For what?
I'm a Central City police officer.
The only rap on me
is that I'm presumed dead.
Then again, I was an undercover,
so that death is probably bogus.
The Vigilante put the fear of God
in these guys.
At least the Vigilante isn't killing them.
Most guys just send flowers.
How about a stroll by the pier instead?
Tomorrow, after your shift ends?
Sure.
Okay.
[device beeping]
Clear.
-What's going on?
-We've been compromised.
Curtis brought down some equipment
into the bunker for John's implant.
We got massive signal interference.
-We got lucky.
-Three months ago,
when Laurel infiltrated the bunker.
She stole one of Curtis' T-Spheres.
James had it on him
back at Starling Stadium.
We were so focused
on what she could have taken.
We never thought about
what she could've left behind.
-Like a bug.
-Exactly.
Then she's been watching us for months.
I put it on loop, okay?
Audio and visual of the bunker.
-He doesn't know that we know.
-All right.
[John] I spoke with Lyla.
She says we can use
A.R.G.U.S. for the time being.
-That's smart.
-No, smart is Cayden James
being one step ahead of us
from the very jump, Oliver.
I hate to belabor
the depressingly obvious,
but secret identities? No longer secret.
[cell phone chiming]
The block between 74th and Jansen
just lost their security signal uplink.
-That doesn't just happen on its own.
-Cayden James?
I'm on it.
Hey, hey, hey. Stand down.
I just needed to get your attention.
You're a hard man to find.
Have you ever considered a website?
Or maybe a spotlight in the sky,
big silhouette of an arrow?
What do you want?
-You know who I am?
-Jerry Bertinelli.
-You're in the Bertinelli Syndicate.
-I am the Bertinelli Syndicate.
At least, what's left of it.
And I can't go down without a fight.
In five seconds,
you're gonna be in a fight.
Just hear me out. Look, I...
I never actually
wanted to get in this life.
I know,
but we do certain things for family.
Am I right?
Now, the ports, these docks,
it's all we got left.
And last night, these people came over,
threatened to take it from me.
You know, some dweeb in glasses, a thug,
a woman with super powers.
-And you know them?
-Maybe.
Yeah, no, I figured you might.
They're looking to control the docks.
So talk to your cousin.
She's been underground. So I'm asking you.
Do you really think
that I'm gonna help you win a turf war?
Well, I think you're
the enemy of my enemy.
Which makes us allies.
We need to know what's on this.
Hi, Felicity, how are you?
Are you busy with anything?
Can you help me with something?
You look tired.
-Hi.
Jerry Bertinelli gave that to me.
The port is the only thing
the Bertinelli family has left.
Cayden James and Black Siren
are trying to take it from them.
So we're getting into bed
with the Bertinellis now?
I remember last time you got in bed
with one of the Bertinellis.
It did not work out well.
I have a long memory for
these sorts of things, call me crazy.
Two nights ago they paid him a visit.
This is the security footage.
They made a threat against his daughter.
Well, what's on here
might help us locate them.
That's the plan.
Well, we'll know about the license plate.
Old school. I like it.
A little bit of old school
combined with some new school,
and I'm about to find us
this Cayden James needle
in the Star City haystack.
Do it.
I mean, I was thinking after school
we could hit up the zoo.
They have this new reptile room
with a Komodo dragon.
Thing's so big, it could eat a cow.
-That's dope, right?
-I guess so.
What's up, sweets?
I thought you were all about
this animal stuff.
I am, but...
Why aren't you going to work today?
I'm going through
a little transitional period.
-Will I have to leave again?
-Hey...
No one will ever take you away from me.
Ever again.
[knock at door]
-What's up, dawg?
I brought crogurts.
-"Crogurts"?
-I didn't name them. I just eat them.
-Hey, Zoe.
-Hi, Curtis.
Hey, go get your bag.
We're about to leave.
Must be great having her back, huh?
Best feeling in the world.
You don't look like you're feeling
the best feeling in the world though.
I can't shake how everything
went down with Oliver.
In order to do right for me,
I had to betray him.
You had to put your daughter first.
She's family.
Is that why you called me over?
Actually, I was thinking...
All the evidence Agent Watson said
she has against me
has to be digitized, right?
-Yeah.
-So what if
that evidence suddenly vanished?
Then I'll be able to... [sighs]
What do you call it? Um...
-Recant.
-You put your family first, Rene.
That's nothing to be ashamed of about.
I mean, now, accessing the files
might be a little easier
now that the case has been moved back
to the Star City DA, but...
So, that's a yes...
No, that's a "Let me think about it."
Fine, yeah, I'll do it.
We all know I'll do it.
Awesome.
That's what I'm talking about, hoss.
[laughing] That was
the worst stakeout of my life.
Do you remember, it was like, what?
Minus one?
It was freezing. I was freezing my ass off
and the car's heater broke down.
-I warned you about that.
-Yeah, you did and I didn't listen.
I think there's a life lesson
in there somewhere.
Oh...
I think I drank a gallon of coffee
that night to stay warm.
I had to pee so...
I never had to pee so bad in my life.
And I had to go back behind the car.
So you know, I mean,
I wasn't gonna ask the scumbag
if I could use his bathroom.
Oh, God, and the second I go back there,
he decides to make a run for it.
That son of a bitch.
I had to go chasing after him,
fall face-first into the snow bank
[chuckling]
and knock myself out on the curb.
This is complicated. I know.
I'm used to complicated.
This is a whole new level.
It doesn't have to be.
I stopped being the Black Canary
five weeks ago.
I really want to uncomplicate
my life right now.
Just so long you don't forget to live it.
[cell phone chiming]
[sighs]
Sorry.
Text from an informant.
My next target's on the move.
Don't worry.
I'm not gonna kill him.
Well, just make sure you bring him in
when I'm off duty.
Okay? Because all this intake
is giving me carpal tunnel.
[Thea] Pen?
I can always count on you.
So, Quentin told me the good news.
-You're back with us?
-Yes, I am.
And you're happy about that?
Well, I'm just sorry that I can't be
of more help to you
and the team, or lack thereof.
It's fine.
I just know you need
the manpower right now,
and I'm not just there...
Thea,
you will always be my Speedy
whether you're using
a bow and arrow or not.
[cell phone vibrating]
[clears throat]
Yeah.
-Found him.
-Where?
His vehicle is parked outside
a warehouse in Adams Heights.
-Looks like he's alone.
-And he doesn't know that we know.
-Okay, talk me in.
-Oliver,
if you do that, you'll be going in solo.
Let us stake the place out, do some recon.
We have the chance
to take him by surprise.
We can't pass it up.
-Hey, Ollie.
-Yeah?
Go get him.
[grunting]
[beeps]
Overwatch, I'm in the east sector.
Where to?
Okay, you're coming up on the main floor.
Same three heat sigs have been
there for a while now.
Good odds that's our target.
[Cayden] I'm sensing some impatience,
Miss Lance.
Would you care to elucidate?
I'm not impatient. I'm annoyed.
We have the numbers.
Why not just take the pier
from the Bertinellis?
Oh, no.
-Not impatient at all.
-[Cayden] Mr. Sheck.
No need to stir the pot.
I think you'll find that brute force,
while it's easy,
is exceedingly messy.
I prefer precision.
Design over chaos.
[grunts]
[choking]
[beeps]
You've taught yourself some new tricks.
No more games.
Overwatch, I have the target.
That's a whole lot of bad news.
Arrow, you're about to get company.
-[feedback ringing]
-Oliver?
Overwatch, do you copy?
I'm afraid Miss Smoak can't hear you.
You see, I also have some tricks,
Mr. Queen.
And I have friends.
Hello, Kapiushon.
How were your holidays?
[Diaz] Funny you should mention that.
[Black Siren coughs]
Looks like we're getting
a late Christmas present.
I only targeted criminals.
I thought you'd know vigilantes
are criminals, Mr. Mayor.
[Cayden] You'll find that I don't play
games, Mr. Queen.
-But I do win.
-It's enough.
I am so sick of everyone not killing him
when they get the chance.
[gun firing]
Let him go.
You know, for a smart guy,
that was a dumb move.
There's a time and a place
for Oliver Queen's demise.
Now is not it.
So Cayden James not only has Laurel,
but he's backed by two
different criminal organizations.
And a deranged killer that we haven't
-been able to put down for two years.
-[sighs] Oliver.
If Cayden James has his own posse men,
maybe we need to think about
evening the playing field.
We're not folding
Curtis, Rene and Dinah back in.
I don't trust they won't compromise us.
Cayden James told you that
he wants to watch the city burn.
This is no time for ego, man.
This is not ego.
John, you more than anyone know
you don't go into the field
with people you can't rely on.
[Felicity] Okay, then,
how about not going to the field?
They need to know what's going on.
Dinah deserves
to know the truth about her ex.
I agree.
So we share intel,
but that's it.
Is that a bottle?
[sighs]
[groans]
Worse. Maybe.
[Quentin sighs]
Oh.
A photo album.
Okay, you've definitely
just hit bottom, Quentin.
I think we need to call your sponsor.
Yeah. Maybe he can
talk some sense into me.
Okay, well,
I've been in a coma for six months,
so why don't you fill me in a little?
Um, you know, last month,
when I was held hostage?
You know, she let me go.
What I saw in her
is what I see here.
Look, I mean,
everyone, even Ra's al Ghul,
has had moments of kindness.
Yeah.
Look, I'm not saying
that this Laurel is that bad, but...
I just can't stop thinking
that if I abandon her,
if I write her off as some kind of psycho,
and I know this...
Sounds crazy,
but if there is just some way
to get through to her,
and I don't take it,
it's going to be like
watching her die all over again.
You're like a father to me, you know that?
If you go down this road, Quentin,
you could end up getting killed.
Even if you don't care
what happens to you,
don't forget to think about
your other daughter.
-Hey.
[John] Thanks for agreeing
to meet with us.
Yeah, I'm not really sure I see the point.
We're out of the game.
I don't exactly see Cayden James
respecting those types of boundaries.
Cayden had Laurel plant a camera...
at the bunker.
We're all compromised.
How long have you all known about this?
Twenty-four hours.
You've known we were exposed
like this for a whole day,
you're just telling us now?
Look, we thought our intel was rock solid.
And then we found out
that Laurel wasn't the only one
that he's in league with.
He's working with the Bratva
and Ricardo Diaz.
Just what this city needs.
She's not the only member of his group.
Dinah...
Vincent's working with them, too.
[scoffs]
No, no. [stutters]
That's insane. That's insane.
Vince hunts criminals,
he doesn't throw down with them.
Oliver saw him with James and the rest.
Well, excuse me if, uh, I don't
just take Oliver's word for it.
I mean, keeping us under surveillance,
sounds like he and Cayden James
have a lot in common.
Rene, we did that
for the good of the team.
Oh.
Is that how you sleep at night, John?
We were facing
an actual breach in security.
You guys gave up on Oliver.
You don't get to stay mad at Daddy
because he read your diary
and you get to just skip out on curfew.
That's not the way it works.
I'm getting sick and tired
of you talking to me
like I did what I did on a whim.
I did it for my daughter.
And your choice
put the whole team in jeopardy, Rene.
We think that showed us where you stand.
-Dinah.
-Where are you going, Dinah?
Out. I'm not gonna sit here
and watch you two point fingers
at everybody but yourselves.
[door slams shut]
Move, or get moved, hoodie.
Hey, stand down. He's a friend of mine.
Well, he's an, uh, acquaintance.
Business associate? What do you need?
You going somewhere?
I got a, uh, text sent to me tonight
from inside my daughter's dorm room.
Cayden James, he can have the port.
You're running scared.
I'm gonna run anywhere
for my baby girl, all right?
As long as James and this crew
are out there,
she will never be safe.
Neither will you.
-But?
-But I can stop them.
With your help.
Listen to me, you do what I say,
we can end Cayden James.
-I'm so glad you wanted to meet again.
-[grunts]
Cayden James.
-You don't understand.
-You lying son of a bitch.
You were just getting close to me for him.
Dinah, can we talk about this
somewhere else?
That's a great idea, Vince.
Precinct has a really nice room for you.
Really nice interrogation room.
I can't let you do this.
I should've taken you in
the second you came back into my life.
[grunts]
I'm sorry.
[device beeps]
[John] Charges are in place.
So are mine.
Oliver. You sure about this, man?
Doesn't sound like you are.
[sighs]
If we do this, Cayden James
will bring his whole group here.
And?
And Cayden will bring everyone, Oliver.
I'm no place close to 100%.
But, look, the rest of the team...
-There is no "rest of the team."
-Oliver, we could use their help.
All you have to do is ask.
We would have to trust them and we can't.
We can't. John, we've been over this.
I know. But we've also
been over other things.
Like you in the League of Assassins,
me, with my secret.
Oliver, the best partnerships
are built on forgiveness, man.
No one knows that more than you and me.
I got arrested in front of my son.
Got dragged away in handcuffs
because of something that Rene did.
I don't know how to forgive him.
I tried.
John, more importantly,
what's Cayden James up to?
We don't know.
He has known our identities for months.
He hasn't outed us. Why?
This started with you, with me,
and with Felicity.
Whatever comes our way, we can handle it.
I believe that.
Are you actually eating the old crogurt?
Shut up. Your old is my delicious.
-How's Zoe?
-I don't know.
I just need her to feel like
everything's going back to normal.
I hope it is.
It'll help if you could delete
whatever the DA's got.
We just found out that Cayden James
had the bunker bugged
for a couple of months,
so maybe we should just
take a little break
on saying incriminating things
like that out loud.
All right, all right. I'm sorry.
I'm just anxious is all.
[sighs] I know.
Unfortunately, they have a backup
of all these files,
and, even worse, their records are
saying that they have hard copies.
Damn.
Yeah. No, but I'm inside the system.
I'm just trying to find anything...
-Whoa.
-"Whoa," what?
I think I just found something. Yeah.
There's a record on how Watson
found out you were Wild Dog.
-There's an audio recording.
-You thinking what I'm thinking?
That depends on if you're thinking
that Cayden James leaked an audio file
of you from the bunker to the FBI.
Is that what you're thinking?
That's what you're thinking, right?
-Yeah.
-Okay, we're on the same page.
[door slams shut]
Don't you knock?
Don't you lock your doors?
You look like you were just in a fight.
You were just in a fight.
-With who?
-Vince.
I confronted him. He did this and ran.
I'm so sorry, Dinah.
It was my fault for believing in him
in the first damn place.
And for confronting him,
exposing the fact that we know
about him and Cayden James.
That's my fault, too. It's great.
Curtis and I were just talking about James
and the bunker being compromised.
Yeah, and how that might have
led to Rene being compromised.
You think Cayden provided
Samanda Watson with her case?
-That's the theory.
-A good one, though.
If Cayden had audio and video
on all of us, especially Oliver,
why would he just tee up Rene?
It figures he'd go after
the most handsome and charming.
Well, maybe when Oliver
finally takes down Cayden James,
we'll figure out the details
of his master plan.
Why assume we're gonna wait for Oliver?
What are we gonna do here?
We're gonna sit around and wait
to see how this all plays out?
Hope it plays out, you mean.
You guys are serious about this?
About taking on Cayden James
and his super posse?
I let Vince walk once. I'm not
gonna make that mistake again.
And I owe that son of a bitch
some serious payback.
If I'm reading the room correctly,
we're gonna form our own team, right?
Right.
[Oliver] What's going on?
Signal chatter from Bertinelli's laptop.
They're bringing in the Red Lions.
Ah. The Red Lions. Chechnyan death squad.
Bertinelli's not gonna
let the port go without a fight.
Well, I'm thinking the enemy
of Cayden James
is my favorite death squad.
The Red Lions liberated a town
in Kizlyar last year.
Turned it into a wasteland.
We cannot let James' group
go up against these guys.
The collateral damage
will destroy the port.
Where are Bertinelli
and the Red Lions holed up?
Storage facility on 5th and Brockton.
[rewinding]
We can take the port
without Bertinelli's say,
but there are
a lot of players in this city.
I think you should set a precedent
for when you're in charge.
I'm already in charge, Miss Lance.
Even more reason
to use his corpse as a message.
I concur.
Mr. Bertinelli has his army.
He should meet ours.
-You think Bertinelli's gonna show?
-He better.
He will.
[Jerry] Let's get this over with.
If Keyhole satellite imagery
is anything to go off of,
it looks like Cayden James took the bait.
Whoa!
Go, go!
Funny thing.
You guys don't look like
a Chechnyan death squad!
[grunts]
We have a Ricardo Diaz in the house,
but no Cayden James.
[Green Arrow] I'll take it.
[men groaning]
[grunting]
[screeching]
Oh, no. We have a very large problem.
Oliver, get out of there.
Send in the cavalry.
So, how does this compare to Halo?
So much better.
[grunts]
Stand down, Oliver.
You're are vastly outnumbered.
[grunting]
-[gunshot]
-Damn it.
[both grunting]
That's it. Let's get the hell out
of this freak show.
[silenced gunshots]
All right. All right.
Don't leave early.
The best parts are always at the end.
[grunting]
I'm disappointed, Mr. Bertinelli.
I truly am.
But not unreasonable.
This can go one of two ways
for you and your men.
The choice is yours.
[Oliver grunts]
Forgive me, kid.
[beeping]
[explosion]
Mr. Bertinelli...
It's fine. Relax, all right?
Just take the freaking port.
Thank you.
Although you elected
to betray me this evening,
you ultimately made the right choice.
[gunfire]
Which is why
I won't have your daughter killed.
I expect you can find the most
effective use for this corpse
to... How did you put it?
"Send a message."
Aren't you happy to be back
in your newly debugged
crime-fighting lair?
Cayden James got away.
Everybody got away. [clears throat]
Did you ever see that movie
-Bull Durham?
-Hmm?
My mom made me
watch that movie all the time.
I mean, it is the best
baseball movie ever,
but she used to say
that Susan Sarandon
was her fictional life coach.
There's a line in this movie
where she says,
"Sometimes you win, sometimes you lose,
and sometimes it rains."
You can't control the weather.
You couldn't control
Bertinelli betraying you.
You know what else I can't control?
Their numbers advantage.
I can't be out there solo
against that group.
It's not the smart move.
I won't make that mistake again.
I just want to say that, I, for one,
think it's great that we're all
back in the same room together.
Trust and forgiveness.
For the past few weeks,
I have been really struggling
to square that circle.
I think all of us have.
Rene, as a father, I understand
why you did what you did.
I also recognize that you might be
taking me away from my son.
I reacted to that and I got angry.
The three of us decided
to put the three of you
under surveillance.
I take responsibility for that.
It was, without question...
It was a breach of trust.
So was lying to the team about Vince.
And I'm not trying
to point fingers, Dinah,
I am simply trying to illustrate
that there is blame on all sides here.
But we don't have time for grudges
or recriminations. We don't.
Not with what the city is up against.
So? What do you guys think?
Clean slate?
Clean slate.
Things just go back
to the way they were before?
Yeah.
I don't think I can do that.
Not after what the three of you did.
This city needs us.
And we know that, and we're not
shirking that responsibility.
We decided to go our own way.
-Wait a minute.
-No, no. Let's...
No, no, no.
This is what Cayden James wants.
Cayden didn't do this, Felicity.
He didn't create
an environment of distrust.
A team where some members of that team
were treated differently than others.
Cayden James didn't demand allegiance
and then play by his own set of rules.
I came because I want
to be a part of a real team.
Point taken.
I'd like to
wish the three of you good luck.
And I mean that sincerely,
with Cayden, with Anatoly, Diaz,
Black Siren, Vigilante,
these people are dangerous.
So, whatever you have planned,
whatever your move is,
good luck.
Let's go, guys.
[sighs]
I may have solved the glitch in my chip.
I hope it helps.
I, um, really do.
[door closes]
What the...
I hope you don't mind.
Found these in my personal collection
and thought that we could add them
to your album.
Oh, thank you very much.
-It's my apology.
-For what?
You were right.
Look, Malcolm was every bit
as bad as this Laurel is right now,
and...
then in the end, he wasn't.
He changed.
And Laurel can, too.
I had no right
to tell you that she couldn't.
Right.
How the hell am I gonna do that?
Well, I can help.
And... I don't know. Maybe together,
we can find a way to break through to her.
Yeah.
[exhales]
When you said
you had something to show us,
didn't you think lights would be useful?
One second, guys.
It is all about the reveal.
What does it look like?
Some place.
[Curtis] No, it's our new lair. [chuckles]
Helix used to operate out of here,
but it's not like
they're using it anymore, so.
Curtis, it's genius.
Seriously, nice work.
I'm glad you guys like it.
Now, I don't suggest
we make this a regular thing,
seeing as how I'm a lightweight and all,
but this event warrants celebration.
Well, I am just glad that
I've found partners who I can trust.
That's what I'm talking about.
I'm concerned.
And the feeling doesn't suit me well.
You got the port like you wanted.
Sorry if I was unclear.
My concern relates to you.
Your continued association
with Miss Drake wouldn't worry me
if this surveillance
didn't suggest that she knows
about our association.
Don't worry.
I can handle Dinah.
There's not a button she has
I don't know how to push.
[Felicity] All right.
The new chip is in.
Just one second.
[sighing]
It doesn't feel any different.
It takes a minute.
[gasps]
Or not.
It worked?
Looks like we're not
as undermanned as we thought.
Yes.