Previously on Arrow...
Roy! Roy!
Roy, stop it!
[Clang]
Dinah: They're dead.
Oliver: We have to
protect him.
Dinah: Yeah. As far
as the SCPD is concerned,
Emiko is the one who
killed those guards.
Thank you for wiping that
security camera footage.
I could not get there
before the cops did.
I thought that was you.
Felicity: The Ninth Circle
has Archer.
They are going to use the
intel they get from the assets
to locate the DNA of the
people involved in Cygnus X-1.
And that DNA could lead them to
exactly where that weapon is.
I copied Archer's
root code.
No. As long as
Archer's out there,
it could fall into the wrong hands,
and I don't know what
my legacy's gonna be,
but it can't be that.
Emiko:
You'll die a villain just like our father,
and I will be the cause
of both of your deaths.
What did you say?
I had the chance to warn our
father about the gambit,
Sara!
Emiko: That it was rigged
to explode,
and I knew about it.
I let our father die
because he didn't
deserve to live,
and neither do you.
Bye, brother.
[Beeping]
[Gasps]
[Coughs]
[Grunts]
Overwatch? John?
[Coughs]
Need some help?
Tommy?
Hey, Ollie.
It's been a while.
[Grunting]
[Coughing]
John!
Rene?
Dinah!
Can anyone hear me?
[Metal creaking]
John: I'm here!
I'm here.
[Groans]
Ohh!
[John groaning]
You OK?
I'm good.
Can't say much
for my helmet.
[Coughs]
[Dinah grunting]
You good?
Well, my Bo staff's smashed,
but other than that.
- Where's Rene?
- I don't know.
- John: Rene!
- Dinah: Rene!
John: Rene!
Rene!
Rene: You guys want to
get me out of here?
Rene, are you
in there?
He's here.
Get him out!
- Dinah: You OK?
- John: Move it.
[John and Roy grunting]
We can't do it.
Dinah: Here. Hurry!
- Let's try this.
- Grab it, grab it, grab it.
Grab it. Dinah,
pull on 3, OK?
- Dinah: OK.
- John: All right. Ready?
- Dinah: Yeah.
- John: 1, 2, 3. Come on!
[Roy and John groaning]
[Grunting]
Got you.
What the hell
just happened?
Emiko just dropped
a building on us.
That's what happened.
We got to get
to Oliver.
As we lost contact,
he was chasing Emiko
on the floor
beneath us.
- We have to get there.
- Then we better hurry.
Hey. Quick. Urgent.
I need our uplink gain augmenter.
Uh, more urgent,
I have something to tell you bef...
OK. Your thing is definitely
not more urgent than mine.
- Welcome to my thing.
- What are they doing?
Don't they remember
we're on the same side,
deputized vigilantes
and everything?
Well, apparently,
they have a warrant.
They what?!
H-hi. Excuse me. What...
an anonymous source sent
us surveillance footage
of last night's incident
in the subway tunnels.
Where you see
Team Arrow valiantly foil
a terrorist attack
just like we told you?
Emiko Adachi didn't
kill those guards.
Your friend
Roy Harper did.
Then your whole team
lied to cover it up.
That's insane.
Digital forensics
also investigated
that bomb, which you said was
the work of The Ninth Circle...
- Uh-huh.
- But that file was activated
from a program
called Archer,
a program which Smoak
tech owns the patent for.
Well, technically, yes,
but it was stolen.
This has to be a mistake.
I mean...
I agree. I know
this sounds shady,
but trust me...
we are the good guys,
and we are after the bad
guys... well, bad girl,
who currently has
your captain
and my husband trapped
under a building.
We haven't received any word
about no buildings going down.
That's because it was
a small detonation
in a chemical plant
outside of town.
Listen! You can talk
to the team all about it,
but to get ahold
of them,
I have to get ahold of a really tiny,
delicate piece of tech
that is in that box that
lieutenant butterfingers
is rummaging through.
Bingsley: I'm sorry,
Ms. Smoak.
- You're under arrest.
- What?
- You can't do that!
- Yes, I can.
Turn around!
OK. Just... Let me
give my friend a hug first.
Go ahead.
Plug your ears.
[Beeping]
[Screeching sound]
[Officers screaming]
[Screech stops]
What the hell
was that?
Oh. It's part
of my new security system,
a remote-detonated
nanoelectric pulse
that I built
into the ceiling.
Oh. Remind me to never
get on your bad side.
- Is Oliver OK?
- I don't know.
I tried. All I got
was static,
but if I can boost
the signal,
I might be able
to contact them.
You mean if we can.
I'm not letting you
do this alone.
OK. Well, then
let's get out of here.
We do not want to be here
when these guys wake up.
Keven:
Crime, violence, anarchy.
The terrible disease
that once infected
the streets of The Glades
has risen again,
but there is a cure
to the vigilante problem
and a chance
for a better, brighter future...
ZETA, powered
by Galaxy One's Archer Program.
They are the front lines
of a citywide initiative
to end the vigilante menace
and restore Star City's
glory once and for all.
Mia: First, Galaxy One puts
a bounty on your heads.
Now they're sending a damn army
of super robots after you?
We are just Keven Dale's
scapegoats
for his larger agenda.
Which is what?
Turn Star City
into a police state,
go under Galaxy One's
control.
We can't let
that happen.
Mia: Oh, yeah?
And how exactly
are we supposed
to stop them?
By destroying Archer.
Dinah: We tried that
once, remember?
It didn't work then,
and Archer was
nowhere near as
advanced as it is now.
That's why we have to
find the mad scientist
who upgraded my creation
into Frankenstein's monster.
Roy: You sure that's
a good idea?
No, but if Galaxy One has an army
of Archer-powered assassins,
we don't stand a chance,
Star City loses.
Well,
I'll put the word out to what's left
of the canary
network,
see what intel
they can find.
William: You know,
if you need a quick and dirty virus,
I'm sure I can whip
something up in no time.
It won't work.
I've tried them all.
But if the network
is still online,
then they can
still track our DNA,
- so we need a plan "b."
- I have a plan "b!"
And all of my plans
include you laying low
and staying safe.
Leave Archer to me.
Thank you.
[Metal creaking]
You look shocked.
Um, is it the beard?
Uh-uh. You look good.
Yeah, I know.
[Sighs] I must have
a really bad concussion.
Yeah, man. A building
just collapsed on you.
It could be a little
PTSD, too.
That position that
you're in with the rebar,
it is remarkably similar to how
you found me all those years ago.
The night you died.
Yeah.
[Cement falling]
And I got to tell you, man,
it looks like
the same thing is
gonna happen to you
if you don't get out
of here, like, right now.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
[Arrow hissing]
Ooh. Yeah.
That was close.
Um... you think you want to
pop that thing back in?
- Mm-hmm.
- OK. 1, 2, and 3.
Aah!
[Moans]
[Exhales]
- That had to hurt.
- Yeah.
You have Oliver
angry face on right now.
Just saying.
[Sighs]
I got to get out
of here.
[Groans]
The team might be dead.
Everything we've built
with the SCPD is... Is gone
because of Emiko.
I need to... I need to
get out of here.
I need to find the others,
and we have to stop her.
Um, isn't that gonna
be kind of hard
considering she's
family?
She's not
my family anymore.
Well, I hope you
weren't planning
on using your bow
to get out of here
'cause...
Yep.
[Sighs]
Overwatch?
Arsenal?
Does anyone copy?
You know,
I know that you were worried about them,
but they are pretty
resourceful people.
They're probably fine.
Let's hope you're right.
I usually am.
You know, it is insane
that we both had
secret half sisters.
Well, yours didn't try
to kill you, did she?
Well, you should give
Thea some credit.
I died before she had
the chance to try.
A couple specialty Arrows left,
two explosive.
Seems kind of risky
considering
the instability
of this place,
especially
without a bow.
Well, there are solutions
for that.
Speaking of, uh,
what about Emiko?
What kind of solution
are you planning
for her?
The one she deserves.
She let our father die.
He abandoned her,
Oliver.
She's been manipulating me,
she's been manipulating
the team for months,
posing as some sort
of hero.
The woman's a murderer.
So now you're gonna
be one, too?
And here I thought that we
were done with all of that.
I don't see another
choice here, Tommy.
It is exactly that kind
of attitude
that's gonna keep you
stuck down here.
[Typing]
Looks like your mystery
contact is as good
at covering their
tracks as you are.
Ugh. I know, which is
why she's so dangerous
and annoying.
William:
So I think I finally figured out a plan "b"
to keep us hidden from Archer
while we try to destroy it.
Blindspots just like the one
Keven Dale used to mask his DNA.
The only way this is
going to work is
if we copy the exact
root code that was used
in the original.
OK. Well, how
do we do that?
Well, we'd have to steal it
from Keven Dale's computer
in his office
at Galaxy One.
Uh, I suppose
I could break in.
No, no. I'm sorry.
Not you. Me.
I mean, Keven Dale
already recognizes me
as a fellow ceo,
and besides,
I think he'd be
a lot more agreeable
to me than... You.
You know, a little flirty flirt
while I hack into his computer,
and then we'll get
what we need.
- Look. I know it's a risk.
- A big one.
One I am not
willing to take.
We have a plan "a."
Let's stick to it.
Like I said, just
leave it to me.
You know you're still
treating me like I'm 13.
What do you mean?
Uh, I mean that you're doing
the exact same thing to me now
that you and dad did
all those years ago,
leaving me out of things
and then getting rid of me.
Your father and I,
we never wanted to let you go.
But you did,
and then even
after everything that happened,
you still stayed away
like... like I wasn't even
part of this family.
Mia: Ooh. I thought
we had problems.
I'm just gonna go
do anything else.
William, I am so sorry.
I realize now that we
made a terrible mistake,
a mistake that I am going to
regret for the rest of my life,
but we really thought
we were protecting you.
We just wanted you to
have a normal life.
[Computer chiming]
At this rate, we won't find
Oliver until sometime next week.
Felicity, cutting in and out:
Team Arrow, do you copy?
[Comms beeping]
Overwatch,
is that you?
Yes. Are you guys OK?
John: You have me, Roy, Rene,
and Dinah. We're safe.
Felicity: And Oliver?
He was in another part
of the building. We...
we haven't been
able to contact him.
I'm guessing you
haven't either.
No, but his comm unit is
still online and active,
so if it wasn't crushed,
it means he wasn't either.
- Roy: We'll find him.
- Felicity: I know.
You guys should know
I don't know what
Emiko is planning,
but she gave the SCPD
the footage of Roy
in the subway tunnels,
and they think that
we are behind
whatever The Ninth Circle
is plotting.
So lying to the SCPD to cover
for Roy was for nothing.
Not to mention
our reputations
and everything
we built this year.
Yeah. Let's move.
You've always been good
at this kind of thing.
Remember when we
were kids
and you learned how to
hotwire my dad's car?
Well, I got grounded
for an entire summer.
Yeah, because you
did it 3 more times.
Then it's a good thing
I should only have to
do this once.
[Draws bow]
Uh-huh. You might only
be making this worse.
All the work we've done
to prove ourselves
to the cops,
to the city.
And poof!
It's just gone.
- Along with my job.
- We don't know that.
All we know is that Emiko
tried to set us up.
Well, yeah. She lied about us being
behind The Ninth Circle attacks,
but she was telling the truth about
us covering up those murders.
We never should
have done that.
Wait. Even if it meant
Roy going to prison?
Two people were murdered.
I'm gonna turn
myself in.
- Roy: It's the only way.
- John: No, you're not.
You've already taken
the fall for us once, Roy.
Let us help you
this time.
And because of that,
everything you've worked for
is at risk.
He's right. I'm sorry,
but the SCPD
has already tried
to arrest Felicity.
It's better one of us
takes the fall
than the rest of us spends
our lives as fugitives.
While we're arguing,
Emiko's out there planning.
We need to get out
of here and stop her.
[Metal creaking,
cement breaking]
Oh, that can't be good.
John: Move, move, move!
Go, go, go, go!
All right. Is
everybody all right?
- Yeah.
- Oh, sure.
- Now the lights come on.
- Uh, guys, if the lights
just came on, that means the
emergency generator just came on.
- That's a good thing, right?
- Normally, yeah,
but the building you're in
used to manufacture
some very flammable
chemicals,
and flammable chemicals plus
sparks equals really big boom.
- OK. What about Oliver?
- If you don't turn off
the generator soon,
there's gonna be no Oliver to find.
The entire building's gonna go up in flames,
and you with it.
All right.
Let's keep moving.
Felicity, we're in
the boiler room.
[Loud rattling]
Rene: OK. Please tell me
that's not the generator.
Well, if it sounds like
a sick dinosaur, it probably is.
Good news is we still
have about 8 minutes
before it incinerates
the whole building.
And where is it exactly?
Felicity:
Lower level, to your left.
Dinah: What do we
think that is?
- Roy: C6H6.
- Alena: Benzene.
Guys, that is
really bad stuff.
- How bad?
- Try irreparable nerve damage
with severe convulsions
and a painful death.
But the good news is
it's heavier than air,
so you are safe
on the mezzanine. Heh.
Roy: And the bad news is that
generator is not on the mezzanine.
Neither is Oliver.
The ground beneath your feet is airtight,
so it can't get to him.
Well, I prefer my friends alive,
so we're gonna have to find
a new way to get you
to the generator, and fast.
Again, I would like
to point out
how structurally unsound
this building appears to be,
so maybe upping the payload
is not the best idea.
It's a risk
I have to take.
This is it.
After this, I'm out of options.
Are you, or is this
just typical Oliver?
Now come on, man.
Don't you ever wonder
why you keep finding yourself
in positions like this
where things just keep
getting worse?
I'm here for one reason and
one reason only... Emiko.
Right. Emiko,
your half sister.
Her being my half sister
doesn't matter.
What matters is finding
her and stopping her
before she hurts
anyone else.
It's a strategy you
should appreciate.
Why? Because of what
my father did to The Glades?
No, Tommy, because
of what he did to you!
Any idea what it's
like to... to...
to run a scenario through
your head a million times,
just wondering
if you could've just
listened to me
a little bit sooner,
but you didn't
because you were blinded
by the fact that
he was your father.
Maybe you'd still be
alive today.
But I didn't listen,
and I didn't make
the right choice,
at least not
until it was too late,
because I was stuck,
Oliver, in my own cycle,
my father's cycle,
just like you are
and just like you
will continue to be
if you don't
break free.
No. No. You're wrong.
This isn't about me.
This is not
about my father.
This is about Emiko,
and the choices that
she made,
they are on her.
Overwatch, any luck figuring
out that alternate approach?
Felicity: Looks like there's
a room behind the generator
with a failsafe switch.
The air ducts should be
able to get you in there.
All right. Yeah. Looks like we're
gonna have to crawl there fast.
John: Yeah.
We'll never
make it in time.
- John: Roy, no!
- Dinah: Roy, no!
Roy, if you breathe that stuff in,
you're dead.
I know.
Stop! We'll find
another way!
There's not enough time.
No!
Please don't tell me
he just went in there!
Overwatch, tell me
how much time he has.
10 seconds,
maybe 12.
Roy, I'm gonna need
a sitrep. Talk to me, Roy!
John: Roy? Roy!
[Generator stops]
He did it.
[Gasps]
- Dinah: Oh!
- John: Roy!
Oh. Come on.
Are you OK?
John: Overwatch,
power's off.
We're headed out
to find Oliver.
Copy that.
I don't know how you ever
breathe on this job.
I don't.
Come on, Oliver.
Where are you?
Hey. Um, Random question.
Did you add another hero
to your justice league?
You I expected.
Too bad for your friend.
Please don't.
I thought you'd be
eager to join you husband.
Please don't kill me!
I'm pregnant!
This baby
is innocent
just like you were when
Robert left your family.
Please don't kill
an innocent child.
Good to know.
Aah!
[Breathing heavily]
[Groans]
I think the concrete
gives up.
I need to get out of here.
You will. Trust me.
What you really need
to worry about
is what happens
when you do.
- Why?
- Everything you've done
this year... working
with the cops,
fighting for the city
without a mask...
you've got a shot at
something we never had.
What's that?
A clean slate.
You can't shed your past,
but you can keep it
from hurting your kids.
That's something our parents
could never give us,
but it is never, ever
going to happen, Oliver,
if you keep seeing red
with Emiko.
As long as she's
still breathing,
my family will never
be safe.
You know this, Tommy.
Then you haven't moved past
your family's mistakes, Oliver.
You haven't broken
the cycle of lies and hate.
You're trapped.
You're trapped
just like you are
in this room.
But you're not here.
You are a...
you are a figment
of my imagination
that has been sent here
to test my resolve.
Won't work.
[Rumbling]
Looks like you found
your way out.
To stop Emiko,
if I need to be
as ruthless to her
as she was to my father,
so be it.
Good luck finding
your team, Oliver.
You're gonna need them.
Good-bye, Tommy.
Comms just
dropped off.
Yeah.
We should be getting closer to Oliver.
- Dinah: You need a minute?
- Roy: No.
Ugh! Yeah. OK.
Maybe I do.
Why don't you guys
go ahead,
find us a way
downstairs?
We'll catch up.
You must be
a pretty big idiot,
risking your life
like that.
Well, we're alive,
aren't we?
You're lucky to be.
I'm surprised you even care if
I made it out alive or not.
Of course I care.
You're our teammate.
Maybe I shouldn't be.
You lost everything
to protect me,
and you don't
even know me.
Those guards that
I killed,
they're innocent.
They had families.
What you did back there,
it was awful,
but we all know
it was the bloodlust, Roy.
That wasn't you.
No. That doesn't
change the fact that
I put everyone else
around me at risk.
You should have just
let me go to prison.
I was wrong.
We all make mistakes.
I was just pissed because we
had just lost everything.
That doesn't mean
I want you dead.
Maybe it's best if
I am 6 feet under.
Dying is the coward's
way out.
Every day that you
stay alive,
you try to redeem
yourself
for that messed-up
thing you did
because this world
is a better place
with a hero like you.
Now let's go.
Bunker is clear
and secure.
- You OK?
- Yeah. Doesn't seem to be
any permanent damage.
Just rebooting
the system,
get the comms
up and running,
and then I'm gonna check
to see if Oliver's OK.
Uh, let me repeat.
You. Are you OK?
Almost dying?
Nothing I haven't done 100 times before.
- Am I right?
- Well, the first time you've
done it when it's
not just you.
Sadly, no.
William, the poor kid,
I mean, all he ever wanted
was a normal life...
loses his mom,
gets kidnapped way too many times,
the final straw...
being taken hostage by a serial killer.
I mean, how's life gonna be
any different for this kid?
You'll make it
different.
You know, you make
that sound so easy.
Growing up,
my parents,
it's just that they
made my life miserable,
and I promised myself
that I would do better
when I became
a parent, that I would...
I would... I would
just be better,
and I imagined this... this...
this life, and this is not it.
I mean, somehow, I've
done something worse,
and I've created
this life where i...
I can't even keep
my children safe.
Hey. At Smoak Tech,
you defended yourself like a badass.
You will find a way
to protect those kids.
- How?
- Think of it like
a computer program.
How do you secure
a system?
You get a really good
firewall,
and you take it offline.
I can't exactly take my
entire life off the grid.
Well, why not?
I have a company
for one.
Well, luckily, you have
a fantastic cto
who can run it
for you.
You want a different
life for this kid, right?
- Yes.
- Well, then
you're gonna need to do
something different this time.
Yeah.
Keven:
Crime, violence, anarchy.
The terrible disease
that once infected
the streets of The Glades
has risen again,
but there is a cure
to the vigilante problem
and a chance
for a better...
Thought you were supposed
to go with Felicity
in case her friend
needed convincing.
She took Roy instead.
Guess she's trying
to protect me, too.
You know,
if you're trying to make me feel better
about being abandoned
by our parents,
just don't.
Fine. Have your
little pity party
because mom
benched you.
You know that's not
what this is about.
Then what is it about?
When we rescued her
from Galaxy One,
mom apologized,
you guys seemed cool.
Yeah. I thought
we were, too,
but she's still pushing me
away just like she always has.
OK. Fine.
So maybe she wasn't there for you
in the traditional
sense,
but mom made sure that your
company was a success.
She was trying.
I didn't need
her money, Mia.
I needed a mother.
To this day, Felicity
still hasn't told me
why she kept me out
of her life for so long
or... why she wanted
no part of mine.
[Sighs]
Look.
When I first found out
mom was keeping secrets,
that she was still
being a vigilante,
I didn't wallow and
feel sorry for myself.
I confronted her,
demanded answers.
Maybe it's time
you do the same.
[Watch chimes]
John?
John: Oliver!
Dinah: Oh.
Thank god!
John: Let's keep moving.
We're lucky this is
still standing.
- Which way?
- East.
Felicity said it was
the best way out.
Emiko: Oh.
It definitely is.
Hi, brother.
Emiko, you have
one last chance
to stand down!
Funny, I was gonna
say the same to you.
Hyah!
[Bones crack]
[Steam hissing]
This place is
about to explode!
Oliver, we have to
go now!
Not without her!
Oliver, now!
- It's over.
- Is it?
I know
about your baby.
[Arrow clatters]
Your family's
gonna die.
I made sure of it.
Oliver, don't.
[Gasping]
Oliver.
John!
[Thud]
Oliver.
Tommy: Oliver.
Oliver!
[Gasps]
What was that?
How would I know?
I'm just a figment
of your imagination...
But if I had to guess,
I'd say it's a reminder
of what it feels like.
Seeing my loved ones die?
Seeing my family
be threatened?
What about that don't
I already know? God.
Well, then you know
exactly what it feels like
to be your father.
[Exhales]
The fear, how that
leads to vengeance,
how that leads
to cruelty.
It's why he abandoned
Emiko.
It is why she is
trying to kill you now.
Look, Oliver.
I know that you think
that you have broken
your father's cycle,
but as long as you are
giving in
to your worst impulses,
you are never going to be free.
What am I supposed
to do?
Just tell me what
I'm supposed to do.
Lean in to the best
parts of yourself...
your loyalty,
your selflessness,
your courage,
your compassion,
and show that side
to Emiko.
You are living proof
that people can change,
and you have got to find a
way to see that in her, too.
I don't know
if I can.
That's OK. That's the risk
you got to take.
Dinah: He should be
in there!
Roy: Oliver!
Looks like
our time's up.
You know, Tommy,
I miss you
every day.
I know,
but I'm always
with you.
Time to wake up now.
[Snaps fingers]
Rene: Hey!
He's over here!
- Roy: You OK?
- Dinah: We're gonna get you out.
John: I thought we lost
you there for a second.
Yeah, so did I.
Oh, thank god
you're alive.
Hey. Are you and the...
Are you OK?
Yeah. Yeah,
we're fine.
Emiko did pay us
a visit, though.
Emiko was here?
If she left
without killing you,
- you got off easy.
- Yeah. Too easy.
She must have been
after something else.
- Our thoughts exactly.
- Yeah, but we checked,
and the only things missing are
a few Arrows from the armory.
Why would she need
Oliver's Arrows
if we already got blamed for
the attack at the subway?
She must have had
something else planned.
Yeah, but Emiko thinks
she killed us.
How could she pin a second attack
against a group of dead vigilantes?
Well, the public doesn't
know that you're dead yet.
Just got an apb.
Green Arrow sighted
outside of SCPD,
shots fired.
At least now we know
what she was after.
Rene: Oliver,
we walk in there,
we're going in
as wanted criminals.
Let's gear back up.
We've got to move fast.
Ah. William,
right on time.
After our last meeting,
I'd hoped to hear from you again,
but I never expected
it to be so soon.
Well, you know
what they say...
strike while
the iron's hot.
[Both chuckle]
I hope you don't mind,
but I was so excited
when you said you
wanted to discuss
our ZETA program
that I invited the man who
inspired it to join us.
Mr. Harris.
Mayor Ramirez. Heh.
You two know each other?
By reputation.
I bought Harris Consolidated
the day of its ipo.
- Smart man.
- Well, we've done well enough.
Speaking of
my profit margins,
who do I have to
sleep with to get
Harris Consolidated in
on those ZETAs?
[Coughs]
I mean, your commercial
was impressive,
but stopping vigilantes?
It's microthinking.
If you really want this
program to be profitable,
you have to think macro.
I mean, imagine what
an army of ZETAs
could do
on a grander scale,
and with Harris
consolidated's global reach,
why, Galaxy One could change
more than just Star City.
It could change
the world.
[Tablet chimes]
If you'll excuse me
a moment, gentlemen,
something's come up which
requires my immediate attention.
Of course.
Have you lost
your damn mind?
You nearly blew
my cover.
I'm sorry.
It was a calculated risk I had to take
to access Dale's files.
Is that why you've been
checking your watch?
You've been hacking
him this whole time?
And now I have
his blindspot code.
We should get out of here
before Dale figures that out.
Keven: Seems I
already have, Mr. Harris,
or do you prefer Clayton?
Such a pleasure
to finally meet the son
of Oliver Queen
and Felicity Smoak.
As for you, Mr. Mayor,
I'm afraid we've reached the
end of your political career.
Seize them.
So you're the fool
who's responsible
for this whole
Archer mess.
And you're the kid Felicity
went into hiding for.
I can see you got a lot
of your mom in you.
Well, that's not all you're gonna
see if you don't step back.
Felicity: Alena has agreed
to help us destroy Archer
for real this time,
isn't that right?
Well,
now that you've frozen my bank account
and shredded
my passport,
yes, I have.
I'm sorry
about your canaries.
I never meant for Archer
to be used like that.
And how exactly did you
mean for it to be used
after you stole it
from Smoak Tech
and sold it
to Galaxy One?
It started as a
software licensing deal
till Keven Dale turned it
into a hostile takeover.
Once he had Archer,
he threatened to use it to hunt
and kill everyone I loved
unless I disappeared,
so that's what
I did
to protect them.
Roy: Why don't you get
to work taking down Archer,
so we can all come
out of hiding?
I guess 3 genius brains
are better than 1.
Speaking of geniuses,
where is William?
Mia: I spoke to him right
after you and Roy left.
Oh. Where the hell is he?
[Typing rapidly]
Mom, what's wrong?
That sequence that
William ran
to steal Keven Dale's
blindspot code,
I think he used it.
How? I thought you said he could
only use it if he actually went...
frak!
Zeta: By the authority
of Galaxy One,
you are under arrest.
Oh, my god.
It's a slaughter.
[Bingsley wheezing]
What happened?
I thought it was you.
Somebody dressed like you stole
the weapon from the subway.
Spread out and find
Emiko.
John: Wild dog, on me.
Hyah!
Raah!
Oliver: Hyah! [Grunts]
Emiko!
You just refuse
to die.
Emiko has the weapon,
and she's up on the roof.
Copy that.
We'll meet you there.
Oliver: Emiko, stop!
Don't make me
do this.
You are supposed
to be dead,
but this will be
even better.
You can watch me burn
your city to the ground.
Haven't you seen
enough death?
Your mother,
our father.
I want you to be
better than him.
I want you to help me...
help me end our family's
cycle of violence.
We are not family.
Do it. Kill me.
No.
[Click, beeping]
She has
the weapon.
Roy: And we have no idea
where she's gonna use it.
- John: We'll find her.
- Rene: Guys, we got company.
Man on P.A.: This is SCPD
aerial support.
Hold your positions.
Man: Greg, move your head.