Bianca!
Bianca Bertinelli?
Who the hell are you?
Your life's in danger. I'm gonna
need you to come with me now.
My night's just getting started. Bye.
Get off.
Help!
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
Seeking his third straight
term, Mayor Ramirez
has declared Star City the
safest city in the country.
In other news, the vigilante
museum has received
a generous 7-figure donation
from Victor and Maria Bertinelli.
What are you doing?
Babe! You scared me.
I'm just the guy who you share
your bed with most nights.
Remember me?
How could I forget? Your
snoring always reminds me.
I don't snore.
Look, I know you hate to be
anything less than perfect,
but you do, like old man style.
- Ha ha. Right.
- Ha ha!
I got up early to
finish writing my speech.
Wait. Is there something
special happening today?
Funny. Ha ha!
A gift for the graduate.
What's happening?
Mia Queen, I love you
more than anything in the whole world.
Will you marry me?
Please say yes.
- Yes, of course.
- Yeah?
Of course. I love you so much.
♪ Sunny... ♪
Excuse me. I'm looking for the owner.
Over there.
♪ Ohh oh, sunny ♪
♪ You smiled at me ♪
♪ And really eased the pain ♪
♪ Oh, the dark days are gone ♪
♪ Now the bright days are here ♪
♪ My sunny one ♪
♪ Shines so sincere ♪
♪ Ohh oh oh ♪
♪ Sunny, one so true ♪
♪ I'm in love with you ♪
Dinah, this is where you've been living?
Well, it's right above the bar,
and it has got a hell of a view.
Black Canary and the Captain
of SCPD now owns a bar.
Also, when did you learn to sing?
We didn't have much time
for karaoke back in 2020,
did we?
So how did you find me? Sara?
She said that she found
you here a couple months ago
and that you didn't want
to come back with her.
The day after Oliver's funeral in 2020,
I woke up here.
I had no idea how or why.
When I got here,
I found out that I don't even exist.
I'm sorry. How is that even possible?
I don't know, but there is
no trace of Dinah Drake
or the Black Canary.
And what, you're just fine with that?
I guess I came to realize that
not having an identity can either be sad
or it can be oddly freeing.
I can let go of the people I lost,
mistakes that I made.
I'm not gonna lie. Your Zen
is kind of creeping me out.
Thank you.
You know, there has been
no real crime in Star City
in 20 years, Laurel.
And Zen's not that hard to come by.
Well, I hate to break it to you,
but Star City isn't safe anymore.
Bianca Bertinelli's been abducted.
Helena's daughter.
The socialite. Why... Why
would anybody want to hurt her?
Money, revenge, something
to do with Helena.
Who the hell knows? D, I
need you to help me find her.
You really came all
the way to the future
to rescue a kidnapped socialite?
- What am I looking at?
- Star City 2041.
This is a year from now.
It's not possible. The city's safe.
It doesn't stay that way.
Because Bianca
Bertinelli gets kidnapped?
No. Because she dies.
3 days from now, her
body is found in the bay,
her killer never caught.
The city falls apart.
Everything that Oliver
sacrificed his life for.
I thought this part of
my life was done, Laurel.
Then don't do it for
you. Do it for Oliver.
Okay.
For Oliver.
Good. Now there's one
more person we need
who's well-connected.
- And who is that?
- I'll inform you on the way.
You do have something
nicer to wear, right?
♪ Lookin' over you ♪
♪ Is something I do ♪
♪ Finally had to look... ♪
Ms. Queen, when is the wedding date?
What are you going to do
now that you've graduated?
Not sure yet on both counts.
What would your dad
think about your life choices?
My father saved Star City
so that we can enjoy it,
and he also never graduated college,
so I think he'd be pretty impressed.
Ms. Queen? Ms. Queen...
It was my Mom's.
JJ knew I'd want the family ring.
He's honestly the most
thoughtful guy in the world.
Can I just say what
an amazing man of honor
I'm gonna make at your wedding?
William!
Zoe, hi!
I hope you don't mind me crashing.
Never. It is so good to see you.
Where's Keven?
No. I thought he was the one.
Yeah. Well, apparently only
having one partner was his problem.
But it's fine. This is your day.
And speaking of,
tomorrow there's gonna be
an office for you at Smoak Tech.
How many times do I have to tell you,
tech is not really my passion?
What is your passion exactly?
I don't know.
Because you can't
be a socialite forever.
Hmm, she technically can.
No. No, I'm sorry. She
is way too smart for that.
Okay, can I just enjoy tonight
before I have to start adulting?
Fine. But I need a drink.
I just want to thank
you all for coming tonight.
You are my life.
I particularly want to thank
JJ for always having my back.
I love you so much.
- Aw.
And William.
I could not imagine life without you.
Thank you for always
tolerating your little sister,
even when I did draw all over
your walls when I was 5. Heh!
- To the class of 2040.
- 2040!
Whoo!
Is it all right for me to be here?
I'm sure it's okay. Hey.
I thought you were
still in rehab, Connor.
What's the matter, trust fund?
You don't want me at
your fancy little party?
As long as you don't punch
anyone or set anything on fire,
we'll be okay.
Can we just try to get
along for one night, please?
- Be right back.
- Okay.
Hey, Trev, have you seen Bianca?
She was supposed to be here an hour ago.
Heh! No, I'm not her keeper anymore.
Okay, I thought you guys were still cool.
No, we are, but even
when we were together,
she never told me where she was.
But you were the last
to see her, weren't you?
Excuse me?
Your number was the last one she texted.
Uh, who the hell are you?
Wait. Is something wrong with Bianca?
I don't know. You tell us.
Ah...
You can't just crash my
party and harass my guests.
Do you know who I am?
A lot more than you do.
We were friends of your parents.
Then how come I've never
seen either of you before?
Long story and less than
zero time to explain.
Your friend Bianca, she's in trouble.
And we need your help to find her.
Yeah. I'm calling security.
Oh. I'm sorry to take
you out of your bubble,
but we really need you.
I know how to protect myself.
- You made sure of that.
- I sure did.
The 4 of you are the
heroes that the city needs.
Hyah!
We are staring at our father alive!
Dad. So what's next?
Mar Novu has seen my fate.
- Dad...
- I don't survive Crisis.
Mia, come on. Mia?
- Back off.
- Um, I'm sorry. You fainted.
Are you okay?
Oh, my God.
Sorry. Uh, sorry. I... I
guess I had too much to drink
without eating or something.
Maybe you should lie down, party animal.
Think I need some air.
- Hey, Mia, listen...
- Ooh. No.
What the hell did you do to me?
I would love to know that myself.
There's this guy, J'onn J'onzz.
He's a Martian or something.
He's why we remember everything
that happened before the Crisis.
Cisco was able to replicate
the Martian's powers using tech.
So a friend of Supergirl's has a power
a friend of the Flash can replicate.
Yeah. That's what I said.
I want to say that you guys are crazy
and that none of this is possible,
but I know you're right.
I remember everything,
you two fighting alongside my dad,
Zoe dying, my...
My fiancé killing her.
I remember my father dying.
Why would you do this to me?
Look, there'll be time
for emotions later.
I woke you up because your
friend Bianca was kidnapped.
There hasn't been any crime
in Star City in 20 years.
What is that, like the city's motto now?
You don't know Bianca, all right?
She's flaky. She's probably on
a beach somewhere having a ball.
I saw her, and she was taken.
How are you even hesitating?
Aren't you supposed
to be the Green Arrow?
Not anymore.
Mia, I understand that you are torn
between two worlds right now,
but we need your help.
Look, I don't even know
if I can do this anymore, okay?
I haven't trained. I don't...
See? Just like riding a bike.
Is Bianca actually in trouble?
Yes. And if we don't
find her, she's going to die.
Fine. I will help you.
But this is a one-time thing, okay?
I'm not interested in joining
your Canary Club, all right?
I have a life now, I am happy,
and I would like to keep it that way.
Whatever.
Well, where was Bianca
when she was taken?
Partying at Club V.
Nothing Bianca loved
more than a good party.
Oh, to be in my 20s again.
Ick. Hard pass. I was married at 21.
Seriously? Who are you?
Bianca. She was adopted.
Any chance that created tension?
Helena was a great mom
before she disappeared.
She lives with her
great-aunt and uncle now.
Back in the old Star
City, the Bertinellis were
one of the biggest
crime families around.
Well, that sounds like enough reason
to violate some privacy laws.
It's time for you
to pay that family a little visit.
I'm sorry Bianca missed your
party. You know how she is.
Free spirit.
Totally. Actually,
I wanted to speak with you about that.
I think Bianca might be
in some kind of trouble.
What kind of trouble?
Mia's in position. D, you're up.
- You ready?
- Never not.
I think Bianca might have been taken.
Ha ha! That's ridiculous.
You know how safe it is here.
I haven't been able
to contact her in days.
Her social media is quiet,
and she's not even posting those videos
she's always addicted to making.
I wouldn't worry about it.
In a couple days, we're gonna find out
she's been, uh, what partying
off the coast of Corto
Maltese or something.
Dinah, what's your progress?
3 more rooms to go.
You're about to have company,
one of the help, I'm guessing.
Mia, we need a distraction.
Wouldn't it be better
to be safe than sorry?
I mean, maybe since we're here,
if we call the police...
Oh, my God! I'm so sorry.
Get Remy!
Remy?
Remy, we've got an emergency.
Do us a favor. Stop
worrying about Bianca.
She's fine.
Okay, I will.
I'm clear.
Please tell me you got
those eyes and ears placed.
All of them.
We can see and hear everything
that goes down in that house.
Good. I'll meet you at the bar.
I want to talk to Bianca's
friends, see what they know.
- You want company?
- Ha ha.
And have to explain who you
two are again? No, thanks.
You know, I could get used
to all this free alcohol.
So that means you will not
be paying your tab downstairs.
I thought it was a friends
drink for free kind of place.
They say anything interesting yet?
A couple stock tips, where to vacation,
nothing that helps.
Ohh, man. This is one hell of a view.
I can see why you hide out here.
Subtle. I am not hiding.
I told you, the world
doesn't remember who I am.
Don't you remember you?
I really don't expect you to understand.
Try me.
I mean, isn't this what friends do?
They sit around and drink,
talk about their problems.
Okay, well, when I first ended up here,
I spent a lot of time asking myself why.
It took a while, but I think
I finally understand the answer.
This is the universe's way of telling me
I'm not supposed to be a hero.
Why? Because you didn't get a gold star?
Because in this version of the
future, the one where I'm not a hero,
everyone is better off.
Mia's happ... Mia was happy
until we dragged her into this.
Zoe's alive because she's not a Canary.
And all of a sudden,
what, you're gun shy?
Zoe didn't die because she was a Canary.
She died because she
was a hero, because you
inspired her and a bunch
of other women just like her
to fight for something
greater than themselves,
myself included.
What, are you guys on
a break or something?
It's called surveillance.
How did it go with Bianca's friends?
Let me guess.
"Oh, Bianca was just being Bianca.
And, oh, my gosh, what
shoes am I gonna wear?"
They didn't know anything.
And, by the way, 3 of
them went to Harvard.
That's awesome.
Oh, Logan Bertinelli
just got chatty. Hang on.
He's worried about something,
"Taking precautions",
specifically moving
"it" out of the city.
What are the odds "it" is Bianca?
Logan's an ass, but he
wouldn't kidnap his cousin.
Well, there's only one way to find out.
Let's suit up.
You earned it.
I'm not wearing that.
- Why? It's yours.
- It's my father's.
She shouldn't have to wear it
if she doesn't want to, Laurel.
Fine.
What the hell are you guys waiting for?
Secure our friggin' position.
You go get Bianca, and we'll
take care of Logan and his friends.
- What?
- You'll be fine.
Bianca's not here.
Looks like some kind
of chemical or drug.
I... I give up, okay?
Run!
Well, that could've gone better.
You've got some nerve
leaving me alone out there.
What if I hadn't
remembered how to fight?
But you did. You're welcome.
I could've died.
Okay, that's a little dramatic.
We were there the whole time.
D, some help, please?
It was pretty risky, Laurel.
How about less talking
about your hurt feelings
and more talking about
the fact that your fiancé
just became suspect number one?
There is no way this is JJ.
The guy who attacked
us in the Deathstroke mask?
You do know who Deathstroke is, right?
It could've been anyone under that mask.
It does seem like a
pretty big coincidence,
especially given who JJ was before.
I mean, he used to lead them.
Yeah, and I used to be a cage fighter.
That is not who I am anymore,
and that is clearly not who JJ is.
Are you really that naive?
Are you really that judgmental?
You don't even have the
slightest bit of doubt
that JJ is the one who
is behind that mask?
No.
Prove it.
Mia Queen. These are my Plus-2.
See? A much better idea
than punching our way in.
A lot less fun, though. Mia,
you sure you're up for this?
I'm here, aren't I?
JJ's office is in back.
Dinah, you take cameras.
Mia, go distract your fiancé.
You sure you're okay?
Yeah. It's the strangest thing.
I have all these
memories of my old life,
but I have my new ones, too.
I just really don't want it to be him.
Hey. Sorry I'm late.
Oh, yeah. I was starting to worry.
You left in a hurry earlier.
Yeah, I wasn't feeling well.
"Actually, I just remembered
you were a dangerous murderer,
probably a kidnapper, too".
Hey, be nice, Laurel.
- I need a drink.
- Yeah.
- Come on.
There's only one guard at the door.
This should be easy.
Where are we on cameras?
Almost there.
In the meantime,
why don't we go back to
talking about Mia's love life?
Let's not.
You know I dated your dad, right?
- Well, a version of him anyway.
- Gross.
My Oliver also went down on the Gambit,
also cheated with my sister.
Please stop talking.
People are who they are, Mia,
no matter what timeline,
universe, or Earth,
and that's not your fault.
Was that supposed to be
some kind of pep talk?
Cameras are down.
That's my cue.
This area is restricted.
Oh, I was just gonna
step out and get some air.
Trust me, I am not an art thief.
Well, you're welcome to step outside.
Okay, let's not cause
a scene here, Laurel.
- I'll do it.
- Fine.
No offense, Mia,
but if I couldn't get in there,
do you really think that
you're gonna be able to just...
Oh, you were saying?
I'm in. Now what do I need to do?
Just put the device
anywhere near the computer.
It'll transfer the
data from your search.
It's working.
Run a search for the Bertinellis.
Maybe we'll get lucky.
Uh, something's wrong.
Mia, you need to get out of there now.
Hey, step away from the computer.
Mia, what are you doing in here?
Where is she?
I'll take it from here.
What is going on with you?
You break into my office,
and you hack my computer?
I know you have Bianca.
That's what this is about?
You think that I kidnapped her?
Do you know how crazy that sounds?
You're calling me crazy now. Wow.
Because you are being crazy.
Okay, if you have nothing to hide,
then show me what's in these files.
Our honeymoon.
You said that you always
wanted to visit Fiji.
I was hoping I could surprise you.
Namaste.
Can I call you crazy now?
Bianca? What the hell?
I have to get back to the party.
Okay. Let me explain.
JJ.
Bianca looks pretty happy to
be kidnapped, don't you think?
Turn off your socialite
brain and use your gut.
Don't you think that
video's a little convenient?
I think whoever posted that is trying
to keep people from looking for Bianca.
We should analyze it, you know,
see what clues we can
get in finding her.
Okay, I just accused
my fiancé for nothing.
Oh, he'll get over it.
Or you'll move on to someone
who wasn't a homicidal maniac
in another life. Win-win.
Oh, frak you.
Okay, that's enough. I think
we just need to calm down...
No. I am not the one who cares more
about my relationship problems
than my friend who might die.
Do you not see how selfish you're being?
Me? You're the one who's using my friend
to drag me and Dinah back
into this superhero crap
just because you can't handle
the fact that Star City's fine
and doesn't need you to be
the Black Canary anymore.
And here I thought making
you remember your old life
would open your eyes to
how pointless and stupid
your new one is.
My stupid and pointless
life is the one that
my father sacrificed himself to give me.
Don't you dare trivialize that.
Okay, I think all Laurel
was trying to say is
that Bianca's out there,
and she's in danger.
Bianca is fine.
You had no right to make me remember.
All that did is bring back
the suffering and the loss,
because that's all being a hero is.
I would've met you at your place.
I needed the drive.
I hope that I
didn't screw up your event too badly.
I wish it was just the
event that you'd screwed up.
JJ, I'm sorry.
You accused me of kidnapping our friend.
How in the world do you think
I could do something like that?
You were keeping things from me.
I guess I just jumped to conclusions.
Jumping to conclusions
is... is I'm cheating on you,
not that I'm a kidnapper.
And for the record, I'm neither.
I know that.
Can we please just go back to a time
before I accused you
of being a criminal?
I get it now.
This never had anything
to do with Bianca.
What are you talking about?
You have never really had to
commit to anything in your life.
That's why you brush off
your brother's job offers.
And it's why you hesitated
saying yes to my proposal.
It's why you're pushing
me away right now.
You don't want to marry me.
That is not true.
Then how come ever since the party...
Ever since I proposed to you, it's like
you're seeing someone else
when you're looking at me?
When I look at you, I
see the rest of my life.
I can't marry someone
who doesn't feel the same.
John, please.
I... no.
I think it's best we take some space.
We're running out of time.
Please tell me you're close to
finding something on that video.
Our hunch was right.
There's evidence the image was altered.
I'm running a decryption program,
but it's gonna take a bit.
Since when did you learn to
do all this Felicity stuff?
I was a police captain,
Laurel. I have tricks,
like knowing when someone's
not telling me everything,
for example.
Like you.
What?
You've been pushing Mia
real hard, which is weird,
because normally, you keep a
fairly healthy snark-filled distance
from caring too much about anything.
This is personal.
Look, I wasted a lot of time
pretending to be something I wasn't
because it was easier, and I don't
want Mia making the same mistake.
You know, part of empathy isn't only
understanding other people's pain.
It's also sharing your own. You
know how hard it is to be a hero.
I mean, hell, I'm
struggling with it right now.
Imagine what she's going through.
The last time Mia put on
that Green Arrow suit was
the day Oliver died.
The program's finished.
Oh, boy.
Whoever did this wanted people to think
she was safe on vacation.
They didn't know they
were giving us a lead.
Well, thank God for morons.
I got to figure out where this is.
But for the record,
I think you're right.
If there is evil back in Star City,
the Green Arrow should be here, too.
Oh, God. Are you crying?
What the hell are you doing here?
I guess it's that feelings
thing or whatever.
Look, I'm sorry.
JJ broke up with me, if you even care.
I do care. You're strong
enough to get through this.
You're strong enough to get through
anything. I've seen you do it.
Is that why you woke me up?
Mia, I spent so much of my
life choosing the easy path.
And for me, that meant
becoming Black Siren
and destroying things
and killing people.
It's not a good look.
That's not exactly what I'm doing here.
Okay, but can you honestly tell me
that you were happy with your life
before I woke you up? Truly?
I spent my whole life
looking at these pictures of my dad,
all of the amazing things
he did for the city,
what a hero he was,
wondering how I could
possibly live up to that
in anything I chose to do.
And...
And so I chose to do nothing.
He would probably be
so disappointed in me.
I doubt that.
Your father. He wanted you to be happy.
And he... he gave you all this,
but I also think he wanted
you to have a choice.
I am not gonna sugarcoat it for you.
Being a hero kind of sucks.
And it never gets any
easier because it is
the hardest thing that you can do.
Then why do it?
For me, it gave me a purpose.
And that's why I woke you up,
so that you could have the
chance to realize your own.
Mia, this is your city,
and you're the Green Arrow.
Hey. How did it go?
Ask her.
I'm glad you decided to join.
Bianca's my friend. Any
luck finding her location?
Not yet. But she's in a
greenhouse of some sort.
Only problem is there
are hundreds in the city.
It's gonna take time.
But that's not a greenhouse.
The design's biophilic.
It's meant to power the
building photosynthetically.
What are you, a botanist now?
I took a couple classes
in design theory and
sustainable concepts.
Socialites can have brains, too.
Great. Well, could you
use your fancy brain
and narrow it down for us?
Uh, there's about 12 buildings
in the city that fit the bill.
But only one of them is
currently unoccupied...
A complex downtown.
Let's go save my friend.
You sure you're ready for this?
One way to find out.
Thermal imaging places
Bianca on the top floor.
There's 2 bodies beside her.
I'm guessing they're guards.
How much more company can we expect?
It depends on how fast we move.
That's comforting.
Oh, and another piece of good news.
The whole place is laced
with meta-dampeners.
- So no Canary cries.
- Perfect. Ready?
I so wish I got that on my live stories.
We have to go now.
Why leave now, huh?
The fun is just getting started.
Trevor.
You know my name. Heh! I'm flattered.
Cool masks.
Yeah, very, uh, 2020.
Actually, I... I have...
I have one of my own.
So this is what you've been
spending daddy's money on?
Ha ha. You know, Bianca
never told me that she had
such, uh, colorful friends.
Oh, I get it.
She broke up with you, and
now your feelings are hurt.
- Aw.
Is that why you're doing this?
Oh, don't flatter yourself.
You're a pawn
with the fancy family name.
That's the only reason you're important.
Yeah, I see why you dumped him.
- Enough talking.
- Great.
So I guess that means
you're waving the white flag.
The 3 of you against all of us.
- I'll take those odds.
- So will we.
- There's too many of them.
- We have to get out of here.
Stay close.
Now what?
We're too high.
How are you still alive?
Death by tantrum? You're gonna
have to do better than that.
Don't come any closer.
You see, all the greenery
in this building is linked
to the same system...
All state-of-the-art
and all very, very...
Explosive.
If he drops that lighter, this
whole place is gonna go up.
Trevor, don't do this.
You can't stop what's coming.
She won't let you.
And who the hell is she?
We have to jump.
I thought you were trying
to save me, not kill me.
Trust me.
Welcome back.
Oof. Who are you bitches?
Any word on how Bianca's doing?
She is back to her old
self, posting live videos.
So I'm not very good at
this, uh, feelings stuff.
I wanted to thank you, both of you.
And now you can go back
to your glamorous life
of singing to drunk
hipsters in your bar.
Oh, thank you for that.
But, uh, actually, I was
thinking of going part-time.
You know, Trevor's not just a
jealous ex-lover trying to get even.
Somebody pushed him to do this,
and we still haven't
figured out who or why.
Trevor's tattoo looked familiar.
We start there.
We?
Star City needs the Green Arrow.
But what about JJ,
and what about your life?
I'm not giving that up,
but I'm also gonna
protect my father's legacy.
Mia, living a double
life is really hard.
Well, somebody once told me that
being a hero is the
hardest thing you can do.
It's also the right thing.
Well, that person sounds really smart.
I mean, she has her moments.
But putting on that
suit again wasn't easy.
But it reminded me
that it's not all bad.
There are some really,
really good parts, too.
Well, uh, before we get
back to saving the world,
I say we should have
a celebratory drink.
And after what we did tonight,
I say we deserve the good stuff.
Cheers. To the Green Arrow.
To the Canaries.
To the future, whatever it holds.
Well, I'm glad you didn't
change the locks on me yet.
Mia...
Look, before you kick me out,
just please let me say I'm sorry.
You were right. I have been acting
weird since the graduation party.
- So then I did spook you.
- No.
This has nothing to
do with you proposing.
Look, graduating got into my head.
I'm trying to figure out what I
want to do with the rest of my life,
what kind of person I want to be. I...
I want to help you with that.
And that is why I love you so much.
You're a good person, JJ.
I couldn't imagine spending
my life with anyone else.
You know, it's been a while
since I had a roommate.
I'll get my own place, I promise.
Your own place? That
sounds pretty permanent.
The city's under threat, and I'm
not gonna leave until it's over.
You know, while you're here,
we could turn this place
into a base of operations
for the Canaries.
Canaries, as in more than just us?
Tonight made me remember
who I really am, Laurel.
I may have been erased,
but I'm not gone.
I need to figure out how I got here.
And while I do that, I can help
a whole new generation of women.
So basically, what you're saying is
that I was right.
Don't gloat.
But please do explain
why you didn't tell me
the whole story about
what Bianca's death
would have meant for the city.
Sara said when the city falls...
Someone's at the center of it... Mia.
But Bianca was dead in the future,
and Mia wasn't the Green Arrow.
We should be in the clear, right?
I hope so.
I can't believe it's been 20 years
since he sacrificed
himself to save the city.
Who's that?
Oh, just the "Star", The
"Globe", the "Gazette",
"Byline", Channel 52.
They all want to know
if I'm the Green Arrow.
Of course they do.
Isn't it a little misogynistic that
they're not calling you as well?
I mean, come on, guys. It's 2040.
Oh, my God. You brought the pet rock.
Excuse me. Are you
referring to the hozen?
This is the closest thing
we have to a family heirloom,
passed down from Dad to
Aunt Thea to Mom and to me.
Show some respect, please.
May I see it?
- Yes, you may.
- Thank you.
What the hell?
William!
Hey, babe. I didn't think
you'd be back so soon.
Who are you? What do you want?
I need you to remember.
I have vision.
We can fix this...
together.
JJ!
You were wrong about me, brother.
It was never a mask.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --