BACKMAN:
Call Cayman Fidelity.
Tell them their favorite accountant
is flying in...
...to make a special deposit
for a special client.
[ELEVATOR DINGS
THEN DOOR OPENS]
That elevator's supposed to be on a key.
Go check it out.
[MAN GRUNTS]
Harold Backman.
You have failed this city.
I'm only an accountant. I'm just the money.
Money that leads to extortion,
kidnapping and drugs.
It's the destruction of innocent lives!
You think you scare me
more than the people I work for?
No.
They can deal with you.
Hmm. Let me guess. Some bad guy
missing his fancy new laptop?
Harold Backman.
He's who Starling City's worst call
when they want to launder money.
Then shouldn't we just turn this over to,
I don't know, the IRS?
We will. Just as soon as you return
the money to the rightful owners.
Sounds like a nice idea, but Backman's files
are protected with an encryption algorithm.
-Really?
-Yeah.
-So it's gonna take a while to break in.
-Days, at least.
Better get started, then.
At the risk of ending up
with an arrow in my eye, can I ask...
-...when are you making peace with Diggle?
-He's the one who left, Felicity.
-I did everything I could to stop him.
-Except apologize.
You promised you'd help track Floyd
and you...
Made a choice that I can live with.
-If he can't, then I don't need him.
-Oliver...
I need to get back to the club.
Let me know when you break in.
I wish someone would send me off
to the Caymans.
Yes, I know it's been six months, but...
I am very well aware of the statistics...
...but I haven't given up hope
and neither should you.
THEA:
That didn't sound too good.
Oh, it's fine.
Who were you talking to?
Just the insurance company.
They insist on paying out
Walter's life insurance policy.
I know we haven't talked about Walter
in a while, but I miss him too.
It's like losing Dad all over again.
MALCOLM: You look radiant.
-Flatterer.
I think you're the last to arrive.
-How's Tommy?
-Tommy is Tommy.
-How's Oliver?
-Still in bed. It's only noon.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
MOIRA: Well, look who I just found.
-Heh-heh.
Get lost trying to find the house?
You say that as if your driveway's
not longer than most roads.
-Can I get anyone anything else?
ROBERT: We're fine.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
Oh. Excuse me.
Hello, Mrs. Queen.
I'm sorry to bother you at home.
Oh, no, no, no. Don't be silly, Walter.
Come in, please.
You're here to see Robert?
Yes, just some papers
he needs to sign for the stock offering.
He's in some private meeting right now,
but you're welcome to wait.
-Thank you.
-Unless you'd like to help me...
...get my children out of the house.
-You don't have children do you, Walter?
-Not yet, I'm afraid.
Well, save yourself the trouble and don't.
They eventually all turn into teenagers.
FRANK: Adam Hunt was reluctant at first,
but was more cooperative...
...upon being informed
we knew about his embezzlement.
The police's communications system
could use an upgrade.
I think Mr. Hunt can be persuaded
to make an anonymous donation.
Well, that will certainly cure
what ails this city.
What's that, Malcolm?
We're emptying the Atlantic
with a tablespoon.
For years, we've been forcing
the city's worst to do what is best...
...leverage them to help us save this city.
But it's not working.
Crime in the Glades is rising.
The cancer is spreading.
-We just need to take some more time...
MALCOLM: Did Rebecca get more time?
Did the man who raped Frank's daughter
give her any quarter?
Everyone in this room has lost something
or someone to the Glades.
And we have committed ourselves
to fixing it...
...but what have we truly accomplished?
Nothing. And maybe it's because
the Glades can't be fixed.
You're saying we should
abandon the project.
MALCOLM:
Yes.
In favor of a new undertaking.
Like Ben Tre in Vietnam.
The village must be destroyed
before it can be saved.
Are you suggesting
we somehow level the Glades?
Down to the bedrock.
Only then can we truly rebuild Starling City
and make it safer for everyone.
That's 24 square blocks.
And if we did,
and I'm not saying we should...
...if we did, wouldn't suspicion fall on us?
Not if the destruction appears to be
caused by a natural disaster.
You've always had something
of a God complex, Malcolm...
...it's part of your charm.
But even you can't create a natural disaster.
Have you ever heard of Unidac Industries?
It's a small company. They have an idea.
An idea that will serve our purposes.
My sources tell me
they're five years away from prototype...
...and any undertaking of value
is worthy of patience.
-And restraint.
-One man alone can't save this city, Robert.
We both know that.
[DOOR OPENS]
"Of all the gin joints in all the towns
in all the world, she walks into mine."
This coffee is terrible, Oliver.
That's what you get
for ordering coffee at a bar.
You look tired.
Too much work?
Too much crying.
Tommy broke up with me.
-What happened?
-I have no idea.
Things were good, they were great.
And then, suddenly, he's packing up
his things and telling me that it's over.
Did he say anything to you?
No. Tommy and I haven't talked
very much since he quit.
But he'll come around.
It's probably just cold feet.
Like it was with you?
Oliver, you don't sleep
with your girlfriend's sister...
...unless you're looking
to blow the relationship up.
If you still want to be with Tommy...
...do what we should've done.
Talk to each other. And be honest.
[DOOR OPENS]
FELICITY:
Oliver, I need to show you what...
I just totally walked in on a thing, didn't I?
I'm sorry, uh, who are you?
Nobody. I mean, I'm not nobody.
I'm someone, obviously.
And so are you. You're Laurel, right?
That Laurel. Gorgeous Laurel.
This is Felicity.
She's setting up my Internet.
Router. And I need to show Oliver
something very important related to it.
I'll let you go, then.
Thank you for the coffee.
And the advice.
[SIGHS]
-Tell me you got in.
-Better.
I hacked Cayman Fidelity and put together a
list of all the deposits Backman made.
What good does that do us?
Look at the biggest deposit last year.
Bottom of the page.
"Two million dollars on Decem..."
December 12th.
-That's...
-The day Walter disappeared.
What if one of Backman's clients
was paid 2 million to kidnap Walter?
Then we find out which client it was...
...and use them to find Walter.
Okay, back trace the account.
Follow the money.
Hopefully, it will lead us
to whoever kidnapped Walter.
After all this time, do you think
Walter might still be alive?
I don't know.
Got it. Dominic Alonzo.
-Ugh.
-Name ring any bells?
Yeah. Alonzo runs the biggest
underground casino in Starling City...
...when he's not busy kidnapping.
He looks like the kind of lowlife
someone would hire to kidnap Walter.
How many arrows you think you'll put
in him before he gives Walter's location?
-Say "a lot."
-It's not that simple.
That casino has its own army.
We need to access Alonzo's computer
but without setting off any alarms.
Looks like we're gonna need
all the help we can get.
It's too bad there's not someone
we could call.
That's enough. We can do this on our own.
Well, then, it looks like someone's
going gambling tonight.
Those guys would make me
the minute I walked in.
Oliver Queen would never be
in a place like that.
I wasn't talking about you.
-Absolutely not.
-I can count cards.
It's all probability theory and mathematics.
Have you met me? Bottom line,
I know my way around a casino.
-Felicity...
-Oliver, the reason I joined you...
...in the first place was to find Walter.
For the first time,
we have a real chance at finding him.
You have to let me do this.
All right.
But we do it my way.
Come on.
I'm sorry to pull you away
from whomever you were meeting.
Oh, it's nothing.
Everyone's left already.
Besides, it's my fault for forgetting
to sign the K-Fives this morning.
I hope you don't mind me asking,
is everything all right?
Just, uh, taking care of some odds and ends.
-Well, if ever you need a friendly ear.
-You're a good man, Walter.
I thought you'd left.
-I'm still waiting for your answer.
-How can you even think of doing this?
-That place took your soul, Robert.
-And doing this...
...won't give it back.
Won't bring back Rebecca, either.
It still feels like yesterday, that day.
When she called my cell phone for the
first time, I remember being annoyed.
She knew I was busy, so I just let it ring.
When she called back a minute later...
...I shut my phone off.
A little after midnight, two S.C.P.D.
officers showed up at my office.
All I remember them saying was...
...she'd been shot.
Murdered. In the Glades.
After the cops left...
...I sat in my office the rest of the night,
listening to Rebecca's messages.
She kept calling my name.
Asking for help.
Until she was just struggling
to breathe.
Gasping for air.
I listened to my wife die
over and over and over again.
-I can't imagine, Malcolm.
-Try.
Imagine it was Moira lying on
that pavement, bleeding, calling your name.
And then tell me you wouldn't be prepared
to do what I am.
[SIGHS]
What do you want?
Is that any way to treat a girl who
just walked up six flights of stairs?
No, it's not. Where are my manners?
Come on in.
Thank you.
Welcome.
Did you do these?
You know, Felicity, Oliver and I don't need
a relationship counselor.
That hasn't been my experience.
We have a lead on Walter.
I need you to come back
and help us find him.
-Oliver put you up to this?
-No. Heh.
He doesn't even know I'm here.
Look, I know Oliver didn't help you
find your brother's killer...
...and that hurts and that sucks.
But you gotta know if it was your
life on the line and not just your...
...very understandable vendetta,
he would be there for you. No hesitation.
And I don't want a partnership
with those kind of qualifications, Felicity.
Look, I know Oliver's religiously against
admitting he's wrong...
...but the truth is, he needs you.
Yeah.
And when Oliver is ready to say that,
he knows where I live.
[SIGHS]
-Sorry for bothering you.
-It's no bother, I hope you find him.
[ALL CHATTERING]
Wow, you really look like your father.
I never thought so before,
but just now I saw him in you.
What are you doing here?
We need to talk.
-I've said everything I have to say.
-Well, I haven't.
Tommy, I love you,
and I think you still love me...
...so whatever problems you think we have,
I know if we face them together...
-You don't understand.
-Then help me understand.
If our relationship is gonna end,
at least let it end with honesty.
Okay, Laurel.
Honestly...
...you belong with Oliver.
Excuse me?
He's still in love with you.
I have a meeting.
-Are you ready?
-I think so.
The plan is for me to get caught
counting cards in a underground casino...
...filled with hardened criminals.
So you can get a friendly warning
from Alonzo...
...and plant a bug on his office computer.
Right. Which will hopefully lead us
to Walter.
That is, assuming I get the
friendly warning and not a bullet.
-Hey. You don't have to do this.
-Yes. I do.
Okay. If anything happens,
I'm right outside.
Okay. Heh.
-Password?
-Snapdragon.
GREEN ARROW [OVER RADIO]:
The password is Snapdragon.
-Password?
-Snapdragon.
[ALL CHATTERING]
Hi.
GREEN ARROW:
What do you see?
Six armed guards. Two pit bosses.
And a floor man.
No slot machines. How can you call
yourself a casino without lucky sevens?
Stay focused, please.
I'll be with you the entire time.
Thanks.
[FELICITY SIGHS]
It feels really good having you inside me.
And by "you" I mean "your voice,"
and by "me" I mean "my ear."
-I'm gonna stop talking right now.
-That would be my preference.
One stack of high society, please.
Thank you for stopping by.
Of course. Uh, you said you had news.
I do.
It's ready.
The Markov device passed
its final beta test this morning.
Applied Sciences is loading it on a truck
bound for Starling City as we speak.
Well...
...congratulations are in order.
To both of us.
Moira, you may be surprised to know
that I sometimes waver in my convictions.
But your friendship, your endless support,
always gives me the strength to carry on.
After all, you and I
will always have a connection.
I'm just sorry that Robert's not here
to celebrate with us.
I'm sorry I had to take him from you.
If anyone's to blame for his death, it's me.
To Robert.
To Rebecca.
MOIRA:
Are you feeling all right?
I know tonight was just another Ted Kord
fundraiser, but you were surprisingly quiet.
Moira, there's something
I need to talk to you about.
If this is what I think it is,
I don't want to know her name.
No, it's about Malcolm.
He wants to level the Glades.
And how does Malcolm propose
to evacuate an entire section of the city?
He doesn't.
Robert...
...this doesn't sound like you.
Because I'm not the man you think I am.
About a month before the opening
of the steel factory, the one in the Glades...
...I was approached by a local councilman.
He wanted money. He told me that's
the way everything was done in the Glades.
I told him I'd never paid a bribe in my life.
We got into an argument.
I didn't want to hurt him.
I swear, Moira.
But he fell.
Oh, dear God.
-Oh, dear God.
-The work I'm doing with Malcolm...
...with the list...
...it's my penance, Moira.
What, so you'll atone for one murder
by committing hundreds? Thousands?
[MOIRA SIGHS]
Robert, you listen to me.
Whatever wrongs you've committed,
whatever mistakes you've made...
...preventing this horror
is your chance to make it right.
Please.
Please, Robert,
promise me you won't let this happen.
FELICITY: Oh!
-Blackjack!
FELICITY: Ha-ha-ha!
-Wow!
Yes. Ha-ha-ha!
Miss, can you come with me?
-Is something wrong?
-Get up.
Well, since you asked so nicely.
Oh, look, there's the bathroom. Heh.
I should've known the manager's office
would be to the right of the bathroom.
PIT BOSS:
Mr. Alonzo.
Yeah.
Have a seat.
-What's your name?
-Megan.
Do you know where the term "86"
comes from, Megan?
Yes, as it happens, I do.
It's from prohibition.
There was an illegal casino...
...not like this one, located
at 86 Bedford Street in New York and...
-Ah. You know, I'm just gonna stop talking.
-And now it means to ban someone.
Someone who's cheating. You're 86'd.
Leave your chips and go.
Thank you. Thank you.
Oh, yeah, Megan. One more thing.
See, the thing about card counters...
...is, uh, that sometimes they work
with a partner.
[RADIO BEEPS]
You're gonna be really upset
when you meet my partner.
[ALL CHATTERING]
[GUNSHOTS OUTSIDE]
[CROWD SCREAMING]
[MEN SHOUTING]
[SCREAMS]
[GASPS]
-I heard you never miss.
-I don't.
[BEEPS]
[FELICITY GASPS]
[GRUNTING]
Where's Walter Steele?
-What? What are you talking about?
-Six months ago, you had him kidnapped.
It was just a job. I was given a name.
I didn't ask any questions.
Last chance. Where is he?
-Below ground.
-You're lying.
I'm not. I delivered him and they killed him.
I heard the gunshot. He's dead.
Oh, let's see that blouse in a violet shade.
[MOIRA CHUCKLES]
You're a miracle worker, Thea.
Oh, when it comes to shopping,
it's not work, really. Heh.
Hey. Just teaching Mom
the joys of online clothes shopping.
Ollie.
Are you okay?
I need to talk to you both.
What is it?
It's about Walter.
Did the police contact you?
One of Mr. Diggle's army buddies
works for the FBI now...
-...and they got news tonight.
-No.
I'm very sorry.
No, no, no. There must be some mistake.
Who did Mr. Diggle talk to?
-Did they find a body?
-Mom.
-Walter's gone.
-This isn't right.
OLIVER: Where are you going?
MOIRA: Out.
-It's 10:00.
MOIRA: I need some air.
-Mom, you're in shock.
-Don't tell me what or how I feel, Oliver.
Why is she acting like that?
Come here.
[THEA SOBS]
I suspect I know what this is about.
You and I got in bed with Malcolm
to cure what ails this city.
But I think you agree killing thousands
of people is not the answer.
Indeed. If we were to wage a war
with Malcolm Merlyn, we will lose.
My family has already suffered enough.
And I have no desire to endanger mine.
Fortunately, there's another option.
Six months ago, Malcolm started
buying up buildings in the Glades...
...through an off-shore company
called Sagittarius.
He made it sound as if this undertaking
of his was a recent inspiration.
If you're right,
he has been thinking about this for months.
If he can't rebuild it,
he'll abandon the project.
How much of the Glades
does he already have?
About a third.
Now, if we can quietly buy up the rest...
...before he can, he won't be able
to gain the control he needs.
-We will need capital.
-Do you still have your contacts in China?
I already have a flight planned
for Shanghai tomorrow.
-Come with me.
-We shouldn't travel together.
Malcolm might get word.
He already knows I have my doubts.
Besides, I'm getting the urge to take out
theQueen's Gambitfor another voyage.
Dad, do you have any cash?
This jerk pizza guy can't break a hundred.
-Oliver, you remember Mr. Chen?
-Hi.
-Hey.
-Waiting. Thank you.
[POP MUSIC PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
OLIVER:
Pizza.
My hero. I'm starved.
[OLIVER SIGHS]
-Hey, Ollie.
-Yeah?
Where do you keep the bottle opener?
Bottom drawer.
-Did you talk to Ray today?
-About the ski trip?
No. He asked Jean to move in with him
last night.
Oh. Guess they've been together forever.
We've been together longer.
Guess we have.
I only bring this up
because your mom busted me yesterday.
And obviously we can't hang out
at my house...
Why? Because your father threatened
to Taser me...
...the last time I closed the door
to your room?
-Wouldn't it be nice to have a little place?
-Yeah.
Maybe.
This is a little fast, Laurel.
I know that you like to think of yourself
as a bad boy, Oliver Queen...
...but I feel like we're ready
to take the next step.
Yeah.
Let's do it.
[CHUCKLES]
You lied to me. We had a deal.
[SPEAKS IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
-What?
-You promised if I cooperated...
...with the Undertaking,
Walter wouldn't be harmed.
-I'm a man of my word, Moira.
-I think we both know better than that.
And I know...
[MOIRA SIGHS]
I know you've had him killed.
Turn on the camera.
Walter.
MALCOLM:
Like you said, Moira, we have an agreement.
Walter would stay in my custody
until the Undertaking was complete.
[OVER RADIO]
We're both in this together.
I've been sitting in the dark all night too.
All these months, I kept thinking
if I could find a clue or get a lead on him...
I guess it wouldn't have mattered.
I can't imagine what your family's
going through.
Walter's alive.
What?
But Alonzo said...
I need you to pull up
Malcolm Merlyn's phone records.
He made a call from his office to wherever
Walter is being kept at 10:30 p.m.
Malcolm Merlyn? Tommy's father?
Why would he kidnap Walter?
Felicity.
LUDs show he made a call to a tenement
complex located in Blüdhaven.
-Can you pull up a satellite view?
-Uh, yeah.
A lot of security for low-income housing.
There's two guards stationed
at all access points.
Just one on the roof.
Exactly. There's no other buildings
in that area.
If you wanna get onto the roof, you're
going to have to jump off of something.
I've got something.
[GUARD GRUNTS]
There's a problem in Quadrant 4.
[ALL GRUNTING]
[MEN GROANING]
[VOICE MODULATOR BEEPS]
[IN DISTORTED VOICE]
Mr. Steele?
Walter.
[WALTER GRUNTS]
What's happening?
You're going home.
I thought I'd never see you again.
[MOIRA SIGHS]
I'm all right.
Welcome home, Walter.
Thank you, son.
Thea.
[WALTER CHUCKLES]
This is totally a family thing, isn't it?
I'm sorry. Who are you?
This is Felicity. She's my friend.
Mine too. It's good to see you.
You too. Uh, I'll let you guys
get back to your hugging.
[ALL CHUCKLE]
[MOIRA SIGHS]
MOIRA:
Oliver.
We're all together again.
Everything is going to be all right.
MOIRA:
Robert, I don't like the idea of this.
ROBERT: It's gonna be okay.
-How long will you be gone?
A few weeks.
Maybe more, depending on weather.
-Why can't you just fly to China?
-It's better the less you know.
I just hate that stupid boat.
Look at me.
I love you.
-Everything's gonna be fine.
-I know.
Hey.
Got room for one more?
-No, no.
-Mom. Let me keep Dad company.
-Oliver, you're in school.
-Not really.
-I forgot to tell you that.
-I could use an extra hand on the ship.
-Robert.
-Moira, let the kid take the boat out...
...with the old man.
[SIGHS]
All right. All right.
But promise me that you'll behave yourself.
Oh, yeah, I promise.
-I love you so much.
-I love you too.
I totally spaced. I gotta call Tommy and let
him know I'm out of town for a few weeks.
See you onboard in five.
Sara, you here? Ahem.
Yeah, you might wanna
circle around the block a few times...
...because your sister just showed up.
Hi. What are you doing here?
You're leaving for three weeks.
I wanted to come say bye to you in person.
I'm glad you did.
And I wanted to bring you something.
[OLIVER SIGHS]
In case you get lonely oversea.
[CHUCKLES]
Thank you.
Hey, is everything okay?
I mean, I didn't totally freak you out when I
brought up the whole apartment thing, did I?
-No.
-Good.
No.
Mm. But I do have to get back to the boat.
Yeah.
MALCOLM:
Is it done?
FRANK:
Yes.
The bomb is in place.
And there's a storm front moving in
along the Gambit's projected course.
Good.
When the Queen's Gambit goes down...
...no one will suspect it's anything
other than an act of God.
Oliver.
Oh. What a miracle.
How's Walter?
The police are saying
he was rescued by the vigilante.
-Yes, he was.
-Has he said anything about his ordeal?
Was he able to identify any of his captors?
No.
Hmm. That's too bad.
They'll get what's coming to them.
I'm just glad that my family
is back together.
We all are.
LAUREL:
Ollie.
Excuse me.
Is Walter okay? I saw it on the news.
Yeah.
Are you okay?
Of course.
-I promise you, now is not the time.
-Oh.
-It's you and Tommy.
-You and me, actually.
I talked to Tommy,
and the reason he broke up with me...
...is because he thinks that you and I
still belong together.
-What did you say?
-Nothing.
He walked out on me.
I just want you to be happy.
It's what I've always wanted.
Then will you please go talk
to Tommy for me?
And say what?
Say that you and I are over.
That you're not still in love with me.
I can't do that.
Why not?
Because it wouldn't be true.
And I have enough lies in my life already.
[SIGHS]
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
-I guess you do know where I live.
-I've always known where you live.
May I?
I'm sorry.
You were right and I was wrong.
-About Deadshot?
-About everything.
About my mother. And about her
involvement in the Undertaking.
She lied to me.
To Thea.
She's working with Malcolm Merlyn.
And they're planning something.
Something terrible.
I don't know what yet...
...but I just know one thing...
...I need your help to stop them.