My name is Oliver Queen.
After 5 years in hell,
I returned home
with only one goal--
to save my city.
Today, I fight that war
on two fronts.
By day, I lead Star City
as its mayor,
but by night, I am someone else.
I am...Something else.
I am the Green Arrow.
Previously on "Arrow"...
Hi, Ollie.
SCPD!
His name is
Vincent Sobel.
He's my old partner.
We have to find him
before he hurts anyone else.
The police are coming.
You should go.
Will you marry me?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
You're the very
best part of me.
I'm a better human being
just because I've loved you.
No matter what life
throws at us,
our love can
conquer it.
Oliver Jonas Queen,
Felicity Megan Smoak,
I now pronounce you
husband and wife.
Please kiss your bride.
There he is.
Hey, buddy.
Aunt Thea said I can
have some champagne.
I said a sip and only
during the toast.
Mom and dad used to
let us do that.
That--that's just fine.
Yeah, and we turned
out all right.
I think that they
would be pretty impressed
with this party
and the groom.
- Think so?
- Yeah. Of course.
Why? Is
everything ok?
Felicity was supposed
to be here by now, so...
What's there to be nervous
about, Ollie?
You guys are
already married,
and it's not like you invited
anyone but John
to the ceremony.
Well, you were still
in the hospital,
and it was just a little
last-minute, ok?
Yeah. I know,
I know.
- Hey, you.
- Hey.
Lyla apologizes
for not being able to make it.
A.R.G.U.S. missions do
not stop for weddings.
Well, she was hoping
that they would for...this.
Congrats, man.
So where is
the bride?
I don't know.
Donna said that she had
a plan, but I...
♪ and your eyes open ♪
♪ for the first time ♪
♪ and I see that moment ♪
♪ all of my life ♪
♪ and I... ♪
Mom insisted
that we make an entrance
since we didn't have
a traditional wedding,
which I'm sure I'll
never stop hearing about
for the rest of my life.
Welcome
to the family.
- Oh!
- Son! Ha ha ha!
I can call you
that now, right?
- Sure. Yeah.
- Great!
I want you to know
that I have forgiven both
of you for running off
and eloping
and for waiting
to propose
to my daughter
until you were
under indictment.
Oh, actually, Felicity
proposed to me.
Come on, Donna.
Let's let them have their day.
They did have their day,
and we weren't part of it, remember?
I guess she's keeping a tradition
of the Smoak women
not having traditional
weddings.
What are you talking about?
We had a wedding.
No. Getting married
by a Tom Jones impersonating rabbi
isn't exactly traditional.
I thought that you
loved Tom Jones.
No, I don't. You love Tom Jones.
You know what?
At least we had
a Jewish wedding.
Seriously, you guys,
would it have killed you
to get a rabbi
or a chuppa?
I'm gonna steal
Felicity for a moment.
- Oh, yes, of course.
- I'll bring her back.
Just a chuppa.
Those whack jobs are
already your in-laws, so if you're having
second thoughts,
it's too late for you.
I wouldn't have it
any other way.
You really do
love me.
♪ ...Your eyes open ♪
♪ for the first time ♪
♪ so raise your glass
if you are wrong ♪
♪ in all the right ways ♪
♪ all my underdogs ♪
♪ we will never be, never be ♪
♪ anything but loud... ♪
I always knew
you guys would end up together.
- Didn't I say that, honey?
- She did.
Even when I saw on the news
that your engagement was off,
I kept telling this one,
"Adam, Felicity and Oliver
"are meant to be together.
They're going to
work it out."
- Didn't I say that, honey?
- You did.
- I did.
- Well, we're so glad you guys
could make it.
It's great to
see you again.
I'd tell you guys
to move back to Ivy town,
but I guess being mayor of Star City
would make that kind of tough, right?
We love Ivy town,
but Star City is our home.
Best part
about weddings--free booze.
Salud.
Unh. Ahh.
Paul and I had,
um, specialty cocktails made
at our wedding.
The Holtini and the Peach
Paul Sangria.
We also wore
matching white tuxes.
♪ wrong in all
the right ways... ♪
Can I have a glass
of champagne, please?
You ok?
Me? Oh, yeah.
Of course.
Just because I'm
divorced doesn't mean
that I can't handle
celebrating people getting married.
Well, I'm not that
into weddings either.
- Shocker.
- Well, the idea of spending
the rest of your life
with one person seems pretty unrealistic,
and, uh, also
pretty boring.
- Hmm.
- That's probably why I've had
so many busted
engagements.
- Say what?
- What?
- Be right back.
- What? You just gonna leave
on that bombshell--that's
what you're gonna do?
Hmm.
Is it me, or has she
been acting weird lately?
Oh, no. She's definitely
been on Upswipz.
She's been secretly
texting with somebody for weeks now.
Good for her.
You know, maybe you
should start dating, too.
Oh. Heh. Yeah.
I date plenty.
Oh, really. Who?
Hmm. Who? Oh, man.
You know, so-- so many guys.
- Wow.
- There's one guy in particular
who I'm dating.
Uh, his name is...
Dom Perignon.
He is smooth
and expensive,
and he's really nice,
uh, but there's, like, other guys, too.
I'm not trying to be
tied down right now, you know.
I'm trying to live
that single life.
Who? Like, Tom Collins,
Rob Roy?
Not actually
a gin guy.
Congratulations,
Mr. Mayor.
Come on, Quentin.
It's Oliver tonight.
Matter of fact, it's
always Oliver.
Well, I got a, uh--
I got a little something for you, Oliver.
Yeah. I know.
It doesn't look like much--
heh heh--but, uh...
My dad gave that to me
on my wedding day.
Quentin, I can't
accept this.
It's not like I got
anybody I can give it to, is it,
and besides, it's not
right you don't have a parent here tonight.
Thank you. This...
This means a lot.
Thank you.
♪ party rock is
in the house tonight ♪
♪ everybody just
have a good time ♪
♪ and we gonna make
you lose your mind ♪
♪ everybody just
have a good time ♪
♪ party rock is in
the house tonight... ♪
Right here, right here, right here,
right here, right here.
- Oh, my God! I caught it!
- Yes!
No!
♪ We just want to see you ♪
Love.
What is love really?
Oh, boy.
It is not tangible,
so who's to say
it's not just made up?
I mean, there's
no hard-core proof
that it actually exists.
I mean, look.
I love a lot of things--
sweaters, math, coffee,
but, you know,
I'm not gonna
marry that stuff.
What is marriage anyway?
Like, what is it?
Like, is it--it's
a paper that says,
"oh, I'm owed to you
forev"--I don't--no.
I can leave like that,
so what is marriage really
when it boils
down to it?
I have some more stuff
to say.
And everybody give Curtis
a round of applause.
Thank you, Curtis.
Thank you.
Um, I--I think what
my friend is trying to say is,
um, true love is so special
that we all dream about it,
and when I look
at Oliver and Felicity,
I'm reminded of how I felt
about my wife
on our wedding day.
We were so in love.
We would do anything
for each other, I mean, no matter what,
and that is the epitome
of Oliver and Felicity.
Yeah. I mean, you guys have
had your struggles,
but you always work
through it.
These are two of the most
genuine people in the world,
and they deserve
all the happiness,
and I'm so fortunate
to call them my friends,
so please raise a glass
to true love.
Oliver and Felicity.
To Oliver
and Felicity!
It's time now for
the couple's first dance.
♪ At last ♪
♪ my love has come along... ♪
This is only
a courtesy dance
because your speech
was so sweet.
I have
my moments.
You ok?
Yeah. You know, just,
um, thought a friend might have come.
Would have been
nice to see him.
Oh, it's a him?
I'm guessing he's more
than just a friend then.
Weddings make you
nostalgic for the ones you love.
I definitely miss
my wife and my family.
You know, for what
it's worth, I did see
the DJ checking you out.
Oh, no, no.
I don't do DJs.
I had a thing once.
It did not work out.
Can you believe
our daughter is married?
- Oh, my gosh.
- I really can't.
Thanks for letting me
back in her life.
I made a mistake
asking you to stay away.
Seriously. Felicity
needs her father in her life,
and just
for the record,
I think Tom Jones
is actually--
he's pretty good.
- I kind of like him.
- Hey.
- I'm sorry. Is this awkward?
You two
know each other?
No. It's, um--we--I--
Well, then this is
awkward.
I'll go get myself a drink.
Wow. You look, um...
You look really good.
- You mean I look sober.
- Yeah.
I'm sorry. The last
time I saw you, I was in--
You were going
through a nightmare.
Uh, it's Jean Loring.
This is Oliver's lawyer,
and I got to take it.
I-I-I'm sorry.
Oh, yeah. No.
Sure, sure.
I was never the girl
who dreamed about her wedding,
but I have to say
this was the perfect evening.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Uh, so sorry.
We--we got a problem.
I think I
jinxed it.
Come on. Come on.
Ahem.
- What's going on?
- Well, listen.
I really did not want
to do this right now,
but Jean Loring
just called,
and she said I got
to tell you right away.
- It's ok. What's happening?
- I told her you were
in the middle of
celebrating your wedding--
Quentin!
What's going on?
The prosecution's
smoking gun.
It's a witness who is
willing to testify
that you are
the Green Arrow.
- Who?
- Well, that information's
still under seal, but it's
someone on the team.
♪ Arrow 6x09 ♪
Irreconcilable Differences
Original Air Date on December 7, 2017
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
I can't believe
this is happening again.
Hey. Hold on a second.
We do not know
this is an Evelyn Sharpe
situation yet.
It's a betrayal.
I never should have
trusted them.
It's not a them.
It's a one,
a one who wants to
out you to the FBI
that would lock you
away for life.
That's an awfully
long time.
I'd wait for you.
Hey. Just got
your message.
Usually, a bride
and groom like to be
alone on their
wedding night. What's up?
Somebody on the team gave
me up to Samanda Watson.
That's impossible, Oliver.
No one would do that.
Lance got it
from Jean Loring.
Jean Loring got it from
district attorney Armand.
I'm running surveillance
on Curtis, Dinah,
and Rene,
and I have worms
crawling through their texts and e-mails.
- You're spying on them?
- I'm not spying on them.
I'm, like,
keeping tabs.
Oliver, why not just
confront whoever this is
and give them a chance
to come clean?
What makes you think
they're gonna be forthcoming?
How do we know that this
isn't just the--
the surface
of this betrayal?
Look, John. I don't want
to spy on them,
but if you have
a better idea,
I'm all for it.
No.
If someone goes
somewhere suspicious, we'll know.
Felicity, we were all
just at the wedding.
The most suspicious place
they can go is out for late-night pizza.
John, either Curtis,
Dinah, or Rene gave me up.
We need to know why,
we need to know who.
Otherwise, when you
put the hood back on,
you could be next.
All right, all right,
all right.
Where do you want to go,
bathroom or couch?
Hey, hey, hey.
I am perfectly capable
of walking myself--
ohh! Ugh.
No, no. That was not
because I was drunk.
That is just because
I am very clumsy.
Wow. So this is
the dog house. Ruff!
Ha ha! It's actually
way cleaner than I thought it would be.
Oh. You have flowers.
Why do you--why do you have flowers?
Are you seeing some
lady friend or something?
It's not like that.
You know who I am
gonna see when I get
to my place
in the morning?
Some hot dude?
Myself.
In the mirror.
Alone. Heh.
Do you think it was
the vigilantism
that drove Paul away,
or did--did I just lose
my charm or--ugh.
Do you--do you ever
feel like life
would be easier if there
was never a team Arrow?
Only all the time.
You know what, though?
Oliver and Felicity got
their happy ending,
which is all that matters
to Oliver at least.
That's just the booze talking,
Hoss, all right?
I mean, you're gonna
find someone new,
but until then,
you got all of us.
That's what I get
for being nice.
You have to stop
contacting me.
I've done all I'm
willing to do for you.
I'm not here to
ask for a favor.
Then what do you want?
I miss you, D.
That dress
reminds me
of the one you wore
for the Guzman Op.
Don't do that.
Don't try to dip me in nostalgia.
I don't even know who
you are anymore, Vince.
The man I knew
would never,
could never kill
an innocent person.
The people I've killed
weren't innocent.
Oh, no? Well,
what about that cop
you accidentally shot
last month?
- Collateral damage.
- What?
Are you trying to tell me that there
hasn't been any
in the war
the Green Arrow's fighting?
No. No.
There hasn't.
Sounds like I'm
not the only one who's changed.
The Dinah Drake
I knew
was never
this naive.
Oliver brought me back
from a very dark, very bad place.
He stopped me
from becoming you.
The only difference
between him and me
is that I don't lie
to myself about what I'm doing.
Look. I may not
be a Saint,
but I do know this.
I care about you.
I always have
and always will.
Don't contact me.
Leave town,
and if I catch you
out in the field again,
I won't let you get
away a second time.
You didn't have to
walk me all the way home, Quentin.
You know I can take
care of myself.
You are still recovering from
6 months in a coma, Thea.
Let me be a little
overprotective here.
Hello, Thea.
Congratulations on not
being comatose.
Cayden James would like
a word with you.
- Get away from him.
- Thea.
You just got out
of the hospital.
Are you so eager
to go back?
Thea!
Laurel, you ca--uh!
Next time, I'll put you
back into a coma...
Speedy.
- Can we get audio on this?
- No. I tracked her
to this location,
then accessed street cams.
Guess we know how
vigilante escaped the cops last month.
There's no way we can tell
what she's saying to him.
It doesn't matter what
she's saying to him.
She lied to the team.
About this.
- Oliver, listen.
- What else has she lied about?
- Let's not get paranoid here.
- Well, it's not paranoia
if it's
a legitimate fear.
I mean, vigilante
tried to kill Oliver last year.
He wants to out
him to law enforcement,
he's virtually doing
the same thing--it puts him away for life.
Ok. I don't think Dinah
would do this.
She cares way too much
about this team. Oliver, listen.
She--she supported me
through my injury
- and as the Green Arrow.
- I know,
and I appreciate that,
but after what happened
with Evelyn,
we need to protect ourselves.
-Thea? You ok?
-Yeah. I'm fine. I'm fine.
- It's ok.
- Well, what happened?
Evil Laurel.
She took Quentin.
- Oh.
- I tried to stop her, Ollie,
but I--I'm not
strong enough anymore.
It's ok. It's fine.
I'm just--I'm glad you're ok.
Yeah, but how
are you all right?
Not--not that I'm not
glad that you're ok,
but it's not like
evil Laurel to leave loose ends.
She needed
a messenger.
What are the chances
that that's gonna ring, like, right--
Fantastic. That's not
creepy at all.
Hello.
This is Cayden James.
- Where's Lance?
- Now why would I tell you that?
- What do you want?
- A nanoaluminum amplifier.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Well, that's all right.
I'm sure you can
research it,
and when you do,
you'll find that it's secured at A.R.G.U.S.
Deliver it to me
or Quentin Lance dies.
The last time we spoke, you
vowed to destroy the city.
I'm guessing this amplifier gets you
one step closer to completing that goal,
so why should I help you?
I did float the concept
of Mr. Lance dying, didn't I?
Now you listen to me--
At nightfall tomorrow,
I will text an address
to this phone.
You'll be there
with the amplifier,
or Quentin Lance
shuffles off this mortal coil.
Oh, and please don't breathe a word
of this to your friends at A.R.G.U.S.
It's safe
to say there are no good reasons
that Cayden wants
that amplifier.
- It sounds like a trap.
- He has Quentin.
It doesn't matter.
He has leverage.
Can you and Curtis make
a--a replica of this thing,
a fake to pass off
to Cayden James?
No. I mean, we're good,
but we're not that good. It's one of a kind.
Isn't this guy some type
of genius hacker?
He knows it's at A.R.G.U.S.
why doesn't he just hack in there himself?
A.R.G.U.S. is 100%
air-gapped.
I mean, you can't
access their network unless you're on site,
and I doubt he wants
to cross paths with A.R.G.U.S.
Since they held him
prisoner for 8 months.
He's using us instead.
A.R.G.U.S. isn't just
gonna hand over this amplifier.
They have a longstanding
policy of not negotiating with terrorists.
- Let's bring in Curtis and Rene.
- No Dinah?
Until we know where
her loyalties lie, she's out.
Oh, Dan, I can't
tell you how much I appreciate this favor.
I know it's not exactly protocol
letting me in here,
but I wanted to
leave this little surprise for Lyla
for when she
gets back.
Not letting protocol
get in the way of romance.
Yeah. Well, thanks
for helping keep the flame alive.
I, uh--I forgot
my card.
It's back at security.
I'm an idiot. I'll go get it.
No, no. I'll grab it.
Don't need everyone
to see you roaming
around without clearance.
Good idea.
Overwatch.
You're up.
Talk to me.
Ok, you guys. I'm working
on locating the amplifier.
Just stand by.
Oh. Ok, you guys. I got it.
It's in the east wing.
I'll shut down security
when I access the panel.
Does everybody copy?
In position.
Still don't understand
why the brown guys
got to be
the janitors, though.
Janitor is a very
honorable profession.
They clean up after
you puke, which is something I might
do very soon.
- Why the hell isn't Dinah here?
- Is it possible that
she could be more
hungover than I am?
Definitely not.
Guys, focus.
Overwatch, I'm in position.
How long until security
is down?
That depends on Curtis.
We're clear. Ohh.
Also, leaning over-- not a great decision.
You are not
throwing up.
I'm already spending
my honeymoon in a garbage can.
- I'm not wearing your puke!
- You slapped me.
Oliver, I can only
buy you 60 seconds
before the security
around the amplifier turns back on.
That's more than enough
time for me.
The floor is
still pressure sensitive.
If you touch it, it will
retrigger the alarm.
Roger that.
On your count.
3, 2, 1. Go.
Almost there.
Guys, you're about
to get company.
We need more time.
Ahh. Sorry.
I got it. Clear in 3, 2, 1.
Got it.
Come on.
How you guys doing, huh?
Good news is this
is exactly what Cayden wanted.
- Bad news is it's--
- Exactly what Cayden wanted.
- Yeah.
- At least, now we know what
he's gonna use
it for.
What? He didn't want to
supercharge his Christmas lights?
Remember that thermobaric
bomb that Cayden stole?
Well, this will
multiply the blast radius 20-fold easily.
That's the entire
city and then some.
Look. I want to save
Lance as much as anyone,
but he wouldn't
want this.
I mean, he wouldn't want
us to just hand over
something so dangerous
to some psycho.
Yeah? Well, that's
exactly what we're going to do.
- Curtis is gonna sabotage it.
- Curtis is gonna do what, now?
The amplifier doesn't
have to work.
We just need Cayden James
to think that it works
long enough for us
to get Quentin back.
I could back-channel
a path into the circuitry.
If you hide it behind
the existing board,
it might buy us enough time to get Lance,
get the hell out of there.
Hey.
Did you guys just get
back from the field?
Why didn't I get a call?
We should speak
in private.
That's a bit dramatic,
don't you think?
Ok. Ahem. I know that
you've been meeting
with the vigilante
in secret.
- You followed me?
- I did.
Whatever business
I have with Vince is none of yours.
It is when it threatens
to put me in prison
and keep me away
from my son.
What the hell are
you talking about?
I'm talking about being
arrested off the statement
of someone who knows
my identity,
somebody on this team.
And you think it was me?
What, because I didn't tell you about Vince?
I think you have given me
no reason to trust you.
Pfff.
And you?
What about you?
You don't trust me
either, John?
Dinah, I'm sorry.
Wow.
No. Uh, no, no. Hey.
I'm the sorry one.
Yeah, I'm...
I'm the sorry one
for having your back
all those times.
- Screw you guys.
- I'm not finished.
- I am!
- Hey. Guys, can we--
can we all just please
calm down for a second?
Look. I know everyone's
stressed because
Cayden's threatening to
blow up the city
and Lance is kidnapped,
but let's just--all
just take a breath.
Now, I'm not saying
that it's me,
but it can literally be
any one of us.
Dinah, you were
the only one with something to hide.
Everyone else
checked out.
- What does that mean?
- Yeah.
What does that mean,
John?
It means we had
you under surveillance.
- What? All of us?
- Yeah.
And by all of us,
you mean all of us.
So just the newbies.
We're out there risking
our lives just like the rest of you are!
Stop.
Dinah isn't
the witness, Oliver.
- You don't know that.
- Yes, I do
because it's me.
I'm the one who's
testifying against you.
Agent Watson came to me.
She said she had proof
that I was Wild Dog
and that she was gonna
use it against me
to make sure that I
never saw Zoe again.
She said she had
a solid case against you
and that she was
gonna arrest you either way.
You were going down.
I just couldn't make
the trip with you.
You should have
told us, Rene.
We could have figured
something out.
There was nothing
to figure out, Hoss.
Right? There is
no other way.
Yeah.
Now we'll never know.
Rene...
Get out.
Oh, good. You're awake.
I wanted us
to have a little daddy-daughter time.
Because of what
happened on Lian Yu?
You make it sound
like I should be over it by now.
You shot me and left
me for dead.
You seem to have
bounced back.
Yeah. Thanks
to Cayden James.
He sent someone
for me.
I'm sorry. I made
a mistake shooting you.
I'm glad you're ok.
Heh. Then you're
an idiot.
Heh. You're probably
right.
You're probably right.
Listen. When you, uh--
when you look at me,
do you see your own
father at all?
No.
Because my father died
when I was 13.
What happened?
It was my 13th birthday,
and he left to go get my birthday cake,
like he did every year,
and then
the phone rang.
There was an accident.
A drunk driver ran
through a red light.
Head-on collision.
I'm sorry.
I used to pick up
Laurel's cake, too,
yellow with
chocolate frosting,
from her favorite
bakery.
Carlye's.
Sorry you didn't get to
know your father.
I guess you're
stuck knowing me.
Ok. It's time.
Remember, if Green Arrow
reneges on our deal, you kill him.
How can you
eat this?
You ask me that
every time.
He means
at a time like this.
Stress makes me hungry.
So does guilt.
I just--I screwed up.
You know, Oliver was
right to kick me off the team.
You were in
an impossible position.
Yeah, and when
you're in an impossible position,
that's why there's
a team, D.
Just like Dig said.
You're uncharacteristically
quiet, Hoss.
Just hungover,
doing some processing.
I'm actually doing
a lot of processing.
Oliver spying on us,
you mean?
Not gonna pretend there's not a difference
between the three of us
and the three of them,
you know, the original 3, but--
Spying on us?
I mean, come on.
- It crosses a line.
- Yeah,
and I just don't like
the way that it makes me feel.
Now I'm stressed.
Wow. It's good.
It's real good.
- Hey.
- Hi.
Felicity told me
what happened.
- Yeah.
- Would ask if you're ok,
but I think I already
know the answer.
Thinking
about what Rene did.
What did he do really?
He kept a secret,
and he--he put his daughter
ahead of the team.
And I feel betrayed.
How can I feel
betrayed
by somebody doing
the exact same things that I've done?
Because you've never
sold anyone out on the team, Ollie,
and if you're convicted,
you could end up spending
a really long time
in jail.
But having said that,
you're doing
the right thing, looking
at things through his
perspective,
and having done that,
maybe you can see
your way to
forgiving him.
Seriously?
Well, Rene is a--
a very desperate guy
who just did
a very desperate thing,
but he's also the same guy
who just last night
was giving such
a heartfelt, sweet speech
and--and calling
you his friend,
and I really think
that he meant that.
It was a betrayal,
no question,
but since you've been
able to see things from his point of view,
you...You should also
be able to see your way to forgiving him.
Listen to you.
Quentin needs the team
right now, Ollie,
but he needs
the whole one.
It's almost nightfall.
Let's have the team
suit up.
John...
The whole team.
Copy that.
Thanks for having me
back, man.
Let's get our
friend back.
This is where Cayden James wants
to make the exchange?
Yep. It's a no-brainer
he picked this place.
It's a digital black hole.
There's no cameras,
insulated walls.
Once you guys get inside,
I'm totally blind.
But that means
so is he.
- Get the amplifier working?
- I hope so
because otherwise
we'd be handing
a crazy psychopath
the means to crater the entire city.
I mean yes.
Yes, it's ready.
I will handle the exchange.
You 3 be my eyes and ears.
The priority
is extracting Quentin,
but if we get a chance to take Cayden
James into custody, we take it.
Whatever we're going through,
whatever issues we have,
let's put it aside
and get the job done.
- Agreed?
- Agreed.
Agreed.
Ok. Let's go.
So we meet again.
Where's Lance?
Oh, somewhere handy.
I'll be taking that
amplifier now.
You will be telling me
where Lance is.
A fair request.
Equally fair, lay
down your bow.
I'll let you speak
with him.
I am a man of my word.
If I wasn't, there
wouldn't be much point
in vowing to destroy
this city, would there?
We can't see anything
from up here.
Let's search
the building.
Green Arrow said stay put
until he makes the exchange.
What? We're--we're
his eyes and ears,
and we can't
even look around?
Guys, we need
you as backup.
Well, maybe if you bugged
Lance like you bugged us,
we'd know where he was.
Whoa. We didn't bug
you guys.
We tracked your GPS.
It's totally different.
- Bugging me now.
- You know I can hear you
through Wild Dog's comms.
You know that, right?
Screw it. I'm not gonna
sit around here
and wait for Oliver
to decide to trust us again.
See? Wasn't
that easy?
Are you all right?
Yeah, yeah. I'm fine.
Accommodations could be nicer,
but, yeah, I'm fine.
Yeah? Well, sit tight.
- I'll be there soon.
- Yeah. Just don't compromise
the city's safety
for me, all right?
Now there's a dedicated
civil servant.
I wish there were
more like him.
Proof of life
as requested.
Your turn now, I think.
Take what you wanted.
I think not.
You see, what I wanted
was a nanoaluminum
amplifier,
one that hasn't been
sabotaged.
He knows. That makes no sense.
How could he know?
I'm disappointed,
though not nearly as much,
I imagine, as your
friend, Mr. Lance.
Kill him.
And kill him.
Team, everything's
gone south.
Back up Green Arrow!
Wild Dog, terrific,
where are you guys?
- We're on our way.
- On your way?
Why weren't you
in position?
Haven't got time
for that now, Hoss.
We've got eyes
on Lance.
Ugh!
Unh!
James is gone.
His men are down.
Where the hell is
everybody?
I've got Lance and Laurel.
They're exiting
the north side
of the building.
I'm on my way.
Laurel's getting
away with Lance.
And we've got
company.
- Ok. One last stop.
- Ugh.
Run.
Laurel.
- You all right?
- Yeah.
Thanks for coming
to get me.
- Can I get a sitrep?
- Is everyone ok?
Yeah. We're good here.
How's Lance?
He's fine.
Sleeping it off.
Any sign of Cayden James
or Black Siren?
Nada. They're completely
off the grid.
But we got
Quentin back.
That was
the objective, right?
Right. You and Rene were
supposed to be backup.
Where'd you go?
We were looking
for Lance,
and from what I
can tell, we found him.
Moving off of
your position, was that
your call or Curtis'?
Look. I was
right there beside--
It was my call,
and it turned out
to be the right one.
You got lucky, Rene.
Doesn't make it the right call.
Look, man. I know
you're pissed at me,
and I don't care
because you left us
blind out there,
and I wasn't gonna
let Lance die
just because you
didn't trust us enough
to go off leash
and look for him.
When we are in the field,
there is a clear
chain of command
plain and simple.
I've been the same guy
tonight that I've always been
since you brought me
onto this team.
Rene, yes, that's true.
You have--sometimes,
you go your own way.
- That's right.
- And I put up with it
because I trusted you.
What's that supposed
to mean?
You got a second chance
tonight, my friend,
and you broke
our trust again.
You don't get a third.
- You're off the team.
- Just like that?
Just like that.
It's been real, y'all.
Yeah, I hate to say it,
but Oliver is right.
We're a team. We need to--
we need to trust each other,
need to believe
in each other.
I don't
believe in you anymore.
- Dinah.
- Don't.
It's too late.
I'm out, too.
Guess we should both
be glad I didn't
leave town
like you said.
Oh, thanks. That's
really what I needed right now,
an "I told you so."
You ok?
You don't look it.
I don't really want
to talk about it.
Then why'd you
reach out?
Because I had no one
else to call.
I'll try not to be
insulted by that.
I really needed someone
who believed in me.
I needed a friend.
Friends.
I can do that.
Sunflowers!
My favorite!
Well, I wanted it
to feel like home.
I'm not gonna have
to leave again, am I?
Hey. I won't let anyone
split us up ever again.
I promise.
I'm just gonna say this.
I don't think there's
anything that has been
said or done that can't be undone.
I don't think
I agree, John.
I agree with Felicity.
We need to move forward.
Sorry I'm late.
Um, I think I
probably might
still be a little hungover.
I've also been
thinking about a few things.
Oliver, you and
Dinah were right.
No trust, no team.
You all spied on me,
invaded my privacy.
Whether you couldn't
trust me or not,
it means that
I can't trust you.
Curtis, what's
that supposed to mean?
I'm still a part
of Helix Dynamics, Felicity.
That's separate,
but this...
I'm done.
Ahem. Like I said,
we need to move forward.
- Oliver.
- Cayden James knew that we
sabotaged the amplifier
last night.
We need to find out how.
When you had me raid their bunker
and plant that minicam two months ago...
Is this the outcome
I had in mind?
Quite so, Ms. Lance,
although I must confess,
things have worked out
even better than
I anticipated.
Hardly impressive.
Left to his own devices,
Oliver Queen will always
push away those closest to him.
So we've got them
fighting with each other
instead of fighting us.
Please tell me
that isn't your whole master plan.
Oh, not at all,
Mr. Diaz.
In fact, I think it
fair to say that this...
Is only the beginning.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man