My name
was Oliver Queen.
For three years,
I worked to save my city.
But to save my sister,
I had to become someone else.
I had to become
something else.
Previously, on "arrow"...
Roy's alive.
We faked his death.
He's starting
a new life.
John.
Oliver?
Bring Nyssa
to the warehouse
at Fullerton
and Halstead...
and I'll let your wife go.
There's no way
I'm getting him back.
He's gone, Felicity. There's only thing
left of him now--us.
Do you recognize this?
The Alpha and Omega
bioweapon.
You will unleash this
on Starling City.
His fever
is getting worse!
Maseo!
A pharmacy!
The Romans
call it "vastatio."
The systemic destruction
of a land to insure its subjugation.
And what they found was
that immolation left
a blank slate to build anew.
Until you have
destroyed your home
and severed all ties
from your old life,
can you begin anew.
I did not foresee the day
that Maseo Yamashiro
appeared at my door.
You had the courage
to demand
an audience of me.
And those who do
usually offer money and treasure
in exchange
for my favor.
But you gave me
the Alpha and Omega.
The plane is en route.
It will be ready tomorrow,
as you've commanded.
You will marry my daughter,
and you will ascend
to Ra's al Ghul,
and then you will
fly to Starling City
carrying death itself.
♪ Arrow 3x22 ♪
This Is Your Sword
Original Air Date on May 6, 2015
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
I hate when they run!
Well, at least you're getting
your cardio workout in.
I still have 40 minutes
on an elliptical
in my immediate future.
You supposed to be
undercover or something?
I sniffed you
three blocks back.
You led me right
to your gang.
Smart plan.
Thanks.
No, I meant smart plan...
Because it was mine.
John, I think he gives up!
John!
Thanks for coming in
through the back.
With Sara and Lyla
gone, the last thing I need
are the neighbors
talking.
About some strange woman
dressed in all black leather,
Yeah.
You're out of ice.
How can you be out of ice?
Here.
Thanks.
Ok, so the night's young,
and there's a meth dealer
working a corner on Fulton.
Sounds good.
Actually, it doesn't.
You were completely unhinged
out there tonight, Dig.
You're in denial
about how angry you are.
No, Felicity,
I'm not in denial.
But I am angry!
Oliver.
He was my best friend.
And he kidnapped...
my wife.
And you think that justifies
hospitalizing people?
No, Felicity,
it doesn't,
you're right.
It won't happen again.
I'm not saying that
life doesn't suck right now,
but you can't go around the city
taking it out on every criminal you see.
How can you, out of all people,
be so sanguine
after what happened
last week?
Because I know
that that wasn't Oliver.
Now who's in denial?
It wasn't!
Our Oliver, my Oliver,
died the day
he joined the League.
This is someone else!
You truly believe that?
I have to.
Don't try to talk me
out of going.
Mr. Harper went through
a lot of trouble to fake his death.
You know he can never
come back here.
Yeah, well, maybe
I'm just going to go there.
Permanently?
Look, I don't know.
Honestly, I--I don't
know anything anymore.
I barely know who I am.
Thea, it's
understandable.
You've been
through something
very few people have
ever experienced.
Of course you feel--
Is that what you think
this is all about?
Almost dying?
Because I'd rather have died
than have my brother
sacrifice his life for mine.
And don't think for a second
that I forgot the whole reason
Ra's al Ghul was brought into our lives
is because of you.
You're no longer
in danger from the League.
Maybe getting away
from Starling City for a while
is--is what's
best for you.
You approve?
Is that supposed
to worry me?
'Cause it actually
kind of does.
Look, the only thing
I know right now...
Is that I need
to go be with Roy.
My daughter.
I am not hungry.
Ah, yes.
Many a bride has skipped
a meal or two before their wedding day.
I would rather die
than wed this pretender.
Well, you speak as though they are
the only two options
before you,
my daughter.
Daughter.
And to think, I once wore
that title with pride.
Perhaps "mother"
will suit you better.
After your betrothal
to Al Sah-him,
you will extend my lineage by having
a child of your own.
If you think I will
bear his child--
Yes! I do.
And you will have no more say in it
than your mother was given.
You're quiet.
I'm prepared for my
ascension to Ra's.
But I'm still...
coming to grips
with marriage.
Perhaps a walk
to clear my head.
I will send a guard
to accompany you.
If I can't
protect myself,
I don't deserve to
inherit your mantle.
You're late.
Sorry.
Nanda Parbat's not exactly
the easiest place to infiltrate.
Don't joke!
Things are worse
than we thought.
Tomorrow?
Ra's plans to transport
the virus to Starling
on a plane.
That is oddly modern
for the League.
Do you think
Ra's suspects you?
He has no reason to.
I warned you it
would be difficult.
I just thought that I'd--
ahem--we'd have more time,
when you explained to me
that my ascension to Ra's
would include
the destruction of Starling.
I anticipated you wouldn't be
Ra's for months.
More than enough time to dismantle
the League from the inside.
Malcolm, we need help.
From all accounts,
you were...
too good at convincing
your friends
that you'd allied
yourself with Ra's,
and I don't think
I carry much credibility with them.
I know someone
who they'll trust.
You've been
gone a while.
There was concern.
I've just been here thinking.
We need to find
ibuprofen!
You know that
can't help him now.
Why isn't the inoculant
working on him?!
He's young. His immune system
probably isn't strong enough.
Akio!
Swallow.
Okaasan...Boku kowaiyo.
Shinitaku naiyo...
♪ Nennen korori yo ♪
♪ okorori yo ♪
♪ boya wa yoi ko da ♪
General Shrieve...
Maseo. I want to
kill Shrieve, too,
but you need to focus
on helping Akio!
Shrieve's men
made a vaccine.
Maybe they also made a cure.
No, Maseo, they
didn't make a cure!
I know it's unlikely,
but I have to try.
Ok.
I'll help you.
Hi, I'm looking for Jason.
Oh, yeah?
Well, lucky him.
Yo, Jason.
Got a visitor.
Jason?
That's right.
I have a '67 Mustang that
needs a little work on it.
Somebody said you were
the guy to see.
You came
to the right place.
I can't believe
you're still alive.
Look, I wanted to tell you,
but if you knew,
you'd tell Oliver.
And then Oliver
would have...
Would have broken
you out of prison.
Yeah.
And probably
kicked your ass.
And I would have
helped him.
I had to do it.
For Oliver.
Do you think there's maybe
some other place
we can go talk?
There's my place.
That's such
a good answer.
Hey.
You got it to fly.
What more do you want?
Well, true art
is never finished,
it's only abandoned.
Plus, I had this
little idea I just couldn't kick.
You ok?
You have this
little cloud
that keeps
following you around.
Yeah.
Well, something
happened while you were away,
and...I'm just
handling it.
Is it, uh,
Oliver-related?
It's Oliver-related.
If you want
to talk about it...
Maybe we shouldn't
cross that line.
It's a long story, anyway.
Well, if you change
your mind, I have time.
And, hey...
you're my friend.
I'm always going
to be there for you.
It's non-negotiable.
Thanks, Ray.
So, while I'm waiting to do
something for you,
there's a little something that
you can do for me.
Sign...here
and here.
Ok.
Right.
What's this for?
Just a little
corporate stuff,
Miss Vice President.
Mm-hmm.
Everything ok?
Probably not.
You've been quiet.
I have a lot on my mind.
I meant
about the virus.
The Alpha Omega.
When did you take it?
From the truck.
Before
we blew it up.
So before...
Even before
Akio died,
I wanted revenge
on Shrieve
for the pain
he caused.
But instead, you used it to trade
your way into the League.
I am not strong.
Not enough for myself,
and certainly not
enough for Tatsu.
If you could go back
to her, would you?
That is immaterial.
Maseo Yamashiro
is no more.
He doesn't have to be.
When I'm Ra's, I can
release you from your oath.
I can set you free.
The League
is not my prison.
From my prison...
There is no escape.
So now Malcolm Merlyn
can summon us.
I really don't like the idea
that he can summon us.
Any idea what this is about?
No, but Merlyn assures me that
he'll be waving the white flag.
I'm sorry.
I forgot the flag.
That's too bad. I would have told you
where you can put it.
What is this about, Malcolm?
Well, this isn't going
to be easy for all of you to believe--
Only because
you're a sociopath and a liar.
Be that as it may,
this will be much quicker
for all of us if we can fast forward
through the cynicism
and reach the conclusion
that I am telling you the truth.
About what?
Oliver.
His allegiance with the League
is a charade.
Why would you even begin to play with
our emotions like that?
This plan was
born the moment Oliver realized
that he had to capitulate
to Ra's to save Thea.
And instead
of sharing this plan
with us,
he trusted you?
The man who
had my sister murdered.
Well, I am better
practiced in the art of deception.
And no offense,
none of you are
particularly good actors.
I'm out.
You've seen for yourselves
how dangerous Ra's
and the League are.
The circle of trust
had to remain as small as possible.
Until now?
What changed?
Forget it, Felicity.
There's nothing he can
say that we can believe.
Mr. Diggle's right.
Which is why
I brought along
a friend of Oliver's.
My name is Tatsu Yamashiro.
And your city
is in great danger.
You expect us
to believe her?
We never even met her.
We never met her, right?
No.
Apart from my brief time
helping Oliver
recover from the wounds
Ra's al Ghul inflicted on him,
my life has been
one of...isolation.
Ok, Merlyn, this is
your big plan?
A woman that we've never met
or even heard of?
Oliver doesn't like
to speak about the past.
Apparently, he's not so forthcoming
about the present, either.
My son was killed by the virus
Ra's intends to use
on your city.
Are you--you're
Akio's mother?
Oliver was with me
en it happened.
He knows that the danger
you all face is very real.
Ok, you know what,
how many times are we going
to believe him after
everything that he's done?
I am not privy
to your history with Malcolm.
This request
comes from Oliver.
We're not sure
that's any better at the moment.
Look, I am not
playing a game here.
My daughter lives
in this city, remember?
This is everything I have
on the bioweapon.
I've arranged passage
for all of us to go to Nanda Parbat.
If you're coming...
be at Ferris Air
before sunrise.
Charming.
It's a sublet. I won't
be here for much longer.
What about
the auto shop?
It's...temporary.
Sure, they don't ask
a lot of questions,
but it's inevitable someone
puts two and two together.
How about your
other night job?
I figured I'd just leave
the crime fighting to the cops.
I kind of just want
to be normal.
Yeah? And how's that
going for you?
I am so bored.
Yeah, well,
that's why
I brought you this.
Malcolm stole it
out of impound.
Don't worry--I made him promise
nobody would get killed.
I never thought I'd see
this thing again.
I figured since everybody
thinks that
Roy Harper
is the Arrow,
They don't have to know
that he's Arsenal, too, right?
Hmm.
So that's why you came here?
Just to give me this?
Well...yes, this.
And...
How could we not
know about this?
How could anyone not know about
a terrorist attack in Hong Kong?
Because Beijing had us believing
that these deaths were caused
by a local chemical spill.
You don't really
believe Merlyn?
Well, looking at this, we can't
afford not to believe Merlyn.
He is a mass murderer
who has lied to us so many times
it should be
a drinking game.
And I have never
even heard of this Tatsu person.
Felicity, I don't know
if you're right
that Oliver's gone
forever or not.
The truth is, for me,
it doesn't matter.
If there's even a possibility of this
kind of danger in my city,
I'm reporting for duty.
Me, too.
I don't believe them.
And even if I did,
I can't go back there.
Not after what they did
to Oliver.
Relax, my child.
Another order
I cannot follow.
You speak to me
as though I'm a monster.
I'm your father,
Nyssa.
Then why do you ask me
to marry someone I do not love?
When I was in a desert
tending to some affairs,
I crossed paths
with a woman.
She was breathtaking
in her visage
and fortitude.
Her name
was Ameena Raatko.
I had taken
other lovers before,
but she was different.
She had a wit
and a fire about her
that I found myself
I could not live without.
So she became my concubine
and the mother of my child.
This was my gift to her
in honor of you.
A gift that she gave me.
And so I kept it
in the hopes that one day,
you would wear it
on your wedding day.
You expect me to marry Al Sah-him
because of some trinket?
I expect you to marry
Al Sah-him
because it is my will.
You defy that,
and I will
see you suffer the pain
of a thousand deaths.
I am sorry
to intrude.
Mr. Merlyn said that
I would find you here.
That might be the only
thing he's ever said that isn't a lie.
I did not come here
to convince you
of the threat to your home.
There's nothing I can say
that you will believe,
more than what you have seen.
Then why
are you here?
To speak with you
about Oliver.
During his recuperation,
Oliver spoke of you.
Of how his last thought
before the fall
was of you.
You love him...still.
Oliver belongs
to Ra's now.
If you believe that,
you must fight for him.
There is no
"him" left.
I thought as you do once.
My husband, Maseo,
was consumed by
the League's darkness.
I was so convinced
that he was lost to me
that I didn't even try
to reach him.
Don't make my mistake...
Felicity.
Are you sure
Shrieve will be here?
Do you know of any other rogue
U.S. army bases in the area?
Shrieve will have
reinforced the station
since the last time
we were here.
Two there.
Waller took you
from Lian Yu
because she saw
something in you.
My son needs that from you.
The killer inside.
Sir, this is
a restricted area.
Is that
a Masamune blade?
A katana.
Passed on for centuries
within my family.
The first son
of each generation.
You are not
a son, Tatsu.
No, I am not.
Let's get this
over with.
The plane's ready;
It should be big enough for all of us.
Including her.
Thought
you weren't coming.
I changed my mind.
But if you betray us,
I'll make sure the whole world knows
that you are alive,
and where they can find you.
So this
is Nanda Parbat.
Next time, we should
really look into getting some horses.
You think they rent
horses here?
There won't be a next time.
There it is.
The plane Ra's
intends to use
to spread the Alpha
Omega over Starling.
I need to be within
50 yards to breech the plane's
internal mainframe
and navigation software,
but then I should be able to remote
ground the thing.
Quiet.
I don't see anything.
There'll be more.
Get to the plane.
We'll cover you. Go!
Close enough.
Surrender now,
and you might live.
Maseo.
Maseo is a memory.
Our child was gone,
and you left me when
I needed you most.
But you can still
come back to me.
It's not too late.
Yes, it is.
You know I wouldn't
have done the same thing for you.
I know.
Your husband is long dead.
If Sarab must die as well,
then so be it.
Oh, frack!
More frack!
Oh. That makes
more sense.
Can you bring it
down from the sky?
They destroyed my gear,
but I had some insurance come along.
What kind
of insurance?
The atomic kind.
Ray!
Ohh. You should see
the other guy.
Tell Akio...
I love him.
You tell him for both of us.
Thank you...
for releasing me...
from my prison.
♪ Nennen korori yo ♪
♪ okorori yo ♪
♪ boya wa yoi ko da ♪
♪ nenne shina ♪
Enough!
You have failed.
Any further attempt to undermine
our cause would be futile.
Uh, you see that burning
plane over there?
We destroyed your
city threatening bioweapon.
No.
You merely think you did.
Surrender!
Or die.
Hey.
Oliver. Oliver,
what's going on?
If any of you speak,
we're all going to die.
What...?
I need you to trust me.
Chinese have a saying.
Stir the grass,
and you stifle
the snake.
My ruse with the plane was
meant to reveal
any traitors among me.
How did you know
of the virus?
Of the plane?
Maseo told me,
and I told them.
So a dead man told you.
How convenient.
He said only three men
knew about your plan.
You, him, and Oliver.
Oliver Queen is dead.
I am Al Sah-him.
This would not be
the first time
that Sarab has
betrayed me
to Maseo Yamashiro's
weaknesses.
And though your timing
was a function of my gambit,
it was nevertheless
fortuitous.
You see, by tradition,
Ra's would contemplate mercy
upon his enemies
on the eve of a wedding.
You are
getting married?
I guess there really is
a kettle for every pot.
The wedding is mine.
I am betrothed
to Nyssa al Ghul.
Take them below.
So can you
tell me now?
Tell you what?
What you're really
doing here?
What, seeing you
is not good enough?
What's going on?
Something happened.
I was hurt.
And...
to save me, Ollie...
had to accept Ra's offer
to join the League.
Oh, my God.
Thea...
I tried to stop him.
I--I couldn't, and...
Now he's become
someone else.
Everything just slips away
when I'm with you.
I understand that.
But?
When bad things happen,
your go-to move is to bolt.
To get out
of Starling.
I don't think
this is something
you can
run away from.
I'm not running away.
Running to you.
Do you not want me to?
The only thing
that I want
is what's best for you.
You always have.
Come here.
Mmm.
I can't believe
he's going to marry her.
You should worry more about getting
out of here alive.
Is that even
a remote possibility?
Didn't think so.
We aren't going
to die here.
Oliver would never
let that happen.
He let this happen.
Wareeth al Ghul
commands your presence.
Leave us.
Is everyone ok?
Like you give a damn!
Didn't Malcolm speak to you?
He did.
So was a part of your plan
to leave my daughter alone
when you kidnapped my wife?
I had to do something
to prove
my loyalty to Ra's.
So taking Lyla?
That was your idea, Oliver?
In front of our daughter?!
Yes.
You met Tatsu.
What does that have
to do with anything?
Tatsu told me...
that in order
to beat Ra's,
I would have
to sacrifice
all of the things in my life that I
hold most precious.
And your friendship
is on that list.
Oliver, you didn't just...
lose my friendship.
You lost my trust.
You lost my respect.
What?!
Ra's demands
that we return
this man
to his friends.
Give us the cure.
You boys make
quite the entrance.
The cure! Now!
The Chinese own enough
of our national debt
to decimate our economy,
and all without
firing a shot.
Or, they could destroy us
with the largest army
in human history.
Enough!
My son needs your cure.
What makes you think--
The next one
goes in your head.
You see that safe
over there?
The passcode is 4587.
He'll have to deliver
the cure subcutaneously,
in the exact ratio
I give you.
You may want
to write this down.
You don't
need to tell us.
You're coming with us.
This is so
beautiful...
and yet so dangerous.
Much like
its former owner.
Sarab's former love,
who's now
my prisoner,
along with Al Sah-him's
former friends.
You see, their treachery
was anticipated.
Yours, however, Al Sa-Her,
is disappointing.
Because I expected
more loyalty
from a man whose
daughter I saved.
The last time I appeared
before you in chains,
I offered my fealty,
and I am here
to offer it again.
You had nothing
to offer then,
and you have nothing
to offer now.
I have the name
of the person
who betrayed you
to Al Sah-him's friends.
It wasn't Maseo Yamoshiro.
It was Oliver Queen.
He's been
lying to you all along.
What's this?
I'm sorry, Oliver.
My name is Al Sah-him.
Not according to Mr. Merlyn here.
You see, he claims
that you've been
deceiving me the entire time.
I have killed
for you.
I have severed all
ties to my past.
I have hurt people
who were friends to Oliver Queen,
and if you hadn't
have stopped me,
I would have murdered your daughter
at your command.
But what if this is all
just part of your own
elaborate ruse?
Then I will have nothing
and no one to go home to.
Oliver Queen is dead,
and the Arrow
is gone.
We shall see.
Roy?
Excuse me, I'm,
uh, looking for--
Jason's friend,
yeah, I remember.
He said you probably
would be stopping by.
Oh. Can I talk
to him?
I don't know where he is.
He came in an hour ago to quit.
He, uh, said
to give you this.
Dear Thea, I wasn't supposed
to make it this far.
I was supposed to end up
in jail or dead by now.
But then I met you, and you made me
want to be the man
I saw through your eyes.
And now all I want to do
is give that back;
help you be the person
you can be without Oliver,
without your father,
and without me.
Living on the run
from the police
isn't the life
you deserve, Thea.
It's not what Oliver
gave up his life for you to have.
Whatever happens with me,
I'll always love you.
P.S.--Thanks for the suit,
but I always thought red
was more your color, anyway.
So what did
Oliver say to you?
Nothing worth hearing.
You were right
about Oliver.
I should have
listened to you.
I told you about Oliver.
You were supposed to--
I was supposed to do
what, Mr. Merlyn?
Grant you mercy?
I am.
Because this death will be
a lot shorter
than the one I had
planned for you.
You--
Oliver, if what Malcolm
said is true,
if you're going to do anything,
now is the time!
Al Sah-him has said that
the swordswoman is inoculated,
so you can take her
to another chamber.
No! Oliver!
Oliver,
we believed in you!
Seal the room.
You're not listening.
Oliver!
For the love of God!
No, Oliver!
What the hell are you doing?!
Come on, you got
to get us out of here!
We trusted you.
You asked us to trust you
and we trusted you!
Don't
do this! Oliver!
Tatsu.
There's a cure, and he knows how
to administer it.
A little help.
Maseo...
He's not breathing.
The cure, he needs it now!
Akio.
Please wake up.
Please wake up!
He was dead the moment
he was exposed.
But you said...
That there is no cure.
Then what the hell
is that?!
Insulin.
I'm diabetic.
Ah.
I want to thank you
for bringing me here.
It would have taken us weeks
to track you all down.
And I do so hate loose ends.
You are
Wareeth al Ghul,
Heir to the Demon.
Before the night
is over,
you will be
Ibn al Ghul.
Son of the Demon.
There is no vow
more sacred,
nor covenant more holy
than the one between
man and woman.
With this ceremony,
your souls
are bound together,
forever joined.
You will never be free.
You will always
be held captive
by your love
for each other.
Continue.
I'm sorry,
Felicity, for everything.
You don't have
to be sorry for anything, John.
I'm glad to have
known you.
We offer blessings.
The union is sealed.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Greg!
Move your head.