My name is Oliver Queen.
After five years in hell...
To save my city.
Now others have joined my crusade.
To them, I'm Oliver Queen.
To the rest of Starling City...
...I am someone else.
I am something else.
Previously on Arrow:
I killed Sara.
Malcolm gave me something
that made me...
...susceptible to suggestion.
What happened wasn't your fault, Thea.
It wasn't your decision.
Malcolm, he's going to face justice.
He's gone.
Malcolm Merlyn will never be seen again.
Welcome to Nanda Parbat.
When I told you that Malcolm killed Sara,
he wanted her dead...
...but I am the one
who fired those arrows into her chest.
I promised you your vengeance.
So take it.
Kill me, but spare John Diggle's life.
Let him go.
I will beg for it.
You've shown tremendous strength...
...fortitude...
...and power.
No, Mr. Queen.
I don't want to kill you.
I want you to take my place.
I want you to become
the next Ra's al Ghul.
Ra's is a title greater than any one man.
Am I supposed to understand
what that means?
No. It's from a dialect no longer spoken.
Said to me by a man whose place I took.
Contemplating the same offer.
And what it means is:
"The tale to be told begins thus."
Don't let your footing betray you.
Let your power come
not from the strength of your attack...
...but from the ground
that holds your feet.
All men seek guidance...
...a purpose...
...a means to live without pain.
Those who journey here are given
such an exchange for their fealty.
You mean, they have to kill for you.
No, Mr. Queen, they have to die for me.
Is all of this supposed to impress me?
No.
To inform you.
Surely, men have branded you a murderer...
...a torturer.
You see, I would never shame you
with such bluntness.
Because I see it in your eyes.
The struggle you have
with your dual identity.
Oliver Queen and the Arrow.
Neither giving you what you crave.
But becoming Ra's al Ghul will?
Oliver Queen is a man destined to be alone.
- He loves a woman he knows he cannot have.
- You don't know me.
But I know the Arrow.
Al Sah-Him...
...will never be anything more than a
vigilante for those whose lives you save...
...at the risk of your own.
Your city will turn on you.
And your closest allies within the police
department will call you a criminal.
You will be scorned...
...and hunted...
...and then killed...
...dying as you began your crusade.
Alone.
Your brother attempted to have me believe
that he killed Sara.
Your confession is even less convincing.
- I don't have a reason to lie.
- Except to protect your father.
Why would I protect Malcolm,
when I turned him over to you?
He gave me a drug called Votura.
I put three arrows into her chest,
and I had no idea what I was doing.
He used me.
Someone she would trust.
So I don't deserve to be living any more
than Malcolm does.
There would be no justice in killing you.
I killed Sara.
Kill me.
Do it!
Do it.
The blood debt ends with Malcolm's death.
Which I can assure you
my father has taken care of already.
- Thea!
- Get away from her!
Nyssa, no!
Are you okay?
How the hell did she get out?
It's League training. Probably.
What were you doing down here?
I just wanted to pay my respects.
It was Herodotus
who first wrote of these waters.
And Ponce de León traveled the earth
in search of them.
And their discovery by Al-Khidr
is chronicled in the Qur'an.
And they have permitted me
to live way beyond my time.
You don't seem too fazed
by what I've told you.
I've seen things
that have helped me to believe...
...that this world is a much bigger place
than people realize.
As I told you on the mountain, boy...
...man can only evade death for so long.
And these water's powers
are losing their effect on me.
My time is almost over.
But my legacy won't be just ash and bone.
It will be history.
And you think
that I'll help you secure that legacy.
You survived my sword.
Your resurrection wasn't a gift
from these waters...
...but rather by force of your own will.
What better heir to immortality than someone
who has already claimed victory over death?
I didn't defy death
just to become an instrument of it.
We are justice.
Isn't that what
you've dedicated your life to?
Why confine your crusade
to a single city...
...when I can give you
a whole world to save?
By executing anyone
who stands in my way?
You would command resources
that you cannot even fathom.
Numbers greater than any army.
And more loyal.
Now...
...if you wish for them
to renounce killing as you did...
...thy will be done.
I doubt that.
It's called the League of Assassins
for a reason.
The League's reason would be your own.
You would be Ra's al Ghul.
And what if I say no?
Then you are free to leave...
...with your compatriots...
...as a gesture of goodwill.
All debts forgiven.
And all blood oaths waived.
Let's go home.
We really need to stop having these
"Thank God you're not dead" reunions.
- I agree.
- Heh.
I'm working on it.
- You look okay. Are you okay?
- I'm fine. Not even a scratch.
How is that possible?
- How did you get him back?
- Doesn't matter.
What matters is, you didn't kill him.
No, I wanted Ra's to kill him.
- And I still do.
- Thea.
He's not staying here.
You know there's nowhere else
I can take him.
If you think I feel bad
for him, you're wrong.
I'm not asking you to feel bad for him.
I'm not asking you to forgive him.
Just let him heal.
I have to go.
How did Thea react to her new houseguest?
- Fine.
- That bad, huh?
She ask how we made it back alive?
- I didn't get into it with her.
- How about me?
Like I said, Ra's had a change of heart.
Ra's doesn't have a heart.
He kicked you off a mountain,
put a sword through you.
Now he's giving you Malcolm back
gift-wrapped?
Diggle, we're back. We're alive.
Let's just be grateful for that.
What's the Chinese word for "okay"?
Or how do you say "okay" in Mandarin?
Everything is gonna be hao ba.
- I wanna go home.
- Yeah, I know, buddy.
But home's not really safe right now.
Because those men tried to hurt us?
Yeah, because of those men.
In fact, Akio, we shouldn't be
out in the open right now.
Akio!
- Oliver?
- Hey. Hey.
Hey, look, you cannot disappear like that.
I thought I saw my father,
but it wasn't him.
All right. Look, I get it, I get it.
I'm sorry.
- We can't get separated.
- The botanical gardens.
- The what?
- Mother and father always told me...
...to go there if we ever got separated.
- Okay.
- Come on!
Well, thank God.
Just because I'm furious with you,
that doesn't mean I want you dead.
What about Malcolm? I mean, I know
Laurel wants him dead. I mean, is he?
No. We got him back.
Well, I suppose, "Congrats," and, "Why,
oh, why did you do that?" are in order.
Oliver?
- Oliver, what are you doing?
- You're free to go.
My father would never trade
my life for yours.
- He certainly wouldn't for Malcolm Merlyn's.
- He didn't.
If no bargain was struck,
then how are you still alive?
Go home, Nyssa.
Okay...
...well, I don't understand
anything anymore.
- Why did Ra's...?
- It doesn't matter.
Let's focus on what does.
Somewhere, there is someone
that needs a reminder...
...that we are still
watching over this city.
There is a robbery in progress
at the Kingston Property Depot on 3rd.
A new shipment just arrived.
Whatever it is, it's worth a lot of money.
Okay, suit up.
- Oliver...?
- Suit up.
- I want this shipment done.
- Excuse me.
We're looking for the Catoca shipment.
Maybe you could help.
The Catoca shipment.
- Where is it?
- Uh... I don't know.
Sorry.
Boss said check the crates
for a Catoca manifest.
Drop it!
Look out!
You still need training.
- When are you gonna stop telling me that?
- When you no longer need training.
Arsenal?
The head guy got away. With these.
Ran into a new player tonight
who dropped some bodies.
I need a name.
- One of these four will give him up.
- Yeah.
But when he does,
you can read about it in the papers.
- Detective?
- It's captain now!
When were you gonna tell me?
Or were you gonna tell me?
You're really gonna stand there
still pretending...
...you didn't know
my daughter was dead?
- Captain Lance...
- My whole career...
...my whole life, even when I knew nothing,
I, at least, knew right from wrong.
And I knew vigilantism was wrong.
The day we take the law
into our own hands is the day...
...that we become outlaws.
And that idea...
That idea was precious to me.
Almost as precious as my own daughters.
I threw that all away the day
I threw in with you.
You know why?
Because I trusted you.
But I see the man under the hood now.
He lies, and he keeps secrets.
All so he doesn't have to carry around
the weight of his decisions.
And I'm done with him.
What would you say...
...if I told you I just connected
the virtual TCP to the open-source sensor?
I would say that you only think you did.
I've been trying to figure that out
for over two weeks.
If it makes you feel any better, I have
been trying for at least two full minutes.
Ah. Let me see.
Oh? You don't believe me?
Well, no, I just wanna make sure
you did it right.
Oh, and if I'm right?
Then I will take you to the best
steak dinner you've ever had.
Mm.
Which I'd probably do anyway.
I hope it's better than
that fusion place...
...where I needed this microscope
to find the food.
Oliver, hey. What are you doing here?
I mean, it's nice to see you here.
- Nice to see you again, Mr. Palmer.
- Likewise.
And, please, call me Ray.
Okay. Ray. May I speak with Felicity
for a few minutes please?
- Uh, absolutely.
- Thank you.
- I should have called.
- No.
I should have told you earlier,
when you got back.
- You don't owe me a thing.
- That's not true.
You're one of my closest friends.
We went up against a new crew last night.
One of them had his lips sewn shut.
- Is that a real thing?
- Apparently.
If only I had known I had that option.
Okay.
- Michael Amar?
- Yeah.
Street name's Murmur
because of the whole lip-stitch thing.
Practitioners say it focuses the mind,
like meditation.
You Okay?
I handed some of Amar's men
over to Lance.
He knows the Arrow knew about Sara
and didn't tell him.
What did Lance say?
Some variation on "go to hell."
- Oliver, he just needs time.
- No, he's right.
I lied to him. For months.
I kept something from him,
and he had every right to know.
Are you okay?
I mean, besides Lance and the whole,
well, me-and-Ray thing...
It just seems like there's
something else going on...
...underneath all of that.
I'm fine. Thanks for help with Amar's name.
- Oliver's not here.
- Actually, I came to see how you were doing.
He told you that Malcolm was here?
Go ahead.
I'd be the last person to stop you
from killing him.
My last attempt to do so
didn't exactly work out.
That's kind of why I'm here.
I'm worried about you.
Everyone's so interested
in saving my soul these days.
Look, no one wants to see Merlyn dead
more than me...
...but Oliver was right.
You wanted your own father killed.
Yeah, and how messed up is that?
I wish that I never learned
Malcolm was my father.
Everything since then has just...
You know, you're lucky, Laurel.
You have a normal father.
Someone who really loves you.
I can't say we're on the best of terms.
- Yeah.
- Ugh, ahem.
You should probably go.
How much of that did you hear?
Enough to know that I am the last person
you wish to see alive.
I'm not gonna apologize for what I did.
And I'd do it again.
I know.
You asked me to teach you to be strong.
To make sure you can't be hurt again.
You learned your lessons well.
I have learned nothing from you.
Do you realize that I'm so messed up
I was willing to die last night?
For what you made me do.
You know, I didn't actually think it was
possible for me to hurt any worse...
...than I did when I came to you.
You proved to me I was wrong.
So, what was it again that you taught me?
Show me the knife.
How did you know?
You are my daughter.
Do it, like I taught you. One strike
to the neck, it'll be over quickly.
You're sick.
I love you. And I want to do
what is best for you.
If that were even close to being true...
...you would have stayed out of my life.
Father.
Your safe return pleases me, my child.
Extend me the courtesy of explaining
why Malcolm Merlyn is still alive.
If you're not going to watch your tongue...
...then at least mind your tone.
Why did you release
al-Sahfer's murderer?
As a gift to Oliver Queen.
In advance for him becoming my heir.
You selected an outsider
over your own daughter?
He survived my sword.
Sara.
You're punishing my love for her.
At least do me the courtesy of
admitting it, you never approved.
I never approved of you allowing
weakness into your life.
And even in death, your devotion to her
pollutes your judgment.
- Target's name is Michael Amar.
- Yeah. Got him here.
Got out of Iron Heights two months ago.
- He escaped?
- No, released.
Turns out he was serving his sentence
based on a coerced confession.
Cops beat it out of him.
He confessed to a crime he didn't commit?
I might sew my mouth shut too.
He's not innocent anymore.
What was he after tonight?
His crew made off with a couple crates,
all containing these.
Industrial-grade diamonds.
The shipment was loaded
with high-end jewels they didn't take.
Why steal worthless diamonds?
- Million-dollar question.
- Street value's only a couple thousand.
We could use Felicity on this, Oliver.
She's preoccupied.
I know a couple of fences
from my less socially-responsible days.
I could talk to them, find out where
Amar's trying to move these diamonds.
That's a good idea.
You wanna tell me what's going on now?
Ra's predicted this.
He said that the city would turn
against me, and I would die alone.
Then we come back and the first thing that
happens is, Lance is shutting me out...
...and I see Felicity with Palmer.
It's like he looked into my future.
Sounds to me like Ra's is playing
with your head.
Question is, why are you letting him?
He wants me to take his place
in the League of Assassins.
It's why he let us go.
As a sign of good faith.
Is there even a world
where he can imagine you saying yes?
He said that I can do more as the new Ra's
than I could ever do...
...as Oliver Queen or the Arrow.
That I would have unlimited resources.
That I could make a difference,
not just a dent.
You're not really considering this?
Just because Captain Lance is angry,
and Felicity is momentarily unavailable.
It's more than that.
I just...
John, tell me honestly.
What have we accomplished?
Oliver.
All the people that we put away, John,
they got out.
The city's no better
off, the Arrow is not...
He's not making a difference.
And if I just can't be me...
...and the Arrow isn't enough...
Oliver.
...then maybe I should be Ra's al Ghul.
Is Malcolm still alive?
In my head I've already slit his throat
seven times.
- Broke his neck twice.
- Sorry that I had to bring him here.
Been trying to remember who I was
before Mom died.
Before Malcolm.
And I don't recognize her.
I couldn't even fathom...
...killing someone.
And in the last month...
...I've held a gun to
Slade Wilson's head...
...and nearly took my father's life twice.
But you didn't kill either of them.
You know why I didn't kill Malcolm?
Mom.
About what she'd think about her daughter
becoming a murderer just like him.
Thea, you're nothing like him.
There's something broken inside of me...
...just like there's something broken
inside of him.
Nothing can change that.
- Where are you going?
- To go buy my evil dad some soup.
- One big happy family.
- What did you do to her?
I encouraged her to kill me.
My version of being a supportive father.
- You really are insane.
- Perhaps.
But I'm not the only one.
Or do you doubt
that Ra's would release us both...
...without conditions?
No conditions.
An offer.
To take his place.
You don't seem surprised.
I don't put much stock in augury.
But there is a prophecy.
The man that doesn't perish
at the blade of Ra's al Ghul...
...will become Ra's al Ghul.
Ra's al Ghul doesn't offer, he orders.
Oliver.
Don't delude yourself into thinking
you have a choice.
Hey, what are those bamboo things called?
Hey, Akio, come on, all right? It's okay.
You need to remember that you're strong,
right? Just like my sister.
- You have a sister?
- I do.
And I miss her just as much
as you miss your parents.
Why aren't you with her?
Well, I told her that I had to hang out
with my good buddy, Akio.
- Really?
- Yeah.
We used to go to botanical gardens
just like these in Starling City.
Except she didn't know the plants
as well as you do.
Oliver, what's wrong?
Run.
Hi.
- Where's Diggle?
- He's out with Roy.
They're on their way back.
Thanks for coming.
Where else would I be?
It's not rhetorical.
Ray and I may be something...
...but that doesn't change
my commitment here.
- Good.
- What about your commitment?
John might have told me about your
employment offer from Evil Incorporated.
He also might have told me
that you may be considering it...
...which is, by the way, insane.
They're the League of Assassins.
That is not the name of a nice group.
I've been an assassin.
There is more than one path to justice.
There are a lot of different ways
I can answer that.
All varying on the theme
of, "You're crazy."
But I'm gonna go with:
What makes you think
that you're not already on the right path?
Okay. Okay.
Because it's been over two years.
You tell me.
What have I really accomplished?
My mother's dead.
Tommy, Sara.
Crime's not down, and my sister
is in 10 different kinds of pain right now.
So, you leave. Then what?
All the people you've lost,
all the sacrifices you've made.
It would have been for nothing.
I don't know why I'm doing this anymore.
I can't answer that for you.
Yes, Captain Lance is shutting you out.
But I don't believe you're the Arrow
so that people can say thank you.
And, yes, you and I are not together,
but that was your choice.
When we thought you were dead...
...each one of us had to figure out
why we were doing all this.
Seems like it's your turn.
Are we interrupting something?
What do you have?
Talked to a friend who ran a munitions
depot back when I was in Afghanistan.
I know why our guy is so interested
in low-grade diamonds.
The type Amar was interested in
is used to make diamond-tipped bullets.
They go through body armor
like tissue paper.
- Okay, so who wears body armor?
- The police.
The guys who beat that false confession
out of him, put him in prison.
- He's going to get payback.
- Okay, Roy, suit up.
Dig, secure the perimeter
of the station. Felicity...
Call Captain Lance. I'm already on it.
Hi.
Peace offering.
- I already ate.
- Right.
You know, it's funny.
A friend of mine is having trouble
with her father.
A son of a bitch who's barely human,
butyouuu
You know, history's taught me that you'll
give me the cold shoulder for a while.
And then you'll move on
to blowing up at me.
And then finally...
...you'll let it all out at a dinner
I've dragged you to after days of pleading.
But my point is, is just let me have it.
I deserve every minute of it,
and I am ready to take it.
But don't you think for one second
that I am giving up on us.
When you were a little girl...
...you used to wait up for me
when I was on nights.
You couldn't fall asleep
until I walked in that door.
- I remember.
- Yeah.
You were always the protector
of this family, of everyone.
Laurel Lance...
...always trying to save the world.
You can't save this.
- Dad...
- You don't know how hard I've tried...
...to forgive you for lying to me
the way you did.
I'm not proud of it.
You're my daughter, I'll always love you,
but I don't know if I'll ever forgive you.
Kill them all!
Duck!
Police band is filled with reports
of gunfire at the precinct.
- Any luck getting to Lance?
- Still trying.
Get down.
- I'll lay down cover fire, haul ass for the exit.
- I'm not leaving you.
Regardless of what you think,
I'm gonna protect my daughter.
Now, on my move, you run!
Go, go, go!
My father's back there.
Hey!
What, are you waiting for a "thank you"?
That's not why I do this.
Nice work.
Not without a few casualties,
but Amar is in custody.
So it's a "no"
on the whole victory-dance thing, then?
You know me, I don't dance.
But I do occasionally say, "Thank you."
You're welcome.
And you were right.
A "thank you" and a "you were right."
I should really be recording this.
I started all of this
because of my father...
...to right his wrongs.
It became something more.
But I never stopped to think about it...
...or about why...
...until you asked me to.
Well, what was the answer?
Tonight, at the precinct...
...the only thing that I could think about
was those police officers.
And how their families
were counting on me...
...and Roy and Diggle...
...to get them home safe.
That's why I'm doing this.
So...
...that means a pass...
...on becoming the most handsome
Demon's Head ever?
It means I'm not ready to give up
on what we're doing here.
You know, you're always saying
how you just want me to be happy.
The thing is...
...as long as you're in my life, I am.
I should probably take this.
- Who are those men?
- I don't know.
Then why are we running away from them?
Shado?
Are you all right?
What are you doing here?
Looking for you, actually.
I missed your sister.
I suppose I wanted something
to remind me of her.
Now's really not the best time.
Are you having problems with your father?
I have some experience in that area.
- Do you want to talk about it?
- With you?
You know what?
I could use a reminder of Sara too.
Dinner's on me.
During the fighting,
your technique was competent.
Why do I feel like that's your idea
of a compliment?
It could certainly be improved.
Is that an offer to teach me?
I have nowhere else to go.
It is not customary for
one to wait so long...
...before accepting a great honor.
I'm not accepting it.
- "The tale to be told begins thus."
- Maseo, this story...
...it's over before it begins.
You misunderstand.
It does not mean the tale is yet to unfold.
It means Ra's has already written it.
- The choice has been made.
- No.
I will always be grateful
for what you've done for my family.
For what you meant to Akio.
But if you insist on pursuing this path
of resistance...
...there will be consequences.
Is that a threat?
It is the will of Ra's al Ghul.
Yeah, who is it?
Hello?
Thea, are you okay? What's going on?
I don't know what I'm doing anymore.
I don't know who I am.
Can I just stay here with you?
Yeah.
Cops believe they've won.
But we still got what?
How many rounds
of those armor-piercing diamond bullets?
You tell everyone who'll listen
what you've seen.
Go.