(PANTING)
(MAN TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
-MAN: Good morning.
-How're you doing?
Hey.
Oh. Okay.
-Hot.
-Ah...
-(SMACKS LIPS) Felicity Smoak.
-Mmm-hmm.
You have failed this omelet.
-Really?
-Yeah.
You know, it's criminal how easily
cooking comes to you.
Well, I always wanted to
expand my horizons
beyond what I could do on the island,
which was basically...
It was cooked and uncooked.
-How was your jog?
-It was good.
I'm getting used to running
without chasing after someone.
-Mmm-hmm.
-I'm kind of sweaty.
I know. It's amazing.
-Yeah?
-Uh-huh.
Why'd you get this one removed?
I don't need it anymore.
So, what do you have planned
for the rest of the day?
A videoconference
with the Palmer Tech board,
who still question whether
I'm fit enough to inherit Ray's legacy.
Hey, how'd you like your company back
as an early Christmas gift?
I think you're doing a better job
of running it than I would.
-It's flirting with bankruptcy.
-Exactly. It's just flirting.
-Mmm. What?
-I got to go.
Where are you going now?
Uh, I have to get stuff at the
farmers' market for brunch tomorrow.
Right, the Hoffmans are coming over.
I forgot.
I don't think I'm ever gonna get tired
of making plans
that don't involve people shooting at me.
(GUNFIRE)
This is so cool!
We're really gonna have to work
on your definition of "cool."
Get me up there!
This is so awesome!
Whoo!
(GRUNTS)
Speedy, behind you.
(GROANS)
I thought I told you guys
to call me Red Arrow.
DIGGLE: A red arrow
just means you can't make a left turn.
Whatever, I'm inside the hijacked truck.
(GRUNTING)
(CLANKING)
(GASPS)
Canary, you're up.
(GRUNTS)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
Damn it! They have backup.
(GUNFIRE)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
Anyone manage to get eyes
on that stolen cargo?
They looked like equipment containers.
Not equipment, weapons.
Among other things, Kord Industries
is one of the largest arms manufacturers
in the world.
They also make
a really awesome cell phone.
-No, but weapons are more likely.
-Much.
These Ghosts, if that's seriously
what we're calling 'em,
are stepping up their attacks, escalating.
People are so scared,
they don't even wanna leave their homes.
Unless it's to pack up
in the middle of the night
and get the hell out of town.
What do you want us to do?
Take our football and go home?
No. We ask for help.
(SCOFFS)
Oliver walked away.
That was before these guys
started taking over our city
and turning it into a war zone.
We're dealing with a crisis.
Which Oliver believed
we could handle, Laurel.
And he was right.
I spoke to Walter Steele last night.
He passed.
(SCOFFS) Does that surprise you?
In three years, we've had three mayors
and one candidate for mayor
who have all ended up dead.
Anyone with any common sense
is not gonna throw their hat in the ring.
So we just go on as we have?
Running City Hall by committee
instead of electing a mayor?
Maybe we should have you focused
on catching these Ghosts.
(SIGHS) That's just what
the media calls them.
Because they disappear like ghosts.
Yeah. I didn't say it wasn't cute.
The truth is
these guys are hard to catch.
They're not your
average everyday criminals.
Average everyday criminals don't have
cyanide capsules in their teeth
so they can off themselves
rather than be interrogated.
I'm doing the best I can here.
We need you to do better.
This city was dying before
more masks showed up to wreak havoc.
Look, we'll get these guys eventually.
And things will turn around.
I mean, look, we've rebranded the city.
We got the new tourism program.
We got the new high-speed rail line
to Central City.
Hopefully, from Central City.
Well, maybe we could have a Flash Day,
just like them.
Bottom line, we need an influx of people,
which means an influx of cash.
No, no, no. Keep your seats.
Excuse me, this is a private meeting.
Oh, excellent, I despise interruptions.
-Who the hell are you?
-Me?
I'm the man you're looking for.
I'm the one who controls the...
What do you people call them? The Ghosts?
So, you're all fretting
about this city dying.
I'm here on behalf of an organization
that wants you to let it die.
See, death is a beautiful thing.
We die, we go into the ground,
our remains grow into flowers.
It's only in the interval after dying
that new things can sprout.
That's enough. Get the hell out of...
Cities are like puppies.
You see them writhing in agony
on the streets,
you put them down,
you don't let them suffer.
I'm getting security.
Susanna, calm down. Get down.
It's very rude behavior.
None of you seem particularly likable,
but if you do have any friends
or anyone who does love you,
I suggest you say goodbye.
My people will be in touch.
Mmm.
Oh, Oliver, these eggs are heaven!
Don't tell me you made them in the...
In the slow cooker.
The slow cooker you got us, yeah.
-LAURA: I knew it, I knew it.
-Aw.
People are always so hesitant to try them,
but slow cookers
are absolute life changers.
I don't know how
that is not a bumper sticker yet.
-(BOTH LAUGHING)
-I know!
ADAM: On the topic of life changers,
you guys really need to
get on the school situation here.
We could write you a recommendation letter
for our school's waiting list.
(LAUGHS) But wouldn't it help to have
kids first? Or, I don't know, a kid?
Oh, it takes years to get on that list.
And I'm sure kids aren't too far
down the line for you two.
Yeah, we haven't talked about it.
(LAUGHS NERVOUSLY) Who wants more mimosas?
-I need to see it. Do you have it on you?
-Honey, it's not...
(SHUSHING) Baby.
You have it on you, right?
-Do you have it?
-Yep.
(GASPS)
-Oh, it's stunning.
-It's my mother's.
-So, when are you gonna pop the question?
-Tonight.
What are you guys talking about? Whoop!
ADAM: Whoa.
Dude! Nice reflexes. (CHUCKLES)
Back off, psycho.
Six people have died
from the crank you've been pushing.
Four of them were kids!
(GUNSHOTS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
You've certainly chosen
an unusual hobby, Mr. Queen.
DISTRICT ATTORNEY:
He said he'd kill us all.
That was a hell of a press conference.
These people needed a strong reminder
that this city doesn't bow to terrorists.
Susanna?
I thought that tasted funny.
(MUG CLATTERS)
-Call 9-1-1!
-What happened?
-I don't know.
-John, we have a new problem.
City leadership is being targeted.
They just poisoned the District Attorney.
I'm headed to my father. I need
you and Thea on the other two members.
-(PHONE VIBRATES)
-(GROANS)
I'm closest to the head of Emergency
Services. Thea, I need you at City Hall.
(MAN GROANING)
Are you okay?
Can we get a nurse over here?
Okay, listen,
the District Attorney just collapsed.
Staffers think it might be poison,
but I need toxicology...
MAN: Drop it!
(GUNFIRE)
All right, all right, all right.
All right, all right.
Just hold on. I'll get you some help.
(CAR ALARM BEEPS)
You, okay?
Captain Lance, you were warned.
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
(GRUNTING)
Ahh!
-Are you okay?
-Yeah, it's just a flesh wound.
Captain Lance,
the District Attorney was pronounced dead.
And reports are coming in
that the city comptroller and
the head of Emergency Services
have also been killed.
That's pretty much the city's leadership.
Carries on like this,
there won't be a city left to lead.
-So, what's the occasion?
-Do we need an occasion for dinner?
No, ever since you discovered cooking,
our life's been a never-ending episode
of MasterChef.
But this isn't a dinner.
This is a production.
Are we celebrating something?
Sort of depends on how dessert goes.
No. No, no. I'm almost disgustingly full.
You are going to have to try a bite
or two of this souffle.
-(DOORBELL RINGS)
-Diet saved by the bell.
(SIGHS)
(DOOR OPENS)
-Um...
-What's going on?
You have visitors.
We probably should've called first, but...
We really need your help.
LAUREL: The media's been
calling them the Ghosts.
They're like nothing we'd ever seen
before. Well trained. Well-armed.
And committed.
Anytime we get too close to one of them,
they off themselves with cyanide.
-What's their agenda?
-At first, we thought they were thieves
because they were hitting banks
and jewelry stores.
But then we found out that they've
just been building their war chest.
They've now been stealing munitions
and heavy arms.
-And assassinating people.
-Hon.
-Where are the police?
-Overwhelmed.
Well, a group of this size has to be
work out of a central location,
a base of operations.
Which we haven't been able to find.
Digs seems to think we can handle it.
You disagree?
(SIGHS) I think we're in over our heads.
(SIGHS)
We need the Arrow.
Uh... (SIGHS)
-The Arrow's dead.
-We're hoping that's not the case.
We're hoping that you can't change
who you are in your bones.
Come help us stop these guys,
and then you can come back here to your
domestic life of tranquility and souffles.
(SCOFFS)
You're uncharacteristically quiet.
What should I say?
Our friends need our help.
We should already be in the car.
How'd you find me?
The world's too small for someone
like Oliver Queen to disappear.
Truth be told,
I expected to find you in Starling City.
(CLEARS THROAT)
I don't wanna be near my family.
Because of what you did to Shrieve?
I read his autopsy report.
I knew you had a capacity
for the unfathomable,
but I actually underestimated you.
What do you want, Amanda?
-To help you.
-(SCOFFS)
You haven't returned home because
you feel you're a monster.
And you're trying to deny it,
channeling your killer instinct
into something productive.
But you can't change who you are
in your bones.
I don't need a therapist.
The hood and eye makeup suggest otherwise.
Stop trying to run
from your inner darkness.
Embrace it.
Let it run its course.
Oftentimes, the only way out is through.
Through what?
A.R.G.U.S. agents.
When you wake up, just remember
that I'm trying to help you.
Here I thought that my days of riding
in the back of limos were long gone.
Oh. One of the perks of being
Palmer Technologies' CEO in absentia.
Now that I'm back,
they might actually expect me to do stuff.
I wouldn't worry.
We're not gonna stay long.
Geez!
It's tough not to look out this window
and wonder.
Wonder what?
What did we really accomplish?
Felicity and I have a lot of catch up on,
so maybe take us through the evidence
the team has gathered.
That's easy. Nothing.
Okay. So, maybe we'll go through
all the encounters
that you've had with the Ghosts,
everywhere they've hid,
and then Felicity can cross...
-John.
-We should've discussed this.
-Thea and I did.
-We need him.
(SIGHS) I'm not expecting you to
welcome me back with open arms.
What I did to you is not easily forgiven.
I'm here to help you with your problem,
and then I'm gone.
Oliver, we don't need your help.
And if we did,
we'd probably choose someone
who didn't kidnap my wife
and endanger my child.
And no one is asking you to pretend like
that didn't happen.
But we're in trouble.
This city is in trouble.
Laurel, I don't need you
to remind me of that.
I just can't go into battle
with a man I don't trust.
Understood, but things are a little worse
than you guys thought.
I hacked into Kord Industries' computers
just to see what the Ghosts stole.
Cluster bombs,
sensor-fused and high yield.
Any more powerful
and they'd have to be nuclear.
What do you wanna do, John?
I'm gonna do whatever it takes
to save my city.
Weapons need targets.
These had to be stolen for a reason.
Felicity, hack into
Kord Industries databases.
I wanna know everything that there is
to know about these explosives.
Laurel, you wanna start a dialogue
with your father,
make a list of potential targets.
Digg, Thea,
hit the streets. See what we can find.
Oh. Sorry, sorry. Just old habits.
It's probably not a bad idea
to give your father a heads-up.
-Copy.
-John.
Look, I have a wife and a toddler
to get back home to.
Felicity, will you let me know
if you find anything?
Will do. Say hi to Lyla for me.
He'll come around.
I'll go hit the streets.
Well, I have to say that it feels good
to be at a keyboard
for something other than a teleconference.
I need a map with a list
of all the spots the Ghosts have hit,
including where they encountered the team.
And if we get lucky maybe we can...
Triangulate and determine
a point of origin
where the Ghosts
are operating out of, yes.
Yeah.
All right, here's a list
of all their heists and attacks.
-That was fast.
-Yeah.
Yeah, like, um, riding a bike.
First spot they hit
was the Larson Credit Union?
-No, no, no, it was Starling National.
-Really?
-Mmm-hmm.
-How'd you know that?
Same way you knew about Larson.
-Felicity. Wanna play again?
-Mmm?
Mmm, what game are we playing?
We're playing "the reason that you know
so much about the Ghosts
"is because you've been helping the team
behind my back" game.
These guys have got cluster bombs now?
You've got to be kidding me.
Well, that's why I'm here, to see
if you're aware of any potential targets.
The only thing I'm aware of is that
I want you to stay as far away
-from this mess as possible.
-Dad, I thought we'd moved past this.
We moved past a lot of things.
And I am glad, really.
But I don't want you mixing it up
with these psychos.
Even after what happened
to city leadership?
I mean, honestly, I thought that
you would be happy to have our help.
Do I look happy?
Dad, the Ghosts were dangerous
before they got their hands
on experimental explosives.
How are you gonna feel
when they take out a city block,
knowing you didn't do anything to stop it?
(SIGHS)
Have you heard of anything going on
that's a potential target?
Landmarks, Starling General, et cetera.
What about city events?
Any dignitaries coming to town?
A few ball games, concerts.
Not that there's anyone to buy a ticket.
Train station's getting reopened
tomorrow night for the new rail line,
and Starling General's
having a canned food drive.
People don't come to
Star City anymore, Laurel.
They wanna leave.
Who is the cutest?
Who is the cutest ever, ever?
Playing with her like that,
I'm pretty sure it's you.
It's amazing how everything else
can just melt away except for her.
(BABY COOING)
What's melting tonight?
I know it's been a rough few months.
These men you're dealing with.
Tonight, it's just one man.
Oliver's back.
That didn't take long.
You knew he was coming back,
why didn't you warn me?
(CHUCKLES) What's the saying?
"Only the dead have seen the end of war."
-Please, Oliver's not a soldier.
-Isn't he?
That's pretty forgiving, considering
he kidnapped you six months ago.
You know why he did.
You have to let go of it sometime.
-I have.
-It's because you're better than me.
It's one of the reasons why I love you.
It was war, Johnny. Maybe not against
a country, but it was war.
And in times of war,
we do what we have to do.
Really, Lyla?
I mean, that includes lying to me?
Lying to Felicity?
Come on, what's the point?
Oliver did what he thought he had to do
to defeat Ra's.
I'm not saying he made the right choice.
But if Oliver Queen
always made the right choice,
he wouldn't need you.
I used to think
that yelling Oliver was scary.
I'm starting to think that
silent Oliver is a lot worse.
I'm just going over
the past five months
-in my head.
-Okay.
When you got food poisoning
when we were in Thailand...
Yes. I might've been secretly
working with the team,
but I didn't exactly lie
about the food poisoning.
Laab Moo is extremely hard to digest.
What about when you missed our boat?
"Missed," in Positano.
Okay, that one was a little fib.
-Bali?
-Mmm...
Oh, Felicity, you said there wasn't
even email involved!
I know, but we both know
I'm just that good.
I don't understand.
The whole point of starting over
was to get away from all of this.
And we were both right there together
leading that charge.
I know. And I thought
that's what we needed.
And the first few months were great,
-really great.
-Okay.
But then when you and Laura Hoffman
started exchanging cooking tips,
I secretly wanted to gouge out my eyes.
-I thought you were happy.
-I was.
Deliriously happy with you,
but bored with everything else.
Look, I miss this.
I miss saving the city and helping people.
It gives my life purpose.
And I wish I got the same thrill
from choosing between
the dimpled flatware and the scalloped,
but I just don't.
Hey, I don't care that you lied to me.
I don't care.
I care that the entire time
we were supposed to be away, together,
part of you was still here.
I love every moment that I'm with you,
no matter where we are.
(COMPUTER BEEPS)
What's that?
I hacked Kord Industries to check out
the design schematics for their bombs.
Turns out they have
a GPS tracker built in.
-Can you find out where it is?
-At least where they've been.
GPS is offline now,
but their last location was...
Admiral Transport Interchange.
It's a truck depot outside Pennytown.
Closed up shop months ago.
I'll call Thea. You get Laurel and Dig.
This may be a good time to tell you that
Cisco worked up a little something
before he knew you were leaving.
A new suit.
I'm not staying long enough
for a new suit.
I heard about places like this.
Owners must've left
when the city started tanking.
Well, our new friends
seem to have found a use for it.
Gentlemen, the world's a funny place.
It resists change, it fights progress.
And so the only way to move things forward
is to fight back.
And you men are here today
because you understand that.
But our cause is only as strong
as our weakest man.
Mr. Alvarez, please step forward.
You commanded the hijacking
the other night.
The cluster bombs from Kord Industries.
Yes, sir. We encountered
some resistance, but we handled it.
MR. X: (CHUCKLES) Han... Handled...
Well, I guess my definition of "handled"
is a little different than yours.
You see, when I handle a problem,
the problem dies.
-Sir, we got away with the bombs, so...
-(SHUSHING)
You know, I love this town in the fall.
I mean, yes, it looks pretty much the same
as it does in the three other seasons,
but I admire consistency.
I respect dependability.
And you've shown me neither.
So, now, allow me to show you something.
It's another kind of beauty.
It's the manipulation
of primordial energies.
No? Over your head? Yeah.
The grazing of the levers
that God uses to move the world.
No? No?
(SIGHS)
This.
(GASPING)
-Oh, my God!
-What the hell is that?
Move!
-(GRUNTING)
-(GUNSHOTS)
(GRUNTING)
Hey, Speedy!
SCPD, put your hands in the air!
What are they gonna do
with the explosives?
Tell me!
They're gonna destroy Star City Station.
Hands where I can see them.
We got to go! We got to go!
Oh, I remember that look.
That is not a good look.
We found out
what they have planned at least.
They're gonna use the explosives
on the new train station.
Yeah, pretty sure
I had that one in the office pool.
Too soon?
They're probably planning the attack
for tomorrow night,
to celebrate the reopening
of the new rail line.
Are we not gonna talk about
what just happened?
That dude just killed that guy
by touching him.
Wait. We're dealing with a metahuman?
Like we didn't have enough problems?
He wasn't a metahuman.
Oliver, what that man did was not natural.
I know. It was mystical.
DIGGLE: How can you be so sure?
Because I've seen things.
There are things that can't be explained,
even by science.
I suppose you aren't gonna tell us
about these things you've seen, Oliver?
We need to focus
on finding the cluster bombs.
Can you reactivate the GPS?
Yeah, eventually, but I'm pretty sure the
train station's gonna be blown up by then.
Fine. So we do this the old-fashioned way.
THEA: So, this is the old fashioned way?
OLIVER: Can we maybe discuss last night?
It's pretty amazing, right?
How could you ever
wanna give up that rush?
Extremely easily.
It's not what I'm talking about.
You seemed a little out of control.
This coming from the guy who used
to use criminals as target practice?
(SCOFFS) I'm amazed by how far you've come
in five months,
and I'm under no illusions
that this isn't a violent life.
I just want you to remember that
it's restraint separating us and them.
Well, you've managed to be back, what,
24 hours before giving me a lecture.
Think I owe Laurel 50 bucks.
I'm being serious.
How long has this been going on for?
Nothing is going on, okay?
I've just become a better fighter.
A better fighter remains in control
when they fight.
Is everything okay?
It's not okay.
My brother
can't seem to stay out of my business.
ANNOUNCER: All passengers...
-Any luck?
-No.
Does Thea seem a little off to you?
No, she's fine.
Just a little too aggressive, maybe.
But I remember you were same way
when you started out.
I saw that you took my advice
on the identity concealment.
Oliver, man, what are we doing?
Pretending everything's normal?
That we are normal?
I'm looking for a way in.
I was furious to think that you trusted
Malcolm Merlyn more than you trusted me,
but then I realized
that I'm not angry at you.
I'm angry at myself for thinking
you're someone that you clearly aren't.
I don't know what that means.
Oliver, after everything
we've been through, man.
I couldn't fathom why you didn't trust me.
But then I realized you couldn't.
It's not who you are.
You don't trust. You don't love.
You were able to fool Ra's
and join the League
because inside you were
every bit as dark as they are.
LAUREL: Thank you for coming.
Responding to a bomb threat's
kind of in the SCPD job description.
You know what I mean.
I'm glad we're working together.
Well, it seems like you're working
with a lot of people these days.
-What's that supposed to mean?
-Excuse me.
-Dad.
-Prodigal Arrow returns.
-Captain Lance.
-I thought that was you last night.
Some mask over your head.
Felt like old times.
Only trying to help.
If that were true,
you wouldn't have come back.
This town started going to crap
the moment you put on that hood.
You brought madness into all our lives,
and the monster you were
inspired monsters.
Maybe.
But I'm not a monster anymore.
Then what are you?
Nice nap?
I wasn't napping, I was drugged.
Where's Waller?
Back in Coast City,
sleeping off the scotch.
Wake her up.
I wanna know what I'm doing here.
Director Waller's asked me to thank you
for agreeing to take on this mission.
Okay, look, I didn't agree to take on...
Sorry, we're on a bit of a clock here.
Now, you're getting out of this plane.
You can do that with a chute on your back
or a bullet in your head. Your call.
Why is Waller doing this?
I guess she likes you. And I didn't think
Waller could like anybody.
-Plus, you know the terrain.
-What terrain?
Your job is to infiltrate the area,
assess the threat and report back.
You have AES-encrypted communication gear
in your pack.
Now, according to our intel,
your target may be radar-capable,
so you'll have to HALO in!
So when you think you're about to splat,
only then do you pull the chute.
Wait. Is that...
Uh-oh. You have mopey face.
Were you worried
after five months of happiness
that you weren't gonna be able to
make it anymore?
I ran into Lance.
And he gave you a hug
because he missed you?
Yeah, well, it's not just Lance.
Thea, there is something wrong with Thea.
She doesn't want my help.
Neither does Diggle.
We should never have come back here.
Well, let's go. Let's go home.
You don't wanna go home.
I love our new home.
And I love you.
But I also love it here, and you can't
honestly tell me that you don't.
Yeah, no, of course, I miss aspects of it.
The sense of purpose, the idea of
helping people, but Lance was right.
About what?
A few months ago, he told me that
all I brought back from the island
was pain,
misery and darkness.
And of course,
I knew that the moment we came back here
that darkness would be waiting for me.
Well, he's wrong, dead wrong.
You didn't bring the darkness back
with you from Lian Yu.
But, Felicity, I'm telling you
that the only way I know
how to fight the darkness
is to be darkness.
That is why I left.
And I don't wanna be
that type of person anymore.
Then maybe you just need to be
a different kind of person.
And you're not doing this alone anymore.
Train station was a bust.
No incendiaries on the platform,
on the tracks or inside any of the trains.
Yeah, but if there's no bomb
in the station,
then how do they expect to blow it up?
You didn't bring the darkness here.
-THEA: What?
-The bombs
aren't at the station
because they're bringing them in.
On a train. When's the reopening ceremony
scheduled for?
9:58. To coincide with the arrival of the
first high-speed train from Central City.
-Let's suit up.
-You should suit up, too.
What?
(TIRES SCREECHING)
Get me closer!
I'm trying!
ANNOUNCER: Ladies and gentlemen,
the first train from Central City
will be arriving shortly.
Everybody, get out of here! It's not safe!
(PEOPLE SHOUTING)
Out of the way!
Out of the way! Out of the way!
(BOY YELLS)
-Whoa. You're really strong.
-Go.
Thank you!
This is SCPD. Everyone,
quickly and quietly evacuate the station.
Everyone, move calmly
towards the exit. Calmly!
Train is 10 minutes out.
Six minutes till safest blast radius.
(RATTLING)
(YELLS)
Situation report.
Mr. Slater?
Sorry, he had to get off
at an earlier stop.
You can't be the Arrow. He died.
So who are you?
You're about to find out.
Stop the train.
No, I don't want to.
Even if I did, I couldn't. I destroyed
the braking system 20 miles ago.
Willing to die to destroy a train station?
No. That would be ridiculous.
Then how were you planning on
getting off the train?
Oh, you don't know who I am, do you?
I'm Damien Darhk.
Is that all you got?
(GRUNTING)
(GROANING)
It seems you've much in common
with the Arrow. You're both dead.
Thank you.
We need to stop the train.
-You got any ideas?
-Yeah. Blow it up.
Whoa.
So what're you gonna call yourself now?
Everybody thinks Roy was the Arrow.
Well, he won't need a code name
if he's headed back to Ivy Town.
Well, then I guess I need a code name.
Felicity and I, we have missed this.
We've missed all of you.
And this city is far worse off
than we thought.
What are you talking about?
The man leading the Ghosts
is Damien Darhk.
Darhk left Star City months ago.
Why would he come back?
Did Ra's tell you anything about Darhk
that'd give us any idea about his agenda?
He said that Damien Darhk
had a hive of operatives at his disposal.
"Hive." That was the exact word he used?
Yes. Why? Does it mean something to you?
Who would wanna kill Andy?
Don't know their names. Just an alias.
Hive.
No.
-No, nothing.
-You all right?
Yeah, yeah, I'm fine, man. I'm just beat.
Plus, I have a little girl to tuck in.
John. John!
Listen, I'm not quite there yet, Oliver,
so let's not do this right now.
No, I know. I get it.
But there is something we do need to do.
-Captain, new problem.
-Seriously?
Someone's hacked into
the Emergency Broadcast System.
They've taken over all the networks.
Six months ago, the Arrow died.
But what he stood for didn't.
It lived on in the heroes
who took up his mantle.
People who believe that this city
should never descend into hopelessness.
Who believe, although life
is full of darkness,
that darkness can be defeated by light.
And tonight, I am declaring my intention
to stand with them.
To fight for this city.
To be the symbol of hope
that the Arrow never was.
I am
the Green Arrow.
(GROANS)
Who are you?
Answer me.
(GASPING)
(SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
(GRUNTING)
You have a visitor.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(CHUCKLES)
Sorry about the arm.
A necessary subterfuge
to prevent anyone from suspecting
your involvement with HIVE.
What do you want?
Well, I'm a little disappointed the train
station isn't a smoldering pile of ash.
I'm not. Mass murder? Killing innocents?
I didn't sign up for this.
You signed up to follow my instructions,
to do my will.
I wanna know everything
about this Green Arrow,
where he lives, and who he loves.
And I want him off the boards
by the time my associates arrive.
And if I don't help you?
Well, then I would be surprised.
'Cause I think I made it abundantly clear.
You don't have a choice.
So my guilt over displacing Thea is
only slightly outweighed
by how amazing this place is.
Thea's actually been living with Laurel
for the past few months.
-Oh.
-Ra's stabbed her right over there.
-We can get a rug.
You know, I'd hate to disappoint you.
That speech is pretty hopeful.
Why would that disappoint me?
Well, you know how you said that
you didn't know how to be a hero
-without the darkness.
-Mmm.
And I know how you hate being wrong.
I'm sorry I missed the funeral.
-Zoom?
-Yeah.
There was a time
I would've thought this was my fault,
that I'd brought this darkness upon us.
But now I know it's not my fault.
It's my responsibility.
Responsibility to do what?
To end it.
I'm gonna kill him.
Is there anything I can do?
I wanna be left alone.
Okay.