Last season on "Arrow"...
Are you offering to
help me find my son?
I want us to find
both of our sons.
I need your help.
Agh!
Oliver's
gonna come for us!
Yeah. I'm counting
on it, sis.
Adrian,
where is my son?!
When we get to the airplane,
I'm not gonna get on it.
- What?
- I'm not leaving William behind.
Don't do that.
He's rigged
the entire island
with explosives.
They're remotely linked to
some sort of dead man's switch.
If he dies, it detonates
all the devices.
- Unh!
- William, come here.
Are you ok?
Are you all right?
He wants you
to kill him
so it kills all of us.
No, Adrian!
I'm on site.
No sign of Faust.
He's not at his
last known either.
Well, his ordinance is.
If Faust is moving
from bombs to missiles,
it makes you wonder
what else he's changed up.
Exactly. Stay sharp.
Boss said stay sharp,
Hoss.
Faust,
it's clear.
Apologies.
Won't be but a minute.
If...You have
the opportunity,
please advise your mayor
next time someone
threatens to launch
a ballistic missile
at his city,
he really should pay up.
Disappointing.
Agh! Agh!
That's an MGM-140.
It's fire
and forget.
You can't stop it.
You can't disarm it.
No, but I have
a very smart friend who can.
My T-sphere's spoofed
the missile's guidance system.
I'm drawing it back
to the water.
You look troubled
as if detonation stirred
unpleasant memories.
Chase sabotaged
the plane.
We can't get
off the island!
There's an Argus supply ship
on the eastern shore.
That's on the other
side of the island.
Slade knows where it is.
Go now!
Hey! Oliver says
there's a boat on the eastern shore.
You lot won't make it
in time.
- I'll take my own chances.
- I always hated that guy.
- What are we gonna do now?
- What about the plane?
Thought you said you
couldn't get it fixed.
For shielding us
from the blast,
- it should work just fine.
- It's not like there's a whole
- lot of other options.
- No. He's right, ok?
It's better than nothing.
Let's go!
No! I have to
find William!
Samantha!
You go to the plane, ok?
I'll get her!
- Careful. Let's go.
- Should be on the plane.
I'm not taking refuge
from 100 bombs without you.
- It's more like 250.
- Let's go. Let's go.
Go, go, go!
What's this?
Remarks for
the Police Academy
graduation ceremony.
Seems my promotion
came
with speech writing
duties.
- You can write?
- You can read?
I can kick both
y'all asses is what I can do.
This is, uh--
this is really good, Rene.
It's like I keep
telling you, Hoss.
I've got the soul
of a poet.
I don't think I have ever
heard you say that.
Who the hell asked
you, Blondie?
You totally missed
me redirecting
a ballistic missile
b-t-dubs.
Oh, man.
Well, I've already seen you do that once.
All right.
Just as you ordered--
a triple stack
with a side of heart disease.
Don't judge me.
Ah, yeah.
That's for you.
Surprise.
This is for you.
Here you go.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Sorry I was MIA.
I pretty much had to
knock my mother unconscious
to get her on a flight
back to Vegas.
- She did not want to go.
- That's fine.
We--we had it
handled.
Yeah. Even
without Dinah in the field.
Come a long way
in a year.
Yeah. It also makes me
grateful for all the times
Oliver kicked
our ass almost.
I'm gonna go home.
We'll walk with you.
Wow. It's been
over 5 months.
Their subtlety hasn't
gotten better at all!
Heard that!
No, it hasn't.
Um, there's some
in there for William, too.
Got some fries and, like,
a mini cheeseburger and then a burger
without cheese because
I wasn't sure if he was, like, lactose--
Do you think there's
enough for 3?
Oh. Well,
I already ate, and--
- Mm-hmm.
- Unless you're asking
because you think
now's a good time.
- Like, do you need a buffer or--
- I don't need a buffer.
I could use some
company.
I know we talked
about it
and that he's
getting used to me
and it might be
a little weird to--
I mean, confusing,
right, for him--
for us--for me--for you.
Just not tonight.
Another night.
Promise?
Promise.
- Ok.
- Heh.
Hmm.
Hey. Look at me.
Where's my--my mom?
Yeah. No. I'm gonna
go find your mom,
but--but the island,
what happened,
it's very dangerous,
and you are safe by the shore,
do you understand?
What happened?
The man who took you
when we saw
the explosions, ok,
he did this.
He said you're
my father?
I--I'm gonna go find
your mother.
I'm gonna find her
and make sure that she's safe,
I promise you,
but you have to stay here, ok?
Good.
That food is junk.
That's why kids
like it, Raisa.
How'd he do today?
New school.
It's hard.
It's been a few months.
You had trouble
fitting in at his age.
What? What are you
talking about?
I had Tommy.
I wouldn't call
having a friend
who helps you get
into trouble fitting in.
That's a fair point.
Hey, kiddo.
Brought home
some dinner.
Not hungry.
How's school?
Fine.
Yeah. Making friends?
This weekend, let's
go see a rockets game.
You know, as mayor,
I get pretty good seats.
I'm tired.
I'm gonna go to bed.
Ok. Good night,
William.
Good night, Oliver.
- Comfy?
- Could I get something to drink?
That will be up
to my lieutenant.
Thanks, Bob.
I got it from here.
Where'd you get
the muscle?
Kettle bell swings.
Oh. Ha.
Heh heh.
Ugh!
- The gun men, jerkwad.
- Agh.
Yeah. You were rolling
with some pretty highly trained
mercenaries tonight.
According to your friend
in the green hoodie.
Highly trained means
highly expensive.
You were probably
paying as much to hire them
as you were extorting
the city for.
So you're saying
there's a problem
with my business plan?
Well, can I get
something to drink?
I'd be more disposed
to linguistics
if I weren't so parched.
What do you want?
Anything carbonated
will do.
Don't look so dour.
Mr. Smug'll crack.
It's not the whack job,
Lieutenant.
It's Quentin Lance.
As deputy mayor,
he was supposed to be here
to review plans
for the academy
graduation.
- So?
- So his appointment
was an hour ago.
All right. It's ok.
I know where he is.
Um, get this guy
a soda or something, will you?
- Ahem.
Hey.
Thanks for coming.
You did the right thing
texting me.
Heh. It's not like I can
call my sponsor, is it?
Why not?
If I tell him
why I want to drink,
what I did,
why--why I did it--
Yeah. He'd think you're
on something a lot stronger than booze.
It's like all I got
is this guilt,
and all I can do is just run, run,
run away from it.
And go where?
To the bottom
of these glasses.
Well, you're not
gonna do that
because you know
and I know that is not
what Laurel
would have wanted.
Which Laurel?
Perfect.
Open it up for me.
Hey. If you think
you can claim some kind of police brutality--
Not at all. No.
I just needed to get this loose.
Ugh! Ha!
C4 implant. Boom.
Ha ha!
You're crazy.
I don't judge you!
Unh!
Well done, Alex.
Right on schedule.
One does one's
humble best.
Wire it up. Make it fast.
We're on a clock.
We're all set here.
Care to do
the honors?
Ha ha ha ha!
Let's go.
♪ Arrow 6x01 ♪
Fallout
Original Air Date on October 12, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
What's
the casualty count?
9 dead,
6 in critical condition,
and 4 injured.
Good thing
the Academy's turning out
a new batch
of replacements.
- Hey. Come on.
- Sorry, sorry.
Look. We might want
to consider canceling the graduation
or at least closing
it to the public.
This city does not bend
to terrorism.
Look. The media's going crazy,
wanting us to figure out
how we're gonna
handle all this stuff.
We have Argus connections.
I'll have them
handle security.
The question is
who would do this and why?
Well, I think
I've got an answer on that.
Got video footage.
Has anyone seen this?
I managed to get
to it before anyone else could.
I thought you
said she died.
You said Black Siren
died on Lian Yu.
She did.
She was dead,
buried under a ton
of rubble
when Quentin and I
found her.
Ok. Well, unless
our Laurel is
mysteriously
back from the dead--
something I wouldn't
put past either
of the Lance
sisters--
Black Siren is
not only not dead.
She is not
on Lian Yu.
Right. And running
with our old friend Alex Faust.
Ok. Clearly,
he was at SCPD
when the explosion
went off.
Which means he either
died or escape.
He escaped.
The question is
why is he working
with Black Siren?
And where did they
hire these mercenaries?
I'll get this image
over to Lyla.
She can tell us
where these guys are from
and when they started
working together.
I promised Raisa
that I would take William to school,
so I'll check in
when I'm done with that.
Hey, kiddo.
Sorry I'm late.
Just that I--
he did not sleep
last night.
Was he having
nightmares?
I mean, he seemed fine
when I left.
I think he puts on
a good act for you,
but when you left
for the emergency,
he cried
about the bad man.
He says the bad man
is why his mother is dead.
Slade?
You all right, kid?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Where is everyone?
I came back here
looking for people.
Came back? What do you
mean you came back?
Two of your friends
went to the monastery
to look
for survivors.
Ra's al Ghul's daughter
went to the cages for that girl,
but your sister--
What about her?
Slade!
Where's Thea?
She's this way.
- Hey.
- Hi.
- What do you need?
- What do I need?
Well, you know,
lots of things.
I mean, you know,
more out of Rene for one.
You know, he's all right
at the new job, but--
- He's not Thea?
- No. He's not Thea.
Actually, I wanted
to talk to you about, um--
about--about her.
- About Thea?
- No, no.
The other, uh, Laurel.
Dinah wasn't being
straight with you
when she told you that she was dead
when we found her.
Well, it--it's
complicated, isn't it?
Y-yeah.
But listen.
The--the point is
is that I was supposed
to be at SCPD last night,
and I think that
maybe she went there looking for me.
Wait. Why? Why--
why would she be targeting you?
Well--
Argus has a lead on Black Siren.
I have to go.
Ok. Well, listen.
I--I got to come with you.
I know it's not
my Laurel,
but I--I can't sit
this out either, so...
Ok.
Nice outfit
except for I would
have gone with fishnets.
Priority is
Black Siren
in custody and unharmed.
Quentin!
Ugh.
- How's Rene?
- Curtis and Lance took Rene
to Dr. Schwartz
for treatment
it's a collapsed lung.
It doesn't look so good.
Black Siren
and the mercenaries escaped,
but we pulled this
off the van.
- GPS?
- Yeah. Let's backtrace it,
figure out where
they came from.
On it.
Dinah, Quentin thinks
the attack on SCPD was targeting him.
- Any idea why?
- No.
If Laurel was
after Lance,
why blow up
the precinct
after discovering
he wasn't there.
Maybe Quentin was wrong.
Maybe our first
instincts were right.
That she's targeting
the police for some reason?
We need to figure out
what that reason is,
and we need to find her.
Oh, funny
you should say that.
GPS' last location
was a warehouse--
surprise, surprise--
outside Pennytown.
If this Laurel is half
as smart as our Laurel,
she would not go
back there.
Maybe she left something
behind for us to go on.
- John.
- We are on it.
The blast blew her
over there.
Thea?!
Clear!
It's all packed up.
Doesn't look like they were planning
on coming back here.
The question is
where were they headed?
Stay sharp. Look around.
In my experience,
bad guys aren't very
good at covering their tracks.
You all right?
Yeah. Why?
Since the bridge,
you seem distracted.
Just worried
about Rene, that's all.
Saw you take the shot
at that merc.
Never seen you miss.
Nobody makes
every shot.
What about you?
I don't know.
What about me?
I saw your reaction
when Oliver asked you
why evil Laurel
targeted Lance.
And I said
I didn't know.
And I didn't find
your answer that convincing.
Really?
What the hell
is that?
It's a map
of city hall.
With ingress and egress marks
and line of sight.
For an attack.
Why the hell would they
want to attack city hall?
After the SCPD
got bombed, they had to
move the academy
graduation to a different venue.
Oliver chose city hall,
but that decision was kept under wraps
for security reasons.
How the hell did
these guys find out?
I don't know, but we're running out
of time to stop them!
Bombs really did
their work in here.
Yep.
Maybe I should just
do this alone, huh?
What, in case you find
my fake daughter dead?
Or alive.
It's all right.
I'll be fine.
Oh. Now what's what,
in case she's not dead?
In case
Talia al Ghul isn't.
That's what John gave
me this for.
Besides, swords aren't
really my thing come on.
Think they knew
what they were signing on for
when they threw
in with Chase?
Seems to me they threw in
with Nyssa's sister.
Either way, I'm gonna
go with a no.
Dinah!
Hi, Daddy.
Laurel.
This might be
a late night, Raisa.
I remember when your
late nights were
more like
early mornings.
Thankfully, I've
exchanged club openings
for Police Academy
graduations now.
Raisa!
Another nightmare.
I know how to get him back to sleep.
No, no. I'll get him.
Hey, buddy.
W--where's Raisa?
I'm here.
It was just a dream.
The bad man
was in my dream.
He's why my mom's
gone.
Well, he can't hurt you
anymore, William.
He's gone.
No, he's not.
Buddy, I'm confused.
I'm...One.
Where do you think
the bad man is?
Hey. Is
everything ok?
I'm worried
about William.
- You want to talk about it?
- I would love to talk about it,
but we have more
pressing business, ok?
- Right.
- Ok.
Ok. Well, I--I
cracked the code,
I mean, so to speak.
You are welcome.
These are
the targeted areas,
which means we can
almost be 100% positive
that evil Laurel
and friends will be attacking
the Police Academy
graduation tonight.
The question is why.
9 dead officers
wasn't enough for them?
No, it wasn't...
Because she didn't get
who she was after.
You mean you?
Quentin.
Dinah, I appreciate you
having my back,
but I appreciate
the truth a little bit more.
Wait. What exactly
are we missing here?
You're missing why I told
you guys that Dinah and I
found Laurel dead
back on Lian Yu.
Quentin, I don't think
you have to do this.
Yeah, I do.
I've been living
with this guilt for too long.
I can't do it anymore.
Bad Laurel...
She wasn't dead when we found her
back on Lian Yu.
The bad news is is that you won't be
able to scream anymore,
but the good news is
is that you'll be too dead to care.
I told Quentin to say
she was dead when we found her
to spare him the pain
of telling you all the truth.
The truth is
he saved my life.
The truth is I killed
my daughter.
I killed my baby girl.
I just left her for dead.
That's the truth.
She was gonna kill me.
As sure as I am
standing here right now,
she was going to kill me,
and you saved my life.
Mm-hmm.
You're staying here
tonight.
I can't.
Quentin, if Laurel
is targeting you, then she--
Then she's not
gonna stop,
and the only way
we can stop her
is by dangling me
right in front of her,
so I'm gonna be there tonight
front and center, ok, you understand?
All right.
You're at
the graduation,
but we need SCPD canine units at
every entry point.
Actually, we can
kill the canines.
- What?
- Um, by kill,
I do not mean kill
the actual dogs. I--
Curtis, what
are those?
These are the latest
in high-tech sniffer devices.
Wait. Those are
bomb detectors?
They can spot as little
as an ounce
of explosive material
within a 1,000-foot radius.
Yeah. The only catch
is that we actually have to be there
to operate them,
which means Curtis and I
need to be on the field,
which means no one will be down here
operating the comms.
I'll do it.
Someone has to take
one for the team.
I can do it.
You sure?
Yeah. My gun would get
lost in all that Argus
and SCPD firepower
anyways.
I'll stay.
Ok.
Ok. Let's get
out there.
We have to get her
out of here.
Oliver?
Samantha?
William?
He's fine, he's fine.
Are you ok?
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Hey. No. He's fine.
He's fine.
We have to get you
medical attention.
No. I just needed to
make sure that he was ok.
He wants to see
his mom.
William needs a parent.
Promise me...
That you will be
his father.
I promise.
Curtis, you got anything?
Negative, and shouldn't
you be calling me Mr. Terrific?
I am in the field.
Yeah, but you're not
in your suit,
so no suit,
no codenames.
Them's the rules.
How about we
try to focus instead?
Spartan, what do you see?
So far, so good.
Yeah. Maybe they
decided to rethink their plan.
That'd be a smart move.
Haven't seen this many cops
in one place in my life.
Me either.
I'm a cop.
Yeah. Well, it doesn't mean
they're not gonna try something,
so everyone stay sharp.
Thank you all
for being here.
In light of the recent attacks
on the SCPD,
tonight's ceremony is
incredibly important,
and while we need to mourn
the loss of life,
I feel the need to mention
that this city
is better off than it
has been in quite some time.
Crime is down.
Our streets are peaceful.
People are
not only moving here,
they are staying here,
and do you want to know why?
It's because you help
them feel safe.
You have chosen
a profession,
one of the most dangerous
professions in the world.
Whereas other people
run from danger,
you run towards it
time and time and time again,
and for that,
we all owe you
a huge debt
of gratitude,
so thank you.
Thank you for protecting
our families,
for protecting us,
and for protecting
our beautiful city.
Thank you.
- Well done, Mr. Mayor.
- Of course.
You keep this up, they're gonna ask you
to run for governor.
Yeah? I'm just glad
a bomb didn't go off during the speech.
Anything from Black Siren
and her crew?
You mean the psychopaths
I unleashed on this city?
No, not yet.
You cannot take that
on, Quentin,
and this speaking
as one of the world's
leaders
in feeling guilty.
Um, have you ever
fired a gun at your own daughter?
That is--ahem--that's
not what happened.
Black Siren
is not Laurel.
She is Laurel.
You know it, and I know it,
and we both know that this parallel
universe crap is crap!
All right. Every time
I see her, I get
that--that feeling,
that instinct.
She's my child.
She's--she's
my baby girl, Oliver,
and I tried to
kill her.
Well, from what I understand,
you were protecting a friend.
You are not just
a good man, Quentin.
You are a good father.
I know because you're
a better father than
I could ever hope to be.
You got to give it
some time.
You only been at it,
what, 5 months?
It's not getting
any easier.
- Well--
- William blames me
for Samantha's death.
- Why?
- Because he's a smart kid,
and he knows what
happened happened
because I was involved.
He shouldn't be with me.
He should be
with Samantha's parents.
Well, listen. That's not what
Samantha thought.
I don't know how to
reach him.
Just be his father.
Hey. Anything?
Nothing. Curtis and
I have scanned every inch of this place.
Something seems
really off.
Let's get in touch
with Spartan,
see if he saw anything
on the cams.
Spartan,
do you copy?
Yeah. Still here,
still nothing.
Maybe Argus scared them off.
Maybe they're targeting
Lance some other way.
Maybe he isn't the target--
John.
John, do you copy?
John, are you ok?
Don't worry, Felicity.
John's fine.
He's just gonna be catching up
with an old friend.
Shouldn't you be protecting
the graduation ceremony?
Oh, but what's wrong?
Did you lose your nerve
along with your aim?
I don't know.
You tell me.
You want me to
kill him?
I'm not paying you
to keep him alive.
Let's get to work.
You're not gonna
feel a thing, promise.
You ok?
Unh!
Pissed!
Just about finished.
Make sure you put
one here, too.
Incoming!
Aah!
God, you are such a bitch.
Yeah. It takes one
to know one, sweetheart.
Hyaaah!
Good news.
The bomb sniffer works.
Bad news--it's
working in the bunker.
Yeah.
The whole place is wired.
Yeah. If you can take
the devices,
I can jam the detonation
signal remotely.
Is John ok?
I don't know,
but...I might not be.
Spartan's fine.
I have eyes on Black Siren.
Err!
To be continued.
Don't move!
I said don't move.
Well, this feels
familiar.
Maybe this time,
you'll aim for the heart.
I'm sorry.
For shooting me
or for leaving me for dead?
You were trying to
hurt my friend.
Oh. So--so you choose
your friend
over your own daughter?
Don't make me do
this, Laurel.
Please don't make
me do this.
So now I'm Laurel?
Don't torture yourself
because if we were back
on Lian Yu
and the roles were
reversed,
I would have
pulled the trigger.
Whoa. Hell of a mess.
Yeah. Ahem. What's
happening with the graduation?
Uh, went off
without a problem
unless you count
some food poisoning
from the city
caterer.
The graduation was
a distraction.
Laurel left that map
for me and Dinah to find.
So when did she pivot
from targeting them to targeting us?
Maybe she didn't.
I mean, maybe the SCPD
and the bunker
were her targets
all along.
That seems pretty random, particularly
considering how much trouble Laurel
went through to make sure
we wouldn't be here.
Well, what if planting
the explosives
wasn't her objective?
Planting the explosives
was cover her objective.
- Yeah.
- What if she was trying to
- steal something?
- Like what?
She doesn't need
weapons.
Mercenaries she's
working with do.
We should inventory
the armory.
We--we should inventory
everything that we have.
If she stole something,
we need to know what it is,
and we need to know
fast.
Hey. You all right?
Uh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm fine.
I'm just glad nobody
was hurt, you know?
- Yeah.
- Listen. I'm sorry
about, uh, lying to you
about what happened on Lian Yu.
Quentin, you don't
have to apologize to me.
I'm sorry that you had
to go through that.
When are you gonna stop
taking on everybody else's sins, huh?
No time soon.
- How you feeling?
- Oh. Like a million bucks.
Yeah?
All right. Maybe more
like a couple hundred,
but I'm alive, right?
Dr. Schwartz would like you in here
for a few more days.
I feel good.
Besides, when have
I ever listened to anybody?
Not to get too personal,
but what would happen to Zoe
if something
happened to you?
Not much.
Well, she's got
a new family now, Hoss.
I mean, she probably
doesn't even think about me.
She's your daughter,
Rene.
Of course she thinks
about you.
That ship's sailed.
I blew that chance
months ago.
Chase blew that chance
for you.
One of the many reasons
why I think you deserve another one.
I tried getting
another hearing.
Yeah. You're not
the mayor.
- You got me another hearing?
- Not just me.
The new DA had something
to do with it.
Ahh. All right. Ok.
Thank you, Oliver.
I owe you one.
Pay me back
by getting better.
Copy that.
Hey, kid.
Hello, Slade.
How's she doing?
She's the same.
What are you
doing here?
I popped by to say
that the Intel that you gave me
on my son Joe,
it panned out...
So I'm heading
to Calgary.
Well, that's great.
I'm very, uh--
I'm happy for you,
and I hope that--
I hope you find what
you're looking for.
You don't think
I will?
Ahem.
I think that finding
your son
doesn't always go
as planned.
Have things been
that hard with you and your son?
Yeah.
Be patient
but be prepared.
For what?
Choosing between being
the man that people need you to be
or the father that your
son needs you to be.
What do you mean
by that?
You and I...walk
between two worlds...
But we can only do
that for so long.
Good luck...Mr. Queen.
Good luck, Slade.
Gah!
You ok?
Yeah, I'm good.
Anything, uh, missing?
No. It's all
accounted for.
Including your gun?
Not that you seem to be
using it that much these days.
I, uh, checked it
after the fight down here.
You checked my gun?
You didn't even
fire it,
and none of the guys
down here got hit either.
Yeah. Dinah...
I found it!
And by "found it,"
I mean, I found
what Laurel--um,
Black Siren took,
which is actually more
like not finding anything at all,
but you get my point.
What poin--no.
We--no. I'm not sure we do.
She took one of my T-spheres,
prototype version.
A prototype,
meaning it's not weaponized?
Well, then they
can't use it against us.
Question is
what can they do?
Hey, buddy.
William, I know that
the last few months
have been difficult
for you,
and I know that you
blame me for part of that.
I used to blame
my dad for things.
He wasn't perfect.
Neither am I...
But he loved me.
I know how much
your mom loved you.
She really did,
but you need to know
that the last thing that she asked of me
was to take care you.
Now you don't have
to like me
for me to take
care of you
because I'm your dad.
The way that works is
I am gonna be there for you
whether you want me
to be or not.
I am never, ever
walking away from you.
There's a game on
tomorrow if you want to...
Stay up late
and watch it.
Football
or baseball?
Baseball.
Ok.
Hi. I was just gonna
give you a call.
Turn on channel 52
right now.
Ok.
...with the discovery
of a shocking photograph
that seems to finally
solve the mystery
haunting Star City
for the past two years--
who is the Green Arrow?
This photo, which was
obtained exclusively
by channel 52 provides
unequivocal proof
of the identity
of the vigilante known
as the Green Arrow.
Oliver...
This is the latest
controversy to hit...
What are we
gonna do?
What else has the mayor
lied about?
As always, we'll keep you updated
with breaking news on channel 52.
I--I don't know.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Greg!
Move your head.