(GRUNTS)
(GUNFIRE)
-FELICITY: I want a codename.
-What?
Well, everyone's got a codename.
You even got a new one. I want a codename.
Find the bomb and then we'll talk.
I'm scanning frequency signatures.
I just know we're not gonna talk about it.
John, you've got a runner.
I'm on it.
Got it. Ghosts' frequency of choice is on
the ground level.
Ten'll get you 20 it's the bomb.
I don't mean that "it's the bomb,"
like it's good, like, "It's the bomb!"
I mean like it's the explosive.
Got it. Ground floor.
You better move it.
The signal strength I'm reading,
they can blow the treatment plant
from Central City.
(BEEPING)
It's done. Get Diggle down here
to handle the dismantling.
You know, it seems like he could
use a codename, too.
Just get him down here.
Saving the city's water supply, that's
an honest night's... Morning's work.
(SCOFFS)
Yeah, but no matter what we do,
these Ghosts, they keep coming.
We still did a good job tonight.
Yeah, not good enough.
Hey, can I talk to you for a second?
Kind of felt like you were
out there for blood tonight.
Look, you haven't been dealing with these
Ghosts as long as we have.
If I go easy on them,
things are gonna end bad really fast.
I'm worried that if you keep going the way
that you're going,
you're going to put one
of them down permanently.
I know where the line ends, okay?
And look, it's almost 9:00.
Mrs. Danforth and Madison are gonna be
at our house in, like, an hour.
So I have time for one of your lectures
or a shower. I pick shower.
Is everything okay?
You look nice.
It's my first day back at Palmer Tech.
I get to be bossy today
because I am the boss of a
multibillion-dollar corporation.
I know I should be nervous, I know,
but I'm not. I'm actually really excited.
You should be excited. That's why I got
you the first-day-as-a-boss fern.
Aw.
And packed your lunch.
Who are you?
-(GROANS)
-Answer me!
All right.
(GRUNTING)
What?
Come on.
OLIVER: Madison, how's school?
It's good. I graduate in May
with a degree in Ancient Philosophy.
Ancient Philosophy? What happened to
your dream of being J.T.'s backup dancer?
-That's still plan B, obviously.
-(LAUGHING)
It is so lovely to see you two. Really.
It's been far too long.
No, Thea and I were glad you got in touch.
Yeah, we were a little surprised though.
Well, I admit that
reconnecting with the son and daughter
of one of my dearest friends is not the
only reason that I wanted to see you.
And here comes the crazy.
Last week, like the rest of the city,
I saw the Green Arrow's broadcast.
And it hit me.
If that man could take up the Arrow's
mantle, I could take up your mother's.
Um, how?
By running for mayor.
See, I told you. Crazy.
No one's opposing me, obviously.
But there'll still need to be an election.
There's a very good reason that no one
else is running.
Yeah, the last three mayors
have been killed.
To say nothing of the city's leadership
last week.
Which is exactly why we need
a mayor more than ever.
I want to step forward,
and I'm asking for your support.
Wow. You guys look bigger than you did
when you were on my computer screen.
Perhaps, we should begin with this
quarter's financials.
Thank you. Uh... Okay.
I know I don't have a business degree
or an accounting degree or an MBA,
but this looks very, very bad.
These are hard times
for everyone in Star City.
This company is not immune.
Fortunately, Mr. Holt
has devised us a way out.
Oh. Goody.
Um... Hello. (CHUCKLES) I'm actually not
a member of the board.
I work in the
Design Innovations department.
Tell Ms. Smoak about your algorithm.
It's pretty simple, actually.
I used specialized A.I.
to determine maximum profits
which can be derived with a minimal
amount of workforce reduction.
Sorry. I probably could've
explained that better.
FELICITY: No. I got the gist.
You came up with a list
of people that you'd like me to fire.
"Workforce reduction"
has a nicer sound to it.
It's just kind of rolls off the tongue.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Yeah. Well, the only thing
we'll be reducing
is all of your bonuses, to start.
We've already been down that road and
exhausted all other avenues, Ms. Smoak.
I didn't come back to this company to put
the people who work here out of work.
I came here to protect
Ray Palmer's legacy.
And if we do not dramatically reduce our
costs or increase our profits,
there won't be a legacy to protect.
Am I the only one that has
a bad feeling about this?
I mean, signing up to be mayor of this
town is like asking to be part of Titanic.
You heard me try to talk
her out of running.
I'm pretty sure that got covered up
by you telling her we'd be at her big
announcement.
MAN: Ladies and gentlemen,
Jessica Danforth.
(APPLAUSE)
Thank you. Thank you all so much.
For the past six months, the mayor's
office at City Hall has stood vacant,
waiting for someone to step forward
on behalf of Star City.
And today, I am here with all of you
to tell you that I am stepping forward.
(APPLAUSE)
Two years ago, I lost my good friend,
Moira Queen,
who was also a candidate for mayor.
And I remain inspired by her kind heart
and her selfless devotion to this city.
(GUNFIRE)
Shots came from up there. No, no, no.
You protect Jessica, okay? I've got this.
(GUNFIRE CONTINUES)
The shots are just a distraction!
There's no Ghosts up here.
Whoa, whoa, wait, wait.
You're not on her detail.
Get back to the atrium!
Oliver, how...
Uh... Self-defense classes.
She announces her candidacy
and two seconds later
someone's trying to kill her?
That must be a record, even for our city.
And she's not dropping out of the race,
so this isn't over.
My father has a protective detail on her.
Yeah, but even with protection
at the announcement,
she didn't seem to be too safe.
Is it just me or is the shooting of a
potential city leader
feeling a little Ghost-y?
This guy wasn't wearing a mask so...
There was something else different
about him. He left behind evidence.
DIGGLE: Fingerprints.
How'd you get the
owner to part with his windshield?
I bought his truck.
It's one of the benefits
of your girlfriend inheriting
a multibillion dollar conglomerate.
We have money now.
I don't exactly think
that was money well spent.
I don't think these prints
are gonna do us any good.
What the hell?
I'm not an expert, but I think our new
friend may have cut off his fingertips
and played a little bit of mix and match.
I'll keep digging. Maybe this is an M.O.
that'll tell us something.
In the meantime, we backstop the SCPD.
Thea was right. Jessica needs
more than the police can offer.
She's in protective custody and I'm
pretty sure my father wouldn't be in favor
of us staking out his precinct.
I'll talk to him.
Oh, yeah. That'll definitely go over well.
Mrs. Danforth is under our protection,
24/7,
until this nutbar's in cuffs.
Do you have a minute?
Caught your TV debut.
Guess you decided to stick around.
It's gonna be different this time.
Yeah, yeah, sure it will, 'cause you got
a new name, now, right? With a color.
"Green Arrow." It's catchy. (CHUCKLES)
Jessica Danforth is a friend.
We would like to help keep her safe.
With everything this city's facing,
I thought you could use
all the help you could get.
You've been gone.
You don't know what this city's facing.
Well, I'm not saying
it doesn't need saving.
But a guy hiding behind
a mask isn't gonna get it done.
What this city needs is someone willing to
stand up in the light of day,
not a guy lurking around in the shadows.
You say you're gonna be different
this time, huh? How?
You're late.
I know. Sorry. I was looking at
the numbers again and...
Oh, you mean the "numbers" of people that
your magic "downsizing algorithm"
is making us fire today.
-Downsizing... You think I... I didn't.
-Let's get one thing straight.
The only person who is allowed to talk in
sentence fragments around here is me.
I developed my algorithm
to create a value matrix.
To argue for company-wide
pay increases. Raises.
Mr. Dennis turned it around and had me
use it to figure out who to fire.
So this wasn't your idea?
I was trying to get people to get paid
more, not paid nothing.
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
Hi. I'm Karla Groves.
My supervisor asked me to come see you.
Hi. Yes. Um...
I don't know quite how to say this...
I'm fired.
But clearly you do.
As rumors go,
downsizing ones tend to go viral.
I'm very sorry. I didn't come back here to
put people out of work.
But I am hoping that by losing a few jobs,
I can save many, many more.
That looks like a little more than a few.
Yes. The company is going
through a difficult time.
I know.
And when we heard you were coming back,
we thought things were going to get
a lot better.
Guess we were wrong.
I'm still hungry.
Is it wrong that I'm still hungry? John?
Shift change is in 10 minutes.
You know, for the past week, you've been
pretty intense.
Are you going to tell me what's going on?
And don't tell me
it's because Oliver is back.
Well, I'm not happy Oliver's back.
Yeah, you weren't exactly
subtle about that.
(SIGHS) Just let it go, Laurel.
No, because we don't keep secrets,
remember?
John, what's going on?
Remember last week,
when Oliver was telling us about Darhk?
He said he had a hive of followers.
An organization called
H.I.V.E. killed my brother.
I didn't know.
Do you think it's some
kind of coincidence?
No. I've been looking into this
organization for two years now.
All dead ends.
But what I did manage to dig up tracks
with what we know about Darhk's Ghosts.
They're H.I.V.E.
Do Oliver and Felicity know?
No.
You've been investigating this for
two years and you haven't told anyone?
This is a family thing, Laurel,
I would think you of all people would
understand keeping secrets
when it comes to the death of a sibling.
I do.
And because I do, I can tell you,
carrying a burden like that,
it never ends in any way but bad.
That was quite the show.
False machine gun.
Impersonating a bodyguard.
You've the flair for the dramatic,
Mr. Machin. I will give you that.
Too bad it was all for nothing.
Half of your fee has been
wired into your account.
This isn't about money for me.
I know. You came to me with promises.
You wanted to impress yourself to my
organization, and you failed.
I'm not done yet. Just give me more time.
I will make sure that Jessica Danforth
does not run for mayor.
Very well. However, a word of caution.
I'm not sure how Rick Pinzolo runs his
operation, but H.I.V.E. does not believe
in third chances. Good night.
Spoke to Diggle.
No movement at the precinct.
That's all right.
I may have some movement here.
I noticed something tacky on the palm
print our guy left on the windshield.
-Tacky?
-Like a residue.
What kind?
Cellulose.
Oh, except this formulation is special.
The molecular structure's been patented.
By who?
Palmer Technologies.
A subsidiary, actually. Palmer Paper.
I had to shut down the mill a couple
months ago as a cost-cutting measure.
Where's the paper mill?
Hey, stay sharp.
He has some sort of electricity weapon.
The man in the photo, have you seen him?
I don't see much. I like my sleep.
But that guy, he sees a lot. He deals
outta here. Does a lot of business.
Hey, we need to ask you a few questions.
Step off, freak.
Have you seen this guy here?
I want a name.
You masks, you think you're in charge.
Yeah, well, maybe you were,
but not anymore.
-There are new masks in charge.
-(GROANS)
I asked you. Have you seen this guy here?
Do you still wanna use your arm?
Let him go!
You still think you're in charge?
-(GROANING)
-Hey! Get out of here!
(GASPING)
(GROANING)
I got an ID on our Mr. Creepy.
I thought his fingerprints were
all screwed up.
Mixed up. But I have an obsession
with jigsaw puzzles.
Lonnie Machin. Part-time mob enforcer,
full-time crazy-pants.
Done jobs for the Bertinellis,
the Triad, Rick Pinzolo...
We're going to talk about this.
We're going to have a conversation
about what just happened.
What just happened was that guy had
information and I was
trying to get it out of him!
-You broke his arm.
-He was stalling!
He was scared. Come here!
What are you doing?
I'll just show you something.
At the water-plant, you took down a Ghost.
You could have done it with a very
simple disarming technique. Like this.
Thea, that's not what you did.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
You went overboard
with a series of techniques
designed to do one thing, cripple!
-Oliver!
-(THEA GRUNTS)
(YELLING)
That's enough!
-Come on! Come on!
-That's enough!
Demonstration's over.
(PANTING)
It's fine. It's fine. It's fine.
After Ra's hurt you,
Malcolm warned me
not to take you to Nanda Parbat.
He said that when people go in the Pit,
they don't come out the same.
And I didn't tell you because
I didn't wanna worry about you.
You seemed normal, Thea.
And I swear to God,
I thought everything was gonna be fine.
And then you left. So you know what?
It doesn't really qualify you to judge me,
or anyone else!
What's going on?
What happened to Thea in Nanda Parbat?
I did what I had to do to save my sister.
That was six months ago.
Why is the Pit only affecting her now?
It's probably been showing up over time.
Subtly.
So what do you want to do about it?
You! Hey! Stay down!
I guess you know what happened to Kenny.
-Don't move! Don't move!
-Just shut up!
That's a minefield, all right?
That's what killed your friend.
And who the hell are you?
My name is Oliver Queen.
Three years ago, the yacht that I was on
went down in a storm.
I washed up here. I survived.
Let's take him to Reiter.
He'll know what to do with him.
Wow. You look like someone who has
to fire a whole mess of people today.
What? Oh, no. I mean, yes.
But this isn't about this.
Not that firing a dozen people is going
to do much for my mood.
Actually, it's two dozen.
-What?
-The pages are double-sided.
But there has to be another way.
This many intelligent people in the
company, there has to be someone who...
Ms. Smoak? Are you all right?
Absolutely.
-It's okay.
-What is?
I'm on the list, aren't I?
Yeah. I'm so sorry.
It's okay. It means one less person that
you have to fire today, right?
You know, actually, this is good news
in a way. My husband'll be thrilled.
I mean, this way, we can take that trip
that he's been wanting to go on.
Of course, I'll have to drive.
You don't have to try and make me feel
better about this.
About what? I sort of fired myself.
Come to visit me in my confinement?
I thought you could use some company.
And a little, "I told you so"?
Oh, I didn't bring it.
You know, that being said,
it's not too late for you to drop out.
And send what message?
That on top of the city's other problems,
we give in to terrorism?
The people here deserve better.
They deserve someone to be brave for them.
That's what the Green Arrow is for.
He's not enough.
Yes, the Green Arrow risks his life to
keep the people of the city safe,
but who inspires them?
You know, who works to make sure
that there's a city worth saving?
Who's there to make Star City a place
that my daughter wants to call home?
Where is Madison?
Oh. Library. Poor kid has finals so I sent
her back to school.
Don't worry. Captain Lance sent her with
more than enough cops to keep her safe.
Maybe you should call her.
(PHONE RINGING)
To the man who took my daughter, please,
I am begging you. Please let my baby go.
She's all I have. She's my whole world.
Killed the officers escorting her
with some kinda weapon.
Shot them up with five thousand volts,
slit their throats for good measure.
His name is Lonnie Machin.
Do I even want to know
how you got that intel?
You can't do this alone. You know that.
Now, two of your guys are down.
Now let us help.
What is this place?
Over there.
Baron, this guy says he's...
Oliver Queen. You don't recognize him?
This man's a minor celebrity
on the other side of the world.
You're supposed to be dead.
Nearly was.
Thank you for rescuing me.
I'm sorry, but we're not rescuing you.
The first thing you do once you get home
is tell people what
it is we're doing here.
I don't know what you're doing here.
Be that as it may, I can't send you home.
Not right now.
Good news, though,
I've no reason to kill you.
So what are you gonna do to me?
Good question.
You've survived three years here.
All alone.
That requires fortitude, intelligence.
Qualities that are of use to me.
As it happens, one of my men stepped
on a land mine.
How would you like his job?
Thanks for coming on such short notice.
What did you do?
Where is Jessica Danforth's daughter?
Did you catch the news earlier?
Ms. Danforth,
begging for her daughter's life.
She'll do anything to get her back.
Or not do anything. Like run for mayor.
All I have to do is make a phone call.
Now I see why Rick Pinzolo banished you.
You're unaware that there are lines
one does not cross.
I met one of your Ghosts.
After I took his tooth, we had an
interesting conversation about H.I.V.E.
I wasn't led to believe
you respected lines.
I respect order, Mr. Machin.
Discipline. Precision. You are sloppy.
All you represent is anarchy. You made
a mess. I suggest you clean it up.
Either way, our relationship is concluded.
Wait. You can't.
You know your hand is on me?
Clean it up.
JESSICA: To the man who took my daughter,
please,
I am begging you.
That's heartbreaking.
Please let my baby go.
Hey.
Are you okay?
Just can't stand watching
Jessica go through that.
I feel like that's what my mom felt like
when Slade Wilson abducted me.
That's not what you asked, though. Um...
I'm fine.
Well, you could have fooled me.
What happened to you on Nanda Parbat?
Ollie didn't tell you?
It's Ollie.
I guess I really am his sister
since I didn't tell you either.
I just didn't want to relive it.
Relive what?
Ra's, he...
He killed me.
(STAMMERING) Or almost did.
Ollie said that it was pretty bad.
And then Ra's
offered to use something...
I don't know, to bring me back.
Something he calls a "Lazarus Pit."
Wait, so what's happening to you now is...
is a side-effect from this Pit?
And Malcolm tried to warn Ollie,
I guess, but he
didn't listen.
No, of course he didn't.
He would do anything to save his sister.
I swear, if there is even
a scratch on that girl, so help me...
I'm afraid that is out of my control.
Yeah, well, so am I. I am out.
I am all the way out!
Well, I suppose you need a reminder
that Madison Danforth is not the only
vulnerable daughter in this city.
You stay the hell away from my daughter,
you son of a bitch!
Language.
What is this?
The location of the Danforth girl.
My sincere threat
against your daughter notwithstanding,
this abduction lacks taste.
The next time we meet, and make
no mistake, there will be a next time,
remember to mind your tone.
Any news?
Only the bad kind.
Hey, we're going catch this guy.
Yeah. And when we do,
there'll be another one waiting for us.
And another. And another.
It's like the most depressing game
of Whack-A-Mole ever.
Can't say we didn't know
what we were getting into.
Or back into.
When we decided to stay in Starling,
I mean, Star City,
I was excited.
I thought it meant a new beginning.
And now, we've only been back a week,
John,
still mad at you, Thea's gone Pit-crazy.
I've spent the last two days
putting people out of work.
If you think that we made a mistake,
we didn't.
Nothing worthwhile ever comes easy.
We said that we're going
to do things differently.
We just need time to figure out how.
(PHONE VIBRATES)
Captain.
Heavy Heavy Club, Fourth and Pierce.
OLIVER: What about it?
It's where Lonnie Machin is
holding Jessica Danforth's daughter.
(MOUTHING)
You said you're doing things
differently now?
Here's your chance to prove it.
(SOBBING)
Sorry to leave you hanging.
I had a meeting. Didn't go well.
Turns out, I can't sit
at the cool kids' table.
When trillions and trillions of
molecules exploded from a pinhead,
were there rules dictating how
to establish a universe?
-No.
-(WHIMPERS)
They found their way through the chaos.
Please, you can still let me go. Please!
Only if you promise not to tell
anybody about me.
Okay. Please.
Pinky swear?
I changed my mind.
(SCREAMS) My God!
The things I'm about to do to you...
(SCREAMING)
Something wrong with the front door?
Get away from the girl.
Could you come back in an hour?
We were just getting started.
Let's get her down.
Felicity.
So now, madman du jour knows you're
working with a Felicity.
This is why I need a codename.
We have Madison, but he's split.
No movement outside the club.
He must still be in there with you.
She needs medical attention.
Get her to safety. We've got this.
Hey, can you handle this?
I'm good.
-(GROANS)
-Speedy!
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Speedy, don't!
-Baby!
-Mom!
My baby!
-I'm okay. I'm okay.
-(BOTH SOBBING)
Madison, are you all right?
Yeah, bumps and bruises.
Probably the world's worst
case of insomnia.
I'm really sorry, but I got
an army of reporters out there
and they wanna know
if you want to make a statement.
Yes. I'll be out in a few minutes.
You don't have to do that tonight.
Yes, I do. Oliver, I have to tell them
what I've decided.
I have to tell them
I'm withdrawing my candidacy.
I'm not running for mayor.
Come on.
Thank you for trusting me.
You weren't kidding about
doing things differently, were you?
Instead of pin cushioning guys,
now you're burning them alive?
Yeah, Captain...
You're lucky Major is on his way to
Starling General,
or I would be booking you for murder.
Just so you're clear
where we stand with each other.
This man needs some water.
Did you hear me?
Yeah, I heard. Get back to work!
What are you going to do when all your
workers are dead from heat stroke?
Not your concern.
Like the man said, get back to work!
Ms. Smoak,
what's this we're hearing about
you halting the workforce reduction?
I thought we agreed...
You talked and I listened.
I wouldn't hardly call that an agreement.
With that said,
I did get around to firing a few people.
They've all been hired back, BTW.
And one of them reminded me that
Ray Palmer never would
have approved of this.
Ray Palmer is dead.
And this company will be too, unless...
I am going to stop you right there.
I'm sorry, Ms. Smoak,
you asked to see me. Uh...
I think there's been a mistake.
No. Actually, you have perfect timing.
I was just about to tell
Mr. Dennis about your project.
After I fired Mr. Holt, I had the
opportunity to review his active projects.
Turns out he is working
on something that is going to
revolutionize technology
and save this company.
Neither of which he can do with
a reduced workforce supporting him.
Intriguing. So what's this revolutionary
technology, Mr. Holt?
-Uh... It's...
-That is proprietary.
But I can assure you,
it will astonish the world.
Our annual shareholder's meeting
is in six months.
Present it there. Astonish us.
Oh, we will.
You don't even have an idea for some
"world-astonishing" technology, do you?
Nope. But I'm betting that you do.
Pretty bold move, Ms. Smoak.
Yeah, well, I'm trying to do things
a little differently.
(CHUCKLES)
Hello. Hey! How are you?
I guess I was wrong when I told you
not to worry about me.
Right or wrong, I'm still gonna worry.
It's right at the top of the
big brother job description.
Thea. I should have told you
about the Pit immediately.
That was the old me.
And who are you now?
Ollie 2.0?
No. I'm more like
Ollie 1.0
who's trying to do things differently.
Look, whatever you are going through,
we will get through it together.
I thought Thea could use some time out of
town. A spa getaway to clear her head.
As long as it's not near any hot tubs.
'Cause that's what got me
in this situation.
I think it's a good idea.
Can you and John handle things
while we're away?
Yeah. As long as we don't
kill each other first.
Bye.
I'm kidding, by the way.
We'll be fine. Probably.
Take care of her, okay?
Okay.
I like a spa as much as anybody, but I
think we both know whatever is going on
with me will not be fixed
with a mani-pedi.
That's why we're not going to the spa.
We're going to Nanda Parbat.
Thea, whatever is going on with you,
the League, they'll know what to do.
Why are we not telling my brother?
Because you're not the only reason
for us going to Nanda Parbat.
(SIREN WHOOPS)
What happened?
The ambulance didn't make it to
Starling General.
We tried to get the paramedics
on the radio,
and then we got a 911
call reporting this.
Machin, he...
I don't really know how to describe
what he did to them.
I'm not sure what that symbol means.
It means "anarchy."
Hello!
Hey, I'm out here.
-You look happy.
-(FELICITY CHUCKLES)
Don't tell me you started
enjoying firing people?
No more firing.
Good.
I figured out another way.
Wow. Maybe you could share
your secret with me.
Doing things differently is what I
promised myself.
You are doing things differently.
Not different enough, apparently.
Both Lance and Jessica Danforth
said something to me
about this city needing something that
the Green Arrow can't offer.
A decent sushi restaurant?
Hope. Inspiration.
Someone who can do things in the light,
who isn't afraid and...
Someone who can protect himself.
-Felicity.
-Mmm?
I'm going to run for mayor.
Are you sure you want to do this?
(EXHALES)