My name is Oliver Queen.
After five years
on a hellish island,
I have come home
with only one goal--
to save my city.
But to do so, I can't be
the killer I once was.
To honor my friend's memory,
I must be someone else.
I must be something else.
Previously on "Arrow"...
Slade!
I need someone qualified
to fix this boat.
I sure hope a Mr. Hendrik
is there with you.
There's no way
in hell I'm going back there.
Please, put the gun down!
You cannot die
until you have known
complete despair.
And you will,
I promise.
Stay away from Thea.
No...I can't!
She's not safe when
she's around you.
You love her,
and that's why you're going to do
what I'm asking.
It's
a dangerous city.
Mr. Wilson?
Call me Slade.
Your mascara
is running.
Thank you.
Are you
all right?
I don't know.
It's my boyfriend.
Ex-boyfriend now.
He just completely out of nowhere
decides to end things.
Heartbreak is something
I know all too well.
It's not an easy thing
to recover from.
Sometimes you never do.
Um, we're not at--
this isn't my home.
You're not
going home, Thea.
Get out.
Get out!
Hello, Thea.
It's a pleasure
to meet you.
♪ Arrow 2x18 ♪
Deathstroke
Original Air Date on April 2, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
No time.
You letting
the bad guys
stay alive
this year
has filled the jails up
to capacity.
Yeah.
Ready?
Well, I've been
working with Sara,
but I'm not exactly
a natural.
Neither was I.
Ok. We have
some work to do.
Sorry, I'm just having
a hard time keeping
my head in the game today.
Thea?
I just can't
stop thinking
what's the worst
that can happen
if I just told
her the truth?
Well, I told a guy
the truth and he got
struck by lightning.
To be fair,
probably won't happen again,
statistically.
Telling Thea the truth
won't make her safer.
Just the opposite.
What we're doing, Roy,
it's dangerous.
And anyone that is
even in our orbit
can get hurt.
Try again.
This time...
Aim.
What are those?
About a month's worth
of phone messages
from Queen Consolidated.
Toss them.
That's what I did with last month's
phone messages.
With Slade out there,
I don't have time for the company.
Well, you have to
make time, Oliver.
At least
three hours.
The annual board meeting.
There's absolutely
zero way that
the CEO can avoid
being there.
And I know
it's been a while,
so in case you've forgotten,
that's you.
Do you remember where
you put your business suit?
Or do you keep it
in a cool glass case, too?
I'm going to kill
all of you!
This is not personal.
Well, maybe a little.
It's not.
This is about
survival.
Survival.
What a noble word for murder.
Slade gave us no option.
Hendrik for Oliver.
And what gives any of us
the right to decide
one's life is more valuable
than another?
He is tied up.
We are not.
Once he gets the boat working,
Slade will have no more need for him.
So let's not kid
ourselves. Doing this
is effectively sentencing
Hendrik to death.
He would do the same
thing to any of us!
In heartbeat!
This is only option.
What if it's also
an opportunity?
To do what?
To kill Slade.
I know that I haven't been
here in a while,
but you don't look
like the entire Board of Directors.
The meeting doesn't start
for another half hour.
Really?
I routinely bump all
appointments 30 minutes
in anticipation
of you being late.
It's good policy.
But, thank you
for coming out
of hibernation for this.
Whether you recognize it
or not, it's your name on the building,
and no matter how many
meetings you miss,
you're still the public face
of this company.
Isabel, I realize
I have been distracted.
Thank you
for picking up the slack.
Ours is an unconventional
partnership,
but it's a partnership.
And it's working.
Indeed it is.
Oliver...
Your mother's here.
Family squabble?
And how is Ms. Rochev
these days?
Still angry that Dorothy
dropped a house on her sister?
Ahem. What are you
doing here?
Have you heard from Thea?
No.
You haven't returned
any of my phone calls,
so I'm left to resort
to checking in person
as to whether you're attending
the debate tonight.
I told you that I would publicly
support your campaign.
Anything else?
It would be
embarrassing for us both
if you couldn't at least
appear to be my son tonight.
I have gotten pretty good at
pretending to be someone I'm not.
I learned it from you.
Oh, excuse me,
have you seen Thea Queen?
Ok.
Speedy, it's Ollie,
and I'm at the debate,
where I thought
you would be.
Listen, I know that
you're upset about Roy,
but mom needs
both of us here.
So please,
just call me back.
You do not look happy.
Is everything all right?
Yes. My sister's
just a little late.
I'm afraid that's my fault.
SCPD insisted that I arrive
with a motorcade.
We tied up traffic
all over the city.
I'm sure Thea's
probably just fallen victim
to gridlock.
Well, I should
probably try her again.
Good luck tonight, Sebastian.
Thank you, sir.
I thought backstage was supposed
to be restricted access.
The benefits of having
a district attorney's badge, I guess.
You stop by to wish
Moira good luck?
I did. But I'm really glad
I ran into you.
I owe you an apology.
I accused you
of really terrible things.
You were going
through a very difficult time.
I'm just happy
you're on the mend.
Good luck tonight.
I'm not the one
who's going to need it.
Sebastian Blood is not
the man you think he is.
He's not going to revive the city
with social services.
He's going to bankrupt it
with unfunded mandates.
Mrs. Queen's problem
with my proposals
is that they will be paid
for by the one percent.
It's time that the wealthiest people
stop avoiding their responsibility.
But it will limit
their abilities to hire people.
All right, that's time,
and I will remind the candidates
to please refrain
from interrupting.
Now we have the next
in our series of video questions
submitted by
Starling City voters.
This one comes from...
Thea Queen.
Ok, there must be
some mistake.
Help!
Help! Somebody
help me, please!
He--sla--
Oh, my God!
We're going to find her, Roy.
We're going to get her back.
She's a tough girl.
Is she going to be alive
when we find her?
You can't think like that.
I can't stop
thinking like that.
Mr. Diggle.
Mr. Diggle!
I think I might have found
something. I'm working on it.
I am suspending my campaign
and devoting its resources
to the safe return
of Thea Queen.
Well, the video referenced
a demand, but no ransom.
Which means this might not
be about money.
We're going to get her
back, Moira.
I promise you.
Thea's coming home.
Now, can you think of anyone
who might want to get
to you through Thea?
No one except
for the families
of the 503 people
that died last year.
This isn't about the quake.
Well, how can you
be so sure?
You just need
to find the man in the mask!
Look, we're working on it.
We're running down every lead.
What are those leads?
Oh, God!
Oh, God, how could I
have let this happen?
Excuse me for a minute.
If I hear
about one more
invasive press inquiry being
sent to Mr. Queen
or to any member
of the Queen family,
I will hold you
personally responsible.
You're very scary.
Thank you.
My job is to take things off your plate,
now more than ever.
To that end, you remember how
at today's meeting,
the board nominated
new officers?
Voting has to take place
within 24 hours.
It cannot be suspended.
It's an SEC thing.
I can't think
about this right now.
I know, and I'm sorry,
but you have to.
You're the CEO and you
have responsibilities--
Which you handle
for me all the time.
A board vote is several orders of
magnitude different
from covering
a missed meeting.
You could appoint
someone CEO pro tempore.
That's not a good idea.
I'm appointing you.
What?
Congratulations.
You are the temporary CEO.
I can't.
Please.
Thank you.
Have Thea thank me,
when she's back
safe at home.
Mr. Queen? I need to talk
to you, it's about Mr. Wilson.
Since the last place
Thea was seen was Verdant
I used credit card receipts,
compiled a list
of customers last night,
pinged all their cell phones
and hacked into their
photos. The NSA is right;
it's a lot easier when
you don't need a warrant.
I eyeballed every photo.
There must have been thousands.
It's Thea.
I found this.
Partial plate
three blocks from the club.
Car's registered
to a Slade Wilson,
and it has GPS.
Where is it
right now?
Parked outside
a defunct bar on Roosevelt.
Ok, this doesn't
seem easy to you?
Slade using a car
registered in his name?
The whole thing smells rotten.
Either Thea's there or he is.
Either way, we have to go.
Yeah, I figured you'd say that,
which is why I worked up these.
Tibetan pit viper venom.
The League of Assassins'
poison of choice.
And the most powerful sedative
that I've ever worked with.
That'll give us an advantage.
But you are going to give us another.
Are you sure
you want me to go?
Are you angry?
Use that rage.
Well, you're just
always telling me to hold back.
Not tonight.
Landmines?
What kind of island
is this?
Can you remove the explosive?
Certainly.
Without it going off, eh.
Less certain.
Ah, KGB.
You taught me
many, many things.
Russian bomb,
Japanese bomb;
they both go...boom.
Congratulations, we are not dead.
Now what?
Well, Slade takes Hendrik
as we agreed.
And then once
they're far enough away...
What--
you want to rig
Hendrik into bomb?
Well, Peter was right.
Handing Hendrik over to Slade
is the same thing as killing him.
And you're right, too.
We don't have a choice.
I mean, at least this way,
he can take out Slade,
and then we can take the ship.
What?
Just...wondering.
When did you
become so scary?
Where is she, Slade?
The man
asked you a question.
Where is she?
What are you going
to do, kid? Kill me?
But then who would tell you...
Where your beloved Thea is?
Call detective Lance.
Tell him
to come down here.
Wh--what? Why?
To arrest
Slade Wilson.
Any idea what this son of a bitch
wants with Thea Queen?
No. We just need to make sure that
Slade gives up where he's holding her.
Does Oliver know?
That you're working
with the Arrow on this?
Oliver doesn't know
anything about the Arrow.
Hey, are you ok?
Yeah. It's just
that look in Moira's eyes.
Terrified she's lost
her daughter.
I couldn't go
through that again, Sara.
Officer Lance?
The Queen
family's here.
Mr. Lance, did he tell
you where Thea is?
Mrs. Queen,
thank you for coming.
This doesn't
make any sense.
Slade Wilson
is a friend.
And he's been in Costa Rica
for the past 72 hours.
He can provide flight manifests,
phone records,
even some videos, so he couldn't have
taken your daughter.
If he didn't,
then why did you arrest him?
We didn't.
He was apprehended by the Vigilante.
Who then contacted
officer Lance.
Lieutenant,
I can explain--
No, I think I got
a pretty clear picture.
God, you're a special
kind of stupid.
The whole reason
you're wearing that uniform
instead of a detective's shield is 'cause
you were working with the Vigilante.
A young girl is missing,
and you just--
And now you arrest someone
on his say-so?
You'll be lucky if the next uniform
that puts you in
isn't prison gray.
They're calling you
Deathstroke.
It's a bit flamboyant.
I like it.
How did you
get off the island?
That is your first question?
Well, you've made it
pretty clear
that you're not going to tell me
where my sister is,
so, yeah. That's
my first question.
I swam.
But it wasn't
without its obstacles.
The rip current
dragged me under.
The rocks on the reef
cut up my flesh to the bone.
But the Mirakuru...
It regenerated everything.
Except this.
You know, it's
just the two of us in here,
so why don't we try
being honest?
Why are you
doing this?
You know why.
It was five years ago.
It was yesterday.
Oh, I tried to let go
of the island...
But it's still got
a hold on me.
And if that hood that you wear
every night is any indication,
it's still got
a hold of you, kid.
She never did anything to you.
I did.
Shado is dead because
of a choice that I made.
So punish me.
Blame me.
But...
Thea.
You want me to beg?
Is that what this all about?
Because I'm begging.
You win.
Just, please...
Please tell me
where she is.
Hmm, that must have been
hard for you to say.
Thea...
Well, Thea's--
Mr. Queen.
Who the hell
let you in here?
Mr. Wilson...
You are free to go,
with the department's
deepest apologies.
No need, Lieutenant.
An innocent girl's life
hangs in the balance.
You need to follow
every lead possible.
Well, still, you should
know that officer Lance
is facing some very
serious charges.
Well, don't pursue them
on my behalf.
I'm not one to hold a grudge.
Mr. Wilson, Mr. Wilson, have
the police cleared you of all charges?
I was in Costa Rica,
but returned to Starling City
as soon as I heard
the terrible news.
What did you tell them about
Thea Queen's disappearance?
I'm offering every resource
at my disposal,
plus a $5 million reward
for any information that leads
to Thea Queen's captors.
This is Dig,
I've got the follow.
Tracker
on his car is active.
Roy, he's coming up
on your position.
Got him. He's
turning up Warner.
I see him. Heading north.
Damn it, I lost him!
It's all right.
I still have eyes on him.
- Sara, cut right onto Downey.
- Got 'em.
Negative.
Negative, it's not him!
What?!
Oh, my God.
He's cloned
the tracker's signal.
Roy, you've got to move!
Roy, you got
to pick him up on Fuller.
Roy, do you
still have eyes on him?
Roy?
Roy!
Leave us.
Sorry I was gone
for so long.
Screw you.
I saw Oliver
and your mother.
They're all quite
worried about you.
If you hurt them,
I swear I--
Please. Go on.
Finish that sentence.
I'm curious to know
what kind of threat
a 19-year-old girl
can make.
What do you want with me?
Well, that, Thea...
is a very long story.
Looks like I've got time.
Not at all.
You're free to go.
What?
I had to make a point,
and I made it.
The door
is unlocked,
so you can leave
any time you'd like.
But those guys
who work for you
will shoot me
the second I walk out.
No, they won't.
Their instructions were to keep
you here until I returned.
And I have. So...
You're free to go.
But, if you do,
you may never know about
your brother's secret.
What?
Your brother
has a secret, Thea.
Would you like
to know what it is?
So...
What now?
Wait for Oliver.
Figure out what our next
move will be.
Wait for him
to tell us, you mean.
We can't do anything
without King Queen's permission.
You're out of line, Roy.
All right, let's all
just calm down here.
Slade outplayed us.
It happens.
No, it only happened because
the police let Slade go--
after we turned him in,
because Oliver told us to.
What were we
supposed to do?
You're Special Forces.
She's an international
assassin. You would think
between the three
of us, we could have gotten answers
out of Slade ourselves
instead of turning him into the police.
Here's what's really sick;
Is we didn't even question him
because he said it was
the right thing to do.
Just like he said  that I needed to
break up with Thea.
One week after telling me that it wasn't
safe for me to leave her alone.
Wait!
You think it's Oliver's fault
that Slade took Thea?
I think it was his fault that
I wasn't there to stop Slade.
And I think you're just
blaming Oliver because you lost Slade.
Well, of course you'd take his side,
you're screwing him.
Can you guys give us
a minute, please?
Do you remember how
she loved to color?
Your father would buy
her boxes of crayons by the truckload.
She could never get enough.
She'd draw on the walls.
And I could never get angry,
because it was just so adorable.
You should try
to get some sleep.
Is my baby still alive?
What?
Is my baby
still alive?
Yes.
I woke up every day
for five years
the mother
who lost her son.
I--
I can't...
I can't
endure it again.
And now you hate me,
and you have every
justification.
Now is not the time.
Yes, it is.
It is exactly
the time.
I've told you
that these lies
were to keep
our family safe;
to keep us all
together,
but that was
the biggest lie of all.
And I told it
to you, to Thea,
to myself.
Because I was too weak
to face
any kind of truth.
What's happening now
isn't your fault.
From the moment
your children are born,
you worry what the world
might do to them.
But you never stop to think what
you might do to them.
That we could be
our own worst enemy.
Ollie!
What did you do to him?
Not enough.
And what did you
do to him?
We just knocked him.
It's better that way.
He wasn't exactly a fan
of the arrangement.
I would imagine.
Hendrik's all yours.
I know.
Wait.
It's an incredible thing,
this Mirakuru.
Not only does it
give you strength,
it also heightens
all of your senses.
TNT has
a particular smell.
How long before
it goes off?
90 seconds?
60 seconds?
You're thinking that
the blast would kill me,
but I disagree.
Not that I could say
the same for you lot.
I am tempted
to see this
blow you to pieces.
But then again, maybe
I'll just shoot you
the same way
that he shot Shado.
No.
Slade...
Hey, where are you going?
Well, sitting around
here isn't helping Thea, now is it?
Neither is you running off
half-cocked, Roy.
I know
that you think
that this is the Mirakuru,
but it's not.
I'm right,
and you know that I am.
So you better get the hell
out of my way.
Roy, just calm down.
It's what Thea
would want us to do.
She's right, Roy.
Come on, let's throttle back.
Aah!
Roy!
Next one goes
into your chest.
Let him go.
You would honestly kill me
because I dare
to criticize the almighty
Oliver Queen?
No, I'd kill you because you're
hurting my friend.
Let him go.
Let him go!
What the hell's
going on down here?
I'm done.
That's what's
going on.
Thea, she's out there, hurt or worse,
because of one person.
And that is not
Slade Wilson.
Roy...
I believed in you.
There's nothing
left for me here.
Oh, my God. Oliver...
Now what?
Publicity has drafted
a rather compelling
statement,
and I will be doing
the talk show rounds
to control the spin.
I'm sorry, Ms. Rochev,
but he was very...
Insistent.
Can you give us
the room, please?
Isabel, what have you done?
Me? Very little.
You're the one who
made this possible
when you made me CEO.
I know it was
only temporary,
but it gave me
the authority I needed
to call an emergency
board meeting.
As of 30 minutes ago,
your company
belongs to me.
The directors
unanimously made
my appointment
permanent.
I'd say they lost faith
in your leadership,
but that would imply
there was any.
Maybe you should
have focused a little less on
your...evening
activities.
Slade...
You're working for him.
With.
He knew planting me
in your family's business
would draw you back
to Starling City.
Truth be told, I was
skeptical, but...
Why are you doing this?!
I think it's sad
you don't know.
The sins of the father
are the sins of the son.
You are going to tell me
where my sister is,
or I am going to kill you.
Where is she?!
He's holding her
at a storage depot
just outside the city
limits. Tosca Cartage.
How do I know
you're not lying?!
It's cute how you think
this isn't all playing out
exactly how he wants it to.
And he wants you
to come alone.
If he even smells
your partners,
he will gut sweet little
Thea like a trout.
It was a pleasure
doing business with you, Oliver.
At least let us
surround the perimeter.
No, Isabel was very clear.
I come alone or Thea dies.
Ollie, this is another one
of Slade's games, and unless--
no, what I can't do,
Sara, is nothing!
What would you do if it were Laurel,
or your father, or your mother?
I will not get dragged into the
same debate over and over again!
Go.
Go get Thea.
Stop Slade.
Do whatever it takes.
End this once and for all.
Holy...Stop!
Stop, stop!
Halloween was six months
ago, ass hat.
Now get off the road
or get put down. You hear me?
I have
a proposal for you men.
Go!
Oliver, are you ok?
Yeah, I'm fine,
but Thea's not here.
You did it.
Did what?
Thea's fine. She's fine.
She walked into the precinct
five minutes ago.
Safe and sound.
What...
Oliver, did you hear me?
Thea?
She's fine, no injuries.
He didn't touch her.
He wasn't there.
He had a lot of men,
hired guns. He wasn't there.
Because he was
busy elsewhere.
Iron Heights reopened a wing
damaged in the quake.
There was a prisoner transfer.
Slade hijacked it.
Soldiers for his army.
Abducting Thea
was all a diversion.
Oliver!
Oh, thank God.
Oh, my baby!
Ohh! My baby.
What?
He told me.
Mr. Wilson...
He told me your secret.
How you've been
lying to me
for years.
How could you not tell me
Malcolm Merlyn was my father?!
I believed in you.
We were trying
to keep you safe.
Do you have any idea
who you sound like?
You sound like her.
Slade...
Death's too good
for them.
This island should be their
punishment.
Death is
too good for you.
This island should be
your punishment.
Their prison
for the rest
of their days.
Your prison for the rest
of your days.
Get him out of here.
Slade...
Get back!
I can help you.
You can live,
or you can die.
You choose.
Would you like to send a message
to your family?
'Cause as soon as this boat is fixed,
I'm paying them a visit.
Hell of a night.
Quentin Lance, master
of the understatement.
A word, officer?
Hold on, sweetheart.
Yeah?
I've spoken to DA Spencer
about your...situation.
She doesn't want
to press charges--
if you cooperate.
Tell us where
the vigilante is.
Well, I'd love
to, but I don't know.
Well, that's unfortunate.
Yeah, it looks like.
Quentin Larry Lance,
you're under arrest
for conspiracy and aiding
in multiple felonies.
What? Are you out
of your mind?!
What are you doing?
Wilson--Wilson did it!
I collared the right
guy. What are you--
You have the right
to remain silent.
What are you
doing?
You have the right to an attorney.
Dad!
Riding what pundits
are calling a sympathy bump,
Moira Queen pulled far ahead
of Sebastian Blood
in the latest polls
conducted in
the last 24 hours
by channel--
The whole thing just
blew up in my face!
How the hell do I
get elected now?!
I think you intended
a different tone.
You said I'd be mayor!
And you just
delivered this election
for Moira Queen,
and for what?
What is this obsession you have
with the Queen family?
You haven't told him?
Shh.
You promised me.
I promised you this city.
I promised you an army
with which to take it.
What is our status?
Queen Consolidated's
Applied Sciences division
is now fully dedicated
to replicating a serum
based on your blood sample.
You see...
Everything
is proceeding as planned.
Where are you going now?
To service my obsession.
Oliver Queen
needs one more distraction.
What are you two doing here?
We thought this is
where you would go.
You're predictable.
That, and you've been
sleeping on
the cot at night.
What are you doing here?
Where else would we be?
Roy was right.
At every turn, I had made
the wrong decision.
With him,
with...the company,
and...
and with Thea.
I was so focused
on what Slade might do to me,
that it never...
even occurred to me
what I could do to myself.
I am my own worst enemy.
That's Slade talking, Oliver.
Don't let him in your head.
I can't keep him out
of my head, Diggle!
I can't...I can't
stop him from doing anything.
Yes, you can.
What makes you so sure?
Because you're not alone, man.
Now what, boss?
Now we fight back.
Police have issued a warrant
for Slade Wilson
after Thea Queen named him
as the mastermind of her
kidnapping yesterday.
This in the wake of Wilson's
arrest and subsequent release
by the SCPD hours before
Ms. Queen was released.
In a statement to the press,
SCPD Lieutenant Franklin Pike
reiterated his support
for his department
despite what appears
to be a serious blunder.
He went on to say,
the SCPD is committed--
To making sure any arrest
they make is a legal one,
but without sufficient--
Don't worry.
I am not here
to harm you.
Go to hell!
All in good time,
I'm sure.
But before then,
I have come
to Starling City
to see Oliver Queen
suffer.
Oliver...What?
Why?
Because he's
not the man you think he is.
And how would you know that?
Because I know
Oliver Queen is...
The Arrow.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man