-You are late.
-It's 12:45.
Invitation said 1. I'm early.
And I'm never early.
Yeah, well, the ceremony's at 1.
Photos were at noon.
-Photos.
-Mm-hm.
Last time Lyla and I got married, we said
our vows on an ATV in a Registan desert.
This time, she hired a photographer.
So, yes, Oliver, photos.
That whole "best man" thing,
it's more like a...
-Not so good.
-No. That's all right. We'll Photoshop you in.
All right.
-Thank you for coming.
-Heh.
-See you brought your plus one.
-Oh, yeah.
-Nice to meet you. Ray Palmer.
-John Diggle.
-You hurt her, they'll never find your body.
-Ha. Ha, ha.
Nice to meet you. Pardon me.
Funny. Five months since we saw
each other. Now it's twice in two weeks.
-It's good to see you, Ray.
-Good to see you too.
Ooh. That was Lyla.
Rick was supposed to be our officiant,
but he got deployed to South Sudan.
-You don't have a minister?
-No.
Okay. What about online certificates?
I need Wi-Fi and three minutes.
Not that I'd officiate,
although I would be honored if you ask.
Or you could just ask me. I'm a minister.
It's a long story.
Normally this is the part where the officiant
offers words of insight about the couple.
Their history.
Which is difficult for me because I just
met John and Lyla eight minutes ago.
[ALL LAUGH]
And I understand
that you have written your own vows.
Which is great,
because that gives me less to do.
-You really wanna do this?
-Hell, yes.
-Do you?
-Even more than the first time.
Good. Because I'm not letting you
get away from me this time.
-I'm holding you to that.
-Good.
-I love you, Lyla.
-I love you too.
RAY:
All right.
John Diggle, Lyla Michaels,
I now pronounce you husband and wife.
[ALL CHEERING]
[ALL CHATTERING]
-Beautiful ceremony.
-Beautiful dress.
-Thank you.
-Did it come with a cast?
I started fighting with a new trainer.
She's enthusiastic.
-"She"?
-She's a friend.
Today's not about that.
-Hey, Laurel.
-Hi.
Nice bouquet.
Ah, yes. I kind of caught it.
-Well done.
-Thank you.
Oh, I hope it's okay
I brought Ray as my date.
Ray saved the day.
For the record,
I am not the one who used that phrase.
He's a good guy
and he clearly cares about you a lot.
-Are you happy?
-Yes. Very.
Good. That's all I've ever wanted.
You deserve a good guy
and a normal life.
[PHONE BEEPING]
Oliver.
LANCE: There were eight victims total,
all shot with arrows.
However, one escaped
and has given us a statement.
Which remains uncorroborated
so the district attorney's office...
...is going to continue
to investigate before filing charges.
REPORTER: So which one is it?
Is the Arrow being implicated here or not?
LAUREL:
We're not sure of anything yet.
We have a statement from Mr. Palmer.
While it's hard to ignore the good
Arrow has done for this city...
...it is equally hard to ignore
evidence of his guilt.
In any case,
the Arrow needs to be apprehended.
And at least brought to trial, if not justice.
I didn't know he was gonna do that.
I'm devoting my substantial
resources towards...
...making certain the Arrow
is apprehended.
Meet with Lance and tell him
it wasn't you.
-My word doesn't carry weight with him.
-Bring in the culprit.
-Figure out who's doing this.
-We know who's doing this.
-The League of Assassins.
-This is how Ra's al Ghul handles rejection?
No, I think the point is that he doesn't.
He's trying to turn the city against me. Make
the offer to take his place more appealing.
Hit the streets.
Whoever's doing this targets criminals.
We need to know who they'll hit next.
We need the information
the police have from the crime scene.
Whoever is under that hood
has to leave a trail, something to follow.
How can we help?
-Go to Starling City Airport.
-Okay. To do what?
-It's called a honeymoon.
-Fiji can wait.
No. Fiji can't wait.
All right? This is still your day.
I'm not gonna let Ra's al Ghul ruin that.
-Oliver...
-You followed me into the lion's den already.
This time, choose your family.
Go. Live. We got this.
If it doesn't feel right
for you to go, we won't.
No, Oliver was right. It's our turn.
Besides, Felicity and Roy have his back.
Mazel tov, newlyweds.
Lawton.
-What are you doing here?
-Hey, when duty calls, we answer, right?
The Suicide Squad rides again.
Sorry to interfere with your
wedding night.
Yeah, I doubt that.
Five hours ago, there was a
terrorist attack in the Republic of Kasnia.
Hospital was supposed to serve and unite
Kasnia's dissident ethnic faction.
-Wait, is that...?
-Senator Joseph Cray.
This hospital was something
of a pet project for him.
Of course, he insisted on
being at the ceremony.
Agent Michaels, you'll lead
Task Force X on the extraction.
I'll have a plane ready for you
in 30 minutes.
I'm sorry, Johnny.
You go on to Fiji,
and I will meet you there in 48 hours tops.
No, you won't, because
I'm not letting you out of my sight.
You remember what I told you
about not letting go?
I meant that.
Waller.
Count me in.
You have the two of us. Deadshot.
Who else is on the team?
CUPID: Who else, indeed?
I've always wanted to see the world.
I hear Kasnia's beautiful this time of year.
Anything?
I'm accessing traffic cameras, ATM cameras,
phone cameras, 911 and squad car chatter.
-And?
-No sign of evil Arrow.
Los Halcones are unloading
a shipment of narcotics.
The entire gang is gonna show up.
This is the thing fake Arrow would go after.
FELICITY:
We really need a better name for him.
-When is this happening?
-Right now. I'll suit up.
Roy, this is the League. I've got it.
-So did you hire a florist?
-Yes, we did.
Didn't that cost a fortune?
For my wedding, I'll have the bridesmaids
make the flower arrangements.
And I'll spend the extra money
on the dress.
-Anything?
-Nope. We're clear.
-You seeing anybody, Cutter?
-Of course I am.
The Arrow. And our special day
is going to be the most glorious day.
And then afterwards, we'll make
strong, beautiful babies. Ha, ha.
And does he know this?
Listen, I got news for you, stalker. You don't
get to do what we do and have a family.
I have a wife right here and a child
that say otherwise. Let's hold up here.
Yeah, well, let's hope
you make it home to her.
Love, children, family.
It's all just a distraction for people like us.
They make us better.
Give us something worth fighting for.
Love is a bullet in the brain and if you believe
any different, you're as crazy as she is.
-Hey.
-All right.
Latest satellite flyover
reveals warm bodies here.
Yeah, that's pretty solid. Fortified.
How are we gonna get everyone out?
Our orders are to retrieve Cray,
no one else.
-What about the hostages?
-They're not U.S. citizens.
Are those your words or Waller's?
Let's not fight, Johnny.
It's our honeymoon.
See what I mean, John?
I'm not you, Lawton.
Yeah.
I wasn't always me either.
Just leave the package at the door.
Ma'am, I think you're gonna
want to sign for these.
Ah! Oh, my God. Floyd.
Why didn't you tell me
you were coming home? I'm a mess.
No.
No, you're perfect.
Mommy, who is he?
Zoe, baby, this is your daddy, remember?
I told you about him.
He was far away fighting the bad guys.
Now he's home.
Hi, Zoe.
Your daddy missed you
every second of every day.
She just needs some time.
I got him. Satellite footage of a man.
Green outfit. Green hood on the roof. Hurry.
[SHOUTING IN SPANISH]
[ARROWS WHISTLING]
[ALL GRUNTING]
[LAUGHING]
You can't kill them all, Oliver.
Where one falls, two more rise.
Maseo.
You can't believe in this.
Murdering all of these people
just to prove a point?
No. To persuade you.
My master sees something in you.
Don't fight it. Embrace it.
You know me better than that.
Don't let your recalcitrance
take any more lives.
Okay, I had no idea the sheer number
of crazies that were in the city...
...until you set up that
1-800 line for Arrow tips.
What's going on?
Ray?
Oliver Queen is the Arrow.
What?
I have a 140 IQ and three PhDs, but...
It's pretty hard to insult my intelligence,
but I think you just did.
It all makes sense now.
Your, uh, sudden disappearances.
Your apprehension with helping
on the mission.
You've been working with the Arrow.
How did you find out?
High spectrum portable radiograph.
Colloquially known as the x-ray machine.
Plus, your facial recognition software.
-Nice code, by the way.
-Hey, you got the suit working.
Hm.
Last night, I saw your friend Oliver
standing over eight of his victims.
Because he was investigating.
He's trying to catch an impersonator,
the one who's doing this.
Please, you have to trust me.
Oliver's not a killer.
This isn't the first time he's been
judge, jury and executioner.
-He hasn't killed anyone in nearly two years.
-That really is not your best argument.
You have no idea what he's been through.
What he's lost. How he's grown. But I do.
I know him better than almost anyone.
Oliver didn't do this.
-You have feelings for him.
-Yes.
I mean, no.
No.
I did.
But that's...
-That's over now.
-And what?
Now I'm supposed to trust you?
From the moment we've met,
I've held nothing back from you.
I did trust you.
And I thought that you were
someone who could be a true partner.
Thought you were someone that I could
rely on in my mission and in my life.
I wanted that too, Ray. I still do.
Ray.
What are you going to do?
I'm gonna honor the promise
I made to this city.
And help them bring the Arrow to justice.
[GRUNTING]
North entrance clear.
Nice work, Deadshot.
We're en route. Move to the X.
Copy that.
Here you go, sweetie. Eat it.
You won't eat it.
Is there something wrong with it?
It's not as good as Mom makes, I guess.
Use your words!
-Hm?
-Baby, what's going on?
-Nothing. I'm fine.
-No.
You're not fine.
You're not sleeping. You barely eat.
You can't hold a job. You can't socialize.
You won't talk to me.
We're talking right now.
So tell me what do you
want to talk about?
I wanna know what happened
to my husband.
You need to tell your story.
There are people who can help you.
Who know
what it's like to come back from war.
They don't understand.
You don't understand.
Nobody understands, do you hear me?
-Make them understand.
-Oh, make them understand.
Like this? You want to
make them understand like that?
How about like this? Huh? Do you want to
know what happened to your husband?
Let me tell you. He pulled triggers.
And every time I did, someone died.
Okay? Every single time.
Floyd.
Stop it.
Please.
Get away from us.
Yes, this is an emergency.
It's my husband. He has a gun.
[GROANS]
Find anything on those arrows?
This one is ours. This one is theirs.
-I don't see a difference.
-Yeah. Precisely.
They're identical.
He knows.
God, he knows.
Last year, Ray's fiancé
was killed by Mirakurumen.
And now he wants to protect the city so he
built a suit out of military-grade technology.
He wants to put you in jail.
He used my software to track you down.
He scanned you with his x-rays. He knows
you're the Arrow. He's gonna tell the cops.
Palmer knows I'm the Arrow?
He has his own mission
to protect the city?
When were you gonna tell me this?
I've been getting a lot of that.
It's not important.
He's gonna tell the police who you are.
Wait, Ray built a super suit?
That's kind of awesome.
And reckless.
Look, he's probably on his way to the
precinct right now. What are we gonna do?
The radiograph technology is infallible.
These are screenshots with time stamps.
That's a very bold claim, Mr. Palmer.
Especially since we've been down that road
two years ago when Queen was exonerated.
Because he's smart.
I believe he allowed himself to be accused...
...so as to be ruled out
as a suspect in the future.
And your proof is x-ray vision?
Digital images can be fabricated.
I can't go to a judge with any of that.
What about my statement?
You mean your
uncorroborated testimony.
[CHUCKLES]
You're protecting him. Of course.
Because you and Oliver are old friends.
You, uh, hurt yourself
signing depositions?
-At the gym, actually.
-Right. You were training with that...
...wildcat, Grant, right?
The one who also used to be a vigilante.
You and Oliver Queen
used to be a couple, right?
How is it you both
ended up wearing masks?
A word of free legal advice, Mr. Palmer...
...if you go to anyone else,
particularly the media...
...with these unsubstantiated
allegations...
...Mr. Queen would have the basis
for a slam dunk defamation suit...
...that would leave you bankrupt.
Who knows?
He might even get his company back.
Yeah. You're right. The court system
isn't gonna be able to help me here.
Ah.
Guess I'll just have to seek out
justice on my own.
[MEN SPEAKING
IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
Don't worry. I'm a United States senator.
Everything's gonna be all right.
Get down! Get down! Get down!
[ALL GRUNTING]
We're here for you, senator,
but we need to move fast.
All right. Everybody, just stay
where you are. Keep calm.
-We'll explain everything once we're in the air.
-What? No. No. This...
It's all wrong. They weren't supposed
to send anybody. That was the whole point.
You shouldn't have come here.
[ALL SCREAM]
We gotta go! We gotta go! Go! Go! Go!
My hero.
Fall back! Fall back! Fall back!
What the hell was that lunatic thinking?
Secure these doors. Lawton, on the table.
Take off that shirt.
Bullet was a through and through.
I ain't gonna die.
Pays to be sure. It's not a request, soldier.
You still gonna patch me up?
Baby, does it hurt bad?
You were so brave.
Okay, I take it back.
I think I do want to die.
Mockingbird, this is Harbinger on
emergency frequency Delta-Charlie.
Task Force X is broadcasting
in the blind. Over.
Damn it. It's not going through.
I think our signal's being jammed.
CRAY [OVER RADIO]:
Harbinger, this is Senator Cray.
Well, I imagine you must all be feeling
a little bit confused right about now.
This is a hostage situation.
A terrorist attack...
Oh, actually, they're not terrorists.
They're mercenaries. They work for me.
-Why would you do that?
-Because I love my country.
And my country loves a hero.
So this is all theater?
-So you can what? Run for president?
-There it is.
The big picture.
Can you imagine what my
poll numbers will be...
...once I heroically defuse
this tragic situation?
Everybody here
was supposed to go home alive.
That was the whole point.
But now, unfortunately, you have turned my
hostages into witnesses.
And I can't have that.
-I'm gonna kill you slow, you son of a bitch.
-You're outgunned and outnumbered.
But if it's any consolation...
...I am gonna nominate the four of you
for the Medal of Honor once I'm president.
You'll be remembered as heroes.
Heh.
-Arrow.
-Super Suit.
I prefer the Atom.
I have to admit, I was surprised
to find you on my calendar this morning.
Find the place all right?
-Laurel Lance called me.
-Yeah. The Black Canary.
She tried to shut me up,
but it's not gonna work.
-I didn't kill those people.
-Yeah. That's what Felicity said.
An impersonator, right?
I hate when that happens.
Five years on a deserted island.
That kind of thing changes you,
doesn't it?
It must have been difficult, if not impossible,
to hold on to your sanity all those years.
And now here you are,
pretending you have everything in control.
Felicity told you the truth.
And you should trust her judgment.
How can I do that?
Her perception of you is clearly clouded
by her emotional attachment.
She's not seeing you
for what you really are.
You have no idea
what this city is up against.
Actually, I think I do.
And I'm gonna stop him.
It's clear.
-Reinforcements just arrived.
-I see them.
Wait.
-Oh, God.
-What? What? What?
Thermal spikes.
Here. Here. Here. And here.
-They've rigged the hospital with explosives.
-Killing all the hostages.
With Cray as the lone survivor.
Why did we come here?
We accepted the mission, Lyla.
We did what soldiers do.
Except we're not just soldiers, Johnny.
We're parents.
I know parents who won't fly together.
They don't wanna risk orphaning their child.
What were we thinking?
Oh, God.
Our baby girl.
-Lawton was right.
-Can you please say that again?
Sorry, I, uh...
I didn't quite hear you the first time.
The Greddians
have rigged the hospital to blow.
-We're not gonna make it.
-Yeah. Yes, we are.
We're gonna get these hostages out.
And you and John are gonna
make it home to your daughter again.
You got it?
Oh, the things I wanna do
to you right now.
-Floyd Lawton.
-Who's asking?
It wasn't a question.
Merely an acknowledgment.
-We've posted your bail.
-"We"?
An organization in need
of your very particular talent.
"Talent." Heh.
Killing people, you mean.
And we will pay handsomely
for the use of those skills.
Again with the "we."
-Who are you?
-Merely a drone.
A piece of a larger entity.
We exist as one organism.
As you might say, a hive.
Well, listen up, honeybee.
I'm done shooting.
I left that life on the battlefield
to come home, be with my family.
I imagine the restraining order your wife filed
against you impedes that plan somewhat.
You'll never be allowed
near her or your daughter again.
You have left the battlefield.
But the battlefield never leaves you.
People like you don't get to
have love, children, families.
These are just distractions
to people like you.
For people like you,
love is a bullet in the brain.
Who's my target?
His name is Andrew Diggle.
-How'd it go with Ray?
-Not well.
Yeah, your new boyfriend is stubborn.
Once he's made his mind up,
that's the end of it.
Sound like anybody we know?
Not only is he untrained, he's unstable.
-"Unstable"?
-Yeah. Yes. Yeah, he's unstable, Felicity.
Because he's flying around in a weapon...
...looking for a man
that has already killed eight people.
-He's gonna be next.
-You'd like that, wouldn't you?
Excuse me?
-You never wanted me to be with him.
-Not true.
Yes, it is. That talk about
wanting me to be happy was just talk.
No, I meant what I said. Right up to the point
where I found out that he is just like me.
-You deserve better.
-What I deserve...
...is to be with someone
who isn't afraid of being happy.
Ray told me he wanted a true partner.
In his work, in his mission and in his life.
Ray wants to be a hero
and a human being.
Because he hasn't realized yet
that he can't be.
I told you that I couldn't be with you
and save the city.
And neither can Ray.
He's just too new at this to know that.
-What's that?
-911 call.
Suspected gang activity
at Meltzer power plant.
This could be Maseo's next target.
Call Roy.
Tell him to suit up,
meet me at the power plant.
There's no one here.
That must be disappointing.
I'm sorry there's nobody for you to kill,
but, uh, I kind of faked that 911 call.
-Palmer.
-I'd say you have the right to remain silent...
...but I'm not a cop.
No.
Agh!
It's over.
That's it. Nice and easy.
[GROANING]
The man you think I am,
he'd kill you here and now.
I told you to back off,
and you didn't listen.
So kill me. Go ahead.
Show Felicity the kind of man
you really are.
I have nothing to prove to her.
But you do.
She chose you.
So trust her.
I am, uh...
I am truly sorry.
Everything was supposed to
work out differently.
At the door!
[ALL GRUNTING]
Stop or I flip this switch
and I blow us all right to hell right now.
You're bluffing.
You'd die right along with us.
I wanna be president for my legacy.
Dying a hero is as good
a consolation prize as any.
The Suicide Squad.
Well, you are true to your name
if you think that the three of you...
...can just shoot your way in here.
Wait. There were four of you.
Unh!
John, 7 o'clock.
You've been a very, very bad boy.
Go. Go. Go. Everybody go, go, go!
Get out. Go.
Move! Move! Move!
Move! Move!
Come on.
Come on, let's go. Quickly.
What about you, baby?
How are you getting out?
LAWTON:
I'm not.
That's not part of the plan.
You said you could find your way.
Yeah, I lied.
Someone needs to cover your escape.
Me up here is what
gets you out down there alive.
Why?
You and your new wife, you just get back
to your baby girl. All right, John?
Go. Go. Go.
Move. Move.
Go. Go.
-Keep on moving.
-Go. Go. Go.
Go. Go. Go.
Come on, Floyd.
No!
No.
How are you?
My ego's bruised.
And my arm, and my back,
and my rotator cuff.
I'm so sorry about...
...all of this.
Ah, well, actually, I think I'm the one
who owes you an apology.
You told me Oliver was innocent, and I
didn't trust you. I want you to know that I do.
About what you said earlier...
...about wanting a true partner...
...is that offer still good?
Yeah.
Once I make an offer.
The Greddian separatists
were led by Floyd Lawton...
...a former sniper
for the United States Army.
Lawton was discharged five years ago
and since then...
...has been linked
to numerous terrorist organizations.
Lawton died as a result of an explosion
intended for a group of hostages...
...including Senator Joseph Cray.
But Cray managed...
He paid the hostages for their silence.
Yeah. Well, the dollar
goes a long way in Kasnia, right?
I tried to set the record straight.
Waller blocked me.
Johnny, there's something else.
Yes, there is.
-I'm leaving Team Arrow.
-What?
Lawton was right.
We can't keep living like this.
It only works until it doesn't.
And then what?
I can't do that to Sara.
And what about this city?
The work you and Oliver do,
it's good work.
Not like what I've
been doing for far too long.
Which is why I resigned.
Lyla, no. You love your job.
And you're damn good at it.
If what happened with Cray can be allowed,
I don't want to be.
What I want is to set
a good example for our daughter.
I want her to be proud of me.
Lyla.
I'm proud of you.
I'm proud of you, Lyla.
Nothing's ever gonna change that.
-Hey.
-Hi.
-Where you off to?
-Ray has a meeting with the mayor.
Seems he's had
a change of heart about the Arrow.
Huh.
-Thanks.
-For what?
Proving me right.
-Hey.
-Hi.
What did I miss?
Oh, not much. I'm glad you're back.
So am I. Turns out Lyla and I
are not very good at vacations.
-The Republic of Kasnia, huh?
-Mm-hm.
And Floyd Lawton?
Yeah.
You were right, Oliver.
Doing what we do,
having loved ones at home...
...it's complicated.
Well, the things that matter always are.
To Floyd Lawton.
[SPEAKS IN RUSSIAN]
Any luck finding your imposter?
He's still out there.
We have to stop this guy before
he puts arrows in any more criminals.
Or before he starts putting them
in innocent people.
RAY:
Madam, I have it on good authority...
-...he's been set up.
-Hold on a second.
You're telling me you think
the Arrow's innocent?
Of these murders, yes.
I believe he's being framed.
We need to address the media right away.
Tell them what?
Some genius changed his mind?
You're letting your personal feelings
towards the Arrow cloud your judgment.
Maybe I'm seeing more clearly
than I have for years.
Enough, both of you.
I am tired of listening...