Previously on "Arrow"...
I'm sorry, I--
I should go.
The night of the siege,
you were
at the train station.
I got attacked by one of those
crazy masked things,
but he got shot
by a cop, I think.
It was Malcolm Merlyn.
He's dead.
Thank you, Dad.
I promised you, Thea.
I will never let anyone hurt you.
Sara Lance is dead?
Yes.
At Merlyn's hand?
It appears.
Al Sa-Her will face
the League's justice.
What of Queen?
He has sworn to protect Merlyn
at any cost.
If that is true...
then Oliver Queens
courts war with us.
Hey.
Very nice.
Merry Christmas.
Well, I feel bad.
I didn't get you anything.
You keep
the city safe.
So do you.
You know, these days, you're
the closest thing to a partner I got.
Happy holidays.
Here you go, buddy.
Merlyn!
Nyssa.
What is this?
We agreed!
To nothing.
My father merely decided
to give you the time
to bring Sara's killer to justice,
and you have failed.
We are doing
everything that we can!
You've been distracted
protecting the city.
And you've exhausted
my father's patience.
In civilizations past,
when someone
in the village was murdered,
the League would come
and kill 50 people a day
until the true criminal
was rooted out.
Find and deliver the one
who killed Ta-er Al-Sahfer.
You have 48 hours,
or the citizens of Starling
will see what the League
of Assassins is capable of.
You're going to slaughter
innocent people.
The cleansing of Starling City
will fall to Sarab.
Maseo?
Maseo is no longer.
As she said...
I am Sarab.
Deliver Sara's killer
or blood will flow
in your streets.
This isn't what
Sara would want!
Sara is dead.
It's time you remember that.
♪ Arrow 3x09 ♪
The Climb
Original Air Date on December 10, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Dad's ok.
Um...working too much.
Sorry.
I never really know what to say
when I come here.
I just...
I wanted to wish you
a Merry Christmas,
and tell you
how much I miss you.
Laurel?
Thea.
What are you
doing here?
I was just leaving
flowers for my mom.
Who were you talking to?
Nobody.
I just come here...
Sometimes.
Even though
Sara's still alive?
Laurel, what--what's wrong?
Everything's fine.
Sara's ok.
No, Thea.
Sara's dead.
What?
What are you talking about?
While you were
gone...
She was murdered.
By who?
I don't know.
I buried her here.
Why didn't you tell anybody,
like at least your father, the police?
No, no.
Thea, no one
can ever know.
Why?
Sara, she was, uh,
she was complicated.
And if my father
found out,
it would kill him.
You have to promise
me that you won't tell Oliver.
Of course, I--I promise.
I'm so sorry.
Hey.
Did you know there's
a cafeteria in the building?
There's a cold press juice bar,
organic salad station.
I know.
I eat there every day,
along with 800
of your other employees.
Now, if you'll
excuse me,
I'm late for a meeting.
Wait, Felicity!
Are we ok?
If by "we"
you mean you and me
as individual entities, then yes,
we are fantastic.
This is about the kiss.
This is not
about the kiss.
You sure? 'Cause it really
feels like it's about the kiss.
Unless it's about
how I left after the kiss.
- I can explain.
- No.
I can explain. It was a moment
and you regret it.
It's over. Now can we please pretend
like it never happened
and go back to being
professionals?
I have to go.
Work.
But you're at...work.
What happened?
Nyssa paid me a visit.
The League wants Sara's killer handed
over in the next 48 hours.
Why do I sense
there's an "or else"
at the end
of that sentence?
Or else they'll start killing
innocent civilians.
Oh, my god, two days?
Caitlin has the DNA that
we pulled off of the arrows
that killed Sara,
but the STR markers are degraded,
so it's taking
a little bit longer.
Felicity...
It can't take
any longer.
If we can't find
Sara's killer in time,
we're going to need
a contingency plan.
I know.
I don't have one.
Here.
Oh, I'm not hungry.
The first time
I interrogated someone,
I lost my appetite
for two days.
You need
your strength.
I didn't interrogate anyone.
I tortured him.
The question is,
did you learn anything about
Chien Na Wei's plans?
There's a biotech
company in Hong Kong.
They were working
on a super-antibiotic.
They got a super-virus instead.
They're calling it
Oh-Mei-Gah,
which is the Chinese
translation for...
Omega.
Said one vile could
wipe out an entire city.
So it's a bio weapon
Chien Na Wei's after.
Did he tell you
where it is now?
Yeah.
He didn't want to,
but I made him.
You did what
was necessary.
One man's agony
is not worth
the lives of
an entire city.
But
you're all right?
Okay. Yes, it is
coming through now.
No, I'm fine. Things are just,
um, tense here.
Thank you, Caitlin.
Happy holidays
to you, too.
Are those the DNA results?
It's the reassembled
genome S.T.A.R. Labs
was able to get off of the arrow
that killed Sara.
I need to run it against
potential suspects.
What database
are you using?
SCPD maintains a genetic
markers database.
Anyone's who committed
a felony in the past three years.
No, that--
that can't be right.
Who is it?
It must be a mistake.
Felicity!
Who killed Sara?
You did.
This must be a mistake.
I took perspiration
off the arrows that killed Sara.
Two years ago when the police
arrested Oliver
because they thought,
accurately, that he was the vigilante,
they took a DNA sample.
That sample is a match for 12
out of the 13 STRs.
The odds of that...
They're impossible.
Ok, so somehow
my DNA is on the arrows.
Someone's setting you up,
Oliver.
Well, somebody with
a vested interest
in pitting me against
the League of Assassins.
It's Malcolm Merlyn.
Merlyn was in Corto Maltese
with Thea when this was going down.
Unless he wasn't. I mean, Merlyn hid
successfully for two years
from the police and the League.
He's good
at covering his tracks.
So we uncover them.
But it might
take some time.
In less than 48 hours, the League
is going to murder 50 people.
We don't have time.
Move to the lab.
I'll deal with
the rest
of security.
Stay on comms.
Maseo, are you set?
Just about.
Found Omega.
Be careful with it.
Yeah, we might
have a problem.
What's wrong?
Somebody already
took it.
How did she get
in here before us?
She didn't need
to get in, Oliver.
She already
had someone inside.
Yeah, I know,
but it's the holidays
and I guess
I'm feeling charitable.
Is that ok?
Jake, I got
to call you right back.
Hey.
Hi!
Look who it is.
How was your ride down?
Oh, uneventful.
Chance to grade
some papers.
Dad, maybe you can tell me
why half your officers
are allergic
to search warrants?
Mom!
Hi, sweetheart.
I didn't know that
you were coming to town.
Well, I guess
that's my fault,
'cause I thought you could
do a little Christmas surprise.
Hmm.
Of course I want to spend
Christmas with my family.
So where's Sara?
She's not returning
my phone calls.
Uh, yeah, that's 'cause
she's, uh, she's traveling.
Backpacking through the Andes.
I think.
Yeah.
I found something!
A.R.G.U.S. monitors air traffic
in and out of countries of interest.
Corto Maltese is on that list.
This is a list of every
commercial airliner,
private jet, sea plane,
and, I'm not kidding,
hot air balloon that took off
from Corto Maltese this past year.
Look at this flight path.
Private charter
from Corto Maltese to Caracas,
then to Cartagena,
only to fly back to Caracas,
and then to Tijuana.
Whoever was on that plane was working
pretty hard to hide where it was going.
The route ends
at a private landing strip
just outside
Starling City.
When did it
land?
The night before
Sara was murdered.
Please! All I do
is fly the plane!
Quiet!
The man in this photo--
did you fly him
from Corto Maltese
to Starling City?
No.
This time,
look at the photo!
He'll kill me.
He's not here. We are.
All right, ok, yes,
I flew him here.
I've got security footage,
you want to see?
Hanukkah present?
Security footage from the airfield
where Merlyn landed.
Check
for October seventh.
Right there,
stop.
I thought you said Merlyn was keeping
his distance from Thea,
that he hadn't had
any contact.
He lied.
And so did she.
Maybe there's something
we should consider here.
Maybe it wasn't your DNA, Oliver,
maybe it was Thea's.
What?
You two are siblings.
There would be overlap, maybe
even enough to--
Diggle, are you
listening to yourself?
You're suggesting that
Thea killed Sara.
Even if--even if she would,
even if she could...
Why?
Well, Malcolm Merlyn
is her father.
I hate to even say this.
Then don't.
Oliver...
I know how much
you love your sister,
but we have to look
at the facts.
The virtual autopsy
I did on Sara;
I thought Roy might
have stabbed her
because the trajectory
wasn't consistent
with that of an archer
of average height.
You weren't considering
a killer of Thea's size.
Enough, both of you!
My sister
did not kill Sara.
The DNA on
the arrows is mine
because Malcolm Merlyn
put it there.
Hi.
Hey, uh,
we need to talk,
so I came here.
Here where?
Where you are.
I might have pinged
your phone...again.
I thought I was pretty clear when I
said I didn't want to talk about this.
You were.
But you were
also pretty wrong
when you said
I regretted kissing you.
I can't imagine
there's a man on the planet
who would ever
regret kissing you.
Well, I can think of one.
But I am sorry about
the way I reacted.
When I kissed you,
I felt guilty.
Oh, my God,
you're cheating on someone.
No.
Her name is Anna,
and we were engaged.
Last spring,
the night those men...
took over the city,
we ran into a few.
We tried to escape, but we couldn't.
I tried to fight them,
but I couldn't.
I wasn't strong
enough. I...
They broke my leg,
and went after her,
but I couldn't
save her.
And I watched
them...
as they broke
her neck.
Ray, I am so sorry.
Anna was supposed
to be the last woman I ever kissed.
And she was,
until suddenly
I was kissing you.
Hey!
What are you doing home?
I wanted the Christmas
tree to be a surprise.
It's a surprise.
I thought since it was
just the two of us now,
smaller the family,
bigger the tree.
What about Malcolm?
Thea, I know you saw him
in Corto Maltese.
Ollie, we've
lost everyone. I--
Malcolm's the only
family I have left besides you.
Thea, I deserve
to know what
you've been doing
with Malcolm Merlyn.
I've just been getting
to know him, that's all.
A couple of months ago,
did you fly back
to Starling City
with him?
No!
Ollie, if I was back
in Starling City,
don't you think
I would have called you?
I was in Corto Maltese
since May.
Now will you please just...
Come upstairs and help me
find some more Christmas stuff?
Ok.
What's
he saying?
He's trying to bribe us.
We want the vial
of Omega you stole.
I don't know
what you're talking about!
I didn't steal
anything!
Don't waste
your energy on lies.
We will get
the truth from you--
one way or the other.
My friend can be
very persuasive.
So, how are you?
Mmm. I'm great.
Work's great.
I--I've just been really busy.
Something's happened.
What?
No. No,
nothing's happened.
It's Sara.
Isn't it?
When I mentioned her earlier,
you seemed so...broken.
Mom,
Sara's fine.
She's just
being Sara.
There are few things
as powerful as a mother's intuition.
You are hiding something.
I know it.
Just like I was the only one who knew
that Sara didn't die on that boat.
I have this feeling
that I would see her again.
And right now,
that feeling...
is gone.
She's dead...
isn't she?
Mom, listen to me.
Sara, she was involved with some
very, very dangerous people.
This has
to remain a secret,
at least until we figure out
exactly what happened.
I don't understand.
Doesn't your father know?
If he knew
about Sara...
He couldn't take it.
And I can't lose
anyone else.
Father.
It's nearly time.
Mr. Queen has not yet
presented the guilty?
Perhaps he believes
our threats are empty.
We must correct that belief.
Return to Starling City.
Be merciless.
Teach Oliver Queen
we only ask but once.
Where you been?
I went
to see Thea.
She lied to me again,
but she didn't kill Sara.
Oliver...
I looked her in
the eyes, Felicity.
These are eyes
that I have known my entire life.
She could lie to me about
Merlyn and spending time with him,
but she could
never do this.
Oliver, you are one
of the smartest men
I have ever known,
but you have a blind spot
when it comes to your family.
Not this time--
First your mother,
then your father,
and now Thea.
That's enough, Diggle!
You know she lied
to you, Oliver!
Both of you, stop!
Oliver,
I can't imagine
how difficult
this must be for you,
but John is right.
Thea lied.
She lied about Merlyn!
But Sara...
I don't want to believe that she can
do something like this.
Which is why you shouldn't be
the one asking the questions.
Thea Queen!
Where is
Malcolm Merlyn?
I don't know! Please,
please don't hurt me!
Stay away from me
and my father!
It's the strangest thing.
Thea just called
and said she was
attacked by the Arrow.
You wouldn't happen to know
anything about that,
now would you, Oliver?
This was you.
You know, I figured
when I spared the man who
murdered my mother,
I would never
kill again.
I was wrong.
You might want to reconsider.
Why?!
For Thea.
Check your phone.
I can wait.
I don't think you want
the League to see that.
And if you kill me,
they will.
This isn't her.
Have you ever
heard of a plant called Votura?
Grows in South America.
In fact, it thrives in Corto Maltese,
making the subject extremely
susceptible to suggestion,
or retaining no memory
of their actions.
I will tell Ra's this was you,
that Thea was under your control.
And he will still kill her.
She fired the arrows.
You have given her
a death sentence.
No.
What I've done
is given you incentive.
To do what?
To tell Ra's that
you killed Sara Lance.
By right, you will be
given a trial by combat--
with Ra's.
His death will erase
any blood debt from his reign,
including Thea's.
And yours.
I have to be honest--
it was my concern that
the whole killing thing
would have been
a dealbreaker for you.
But, uh, I'm gratified
to see that Thea
is still sufficient
motivation.
Don't take too long
making up your mind.
Ra's isn't known
for his patience.
Thea was always so kind.
Kindest person
I've ever known.
My sister wasn't
born a killer.
Malcolm Merlyn
made her one,
and I let it happen.
No, you didn't.
When it comes to your family,
you always place the blame
on yourself,
but this is not your fault.
She's right, Oliver.
Throw Malcolm in front of Ra's,
let the League
sort this out.
Merlyn has a video.
He made contingencies.
Oliver, if you
fight Ra's al Ghul,
he'll kill you.
No, he won't.
During the Undertaking,
Merlyn told me
that I couldn't win,
because I didn't know
what I was fighting for.
Now I do.
I'm fighting for Thea.
He should have
confessed by now.
We have video evidence of him
taking the vials.
He says he doesn't remember.
He's lying! You don't
do something like that
and not remember it!
There is a way.
I didn't think it
a possibility until now.
There's a drug.
It's called Votura.
I've heard it makes people extremely
susceptible to suggestion.
Like mind control?
Really,
that's a thing?
Those who get dosed
often have no memory
of what they do
while under the influence.
Oh, great. All this
was for nothing?
Chien Na Wei
has the vile,
and we have no way
of finding her!
We've taken her inside man.
Finding her may not be
the problem at hand.
The problem could be
her finding us.
Hello, Mrs. Yamashiro.
Is your husband home?
Don't you dare
talk to my son!
Quaint house...
for a spy.
Except for these.
They belong to you,
don't they?
Tatsu, isn't it?
Beautiful blade.
Where is he?
You really think
my father,
the Demon's head, would travel
all the way from Nanda Parbat
simply because you wished it?
Yes.
This way.
Kneel before
the Demon's head.
You're just a boy.
Well, Mr. Queen,
you failed to protect
the city you love.
Now you'll watch it bleed.
Nobody in my city
will die tonight.
Well.
There was only one way
to prevent that.
You were to produce
for me the one
who killed
Ta-er Al-Sahfer.
And yet
you've come alone.
Because it was me.
I killed Sara.
Why would you kill a woman
you once professed to love?
Because she
begged me to.
You lie.
It wasn't the first time Sara chose
death over a life in the League.
And meeting you now,
I can see why.
I should have Sarab cleave
your head from your shoulders.
Not for killing
my daughter's beloved,
but for thinking me a fool.
By League law,
I have the right
to challenge you to
a trial by combat.
It's been 67 years
since a man challenged me.
You covet death that much?
Do you accept?
Oh, yes.
I see the years have done little
to dull your stubbornness.
Maseo...
My name is Sarab!
You told me once a man cannot
live by two names.
And I don't.
Maseo is dead.
I am all that's left, Sarab.
A phantom.
After it happened,
you went
to Nanda Parbat.
I arrived the same year
as Ta-er Al-Sahfer.
She was a great warrior.
You did not kill her.
When you face the Demon,
it will be my duty
to bear witness.
I have no desire
to watch you die.
Under our code,
you have 12 hours
to settle your affairs.
The 13th hour,
be at this place.
This location is consecrated
ground for the League.
A place for the settlement
of blood debts--
if one survives the climb.
If you do.
See you
on the mountain.
Do you remember how when
the two of you were little,
you'd play dress up?
One day I overheard
you and Sara.
You were pretending
to be grown-up
versions of yourselves.
That day, you
and your sister,
you had your own
families.
Careers.
I was a cop, just like dad.
And Sara...
Was a doctor.
She wanted
to heal people.
She deserves
more than this.
Mom, can I tell you
something?
Whoever did this to Sara,
I am going to find them
no matter what it takes.
And I am going
to make them pay.
Then you
make them pay.
And you make them
suffer.
Looks good.
That window
should be as good as new.
Thank you.
What happened
to the window?
Oh, God, you should
have seen it.
This bird went completely
Hitchcock on the thing.
I vacuumed up
most the glass,
but I'd still watch your step.
I'll be
extra careful.
Are you ok?
Last time you had
that look on your face,
you told me dad
committed suicide.
You haven't
called him dad
since you found out
about Malcolm.
What's going in
with you, Ollie?
You think you know who
Malcolm Merlyn is.
But there are things that
I've discovered,
years ago,
recently, that...
He doesn't
love you, Thea.
Because he's not
capable of it.
Ollie, please.
Don't.
Don't make me choose
between my father
and my brother.
I would never
make you choose.
You are my family.
There's nothing
that I won't do to protect you.
What does that mean?
It means I love you,
no matter what.
Tatsu?
Akio! What happened here?
Oh, God, no.
No, no, no!
Akio, no!
Daddy!
Akio!
Akio, where is your mother?
The white-haired
woman! She took her!
Guess who just designed
a microprocessor
with a SPECint score
just north of 9,000?
Ray...What are you doing
with Queen Consolidated?
Why did you buy it?
Because it was
for sale.
My life is a little more
complicated than I let on.
Suffice it to say, I have gotten
very good at keeping secrets,
particularly the kind of secrets
someone like you keeps.
Someone in pain.
Wasn't easy for me to tell you
about Anna.
You told me about Anna,
but you didn't tell me the truth
about what it is you're doing.
So tell me, or I walk.
I can't tell you.
I have to show you.
The dawn
of the computer age,
developers thought
the only way a machine
could process information
as fast as a human brain
was to build a mainframe
the size of Texas.
But one developer
realized that the only way
to reduce heat
and power consumption
was to bring the components
closer together.
Which meant
making them smaller.
But why stop
at computers?
What if it could
take other things,
like, say, all of
the military-grade technology
in Applied Sciences,
and make it smaller,
too? So small
that it can fit in
the palm of my hand.
I can help a lot
of people that way.
- I don't understand.
- This will help.
Whoa.
What is it?
OMAC
is a Queen Consolidated
designation.
But I'm kind of partial
to A.T.O.M.
Advanced Technology
Operating Mechanism.
A.T.O.M.
What are you going
to use it for?
To protect
the people of this city.
And I want you
to help me.
Why does this keep
happening to me?
Oliver...
John, I have to do this.
I know.
I'd just rather die than let you
go it alone.
Not this time.
Take care of Thea.
Absolutely.
I'm sorry.
Something came up...
No.
Let's give them
a minute.
So you're going?
Mm-hmm.
To Nanda Parbat?
No, it's a neutral site.
It'll be fine.
I'll come back.
Thea will be ok.
I wish that sounded
more convincing.
And I wish you wouldn't go, but
I know you better,
so I'm not going
to ask you to stay.
I appreciate that.
But there is
one thing
I need
to ask you to do.
And you're not
going to want to.
Well, if it's you
asking, I'll do it.
Kill him.
You have to kill
Ra's al Ghul.
This is a duel...
Oliver,
with one of the most dangerous men
that has ever walked the earth.
I wouldn't be doing it
if I didn't think I could win.
I don't doubt that.
I don't doubt that you can beat him.
I am terrified that
you won't kill him.
Because that's not
who you are anymore.
And I am so afraid
that Ra's al Ghul
is going to use
your humanity against you.
Felicity,
I honestly don't know
if I'm a killer anymore.
But I do know two things--
the first is that...
whoever I am,
I am someone that will
do whatever--whatever--
it takes to save my sister.
And the second thing?
I love you.
Remove your shirt.
This is custom.
Ra's al Ghul is not know
to be merciful.
But if there was a chance,
this will be your final
moment for it.
Choose your weapon.
I was 11 years old
when I killed my first man.
I remember the look
in his face
when the light went out
behind his eyes.
Such a sudden change,
almost imperceptible,
between life and death.
And I felt ashamed.
I had stolen
from that man
the most precious
gift of all--
life.
But I also felt
something else--
pride,
because I had taken up arms
against someone
who sought to do ill
against my family.
And I realized what I had
done was necessary.
You see...
I had replaced evil
with death.
And that...
is what the League
exists to do.
And I have killed several
thousand more men since then.
And the world
is better off for it.
You've taken
your last life.
No.
You have lived your last day.
We are ready.
I am envious of you.
You will see her
before I do.
Fight me, boy.
You're unnarmed.
I'll take your blades from you once
you are through with them.
You should take pride.
You survived
longer than most.
Don't be afraid,
my son.
Death comes for us all.
We can only
evade it so long.
Consider this
an honorable exit.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man