[electronic music playing]
[laughing]
[speaking Russian]
[sighing impatiently]
[exclaiming excitedly]
Taxi.
[screaming]
Kapiushon.
[in English]Rumors are true.
Kapiushon is back.
You cost us a lot of money
back in Star City.
And you'll more than make up for it
by taking over his drug operation.
You kept your end of bargain.
Now, you keep yours.
By the time you get back to America,
it will be done.
No, I need more than your word.
Show him that.
He'll know it's from me.
Man, I can't believe how good
this crappy hallway looks.
Yeah, and it really is crappy.
I mean, this paint looks like
it's been here since the '60s.
Yeah, it's...
But it must be good
to be home, right?
Yeah, to be home and to see my baby.
You told Zoe to come straight here
after hockey practice, right?
Actually, she wanted to skip
hockey practice today.
-Welcome home!
-Oh! I missed you so much.
-I missed you too, Dad.
I'm so glad you're back.
[grunts softly]
Ah, you guys didn't have to do all this.
Hey, you've been in the hospital
over a month.
You deserve a hero's welcome.
We have cake, too. Your favorite.
[laughing]
-Is that red velvet?
-I'll cut you a slice.
I love you so much.
[laughter]
So how are you feeling?
Better than ever. Ready to take down
Diaz anytime, anywhere.
We haven't been able to find him
or his lair
using our usual tracking methods.
That's probably because Diaz
is controlling the entire city,
including police and cameras.
I just hacked a new thermal sensing
program from the NSA,
so maybe that gets us somewhere.
Point is, now, us is back to full
strength.
That's right.
Ricardo Diaz is working with
SCPD Captain Kimberly Hill,
District Attorney Armand,
and former Bratva Pakhan
named Anatoly Knyazev.
But that is just the tip
of the iceberg.
Ricardo Diaz has members
of Star City's
entire governmental infrastructure
either bought or compromised.
So how are we supposed to find him?
24/7 surveillance on all of Diaz's
known locations and subordinates
until either he or someone
he is working with makes a mistake.
You have your orders.
-Everything all right, sir?
-You can drop the "sir."
A.R.G.U.S. isn't the Army.
Just checking to see
how you are acclimating.
[chuckles softly]
I feel like I'm getting my sea legs.
You might feel that way,
but it doesn't look it.
From where I'm standing,
it looks like you've been doing this
your whole life.
At least that's what I told the boss.
You're talking to Lyla.
[laughing]
Talking might be a bit
of an exaggeration.
Maldivian phone lines
aren't exactly the best.
Copy that.
I got something
that might help with Diaz.
Lydia Cassamento.
Gun lobbyist who took control
of her family business.
Now she runs weapons
for the Quadrant.
The Quadrant?
High-end cartel, ruled
by moneyed families
with ties to all things black market.
Guns, cryptocurrency, drugs, humans.
KH-11 picked up Cassamento
coming into Star City.
And you think Diaz is looking
to restock his firepower.
And if she's making
the trip personally
that means the deal she is working
on is big.
I got a tact team ready
to take her out.
No, belay that order.
If she's bringing guns to Diaz,
she may lead us right to him.
What kind of wool is this again?
Rare vicuña.
A suit like this is worth what,
100 grand?
For a basic cut, yes.
Hey, I don't want the basic cut.
Leave a little room for the guns.
And don't forget, the muscles
are getting bigger.
You said she'd be here by now.
I called her three times.
[Black Siren] You called me once.
Since when did you let these guys
start lying to you?
Don't tell me that the Quadrant's
money has made you go soft?
I thought we were supposed
to meet up last night.
Well, I guess your men are lying
to you again.
I told them I would be down
by the docks.
There were some Halcones
that needed disciplining.
Good.
There's somebody else that needs
a little instruction.
The new mayor.
You mean my father.
I thought he wasn't your father.
You know what I mean.
Need to have a conversation with him.
Lay down some of the ground rules.
I'll talk to him.
No.
You set it up.
You do trust me, don't you, baby?
Of course I do.
I'll make it happen.
[man speaking indistinctly on tv]
[speaking Russian]
[laughing]
[TV turns off]
[objects clattering]
[in English]
If I'm supposed to be frightened,
you are wasting your time, Kapiushon.
I just wanna talk.
We stopped talking year ago.
How you find me?
I got a tip
from a friend of yours in Russia.
I have no friends in Russia.
Your doing.
That's fixed.
Also my doing.
This is Pakhan's.
How you come to have it?
He told me that the Bratva exiled you
because of your friendship with me.
I owed you a debt,
I owed them a debt.
I paid it.
You can go home now, Anatoly.
You said you were an honorable man.
Now, I think you know deep down
that Diaz isn't.
Help me stop him.
[sighs wearily]
Yeah, you're right.
I was honorable man.
-[electrical buzzing]
-[grunts]
Handcuffs would have been fine.
What, so you can dislocate arms
and escape?
[Anatoly chuckles]
Come on, Oliver,
most of your tricks, I taught you.
I also taught you not to go
into a situation alone. Hmm?
I've gone back to basics, Anatoly.
I'm working alone.
That explains why you broke into SCPD
wearing Kapiushon outfit.
[laughing]
Oh. Diaz and I had good laugh
on that one.
Maybe one day we will have
bigger laugh about this.
So you two are friends now?
I thought you wanted back in
with the Bratva, Anatoly.
So I delivered that to you.
And I thank you.
But over past year,
I see things a little more clearly.
I devote my whole life to brothers,
I even become their Pakhan,
and for a setback, they cast me out.
Well, Diaz is gonna do far worse
than cast you out.
If I betray him, yes,
but why would I do that?
[Anatoly chuckling]
Diaz is going to make me
a very rich man.
Bratva took 100 years to go
from prison into government,
Diaz did same thing in months.
I'm still gonna take him down.
Not alone, you cannot.
My mission was always supposed
to be solitary.
Put me with a team, fill it
with people that I care about,
it splits my focus.
Was that why you think Diaz
was able to beat you?
He took over the city
while I was distracted.
If you seriously believe that,
then you are even bigger fool
than I thought.
That is saying something.
Damn, it is good to be back.
[Curtis] Guess it's true what they say,
"There's no place like bunker."
I bet you really miss Curtis'
dad jokes.
You know what, I did, a little.
I missed this baby more.
Well, good. Because you are gonna be
wearing it plenty.
We are the only vigilante team
left standing.
What do you mean?
John got into a huge fight with
Oliver and joined A.R.G.U.S.
Then Oliver kicked Felicity
out of the bunker.
So now he's gone solo.
Oh. So Oliver finally
drove them all away.
Can't say I'm surprised.
Or that I care.
Taking down Diaz was always gonna
come down to the three of us.
So what's the plan?
Well, we can wait until
my NSA lead pans out.
Until then, we are kind of
dead in the water.
The city's dying. We just can't sit
around here picking our noses.
No, you're absolutely right. And we
need to go at this some way
that does not depend on finding Diaz.
Even if that means grasping
at straws.
Look, forget grasping at straws.
What if we grasp at his wallet?
The best way to get to Diaz
is to go after his operation.
What operation?
He was really deep
into pushing Vertigo.
Was?
John and Oliver took out
his operation three weeks ago.
Well, then that means Diaz has to be
in the market for a new supplier.
Or an old one.
Before Diaz went to prison,
he led the Scorpions.
That is Star City's biggest supplier.
That feels like a leap.
It may be, but it's all we got.
And even if it doesn't lead to Diaz,
we still take down a drug operation.
That's a win-win.
You know, but the problem is,
with me boxed out of the SCPD,
it's gonna be a lot harder
to get intel on the Scorpions.
Maybe not.
Diaz isn't the only person
who grew up in the Glades.
[Quentin] Well, I was pretty surprised
to get your invite.
Especially to this place.
You remember what I said about
coming here with my girls, huh?
[chuckling]
And the new location got an upgrade.
Not fancy enough for the new mayor?
It's perfect.
You okay?
I'm really sorry.
What are you talking about?
Mr. Mayor.
I've been meaning
to congratulate you.
I thought I'd come down here
in person.
I mean, you are the mayor of my city.
And we have a lot in common.
What the hell do you want?
Straight to business. I love it.
Here's an executive order
for a certain piece
of municipal real estate
to be sold privately.
Now, the good news, it's a bargain.
Well, I'm not signing this.
I'm not signing anything for you.
I would reconsider your position.
Really?
I bet
she'd give you that same advice.
I'm telling you right now,
if anything happens to her...
Why would I wanna hurt Laurel?
Hmm?
She's with me now.
And she is
such a smart, little thing.
[sighs]
She knows how to pick
the winning side.
I hope it runs in the family.
Let's go, baby.
Come on.
Behind that glass door is where
the Scorpions do their business.
-The problem is, it's sound proof.
-But not laser proof.
-You sure this is gonna work?
-Absolutely.
The CIA would kill to get a laser
microphone with this capacity.
How long is this gonna take?
Just trying to find a signal.
All right, well, let's hurry it up.
I didn't get a severance.
I really shouldn't be gambling.
Got something. [clears throat]
[beeps]
Huge deal going down tonight.
New buyer.
Is trying to get some product
to tide them over for the short-term.
Could be our friend.
They say when it's going down?
No, no, no. I lost the signal.
The big guy is blocking my laser.
I'm on it.
Yo, man.
Yo, man. You think I didn't see that?
You trying to copy my bets, hoss?
You trying to ruin my odds?
What the hell are you talking about?
[scoffs] So we lying now?
That's what we're doing?
-Let me see that paper.
-You're crazy.
Oh, damn.
Uh, you know what, I'm sorry.
I was wrong.
Here you go, man. That's yours.
I just get a little crazy
when I lose. Everybody, chill.
I'm leaving.
-You get the location?
-Got it.
Well, let's ruin Diaz's next party.
[Mr. Terrific] What if we're wrong?
And those crates are filled with
something other than narcotics.
Like lollipops,
or I don't know, puppies.
[Black Canary] I counted a dozen
more guys out front, strapped up.
I'm guessing it's not puppies.
[Wild Dog] Look, we got to get this done
before the group outside
notices we're here.
And before Diaz's crew shows.
Let's do this.
[T-Sphere warbling]
-[gunshots]
-[men groaning]
Still got it.
Still humble, I see.
-[Mr. Terrific] Definitely not puppies.
-Or drugs.
The product
the Scorpions are moving is M4s.
You guys still think Diaz
is the buyer?
Yeah. Definitely.
Nobody's doing anything in this city
without his say so.
[gunfire in distance]
[Wild Dog] Diaz's crew is a little early.
Come on.
[guns firing]
We got more company.
[Wild Dog] Who are the guys in the suits?
[Wild Dog] We got to get out of here.
-[guns firing]
-[men groaning]
Back door. Over there.
[gun cocks]
-[screeching]
-[men groaning]
[gunfire continues]
We're trapped.
-[radio beeps]
-Blow them all to hell.
Let's go, now!
The Quadrant.
You know, I heard about these guys
when I was working undercover.
I never could get anyone to confirm
their existence.
Yeah, well, they are real.
Very, very, real.
We're tracking this one. Cassamento.
Hoping she will lead us to Diaz.
Yeah, well, we were hoping the
Scorpions would lead us to Diaz, too.
Got some intel they were planning
a huge thing tonight.
We just figured it was drugs.
Turns out it was an ambush.
Quadrant wanted the Scorpions dead.
They wanted us dead, too.
It's a good thing you guys showed up
when you did.
You probably want a thank you
or something, huh?
[scoffs]
What I want is to apologize, Rene.
My feelings on how you guys
conducted yourselves aside,
[sighs]
things got really out of hand.
And I'm sorry for the part
that I played in it.
Thanks, hoss.
Let's get back to work.
Everyone who thinks the Quadrant
showing up
when Diaz gets control of the city
is a coincidence
raise your hands.
The muscle that they brought in
yesterday were Diaz's guys.
The question is, what are they doing
working with the Quadrant?
A.R.G.U.S. think Cassamento is
planning to move a huge shipment
of weapons into the city.
Kasnian weapons.
Military grade. Much worse than
what we saw tonight.
[door opens]
We think Diaz may be helping her
with that operation.
Wasn't expecting to see you here.
Wasn't expecting to see you either.
Everything all right?
Not really.
Diaz just paid me a visit.
He wants me to sign over a piece
of city property to him. A building.
So why are you here instead
of talking to your boy?
Because I couldn't get in touch
with Oliver.
[sighs]
The Quadrant. What is that?
Just a super powerful,
monolithic, secret organization.
No big deal.
Diaz was wearing that ring.
So Diaz isn't just working
with Cassamento. He...
He joined the Quadrant.
The attack on the Scorpions
was to take out the competition. His.
And I'm guessing
that that city property
will be a really nice place
to store all that foreign ordnance
that Cassamento is planning on
bringing into the city.
This city building that Diaz wants,
where is it?
My men have woken up
from tranquilizer dart.
Time to go see Diaz.
You think he'll give you a reward?
A man can dream.
But I settle for satisfaction.
Enjoy it while it lasts.
Because, Anatoly,
when you are no longer useful,
he'll cut you loose.
Just like Cayden James.
Cayden James made fatal mistake.
Underestimating Diaz.
I do not.
I see him for who he is.
I understand his code.
Diaz doesn't have a code.
He doesn't have honor.
But you working with him,
you are betraying everything
that you've ever believed in.
No need to be gentle with this one.
[Oliver grunts]
[John] It's pretty quiet around here.
You're really quiet, too.
Should I be taking that personally?
No, hoss. We're good.
That apology you made,
you got fiber, John.
What's on your mind?
I can't stop thinking about dying.
Hmm.
In the middle of the fight,
I just froze.
PTSD, fritz out... I mean...
Actually, it wasn't just so much
about dying as it was about...
Leaving Zoe without a father.
Yeah, you get it.
You got a kid younger than Zoe.
How do you deal with it?
I don't, man. Not out here.
When I put this holster on,
I leave daddy home.
I put the walls of
compartmentalizing up hard, Rene.
You've been out of the game
for a month, over a month.
It'll come back to you.
Just give it some time.
Yo, take a look at that.
[beeping]
[Rene] If Diaz's plan is
to store the weapons,
why are they bringing the crates
to the truck?
Cassamento's not looking
to move guns into the city.
She and Diaz are using the city
to ship them out.
Turning Star City into a way station.
Curtis, Dinah,
we've seen all we need to see.
Let's regroup at A.R.G.U.S.
-[knocking at door]
-[Quentin] You still here, Becky?
Nope.
Sorry. Not Becky.
Or Laurel. At least not my Laurel.
She wouldn't choose a guy like
Diaz.
You think he gives anyone a choice?
Do you?
That's why I'm here.
To tell you
that you don't have a choice.
You have to sign this.
Whatever Diaz wants you to sign.
Don't pretend like you give a crap
about me, all right.
You proud of yourself for turning
a father's grief against him?
As far as I'm concerned,
you're worse than Diaz.
You have no idea
what he is capable of.
I know what you're capable of.
You can bring walls smashing down.
You really expect me to believe
that you are scared
of a thug like Diaz?
So much more than just a thug.
And, yes.
Yes, I am scared.
And you should be scared, too.
So just sign the damn paper.
[exhales sharply] God damn it!
I made this so easy for you,
didn't I?
I let you into my home,
set you up,
the law books, everything.
I bet you and Diaz,
you must have just loved that.
Hate me all you want.
I'm sure I deserve it.
But I need you to sign this
or he's gonna kill you.
Now that the daughter act is shot,
there's no need for you
to be in my home,
is there?
All right, so when I get home
tonight, please,
I expect you to be gone, all right?
Please just be gone.
-Quentin...
-Please get out of here, now!
Now!
[John] Those Kasnian weapons
Cassamento imported
are shipping out tonight
for the Eastern Seaboard.
But even with A.R.G.U.S. backing
us up there's no way
we can stop all that ordnance.
-So what's the play?
-The play is we destroy it.
Tag the trucks. Let A.R.G.U.S.
attack them separately.
If Diaz is there,
we're taking him out.
That's the plan, right?
That is still the plan.
I won't let anyone split us up
ever again. I promise.
Rene.
You good?
I don't think so.
That compartmentalizing you talked
about, it's not kicking in.
-Give it some time, man.
-Maybe.
I don't know.
But what I do know is,
if I go out there like this,
I'm no good to anyone.
Sorry, but I think I might have to
sit this one out.
[Curtis] Wait, what's happening?
Just a tough reentry, that's all.
The three of us, plus A.R.G.U.S.
We'll be fine.
I'll be gone in a minute.
Just wait.
[sighs]
Listen, back there at my office, I...
I've never heard you sound so scared.
It made me realize, you were serious.
Diaz is a monster.
And you can't even imagine
what it's been like.
Okay, back on the Earth you're from,
you got a guy named Damien Darhk,
real son of a bitch?
-Yeah.
-Well, I worked for him.
I'd do whatever he wanted
to keep my Laurel safe.
And then when I betrayed him...
He killed her.
What I'm trying to say is,
I know what it's like
to do a bad thing for a good reason.
You signed it.
One condition.
You let me help you get away
from this guy.
-That's not possible.
-Come on.
I've known a lot of bad men,
and they've been filled with anger
and with hate, but not Diaz.
He's not filled with anger inside
because he's not even human inside.
I watched him burn a man alive
over a childhood grudge.
If I cross him,
what is he gonna do to me?
Well, I'm not gonna let him do
anything to you, all right?
Yeah, you're gonna protect me
because you're the mayor.
You're not the mayor of anything.
Okay, listen, I'm gonna protect you,
because I refuse to let
what happened to my Laurel
happen a second time.
Okay.
So we protect each other.
[chains jangling]
[speaks Russian]
[in English] You say
I betray myself working with Diaz.
I think much on this.
-And?
-You may be right.
But I realize
moment things went wrong.
Last year when I trusted you
to bring me into city.
So if I betray myself,
Kapiushon,
it is because you,
you betray me first.
Come on. Diaz in here.
If Diaz and the Quadrant ship even
one of those crates...
They'll be arming their syndicates
with weapons
intended for hi-tech warfare.
Yeah, I got it.
The drone is three minutes out.
It won't circle long.
Okay, folks. We have a window.
Their weapons are equipped with
stealth adapters,
making them invisible to ASMs.
You know what to do.
You guys provide me cover fire,
I'll tag all the trucks by hand
so the drones know where to aim.
I think maybe we should
paint the targets.
Olympic decathlon medalist here.
I got this.
[Lydia] Not having a police presence
to worry about
has made our jobs easier.
The first convoy is ready
to move out.
[T-Sphere warbling]
Not again. This time take care
of them, please.
[groans]
[screeching]
[John] Go, go, go!
[groans]
Drone is en route. Panel commencing.
Five down, three to go.
[groans]
One left.
I guess you're not gonna make it
any easier?
[T-Sphere warbling]
Your friends just blew up
12 million dollars
in next-gen firepower.
I don't have any friends.
Tickles.
You see this man?
Savior of this city.
It's pathetic.
[groans]
I feel like you can do better
than that.
Stop it.
This is pointless.
You said you had plan for him,
that you need him alive, no?
In Bratva we have ways of dealing
with conflict like this.
We fight with honor,
we don't do this.
You want me to fight him fairly?
Life ain't fair.
Every drop of blood you draw
from prone man
is sign of weakness. Your weakness.
I'm not weak.
Let's go.
Thank you.
I not do this for you.
[grunts]
Let's make things interesting.
I put you on the ground,
you leave Star City forever.
You put me on the ground,
I do the same.
That fair enough for you?
Yeah.
You think you're so tough
because you spent five years in hell?
I was born in it.
[both grunting]
[groaning]
Come on.
Yield!
Yield or I'll break your neck!
[exclaiming in pain]
[both panting]
It's like I said,
life ain't fair.
You, you have failed this city.
And I'm gonna take it back.
Maybe he won't be so smart
when he wakes up.
Thank you.
Bandage is least I could do.
Not for the bandages, Anatoly.
Thank you for giving me the chance
to take out Diaz.
What makes you think that's what
I was doing?
Maybe I want to see it for myself.
See what?
Which one of you had honor.
Just like you wanted, no?
You allow yourself to be captured,
so I bring you to Diaz.
You know, I just thought that I could
count on you to be the man I knew.
That man was my friend.
Hurry up with bandages.
I have plan to get you out of here.
He wants to see you.
[sighs]
You know, I'd almost forgotten
how awesome it is.
Being a team, working together.
It's almost like Captain Planet
or the Power Rangers,
or whatever references
you guys understand.
-Star City Rockets.
-Is that like a sports team?
I gotta get going.
I got a debrief on my schedule.
Having a day job
has been a definite change.
Hey, John, um,
if you ever think about dropping
the ARG and, you know, joining us.
Oh, I hate puns,
especially bad ones,
but he does have a point,
and we are down one teammate.
Guys, look, I've made a decision.
I'm gonna see it through.
But if we need to, it doesn't mean
we can't ever help each other.
And by the way, even if I do
join you guys,
you'd still be down a teammate.
[knocking on door]
-Yo.
-Hey, what's up?
Is that a cake?
Wow. Zoe keeps this up,
you guys are gonna have to
open up bakery or something.
Yeah, this is her biology homework.
I'm letting her sleep in.
She crashed hard after finishing her
leftover mitochondria.
Gummy Worms. Good choice.
What are you doing here, hoss?
[sighs]
Just checking up on you.
Seeing if there is anything I can do
to speed up that
compartmentalizing you were
talking about.
It's been half a day, hoss.
Plus, you guys had a big win
without me yesterday.
It was just a small win, really.
Seriously, with Diaz working
with the Quadrant now,
things are only gonna get worse.
If we're gonna have a chance in hell
of stopping him,
we're gonna need all the help
we can get.
We're gonna need you.
Look, man,
every time I think about
going out there again,
all I can think of is Zoe.
What's gonna happen to her
if something happens to me?
I'll be fine, Dad.
Uncle Curtis and I were just
talking about...
How you both wear masks and go
and fight bad guys?
It's way obvious.
And you and Dinah talk way louder
than you think you do.
Really? [softly] Really?
Oh, I can actually hear it.
It's pretty loud.
[softly]
Sweetheart, come here. Sit down.
I'm sorry I didn't tell you sooner.
I don't need to be Wild Dog anymore.
Dad, this is my home.
And I want you to fight for it.
You know, I've been hurt in the past
year twice already.
I know.
And that was scary.
But you taught me to be brave,
and face up
to the things that scare me.
Come here. Come here.
I'll be brave
just like my little girl.
Okay?
Okay.
[sighs impatiently]
Now, who we planning on whacking?
That's what I've been thinking of.
Maybe your daddy.
Which is why I came to see you.
Mazel tov.
This is good.
What do you care about
owning this property legally?
It's not about legality.
It's about this.
I needed to know if I could trust
the new mayor.
And what if he didn't sign it?
What if?
We had an agreement if I recall.
I put you on the floor,
you leave the city.
That assumed a fair fight.
Potato, patato.
But I have a certain pang
of conscience.
I changed my mind.
You could stay in this city.
For 25 to life.
I'm thinking about moving up
your trial.
[groaning]
How's next week for you?
[handcuffs clicking]
Don't even think about getting bail.
I got a lot of friends
at the courthouse.
[Reporter 1] Mr. Queen.
[Reporter 2] Mr. Queen.
[Newscaster on TV]
A shocking development today
as Oliver Queen's bail was revoked.
Speculation that the former mayor
is secretly the Green Arrow
has multiplied in recent weeks
after his decision to terminate
two city officials investigating him
led to his impeachment.
The trial is scheduled to begin
May 3rd.
Jean Loring will represent
the suspected vigilante,
but she has an uphill battle
ahead of her.
If convicted, Oliver Queen
could face a life sentence.
His fate now rests in Star City's
justice system.