PREVIOUSLY ON "ARROW"...
JOHN:
THE DANTE PAINTING.
IT'S BEING USED
AS SOME SORT OF
HIGHLY ADVANCED
IDENTIFICATION PROTOCOL
WITHIN TERRORIST CIRCLES.
JOHN: I'M HERE TO
OFFER YOU A DEAL.
YOU GIVE US DANTE,
YOU GO FREE.
DIAZ: NO ONE SAID ANYTHING ABOUT
STICKING A BOMB IN MY HEAD.
DR. JARRETT PARKER:
WHAT DO YOU SEE?
I'M WITH MY FATHER
AT SEA.
HIS BODYGUARD
HA-HACKETT,
MY DAD SHOT HIM.
PARKER: YOUR FATHER
WAS A MURDERER.
MR. QUEEN IS
OFFICIALLY WORKING
FOR THE SCPD.
WE NEED TO ANALYZE THIS DNA.
IT BELONGS TO
THE NEW GREEN ARROW.
FELICITY: THE VIGILANTE
IS YOUR SISTER.
THE DNA MATCH IS ON
YOUR FATHER'S SIDE.
OLIVER: HE HAD
A SECOND FAMILY.
HOW...HOW COULD
HE ABANDON THEM?
HELLO, EMIKO.
WE'RE TALKING TONIGHT
WITH TWO FORMER VIGILANTES
TURNED PUBLIC SERVANTS...
OLIVER QUEEN
AND LAUREL LANCE.
MS. LANCE, YOU'VE HAD
AN IMPRESSIVE START
AS DISTRICT ATTORNEY.
TELL ME WHAT
THESE LAST FEW MONTHS
HAVE MEANT TO YOU.
WELL, RICH,
WHEN I FIRST GOT THIS JOB,
I DIDN'T THINK
I COULD DO IT,
CONSIDERING...THE TRAUMA
THAT I HAD ENDURED.
BUT I WANTED TO HONOR
MY FATHER'S LEGACY.
AND I THINK
YOU HAVE.
WELL, I KNOW SHE HAS.
RICH: MR. QUEEN,
YOU'VE TALKED BEFORE
ABOUT HOW MUCH
YOUR OWN FATHER'S
SACRIFICE INSPIRED YOU.
YES.
DO YOU BELIEVE
THAT'S HIS LEGACY?
[WIND BLOWING]
HELLO, EMIKO.
I KNOW EVERYTHING.
YOU'VE WASTED YOUR TIME
COMING HERE.
WHAT OUR FATHER DID TO
YOU, TO YOUR MOTHER
WAS UNFORGIVABLE.
I NEED TO TRY AND MAKE
THINGS RIGHT.
MY FATHER DID SACRIFICE
HIMSELF FOR ME, AND...
I'LL ALWAYS BE GRATEFUL.
STILL, THAT EXPERIENCE
ON THE RAFT...
JUST THE TWO OF YOU...
WATCHING YOUR FATHER
COMMIT SUICIDE
RIGHT BEFORE YOUR EYES,
THAT MUST HAVE BEEN
HARROWING.
WHAT A TRUE HERO
YOUR FATHER WAS.
I CAN PROVE TO YOU THAT
I'M NOTHING LIKE HIM.
YOU'RE A QUEEN.
ALL YOU KNOW
HOW TO DO IS LEVERAGE
YOUR OWN PRIVILEGE
TO HELP YOURSELF.
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU
WAS WRONG.
YOU SHOULD HAVE BEEN
A PART OF OUR LIVES.
YOU SHOULD BE A PART
OF MY LIFE NOW.
WHY DO YOU THINK
I WANT ANYTHING
TO DO WITH
THE QUEENS?
'CAUSE YOUR FAMILY
DESTROYS EVERYTHING
IT TOUCHES.
I JUST WANT A CHANCE.
JUST GIVE ME A CHANCE.
EMIKO...
YOU'RE MY SISTER.
I HAVE NO FAMILY.
MY GOAL HAS ALWAYS BEEN
TO SERVE THIS CITY.
I UNDERSTAND THAT
THERE ARE PEOPLE WHO...
THEY DISAGREED WITH MY
METHODS BEFORE.
SO I WOULD LIKE TO ASSURE
THE PEOPLE OF STAR CITY
I WILL NO LONGER BE HIDING
IN THE SHADOWS,
AND I PROMISE TO ALWAYS
BE ON THE SIDE OF THE LAW.
I BELIEVE THAT TRUST
CAN BE BUILT
THROUGH TRANSPARENCY.
AND I'M GONNA PROVE IT.
THANK YOU.
[WHISPERS]
YOU WERE AMAZING.
YOU WERE GENUINE AND
HEARTFELT AND AMAZING,
AND FOR A SECOND THERE,
I ALMOST BELIEVED THAT
YOU LIKED LAUREL.
I ALMOST DO.
IF DINAH'S GOAL IS
TO CONVINCE THE CITY
TO ACCEPT YOU
AS SCPD,
I WOULD SAY
MISSION ACCOMPLISHED.
WE'LL SEE.
EMIKO WILL COME
AROUND, TOO.
WELL, SHE HAS EVERY RIGHT
TO BE ANGRY.
MY FATHER ABANDONED HER.
I JUST...
I NEED HER TO SEE
THAT HE AND I ARE NOT
THE SAME PERSON.
WELL, SHE WILL, BECAUSE
YOU'RE NOT THE SAME PERSON.
LOOK, THAT WAS
AN EXCELLENT FIRST STEP.
IF YOU CAN PROVE
YOURSELF TO THE CITY,
YOU CAN CONVINCE
YOUR SISTER TO
GIVE YOU A CHANCE.
I HOPE YOU'RE RIGHT.
YOU'RE HERE BECAUSE
A.R.G.U.S. IS ASSEMBLING
A UNIQUE TASK FORCE,
AND YOU'VE BEEN IDENTIFIED
AS A POTENTIAL CANDIDATE.
FOR A BOMB IN MY HEAD?
NO, THANKS.
I HEARD WHAT HAPPENED
TO THE MEMBERS
OF YOUR LAST SQUAD.
WE ARE OFFERING YOU A CHANCE
TO LESSEN YOUR
PRISON SENTENCE
BY REPAYING YOUR DEBT
TO SOCIETY.
AND WHAT ABOUT
YOUR DEBT TO SOCIETY?
ARROW WAS A CRIMINAL,
AND YOU FOUGHT
ALONGSIDE HIM.
YOU'VE DEMONSTRATED
A SEVERE NEGATIVE RESPONSE
TO MALE AUTHORITY FIGURES.
YEAH. WELL, WHEN YOU GROW UP
WITH A FATHER LIKE MINE...
DADDY ISSUES.
YOU'RE ONLY ALIVE RIGHT NOW
BECAUSE OF YOUR FRIENDS.
JOHN: WELCOME BACK TO
A.R.G.U.S., MS. CUTTER.
"MS. CUTTER." SO FORMAL.
TELL US ABOUT
A CHALLENGE
THAT YOU'VE WORKED
TO OVERCOME.
WELL, THE LOVE OF MY LIFE
REJECTED ME...
FOR A BLONDE.
CURTIS: MAN, WHAT
THE HELL IS GOING ON?
CHINA WHITE, SPAWN OF SLADE,
AND NOW CUPID?
IT'S LIKE THE GHOST OF
VILLAINS PAST IN HERE.
HAVE WE MET?
LYLA: AGENT HOLT, A WORD.
YOU'RE NOT MY TYPE.
THE GHOST INITIATIVE
IS JUST
A COOLER-SOUNDING
NAME FOR SUICIDE S...
LOOK, I KNOW YOU'RE ANGRY,
BUT THIS IS ABOUT DANTE.
SO I WAS RIGHT.
THERE'S A HIDDEN MEANING
IN THAT PAINTING.
JOHN: IT TURNS OUT DANTE'S
A PERSON...
A VERY DANGEROUS ONE.
LYLA: INTEL FROM OUR
OVERSEAS OFFICE INDICATES
THAT HE IS THE FINANCIER
BEHIND DOZENS OF
TERRORIST ATTACKS
ALL OVER THE WORLD.
JOHN: APPARENTLY, THERE'S
ONLY A FEW PEOPLE
WHO HAVE
DIRECT CONTACT WITH DANTE.
WE TRACKED ONE BACK TO
A COMPOUND IN EGYPT.
WE GET A HOLD OF THIS GUY,
WE CATCH DANTE,
AND THE GHOST INITIATIVE IS
OUR BEST SHOT AT DOING THAT.
HOW DID YOU ALL
FIND ALL THIS OUT?
WHY WAS I LEFT
IN THE DARK?
THE LEAD CAME FROM
A SOURCE...
OUR FIRST MEMBER IN
THE GHOST INITIATIVE.
[CURTIS SCOFFS]
HAVE YOU ALL LOST YOUR MIND?
RICARDO DIAZ?!
THE SAME RICARDO DIAZ
WE JUST PUT IN PRISON,
THE GUY WHO STABBED ME,
WHO TRIED TO KILL ALL OF US
ABOUT 17 TIMES? THIS...
CURTIS, WE KNOW THAT
IT'S NOT IDEAL.
THAT IS THE DEFINITION
OF AN UNDERSTATEMENT.
DO OLIVER AND FELICITY KNOW?
NO ONE KNOWS, AND IT HAS
TO STAY THAT WAY.
A.R.G.U.S. KNOWS
THAT WE RESTARTED
THE GHOST INITIATIVE,
BUT THEY DON'T KNOW THAT
WE'RE USING THEM
TO GO AFTER DANTE.
LYLA: AND IF THEY DID,
THEY WOULD KILL THE MISSION.
REMEMBER SWITZERLAND?
NOW THAT YOU'RE LOOPED IN,
WE NEED YOUR HELP.
I'M NOT PUTTING ANY BOMBS
IN ANYONE'S HEADS.
I DON'T CARE HOW EVIL
THAT HEAD MIGHT BE.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO.
WE JUST NEED YOU
TO MAKE SURE
THE BOMB TECH
ISN'T REJECTED BY
THE SUBJECTS' BODIES
AFTER INSERTION.
YEAH, 'CAUSE THAT'S
SO MUCH BETTER.
CURTIS, THIS IS HOW
WE CATCH DANTE.
AND IT'S NOT A REQUEST.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
I HOPE YOU LIKE
MALBEC.
IF IT'S ALCOHOL,
I LOVE IT.
GOOD. WELL, ACTUALLY,
I DON'T KNOW
YOUR EARTH-TWO
SITUATION.
MAYBE YOU SHOULDN'T BE
DRINKING?
OH, PLEASE.
I DON'T HAVE A PROBLEM
WITH ALCOHOL,
MAYBE THE FIRST THING
I'VE MANAGED
TO ONE-UP
YOUR LAUREL ON.
WELL, THEN HERE YOU GO.
SO WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
YOU TOLD ME TO MEET
YOU HERE.
MM-HMM.
USUALLY, THERE'S A REASON,
LIKE A KIDNAPPING
OR MAYBE YOU NEED HELP
TORTURING SOMEONE AGAIN.
I JUST WANTED
TO CELEBRATE WITH YOU
AFTER YOUR INCREDIBLE
INTERVIEW.
OH. OK.
QUENTIN WOULD BE
REALLY PROUD OF YOU,
THE WORK YOU'VE DONE
AS A D.A.
AND THE PERSON THAT
YOU'VE BECOME.
REALLY.
THANK YOU.
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK,
BUT PACE YOURSELF
BECAUSE WE
ARE GONNA DRINK
THIS WHOLE BOTTLE.
BETHANY SNOW ON TV:
...INCLUDING A START
ON PRO BONO CASES AT CNRI,
THE QUESTION AS TO WHETHER
LAUREL LANCE WAS
THE RIGHT PERSON
TO TAKE OVER AS D.A.
WAS PUT TO REST AFTER
A RECENT POLL INDICATES
SHE IS THE MOST POPULAR D.A.
IN THE PAST 10 YEARS.
THE DISTRICT ATTORNEY'S
POSITION IS
NOT AN ON-THE-JOB
TRAINING TYPE.
IT REQUIRES EXPERIENCE
TO LEAD, TRAIN...
LAUREL LANCE.
[MUFFLED] IT IS A MUST TO KNOW
CRIMINAL LAW INSIDE AND OUT.
THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
HELLO, BRETT.
WHO THE HELL ARE YOU?
I DISCOVERED
A NEW TALENT.
I THOUGHT YOU SHOULD BE
THE FIRST TO HEAR IT.
[SIREN SCREAM]
[CRASH]
[DOG BARKING]
WE BOTH KNOW YOU'RE NOT AS
PERFECT AS YOU SAY YOU ARE.
YOU SHOULD BE BEHIND BARS.
I THINK YOU'VE HAD
ENOUGH, BUDDY.
WHAT JUST HAPPENED?
WHO'S THAT GUY?
I GUESS NOT EVERYONE'S
A FAN OF THE D.A.
OK, BUT THE WINE, THE WINE.
OH, MY PRODUCER LOVES
THE PIECE.
YEAH. HE THINKS IT'S
GONNA BE HUGE.
YEAH, I'M STILL HERE.
[ELECTRICAL HUM]
HEY. I'M GONNA HAVE
TO CALL YOU...
RICH KANNON LEFT
THE STUDIO JUST
AFTER 8:00
TO MEET HIS WIFE
FOR DINNER
BUT NEVER
MADE IT TO
THE RESTAURANT.
NEVER EVEN MADE IT
TO HIS CAR.
THEY FOUND IT IN
A PARKING LOT THIS MORNING.
SECURITY CAMERAS?
EVERY SINGLE ONE
OF THEM SHORTED OUT
JUST A FEW MINUTES
BEFORE KANNON
DISAPPEARED.
OH. OVERHEAD LIGHTS
WERE BLOWN.
SUGGESTS A POWER SURGE.
THAT MEANS
OUR KIDNAPPER
KNOWS HIS WAY
AROUND AN
ELECTRICAL GRID.
THAT TAKES PLANNING.
THIS WASN'T JUST
SOME RANDOM ATTACK.
WELL, MAYBE SOMEONE SAW
MY INTERVIEW
AND DIDN'T LIKE
WHAT THEY SAW.
THIS DOESN'T FEEL LIKE
A COINCIDENCE.
WELL, PROBABLY NOT.
BUT UNTIL WE KNOW
MORE, WE CAN'T
ASSUME ANYTHING.
CAPTAIN, YOU NEED
TO SEE THIS.
KANNON ON TV:
OLIVER QUEEN IS NOT A HERO.
HE'S A FRAUD AND A LIAR.
HE DOES NOT
DESERVE TO REPRESENT
THE PEOPLE OF STAR CITY.
AND IF HE DOES NOT QUIT
THE SCPD,
MEASURES WILL BE TAKEN,
PEOPLE WILL SUFFER.
HOW'S THE ANALYSIS
COMING?
ALMOST FINISHED
WITH MY ALGORITHM.
AND THEN AFTER THAT,
I SHOULD BE READY
TO START TESTING,
ASSUMING THEY
DON'T TRIP-WALK
INTO THE BATHROOM
AND ACCIDENTALLY SET OFF
THE BOMBS IN THEIR NECK.
I GUESS THAT SAVES ME
FROM ASKING
IF YOU'RE STILL HAVING
A PROBLEM WITH ALL THIS.
LOOK, I KNOW THESE ARE
BAD PEOPLE,
BUT WHAT WE'RE DOING
IS INHUMANE.
CURTIS, RESTORING
THE PROGRAM IS
THE ONLY WAY WE
CAN GET DANTE
WITHOUT A.R.G.U.S.
OVERSIGHT.
AND THAT MAKES IT RIGHT?
HOW CAN YOU BE OK WITH THAT?
I'M NOT. I'M NOT.
WE ARE FIGHTING EVIL
THAT MOST PEOPLE DON'T
EVEN KNOW EXISTS.
AND SOMETIMES THAT
MEANS MAKING
VERY DIFFICULT
DECISIONS, CURTIS.
THE BOMBS ARE JUST
A FAILSAFE. THAT'S ALL.
THERE HAS TO BE
A BETTER WAY.
I WISH THERE WERE.
COMPUTER: DISTRICT ATTORNEY
LAUREL LANCE ENTERING
QUEEN RESIDENCE.
PHASE ONE IS ONLINE
AND OPERATIONAL.
WHAT THE HELL WAS THAT?
JUST A LITTLE SOMETHING
I'VE BEEN WORKING ON.
OH, GOOD. THAT'S WHY
I'M HERE, ACTUALLY.
I WAS HOPING TO UTILIZE
SOME OF YOUR SKILLS
TO HELP ME WITH SOMETHING.
-OOH.
-HYPOTHETICALLY...
OK, LET ME
STOP YOU RIGHT THERE
BECAUSE WE
BOTH KNOW THAT
"HYPOTHETICALLY" MEANS
THAT THIS IS
DEFINITELY HAPPENING.
I NEED TO KNOW IF SOMEONE
FROM EARTH-TWO IS HERE.
OK. THAT'S NOT
WHERE I THOUGHT
YOU WERE
GOING WITH THAT.
IS IT THAT GUY
FROM THE BAR?
I KNEW YOU RECOGNIZED
HIM. WHO IS HE?
THE MORE I KNOW,
THE MORE I CAN HELP YOU.
DO YOU REMEMBER
WHEN I HELPED YOU
WITH THAT WHOLE TORTURING
THE ASSASSIN THING?
NO QUESTIONS ASKED?
VAGUELY. OK, FINE.
I WILL SEE WHAT
CISCO CAN DIG UP,
BUT THEN WE ARE
DONE PLAYING
HYPOTHETICAL GAMES.
DEAL.
HIS NAME'S BRETT COLLINS.
YOU KNOW, ONE OF
THESE DAYS,
YOU ARE GOING TO
REALIZE THAT YOU
CAN TRUST PEOPLE.
[COMPUTER CHIRPS]
DINAH: HEY.
OLIVER: YEAH.
YOU KNOW, WE KNEW
NOT EVERYONE WAS
GONNA BE A FAN OF
YOU WORKING HERE.
I MEAN, YOU SHOULD SEE
MY STACK OF HATE MAIL,
AND THAT WAS
WITHOUT EVERYONE
KNOWING ABOUT ME.
MM-MM. THIS GUY'S
AN AMATEUR.
THE VIDEO QUALITY,
THE EXECUTION...
HE'S NEW AT THIS.
HE ALSO DIDN'T DO
A VERY GOOD JOB
COVERING HIS TRACKS.
THE VIDEO WAS UPLOADED
FROM A COFFEE SHOP
IN THE SOUTHEAST
QUADRANT OF THE GLADES.
DO WE HAVE SATELLITE
IMAGERY THERE?
I THINK SO.
HOLD ON.
WHAT ARE WE LOOKING FOR?
WE'RE LOOKING
FOR WINDOWS.
IF HE DIDN'T KNOW
TO COVER HIS TRACKS,
HE MIGHT NOT
HAVE GONE TOO FAR
FROM HOME.
THERE.
THAT'S A MATCH.
LET'S GO GET HIM.
[COMM DEVICE BEEPS]
KANNON'S BEEN MOVED.
NOTHING DOWN HERE EITHER.
I GOT A VISUAL,
SOUTHEAST CORNER.
COPY. CLOSING IN FROM BELOW.
[KANNON PANTING]
PLEASE! HELP ME!
COME ON, NOW.
YOU DON'T WANT
TO DO THAT.
WRONG. PEOPLE WITHOUT
THE LAST NAME QUEEN
ARE HUMAN BEINGS, TOO.
[KANNON YELLING]
[ARROW FLIES]
OH. OH, GOD.
I GOT KANNON. ANYONE
HAVE EYES ON THE TARGET?
[TIRES SCREECHING]
LOST HIM.
WE GOT THE REPORTER.
THE KIDNAPPER
GOT AWAY.
THAT'S NOT THE ONLY THING
THAT'S BOTHERING YOU.
IT WAS SOMETHING
THAT HE SAID:
"PEOPLE WITHOUT
THE LAST NAME QUEEN
ARE HUMAN BEINGS, TOO."
OH, AND YOU DISAGREE?
I AGREE.
THE TIMING'S FUNNY.
WHAT WITH YOUR SECRET
HALF-SISTER MYSTERIOUSLY
RETURNING INTO YOUR LIFE,
IT'S STRANGE.
IT'S NOT THAT IT'S
STRANGE. IT'S FAMILIAR.
THE PSYCHIATRIC RECORDS
FROM SLABSIDE
THAT YOU LEAKED
TO THE PRESS.
CAN YOU PULL UP MY
TRANSCRIPT WITH DR. PARKER?
NOT EXACTLY SURE WHAT THAT
HAS TO DO WITH ANYTHING,
BUT, YES, I CAN.
THANK YOU.
HERE YOU GO.
CAN YOU SCROLL DOWN
A LITTLE BIT, PLEASE?
-MM-HMM.
-THERE.
"WHAT BECAME OF HACKETT?
"YOUR FATHER SHOT HIM.
THEN WHAT?
"HE DOESN'T MATTER
IN THIS STORY,
"JUST COLLATERAL DAMAGE?
PEOPLE WITHOUT
THE LAST NAME QUEEN
ARE HUMAN BEINGS, TOO."
THE FILES I SENT TO
THE PRESS WERE REDACTED.
THE ONES YOU SENT TO
THE D.A. WEREN'T.
SO THE KIDNAPPER
HACKED THEM, BUT WHY?
WHY THESE PARTICULAR
SESSIONS WITH PARKER?
CAN YOU LOOK UP HACKETT,
FIRST NAME DAVID?
HACKETT, DAVID,
DIED IN 2007.
SURVIVED BY HIS SON SAM,
NO OTHER LIVING RELATIVES.
I MET SAM A FEW TIMES
GROWING UP.
YEAH, HE'S GOT QUITE
THE RAP SHEET...
ASSAULT,
ASSAULT WITH INTENT,
A BUNCH OF DRUNK
AND DISORDERLIES.
HIS FATHER WAS
LOST AT SEA.
OR SO HE THOUGHT
UNTIL HE READ YOUR
SESSIONS WITH PARKER.
AND HE FOUND OUT HIS
FATHER WAS MURDERED
BY MY FATHER.
EMIKO WAS RIGHT.
MY FAMILY DESTROYS
EVERYTHING IT TOUCHES.
[CELL PHONE CHIMES AND VIBRATES]
CRAP.
HEY, I HAVE TO GO.
-OK.
-AND I'M SORRY.
I LOVE YOU.
I LOVE YOU, TOO.
[DOOR OPENS]
LOOKIE HERE.
MR. TERRIFIC.
IT'S BEEN A WHILE,
MY FRIEND.
YOU LOOK
A LITTLE NERVOUS.
IS THAT BECAUSE
THE LAST TIME WE MET
I HAD MY KNIFE
IN YOUR GUT?
WASN'T PERSONAL.
IT'S PROBABLY BEST NOT TO
TALK DURING THE PROCEDURE.
HEY.
HE LOOKS A LITTLE NERVOUS,
DOESN'T HE?
I CAN SMELL IT ON HIM
FROM HERE.
IT'S OK, SWEETIE.
I'LL PROTECT YOU.
CURTIS: YOU KNOW, IT'S
REALLY GONNA BE NICE
TO FINALLY HAVE SOME
PEACE AND QUIET.
[DEVICE HISSES]
WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU DOING?
MAKING SURE THE BOMBS
INSIDE OF YOUR NECK WORK.
BUT TO DO THAT,
I NEED TO TURN THEM OFF,
WHICH MEANS THAT YOU HAVE
TO TAKE A NAP.
IT'S STRANGE...
YOU THINKING
IT'S A GOOD IDEA
TO GIVE ME DRUGS.
[COMPUTER BEEPING]
NO. NO, NO, NO, NO.
THIS CAN'T BE RIGHT.
[RESTRAINTS BREAK]
[THUD, BONES CRACK]
I THOUGHT YOU WERE
SOME KIND OF GENIUS.
DIAZ: WAKE 'EM UP!
CURTIS: NOT A CHANCE.
I SAID, WAKE THEM UP!
OK, OK.
IT DOESN'T MATTER.
EVEN ONCE YOU GET
OUT THAT DOOR,
A.R.G.U.S. GUARDS
ARE GONNA BE
ALL OVER YOU.
YOU LET ME WORRY
ABOUT THAT.
MOVE!
UP. HEY. GET UP.
WHAT THE HELL'S GOING ON?
EARLY RELEASE
FOR GOOD BEHAVIOR.
KANE: WHAT ABOUT THE BOMBS
IN OUR NECKS?
THANKS TO OUR FRIEND HERE,
OUT OF COMMISSION.
MOVE.
[CAR ALARM SOUNDS]
[ALARM IS DISARMED]
[LOUD MUSIC PLAYING]
[SNIFFLES]
YOU'RE STILL
A DISGUSTING DRUNK.
YOU HAVEN'T
CHANGED A BIT.
BUT YOU HAVE.
LOOK AT YOU, PRETENDING
TO BE REFORMED,
PLAYING MAKE-BELIEVE LAWYER
IN THOSE FANCY D.A. SUITS.
YOU'RE A WOLF
IN SHEEP'S CLOTHING,
A WOLF THAT THIS CITY
NEEDS TO BE RID OF.
-UH! HYAH...
-HYAH! HYAH...
YOU SHOULD HAVE STAYED
ON EARTH-TWO.
WHAT THE HELL IS EARTH-TWO?
YOU KNOW,
THREATENING ME...
THAT WAS A BAD IDEA.
THEN AGAIN,
YOUR JUDGMENT'S
IN A PERPETUAL STATE
OF IMPAIRMENT.
I SHOULD'VE FINISHED
YOU OFF THE FIRST TIME,
ALTHOUGH I DOUBT ANYBODY
WOULD'VE MISSED YOU.
LAUREL!
[BRETT GROANING]
WE'RE LEAVING NOW.
YOU FOLLOWED ME HERE?
I DIDN'T FOLLOW YOU.
I...I...I FOLLOWED
YOUR DNA,
WHICH YOU LEFT ON
MY DOOR HANDLE.
IT'S ALL PART OF
THIS NEW PROGRAM
THAT I'M WORKING ON
THAT TRACKS
GENETIC MATERIAL.
AND HERE I THOUGHT I
ONLY HAD ONE STALKER
THAT I HAD TO
WORRY ABOUT.
SO YOU SHOULD BE
FLATTERED
BECAUSE I ONLY STOP
PEOPLE THAT I LIKE.
AND NOW THAT I'VE FOUND YOU,
YOU ARE GOING TO TELL ME
WHAT IS GOING ON.
HEY, I KNOW YOU'RE
NEW TO THIS
WHOLE COP THING,
BUT THE SCPD IS NOT
EXACTLY TOO POPULAR
IN THE GLADES.
RIGHT.
WHERE ARE WE ANYWAY?
KIDNAPPER'S APARTMENT.
HIS NAME IS SAM HACKETT,
AND HE HAS A DEGREE IN
ELECTRICAL ENGINEERING,
AND HE HAS MOTIVE.
HIS FATHER, DAVE, WAS
MY FATHER'S BODYGUARD
ON THE QUEEN'S GAMBIT.
WH...WHY WOULD HE BE GOING
AFTER YOU FOR THAT?
DAVE MADE IT
TO THE LIFE RAFT
WITH MY FATHER AND I.
WHEN MY FATHER
REALIZED
THAT ONLY ONE OF US
COULD SURVIVE,
HE SHOT HIM.
I DIDN'T KNOW.
NOBODY KNEW UNTIL
DR. PARKER.
[KNOCK KNOCK]
SAM HACKETT, SCPD.
OPEN UP.
DINAH: HUH. SAM HAD
A SEARCH TRIP PLANNED
TO THE NORTH CHINA SEA.
I'M SORRY. HE WAS STILL
LOOKING FOR HIS FATHER?
STILL HOLDING OUT HOPE
HE WAS ALIVE? WHY?
BECAUSE YOU SURVIVED.
AND HERE ARE
MY UNREDACTED TRANSCRIPTS
WITH DR. PARKER.
ALL THESE YEARS, DINAH.
ALL THESE YEARS HE
NEVER GOT CLOSURE.
OLIVER.
YOU GOT TO SEE THIS.
LOOKS LIKE HE WAS BUILDING
SOME SORT OF WEAPON.
[ALARM BLARING]
REMEMBER, THEY'RE THE
ONES THAT NEED US ALIVE,
NOT THE OTHER WAY
AROUND.
CUPID: I LOVE IT WHEN
A PLAN COMES TOGETHER.
[MEN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
LOOKING FOR THESE?
YOU JUST KEEP TRYING
AND FAILING.
THIS TIME I CAME PREPARED.
NOT PREPARED ENOUGH.
THIS TIME, I'M GONNA
FINISH THE JOB.
[YELLS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
THIS IS THE DRAGON.
A.R.G.U.S. IS COMING
FOR YOU.
CURTIS ON PHONE:
AND WE'LL BE SURE
TO SEND HIM
YOUR REGARDS
WHEN WE DO.
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
YOU LOOK LIKE YOU'VE
HEARD A GHOST.
[GASPS]
WHAT THE HELL JUST HAPPENED?
WELL, FIRST, I OVERRODE
THE EXPLOSIVE PROGRAM
A.R.G.U.S. PUT INSIDE
YOUR HEAD
WITH A VIRTUAL REALITY
SIMULATION THAT
STARTED RUNNING ABOUT
20 MINUTES BEFORE
YOU REMEMBER GETTING
YOUR SEDATIVE.
THEN I OWNED YOUR ASS.
YOU'RE DEAD.
NO. SEE,
THAT ALL HAPPENED
IN YOUR HEAD, TOO.
BY THE WAY, HARSH.
GET ME OUT OF HERE.
SEE, I DON'T THINK
YOU'RE GONNA WANT TO BE
GETTING OUT OF HERE
BECAUSE IF YOU WERE
TO DO THAT, DANTE WOULD
BE WAITING FOR YOU.
AND I THINK HE'S GONNA
BE REALLY PISSED
WHEN HE FINDS OUT
YOU GAVE US EVERYTHING
WE NEED TO GET HIM.
A.R.G.U.S. THANKS YOU
FOR YOUR COOPERATION.
AS STAR CITY'S NEWEST KIDNAPPER
CONTINUES TO ELUDE THE POLICE,
THERE HAVE BEEN RENEWED CALLS
DEMANDING OLIVER QUEEN
STEP DOWN.
A RECENT POLL SHOWED
THAT AS MANY AS 77%
OF STAR CITY CITIZENS
WOULD SUPPORT HIS REMOVAL
FROM THE SC...
[TAPS ON GLASS]
ANY LUCK
WITH THE EVIDENCE
AT HACKETT'S PLACE?
WELL, THE GUYS IN TECH ARE
STILL WORKING ON I.D.-ing
THE FRAGMENTS, BUT JUDGING
FROM HIS NOTES,
PLAN "B" INVOLVES
A LOT MORE
THAN JUST KIDNAPPING
A REPORTER.
BUT WE CAN'T STOP HIM IF
WE DON'T KNOW WHERE HE IS.
I KNOW ONE WAY YOU
CAN STOP HIM...
FIRE ME.
77% OF STAR CITY
AGREES WITH ME.
SO THAT'S WHAT THIS
IS ABOUT, PUBLIC OPINION?
NO. I...
I WORE THAT MASK
FOR A REASON.
NOW THAT I'VE TAKEN
IT OFF, MAYBE THE CONSEQUENCES
ARE FINALLY CATCHING
UP WITH ME.
WELL, YOU CAN'T TAKE
RESPONSIBILITY
FOR EVERY CHOICE SOME
LUNATIC MAKES, YOU KNOW?
NO. I HAVE TO TAKE
RESPONSIBILITY FOR THIS.
ME BEING ON THE FORCE
PUTS YOUR REPUTATION
AT RISK,
AND IT'S PUTTING LIVES
IN DANGER.
COPS FACE RISKS EVERY DAY.
THAT IS THE JOB.
AND YOU ARE NOT PUTTING
ANYONE'S LIFE IN DANGER,
NOT UNLESS YOU STOP
FIGHTING FOR THEM.
YOU THINK YOU'RE GONNA DO
ONE INTERVIEW,
AND ALL OF A SUDDEN, YOUR
PROBLEMS GO AWAY OVERNIGHT?
I THINK I HAVE BEEN
SO OBSESSED
WITH PROVING TO PEOPLE
I'M NOT MY FATHER
THAT I DIDN'T STOP
AND LOOK AT ALL THE WAYS
THAT I AM EXACTLY
LIKE HIM.
I SHOULD HAVE COME CLEAN
WITH SAM YEARS AGO.
BUT YOU DIDN'T,
AND YOU CAN'T STOP THE PAST
FROM HAUNTING YOU.
THE ONLY THING YOU HAVE
CONTROL OVER IS
WHAT YOU DO GOING FORWARD.
FELICITY: LET ME BREAK
THIS DOWN FOR YOU
IN WORDS THAT I THINK
THAT YOU'RE GOING TO BE
ABLE TO UNDERSTAND.
YOU ARE THE D.A.
YOU CANNOT BE SEEN
ATTACKING RANDOS
OUTSIDE OF A BAR!
BRETT COLLINS ISN'T A RANDO.
HE'S SUPPOSED TO BE DEAD.
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?!
[HEAVY SIGH]
COLLINS IS THE DRUNK DRIVER
WHO KILLED MY FATHER, OK?
I WAS 13.
AND I SPENT SO MANY YEARS
JUST DREAMING
OF THE WAYS THAT I WAS
GONNA MAKE HIM PAY.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT? I DID.
WHEN I GOT MY CRY,
I TRACKED HIM DOWN,
AND I KILLED HIM.
OR AT LEAST I
THOUGHT I HAD KILLED HIM,
BUT, APPARENTLY,
HE'S STILL ALIVE
AND...AND STALKING ME
ON ANOTHER EARTH. HERE.
WHAT? WHAT?
IT'S YOU HAVEN'T HAD
A PROBLEM TALKING ABOUT
THE DOZENS OF
OTHER PEOPLE THAT
YOU HAVE KILLED.
UM, SO WHY...OH, WHY KEEP
THIS ONE A SECRET?
IF SOMEONE
HAD KILLED MY DAD,
I WOULD WANT
REVENGE, TOO.
COLLINS...HE CAUSED
THE ACCIDENT
THAT KILLED MY FATHER,
BUT HE WASN'T THE REASON
MY FATHER DIED.
HE NEVER SHOULD'VE BEEN
ON THE ROAD THAT DAY.
HE WAS WORKING A LOT,
WHICH...
I HATED...
[INHALES AND EXHALES]
BUT I KNEW ON MY BIRTHDAY
THAT WE WOULD BE
ABLE TO CELEBRATE,
ONLY HE...
HE SHOWED UP
WITHOUT MY CAKE,
AND I THREW A TANTRUM.
SO HE WENT BACK OUT.
THAT'S WHEN COLLINS DROVE
HIM OFF THE ROAD.
AND DO YOU KNOW
THE LAST WORDS
THAT I SAID TO MY FATHER?
THE LAST THING THAT I SAID
TO HIM WAS "I HATE YOU."
MY DAD DIED BECAUSE OF ME.
WELL, NOW THAT YOU'VE
SAID IT OUT LOUD,
CAN YOU UNDERSTAND
HOW IRRATIONAL THAT IS?
THIS IS EXACTLY THE REASON
I'VE NEVER TOLD
ANYONE BEFORE.
WELL, YOU SHOULD'VE
SO THAT THAT SOMEONE
COULD TELL YOU THAT
IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT.
[SOBBING SOFTLY]
IF SOMEONE IS AFTER YOU
ON THIS EARTH
OR ON ANY OTHER EARTH,
WE ARE GOING TO GET HIM
WHOEVER THEY ARE TOGETHER.
OFFICER SELWAY,
WHAT DO YOU GOT?
THERE'S SOMETHING
STRANGE ABOUT
THESE FRAGMENTS.
THERE'S A PARTIAL ETCHING
ON SOME OF THEM.
SEPARATELY,
THEY DON'T MEAN MUCH,
BUT YOU PUT THEM TOGETHER,
YOU GET THE LOGO FOR
STAR CITY ELECTRIC.
THEY USE IT TO TAG
PROPRIETARY PARTS.
DINAH: WELL, HACKETT
HAS A BACKGROUND IN
ELECTRICAL ENGINEERING.
DO YOU THINK
HE WAS MOONLIGHTING
FOR THIS COMPANY?
I RAN HIS SOC.
THERE'S NO RECORD OF HIM
WORKING THERE.
MAYBE TRY DAVE HACKETT.
AFTER HIS FATHER DIED,
SAM SPIRALED.
SEVERE DEPRESSION,
GOT PICKED UP FOR DRUGS.
IF HE WANTED TO GET A JOB,
HE'D HAVE TO FIND A WAY
TO HIDE THAT.
WELL, DAMN.
SOMEONE
WITH THE FATHER'S SOC
HAS BEEN WORKING AT
SC ELECTRIC SINCE 2015.
HEY, DOESN'T THE SCE
USE GPS TRACKERS IN
THEIR WORK VANS NOW?
YUP, I'LL RUN A TRACE.
HOW DID THAT 240 GO?
A COUPLE OF DRUNK FRAT
BROS. WASTE OF TIME.
WHAT'S GOING ON
OVER THERE?
OFFICER: I GUESS THE BOX
NEEDED WORK.
AND 3, 2, 1. BAM. HUH.
FOUND
THE LOCATION?
SELWAY: YEAH,
BUT IT CAN'T BE RIGHT.
IT SAYS THE VAN'S HERE.
OFFICER: HEY, DID
SOMEBODY CALL THIS IN?
NOT YET.
-COME ON!
-WHAT'S HAPPENING?
HEY, DID SOMEBODY
CALL SC ELECTRIC?
YOU OK?
YEAH.
OK.
DINAH, YOU OK?
WHAT THE HELL WAS THAT?
I DON'T KNOW.
[MEN GROANING]
[PISTOL COCKS]
SAM: THAT WAS ONLY A WARNING.
BECAUSE YOU'VE AIDED AND ABETTED
OLIVER QUEEN,
YOU'RE ALL GOING TO SUFFER.
UH!
SAM: THE STATIC GENERATED
BY THE ELECTRICITY
COURSING THROUGH THESE
WALLS RIGHT NOW,
IT MAKES THIS VEST
AND EVERY SUBSTANCE THAT
CAN HOLD A CURRENT DEADLY.
[OFFICERS GROANING]
WHAT THE HELL DO YOU WANT?
OLIVER QUEEN.
UNTIL I FIND HIM,
EVERY MINUTE,
A BODY DROPS.
HE MUST'VE HACKED INTO
THE ELECTRICAL GRID.
I WANT YOU
TO GET OUTSIDE,
AND YOU SHUT IT DOWN.
I'LL STALL HIM.
HOW? HE WANTS YOU DEAD.
JUST HURRY.
SO MUCH FOR YOUR HERO.
WHO'S READY TO DIE?
SAM, THAT'S ENOUGH.
YOU WANT ME? I'M RIGHT HERE.
BUT I NEED YOU TO LET
THESE PEOPLE GO.
THEY HAVE NOTHING
TO DO WITH THIS.
OF COURSE THEY DO.
[GROANING]
SAM: SCPD, THE NEWS.
THEY'RE THE ONES WHO
ALLOW YOU
TO FOOL EVERYONE INTO
THINKING YOU'RE A HERO,
BUT I KNOW
WHAT YOU REALLY ARE.
I'M A LIAR, RIGHT, SAM?
BECAUSE I DID LIE
ABOUT YOUR FATHER.
HE WAS ON
THE QUEEN'S GAMBIT.
HE MADE IT TO THE LIFE RAFT.
AND BEFORE MY FATHER
TOOK HIS OWN LIFE,
HE MURDERED YOUR DAD
SO THAT I COULD SURVIVE.
[EXHALES]
GOOD. YOU FINALLY...
YOU FINALLY ADMIT IT.
I WAS WORRIED THAT I WAS
GONNA BE JUDGED
BY THE SINS OF MY FATHER...
BUT...BUT NOT COMING TO YOU
FOR ALL OF THESE YEARS
AND NOT TELLING
YOU THE TRUTH,
I NEVER GAVE YOU A CHANCE
TO GET CLOSURE.
THAT'S ON ME.
I'M TRULY SORRY.
NO, NO, NO, NO.
WE ARE WAY, WAY
PAST APOLOGIES.
MY FATHER IS GONE
BECAUSE OF YOU,
AND I NEED TO MAKE
THAT RIGHT.
UH!
SAM: I'M GOING TO GIVE
EVERYONE HERE
THE CHANCE TO MAKE
A DECISION
MY FATHER NEVER GOT TO...
WHETHER TO LIVE OR DIE.
SAM, NO ONE IS DYING
TONIGHT.
KILL HIM, YOU LIVE.
DON'T, YOU ALL FRY.
YOU HAVE TILL
THE COUNT OF 3. 1...
DON'T DO THIS, SAM.
2...
[PISTOL COCKS]
I DON'T WANT TO DIE.
IF YOU REALLY BELIEVE
THAT YOU HAVE TO DO THIS,
I UNDERSTAND.
3.
PULL THE DAMN
TRIGGER.
SAM: THEN I GUESS WE ALL DIE.
[LOW BUZZING NOISE]
OFFICER: GUN!
LIKE I SAID,
NOBODY DIES TONIGHT.
THAT INCLUDES YOU.
I THINK THE ENTIRE CITY
CAN SLEEP A LITTLE MORE
SOUNDLY KNOWING THAT
SAM HACKETT IS
BEHIND BARS.
WELL, THAT'S THE REASON
I ASKED TO BE HERE TODAY.
I'D LIKE TO SET
THE RECORD STRAIGHT.
12 YEARS AGO,
WHEN MY FATHER'S
BOAT WENT DOWN...
HE AND I WEREN'T
THE ONLY TWO PEOPLE
TO REACH THE LIFE RAFT.
A THIRD INDIVIDUAL,
HIS BODYGUARD, DAVE HACKETT,
WAS ALSO ABOARD.
NOW, WHEN MY FATHER
REALIZED THAT THERE
WASN'T ENOUGH FOOD AND WATER
FOR EVERYONE, AS YOU KNOW,
HE SACRIFICED HIMSELF
FOR ME.
BUT BEFORE HE TOOK
HIS OWN LIFE,
HE TOOK DAVE HACKETT'S.
YOUR FATHER KILLED
DAVE HACKETT.
MY FATHER KILLED
THE PEOPLE OF S-STAR CITY
DESERVE THE TRUTH.
WHY COME FORWARD NOW?
HACKETT HAS BEEN
APPREHENDED.
THE THREAT IS OVER.
BECAUSE TRANSPARENCY
IS ABOUT
MORE THAN JUST NOT
WEARING A MASK.
I'VE MADE MISTAKES.
I'M SURE THAT I WILL
MAKE MISTAKES AGAIN.
BUT WHAT I WILL NOT
DO IS LIE.
THAT IS MY PROMISE TO YOU,
THE PEOPLE OF STAR CITY.
I HAVE WAITED
A LONG TIME
TO WIPE THE SMIRK
OFF OF DIAZ'S FACE.
CURTIS, THIS IS
VERY, VERY GOOD WORK.
WELL, I AM HAPPY TO HELP
MAKE DIAZ'S LIFE MISERABLE
ANYTIME ANYWHERE.
YOUR VR PROGRAM, IT IS
A GAME CHANGER.
NOW THAT WE GOT
THE DANTE INFO,
WE CAN GET RID OF THOSE
NECK BOMBS
AND FINALLY CANCEL
THE GHOST INITIATIVE
ONCE AND FOR ALL, RIGHT?
RIGHT?
CURTIS...
THE GHOST INITIATIVE PROGRAM
STILL HAS VALUE.
WE NEED BOOTS ON THE GROUND.
LOOK, THANKS TO YOU, WE CAN
NOW GET IN THEIR HEADS,
PREDICT PROBLEMS BEFORE
THEY ARISE.
THIS IS GOING TO SAVE
A LOT OF LIVES IN THE FIELD.
EXCEPT MAYBE THEIRS.
WHEN THE DANTE THREAT
IS OVER,
I PROMISE YOU WE WILL SHUT
THIS THING DOWN FOR GOOD.
THERE'S ALWAYS GONNA BE
ANOTHER DANTE.
A LOGICAL REASON TO
COMPROMISE,
BUT I'M NOT
DOING THAT ANYMORE.
WE'VE HAD THIS CONVERSATION.
WALKING AWAY IS NOT
THE ANSWER.
OH, I'M NOT
WALKING AWAY.
I'M JUST NOT
GOING TO BE
FOLLOWING ORDERS
BLINDLY ANYMORE
EITHER.
I'M GONNA CALL
MY OWN SHOTS.
A STALKER FROM
A DIFFERENT EARTH.
OF COURSE.
WHY WOULDN'T THERE BE?
AH. I HOPE YOU'RE NOT
LEAVING
BECAUSE I HAVE
SOME GOOD NEWS.
WE HAVE BRETT COLLINS
IN CUSTODY.
AND AFTER WHAT YOU JUST
TOLD ME,
I'M GONNA MAKE SURE HE STAYS
THERE FOR A VERY LONG TIME.
BUT HOW CAN YOU HOLD HIM
FOR CRIMES HE COMMITTED
ON ANOTHER EARTH?
THIS SCUMBAG IS,
UNFORTUNATELY,
OUR EARTH'S PROBLEM.
BEAT COP PICKED HIM UP
FOR PUBLIC INTOXICATION,
AND IT LOOKS LIKE HE HAS
A HISTORY OF STALKING
AND ANTI-VIGILANTE VIOLENCE.
WELL, THAT MAKES SENSE.
I MEAN, HE WOULD'VE SEEN
YOUR INTERVIEW,
AND YOU ARE THE FORMER
BLACK CANARY, SO...
[CELL PHONE CHIMES AND BUZZES]
AND THE KARMA GODS MUST
REALLY BE ON YOUR SIDE,
BECAUSE CISCO JUST TEXTED
THAT BRETT COLLINS
FROM YOUR EARTH
DIED 5 YEARS AGO
ON HIS PORCH
FROM UNKNOWN CAUSES.
SO 5 MINUTES AGO,
I HAD 2 BRETT PROBLEMS,
AND NOW I HAVE NONE.
NONE.
WELL, THANK YOU. THANK
YOU TO THE BOTH OF YOU.
IT'S NOT SO BAD HAVING
OTHER PEOPLE BACK YOU UP,
IS IT?
HEY.
LAUREL HAS
A STALKER?
YEAH, IT'S BEEN A CRAZY
COUPLE OF DAYS.
YUP.
SPEAKING OF,
I SAW YOUR INTERVIEW.
I'M SO PROUD OF YOU. THAT
COULDN'T HAVE BEEN EASY.
IT'S A START.
IT'S GONNA TAKE
A LOT MORE TO
CONVINCE THIS CITY
I'VE CHANGED.
OH, I THINK YOU'D BE
SURPRISED.
I, UM, I FORGOT...
I FORGOT SOMETHING
OVER HERE.
I SAW YOUR INTERVIEW.
HMM.
THAT TOOK GUTS.
IT WAS THE TRUTH.
IT TOOK ME TOO LONG
TO SAY IT.
BUT YOU DID.
AND THAT'S A START.
WHEN I WAS LITTLE,
I IMAGINED
WHAT IT'D BE LIKE TO LIVE
IN THE QUEEN MANSION.
YOUR LIVES SEEMED
SO GLAMOROUS...
BUT EVEN MORE THAN THAT,
I IMAGINED
WHAT IT MUST HAVE BEEN LIKE
TO HAVE A FAMILY.
YOUR FATHER ROBBED ME
OF THAT,
SOMETHING I SWORE I COULD
NEVER FORGIVE.
BUT I SEE NOW YOU
ARE DIFFERENT FROM HIM.
I'M TRYING TO BE.
DOES ALL THIS MEAN
YOU'RE READY TO TALK?
IT MEANS I'M READY TO
THINK ABOUT TALKING.
I'LL TAKE THAT.
[CAR ALARM IS DISARMED]
MAN: GREG, MOVE YOUR HEAD!