Previously on "Arrow"...
No, Adrian!
The two of you are
working for Ricardo Diaz.
You're both fired
effective immediately.
Obviously, the mayor
terminated us
to impede the prosecution
of his activities
as the Green Arrow.
What Oliver Queen did is
an impeachable offense.
The way you lead
alienates
everyone and everything
around you. Look.
You put the team
at risk by lying!
You leave a trail
of bodies
every damn place
that you go!
My trail of bodies
doesn't include
my own brother.
Truth is, Oliver,
you have become a better man
but, with your focus split,
a worse leader.
If I'm gonna be
the best version of myself,
it can't be with you.
You told Rebecca
what's going on?
You kidding? She'd have
my nuts in a vise
if she knew I was
on the take.
She doesn't get it.
It's a different city now.
It's a different world.
We better call
backup.
It might just be
a power surge.
It's not.
Call backup now!
Unh!
What the hell?
Come on out,
you son of a bitch!
Where's Diaz?
Somewhere inside
surrounded by a hundred cops.
You'll never
get to him.
- He's here.
- That was predictable.
lockdown mode now.
Protect Diaz.
Agh!
Where's Diaz?
In there.
This is gonna be fun.
♪ Arrow 6x18 ♪
Fundamentals
Original Air Date on April 12, 2018
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Allies are
in short supply for mayor Queen
as the city reacts
in the wake
of the sudden firing
of Captain Kimberly Hill
and D.A. Samir Armand.
Though city hall maintains
the firings had no relation
to the ongoing investigation
into the mayor's
reputed vigilantism
as the Green Arrow,
sources
within the city council say
that impeachment
is highly possible.
No. They can't actually
impeach you for firing
two people
on Diaz's payroll.
They can if they claim I did it
to protect myself.
Look. We need
rock-solid proof
that they are
working for Diaz.
That's why you have me,
but in the meantime,
I have something else.
I just got some
more evidence
on how Diaz has
corrupted the SCPD.
So ever since Dinah
and company got fired,
I have been monitoring
the station's
internal security feed,
and every night
at 10:13, this happens,
and then--boop--
45 minutes later,
the feed goes back
online like clockwork.
He's monitoring
his minions in blue.
- He's got to be.
- I agree.
If you're thinking what I think
you're thinking,
you need to stop
thinking it right now. It's bad.
I can't make a move on Diaz
unless I know where he is,
and you just told me
where he is
every night at 10:13.
You can't storm the bad cop castle
by yourself, Oliver.
- It is suicide.
- If I get Diaz,
this is all done--
the investigation,
the corruption,
the impeachment,
all of it.
I stop all of it.
You can't go there
alone.
You will not
come out.
You need help.
All of our help quit.
Well, maybe John
has changed his mind.
What are you
talking about?
Hey, Oliver.
John.
What do you need?
Well, Felicity said
that she needed
to update the code
on my chip.
She also said that you
would be at city hall.
Well, I said
he might be.
I didn't say
he would be,
and, yeah,
I "Parent Trapped" you,
but it was a little naive
of you to think
that I wouldn't
considering how well
you know me, you know.
Now that we are
all together,
we can talk
about what happened.
I'm pretty sure John
has said everything he needs to say.
I think you're
absolutely right. I did.
Guys, this isn't
about what he said
or what he said
or your egos.
We have bigger problems
at hand here.
We need to stop Diaz,
and we have
some pretty good Intel.
Good Intel tends
to fall apart in the hands
of bad leadership,
don't you think?
Oliver, come on.
It doesn't have to be that way.
How would you
like it to be?
Well, it doesn't change
the fact that neither of you
can take down
Diaz alone.
I think there's more
than one way to catch Diaz.
I've been offered
a job at A.R.G.U.S.
Gonna take it?
Thinking about it. Why?
Last time you needed something
from A.R.G.U.S., you had to steal it.
Oliver, you keep
that attitude, man,
you're gonna end up
all alone.
I've listened
to your advice
for the last
6 years.
I think I've earned
a reprieve.
That is not how
I thought that would go.
Sure it was. This is
who he is, Felicity,
and no one knows that
more than you.
Elected officials
cannot fire
the very law enforcement personnel
investigating them.
To do so is the definition of
obstruction of justice.
Captain Hill
and D.A. Armand
were actively sabotaging
this city
by aligning themselves
with Ricardo Diaz.
I was not obstructing
justice.
- I was serving it.
- From what I understand,
Ricardo Diaz is
a second-rate drug dealer
who was released
from prison on a technicality.
I fail to see
your point.
The idea that he
could compromise
a police captain
and a district attorney
is laughable.
I assume that the mayor
will get a chance to address
the city council,
lay out the facts
as he sees them.
Preliminary impeachment
proceedings
begin
this afternoon.
The mayor
will have a chance
to plead his case,
of course.
For your sake,
Mr. mayor,
and for the sake
of your administration,
I hope you have something more
concrete to offer
the council other
than unsupported suspicions.
And I know we
haven't always gotten along,
but I do believe
in due process.
I'll make sure
the council
approaches this
fairly.
I will see you
and the council this afternoon
with evidence.
Uh, you mind if I ask
what evidence exactly?
Felicity's working on it.
Oh. I guess that's
somewhat reassuring.
On the bright side,
if I get impeached, you get promoted.
Heh heh heh!
I'm not much
of a politician,
Oliver.
Well, with Diaz
running the city,
it's not really
politics, is it?
Is that the only
thing bothering you--Diaz?
You've looked
better.
John quit.
I'd say he quit
the team, but...
There's no team.
He seems to think
I'm to blame for that.
Well, I don't see
it that way.
- You're not there, Quentin.
- Yeah, I know,
but I was there when the hood first
showed up, remember,
and that guy bears
very little resemblance
to the guy I'm
talking to now.
I mean, look at you.
You're the mayor, you're a family man.
You're out busting
your hump every night for this city.
I've seen how much
you've changed, Oliver.
So why is all this
happening?
Cayden James and Diaz,
they've done a number,
but things
will get better.
You just got to
stay the course.
Where you going?
I'm going to check in
on Felicity,
see if she's making
any progress,
and I promised William
that I would take him
to his science fair.
It's not
the best timing.
Eh, I think schools
plan it that way.
Well, I mean,
you outdid me.
For my science fair project,
all I did was hack Napster.
What's Napster?
Wow. I am getting older
by the minute.
I can't believe you
cloned a cabbage.
When I was a girl,
cabbage grew in the ground.
Well, you're a long
way from home, Raisa.
That I know.
I'll put these in the car.
- Thank you.
- I just really hope it's better
than Sarah Epstein's
solar hot dog cooker.
She's really been
talking it up.
We're gonna be late.
Where's dad?
- Oh, he'll be here in--
- Hey.
- Finally. Let's go.
- Yeah. I know.
I just got to talk
to Felicity for one second.
- But we're already late.
- Just a minute. I promise.
Council's convening.
I promised them
I would show
them something.
Prepare to be
happy.
Documentation
of threats from Diaz
to Hill's family
and bank statements
proving that he paid
for Armand's son's cancer treatment.
- That's it. That's good work.
- Yeah. It's really good work.
It might be too good
of work.
Without the SCPD,
the only person that
can really obtain this
type of evidence is--
well, as far as city council's
concerned is you.
Are you telling me
that the single piece of evidence
that will stop
this imminent impeachment
is also the evidence that will directly
connect me to being the Green Arrow?
I mean, you could tell them that
you're married to a super-hacker.
- That's not funny.
- I know.
I tried to plant
a fake trail.
It was just that
I ran out of time.
You ran out of time
because you're focusing
on making John and I
reconcile instead of doing your job.
- Hey. I'm on your side here.
- Are you on my side?
- Of course I'm on your side.
- Are you sure you're on my side?
How could you even say
something like that?
- What is wrong with you?
- Dad, you said you'd--
William, I'm right in the middle
of something, please.
- We're gonna be late.
- Well, then we're gonna be late!
Buddy, I'm really sorry.
- Get out.
- Felicity, it was an accident.
I will take care
of William.
Get out.
- Oh!
- Oh! What's wrong?
Looks like you half-expected me
to be a member
of the League
of Assassins.
No. I thought I heard
something.
-How's William?
- He won't come out of his room.
Look. I don't--
I have no idea
what came over me,
what made me lose it,
uh, on him like that.
Everything's piling up.
Yeah, I know.
I think we should take
some space, Oliver.
Um...
I'm sorry. What?
How you lost it
on William,
that is crossing
a line.
I know that you have
a lot on your plate
with Diaz and John
and the impeachment,
but that is
no excuse.
It can't be an excuse.
He's your son,
and you just showed him the man
his father really is.
That is not the man
that I married.
Hey.
- You ok?
- Thanks for coming.
Listen. I, uh, know
I've said this already,
but, uh, you don't
look good.
Felicity...
Felicity found proof that Hill
and Armand are in bed with Diaz.
That's great.
It's great.
Why you got a face
that says otherwise?
Council's gonna
ask me how I got that evidence.
And you don't exactly
want to tell them it's-- it's your wife.
Just shine
a big fat light
on the suspicion
I'm the Green Arrow.
What are you gonna do?
I don't know.
My wife wants
a separation.
I lost my temper
in front of my son.
I scared him.
It was really bad.
Well, you know, I mean,
just apologize to the kid,
sleep on the couch
for the night, and--
a separation just seems
a little extreme.
You know, Quentin,
with everything that's been happening,
it feels like par
for the course.
You talking
about John Diggle?
John, Curtis, Rene,
Dinah.
Why haven't you
quit?
Promise of a raise.
Ohh. Look. You said--
you said I've changed.
I--I appreciated
what you said.
Why does everyone
keep leaving me?
That's the thing
about change, right?
You hope you're doing
the right thing
by becoming
a better person,
but you're also becoming
a different person.
Some people, they just--
I guess like John,
they just react badly.
- That's one possibility.
- What's the other?
That I haven't really
changed at all.
Oh, come on.
I don't buy that.
What you've told me
about John and Curtis,
all those guys, they got their own
issues, all right?
They're just putting
them on you.
And Felicity?
Felicity loves you, man.
That thing with her
and William, it's gonna blow over.
Don't worry about that.
My advice--
you just got to focus on what's
right in front of us now, ok?
I'm gonna reach out
to Samanda Watson.
Maybe she can help
cover us on this.
Quentin, the woman
wants me in prison.
But she also wants
justice, right?
Taking down a crime boss
who's overrun a city
seems to fit the bill
in my eyes.
Yeah, call her.
Now listen.
That council meeting's in an hour.
I got to focus.
I got to--I got to push
this stuff
out of my head,
but I'll--I'll--
I'll be there.
See you back
at city hall.
Hello, Oliver.
Long time.
No. You--
you killed yourself.
Funny thing. You never did go
back for my body.
Guess you were somewhat
preoccupied, right?
Still, seems
a little careless.
Come on, man!
You've seen people come back
from what seemed
like certain death.
As I recall...
You once were stabbed
and fell off
of a mountain,
yet here you are!
Do it!
I didn't last time.
And then I killed
the mother of your son.
I'm not playing games
this time.
This time, I'm
coming for you
and Felicity
and William,
anyone and everyone
who's ever been close to you...
And there's only
one way
that you can stop me.
Oh, now wasn't
that better?
You know, you might
just have to start considering
the possibility that I'm just not
killable, Oliver.
Heh.
No, Adrian.
You're dead.
Still on Lian Yu.
I'm hallucinating.
I knew you'd
kill me or try to.
I always was the one person
who saw you
for the murderer
you are.
What are you doing?
Oh. Oh. You're
running a blood test.
You think you've been
dosed with something.
You know, there is
another explanation,
a more likely one
in my considered opinion.
You're finally
going crazy.
It's completely
understandable, Ollie.
You've lost everything. Heh.
Even the people I couldn't
manage to take from you.
I really like
this Ricardo Diaz.
If he didn't exist,
I'd have to think him up myself.
He's going about all
of this exactly right.
Don't--don't hurt
the people that you love.
Just get them all
to abandon you.
It's actually the easiest
thing in the world.
I told you this, Ollie.
I told you this, man.
Everything you touch
dies.
What you're going
through right now--
losing your team,
your wife, the impeachment--
all of it is happening just
like I told you it would,
and nothing
in that blood test
is gonna change that.
Well?
Vertigo?
Absorbed it
through my--
Ahh. Kullens.
Friend of yours?
Apparently not.
Don't--don't
go talk to Quentin.
You are not in the state
of mind to be talking to him right now.
He might have you
committed,
which would be
a shame
since by my count
he's the only person
still left
in your corner.
Ok. Felicity, William,
and I will be fine.
I just need to
talk to them.
Maybe, but what
about the rest?
It's tough to say
you're in a good place
when your oldest friend
leaves you high and dry.
John made his choice.
Deep down, you know
he's right.
You've changed. Sure.
Maybe you are a, uh--
a better Oliver Queen,
a happier
Oliver Queen...
But it has sure made
you a worse hero.
You have a wife,
a son, you're the mayor,
all of which, yes,
may be going away,
but still, it's
a fair assumption.
You're stretched
too thin, buddy.
Maybe you've gotten
so good at being Oliver Queen
that the Green Arrow's
mission is suffering.
You may be happier,
but the people that you love,
they're not.
Hey. What's
Vertigo do?
Does it show you
your worst fear?
You're not
my worst fear, Adrian.
You're nowhere close.
Oh. I know.
Your worst fear is yourself.
Your worst enemy
is yourself.
Guys like me, Ricardo Diaz,
Damien Darhk, Ra's al Ghul,
when it comes
to destroying you, Oliver,
we all come
in second place.
You're the one enemy
you can't defeat.
Yes, Quentin?
Hearing's about to start.
Where the hell are you?
Well, Kullens dosed me
with Vertigo,
and I have been
dealing with it.
Didn't you say that
Diaz was dealing Vertigo these days?
Well, Kullens is
working for Diaz apparently.
Listen. Where are we
with Agent Watson?
- She's mulling it over.
- She's got to mull faster.
All right. I'll give
her another call.
Listen. Just get down here as fast
as you can, all right?
I'm on my way.
Ollie.
Why are you looking
at me like that?
Ollie?
Are you ok?
I don't know.
You know, if
you tell her the truth,
she'll just think
you're crazy, Oliver.
You'll break her heart
all over again.
Nobody wants that.
Hey. Hey. You can tell
me anything. You know that.
I know that.
I need to leave.
I thought
the boat left at 6:00.
- What?
- The Gambit,
the trip that you're
going on with your father.
I ran into Sara. She said that you
hadn't packed yet.
Do you want me
to help you?
Man, look at how
innocent she was,
how much
she loved you.
-You destroyed that.
-Ollie.
Oh. Tell her about
her future, man.
Tell--tell her
about what happens
when she becomes
the Black Canary.
Ollie, please help me.
Please. I'm scared.
I don't want to die.
This is gonna destroy
my father.
He can't handle this.
She's got
a point.
My question is,
why did you let her
become the Black Canary
in the first place?
Heh. She's a lawyer.
What, after a couple
self-defense classes
and a few sparring
sessions with you,
you think she's ready
to go handle thugs and killers?
- It was a mistake.
- Yeah. Your mistake.
Which I had to pay for.
It was a mistake...
But I knew you,
and I knew that
you would do it
with or without me.
I thought this way
I could protect you.
And how did that work out
for you, Ollie, huh?
Yeah, Ollie.
How'd that work out for her?
For me, not too good.
Uh-uh. I gave you an out.
I told you to stand down.
- Stay down!
- No way!
You know, John came
to see me in here.
Felicity, too,
but you were nowhere, Hoss.
He's got
a point, Oliver.
If your conscience
is so sparkly clean,
why didn't you
check on Rene?
You were here.
Rene made it clear.
Matter of fact,
all of you have made it clear
that you don't want
anything to do with me.
Always a comeback
for everything.
That's enough.
It's not real.
Raisa.
It's not safe here
for you.
A man came.
Hey, hey, hey.
Hey, hey.
Raisa, what--what man?
With a dragon tattoo.
He wants to hurt you.
I tried to stop him.
Little lady
wouldn't go down without a fight.
Your wife and kid
aren't here.
They're at some
science fair.
Come on, come on, come on,
come on, come on.
You still think
this isn't real?
Unh!
Does that feel real
enough for you?
I always wondered
why nobody just does that--
kill you straight.
Turns out, it'd be
a waste of time.
You're more dangerous
as a martyr
than you are
as Green Arrow,
but before
that happens,
there's a lot left
of you
that I want to break.
Ohh.
Ugh.
Ahh.
Yeah. Quentin, hi.
I'm gonna need that hearing delayed.
I'll explain everything.
I'm on my way to city hall.
You have failed
this city,
and you know why.
Because I got
away from you.
You were never supposed
to have partners.
There was never supposed
to be a John Diggle,
a Felicity Smoak,
a team Arrow.
There was never supposed
to be a Green Arrow.
There was only the mission!
I lost sight of that.
You lost your city!
And now you know
what you have to do
to get it back.
It's been
over an hour.
Where is the mayor?
Well, why don't
you ask Ricardo Diaz?
Apologies
for being late.
Over an hour late,
and we certainly hope
you've come with something
worthy of our time.
One minute.
- You all right?
- No.
Where are we
with Watson?
We're on our own.
It's our only card.
You sure you want to
play it?
It's our only card.
- Mr. Mayor.
- Ok. This flash drive,
it contains financial data
and correspondence linking
Captain Hill and D.A. Armand
with a known felon
named Ricardo Diaz.
Known by whom?
I've never heard
of a Ricardo Diaz.
By design. He's kept
a very low profile.
How did you obtain
this purported evidence
against our former police captain
and district attorney?
The Green Arrow
gave it to me.
Or perhaps you gave it
to yourself.
I'm not the Green Arrow.
Not according to
the police captain
or D.A.
that you fired.
And it also seems
rather convenient
that you're not
the Green Arrow
but enjoy a close personal
relationship with him.
That go down
how you expected?
Are you aware
that we can impeach you
not just for obstruction
of justice
but for perjury
and vigilantism, as well?
Ok. I am so sorry,
but something
very urgent
has just come in.
I need to speak
to the mayor, please,
so, uh, please.
10 minutes...Tops.
Thank you.
Wait, wait.
What's happening?
Are Felicity and William
all right?
Listen. The urgent thing
was just a lie to buy us some time.
Felicity and William
are fine, ok?
It is you
I'm worried about.
Have you still got
that Vertigo crap in your system?
- Yep.
- Ok. Listen. We need to retreat,
we need to regroup, ok,
so I'm gonna go back in there,
and I'm gonna tell them you got
a family emergency.
You might not
be wrong.
Ok. Listen. You need
to go back to your secret lair.
Get yourself well.
We'll figure out
the next steps.
Sorry, Oliver.
Bad beat,
but for what it's worth,
I always thought
you were a halfway
decent mayor.
Not a great track record
when it comes to hiring D.A.s, though.
This Vertigo
is going to be out
of my system eventually,
and you'll be gone.
Not possible.
I'm not here, remember?
I'm here.
I'm you...
Which is why you're
gonna listen to me
when I tell you
what you have to do.
The only way to prove
that you're the hero that you say you are
and keep being mayor
is to take down Diaz tonight.
No. He's got an army.
You mean, all those cops
at the SCPD?
I mean that walking
in there is a suicide mission.
That's the risk a hero takes,
isn't it, Oliver?
Diaz is there
every night, 10:13 pm.
The question is
will you be there
to meet him?
Thanks for helping me
put my project back together.
No problemo.
Second place, too.
Pretty good even
if that cheater
Sarah Epstein got the gold for her
solar hot dog cooker
that I swear I've seen
on Amazon.
Ohh. You know,
when I was your age,
I could hit, like,
3 science fairs a day,
and now one--one
knocks me right out.
- Where's dad?
- Ohh. He's buying us
expensive gifts if he knows what's
good for him.
Uh, your purse
is beeping.
- William, go play video games.
- What--
got to do some work,
buddy, all right?
- I'm sorry.
- I know what kind of work.
Good luck.
Pick up, pick up, pick up...
- Quentin.
- Felicity.
Tell me Oliver's
with you.
Well, he was. I--I just sent him
back to the bunker.
No. He's not
on his way there.
I have a GPS on his bow,
and it's on the move.
All right. Slow down.
Let me explain.
It has been a hell
of an afternoon.
-What happened?
-Oliver was dosed with Vertigo.
- Kullens did it.
- That would explain why
he lost it
on William.
He said, you, uh--
you kicked him out.
No, I didn't.
I would never.
Uh, he's on his way
to the precinct.
I mean, that's
totally my fault.
I told him that Diaz
would be there.
Quentin, this is
a suicide mission.
- You have to stop him.
- I'm on my way.
Ok.
What's happening?
Is dad all right?
No. Dad is on drugs.
I mean, not that kind of drugs.
He's gonna be fine.
I just--I have to go help him, ok?
I know. I was listening.
You're an angel.
Actually an angel.
- Hey!
- Get out of here, Quentin.
What are you doing
in that old thing?
Getting back to my
original mission.
Listen. That's just
the Vertigo talking.
- You cannot go in there!
- This ends tonight.
Listen. Even if you weren't high, this
would be a bad idea.
- You're outnumbered!
- I can handle it.
- Listen to me.
- I said--unh--
I can handle it.
Quentin? Quentin!
Hey! You ok?
Oh. Wow. Your husband
packs a punch.
Diaz's men cannot find
the deputy mayor here, ok?
You have to get
out of here, all right?
- Ooh.
- I have to go save my husband.
Yep.
Don't, don't, don't
don't, don't, don't!
Ohh! Do not open
that door.
On the other side of that door,
there's a bunch
of trigger-happy cops
just waiting for you.
- It is a trap.
- You're not here!
Yes, I am.
It's me, ok?
It's the real me.
Do not go
through that door.
I have to.
I have to stop Diaz.
And you will,
but not like this, not tonight.
He is right on the other side
of that door!
So are a bunch of angry cops just
waiting for you.
You go through that door,
what happens to William?
William has you.
Well, what happens
to me?
- You left.
- No, I didn't.
That was not me,
Oliver.
The real me is
standing right here,
and I'm not going
anywhere.
I'm glue, baby.
Please.
Where are you?
The Vertigo, it's making its way through
your system, ok?
It's on its last gasp,
so just--just listen.
Listen to my voice.
No, no, no, no.
Don't. Don't listen to her.
Remember what
your told yourself.
You were never supposed
to have partners.
I know it feels
like you've lost everything.
I don't know how to tell
if you're real.
That's the Vertigo.
It's just messing with your head.
Don't trust it.
Ok. Listen
to your heart.
Come on.
Screw it.
Go after him.
- Ohh! Come on!
- Just like old times.
Well, thanks
for coming back for me.
Ok. Well, less thanking,
more escaping!
Right!
- What's this?
- It's an isotonic concoction
of my own making.
There are oranges
in there for vitamin C,
there's almonds
in there for vitamin E,
there's avocado
in there for omega-3s.
Do not smell it.
Just drink it.
- Salty.
- Yeah. That would be
the fermented
fish oils.
Supposed to help
balance your serotonin levels.
I call it Felicity's party raver hangover
supreme cure! Heh.
Though that might an insensitive choice
of words considering
what you just
went through,
but trust me--
it works like a charm.
Not that I've
used it much.
I mean, that was all in the past.
Trust me. Ahem.
Drugs are bad.
Listen.
That was gutsy as hell,
you going in
the precinct like that.
Yeah. Well, my man
was in there.
Yeah, but whatever
you said to him
could have been caught on
security cameras.
No. Diaz had
shut them down,
so our identities
are safe.
Irony sold
separately.
Excuse me.
I got to take this.
It's the office.
I haven't seen that
in a while.
Wanted to take it
for a spin down memory lane
- or something?
- Something like that.
- Heh.
- The Vertigo gave me
some...Clarity.
- Sure you're not still high?
- Mm-hmm.
John had a point.
I have spread myself
pretty thin.
I'm not giving up on you,
not giving up on William,
and if by some miracle,
I'm not impeached,
I will keep being
the mayor.
I believe deeply
in the good
that I can do
as the Green Arrow...
But I need to bring
the mission back to basics.
I need to bring it back
to where it started.
You mean alone.
Alone.
Sorry, guys.
I hate to interrupt,
but, uh, we got to
turn the TV on. News.
In a shocking fall from grace,
the Star City council has voted
to impeach mayor Oliver Queen
and remove him from office.
We now go live
to councilman Kullens'
public statement.
Mr. Queen's affect
at today's inquiry
certainly placed his fitness
for office into question,
but fundamentally,
it was the unilateral firing
of Captain Hill and D.A. Armand
that ultimately
sealed his fate.
Sorry. I just couldn't stand
to listen to him any longer.
Ok. Listen. I'm gonna
call Jean Loring.
There's got to be
legal options we can pursue.
No.
I don't want you wasting
any more time
or political capital
on me.
I don't give a crap
about political capital!
You should because
you're the mayor now.
Thank you so much, Raisa,
for coming
on such short notice.
I'm used to it.
Thank you, Raisa.
Are you ok, Oliver?
I'll be just fine,
thank you.
I know this question
might be questionable,
but from what it sounded
like earlier--
it's like you were
firing Overwatch.
I'm not firing anyone.
I just--I need to go
back to doing things
like I did
when I started,
and that--that means
doing it alone.
I need to stop Diaz,
and in order to do that,
I need to have
a single-minded focus.
I've got to separate
these two worlds.
I just don't think that that's the best
possible solution, Oliver.
I respect your concern,
and I love you
very much for it.
We will talk more
about this,
but I need to chat
with William.
Yeah.
Hey.
I didn't know
if you'd be awake.
I can't sleep.
I got a news alert
about the impairment.
It's impeachment.
Don't worry.
I'll be fine.
I'm worried
about you.
I'm really sorry
about before.
I would never
purposefully
try to make you
afraid or--
Felicity said you were
on some sort of drug.
Accidentally.
I was dosed by someone
who works for the man
I'm trying to stop.
Ricardo Diaz?
Can you stop him?
I think maybe
I found a way.
Most importantly,
I need to know that
I'm not gonna lose you
or Felicity...Ever.
You won't.
Hey. What are you
doing here?
I heard about
what happened.
I wanted to see
how you were.
Clearly, I should
have brought a broom.
He's spiraling.
The Vertigo worked even
better than I was hoping.
I don't understand
why you don't just put a bullet
in him or 20.
Because it'd be
a waste of time.
He's more dangerous
as a martyr
than as the Green Arrow.
I'm gonna dismantle him
piece by piece.
Like with
the impeachment?
The impeachment was
just the latest step.
And what's
the next one?
We spread the word
that with mayor Queen out
Star City,
it's open for business.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man