[STICKS CRACKING]
-Did you learn all this in nine months?
-Malcolm's a good teacher.
Did he teach you to cheat?
He said there's no such thing.
There's only survival and death.
He's not wrong.
This is good. What is it?
If I told you what it was,
you probably wouldn't eat it.
Is it weird?
You know, being back here with me?
I've been back here before.
You know, in a lot of ways,
this place reminds me of who I am.
Or I guess who I've become.
It's probably why Malcolm suggested
we train here.
It's kind of cool that we're here.
It's like there's really no more secrets
between us anymore.
Yeah.
When you were here, did you ever think
you were gonna see us again?
Get home again?
Chien Na Wei touched ground
in Starling 24 hours ago.
We're trying to determine
how she made it into the country.
But we believe she's here to auction off
the Omega bioweapon to the highest bidder.
The Omega's inert without its counterpart.
-Who's gonna pay for a useless super virus?
WALLER: Rogue nations.
Terrorist groups who believe they can
replicate the Alpha component on their own.
-Why does she have to sell it here?
-There's a corporate executive in town.
A man on the Triad's payroll.
He's committed several acts
of industrial espionage over the years.
His name is Peter Kang.
Yeah, I know him.
He works at my family's company.
That guy came to my house for Christmas.
And that, Mr. Queen, is exactly
why you and Mr. Yamashiro are still alive.
Chien Na Wei chose the one place
on earth...
...where your continued breathing is still of use
to me and my superior.
But have no illusions.
If you threaten to compromise the mission
by contacting anyone in Starling City...
...I will remove you and Mr. Yamashiro
from the equation.
Along with anyone
who discovers Oliver Queen is still alive.
Tracker's in place.
Now what? Follow Kang to Chien Na Wei?
No, she's too smart
to keep the Omega on her person.
She'll keep it secure till the auction.
We need to figure out
where that auction's gonna be.
Kang's on the move.
[COUNTRY MUSIC PLAYING]
Laurel, hey.
What you having, sweetheart?
Next round's on me.
Your desk sergeant called
wondering why you weren't on duty.
Yeah. Well, this is Laurel.
You know, the daughter that lived.
Is there a bartender in the city
that doesn't know that?
Well, excuse me
for seeking a sympathetic ear.
Takes more than some fancy
corporate law-firm job...
...for some of us to get over Sara's death.
I love you, so I'm gonna pretend
you didn't say that and drive you home.
Not now, sweetie. Not now, please.
Hit me again, Frank.
[CHUCKLES]
[LANCE CLEARS THROAT]
Later, Frank.
I'm sorry for all the trouble.
Kang's headed inside.
MASEO: A.R.G.U.S. detected data emanating
from Kang's computer.
But it's protected by SHACAL-4 encryption.
-Okay, pretend like I don't know what that is.
-It means we can't hack into Kang's computer.
You'll need to get
onto the Queen Consolidated network.
Waller was clear what would happen to people
if they found out I'm still alive.
So taking a stroll through my family's company
is probably not the best plan.
You'll go in at night. I don't have time
to familiarize myself with the office floor plans.
Oh, my God.
Who is that?
That's my sister.
Sara. Sara.
-Hey.
-Are you okay?
-Yeah, why?
You kept saying Sara's name.
Oh. Um...
Yeah, well, I was... I was dreaming.
Why didn't you tell me?
-What?
-That Sara died.
Laurel told me.
Kind of by accident, but...
Well, I didn't want to upset you.
And Laurel didn't want...
-...anyone to know.
-Why?
After everything that happened with Slade...
...Sara went back
to the League of Assassins.
She had her own secrets, Thea.
And, uh...
...those weren't my secrets to share.
Was it the League that killed her?
-Where are you going?
-I'm gonna...
...take a walk and clear my head.
Slade.
Told myself I wasn't gonna
come down here.
That I never needed to see you again.
You'll be happy to know I was wrong.
SLADE:
You think I won't get out?
You think I wouldn't kill those you care for?
I keep my promises, kid.
I keep my promises.
Thea.
Hey, the fire went out.
-Ollie, what is it?
-We need to get off the island.
-We're in danger.
-What are you talking about?
-Slade Wilson's here.
-That is ridiculous.
It's not. Just listen to me.
-Slade was...
-I was keeping him prisoner here.
What do you mean "was"?
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
MALCOLM [OVER PHONE]: Hello, Oliver.
-You let him out.
You told me you lost your deal with Ra's...
...despite your willingness to kill him
because you hesitated.
For you and Thea and even myself to have
any hope of surviving the next encounter...
...you need to regain that killer instinct
born of a primal need to survive.
You're sick.
Your sat phone is going to stop working
after this call.
Ollie.
Merlyn set Slade loose as an object lesson.
-That's insane.
-He thinks it'll help me regain my killer instinct.
-If he doesn't kill us first.
-Come on.
-Last time I saw her, she was in pigtails.
THEA: Wait here, okay?
Where is she going?
Hi, Ollie, Dad.
I stopped by the office today.
I saw Mom talking to Walter.
Starting to think
that something's happening there.
-But I don't know.
-Queenie.
Sister's boyfriend?
-I don't know.
-You have my delivery?
You have some of that inheritance?
TOMMY: What the hell is this?
-What are you doing here?
TOMMY: I was about to ask Jordan the same.
-Just paying my respects.
And so you did.
Now you're gonna stay away
from her permanently.
Whatever.
You should be bringing flowers here.
Not looking to score drugs.
What are you even doing here, Tommy?
I came to thank you for my birthday card.
And to tell you
that my party tonight's 21 and over.
Well, I think we both know that
that's not true.
Oh, it is, as far as you're concerned.
-You shouldn't grow up too fast.
-Yeah, well, you're not my brother.
TOMMY: You're right, no, I'm not,
but I think about him every single day.
For the first time, I'm glad he's gone.
Because seeing you like this
would break his heart.
It's funny how Ollie seems to care more about
me now that he's dead than when he was alive.
THEA: Every time I spoke to his grave,
it always felt so empty.
That's because he was here
watching over you.
Why did you bring me here?
He has something we need.
-I thought you were better with a bow.
-I am. It's for you. Just in case.
What is it?
He's been here.
[ALL GRUNTING]
Nice to see you again...
...Miss Queen.
-You okay?
-Yeah.
She's unhurt.
I have no desire to kill either of you.
This time tomorrow,
two bodies will be found in Starling City...
...burned beyond any recognition...
...but ample evidence...
...that Oliver and Thea Queen
have been killed in some horrible accident.
I'm gonna leave you, kid,
the same way you left me.
Alone in purgatory.
You leave me and you let my sister go.
You're lucky I didn't bury her next to Shado.
Did he tell you about her?
Shado...
...is the reason why this is all happening.
Why I killed your mother.
He doesn't need to.
I figured out you're a sick son of a bitch
all on my own.
Well, of course he didn't tell you.
Your brother likes his secrets.
You always have.
That's who you are.
You know, if you'd told me
what really happened with Shado...
...your mother would still be alive.
-That's enough!
-I agree!
Welcome home, kid.
Slade.
Slade!
MASEO [OVER RADIO]:
Are you in position?
-Yeah.
-The company computers...
...are protected by biometric encryption.
Look for a fingerprint reader.
Okay, but why wouldn't they take me out
of the directory?
Why would they? You're dead.
Yeah, I'm in.
The crawler's programmed
to seek out all of Kang's network traffic.
And it's running.
The program should take 90 seconds.
What's that?
-Oliver, you have to go.
-I'm not done.
You have to go. Someone's coming.
You're cute.
It's too bad you're, you know, dead.
Which is obviously a lot worse for you
than it is for me.
I really need to learn...
...to stop talking to myself.
According to the information we took
off Kang's computer, the auction is tonight.
-In four hours.
WALLER: Where?
MASEO:
Still working on that.
The crawler program
retrieved 2.7 gigabytes of data.
-It's taking some time to cull through.
-You have less than four hours.
Where's Queen?
Probably went to check on our weapons.
[OVER SPEAKERS]
You spin my head right round, right round
Oh.
-Pig.
WOMAN: A little early.
Hoo. Uch.
Thanks, bud.
Yeah, no problem...
...bud.
GUY:
Whoo.
Nothing like a rich kid's party
to remind me what I missed...
...about being shot at in Afghanistan.
When I hooked up my brother
with his first stateside job...
...I somehow expected more gratitude
and less complaining.
-Less complaining. You sound like Lyla.
-You should've never divorced her.
You big dummy.
Thank you, Andy. I appreciate that.
You spin my head right round, right round
When you go down, when you go down, down
TOMMY:
Do you like sushi?
Have you ever had anyone
eat some off of you?
I promise not to use chopsticks.
LAUREL:
Are you still using that line?
-Well, it looks like I scared her off.
-Oh, it's all right. She's vegan anyway. Ha, ha.
What are you doing here? I heard you decided
to go corporate in San Francisco...
...instead of saving the world in Starling City.
I realized that maybe the world
can't be saved.
-What is it?
-I just don't believe who's here.
Queen.
She's amazin', she's blazin'
Hotter than Cajun
Girl, won't you move a little closer?
I thought I told you this party is 21 and over.
No worries, I came prepared. Fake ID.
Laurel, how are you?
I'm handling.
-How's school?
-Straight-A student.
I'm gonna go grab a drink.
Nonalcoholic, I swear.
Queenie.
-Isn't this past your bedtime?
-Maybe I need something to keep me awake.
You holding?
-Stay away from Thea Queen.
-Who the hell do you think...?
Holy crap.
You're Oliver Queen.
You're supposed to be dead.
People are gonna lose their minds.
Stay away from my sister.
How'd you like to be dead again?
How many people are in this prison?
You know, maybe there's somebody
we could call for help?
Well, Slade killed the guard.
There's one other inmate.
He's not gonna be helpful.
Then how are we supposed
to get out of here?
This is a Chinese prison retrofitted
by eight A.R.G.U.S. technicians.
There is no getting out of here.
So we're just supposed to sit here
and starve to death? That's your plan?
I am working on a plan.
-What did he mean?
-What?
Wilson, when he said that you were still
hiding something.
-He's insane.
-Yeah, I picked up on that.
I also picked up on how you reacted
when he said...
...that you were keeping secrets from me.
Was he telling the truth?
I don't think that this is the right time.
Actually, I think time is something
that we have a lot of right now.
-Why didn't you tell me about Sara?
-Come on, Thea.
Now that I know about your secret,
everything has become a whole lot clearer.
And I can tell when you're hiding
something from me.
Like you are doing right now.
So, what is it gonna take for you to stop
treating me like this tiny fragile little object?
Tiny?
What?
This prison. These...
...cells, they were made for men.
Fully grown men. Come here.
I can't... Never thought I would wish
for longer arms.
There's a way that we can do it.
But it's gonna hurt.
[SIGHS]
Just do it.
Okay.
On three. One.
Two. Three.
[GROANING]
-You okay?
-I, uh...
[THEA GROANS]
All right.
[GRUNTING]
[LOCK BUZZES]
That's good.
Come on.
Malcolm would've told Slade
about the plane we used.
That's how he plans to get back.
[CROWD MURMURING]
No, I didn't...
-Queen?
-What?
Anybody see who Peter Panned him?
Witnesses saw someone head upstairs
before it happened.
Male. White or Hispanic. Twenty to 30s.
That narrows it down.
Maybe it's a vigilante doing some
public service.
Heh. Sure.
-Thea, right?
-Yeah?
-Aren't you young to be at a party like this?
TOMMY: I invited her.
Oh. Well, you spoiled billionaires sure know
how to throw yourselves a party.
You got underage girls, drug dealers.
You got dead drug dealers.
If I'd known, he never would
have made it past the front gate.
-We had a lot of crashers here tonight.
-Yeah, right. I can see that.
What are you doing here?
They asked us to stay and give statements.
-No. I mean at this douche bag's party.
-Tommy, I'm sorry.
Wow. You really have a thing
for rich bad boys.
You'd think one of them getting your sister
killed would have gotten you cured of that.
Dad.
LANCE:
What about you, sweetheart?
Funny, can't figure out if you're following
in your brother's footsteps or my daughter's.
-That is enough.
LANCE: Just observing how one boat trip...
-...can turn everyone's life to crap.
LAUREL: No, that is enough.
-We're not doing this.
-We're leaving. Right now.
Well, thank you for that.
-I'm sorry, was I embarrassing you?
-No.
-Yourself.
-At least I know who I am.
I'm not becoming someone I'm not.
Hanging around with billionaire playboys
like some gold digger.
Taking on a sellout job in San Francisco.
Is that what this is about?
When Sara died,
you wanted to go to law school...
...because you wanted
to make the world a better place.
Wethersby Posner is one of the most
prestigious firms in the country.
You wanted to help people.
All you'd be doing is helping fat cats.
This sermon would have a bit more credibility
if you weren't so lit right now.
Well, I don't need to be sober
to see what you're doing with your life.
I just wish you could too.
What were you thinking?
-Anyone at that party could have seen you.
-Yeah, I pulled...
...the hoodie down to cover my face.
That wouldn't work even if you
smeared greasepaint on your face.
So, what, you came to chastise me
at gunpoint?
We got the auction location
from the scraper program.
Kang is using a defunct factory
owned by your family's company.
I don't care. I'm done with the mission.
-Oliver.
-Coming back here, Maseo...
...has shown me all the wreckage
that I have left behind.
If I go with you tonight and I get killed...
...then I lose any chance I've ever had
of fixing all of the things that I broke.
You don't have that chance.
Waller will kill your...
My family is resourceful.
We have connections in the media.
There has to be a way to shelter us
from whatever Waller does.
Look, Oliver, if you want redemption...
...start with the lives Chien Na Wei's
bio weapon could end.
These people are strangers to me.
These people...
...they're my friends and my family.
And they would be ashamed
of the selfish choice you're making.
They're already ashamed of me.
Goodbye, Maseo.
Hey, wait. I think I found a path.
Thea. Stop!
Oh, my God.
-What the hell was that?
-It was a booby trap.
What kind of psycho
would put that thing there?
[GROANS]
-Me.
-Oh, God.
[BOTH GROAN]
Slade's gonna be at the plane.
We need to move.
No, we need to rest.
Just a few minutes, okay?
-Slade gets to...
-He will kill us if you end up passing out.
Okay, okay. Okay, a couple of minutes.
Why didn't you tell me about Sara?
Oh, come on.
Every time I bring her up,
you end up evading it.
Because this isn't the time.
We just need to focus.
Well, I'm not, okay?
Knowing that you're keeping something
from me again...
...it's keeping me everything
but focused right now.
-So tell me.
-Malcolm killed Sara.
No, no. He was in Corto Maltese
with me, okay?
He didn't kill her directly.
He used someone.
He put them under the influence of a drug.
So she wouldn't know what she was doing.
She?
She who?
You killed Sara.
Oh, God. Oh, God.
No, Sara... No, she...
She was my friend.
-How could you not tell me?
-Because you weren't you.
Oh, God.
You had no control over your actions.
You cannot blame yourself.
You were right about Malcolm, okay?
He doesn't love me.
-I'm an idiot.
-No, you're not.
This whole thing with Lian Yu.
This is ridiculous,
and what the hell are we even doing here?
I ask myself the very same question.
Over and over.
Slade.
Don't.
Oh, yeah.
You've come a long way.
[BOTH GRUNTING]
I'm here to make good with my promise, kid.
Hello, Oliver.
Well, I told myself I was recording
this message in case I died suddenly but...
I wonder if it isn't just easier to say
what I have to say with a video camera.
I'm not the man you think I am, Oliver.
I didn't save our city. I failed it.
I did something terrible,
and in my efforts to make it right...
...I ignored my conscience
and made alliances with terrible people.
There's a book.
Book with a list of all their names.
And with these people...
I always told myself that everything I did...
...I did for my family.
That's a lie.
Because what good is a family...
...without a soul?
You can right my wrongs.
You...
...can be better than I was.
You can save this city.
I love you.
Thank you all for coming.
I promise that for one of you...
...it'll be well worth your time.
You've read the briefing.
With the proper resources...
...you can own...
...Armageddon.
The bidding will begin at $50 million.
Fifty-five?
Do I hear 60?
[METAL CLANKS]
[YELLS]
[GUN CLICKS]
I have $60 million.
Going once.
Going twice.
MAN:
Ninety million.
Anyone care to make it an even hundred?
Just a moment.
I don't like uninvited guests.
[IN CHINESE]
I'm sorry I'm late.
Actually, you arrived right on time.
Let's go.
[GUNFIRE]
[IN ENGLISH]
Make the call.
Find me the Yamashiros.
They die tonight.
You have a choice to make.
-What choice?
-Whether or not you wanna keep your hand.
-Come on, then. You've earned it.
-Thea, don't.
-He killed Mom.
-And he will continue to pay for his crimes.
But not like this.
You're not a killer.
-You tell that to Sara.
-What happened to Sara is not on you.
What happens to him is.
All this is what Malcolm wanted.
He freed Slade...
...to prove that we're killers
because he wants you...
...to be just like him.
You gotta prove to him that you're not.
[GRUNTS]
[GUNSHOT]
SLADE:
A flesh wound.
You're clearly not the killer
that your brother is, Thea.
Yeah, I wish that were true.
-She's lost, your sister.
-No, she's not.
You can see it in her eyes.
She's been touched by darkness.
Was it Merlyn?
He's an interesting man to do that
to his own daughter.
So now you've lost your father...
...your mother and now your little sister.
How's the girl with the glasses?
What's her name? Felicity.
[GRUNTS]
How many people can Oliver Queen lose...
...before there is no more Oliver Queen?
Thanks for the trip home.
Have a nice flight back to Hong Kong.
I'm afraid it's not that simple, Mr. Queen.
The hell it's not. You have the Omega.
You have Chien Na Wei. It's over.
I'm sorry to say
that's not up to either one of us.
SHRIEVE:
This him?
General Matthew Shrieve.
You've done your country
quite a service today, Mr. Queen.
That said, I've got some news
you're not gonna wanna hear.
Well, general, I'm used to that by now.
We're gonna need to debrief you.
Back in China.
But once that's accomplished...
...and the Omega secured...
...I'll make sure you go any place
in the world you wanna go.
Sound fair?
Yeah.
[LAUREL CHUCKLES]
Tommy Merlyn.
Are you stalking me?
Just checking on you.
Things with your father seemed, uh...
They seemed tense.
Your roommate told me you were taking
a job here. I said that couldn't be true.
That you were going to work
for a white-shoe firm.
Ah. I was.
Then someone reminded me
why I became a lawyer in the first place.
You wanna tell me about it over dinner?
Hey-ey-ey.
It is just dinner.
How many girls have you used
those three little words with?
Those are the only three little words I say.
Fine. Just dinner.
-Let's go.
-Maybe drinks?
-Maybe.
-Okay.
Dad.
-I didn't know that you were gonna be here.
-Where else would I be?
Gotta figure out a way
to tell your mom about this.
Um...
She already knows.
You weren't worried
about her heart giving out.
If you were gonna drink that,
you would have done it by now.
Really?
What, you gonna go get your mask and
your billy club and take it away from me, huh?
-Black Canary.
-Dad.
When does your shift start?
Shouldn't you be running around?
Hey.
Do you remember when I was gonna take
that corporate job?
You remember what you said?
You were mad because I wasn't choosing a life
where I was going to help people.
It's like you knew...
...already, even then.
You knew that my life was always headed
towards that mask.
You think that's what I'm all torn up about?
The reason why I wanna open up this bottle...
...I wanna crawl inside,
is because of what you did to us.
I love your sister, I love your mom.
So much like each other, you know,
these wild spirits.
But you and I, we had something.
Because we were the ones who were alike.
And we had a trust, we had a bond,
and you broke it.
And, I don't know...
...how you could do that to us.
But I'm gonna survive this.
And what I got is my baby girl.
What you've done...
I don't know how I'm gonna live
through this.
-Daddy, I think we should go to a meeting.
-Yeah.
I'll go to the one on Broxton.
You go to the one on Fourth.
I need a shower.
I need 10 showers.
-Thea.
-I'm fine.
I would be really, really worried
if that were true.
What do you wanna hear?
Nothing.
And I don't want you to tell anyone
about this, especially Laurel.
And why is that?
Because she loves you like a sister,
and it would hurt the both of you too much.
Does she know about Malcolm?
No.
No, that would complicate things...
...and despite everything that he has done...
...we still need him.
MALCOLM:
I agree.
I guess A.R.G.U.S. is looking for a few guards
to volunteer for island duty.
You almost got us killed.
I had more faith in you and my daughter
than you obviously have for yourselves.
-How could you do that?
-To challenge you, see if you both could work...
How could you make me kill a friend?
He should not have told you that.
I trusted you.
I let you into my life.
How could you have done this to me?
Because you are my daughter
and I care about you.
God, that's sick.
And not even remotely true.
You do not understand the danger we face
from Ra's al Ghul.
Just stop. Stop using him as an excuse.
The only person that I'm afraid of
right now is you.
-Please do not do this.
-Just stop.
I will work with you to stop Ra's.
Because that's what my brother says
we need to do.
So I will be your student.
I'll be your partner.
Even if I have to, I will be your soldier.
But never again will I be your daughter.