Previously on "Arrow"...
Tibetan pit viper
venom.
A constant dose of that
can't be good for you, right?
It'll keep him sedated
like it did Slade.
No mention on
Isabel Rochev's death?
Not a thing.
Choose. Choose!
No! No!
No, mom! Mom,
what are you doing?
Both my children will live.
What are
you doing?!
You possess true courage.
No!
There is still one person
who has to die...
Before this can end.
- No...
- Mom?!
I do solemnly swear
that I will support,
defend, and abide by
the Starling City charter.
And that I will faithfully
discharge the duties
of the office
of mayor of Starling City.
That I will tirelessly
pursue justice on behalf
of all of starling's
citizens...
Impartially,
to the best of my abilities.
So help me God.
Thank you.
Thea.
Hi.
I'm here for you.
I know.
Ms. Queen.
I wanted to offer my sincere
condolences on your loss.
Your mother was a good woman.
She would have made
a wonderful mayor.
Thank you.
I'd love to speak with Oliver.
Well, if you see him,
tell him he missed his
own mother's funeral.
No one's seen Oliver
for a few days.
We all deal with grief
in different ways.
And the loss of a parent is...
Well, it changes you.
When you realize that your
ancestors now look to you;
that your family's legacy,
their continuing works,
are solely in your hands.
If you see Oliver,
please tell him that I came by.
Of course.
Hey.
Thanks.
I don't even know
why I'm crying.
I didn't even
like Moira.
Terrible thing to say about
someone after they've just died.
In my defense,
she was not nice.
She was diabolical.
Not a word you often
hear at someone's funeral.
You're not crying for her, Felicity,
you're crying for Oliver.
Where is he?
How could he
not be here?
I don't know.
If Oliver's smart...
He ran back to his
island to hide.
But maybe he'll attend
your funerals.
I always loved
this photograph.
I thought your mother
looked particularly beautiful.
Well, she didn't.
She thought
she looked bug-eyed.
She never said.
How are you holding up?
I'm not.
Your mother gave her
life for you, Thea.
She showed you how much
she loved you in ways
very few parents
ever could.
I know.
She died thinking
I hated her.
But all we ever needed
was the truth.
It was a lie
that killed her.
I don't understand.
Slade Wilson.
He was on that
island with Oliver.
And despises him
for some reason.
There was a psychopath
in our lives
and my brother never
warned us about him.
Thea, your brother loves you
more than life itself.
You should
keep that photo.
This sub is over
60 years old.
It was carrying the Mirakuru during
the war when it ran aground.
Blood.
Slade's.
He was bleeding out, dying.
Until we decided
to give him the Mirakuru.
Not one of your
better ideas.
What about my idea
for you to fix this sub?
You were in the Navy.
The Russian Navy.
They taught us how
to sink Japanese sub, not pilot them.
Anatoly, please.
I know it's a long shot,
but if we get this sub operational,
we can blow Slade
and the Mirakuru out of the water
and get the hell
off of this island.
I mean, unless
you have a better idea,
this is our only chance
of getting home.
Ok. I try.
No one has seen Slade Wilson since
the night of the attack.
I mean, he hasn't made any further
threats on the Queen family,
but we got to find
this son of a--
Excuse me. Hey.
Missed you
at the reception.
Yeah. I had to get back here,
see what was happening
with the case.
Any leads?
No. Wilson's a ghost.
He's not the only one
who's disappeared.
You heard from your sister?
Nothing apart from a text that
she needed a change of scenery.
Something else on your mind?
It's Sebastian Blood.
There's something that
doesn't seem right.
Laurel...
Dad, I know what you're thinking.
When I accused him
of killing his father, I was upset.
But just because
I had a problem
doesn't mean
I was wrong about Sebastian.
Please, don't go down
this road again, ok?
What's bringing this on?
I saw him
at the reception.
And it struck me that the only reason
that he's mayor now
is because Moira
was killed.
Yeah, by Slade Wilson.
What if there's
a connection?
You once told me,
a cop is only as
good as his gut.
Well, I'm the daughter
of a cop,
and I know in my gut Sebastian is not
the man that you think he is.
You sure?
Baby, last time...
I was a drunk.
And you were right
not to trust me.
But, Dad...
I need you
to trust me now.
This legislation
is the first step
toward making Starling City
the jewel that it once was.
The jewel that
it can be again.
Phone call for you,
mayor Blood.
I'm still getting used
to people calling me that, Alyssa.
Please take a message.
The caller insisted.
He said he's your father.
That's impossible.
Never mind.
I'll take it.
Hello?
Hello, Sebastian.
I'm sorry to bother you.
I just wanted to check in
and see how
your first day is going.
Very well,
thank you.
But I'm a little
busy right now,
so if you'll allow me
to call you back,
I'll do that
as soon as I can.
I'm sure you have quite
a lot of business to attend to.
You are the major
now, after all.
So get to work.
We're almost
out of snake venom.
Seeing Roy like this
reminds me of Barry.
And Barry reminds me
of S.T.A.R. Labs.
S.T.A.R. Labs reminds me of the
Mirakuru cure that they're working on,
which we could really
use...right now.
Yeah, especially since Isabel Rochev
was clearly injected with the stuff.
How do you know?
'Cause there's no other way
she could be walking around
after being shot dead-on
with a nine-millimeter
hollow point.
I've left about
a dozen messages for Oliver
about Isabel being back.
No response.
You have any luck finding him?
Tons. All of it bad.
There's been
no activity
on his passport,
cell phone,
or bank accounts--
what's left of them, anyhow.
And facial recognition
hasn't spotted him in any airport,
bus, or train station.
Right.
What about Sara?
Nothing either.
Dig, people don't just go missing
like this, unless...
Don't go there,
Felicity.
What if she is?
What if Oliver is?
Maybe the reason we can't
find him is because--
He's alive, Felicity.
If he wasn't, Isabel Rochev
wouldn't be so shy
about rubbing it in our faces.
Believe me, he's alive.
Well, I hope you have
some way on how to find him,
because I am running out
of places to look and people to ask.
I know who to ask.
Thanks for agreeing to see us.
Mr. Diggle.
Thought I made it clear
after our last meeting.
As far as A.R.G.U.S. is concerned,
you're out of favors.
I'm not asking
for myself, Amanda.
I'm asking for everyone
in Starling City.
I need you
to find Oliver Queen.
♪ Arrow 2x21 ♪
City of Blood
Original Air Date on April 30, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Dig.
That computer's running
an XK-15 processor.
Felicity...
But that's not even
supposed to exist yet.
I want one.
Let me know
what you find.
I don't have time
to keep track
of your friends,
Mr. Diggle.
We deal with
more pressing issues here.
You don't understand.
Oliver's disappeared.
Maybe he needs
some time.
Or is it possible
that the two of you
simply haven't been looking in
the right place?
Did you try facial
recognition?
Yes, I ran it three times.
Amanda, please.
Slade Wilson has an army
of men just like him.
How many men have been exposed
to the Mirakuru?
Enough to lay waste
to this city.
We need to find Oliver
right now.
I'll see what I can do.
Have you
heard from Sara?
No.
Can you just call Mandy and see if
she can cover the bar?
Isabel Rochev.
I know who you are.
What can I do
for you, Ms. Rochev?
I'm sorry for
your loss, Thea.
Is that why you came here?
Offer me your condolences?
My condolences,
and to give you this.
It's a notice
to vacate the premises.
This club and the steel factory
in which its located
are all assets
of Queen Consolidated.
No, you--you can't do this.
It's already done.
How long do I have?
A couple days.
Councilman Tyson
is asking about dinner.
I already have
plans tonight.
Hi. Excuse me,
I didn't mean to barge in.
It's just that nobody
was at your front desk, so...
Laurel, of course,
please come in.
Give us a moment.
Twice in two days.
To what do I owe
the pleasure?
I wish I could say
that this was pleasure,
but it's about a case.
I've barely moved in and people
are already asking me for favors.
I guess I really
have arrived.
You certainly have.
So tell me,
how can I help you?
Murphy vs. Dunleavy.
The state's charged
a real estate developer
for turning away
low-income tenants
based on his so-called
"morality."
Have a seat.
Let me guess.
Our dear fair
housing commissioner
isn't willing to testify
as your expert witness.
Exactly.
And your predecessor
wasn't willing to lean on him.
Well, lucky for you,
I'm not my predecessor.
You know, this actually
reminds me of one I had
during my days
as a community organizer.
I was hoping that it would.
I've seen dozens
of cases like this at CNRI.
Well, it's a good thing we both
remember where we came from.
I'm happy to help.
Thank you.
Laurel...
I'm really glad you
got your job back at the DA's office.
I look forward to us
working together for a long time.
As do I.
Is it working?
We're about to remote access
the computer right now.
I'll tell you this,
if you ever
get tired of
practicing law,
you'd make a pretty
decent spy.
You guys have a warrant
for this, right?
Just...
Terrific.
Could you at least
tell me who's computer you bugged?
You're kidding.
I voted for him.
Yeah.
I need to know
if there's anything
incriminating in Blood's files.
What the hell, this is
a dead end job, anyway.
This all looks
pretty benign.
Lots of policy papers,
old documents transferred from
his campaign office.
Draft press releases...
Wait, wait, wait,
click back.
"For immediate release--
my thoughts and prayers
are with the Queen family
in the aftermath
of this unspeakable tragedy.
So he worked up a press release
after Moira was killed.
No, he didn't.
He wrote that
the day before
Moira died.
She's right.
Look at the timestamp.
Oh, my God.
Sebastian knew Slade
was going to kill her.
Is that the satellite
frequency communicator
TX50?
Can I touch it?
I know that sounds
a little weird and creepy,
but I've never seen
one in real life.
It's classified equipment,
Ms. Smoak.
You must feel
very powerful...
Knowing everything
about everyone.
Not powerful in an evil
dictator Stalin way.
More of a...
Knowledge is power, way.
Ma'am.
We have something.
I should have known.
What?
Oliver's at the lair
from which he conducts
his operations.
But we were
just there.
Not that lair.
His other one.
Like riding bicycle.
Underwater.
What's that sound?
We're stuck.
Like
Japanese were.
Submarines have
torpedoes, right?
Can we blast our way out?
I can see why you two
are made for each other.
You like
your explosions.
Chert voz'mi.
What?
These are Kaiten
torpedoes.
Manually operated.
Someone needs to
steer from inside.
Okay, but then, how do they
get away from the explosion?
They do not.
Oliver.
How did you find me?
Waller.
We were worried
about you.
After you missed
your mother's funeral.
I'm sorry that I didn't go.
I left for the cemetery.
But I ended up here.
Here is...
Here was a secondary facility
in case the foundry
was compromised.
But it became somewhere
that I could just go and...
Be alone.
She's dead
because of me.
Five years ago...
I could have cured Slade.
And that would have
prevented all of this.
And now,
all the people left
that I care about,
we are all
in his crosshairs.
It ends tonight.
How?
I turn myself over to Slade.
I end this vendetta.
Oliver,
you think this ends
with you turning
yourself over to Slade?
Yes, I do.
After she was gone...
He told that
one more person had to die.
And then it would end.
This ends for Slade
when he kills me.
I don't accept that.
You shouldn't,
either.
You can't just accept
things, Oliver.
If I had accepted
my life, I would be
a cocktail waitress in
Vegas like my mother,
and I never would
have gone to college,
and I never would have moved
a thousand miles away
to work at Queen Consolidated,
and I never would have
believed some
crazy guy in a hood
when he told me I could be
more than just some IT girl.
Please don't do this.
Felicity...
Someone once told me
that the essence of heroism
is to die so others can live.
It's not that
simple, Oliver.
Yes, it is.
Slade's whole plan
was to take everything from me.
He did.
He wins.
All that's left
is for me to die.
No, there has to be
another way.
There isn't.
Thea, please.
I understand you're upset.
This is an emotional time
for all of us.
I'm not being
emotional.
I'm...I'm an orphan!
I'm a jobless
and homeless orphan.
There's nothing
left for me here.
I'm here.
I thank you
for that, but...
Honestly, I need
to start over.
Oliver.
We missed you at the funeral.
And the reception.
I'm sorry that I
couldn't be there.
What's
going on here?
Thea's thinking
of leaving Starling City.
No, I am leaving.
Walter, could I speak to
my sister for a moment?
I'm sure you'll have
better luck.
Ollie, please.
Just don't even try
to convince me to stay.
I won't. I think
it's a good idea.
You should get
as far from Starling City
as you possibly can.
In our family,
out of you, me,
mom and dad,
you are the best of us.
You have
the purest heart.
And I can't ever
have you lose that.
Ok?
You promise me?
Ok.
I know that I haven't always
been the best brother,
or friend, or whatever
you've needed me to be.
But there has not
been a day since you were born
where I didn't cherish having
you as a sister.
I'll, um,
get in touch when
I get settled somewhere.
It's Oliver.
This ends now.
I'll be at the pier,
I'll be alone.
I'll do it.
Peter, you'll die.
I'm already dead.
Radiation poisoning.
Ivo's little gift.
He said he needed to find out
if Mirakuru could cure cancer.
Guess we'll
never find out.
Oh, I'm sorry, Peter,
I didn't know.
Ivo said the essence of heroism
is to die so that others can live.
I held on to that.
It's the only thing
that gave me hope.
So I'll go.
I mean, I may not
be saving millions of lives,
but I'll be
saving yours.
This is where
it all started.
Got on the "Queen's Gambit"
right over there.
I should have died
on that boat.
If I had, none of this
would have happened.
I never would have met you.
Shado and my mother
would still be alive.
No one else is going
to die because of me.
Aah!
Diggle, what the hell?
Slade Wilson.
He told me
who you were.
Did he hurt you?
No.
He was trying
to hurt you.
And when
you went missing,
I reached out...
to your partners.
They told me what you
were planning on doing.
It's what I have to do.
Will you give us
a moment?
You thought about
telling me...
The night
of the Undertaking.
I thought about telling you
almost every night.
Why didn't you?
Tommy knew.
Didn't he?
You were with him.
You were with him
at the end.
His last words
were about you.
He wanted to know
if you were safe.
Sorry I couldn't
save him.
And my mother.
But I can save you.
And Thea.
I can save the city
if this ends tonight.
No.
No!
You can't commit
suicide, Ollie.
You won't do that to me.
Or to Sara,
or to your friends.
Or to Thea.
Oliver...
She just lost
her mother.
Losing you
would destroy her.
But she'll be alive.
I don't know anything about hoods
and masks or human weapons
or any of this.
But I know you.
I know you like
I know my own name.
And I realize it may
sound crazy in light of your secret,
but I know who you are
in your bones, Oliver.
And that person--
that person
doesn't give up.
That person,
he always finds a way.
Not this time.
You're wrong.
You want to protect
the people who you love?
Then the only way
to do that is to stop Slade Wilson.
Laurel, I can't!
Yes, you can!
By stopping Sebastian Blood,
because Sebastian
is working
with Slade Wilson.
I have proof.
Slade Wilson
killed your mother
so that Sebastian
could become mayor.
You were right about him.
The man in the skull mask
works for Slade Wilson.
And this entire time,
it was Sebastian.
What's happening
is bigger
than you and Slade.
This city needs
the Arrow.
What's this for?
I don't want you
to be in here.
No, I'm going to stay with you--
Sara.
If this doesn't work,
I need you to be safe.
We will come for you
when it's over.
Ok.
Do you know how
the torpedo works?
I get in, he fires,
I steer, you pray.
Peter, what
you're doing is...
Practical.
My time's already up.
Brave.
You need to know that.
And I don't think that I could do
something like this.
You have. What you did for us--
coming back to that boat,
setting us free?
I came back to the boat
because I want to go home.
I wasn't thinking
about saving anybody.
It's...It's not
who I am.
Maybe not yet.
Go?
Is Sara clear?
Yes.
Hello. Good
to see you.
Clinton. You can
wait in the car.
Are you sure
that's a good idea?
Nothing's going
to happen to me here.
How are you doing,
Mr. Mayor?
Hi. Good to see you,
good to see you.
Congratulations, mayor Blood.
Thank you.
Mayor Blood, hello!
Hi.
We're all behind you,
Sebastian.
Nice to see you.
Sebastian,
may I join you for dinner?
Hey,
can you hold that?
Oh, thanks a lot,
man, appreciate it.
Clinton Hogue.
I have some
questions for you.
Go to hell.
You sure that's how
you want to play it?
You think I've never
took a beating before?
Pal, you're going
to wish I beat you.
Hi.
I'll be
your interrogator.
Is this a joke?
Clinton Hogue.
Social Security
number 306003894.
What the hell's
this supposed to be?
Oh, look at this.
You have a bank account
in the Cayman Islands.
Wow.
$2 million, quite
the little nest egg.
But...Looks like you just
approved a wire transfer of $1 million
to a charity here in Starling City.
Very generous.
What should I do with the rest?
Greenpeace.
Great cause!
And they really
appreciate the support.
You bitch!
Bitch with WiFi.
Hey, Clinton, looks like
your mom and dad have
a really nice
retirement portfolio, too,
but they, oh, no, are just
about to make some really
bad investments.
Ok, wait, just
wait--just--stop!
What do you want to know?
I missed you
at your mother's
memorial service.
I wanted to offer
my condolences.
You're the mayor.
Congratulations.
You've always wanted that.
Believe me, Oliver, I wish it
had happened a different way.
Your mother and I,
we--we didn't agree on much.
But we both wanted
what was best for Starling City.
I will help this city find its
heart again, I promise you that.
Do you really think that he...
Will let that happen?
Slade Wilson.
How do you know
I've been working with Slade Wilson?
Because I'm the Arrow.
Of course.
It all makes sense now.
It was right
in front of me.
You came to my office
and you shook my hand.
You said that together,
we can save this city.
You think that there will
be a city to be saved
after you unleash Slade's
Mirakuru army?
They'll only cause enough
damage to make the city ready.
Ready for your leadership?
For my vision
of what this city could be.
A better city.
And after the storm
they're about to suffer,
the people of Starling
will support
and follow me to that city.
Whatever Slade promised you,
he will not deliver.
He wants to hurt me.
You are a pawn
in a much larger game.
Slade promised me
city hall.
And he delivered.
He makes good
on his promises.
I understand he made
you a promise, too.
What are you going to do?
You going to stab
the mayor
in a restaurant
full of people?
It's a new day
in Starling City, Oliver.
And there's nothing
you can do to stop it.
Slade's men are
taking the city tonight.
They can try.
There's more men
than we thought,
all on Mirakuru.
It could be a massacre.
Not if we get to them first.
We stick to the plan,
no matter what.
Slade's using the sewer system.
You can drop in at Rock Avenue
and then head southeast.
The lines converge
at Water Street.
If Slade's army's underground,
that's probably where he'll be.
Good. Let's go.
Diggle, you ready?
Never not.
I'm coming, too.
No, you're not.
Felicity can
give me a radio.
I'll just be your
eyes and your ears.
I'll stay out of
your way, I promise.
Nothing will happen to me.
What if it did?
Slade's men, one on one, they
are nearly impossible to stop.
I need you to trust me.
And I need you to be safe.
But not them?
This started
with the three of us.
It's time
we got back to that.
Tonight we forge
a new history.
Tonight
we rise up as one
and take back
this city.
I have eyes on
Blood's army.
Got it. I'm forwarding
Dig your ping
along with the foundation schematics
of the Topside Avenue.
Follow the route
I laid out on the blueprints.
You'll see structural
joints in the concrete.
Blow them all
and Blood gets buried.
Got it.
The market
opened today at 400 points
thanks in part to the surprise rally
of Queen's Consolidated.
New leadership has--
...the company's future in spite
of this recent tragedy.
Um, excuse me,
why can't I board my train?
I'm sorry, ma'am, it's just
business class right now.
Coach will be boarding soon.
Ok.
Come on, pal.
Isn't that one
of the Iron Heights escapees?
Dumbass here tried to rob
a convenience store
but gave up as soon
as I pulled in.
Mind if I just stick him
here for a minute?
No, go ahead.
I'm just asking here.
Oliver, you've worked
really hard not to kill anymore.
Dropping an entire block
on these guys is murder.
Manslaughter, at least.
They're not men.
Not anymore.
Have Diggle blow the charges
the moment he's ready.
Oliver?
We will lead this city
out of the darkness,
and each one
of you will help me.
Come on.
Oliver, where
the hell are you?!
You killed me...
Let me return
the favor.
Hey.
You got the time?
It's, uh, 9:00.
Thanks.
Oliver, please.
Cisco, now is really
not a good time.
There.
Ollie!
There's too many
of them!
We can't fight.
We're not going to.
Turn the wheel!
What direction?
It does not matter.
Just turn the wheel.
I can't!
That is not an option.
I got it!
We're moving!
Good, good.
Sara, we did it.
Sara!
Oliver!
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man