NYSSA:
Oliver Queen is still alive.
Somehow Ta-er al-Sahfer's killer
still yet breathes.
RA'S AL GHUL:
Yes, I know.
He has returned to Starling City, apparently.
Why did you not tell me?
I had a right to know
that justice has not been done.
Because Oliver Queen
did not murder Ta-er al-Sahfer.
Do you not believe his own confession
because you doubt his motives?
Or because you don't approve of my grief?
-Sara was your beloved.
-And you've never approved.
I knew Sara would leave us, leave you...
...one way or the other.
I didn't approve of the love that I knew
would end only in heartbreak.
Whether Queen killed Sara or not...
...he challenged you, he defied you.
For that alone, he must die.
Coordinate your attacks.
If you don't fight in unison,
your numbers become my advantage.
You both have a long way to go.
Particularly you, Oliver.
You've spent years preparing
to bring a bow and arrow to a swordfight.
That's almost funny coming from you.
You're the reason the League is targeting us.
Thea has the club closed for renovations.
I've reinforced all the entrances
with A.R.G.U.S. tech. We're secure.
-John.
-My friends call me Dig.
You shouldn't even speak to me.
If the club is secure as Dig says,
perhaps you and Thea should relocate here.
We discussed that.
Thea wants to stay in the loft.
I have been able to survive
in Starling City...
...because the League has no idea
where in the city I am.
We are not leaving the loft.
You and your sister
have the same stubbornness.
Clearly it comes from
your mother's side of the family.
It's pretty amazing how much Malcolm
taught you in such a short time.
Yeah. He's father of the year.
Your fighting style, it...
It reminds me a bit of Sara.
That's probably because the same people
taught Malcolm and her to fight.
I need to take a shower.
What?
I was gonna ask for a favor,
but I'm really more concerned...
-...about you at the moment, Oliver.
-I'm fine.
You've been pushing it hard
with Malcolm lately.
-When's the last time you got a decent sleep?
-I will sleep when this is over.
We recovered the Omega
from Chien Naa Wei.
We stole the Alpha from the Hong Kong
military and gave it to Amanda Waller.
Look, no matter how many times you make
me say it, it's not gonna be any less true.
-That's enough. You're relieved.
SOLDIER: Yes, sir.
Sorry. Waller's a little too thorough
for her own good.
And by "thorough,"
I think you know I mean paranoid.
Well, I've gotten used to it by now.
Where is she, anyway?
Well, the mop-up of the Alpha-Omega
bioweapons problem...
...has become a United States Army
operation.
Ms. Waller's participation is concluded.
I'm sure that comes
as a profound disappointment.
Oh, like you wouldn't believe.
I apologize for the invasiveness
of your debrief.
And now that it's over, you're free to go.
The Yamashiros have been released too.
They're returning to Japan.
You go with them, and from there
you can return to Starling...
...or go wherever else on earth you wish.
Thank you, General Shrieve.
After what you did, son...
...that's the least I can do.
This is hardcore.
When Dig said he was fortifying the club...
...I figured there'd just be
a few extra locks and cameras. Heh.
-Are you okay?
-No, no.
-Not really.
-What's wrong?
Ollie told me that I can't tell anyone.
Whatever it is, you have to be able
to talk about it with someone.
Someone who's not your brother.
I killed Sara.
-It was Malcolm, he...
-I know.
And none of you told me?
You know last year when I kind of
went off the rails for a bit?
-Yeah.
-I was also under the influence of something.
And just like you, I killed someone.
A cop.
-Roy...
-They didn't tell me either.
-And when I found out...
-You wished that you didn't know.
I'm not gonna lie and tell you
that the feeling ever goes away...
...but I can tell you that it gets easier, Thea.
You don't have to see that cop's family
almost every single day.
I can't imagine
that it's gonna get any easier.
And I don't think that it should.
[BELLS CHIME]
So he is alive. There were doubts.
Any idea what happens to the stock of Palmer
Technologies when Palmer goes missing...
...for a week?
Whoa.
It's been a week?
I've been a little distracted.
Can't get the modulator
to interface with the system.
-I've been working the problem but...
-Stop.
I imagined you'd say that. This is the step
toward the suit becoming operational.
-A little facial hair is a small price to pay...
-Stop.
This is a subsonic ionizer. If you try to use
it on quad-band circuitry, it could result...
In a catalytic reaction that could destroy
the entire building. Oops.
You need to get some sleep.
-I will once I've cracked the problem.
-Or blow yourself up.
-Whichever comes first.
-Ray.
When those men killed Anna...
...I promised myself I would never
feel that helpless again.
So can you imagine how I felt when Brick's
men took a portion of the city hostage?
Lousy. We all did.
-But if you're punishing yourself...
-I'm not punishing myself.
I'm focused on the task at hand.
Too focused, clearly.
I'm sorry, but I've got a lot of work to do.
Hey, Dad, it's me again.
Listen, I know you're upset,
and you have every right to be...
...but it's been over a week,
and now that you know the truth...
...neither of us should go through
this alone, so please call me back.
I love you.
Hey. What are you doing here?
I need to talk to you.
-Is everything all right?
-No.
It's about Sara.
Okay.
Malcolm drugged me.
He gave me something...
...that made me susceptible
to suggestion, and I...
Thea...
...what are you talking about?
I killed Sara.
I didn't know what I was doing, okay?
It wasn't me.
I'm so sorry, Laurel.
If Merlyn drugged you...
...then it wasn't your fault.
But how could you work with him?
How could you stand by his side?
Because of the threat of the League.
We have to work with him.
I don't have a choice.
Yes, you do.
What happened wasn't your fault, Thea,
because it wasn't your decision.
If you want to make this right,
what you do from now on...
...that is.
I can't remember Sara's smile.
It's weird, isn't it?
I mean, I know Sara used
to smile and laugh, but...
But when I close my eyes
and I try and picture it...
...all I see is the way that I found her.
Sometimes the only thing
that keeps me going...
...is the thought
of one day finding her killer.
We will.
I promise.
How do you do that?
-Do what?
-Lie.
Right to my face.
Thea told me, Oliver.
She told me everything.
How could you keep this from me?
After what you wanted to do
to Lacroix and Merlyn...
...do you really need to ask me
that question?
I am not so consumed with vengeance
that I blame Thea for Sara's death.
-I blame Malcolm Merlyn.
-I need him.
He murdered my sister.
With the League targeting us,
he is the only chance I have of saving mine.
This is how it has to be.
It's really amazing.
The way Merlyn always finds a way
under your protection.
I'm sorry, Laurel.
You know, it's hard to remember a time...
...when I was actually in love with you.
I told you not to tell anyone.
I guess I'm just not as good
at keeping secrets as you are.
Thea, I'm not gonna pretend that I understand
all the different types of pain that you're in.
But the threat, it is very real.
And the only way that we are gonna survive
is by acting in unison.
Are you really quoting Malcolm Merlyn
to me right now?
Yes, because he, better than anyone...
...understands the danger
the three of us are facing.
We're not in any danger.
Not anymore.
Not you or me.
But Malcolm?
He's going to face justice.
Thea, what have you done?
You're clearly not League of Assassins.
They wouldn't be this sloppy.
[BOTH YELLING]
That's right, I forgot. Oliver mentioned
you were having some identity issues.
Though he didn't mention
about your delusions of grandeur.
You killed my sister,
you stupid son of a bitch!
Now you're just embarrassing yourself.
Your sister's teacher was my teacher.
Did you think you could really dispatch me
with a stick?
No.
I suppose we're gonna see
if being a killer runs in the family.
[GRUNTS]
-Step aside, Laurel.
-Nyssa.
This does not concern you.
We've come for Al Sa-her.
You swore to me you didn't kill Sara.
I never believed you.
[GRUNTING]
It is admirable of you to honor your sister,
but you can rest now.
Sara's murder is avenged.
Where is she? Hey!
I told you Merlyn was off-limits.
I know. Then I realized
that I didn't really give a damn.
This is why I keep secrets from you.
Because you let your emotions dictate
your actions, and it is gonna get you killed.
You really think that you had a chance
against Malcolm Merlyn?
-Nyssa and the League kidnapped Merlyn.
-I know.
Thea traded Merlyn for safety.
She was able to contact the League
because they're in town on the hunt.
Merlyn has a video of Thea killing Sara.
First thing he's gonna do is show that to Ra's.
-Then we're right back at square one.
-That was a bluff to make me challenge Ra's.
Merlyn loves Thea.
He would never just serve her up.
We have to get him back.
-What?
-Yeah, I'm with her.
It just sounded like you wanted to rescue
Malcolm Merlyn from the League.
My sister did this because she is angry.
Eventually she will settle down and realize...
...that she basically
just killed her own father.
There's no coming back from that.
The guilt will just eat away at her
until there is nothing left.
Please.
I'll start with the private airfields.
No. Oliver, Merlyn murdered my sister
and corrupted yours...
...and now you wanna save him?
I'm trying to save Thea's soul.
-You're out of your mind.
-You don't need to be here.
I got something.
Unless it's a big fat coincidence...
...that the security cameras
at Starling City Aviation just went dark.
I'll handle it.
I'm going home.
We hope you'll consider
staying with us in Tokyo for a day...
-...before you leave for Starling City.
-Don't pressure him, Tatsu.
He's been away from home a long time.
You can stay with us forever.
I like playing games with Oliver.
Maybe I can send my family's plane...
...and then you and your parents
can vacation in America.
Your family owns a plane?
It's more of a jet.
I see it, I see it. I see our boat.
I hate boats.
-Oliver.
-What is it?
Hell will be a paradise compared to what
my father has in store for you, Al Sa-her.
MALCOLM:
Only because of my undertaking.
Your father doesn't care about Sara's death,
just as you know in your heart...
...that your relationship with Sara has cost
you any chance of taking your father's place.
Get him aboard.
I'll deal with this one.
[ALL GRUNTING]
Your sister told us Merlyn killed Sara.
Are you so lost you'd deprive me
of my justice?
This isn't justice, it's vengeance.
Vengeance is justice.
[ARROW WHISTLES]
Go!
He's gone.
Malcolm Merlyn will never be seen again.
So, what's the play? Trade her for Malcolm?
Ra's will not make that deal,
even for his own daughter.
What are you doing with her?
She's a source of information and leverage.
I need the room.
You're gonna torture her to find out
where Nanda Parbat is?
I need the room.
Everyone clear out.
Oliver, listen, I know what you're doing,
and I know why you're doing it.
But you can't save Thea's soul
at the cost of your own.
Laurel was right.
I need to know where Nanda Parbat is.
Was she also correct you intend
to torture me for that information?
No. Because we know I won't have to.
You placed Sara's killer
under your protection.
Your every action has been aimed
towards the frustration of justice.
I will gladly tell you
where to find my home...
...because you will die there.
-It's likeMission: Impossiblein here.
-Yeah, that's the idea.
Make it impossible for the League
to get the drop on us.
I thought Thea got us off their hit list.
Yeah, that was before we put
Ra's al Ghul's daughter in a box.
Taking prisoners?
Isn't that crossing a line?
Actually, Oliver has an entire prison
on Lian Yu.
Maybe I shouldn't have told you that.
Nanda Parbat is hidden
beneath the Hindu Kush.
-That was quick.
-She wanted to tell me.
-She thinks I'm gonna die there.
-She's not the only one.
-I understood facing Ra's for Thea, but...
-I am doing it for Thea.
Look, I may not agree with it,
but I understand what you're trying to say.
You don't want Thea to live with the guilt
of getting her father killed.
But how is her brother dying any better?
I don't plan on dying.
That's what you said the last time
you went to go face Ra's.
And how did that turn out for you?
Oliver, I'm about as angry with you right
now than I've been with anyone in my life...
...but that doesn't mean
I want you going on a suicide mission.
You're unusually quiet.
Yeah.
Guys wanna give us a minute?
So Thea served up Merlyn, you wanna
save her from regretting that decision.
Yeah, I get it.
-But?
-But Oliver, there's something more at play.
It's Thea.
-Plain and simple.
-Are you sure?
Right now it's the only thing
I am sure about.
What the hell?
Did you get locked out
of the Palmer Technologies server?
That's a shame.
You did this?
I just came from a friend of mine who has
his head shoved so far up his colon that...
And I'm pretty sure this is true.
...he's literally going to get himself killed.
Him, I can't do anything about.
-You're a different story.
-Great.
Tell me the story while you
unlock the ATOM subroutine directory.
You have two options, Ray.
Option one: You can find a way to break
the encryption I used to lock up your server...
...which by my calculations
will take you roughly 6.25 hours.
Or you can use that time
to eat a proper meal, take a shower...
...and get no less than five hours of sleep...
...at the completion of which
I will give you the password.
I see.
It's your choice,
but I highly recommend option two...
...because this whole situation
has gone from endearingly eccentric...
...to creepily not okay.
If I had the energy
I think I'd be getting angry right now...
...but instead I'll just take option two.
That's a wise choice.
After your dinner and a shower,
I am taking you straight to bed.
Putting you.
Why do I do that?
DIGGLE:
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh. Shh, shh.
I didn't hear you come in.
Why can something so small
change the way you view the entire world?
What did Oliver say?
Did you ask him?
-Oliver has other things on his mind.
-Like what?
He's going to Nanda Parbat.
Cheating death once
wasn't enough for him?
Well, he's convinced
he's doing the right thing.
Is he?
You going with him?
Oliver has to do what's right by his family.
I have to do what's right by mine.
That why you didn't go the last time?
Last time Oliver wouldn't let me.
When you thought he died
you blamed yourself.
I don't wanna see you
put yourself through that.
-I can't stop Oliver from going.
-Then go with him.
You might have hung up the uniform,
Johnny, but you're still a soldier.
Standing down while your friend
goes into battle just isn't in your DNA.
Just get there and back in one piece.
About that...
You think I could borrow the A.R.G.U.S. jet?
What the hell
do you think that you're doing?
Roy told you?
Roy and Laurel.
They both think
that you are out of your mind.
-Me? I know it for sure.
-I'm doing this for you.
If your father dies
because of something you've done...
...a piece of you will go missing
and you'll never be able to get it back.
That I can live with.
But not you dying because of me.
I'm not gonna die.
And the only reason you think
you can live with Malcolm's death...
...is because you don't really know
what it's like to take a life.
You're a good person, Thea.
Both of our parents are dead because of me.
And that guilt,
that's something that I have to live with.
I don't want that for you.
No, please.
Please just don't go.
I'll be back as soon as I can.
I got a Gulfstream at Starling City Aviation.
-I can't ask you to come with me.
-You didn't ask me.
Besides, you don't own a jet anymore.
In 1854, I encountered
an illusionist in Vienna...
...and he was dazzling,
magnificent, powerful.
And then, nearly half a century later,
I stumbled upon this man again.
He was withered...
...broken...
...dying.
You see, a magician can cheat many things,
except one.
Please. I was your horseman.
Let me hunt for you once more.
Allow me to prove to you my reborn loyalty.
Al Sa-her, face your death with honor.
Or at least dignity.
Please don't do this.
There is a price you must pay
for your crimes...
...that can only be measured
in agony and blood.
But know I will take no pleasure in this.
Take him away.
No.
No. No. No!
Shut. Up.
Is this an actual Van Go...? Oh!
It's a Vermeer, actually.
I rotate the paintings I have here
with my collection at Starling Museum.
Yeah, I'm really into the Dutch masters
this month.
You're very attractive.
I mean, they are.
-You were right.
-Mm?
Food was delicious, the shower was amazing.
Thank you for insisting on it.
Well, a deal's a deal.
Password's inside.
You know, you didn't have to blackmail me.
I trust your judgment.
In fact, I pretty much depend on it.
Well, that would make you the only one.
I can be as obsessive
and stubborn as the next billionaire.
I know the value
of somebody calling me on it.
Telling me when the emperor
has no clothes.
Speaking of...
[LAUGHS]
Right. Uh...
You know what?
Sometimes I forget that we work together.
When I'm with you, it's just you.
I don't think about work or the mission or...
I'm sorry.
I'm not.
There it is. Nanda Parbat.
Centuries old.
Never taken by force.
Then why are we doing this, Oliver?
I mean, why are we really doing this?
The League will have sentries
patrolling the area.
If they spot us,
we cannot let them get away.
Surprise is our only advantage.
I'd say they spotted us.
What's your count?
Six on the south side, four on the east.
I don't wanna go out
like Butch and Sundance.
-So, what's the plan?
-Shoot straighter than they do.
Cover me.
Go, go, go!
-If he gets to the fortress, we're dead.
-He won't.
[IN JAPANESE]
One sniper on the roof.
They're A.R.G.U.S. They work for Waller.
Waller? General Shrieve
said she wasn't involved anymore.
Maybe that decision didn't sit well with her.
We can't stay here.
Delivery truck.
-Sniper will take us out before we get there.
-Pass me your gun. I'll cover you.
Thank me later. Give me your gun.
[IN JAPANESE]
Go!
I am the prisoner,
yet you look the more tortured.
By now Sa-her
is in the presence of my father.
His last hours will be spent in agony.
Begging for death.
-That doesn't please you?
-I thought it would.
Having Merlyn to hate...
...it's like a piece of Sara
that I can still hold onto.
But once he's gone...
...so is another part of her.
She would want to be avenged.
Can you remember the sound
of Sara's laugh?
When Sara was first brought
before my father...
...the moment he weighed
her apprenticeship or her execution...
...she bore witness
to a demonstration of his power...
...one that inspired terror
in all who had come before.
But Sara laughed.
It was so innocent...
...so genuine.
That was the moment
I fell in love with her, I think.
All I knew, all I craved
was to hear her laugh once more.
Thank you.
[IN ARABIC]
Agh!
[ALL GRUNTING]
This place is humongous.
How do we find Merlyn in all of this?
The nanites that I tagged him with
four months ago, this can track them.
Down!
Thanks.
[GRUNTS]
Oh, my God.
OLIVER:
Malcolm.
Help me get him down.
Trap.
RA'S AL GHUL:
Mr. Queen.
Welcome to Nanda Parbat.
DIGGLE:
Oliver.
-I tried that. Nothing's happening.
-We need to get out of here now.
Save your strength. We're gonna need it.
-I'm not gonna let you die.
-I don't think that's up to you.
-I shouldn't have let you come.
-Not up to you.
You don't understand.
No, I think I do.
You forget I know you.
Sometimes better than you know yourself.
You could have told me
I wasn't doing this for Thea before we left.
You are doing it for Thea.
But, yeah, you're right.
It's not just about her.
You know, every time I close my eyes...
...all that I can see...
...all that I can hear, feel is...
Is the fall.
I couldn't live like that.
I couldn't live knowing that...
...there was someone out there
who beat me.
Yeah, that makes sense.
No, it's egotistical and insane.
So is putting on a mask
and jumping off rooftops, Oliver.
To do that
you have to be in a certain mindset.
Every soldier has to believe
he's coming home...
...otherwise he's paralyzed.
Ra's got in your head.
What was that favor
you wanted to ask me?
-I don't think now is the right time.
-We're not dead yet.
Now might be the only time.
I always assumed if I ever got married again
that Andy would be by my side.
When I lost my brother...
...I never thought I'd get another one.
So pretending for a moment...
...that we aren't two dead men
chained to the floor...
...how do you feel
about being my best man?
I'd feel pretty good about it.
[DOOR OPENING]
Oliver.
It's time.
-I count at least three shooters.
-Let's move.
Stay down!
Agh!
-Tatsu, come on!
-Dad!
No!
No! Stop, stop!
Go! Get him out of here!
[SCREAMING]
I'm really starting to wonder
why I decided to come with you.
I told you.
I want to show you how I deal
with the things that you're going through.
That's Michelle Vincent.
And her son, Rory. He's 4.
Roy, why are you stalking
some random family?
They're not random.
That's them.
That's the police officer's family.
I give them cash.
Bring them groceries.
I even got Rory a Boba Fett for Christmas.
-Don't worry, they don't know it's me.
-You're torturing yourself.
No, it helps, actually.
It helps me with the guilt.
Look, I appreciate...
...what you're doing here.
Showing me this.
But the cop...
...and Sara...
...they're just not the same thing.
You weren't any more in control
of yourself than I was.
No, not when I...
...killed Sara.
But when I traded Malcolm to the League...
...when I let him into my life...
...I knew exactly who he was.
What he was.
He taught me how to kill.
Maybe I am a killer.
Maybe that's the real me.
Maybe I deserve to be punished.
I don't believe that.
I just tried to have my father murdered.
Can you please just take me home?
I'm in no mood for conversation.
You'll want to hear this.
There's something that I need to tell you.
I can't live without you knowing.
The guilt is far worse
than anything you could do to me.
I lied to you.
And you believed it.
When I told you that Malcolm killed Sara.
He wanted her dead.
He put certain things in motion...
...but I am the one...
...who fired those arrows into her chest.
And when I made the deal...
...to give up Malcolm...
...I promised you your vengeance.
So take it.
You tasted death.
And you wanted more.
But the truth is...
...everyone...
...and everything must come to an end.
Even for one such as me.
Kill me.
But spare John Diggle's life.
Let him go.
I will beg for it.
You have shown tremendous strength...
...fortitude...
...power.
No, Mr. Queen, I don't want to kill you.
I want you to take my place.
I want you to become the next Ra's al Ghul.