My name is Oliver Queen.
After 6 months in hell, I
have been released from prison
and returned home with only one goal...
To save my city, but
things have changed.
Instead of operating outside the law,
I am now working alongside the police.
I am no longer inmate 4587.
I am once more the Green Arrow.
Previously on "Flash"...
Dr. John Deegan,
use this book to reshape the world
as you see fit.
I can see everything.
Barry, are you okay?
I'm Barry.
I'm Oliver Queen.
Maybe it's just Earth
1 that's been affected.
If we can get to Earth 38 and find Kara,
if she remembers us, then maybe she
can help fix whatever's happening.
Whoa, Lois. Wait, wait.
This is Barry and
Oliver. They're friends.
So you know that I'm
Oliver and he's Barry?
- Why wouldn't I?
- We could use your help.
I vibed somebody in the speed lab,
some guy with ridges on his head.
I know where to find him.
So what's our next move?
We're going to Gotham City.
Ohh!
Okay. I know this sounds nuts
and completely unscientific,
but I think that freaking
lightning is following us.
- Focus, Curtis.
- This is me focusing.
These atmospheric anomalies
are playing all kinds
of hell on my equipment,
plus you don't want
that lightning to hit
when you're engaging Deathstroke's son.
I just had to say it.
Kane Wolfman, you're under arrest
for 19 violations of international law!
Really? Does that
include the murder of...
4 A.R.G.U.S. field agents?
Last chance! On the ground now!
This isn't personal. Just business.
Son of a bitch.
Is that any way to greet your friends?
All I know is that whenever
the three of you show up,
it usually means we
have one huge problem.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
So you're you.
And you're you.
An immortal Egyptian,
aliens, parallel earth Nazis.
I have no idea why I'm even
surprised at this point.
I'm still trying to
figure out if this is
more like "Freaky
Friday" or "Quantum Leap."
No. If this were like "Quantum Leap,"
I'd only look like myself in the mirror.
Yep. You are definitely
not Oliver Queen.
We think that the red skies
and these lightning
strikes have to be related
to whatever happened to
Barry and Oliver somehow.
We need you to solve the
somehow while we're in Gotham.
No problem. I mean, A.R.G.U.S. has
all the best analytic toys,
but what we really need is a
pattern recognition algorithm,
and, unfortunately, Felicity isn't...
- I called Felicity.
- Wait, wait.
- You called Felicity?
- Yeah.
Okay. Right. Well, I
guess that makes sense
because technically,
you are her husband.
I'm confused.
I've been summoned?
- Yes. Thank you for coming.
- Of course.
I mean, things might be
fraught between us, Oliver.
That doesn't mean I'm not gonna show up.
They are? They are?
They are. Yeah, which is... Sad.
So, um, this lightning thing.
Um, could you help me out with that?
Can I kind of show you
kind of what I'm thinking?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Okay. So why didn't you tell Felicity?
Well, because we tried to tell
everybody at S.T.A.R. Labs,
and it didn't really go over so well.
Felicity and I have
enough problems as it is
without introducing body swapping.
We thought we'd just let
her think everything's
normal and that Barry and I are solving
another problem.
If you find out how this lightning thing
relates to whatever it is
that we're dealing with here,
can you please tell us?
Copy that.
Hey. This thing isn't
gonna be permanent, is it?
- I hope not.
Jinx.
Oh. Barry, there's something
I'd like to discuss before we go.
- What's that?
- That you probably shouldn't go.
What?
Oliver Queen is a public figure
and an infamous vigilante.
If you are in Gotham
City, you're attracting
the type of attention
that we don't want.
No. If... if Gotham
can handle the Batman,
it can handle the Green Arrow.
The Batman's an urban legend.
Wait. You don't believe Batman's real?
He's not real. He's an urban legend
concocted by the
Gotham police department
to scare criminals.
And I'm the original vigilante, Barry.
Okay, if you guys are
done fooling around...
Actually, you know what?
Could you pull that thing up?
Because, unlike you, my
identity's not public,
and I'd like to keep it that way.
This isn't your real face!
It might end up being my real face
if we don't sort this
mess out, so could you?
- Happy?
- Ecstatic.
Apparently, you guys
aren't done fooling around.
Well, I guess I'm running alone.
Ho ho ho! That is so awesome.
So this is Gotham.
Doesn't look so tough to me.
Where's Oliver?
Huh. I don't know.
Guess he's still getting the hang of it.
Yeah.
Ha ha ha!
I'm still getting the hang of it.
All right. All right.
So how do we find two people
in a city of 1.6 million?
There is a radio personality
named Vesper Fairchild.
She knows everyone in
Gotham, and I know her.
She was doing an exposé
on white-collar crime
back in the day, and I
wanted to persuade her
that Queen Consolidated was above board.
So you slept with her, right?
No. I... I don't know.
Gosh. You really got around
back in the day, didn't you?
Oh. One time, Oliver
cheated on his girlfriend
with her sister.
- Barry!
- Oh, no! Ohh!
What? You did!
So, what, depending on this past
relationship with this woman,
we might have to come
up with a plan "B."
Is that what you're saying?
- Yeah.
- Guys!
Take a look at this.
You still think he's a myth?
Yeah! Let's go.
Batman's real.
If I remember right,
the radio station was this way.
I'm surprised they put it
in the bad part of town.
It's cute how you think
there's a good part of town.
Looks like the one percenters
bring the good part with them.
This is why nobody
talks about Gotham, okay?
City might as well be dead.
Sounds like you guys
aren't from around here.
Probably don't know,
but Gotham tourism bureau collects a tax
on out of towners,
so phones, wallets, watches now.
You know what, fellas? I...
we don't want any trouble,
so maybe we can just
talk this out, okay?
Ha ha ha! Talk it out.
Okay. I'll talk first.
Hey!
Agh!
Oh, great.
On the ground now!
All of you, on the
ground! Show me your hands!
Oh, crap.
I need SWAT at Nolan and Burton.
Green Arrow sighted at Nolan and Burton.
Sir, we don't want any trouble.
Yeah. Tell that to Oliver Queen here.
Oliver, stand down.
Pattern recognition algo
is locked and loaded.
Bringing it online now.
You realize that this
may not work, right?
Like, there may not be
a pattern to recognize.
Is there a suggestion bound
within that dose of pessimism?
Does the energy
discharge of the lightning
look familiar to you?
The quantum amplitude is consistent
with a dimensional breach.
Exactly. We're gonna need
Cisco's help on this one.
I've been summoned!
Okay. That was a disturbingly
coincidental entrance.
It wasn't coincidental.
We'd been getting the same red skies
and freaky lightning in Central City,
and I'll tell you this
much... It wasn't speed force.
Wait, wait. Hold up.
"We'd been," "wasn't,"
as in past tense?
Interestingly, the
atmospheric phenomenon ceased
the moment Barry and
Oliver left Central City.
It's like it packed up its
bags and followed them here.
That's why we came.
The phenomenon has to be
related to Barry and Oliver's...
- Okay, Caitlin. Okay?
- Body swap?
Ahem. Don't... Don't say... ahem.
I'm sorry. Body... body what?
You, uh... you didn't tell her?
Again, tell me... heh... what?
Um, excuse me, Officer.
Were you able to get in
touch with Laurel Lance
at the Star City D.A.'s office or...
Yeah. She said, uh, "I
think a night in jail
would do them some good."
Heh.
What were you thinking?
That you were about
to get yourself shot.
- You're welcome.
- I was deescalating
the situation, you know, like, uh...
- Like I would?
- Uh-huh!
Guess what, man.
I handled it exactly how you would!
Okay. You guys, maybe taking
on each other's personalities
worked for AMAZO, but you were not gonna
talk your way out of getting mugged,
and you escalated the
situation way too fast.
So what would you have done?
What I would have done is
supersped us right out of there.
All they would have
seen is a gust of wind.
I mean, hindsight is 20/20,
but we'll follow your lead next time.
Because there will really be a next time
when someone threatens
3 superheroes with a gun.
Good news.
Somebody posted your bail.
- Who?
- I don't know.
Guess someone wanted to
make you guys their headache
instead of mine.
We'll show ourselves out.
Please come with me.
I'm guessing this belongs
to whoever bailed us out.
I really think we've had
enough distractions for one night.
Yeah. I agree with my friend.
We appreciate the
early release, whatever,
but we're really fine on our own.
I'm afraid my employer insists.
Okay.
And you said it wouldn't happen again.
Bruce Wayne got us out of jail?
Doesn't sound like him.
No, it wasn't. Wayne
left Gotham 3 years ago.
Why? To go where?
No one knows.
So who's manning the shop now?
Apparently after he left,
Bruce's board of directors
went to town with a bunch of
aggressive get-rich-quick deals.
Yeah, but an abandoned building
didn't bail us out, right?
Whoa. That is definitely
not Bruce Wayne.
Oliver Queen.
Ahem.
Yeah, yeah. I'm Oliver Queen. Yeah.
- And you are?
- The rain on your parade.
If you're visiting Gotham
to compare grappling hooks
with Batman, you are out of luck.
No one's seen him in years.
Told you.
Myth.
I would never compare
myself to a total badass
like Batman.
What I think Oliver is trying to say
is thank you for getting us out of jail.
What Oliver's actually trying to say is
who are you, and why are you helping us?
Gotham has enough problems without a guy
in green leather showing
off his arrows to everyone,
so the faster you find
what you're looking for,
the faster you can get
the hell out of my city.
Uh, but, what... what
should we call you...
Rain, Ms. Parade?
Kane, Kate Kane.
You didn't tell her?!
Oliver... the actual
Oliver thought they had
enough problems with Felicity already.
Oh, and you didn't think to
loop us in on the fact that you
were keeping the "Freaky
Friday" situation on the hush?
I was thinking it was
more like "Quantum Leap."
No. If this were like "Quantum Leap,"
they'd only look like themselves when
they see themselves in the mirror...
It depends on what
type of quantum leap...
Shouldn't we concentrate on
what this lightning came from?
- Right?
- Right, but...
Oh. Ahem.
Ok, guys. You don't need
to tip-toe around me.
It's just a lot to process.
It's not every day that
you find out that your ex
is your husband and vice-versa.
Yeah. Iris was, pretty freaked
out, too, when she sussed it out.
Wait. Iris.
You know, actually, John...
right before you came in,
John was just saying that we need
to really handle that lightning...
Iris was able to tell that
something was off with Barry?
- No, not exactly.
- Oh, totally. I mean,
it was like lover's intuition.
That's how you can
tell these two were...
You know, Felicity, um, there's
something very strange going on here,
so I wouldn't take this as a commentary
on you and Oliver's marriage.
No. My marriage with Oliver is strained
by the fact that we've
become different people...
Quite literally in Oliver's case.
If the lightning strikes are
attempted dimensional breaches,
there might be a way to
stabilize the quantum flux
to allow whatever's trying to
get through to get through, right?
- Yeah. Of course.
- Yeah.
You guys try facial recognition?
One of Bruce's R&D guys
still works in the building.
I can give this to him.
Uh, we did try it,
so thank you, but no luck.
Besides, I'd think if Wayne's R&D's
in the same shape as this building,
it's not gonna really do us any good.
Suit yourself.
Seems strange, doesn't it,
that Bruce Wayne and Batman disappeared
from Gotham around the same time.
Well, when Batman left, the city went
to 5 different kinds of hell,
which for Gotham is
really saying something.
Took a toll on Bruce.
Is that why he left?
Still trying to figure that out.
Right, but you work for him,
and you don't know why he left?
Who said I work for him?
How'd it go with Vesper?
She hung up on me.
Apparently, I did sleep with her.
- Hmm.
- Okay. The building is
under renovation, so this is
the best place for you
guys to work out of.
Oh, and the, uh, Wi-Fi
password's "Alfred."
So if Vesper's not gonna help us,
we're just back at square one.
No, we're not. I lifted this off
of a computer at the precinct.
It should have the entire GCPD database.
You stole data from the police?
No. No. The Flash did it.
- It's not funny.
- I'm not laughing.
Did you lose the coin flip
on who has to come talk to me?
We didn't flip coins. We drew straws.
I'm kidding. Actually, I
wanted to come talk to you
because I think I've got a
little bit more experience
with alternate realities than you do.
So what words of wisdom
do you have for me?
That Iris probably has a little
bit more experience, as well,
and maybe that's why she would have seen
something that you didn't.
As for Oliver keeping you in the dark,
when he and Barry tried to tell
us what was going on with them,
we knocked them unconscious
and locked them in the pipeline.
- Seriously?
- Wasn't our finest moment.
Look. I'm sure that that's the reason
that Oliver didn't want to
take any chances with you.
I appreciate you saying that...
But it's just another excuse
in a long list of excuses
for Oliver's behavior.
Oliver does love you, Felicity.
Yeah? Well, what's love
without respect or trust?
I don't know,
but as long as there is love,
you can't give up on it.
That's the one thing I do know
after everything I've been through,
everything I've suffered.
Thank you.
Well, one good thing
about what's going on
is that I have something to distract me.
Look at this.
- That looks like...
- A quantum flux anchor.
I'm pretty sure if we build it,
whoever's trying to
breach through will come.
Let's get to work.
You really know your
way with a computer.
Well, when I was first starting
out, I had to hold my own
before Felicity showed up.
Got him. John Deegan.
Oh. Illegal experimentation, torture.
Hmm. Seems like he was
conducting experiments
on his own patients' brains.
Sounds like a real charmer.
Well, he was acquitted. All the charges
were dropped on technicalities.
So where can we find him now?
- No known address.
- What about employment?
Well, he was fired, suspended
by the medical board for two years,
but that was... 5 years ago.
- So no idea where to find him.
- No.
Except somewhere in Gotham.
Needle in haystack.
- All right.
- Where you going?
I'm gonna put on my work clothes
and do an X-ray flyby of the city.
I don't think miss Kate
would be too thrilled
with us running around her city.
Well, unless she has some
kryptonite stashed somewhere,
I'm really not worried.
Heh. You lost?
No. No. Um, just needed
to clear my head for a sec.
Actually, you know what?
I'm sorry
about the third degree earlier.
I guess the name Bruce Wayne carries
a certain notoriety.
Oh, I know. Bruce Wayne's my cousin.
Your cousin?
That makes a lot of sense.
Actually, I'm in the process
of turning this building into
a real estate development firm,
so this is me hijacking his office.
My cousin's actually friends with Bruce.
Um, well, frenemies.
- Hmm.
- Heh.
Do you ever wonder if trying to keep
his private life from the public eye
just got to be too much
for him and he broke?
Heh. Sitting at that desk,
staring out that window,
watching this city that we grew up in
rot at its core,
you find a way to not break.
Bruce didn't leave
Gotham without a fight.
Hmm.
You know, I got to say, all the
corporate billionaires I know
wear Versace and have 500 fewer tattoos.
Hmm. Those are the
ones that you can see.
Well, that's a mystery.
Oh. Is this the... The
old bard himself? Ha!
Hey. You... you wouldn't happen
to know a John Deegan, would you?
I would, actually.
He's a doctor at Arkham Asylum.
Ah. I have to go tell the boys.
Uh, hey. Thanks for
the help and the chat.
What the hell is this?
No offense, but you'd need like
5 Ph.D.s for the dumbed-down version.
How about the very dumbed-down version?
It's a quantum flux anchor
that utilizes wave theory
to fire nano-particulates
across an Einstein-Rosen bridge
to create a secure claxon field.
How about the very,
very, dumbed-down version?
Felicity made a magnet
that will draw whoever's
trying to breach through to us.
You could have just said that.
All right. Field's stable.
All readings are in the
green. You guys are good to go.
I'm reading multiple quantum surges.
I don't think this is working!
This is what working looks like!
Ca... you... Hear me?
You've got... to... get... the book.
Jay?
Only... book... make this right.
If you get the book, you can fix this.
Am I the only one who
thought that was very cool?
So we're sure he works here?
Well, it's probably too late
for him to still be at work,
but if we find his office, maybe
we can find his home
address or something.
Do you think you have enough
of a grip on your powers
to do a superspeed reconnaissance?
I don't think that we
should risk it if I don't.
Okay. Well, then, we break in,
do some old-fashioned snooping.
- Ohh!
- Aah!
Aah!
- Got new intel.
- Those lightning strikes,
they were a Flash from another dimension
trying to breach to us.
We think it was Jay Garrick
or a Jay Garrick.
He said to fix the situation,
we have to "get the book."
John Deegan was reading a book
in the drawing Oliver drew.
Okay. So we find the book in there
or we find Deegan, and we
make him tell us where it is.
Wait, wait. Hold on. Another
Flash from a parallel universe
just lightnings in, tells us
to jump, and we ask, "how high?"
If we want to sort this
thing out, then yes.
I have no idea how we're gonna
break into a mental asylum.
I have some ideas.
Uh, how can I help you?
New patient transfer from
Gotham Central Hospital.
Dr. Danvers said Arkham was
the more appropriate place
to treat her... Condition.
What's the diagnosis?
Persistent subthermal homeostasis
with, uh, involuntary
gelid substantiation.
She gets cold and freezes stuff.
Yeah. We got a few of
those in here like that.
- Fill this out.
- Okay.
We'll take it from here.
Officer Allen, it really is very...
This is a GCPD-A.R.G.U.S. operation.
We don't need your help.
Whew.
Barry... I mean, Oliver, look.
John Deegan.
Oliver Queen! Ha ha! Whew.
It's a genuine pleasure
to meet you, sir.
He knows who you really are.
Gentlemen, I was thinking,
"Why did I not become the Flash?"
And it seems changing reality itself,
it's got a bit of a learning curve,
so, yeah.
This actually explains a lot.
You did this to us?
You can undo it.
That is true, but I
think the question is,
um... Why would I want to?
What the hell did he just do?
He bought himself some time.
What's happening?
Trouble.
The crazy bastard let all the other
crazy bastards out of their cages.
All right. Get the
patients back in their rooms
and find that book.
Finally, the inmates
are running the asylum.
Not for long!
Fries, fries, fries, fries.
Come on. Where is it?
Are you okay?
My cryostasis shut
off when the locks did.
I... I need to be cold.
196 below zero. 196, he said.
How does this thing work?
Okay. Maybe you should
just take a step back.
Just get away from me!
Ohh. You cold bitch.
Unh!
Aah!
Agh!
No sign of Deegan or the book.
What the hell are you supposed to be?
Nicely done. Floor it.
Aah!
Who's this badass?
Agh.
That's... Not Batman.
Kate Kane told you to get out of Gotham.
You should have listened to her.
Guys, I've been all over this place,
and I can't find anything.
Guys, I could use a little backup.
On it.
There you are.
Took the words right out of my mouth.
Slippery.
Listen to me.
Caitlin.
Wait. No, Oliver.
Hey. Remember what
happened in Central...
Oliver!
Oliver's not here.
In fact...
No one's coming to save you.
You should have killed me
when you had the chance.
You left me to die on Lian Yu.
Unfortunately for you...
Heh heh... I didn't.
Does anybody copy?
Because... I think
we have a new problem.
Come on. You can do better than that.
You're a killer, a depraved monster
who found a way to channel his darkness
and pat himself on the back for it!
You'll never beat me.
Too slow, big heart.
Mama raised you right, so right,
you couldn't stop me from killing her.
Your father took the coward's way out,
and all these years, you
told yourself it was brave,
but he was a coward just like you.
A failure.
Selfish.
Slow.
Pathetic.
Who the hell are you?
No. Seriously, who are you?
Your friends were exposed
to a powerful hallucinogen.
Are you guys all right?
Define all right.
So how does a book make
people change bodies?
Deegan said he was using
the book to change reality.
Same question. How does
a book change reality?
We'll figure that out when
we get back to Star City.
Guys, we're gonna need
some help with this lock.
Good. Then you'll be leaving Gotham.
You guys have caused enough
problems for one night.
Hey. Would hitching a ride in the
Batmobile be out of the question?
Get... Out.
Sure.
- She really is like Batman.
- Yep.
I don't do tearful good-byes.
No. I... i just wanted to wish you luck.
Wherever your cousin is,
I'm sure he's really proud of you.
X-ray vision.
You really do have a lot of tattoos.
Somehow, I feel like Kara
Danvers doesn't have a single one.
You know, it's such a shame I have to go
because I feel like we
would make a good team.
World's finest.
Heh heh.
Oh. Look who finally came back.
With what looks like
a fairly infamous book.
A book with a cryptographic lock on it.
Can you get to work
on opening it, please?
We don't have a lot of time.
Okay. Geek squad, form up on me!
Not much of a heartfelt reunion.
She's getting used to everything.
Do you want me to talk
to her as, you know, you?
I think I'm in enough trouble
with Felicity as it is,
but no offense.
Hey. Can I talk to
you for a minute, then?
- Yeah. What's up?
- I just wanted to see
how you're doing.
I'm compartmentalizing.
I'll fix things with Felicity later.
I don't mean with Felicity.
We both saw some stuff back at Arkham.
I saw Evil Flash.
Eobard Thawne.
I saw Malcolm Merlyn.
- Oh.
- I knew you'd been
through a lot, but...
I don't know, man. I never realized.
I don't know how you do it.
I wouldn't be able to live
with the burdens that you carry.
Yes, you would.
Barry, I always thought
that you had it easy,
everything was just
sunshine and rainbows
and... Everybody likes you.
You have real steel in you, my friend.
You can carry any
burden thrown your way.
Some unsolicited advice?
Hmm.
Don't wait to work
things out with Felicity.
Our line of work, you never
know how much time you got.
Not only is the lock cryptographic...
It's metaphysical. The readings
I'm getting off this thing
are nuts... and, yes,
that's a technical term.
Um, may I speak with
Felicity for a minute?
Sure thing, Barry... Oliver... Boliver.
Stop helping.
This must be strange for you.
Oh. What gave you that idea?
I don't know. Maybe it's
easier for you to hear this
coming from... Barry Allen.
- What a stupid...
- Hear what?
That we're gonna be okay.
People change, Felicity.
It means we're growing.
It means we're evolving,
except for one thing,
one thing that will not change...
Is how I feel about you.
Love is too small a word...
And no matter who you are
or... or what you become,
no matter who I am
or... or what I become...
You will always be...
You will always be the love of my life.
People change.
That never will.
Oliver, I...
Jay?
- No.
- Oh, my god. Dad?
My name is Barry Allen.
Hello, John.
Do... do I know you?
You're not wearing your ring.
Things must be different here.
Barry, where's there?
My earth, Earth 90.
I've traveled from there to warn you.
- Warn us about what?
- His name is Mar Novu,
but he calls himself the monitor now.
He's been unleashing the Book of Destiny
across the multiverse
to test different earths.
Test them for what?
A crisis that he believes is coming.
Novu thinks the elseworlds created
by the Book of Destiny approximates
the collision of realities
that we're facing.
Guys...
We got a situation.
Cisco.
That... that's him from the vibe.
Mar Novu,
you're gonna stand down.
You're gonna use that book
to help us set reality right.
Well, I certainly
wouldn't have placed it
in Deegan's hands if
that were my intent.
Enough.
You will not do to this earth
what you did to mine.
I admire your persistence, Barry.
He said you were testing us.
Indeed, and thus far,
I am unimpressed.
A crisis is imminent.
Someone is coming,
someone far, far more
powerful than myself.
I mean to prepare.
By giving a nut bar an all-powerful
reality-rewriting book?
I am testing universes
to find one, I hope,
strong enough to stand against him.
You're causing chaos,
and you're blaming everyone else!
In the hope of finding the champions
that would save the multiverse entire.
You are the first of those
I've placed under fire
who have managed to retrieve
the Book of Destiny...
For all the good it did you.
Enough of this. Kara?
Yeah. I'd love to.
You show potential.
Let us see if it's anything more.
What is he talking about, Barry?
I offered you godhood,
and you squandered it on a petty dream.
Do better.
Think bigger.
Ohh.
What the hell?
Where'd he go? What the hell?
He went to give Deegan the book... back.
How do you know?
He did it again. He rewrote reality.
How far do you think
the changes go this time?
- Freeze!
- On the ground!
Now!
Uh... Speed us out of here.
I can't. Can you?
Nope.
Oliver Queen.
I've been waiting to do this
for a long time.
Unh!
Aah!
Should I follow you? What...
Hey!
There's no place you can
run where I can't find you.
It's over.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --