[GRUNTING]
-You feel better?
-I'll feel better once we end Deadshot.
MAN: Welcome to Germany, Mr. Ambassador.
-Henrik, you're looking great.
We have to end this guy before he makes
any more widows out of wives.
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
We will.
Diggle, we'll stop him.
I promised you I'd help take him down
and I keep my promises...
-...but he's on another continent.
FELICITY: Not anymore.
Thought it'd be helpful
to track A.R.G.U.S.'s manhunt...
...for Floyd Lawton a.k.a. Deadshot,
so I decrypted their communication logs.
Which means,
I just hacked a federal agency.
Makes me a cyber-terrorist,
which is bad.
I don't see myself
fitting in at Guantanamo Bay.
Don't worry, Felicity,
they don't send blonds there.
I dye it, actually. I keep your secret.
Hey, what'd you find?
Deadshot is scheduled to meet with
a potential new client here in Starling City.
Except the potential contract is bogus.
Your friend Lyla is setting a trap for him.
-Lawton took the bait.
-Great, I'll talk to Lyla...
-...see if I can suss out any details.
-Good. I've gotta have lunch with Laurel.
So when did you become, uh,
lunch dates with Laurel?
Look, we're just...
-We're friends.
-Friends are good.
-But?
-Couldn't you be friends...
...with someone less complicated
than your ex-girlfriend...
...who's your ex-best friend's
current girlfriend?
I wear a hood and I put arrows into
criminals, so when it comes to complexity...
...I grade on a curve.
Rescuing your father and stopping Fyers
is not gonna be some walk in the park.
They're not gonna allow us
to just stroll on into their camp.
Which is why we'll need cover.
If both of us are infiltrating,
who'll provide that?
He will.
-Me?
-Ha-ha-ha.
-The assault rifle is flushed. It's useless.
-We have a bow, arrows.
And no one capable of shooting them.
No offense, kid.
I was gonna say the same thing.
I think we should be spending our time
trying to devise a plan...
...not lower our already slim chances
of survival.
He'll hit his mark by sundown.
If not, we'll do it your way.
DIGGLE: Lyla?
-What is it, Johnnie?
Came by to see how your Deadshot
investigation is going.
-Anything new come up?
-Funnily enough, it did.
I was curious why you, a bodyguard,
were so keen on taking down...
...such a high profile assassin,
so I did some reading up on Lawton.
Lyla, listen...
Did you think I wouldn't find out
he killed your brother?
That you were using me. Me.
To what? Draw him into the open
so you could take him down yourself?
I will not let you use my agency
to settle your blood feud.
Lyla, I need to see this guy in a bag.
You of all people should get that.
Get this: stay away from Lawton, Johnnie,
or so help me, I will have you arrested.
You doubt me?
Never have.
-Hi.
-Did you get my voicemail?
-No.
-Things got a little crazy around here...
...back-to-back meetings,
I am so sorry, rain check?
Sure. I could definitely catch up
on some club paperwork.
I'm way behind since Tommy left.
I'm still shocked that he went
to go work for Malcolm.
You know, you were really understanding
to let him take this opportunity.
-Tommy said you were cool with it.
-Why wouldn't I be?
He's my friend. Like you.
-I'm sorry, are we early?
-No, not at all.
Uh, Oliver, this is Eric Moore
and his wife, Nancy.
I'm prepping them
for a deposition for tomorrow.
-And this must be your bodyguard?
-This is our son, Taylor.
Well, you're in very capable hands.
It's nice to meet you.
Eric, Nancy, I wanna make sure
that you guys are up for this.
Edward Rasmus isn't known for playing
with kid gloves, so this could get rough.
We invested our entire life savings
with Rasmus and he stole it.
Our retirement. Taylor's college fund.
He stole our future, Ms. Lance.
We want it back.
Well, then let's go get it.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
-Hello?
MAN: Mr. Moore.
I have some documents
for you from Ms. Lance...
...related to tomorrow's deposition.
What a nice home you have here.
You can really feel the love.
[SILENCED GUNSHOT]
Sorry about the mess.
This works better if it looks like a break-in.
[LOCK CLICKS]
[PHONE RINGS]
-Is it done?
MR. BLANK: Parents, yes.
I'm afraid there's been a variable.
The child got away.
-Got away? Did he see you?
MR. BLANK: No, Mr. Rasmus.
What he saw was the face of the man
who will reunite him with his parents.
MAN [ON TV]:
Starling City is expected to be host...
...of this year's Festival of Lights exhibition.
In other news, the bodies of Eric and
Nancy Moore were found early this morning.
The couple were being represented
by attorney Laurel Lance of CNRI...
...in a lawsuit
against financier Edward Rasmus.
Miraculously, their 7-year-old son, Taylor,
survived the horrific attack.
This isn't your fault, Laurel.
You shouldn't feel guilty.
I don't feel guilty. I'm angry.
This wasn't some random break-in.
-Edward Rasmus is involved, I know it.
-Listen, our guys are looking into this.
But you need to stay out of it, okay?
Because if Rasmus is behind this...
...he's clearly not messing around.
If you'd like to say goodbye to Taylor,
I will be taking him over to Child Services.
-Doesn't he have any other family?
-Grandparents are in Melbourne.
We're tracking them down...
...but until then, he's gonna be
a temporary ward of the State.
He can stay with me.
As his attorney, I am assigning myself
temporary guardianship.
-You'd still need a judge's order.
-I'll have it to you in an hour.
Well, have it your way.
Okay, look, I'm gonna park
a patrol car outside your place.
-Fine.
-And you.
-You look after them.
-I spend most nights at you daughter's.
There was probably a better time
to tell you that.
Probably not.
Hi. So you're gonna come
stay at my house, okay?
-What are you doing here?
-I heard.
-I wanted to make sure Laurel was okay.
-You could have just called.
I met Laurel's clients
and their son yesterday and I felt badly.
You met them?
Yeah, when I was picking up Laurel
for lunch.
-Which she didn't tell you about.
LAUREL: Tell you what?
Nothing.
It's settled.
Taylor's coming home with us tonight.
OLIVER: Well, if you need anything...
-We're fine.
-Okay.
-We should really get going.
LAUREL:
Here.
SHADO:
Set your sight.
Hit the tree.
Probably hit a tree.
Set your sight.
Hit the tree.
Steady your anchor point.
SLADE:
I hope you're getting closer.
At teaching him
how to be a better marksman.
It's not as though our lives depend on it
or anything.
-Try again.
-Okay.
What's this?
Lyla's mission profile on the trap
they've set for Deadshot.
Lawton is set to meet his new employer and
get his assignment tomorrow at 8 p.m.
Only, his new employer
will be an A.R.G.U.S. agent.
Lyla will then swoop in with her team
and arrest him.
Do you want Lawton arrested?
No.
Then tomorrow night, we cross
Floyd Lawton's name off your list.
There is something else
we need to look into.
Two of Laurel's clients
were murdered last night.
-Their 7-year-old son barely escaped.
-That's terrible.
Edward Rasmus, the financial advisor
Laurel was taking to court...
...may not have pulled the trigger,
but he probably called in the hit.
I want you to get into his corporate accounts,
phone records...
...anything that may link him
to the killer, okay?
Where are you going?
-Laurel's.
-Another friendly meal?
-My daughter is secure at her place?
OFFICER: So far, all quiet.
All right, let me know
if there is any movement.
OFFICER: Yes, sir, roger that.
-I'm heading over there right now.
What did you steal this time?
-You got a minute?
-No.
It's about the Hood.
When my men found you on
that subway car after you were kidnapped...
...you told me you didn't know anything
about the vigilante.
-Something you forgot to tell them?
-No.
I just wanna see him brought to justice
like everyone else.
Don't worry, kid. We'll get him.
Just keep making sure
I don't have a reason to get you.
Taylor? Sweetheart? Are you hungry?
You know, I make
the world's best macaroni and cheese.
TOMMY:
It's the only thing she knows how to make.
I miss my mom and dad.
When I was your age, my mom tucked me
into bed at night before going out.
Then the next thing I knew,
there was a police officer at my door.
He said that she was gone
and that I would never see her again.
But you know what?
-He was wrong.
-You saw her?
Mm-hm.
Every time I close my eyes, I can see her.
Every time I go to bed,
I see her in my dreams.
Really?
Yeah. Try it, close your eyes.
I see them.
Whenever you are sad or scared...
...just remember
that they will always be there.
You constantly surprise me, Merlyn.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
I'll get it.
MR. BLANK:
Ms. Lance? It's Lieutenant Kessel, S.C.P.D.
Your dad asked me to check in.
Lieutenant, can you hold your badge up
to the door, please?
Okay, great. Just one sec.
-What?
-His badge number begins with a zero.
Lieutenant's badge numbers
begin with a one.
[SILENCED GUNFIRE]
[FLOORBOARD CREAKS]
It was the badge that gave me away, right?
You know, my father's a cop.
And that's not all he taught me.
[CLICKS]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER
OVER POLICE RADIO]
Feeling like it might be time
for you to move.
Dad, whoever Rasmus hired is gonna
keep coming until he finishes the job...
...otherwise Rasmus will
just hire someone else who will.
Listen, I want the three of you
in protective custody immediately...
...and don't even think about it.
He killed two of my men.
The Hood just saved our lives.
We can trust him.
He won't let anything happen to me.
LANCE:
Even if I was comfortable with the idea...
...of him watching over you 24/7,
which I'm not...
...something tells me
he's got better things to do.
What about Oliver?
Sorry, you got another friend
named Oliver?
The Queens have more security
than the president.
They've got cameras everywhere,
bodyguards in every wing...
...and no one goes in or out
without being accounted for.
We both only want
what is best for Laurel.
And right now that is to stay
close to Oliver. Trust me.
[SIGHS]
This is Mr. Robbins.
Where you go, he goes.
You'll be very well protected, Ms. Lance.
-Thank you.
DIGGLE: I hand-selected these men myself.
The house and the grounds
are completely secure.
Please make yourself at home.
You must be Taylor. How about I show you
where I hide the good cookies?
Mr. Queen, whenever you're ready, I can
take you to your next appointment, sir.
-The Lawton meeting?
-Yes.
I just need to swing by the club
and pick up my good suit.
-So I'll meet you there.
-Of course, sir.
You're leaving?
There's something else
I need to take care of. It's important.
More important than what's here?
No offense to Oliver,
but I think we need Mr. Robbins...
...and his men more than him.
You are the reason why we're here.
Trust me, that wasn't easy to admit.
You'll be fine. I promise.
-You know, chewing might help.
-Not dainty enough for you?
I can eat you under the table, Roy Harper.
Don't forget that.
Yeah.
All units, code 10-80. Starling City port...
What is that?
Suspected vigilante activity,
requesting all available units.
Do you have a police radio
in your pocket?
No, I'm just happy to see you.
Got to run.
Oh, wait.
Heading on East Gary.
We're 20 minutes out.
Nice evening, huh?
Hey, I think you got something
that belongs to me.
You set this up,
just to get your radio back?
Well, I do love that radio. Come on.
I'm uploading a satellite overview
of the plaza to your phone.
OLIVER: I know the place.
-Dig was specific...
...about where you should perch.
You know...
...what position gives you
the best shot at Lawton. I think.
He used a lot of military jargon.
So you're sniping a sniper.
Kind of ironic, don't you think?
Me neither.
What's that?
I had a remote access trojan
scouring the Internet for Edward Rasmus.
His name just popped up
on a flight manifest, 8:15 to Shanghai.
-He's running.
-That's good, right?
If he's leaving town, he won't be
after Laurel and the child anymore.
But if you did wanna stop him,
looks like it's now or never.
Deadshot or Rasmus. Your choice.
Trap 1, this is Harbinger.
Wait for Lawton to enter and make contact.
Then we take him down.
DIGGLE:
Damn it, Oliver.
RASMUS:
Just until this CNRI mess dies down.
Ha, if it doesn't, two best things about China:
wontons and no extradition treaty. Ha, ha.
Hey, hey, I thought I was paying you extra
not to stop at the reds.
Trap 1, possible target acquisition.
Get ready.
Stand down.
Maybe Lawton didn't take the bait after all.
We're blown. Take cover.
Lyla?
[GRUNTING]
On your knees. On your knees.
Hands behind your head.
I saw you coming a mile away.
Thanks for tipping me off.
I'll kill you for what you did to Andy.
I'd be pulling these triggers right now,
except there's nobody paying me.
There's space for you right here,
right next to your brother.
You'd do best to remember that.
[GROANING]
What happened?
You didn't show, things didn't go well.
Rasmus was skipping town
and I had to reprioritize.
Thanks to your new priorities,
four agents are dead, Oliver.
You could have stopped this guy,
ended this maniac once and for all.
Lawton got away?
You seriously think
a man who goes by the name Deadshot...
...was going down without a fight?
I needed you there, man.
Taylor Moore was relying on me, Diggle.
This was never about that kid. He is safe
under armed security at your house.
-This is about Laurel.
-Diggle, I made a choice.
I know. You chose Laurel. Always her.
Everybody else be damned.
-Something to say, Felicity?
-Nothing you wanna hear.
Try again.
[OLIVER SIGHS]
-You're thinking too much.
-Nobody ever accused me of that before.
Show-off.
I see my target in the distance,
I feel the variation in the wind.
I hear the bowstring tighten
and I let go.
Give in to your senses, don't think.
You're right, this is definitively
not the time or place.
No, it's just there's, uh...
There's someone.
And it's a mile past complicated, but I can't.
Does she know how much you love her?
I suspect right now she doesn't.
But as soon as I'm home, she will.
You looked so beautiful that night.
I remember Oliver telling me once...
...that he wished your father would let him
come over to your house more often.
That being there made him feel less like
Robert Queen's son and more like himself.
I liked who my son was
when he was around you.
Thank you.
OLIVER:
Hey.
The police just called.
Edward Rasmus was arrested.
-Really? What happened?
-Apparently he confessed to everything.
He's going to prison a long time.
Won't be able to hurt anyone ever again.
-Why would he confess?
-The vigilante was involved.
TOMMY:
Good for him.
-So I guess it's over.
-Yes. Yeah.
-Great, I'll go wake up Taylor.
-No, Tommy, please.
He's sleeping, he's been through a lot.
Now, you all are welcome to stay.
We certainly have enough room.
It's your call.
Thank you, Mrs. Queen.
-I guess we'll stay, then.
MOIRA: Good.
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
OFFICER:
Your lawyer's here.
I'd like to discuss loose ends.
You didn't get my message?
Forget about the Moore boy.
I already confessed. That freak show
in a hood told me he'd kill me if I didn't.
We need to make this meeting
appear legitimate.
Lawyer stuff.
-Sign here, please.
-Am I clear? You leave the boy alone.
I wish I could, but he's seen my face.
Just like you.
If you put pressure in just the right areas
above the forearm...
...like I did to you, an embolism will form
in the medial antebrachial vein.
When the air pocket reaches your heart
in give or take 15 seconds, you'll die.
It's relatively painless.
Oh.
Nothing personal.
We're done here.
[GASPING]
Excuse me, hi,
I'm looking for my boyfriend.
He's kind of a regular around here.
Piercing blue eyes and may or may not
have stolen a police radio.
Yeah, that's him. Behind you.
Well, that's a nice look.
What were you thinking?
Well, if it isn't the wonder twins.
He's very sorry for stealing the radio
and he won't ever bug you...
...or steal anything from you guys
ever again.
Both of you. Come with me.
THEA:
What are we doing here?
Well, your boyfriend is so interested
in the Hood...
...I thought he might like to meet someone
who's already made his acquaintance.
Oh, God.
-Who was he?
-Well, that's the thing.
When you're alive, you get a name.
When you wind up down here,
you get a number. Meet 26.
See, your pal the Hood,
he's already sent 26 stiffs down here...
[THEA GROANS]
-...since he started his little one-man war.
-Maybe this guy deserved it.
Maybe he did.
But that's not how justice works.
You see, the vigilante, he doesn't have to
answer to anyone but himself...
...and that's a very dangerous power
to give to any one man.
He saved my life.
How do you know tomorrow
he won't just as easily take it?
-Get out of here.
THEA: Let's go. Come on.
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
He's safe now, Laurel.
With a hard road ahead of him.
Well, he's lucky to have you in his life.
I know the feeling.
When you first got home,
I didn't think that you had changed much.
But you have...
...and it's nice to see.
Thank you.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
GUARD: I have a delivery van coming in
for Ms. Lance. His ID checks out.
Thanks for the heads up.
For Ms. Lance.
[SILENCED GUNFIRE]
What a beautiful home.
Hmm. Such pain here.
A sense of loss and regret, you can feel it,
down to the wood paneling.
Tommy.
Okay, you two stay here with Taylor.
Where are you going?
It's an old house, fuses blow all the time.
It's probably nothing. Just, please, come on.
He's here.
[GUARD GRUNTING]
Where's the child?
This house is quite large and I don't
particularly care to check every room.
Very well. Have it your way.
[SILENCED GUNSHOT]
-Laurel. Laurel, don't.
-No, Ollie is still out there.
[GRUNTING]
-What happened to you on that island?
-Let's go. You're about to find out.
Death by poker. That's a new one.
He was gonna shoot me.
And then, uh, Mr. Robbins...
...he grabbed the poker and saved my life.
Mr. Robbins was a real hero.
-If it weren't for him, we'd all be dead.
-I've got enough details for my report.
I'll clear my boys out of here.
Let's go.
Come on, Taylor.
-You still love her. Don't you?
-Doesn't matter how I feel.
Because of what I do...
...I could never be with her.
So you don't have anything
to be afraid of. She is never...
-...ever going to know my secret.
-It doesn't matter if she knows.
I know. And I don't know how to be
with Laurel knowing the entire time...
...that if she ever found out
who you really are...
...she would choose you.
Thank you for everything you tried to do
for Eric and Nancy.
And for keeping Taylor safe.
Come here.
You keep being a good boy, okay?
Tommy, I really need to talk to you.
What's that for?
It's my stuff.
What's going on?
I'm not sure that I'm ready for the kind
of commitment that you're looking for.
-I don't wanna hurt you in the long run, so...
-Wait.
We both almost lost our lives and I'm
emotional too but you can't be serious.
This is me serious, Laurel.
But it doesn't make any sense,
I mean, why? Why now?
-Why even at all?
-I thought that I wanted this. You.
And the other night made me realize I don't.
You're lying.
I am not a liar.
If you've changed
and I know that you've changed...
...then you would...
You would never do this.
Then I guess I haven't changed
as much as we all thought, then.
I know. You think I'm an idiot.
I always thought you were an idiot.
Now I think you're brain dead.
Yeah, you're probably right.
Look, I don't understand this, Roy.
Why is finding the Hood
so important to you?
I can't stop replaying that night
in my head.
The night I got kidnapped by that psycho,
I just... I thought I was gonna die.
-But you didn't.
-Yeah, because of him.
-You don't owe him anything.
-You're wrong, I owe him everything.
I can't go back to the way things were, Thea.
I can't just go back to being nothing.
You're the one that keeps telling me
that I can be better than who I am...
...and this is my chance to be.
I can't explain it.
It feels like my life is connected to his.
So let's find him.
I can tell this means the world to you.
And you mean the world to me.
So let's find him.
You and me. Vigilante, here we come.
Was hoping you'd be here.
I want us to get back on the same page.
Oliver, we're not even in the same book,
you and me, not anymore.
I just did what I thought I had to.
Just like I'm doing what I have to.
[SIGHS]
We're done.
Don't do this.
The only thing you have to stop me
from going out that door is an arrow.
FELICITY:
Hey.
Where's he going?
So how did our Robin Hood do?
As expected?
So back to the drawing board we go.
[LEAVES RUSTLING]
OLIVER: Yao Fei.
-Ba!
How did you escape?
I didn't.
-You son of a bitch.
-Hey.
Your time on this island is at an end.