LANCE:
Hugo Mannheim.
Warrants out for racketeering,
extortion, murder.
The goombah trifecta.
But he never travels alone,
so watch your back...
...watch your partner's back. Let's go.
Thanks for helping me
keep watch over my dad tonight.
As long as Slade's out there,
neither of our families are safe.
[GUNFIRE]
OFFICER: This is the S.C.P.D.
Put your weapons on the ground!
Move, move, move!
[MEN GRUNTING]
Freeze!
[GROANING]
I'm fine. Go.
Go!
[ARROW WHISTLES]
[GRUNTING]
-Frank Bertinelli.
-Did my daughter send you to kill me?
[GLASS SHATTERS &amp; MAN YELLING]
[SIRENS WAILING]
[SIREN CHIRPING]
-Hey.
-Dad, are you all right? Are you hurt?
Yeah, I'm fine, sweetheart.
I know you don't believe
in reading perps their Mirandas...
-...but you can't just toss a guy out a window.
-He shot you.
I'm still here, ain't I?
Just next time, show a little restraint.
That was me showing restraint.
-Detective, we have another problem.
LANCE: Yeah, I know.
With Frank Bertinelli in custody, it's just
a matter of time before she rolls back in town.
Who's she?
DIGGLE: Helena Bertinelli.
Daughter of Mafia boss, Frank Bertinelli.
Or as I call her, Oliver's psycho ex-girlfriend
hell-bent on revenge against her father.
-Ex-girlfriend?
-That's what you took from that sentence?
Why does she want her father
killed so badly?
He had her fiancé murdered.
She wants payback.
That puts the fights with my father
in perspective.
I've been keeping tabs on Helena.
Last known sighting was a month ago.
Palermo.
She's been busy.
If you mean torturing and killing mafiosos
that might know where her father is.
DIGGLE:
Bertinelli's arrest hit the wires.
How long do you think we have
before Helena books a ticket back home?
[GRUNTING]
Go ahead.
Slade...
Please... Agh!
Why aren't we moving yet?
MAN:
We managed to repair the hull, but the, uh...
The engine's too damaged.
So fix it.
I can't.
I don't know how.
Then find somebody who does.
Hi, my name's Laurel. I'm an alcoholic.
ALL:
Hi, Laurel.
And this is actually
my second meeting today.
It's just, uh...
It's just so hard because I don't know
what to do with myself all day.
I'm a lawyer, but...
I was...
...a lawyer.
I loved it.
But I guess I loved drinking more.
I know that I can make it down here
with all of you. I just...
I'm not sure I can make it out there.
Ah, anyway, thank you for letting me share.
[PHONE BUZZING]
Thanks for coming.
Sorry about the way things ended here.
No. Don't be.
You did me a favor, Adam.
It was the only way
I was gonna hit bottom, and...
And I did.
How about you do me a favor now?
Come back to work.
You want me back?
I'm looking for someone to try this case...
...and, honestly, yours was the first name
that came to mind.
I'm still facing sanctions from the Bar.
I got a buddy on the committee.
I squared things for you.
An S.C.P.D. raid last night
brought in Frank Bertinelli.
He came back to Starling
to collect on some old debts.
The DA's office is clear to prosecute him,
for you to prosecute him.
I appreciate the offer, Adam, but why me?
There are RICO counts that your time at CNRI
make you ideally suited for.
Laurel, it's a case. If you want it, it's yours.
But only if you're ready.
[PEOPLE CHATTERING]
-What's the special occasion?
-I got paid.
So if it's not nice enough, you only have
yourself to blame for not giving me that raise.
[CHUCKLES]
Oh. Roy, I love it.
Thank you.
Hey, give me a second.
I forgot to put an order in.
Okay.
Hey, what's going on?
-I got a line on Michael Staton, Helena's fiancé.
-Felicity, he's dead.
-He rented a car last night. Impressive.
-That's Helena.
The car's got GPS. I'm hacked into it.
Yeah, she's headed straight for Starling City.
You ready to get back in the field?
I thought you'd never ask.
It's over, Helena.
Get out of the car!
Gun!
Don't hurt me!
GREEN ARROW:
Stand down.
-Don't hurt me!
-Speedy!
Enough.
He was just Helena's decoy.
Where is she?
I don't know.
Some chick just paid me
to take the car for a joy ride, I swear.
MAN:
Please don't kill me.
I'm getting married next month.
Just drive.
According to the S.C.P.D.,
the guy that gave Helena a ride into town...
...is a 22-year-old, poli-sci major at SCU,
and a member of Gamma Tau...
...which explains the whole "I didn't know
I was aiding and abetting a known felon" thing.
Anyone with boobs
can get a frat boy to do anything.
-I was a frat boy.
-I rest my case.
At least she didn't kill him.
That's something.
-It's not like Helena to show restraint.
-Sounds like you have a type.
Keep tabs on the police.
-Let me know if they get leads.
-I'll do canvassing.
SARA:
Hey.
You okay?
Tomorrow, it will be like nothing happened.
-That's one upside to the Mirakuru.
-The only one.
[SIGHS]
Look, I know what you're gonna say.
I had it under control last night.
So under control,
I almost put another arrow in you.
-I was gonna back off, never gave me a chance.
-You snapped out of it when I brought up Thea.
That's why you called me Speedy?
I thought you were trying to
give me a nickname.
-For the record, don't call me Speedy.
-Noted.
Roy, you're dangerous.
I thought I was helping you control it.
You are. I can't look at a bowl of water
without slapping it.
The first time that you're out in the field
in weeks...
...and you're ready to kill somebody?
Come on.
I should've asked you to do this months ago.
Asked me to do what?
Stay away from Thea.
No.
I can't.
She's not safe around you.
I'm not sure anybody is
when you lose yourself to this rage.
You love her.
That's why you're gonna do what I'm asking.
FELICITY:
Such a big uh-oh.
Helena?
Laurel.
MAN [ON TV]:
Adam Donner announced the return...
...of Laurel Lance to the DA's office
after a brief sabbatical.
She will lead the prosecution
of Mr. Bertinelli.
Jury selection starts today.
Hey.
Hey, what are you doing here?
I heard you picked up some big new case
on the news. How come you didn't call me?
I was going to, but it all happened so fast.
Plus, I thought you and dad would try and
talk me out of going back to work so soon.
-Which is why you're here.
-I'm worried about you.
If you're worried I'm gonna slip,
I'm still going to two meetings a day and...
No, it's not that.
Everybody knows
what kind of guy Bertinelli is.
Not to mention his psychotic daughter who's
on her way back to Starling City to kill him.
How do you know that?
I don't.
I just want you to be safe.
And I love you for caring.
But, Sara,
you've never seen me be a lawyer before.
And I'm really good at it.
And I miss it.
I have to run.
I can't be late for court.
Yeah, this is much better than the freighter.
You prefer boat, Hendrik?
Feel free to swim back.
PETER: Sara said Oliver survived here
for over a year.
We can do the same.
Unless Ivo and his men come find us.
We don't know what happened on the boat.
Who's alive and who's dead.
SLADE [OVER WALKIE-TALKIE]:
Sara. Are you there?
Slade. Is Oliver...?
He's in pain. Yes.
But he's still breathing.
For now.
Slade, listen, you won, okay?
You have the Amazo.
Just let Oliver go,
and then you can leave us here.
There's my problem, Sara.
I can't leave.
Why not?
During our assault,
the ship's engine was damaged. She won't sail.
During the attack, unfortunately,
I decapitated the engineer.
So, what can we do about our problem, Sara?
You want Oliver back.
And I need someone qualified
to fix this boat.
For Oliver's sake...
...I sure hope a
Mr. Hendrik is there with you.
Non-lethal arrows?
It's not like you to play with kid gloves.
How's Roy?
Like Helena, he is not too pleased
with my skills as a mentor.
Laurel won't drop the case.
She's headed to court right now.
-Where are you going?
OLIVER: The courthouse.
Well, hey, you forgot your baby arrows.
I get your whole no-killing spree, but if it
comes to saving Laurel or killing Helena...
Those aren't the only two choices.
You were happy to let Dig take the kill shot
when it was Slade threatening your family.
This is different.
I failed Helena.
I created the Huntress.
Yeah, well, you created Slade too.
You're right.
But when it comes to our families...
...neither one of us thinks clearly.
Which is why you have to stay here.
Ollie, I can't.
I'm not gonna let anything happen to Laurel.
I love her too.
What do you guys think?
Oh, I think if the Huntress shows up,
you should totally kick her ass.
Don't tell me you're worried about me too.
No. I just wanted to watch the trial.
I heard the prosecutor was something special.
That's odd. Why are they bringing him in
through the front entrance?
Everybody, get down!
[BOLTS WHISTLING]
Hey, Dad.
Sorry I'm late,
but you're a hard man to track down.
But it's fitting that you came back to Starling,
where it all began.
Where you killed Michael.
You know, I almost feel sorry for you.
OLIVER:
Helena.
Stop this.
Oliver, you know I can't.
Well, what are you waiting for?
I said, what are you waiting for?
OFFICER:
Helena Bertinelli, put down your weapons...
...and place your hands above your head.
So this was a big trap.
With you as the bait.
What did they offer you?
Oh, they didn't have to offer me anything.
OFFICER: Give up, Miss Bertinelli.
The building is surrounded.
What was it you always taught me, Daddy?
Be prepared for anything.
Now!
Take hostages and fall back.
Hey, hold your fire! Hold your fire!
They have hostages!
Hold fire. Say again, hold fire.
They've taken hostages.
Where's Laurel? Is she with you?
Sorry, Mr. Lance, we got separated.
She's still inside.
REPORTER: We are live
outside the Starling City Courthouse...
...where Helena Bertinelli
and a number of assailants...
...seized control of the building.
And I'm now being told
they are holding a number of hostages inside.
I want snipers with thermals
on every building for a two-block radius.
This was not
how it was supposed to go down, captain.
You promised me
there wouldn't be any casualties.
-This was your idea, huh? You son of a bitch!
-Unh!
My daughter's in there! What are
you thinking, putting lives at risk? Get off!
-Listen. I was following orders.
-Orders?
MAN [OVER RADIO]:
All units, we have an incoming call.
[RINGING]
Keep these airways clear. Airways clear.
Miss Bertinelli, no one has to die today.
HELENA:
My father does.
And unless you hand him over to me,
I'm gonna start killing hostages.
This, Mr. Donner, is what happens
when you let freaks with masks run wild.
-Get them the hell out of here.
-Don't touch me.
[PHONE RINGING]
It's my mom.
-Detective.
-Helena Bertinelli just took 10 hostages.
Laurel's one of them.
Yeah, I'm aware of the situation.
[PHONE BUZZING]
Oliver, where are you? Are you okay?
I'm with Lance as Oliver.
He just called the Arrow.
Oh. Oh!
It's hard to keep track
of who knows whose identity.
Laurel's inside the courthouse.
-What do you need?
-My work clothes.
-I'm on it.
-Put Sara on the phone.
She's not here.
Where is she?
[BOTH GRUNTING]
Are you one of the good guys?
No. But I'm friends with them.
[DANCE MUSIC PLAYING]
-Dude, watch it.
-Screw you.
[GROANING]
-Thea, we need to break up.
-What?
No.
What do you mean, no?
Thea, I'm breaking up with you.
No, you're not.
You can't make me date you.
Roy, yesterday you gave me
a bracelet worth every dime you had.
And now, what, you wanna end things?
You're clearly going through something
right now.
And I'm not gonna let you
go through it alone.
I'm always gonna be here for you.
Sorry, the guy from the private party
said we stocked the wrong vodka.
He's freaking me out.
We'll talk about this later, okay?
Are you hurt?
I'm so stupid.
Hey, you don't wanna do that.
Oh, no. Trust me, I do.
What about your sobriety?
How do you know about that?
The A.A. chip on your keychain.
Thirty days.
Do you even know why I'm here today?
Turns out I'm decoration.
Expendable decoration.
What do you mean?
This whole trial was a sham.
I should've seen it.
Sara was right.
Sara, she's my sister.
She said that I wasn't ready to come back.
I just thought she was being overprotective.
Sisters can be like that.
You should meet mine.
She's gone through a lot.
She must have been so strong.
I just wanted to show her, show myself...
...that I was still strong too.
So show me.
Let's go.
GREEN ARROW [OVER COMM]: Where are you?
-Inside. I've got Laurel. She's okay.
Is that the Arrow?
-I'm headed to an egress point, south wing.
-Wait.
What about the other hostages?
You're just gonna leave them?
I need to get you to safety.
I don't understand.
What is so special about me?
-What's going on?
-She won't leave.
I know Helena.
She's gonna kill all of those people,
innocent people.
You wanted me to show you I'm strong.
This is me being strong. I'm staying.
Are you gonna help me or not?
Get her out of there now!
It's not like I can just knock her out.
I don't want you engaging Helena.
Are you afraid of what she'll do
or what I'll do?
Sara, you're not a killer.
I am what I need to be.
SLADE:
Sara, did you hear me?
I heard you.
Hendrik's not here.
There's someone I'd like you to say hello to.
Don't give him anything, Sara.
Ollie.
One last chance. Oliver for Hendrik.
I told you. Hendrik, he didn't make it
to the island. He drowned.
To think, it was only a year ago,
you were a little college girl...
...fretting about boys.
What's your point?
You're not a good liar.
[SCREAMING]
Slade! Stop, please!
Look, he's your friend!
That is the sound of electricity
surging through my friend.
Five milliamps, to be exact.
Seven causes cardiac arrest.
[SCREAMS]
Oliver just passed out with six milliamps.
He'll be delivered with the fatal blow of seven
in one hour...
...if Hendrik is not standing here by my side!
No way in hell I'm going back there.
I was almost married once.
Agh.
It's been an hour.
And I'm a woman of my word.
Just ask my father.
No, please.
[HIGH-PITCHED WAILING]
Everything's gonna be okay.
[BOTH GRUNTING]
-Behind you!
-Agh!
Oliver sure does like to dress up his girls.
[GRUNTS]
Agh!
Are you all right?
Laurel. She's still in there.
Nice to see you again, Laurel.
[PHONE RINGING]
GREEN ARROW:
Helena, listen to me.
-This has to end.
-I agree.
And it ends with my father in a box.
The police are never gonna
hand over your father.
No, they won't.
That's why you're gonna do it.
Simple trade.
My father, for Laurel.
Hey, guys, we need more vodka.
Okay. I'll get it myself.
-Where are you taking me?
-Safe house.
Listen. Front's mobbed with reporters.
Let's take Bertinelli out the back.
Bring the van around.
All right.
[ARROWS WHISTLING]
-What the hell? What's going on?
-Don't worry about it.
-Just get in the van.
-Hey! Hey!
-SWAT's ready to breach the courthouse.
-Then we make the trade now.
I'm not gonna lose any sleep over Frank here,
but are you gonna serve him to his daughter?
No.
No one dies tonight.
Are you okay?
-Everything's gonna be fine.
-I said, no talking.
We talked that night.
You, Oliver, Tommy and I, at dinner.
I remember you telling me
your fiancé was killed.
I'm so sorry.
Does this make us girlfriends?
No.
But I know what it's like to lose someone.
Oh.
Poor Laurel.
Did Tommy dump you?
No.
He died.
And I couldn't deal with it.
So I became a drunk.
Every problem I had...
...I solved with a pill or a drink.
My friends and my family, they tried to help me,
but I wouldn't let them.
You don't have to do this, Helena.
It's not too late.
Yes, I do.
Because once you let the darkness inside...
...it never comes out.
[PHONE RINGING]
Helena, I have your father.
I want four-man teams.
Diamond formations.
Move fast. Shoot sharp.
One more thing: Vigilantes are not the law.
If they're wearing a mask, they get a bullet.
-Let's move out.
-Copy that.
[ALL SHOUTING]
Hands up, Bertinelli! Do it, now!
Please don't kill me! Please!
She told me, she told me to wear it
or she'd kill me.
Where the hell is she?
Don't look so scared, Laurel.
You might just live through this.
You're gonna hand me over to my daughter?
I thought you were good guys.
Shut up.
Remember all that stuff I said about restraint?
Forget about it.
Hey.
You can't stop someone like Helena
by becoming her.
I will do what I have to
to protect someone I love.
PETER:
Hendrik, please, put the gun down.
Why? So you can send me back
to that hell hole? I don't think so.
It's not for any of us to decide
who lives and dies.
In Hendrik's case,
I'd be willing to make an exception.
I'm leaving. Don't stop me.
You're good at talking,
but you will not kill me.
Let's find out.
[GRUNTS]
OFFICER [OVER RADIO]: We got a ping off Miss
Lance's phone. She must still have it on her.
-Where?
-A machine shop at Gail Street and Simone.
Should we rally up there?
-Negative. Hold your location.
-Yes, sir.
Sergeant, keep this position.
Well, this is irony for you, Dad.
Didn't you have Jimmy D'Agostino's body
buried under the building next door?
I'm sorry, my girl.
Now you're about to die, I'm sure you are.
No.
I'm sorry for that little girl
I used to take to ballet class.
And go on ski trips with.
The one I used to help
with her math homework.
She hated math.
I'm sorry that I caused her so much hurt.
Because she brought me so much joy.
[GRUNTS]
Helena, don't kill him.
You can never come back from that.
It's too late. I'm already gone.
Goodbye, Dad.
STEIN:
Damn vigilantes!
You are not above the law!
The last time this happened,
I threw you out a window.
I was holding back.
I won't do that again.
[BOTH GRUNTING]
LANCE: Hey.
-Unh.
No!
You're not a killer.
-You don't know who I am, Laurel. Not really.
-Then show me.
[GASPING]
No.
It was supposed to be me.
-It was supposed to be me who did it.
-That's enough.
[SIRENS APPROACHING]
Go.
How did you get in here?
My family makes a generous donation
to the policeman's retirement fund.
Every once in a while I get to call in a favor.
Maybe you can ask them to send me to prison
somewhere tropical.
I thought I'd feel different.
Now that he's dead, but I don't.
You always told me that...
...killing him wouldn't change anything.
You were right.
But I was wrong too.
About what?
I thought I could help you.
Stop you from being a killer.
[SIGHS]
But I was just starting.
And I was a killer too.
What are you now?
I'm trying to be better.
It's so stupid, but...
...I keep thinking, now that he's dead...
...my father and Michael are together.
And I'm still here. Alone.
You're not alone.
What are you doing to me?
In Roman times...
...a criminal was branded...
...to identify his crimes to the world.
And to forever remind him
of what he'd done.
Agh! Unh!
Shado wore this tattoo on her back.
Now you shall wear it for the rest of your life.
However short that might be.
SARA [OVER WALKIE-TALKIE]:
Slade, Slade.
Hello, Sara.
I hope you've made the right choice.
Yes.
Look, on behalf of the entire DA's office,
I have to apologize.
Adam Donner's employment here
has been terminated.
Obviously, we had no idea
what he was plotting.
I would hope not.
Unfortunately, Adam was not authorized
to offer you your job back.
I'm sorry, but nothing's changed.
Yes, it has.
Excuse me?
You are going to rehire me, Kate.
Unless you feel like explaining to the press...
...that your own assistant district attorney
was the brilliant mastermind...
...behind tonight's hostage crisis.
Welcome back.
I have to say, I am impressed.
I would've thought blackmail
was a little dark for you.
Someone recently told me:
"Once you let the darkness inside...
...it never comes out."
Hey.
What are you still doing up here?
Thinking. Crying.
Roy and I are...
What happened?
I caught him with some slut.
Right over there, actually.
I'm sorry.
He was doing it to push me away,
which clearly worked.
I just... I don't know why.
Why is it so hard for everyone
just to tell the truth?
I mean, Roy can't even tell me the truth
about why he wants to end things with me.
Mom, she...
She keeps all of these secrets.
I mean, doesn't it...? Doesn't it feel like
she's still keeping something from us?
I don't know, Thea.
You're the only one
that doesn't lie to me, Ollie.
You're the only one I know
who doesn't keep secrets from me.
I gotta go.
Let me drive you.
I just wanna be alone right now.
Is she okay?
She will be.
Eventually.
You did good tonight.
That's what heroes do, right?
MAN:
It's a dangerous city.
You shouldn't be out on the streets alone.
Mr. Wilson?
Please.
Call me Slade.