OLIVER [VOICE OVER]:
My name is Oliver Queen.
For five years, I was stranded
on an island with only one goal: survive.
Oliver Queen is alive.
OLIVER [VOICE OVER]: Now I will fulfill
my father's dying wish.
To use the list of names he left me...
...and bring down those
who are poisoning my city.
To do this,
I must become someone else.
I must become something else.
NARRATOR:
Previously on Arrow:
DR. LAMB: The Oliver you lost
might not be the one they found.
When you were plotting your plan
to save the city...
...I don't think you considered the effect
it would have on the people in your life.
OLIVER:
You're wrong.
Not being able to tell my family the truth
doesn't hurt anyone worse than me.
I made you a promise I couldn't keep.
After being granted the miracle
of having my child returned to me...
...that you seem to have no interest
in telling me the truth.
You've gotta let me in, Ollie.
You've gotta let someone in.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
- Hello?
- Hi.
Mom said I'm supposed to remind you
to pick her up for lunch.
Was I supposed to have lunch with her?
She said she left you five messages.
Bite the bullet
and have a Cobb salad with the woman.
Sometimes it's difficult to remember
which one of you is my mother.
Mrs. Queen, all I'm asking for is a chance
to sit down and discuss our proposal.
If that's all it is,
then I can save us both the time.
-It's rejected.
- I see. May I ask why?
Do I really need to answer that,
Mr. Copani?
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I'm meeting my son for lunch.
[TIRES SCREECH]
Get down!
[EXHALES]
- Mom? Are you okay?
- I'm all right.
- Are you hurt?
- No, I'm...
- Are you sure?
- I'm fine. I'm fine.
Call 911.
[CAR TIRES SCREECH]
[HORN HONKS]
[PANTING]
Hi.
- Are you okay?
- I'm fine.
I'm fine.
- Did you reach Walter?
- No, I'm sorry.
As I was telling
your mother and sister...
...the CAT scan showed a grade-2
concussion. She can go home so long...
...as someone stays with her.
- Thank you.
MOIRA: Hm.
I'm sorry. I shouldn't have left you.
I thought you were fine.
What did you think you were doing?
I wanted to get the license plate
of the guy who took a shot at you.
- Well, that was foolish.
- Yeah.
- So did you get the license plate?
- No, he got away.
Maybe you should spend
a little less time trying to be a hero.
You're obviously not very good at it.
- That's cute.
- Wasn't trying to be.
You left Mom in the street.
Alone and hurt in the street.
Heh, to get a license plate?
- You don't believe me?
- I love you. Mom loves you.
But it's getting hard
when you won't be truthful with us.
Detectives.
- Do you have any leads on the shooter?
- Not yet.
- Did you get a look at him?
- He was wearing a helmet.
- Don't worry. We'll find him.
- My head of security is on his way.
I wanna make sure there are men
outside my mother's door.
She needs to be protected.
You know your family's
at the tippy-top of my list of priorities.
The guy she was with was connected.
Mobbed-up-to-the-eyeballs connected.
She wasn't the target.
And you're welcome.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Uh, technically, I did get here, like,
1O seconds before this guy.
Keep the change.
So, Tommy,
what brings you by so late?
Well, I assumed, rightly, that you would
be at home working tonight...
...and I also assumed
that you might be hungry. Also rightly.
I don't know.
This is a mushroom and olive pizza
from Mario's.
Oh, that is damn good pie.
- All right. What do you have to offer?
- Spicy tuna on crispy rice from Toro.
Oh.
Damn you, Merlyn.
I hope sushi was all you had in mind.
Uh, actually, there was something
that I wanted to ask you.
- And what's that?
- Will you go out with me?
Like, on a date?
You brought me dinner
to ask me to dinner?
Oh, uh, well, I also did throw you
a really big charity gala.
See, I thought you threw it for
the hundreds of people it would benefit.
Oh, yeah, hundreds of people.
Plus one more.
- Tommy, heh.
- Laurel.
I get it. Okay, this is all happening
for us in the wrong order.
First, we're friends for many years...
...and then, briefly,
we are friends with benefits...
...extremely excellent benefits,
and now I'm just hoping...
...that we can be two people
sitting at the same restaurant...
...at the same table at the same time.
See, when I say it like that,
it doesn't sound so scary, does it?
Oliver, your mom's nearly killed...
...I think you can take a day off
from training.
My mother wasn't the target.
This man was. Paul Copani.
He was trying to close a deal with her
when they were shot at.
[PANTING]
Copani works
for Bertinelli Construction.
- And Frank Bertinelli.
- The mob boss.
I did some digging.
Copani isn't the first member
of Bertinelli's crew who's been hit.
You did some digging.
Bertinelli has a lot of enemies.
The best way to figure out
who's trying to target his organization...
-...is to get inside of it.
- So let me get this right, Oliver.
Your mother's shot at, nearly killed, and
the way you process this emotionally...
-...is by going undercover with the mob.
- I'm not trying to process it emotionally.
Yeah, well,
maybe that's your problem, man.
You ever thought about
just being there for your family?
I tried that today with Thea.
She told me I wasn't being honest
with her and she's right.
I can't very well explain to her
that I left our mother alone...
...and bleeding on the pavement
because I'm fast enough...
...to almost run down the attacker.
But what I can do
is protect my family.
And, Diggle, when I find out
who this guy is, he's a dead man.
- Speedy, where you going?
- Clubbing.
Which is difficult to do in your house
and not at an actual club.
I have to go out tonight.
- I thought you'd be watching Mom.
- I've spent the whole day with her.
- I thought you were taking the night shift.
- I'm sorry, but this thing, it's important.
[SIGHS]
You know, sometimes, Ollie,
I just don't get you.
And by "sometimes" I mean never.
You're not the first person
to say that to me today.
Why am I not surprised?
- Oh, nice dress. Where you headed?
- Upstairs. Apparently.
- Long story.
- Hey, I heard about your mom.
- Is she all right?
- Well, she's resting upstairs.
More shaken up than anything.
I gotta run to this, uh, business thing.
I appreciate you stopping by.
No problem.
Just so long as your mom's all right.
Yeah.
Hey, one more thing.
Mainly because I don't want you
to find this out from someone else...
...that someone else
especially being Laurel...
...uh...
...we're going to dinner,
as in a, uh, date.
That's good.
Laurel deserves someone special
and so do you.
Thanks, man.
- I gotta run to this thing.
- Absolutely. I'll catch you later.
Oh, and, uh, Tommy, if you hurt her,
I'll snap your neck.
I'm just kidding, heh.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
Mr. Bertinelli.
- Call me Frank.
- Call me Oliver.
Yeah, heh.
Thank you for agreeing to meet me
at my home.
Living rooms make
the best conference rooms.
- Oh, I'm gonna steal that.
- Heh.
- Nick Salvati, my associate.
- How do you do?
Let's have a drink.
THEA:
So, what are you in the mood for, hmm?
We could watch reality housewife
cooking show or Cop Docs.
It's where doctors run around
fighting crime...
...when they're not all
sleeping with each other.
[CHUCKLES]
Whatever you want, sweetheart.
You're the one who's given up
your evening out.
Aw, it's not like there's anybody else
who could be staying with you.
[GASPS]
- Oh, wait, yes, there is.
- Don't be too harsh on your brother.
[SCOFFS]
Why not? I mean,
aren't you getting, heh, sick of his lies?
Thea, everyone has secrets.
I mean, we all have things
that we wanna keep to ourselves.
I just don't get him sometimes.
I know.
You know, being in that hospital
and seeing Dr. Lamb again...
...it made me remember the day
that Oliver came home.
It was Dr. Lamb that told me
that the Oliver we'd lost...
...might not be the Oliver
that they'd found.
I think it's easy to forget, but he lived
apart from civilization for 5 years.
THEA:
Hm.
- So, what, he gets, like, a free pass?
- No, no, no, not at all.
I just think we need to stop judging him
for the Oliver he was...
...and start accepting him
for the Oliver that he is.
So, Oliver, I'll be honest with you,
I was surprised to hear from you.
It was my impression from the news...
...that you weren't gonna be involved
with your family's business.
There were a few catchphrases I missed
while I was away for five years.
One of them being
lame-stream media.
[ALL CHUCKLE]
- The press never gets anything right.
- Oh, I know a thing or two about that.
[CELL PHONE RINGS]
- So, Oliver, I'll be blunt.
- Hmm?
I want the contract...
...to build Queen Consolidated's
new applied sciences division.
- And I'm inclined to give it to you.
- Your mother wasn't so enthusiastic.
- How is she by the way?
- She's recuperating at home, thank you.
What a terrible thing.
And, Frank, I was very sorry to hear
about what happened to Paul Copani.
Paul was a good friend.
He was a good man.
[SIGHS]
The violence in this city...
Sometimes I wonder why I stay.
I had the same thought.
So Why'd you come back?
You could have settled
anywhere in the world.
Because Starling City is my home.
[SPEAKING IN ITALIAN]
No matter which way you go or turn,
you always end up at home.
- Oliver, this is my daughter, Helena.
- Hello.
- Nice to meet you. I'm heading out.
- All right. Take one of the guys with you.
- I can take care of myself.
- Heh.
I wasn't asking, sweetie.
Frank, that meeting you requested?
They can do it.
Now.
- I can come back another time.
- No, no, no. Just, uh...
Just excuse us for a moment,
would you?
OLIVER: Mm-hm.
- Thank you.
Oliver Queen.
The rich man's Lindsay Lohan.
Look, um...
...I've gotta go to this other meeting.
But I need someone
to take him to dinner.
So you pimp out your daughter.
No, I ask her to help me
close a business deal.
I remind her
that the family business is dying...
...and that we need this contract
and Oliver Queen can give it to us.
Please, sweet pea, huh?
For us. For me, hmm?
That's my girl.
Oliver, I'm so sorry,
something has come up.
But Helena would love to take you
to dinner and discuss the deal further.
- Oh.
HELENA: Hm.
I was hoping to speak with you.
Well, as you, uh, speak for your family,
my daughter also speaks for ours.
It's really not necessary.
-It'd be my pleasure.
- Sure.
I look forward to working together.
FRANK: Thank you for coming.
- Anything for a friend.
[SPEAKING IN CHINESE]
We're not responsible
for the attacks on your people.
These attacks on my business,
on my family's lifeblood, they stop now.
Or I'm coming for you.
[SIGHS]
What does the Triad have to gain
by provoking you?
Well, no one ever credited the Triad
with rational thinking.
If not them, then who?
FRANK [OVER COMPUTER]:
Whoever it is...
...when I find out who's behind this,
there will be blood.
Bertinelli's ready to put the screws
to everyone...
...who pays him protection money.
Three of his best earners
have been murdered.
He's gotta make up the cash
somewhere.
Whoever is pruning the family tree
is looking to make Bertinelli suffer.
- You think it's one of the other families?
- No.
HILTON:
Then who?
According to the coroner,
none of the vics took a clean shot.
Half the bullets missed.
Our killer is not a pro.
That's not stopping them
from pulling that trigger.
That's up to us.
Or this is gonna blow up
into an all-out mob war.
- You're an angel, Helena. So beautiful.
- Heh.
Well, we are gonna take good care
of both of you tonight.
- You'll tell your father hello from us?
- Of course, Mr. Russo.
- I'll give you a minute.
- Thank you.
I heard about your mother's accident.
- Is she gonna be okay?
- She's gonna be fine. Thanks.
I'm glad.
So why would you wanna go
into business with my father?
You know who he is
and how he made his money.
You don't approve
of your family's enterprises?
We share a name.
That name defines us
whether we want it to or not.
You've already made judgments
about me...
...like I've made judgments about you.
Right.
I'm the rich man's Lindsay Lohan.
Heh, sorry.
- That's okay.
- Heh.
- Hey, can I ask you something?
- Yeah.
I know it must have been hell for you...
...alone on that island for five years,
but, um...
But what?
But was there ever a day when you were
just happy to be away from everything?
No pressure from your family.
No need to be the person
that everyone else expects you to be.
- Was there ever a day when--?
- When I didn't feel lost, that I felt...
...free?
[CHUCKLES]
More than one and, uh...
And those are the days that I miss.
[TOMMY GASPS THEN COUGHS]
- What, is it too spicy for you, Merlyn?
- No. No, not really.
I'm just, um, crying because I was thinking
of a Hallmark commercial...
...I saw earlier today
featuring a sick kitty.
It was very emotional.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
WAITER: Will there be anything else?
- No, thank you.
Yep.
Thanks for letting me
take you to dinner.
Well, thank you
for letting me choose Indian.
Yeah, I read this article
by a film critic once who said...
...if he could have one wish it would be
to watch his favorite movie again...
...for the first time.
I kind of wish that was us.
So you want dinner and a movie?
No.
I wish we had just met,
and that all this was just beginning...
...and there wasn't so much of me
I wish you'd forget.
Well, keep saying nice things
like that...
...and maybe next time
I'll let you choose the restaurant.
- Mr. Merlyn?
- Yeah.
I'm sorry, I'm afraid your credit card
has been declined.
You swipe it a few times?
Sometimes those things can be glitchy.
I did. And, um, I'm afraid the credit card
company wants me to confiscate it.
Sorry.
OLIVER: People are always asking me
what did I miss the most.
[SIGHS]
Uh, air conditioning.
Satellite radio. Taglia...
- Tagliatelle?
- Right.
Hmm.
Those are the answers I give because
those are the answers they're expecting.
- Why can't you just be truthful?
- I don't know how truthful I can be.
You've been through a crucible.
And it changed you. How could it not?
That's beautiful. Your cross.
-It's a gift. From my fiancé.
- Heh, fiancé.
- I didn't know you were engaged.
- I'm not. Anymore.
- He died.
- I'm sorry.
Me too.
That was my crucible.
Boy, it's nice to...
It's really nice to be with someone
that I can be myself with.
It's nice to be with someone
who knows how hard it can be.
[CELL PHONE VIBRATES]
- Ugh, I'm really sorry.
-It's okay. Take it.
Thank you.
- Yeah.
DIGGLE: Hey, it's Dig.
Something came up.
You gotta get out of there
and call me back.
Helena, I have to go.
There's something that I have to do.
It's about my mother.
Otherwise, I would, uh, stay.
And I would like that.
Uh, my father would kill me
if I let you pay.
[SCOFFS]
I have a confession.
- I didn't wanna go out with you tonight.
- That makes two of us.
I'm really glad that I did.
That makes two of us.
[CHUCKLES]
Oliver.
Be careful with my father.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Thea, you don't need to knock,
sweetheart.
[DOOR OPENS]
MAN:
What about me?
I hope you don't mind.
Thea let me in.
What are you doing here?
I wanted to see how your recovery
was going.
Surely someone of your means
has a telephone.
I like to see someone when I have
something important to talk about.
We used to be friends, Moira.
I still remember that time.
You, me and Robert.
Which is why I came by.
You are a vital part
of Starling City's future.
Robert feared that future.
He lost his conviction.
It's been my experience that
when someone has a brush with death...
...like you experienced today, even their
deepest held convictions can change.
- Have they?
- No.
You didn't have to say it.
I can see that they haven't.
- What happened?
- Yeah, it's what's about to happen.
Bertinelli's enforcer, Nick Salvati?
Yeah, we drank a Scotch together,
he seems like a real stand-up mobster.
He's paying visits to everyone
who owes the mob protection money.
I'm trying to figure out
who took a shot at my mother...
...not take on all of organized crime.
Salvati and his goons have put
four people in the hospital...
...and if somebody doesn't stop him...
...the poor bastard
who owns Russo's is next.
- Wait, wait. Russo's?
-It's at the corner of Adams--
I know where it is. I'm here right now.
What?
I was having dinner
with Bertinelli's daughter.
You're supposed to be undercover...
-...not speed dating.
- I didn't have a choice.
Yeah, well, uh, I've seen her on the web.
You made quite the sacrifice.
Salvati's here.
I'm sorry, we're closed.
Huh? Mr. Salvati.
[SPEAKS IN ITALIAN]
- Uh, I have some fresh-made lasagna.
SALVATI: We're not here for food, Mr. Russo.
- Your payment's due.
- I already made my payment this month.
You need to pay again.
I can't afford to make
another payment if I'm--
Going to what? Restock your bar?
- Break his fingers.
- Leave him alone!
- Break hers too.
- No, don't touch her!
[EXPLODES]
[MAN GRUNTS]
OLIVER:
Go!
[GUNSHOTS]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[PANTING]
OLIVER:
I don't understand.
- Why is she targeting her family?
- I don't know.
- Here I thought you had parental issues.
- This is not a joke, Diggle.
Oliver, you're not falling for this girl,
are you?
Because I know
you can't be that crazy.
Helena Bertinelli shot at your mother.
She also murdered four men
in cold blood.
She has to have reasons
for what she's doing.
Reasons?
Since when do you care
about the bad guy's reasons?
Oh, she is bad guy, Oliver.
She's the killer.
Whatever's going on in your head,
get it straight.
Any attempt on his right hand...
...is gonna send your new friend's father
on a Warpath.
I know what I'm doing.
Now I know how your family feels
when you lie to them.
Is this the only angle you've got?
The Russos chintzed out a bit
on their security package.
Somebody's in the wings with a gun
shooting at these guys.
- What do you got from earlier? Yeah.
- Before the shooting?
Business dinner, birthday dinner,
couple of blind dates.
Any guests
of the Chinese persuasion?
- Why?
- Humor me.
Whoa, whoa.
- Wait. Wait a second, what was that?
- Help yourself.
Come on.
Son of a bitch.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Detective. ls everything okay?
Your, um...
Your buddy with the arrows
was at Russo's last night.
And I was there earlier with a date. So,
what, you think I'm the hood guy again?
Heh,no.
Your date. Helena Bertinelli.
If I were you, I'd stay away from her.
Her family is bad news on a good day.
Why the sudden concern
for my well-being?
A few weeks ago, I made a mistake.
I almost got you killed.
And you felt like you owed me one?
If I did, as far as I'm concerned,
this clears the books.
Can I talk to you? Dad.
MALCOLM: In case you haven't noticed,
I'm a little occupied at the moment.
I just talked to the accountant.
He said my accounts were frozen.
He said my credit cards
were all canceled.
MALCOLM: I pay Sandy a king's ransom
each year in fees, Tommy.
When it comes to money,
if he says it's so, it's so.
Do you think this is a joke?
MALCOLM:
No.
[PANTING]
You are.
Although, I must say,
your chronic irresponsibility...
...and terminal laziness
has lost its humor.
Heh.
You're wondering why now.
- The better question is why not sooner?
-It's...
-it's my trust fund.
- Which is comprised of my money.
Oh, excuse me.
Was comprised.
Helena.
- How did you find me here?
- I followed you from your house.
Your fiancé?
Yeah.
You said that losing him
was your crucible.
That it changed you.
You didn't say how.
When you love someone
as much as I loved him...
...with all of your heart...
...then you can't just turn that emotion
off when they're taken from you.
You still feel things as deeply.
And if it...
If it can't be love that you feel...
...then it becomes hate.
Hate for who?
Oliver.
You should stay away from me.
Helena.
Get in.
My father is going to kill you for this.
[CHUCKLES]
[GRUNTS]
I've been wanting to do that for years,
you spoiled bitch.
I knew it was someone from the inside
waging war against your father and me.
I just never thought it'd be this inside.
[SCOFFS]
You dropped this at Russo's.
You're smarter
than I gave you credit for, Nicky.
- You're not.
- Hey!
You're a businessman, right?
So let's talk business.
I can offer you a lot of money
if you let us go.
This isn't about money, Richie Rich.
This is about loyalty.
HELENA: He's got nothing to do
with any of this.
SALVATI: Then what the hell is it about?
- My father had Michael murdered.
[SALVATI CHUCKLES]
Of course he did.
He didn't want you to know the truth.
Your rat of a fiance
was gathering evidence.
He was talking to the frigging FBI.
The love of your life
was going to destroy your father.
You're wrong.
[GRUNTS]
We found a laptop in Michael's bag,
Helena.
Everything that could send your father
and me to prison...
...for the rest of our lives was on it.
- That computer--
- Was mine.
Michael wasn't the one
talking to the FBI. I was.
- You?
- My father is a monster...
...who doesn't care who he hurts
to keep his money and power.
And I wanted it to stop.
SALVATI: Well, then it's your fault
Michael's dead.
Not your father for ordering the hit
or me for carrying it out.
Yours.
You shot Michael?
In the chest. So he knew it was me.
Just like this.
[ALL GRUNTING AND GROANING]
You're gonna burn in hell.
It'll be worth it.
[PANTING]
Helena?
I didn't have a choice, Oliver.
No one can know my secret.
CSU didn't find any usable prints
except for the three victims'.
One of them had a GSW to the chest.
So who broke the necks
of Salvati and his buddy?
Look, it's been a while
since the hood broke anyone's neck.
And I didn't see any arrows
laying around.
Well, better pray that Frank Bertinelli
blames the hood for this.
Because if he thinks it's the Triad...
...Starling City is ground zero
to World War Ill.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
You Okay?
- Spoke to my dad today.
- I bet that was fun.
He explained to me what happened
with my credit card yesterday.
And my checking account,
my savings account...
...my brokerage account,
my stock portfolio.
He cut me off completely.
What?
My car got repossessed. That was fun.
And I have to move out of my apartment
by the end of the month.
You are gonna be fine, Tommy.
[SCOFFS]
In fact, you are gonna be great.
Merlyn money or not.
And, you know...
...I have a mushroom
and olive Mario pizza...
...in my refrigerator
waiting to be eaten.
- I suppose it's already paid for, right?
- Exactly.
- When did you get back?
- Just now.
[SIGHS]
- I'm so happy to see you.
- Hmm.
But did you come home only
because you heard I was hurt?
No.
I was already on my way
when Thea called.
I actually came home
because I missed my wife.
MOIRA:
It's okay.
- Is she all right?
- Walter's home.
She's gonna be fine.
Look, I'm sorry if I was a bitch
with you earlier.
There were a few times.
- Could you be more specific?
- Don't push it.
Don't worry. You weren't a bitch.
At the hospital, you were a little...
A little bit.
[CHUCKLES]
Look, I'm just worried about you.
You seem really lonely.
And we all have our secrets, Ollie.
Clearly you have yours.
And it's fine
if you don't wanna share them with us.
But I just really think you should
share them with someone.
I'd ask how you got in here...
...but the Starling City vigilante
comes and goes...
...as he pleases, doesn't he?
How'd you know?
I saw you fight.
And I saw your eyes.
That island changed you in ways that
only someone like me could understand.
No.
What you're doing right now...
...I know that it feels like justice,
but it's not.
-It's revenge.
- Sometimes revenge is justice.
- Your father killed your fiancé.
- And what did your father do to you?
Isn't the man in the hood
fighting to set things right?
Why is your vendetta more valid
than mine?
We're the same, you and I.
- No, we're not.
- Heh.
Hiding in plain sight.
Concealing our anger
with smiles and lies.
Don't lie to me, Oliver.
You feel the same as I do. I know it.
Why are you crying?
I don't know.
Maybe it's because I have been alone
in my hate for so long.
- It feels--
- So good to tell the truth.
[English - US - SDH]