[door closes]
[instrumental music]
[coughing]
Hey.
Oliver?
You're that vigilante.
Easy, Dig. You were poisoned.
Son of a bitch.
I could have taken you anywhere,
I could have taken you home.
I brought you here.
You really did lose your mind
on that island.
Found a couple things
along the way.
- Like what, archery classes?
- Clarity.
Starling City..
...is dying.
It is being poisoned
by a criminal elite
who don't care who they hurt
as long as they maintain
their wealth and power.
What are you gonna do?
Take 'em all down
by your lonesome?
No.
No, I want you to join me.
Special forces
out of Kandahar.
It's perfect.
You're a fellow soldier.
Oliver, you're not a soldier.
You're a criminal.
And a murderer.
[music continues]
[theme music]
Where were you?
What?
What are you doing here?
I heard about the shooting,
and I wanted to
make sure you were okay.
You did?
Yeah.
I knocked on the door,
and I found a family
terrified for you.
They had no idea where you were.
Oh.
Oliver, are you so self-centered
that you don't think
that people who care about you
are gonna wonder where you
are after you all got shot at?
You're right.
I made peace with your
selfishness a long time ago
but Moira, Thea, and Walter
they don't deserve that.
They deserve better.
Someone who doesn't care
only about himself.
Laurel.
Thank you for coming.
I care about the lives
of other people, Oliver.
Maybe you should try it
sometime.
[instrumental music]
Oh, man.
That was harsh.
You okay?
Sure.
Second time tonight,
that a friend of mine
has taken me to the woodshed.
It kind of tires you out.
Yeah.
Goodnight.
[bird chirping]
Shengcun.
What am I supposed
to do with that?
Shengcun.
Does that mean "Bird"?
-Shengcun!
- I don't speak Chinese!
I'm sorry, Laurel.
I'm so sorry.
[breathing heavily]
(man on TV)
'There were no signs
of forced entry'
'or any evidence
of a struggle'
'but hours later, the police
found a bloodstained'
'kitchen knife in the trunk..'
Couldn't sleep, either?
No.
What are you watching?
- Peter Declan.
- Hm?
A guy who killed his wife.
Right, this guy killed his wife
in their baby's room.
Psycho.
Camille was everything to me.
I couldn't kill her anymore
than I could kill myself.
And why can't you sleep?
Bad dreams.
About?
Laurel.
So why don't you make a play?
I mean, she did come over here
just to make sure
you didn't get shot.
- There are reasons.
- Mm, what are they?
Besides, you sleeping
with her sister
and her sister dying,
and her father hating your guts
and you basically,
being a jerk to everybody
since you've been back?
Those are the top ones.
I know that it might not seem
like it sometimes, but..
[instrumental music]
...I'm not the same person
I used to be.
So show her.
Be yourself.
I mean your new self.
How did you sleep?
- Just fine. Thank you.
- Hm.
- We have a visitor.
Mr. Diggle's replacement.
Replacement?
Yes. He tendered his resignation
this morning.
Did he say why?
He said he didn't approve
of the way you spend
your evenings.
Particularly given that
they always begin
with you ditching him.
- Hi.
- Mr. Queen.
Rob Scott.
I'll be your new body man.
That's a firm grip
you got there, Rob.
That's five years SWAT
with Monument Point MCU.
I feel safer already.
Ah, thank God,
we don't have to hear
about this awful man anymore.
'Declan's execution is set
for midnight two days from now.'
'Camille Declan's former
employer, Jason Brodeur'
'released a statement
saying, quote'
'"I hope this gives Camille
the peace she deserves."'
- Jason Brodeur?
- What?
The dead wife worked
for Jason Brodeur.
Apparently so. What..
Why?
No reason.
Say, Rob, I wanna go into town.
Could you please
get the car for me?
No offense, Mr. Queen,
but I have been filled in
on your tendency
to slip the leash.
If it's all the same to you,
I'd prefer
keeping you in my sights
at all times.
We're 20 miles from the city.
If you don't drive me
how else am I gonna get there?
Right?
I like him.
[instrumental music]
[bike revving]
Hey!
(Oliver)
They say Peter Declan
murdered his wife in
cold blood.
He had no alibi.
And all the evidence
pointed toward it.
He was tried, convicted,
sentenced to death.
An open-and-shut case,
except for one thing.
Declan's wife, Camille
worked for Jason Brodeur.
And Jason Brodeur
is on the list.
Mr. Brodeur.
Admiring your handiwork, Ankov.
You should have just let me
kill both of 'em.
Peter Declan
is worth more alive.
"Husband kills wife"
is a much better headline
than "Whistle-blower uncovers
toxic dumping," don't you think?
Either way, 48 hours,
all this'll be over.
(Oliver)
The odds are good
that Brodeur is involved
in this woman's murder,
which means
an innocent man
is facing execution.
He'll need a good attorney.
So, I take it
there's absolutely no point
in asking if you'd
like to grab a drink?
I can't,
I have to go over transcripts
for the Fernands case.
You know, if you go somewhere
that's not work or your home
your odds of meeting someone
increase by
like a gazillion percent.
Oh, that's not true.
I could still get mugged
on the way home.
I-In that case, I hope
he's cute and single.
Goodnight, Joanna.
[dramatic music]
Hello, Laurel.
Don't move!
I'm not gonna hurt you.
Stay back. My father's a cop.
You are making a huge mistake.
I'm not the person
you think I am.
'And I need your help.'
Peter Declan is gonna
be executed in 48 hours.
I think he's innocent.
'Declan's wife was gonna blow
the whistle on Jason Brodeur.'
'Brodeur had her murdered.'
There are a thousand lawyers
in Starling City.
Why me?
We're both trying to help.
What makes you so sure
I'm gonna help you?
Because I know
you'd do anything
to save the life
of an innocent man.
[music continues]
[bell ringing]
(Laurel)
'A jury has found you guilty,
Mr. Declan.'
The evidence
was stacked against me
but I didn't kill my wife.
I didn't take my daughter's
mother from her.
The murder weapon was a knife
from your kitchen,
with your prints on it.
'It was found,
along with Camille's blood'
'in the trunk of your car.'
Your neighbors said they heard
an argument that night.
We had a knockdown fight
over Jason Brodeur.
Camille worked for him,
and his company had been
dumping toxic waste
into the Glades.
Camille told me that she'd gone
and told a supervisor about it.
I was afraid
for my family's safety.
And we argued.
Very loudly. Yes.
Izzy started crying
so Camille went
and stayed in her room.
In the morning,
I went to apologize and uh..
And that's when I found her.
So I just grabbed Izzy
and I ran outside,
and I called 911.
I'm innocent, Ms. Lance.
Well, it looks like someone
forgot a lunch date
with his wife.
What do you mean?
Lunch isn't for another..
...forty-five minutes ago.
I'm so sorry.
It's alright. The restaurant
is holding our table.
Is there something wrong?
Compliance department
has tagged something
$2.6 million withdrawal
'from one of our
Vancouver subsidiaries.'
What, do you mean,
a-are you saying that someone
embezzled $2.6 million
from the company?
Well, it's probably
a bookkeeping error
but, compliance
is understandably
worried about an IRS audit.
Hm.
But don't worry.
I'm sure it's nothing.
Oh, come on.
We're gonna be late.
'I mean later.'
[indistinct chatter]
Well, I wasn't the lead on this
but from what I recall,
we had fingerprints.
We have blood.
We got motive, everything.
Brodeur seems like
the type of guy
with resources
needed to frame someone.
Laurel, in 24 hours,
Peter Declan is lying down
with a needle in his arm,
he's not getting up.
If I thought for a second,
we didn't have the right guy
do you think there's anything
else I'd be doing right now
except trying to get at
what really happened?
Declan said his wife
went to her supervisor
with allegations that Brodeur
was dumping toxic waste.
Yeah, but that supervisor
he said that never happened.
Let me see.
What was his name?
Here you go.
Istook, Matt Istook.
He said he didn't even
see Camille that day.
Happy now?
Yes.
You know, I thought
it'd be a cold day in hell
before you started
defending criminals.
I'm not so sure
Declan's a criminal.
Like you said,
he's on a clock.
Can't leave
any stone unturned.
Oh, yeah.
[instrumental music]
So when are you
gonna tell me?
Hm?
About what happened
to your arm.
Oh, it's my shoulder,
and it's, it's fine.
I knew that Queen guy
was trouble.
Hey, I never said
this happened protecting Queen.
(Carly)
'Oh, yeah?'
Then what's he doing here?
Area is secure, sir.
Thank you very much, Rob.
Hello, Diggle's
sister-in-law Carly.
I'm Oliver Queen.
- I know who you are.
- No, you really don't.
Hello.
I couldn't help but notice
a distinct lack of police cars
when I got home, I knew you
wouldn't drop a dime on me.
So..
...have you considered
my offer?
Offer? That's one hell
of a way to put it.
It is an offer.
It's a chance to do
the kind of good
that compelled you
to join the military.
Please.
You were born with a platinum
spoon in your mouth, Queen.
What, you spent five years on
an island with no room service
and suddenly you found religion?
This was my father's.
I found it when I buried him.
I thought you said your father
died when the boat went down.
We both made it to a life raft
but there wasn't enough
food and water
for both of us,
so he shot himself in the head.
And as much as he was doing it
to give me a chance to survive
I believe that he was also
atoning for his sins.
I need to right
the wrongs done by my family.
And I'm offering you the chance
to right the wrongs
done to yours.
Oliver, what are
you talkin' about?
The police never caught
your brother's shooter.
Hey, you leave Andy
out of this.
The bullets were laced
with curare.
That's Floyd Lawton's MO.
He is the sniper..
...that I stopped.
Are you trying to tell me that
you took down Andy's killer?
I'm..
I'm giving you the chance.
A chance
to help
other people's families.
Do you remember when the people
in this city helped each other?
They can't do that anymore
because a group of people..
...people like my father
they see nothing wrong
with raising themselves up
by stepping on
other people's throats.
It does need to stop
and if it's not
gonna be the courts
and it's not gonna
be the cops..
...then it's gonna be me.
And, I hope, you.
I'm gonna go
to the washroom, Rob.
[instrumental music]
Oh, that boy's long gone, man.
Phew.
You still following
the money trail?
Mm-hmm.
Don't we have accountants
for that sort of thing?
They're being singularly
ineffective in this instance.
Well, then..
...it's fortunate that
I've solved the mystery.
I think I'm the culprit.
$2.6 million
is a rather specific figure.
That's the exact amount
the company invested
in a friend's start-up venture
three years ago.
I will call accounting.
They'll clean it all up.
Then there's nothing
to worry about.
Okay.
You really are putting a lot
of hours into this Declan thing.
You actually think
he's innocent.
Someone does.
So you said..
...but you didn't say who.
The guardian angel.
The guy in the hood?
Look, you-you're kidding.
He tracked me down and asked me
to look into the Declan case.
But you've met him?
But he goes against everything
that I was ever taught
to believe in.
He breaks the law,
and God knows what else.
How are you not afraid
that he is gonna do
God knows what to you?
He won't.
I don't know. I can feel it.
You know, when I told you
to meet someone
this is far, far away
from what I meant.
I got your message.
Is there a reason
we can't do this face to face?
You've met with Peter Declan.
You were right.
He might be innocent.
Declan said his wife
blew the whistle on Brodeur
the day she was murdered.
Then we need to get whoever she
told about Brodeur to testify.
He already has.
Matt Istook.
Camille's supervisor.
Only, he says that she didn't
say a word to him.
He could be lying.
Well, if he is,
then he's very convincing.
He had the jury
and police believing him.
He hasn't been questioned by me.
'I didn't become a lawyer to
break the law, or hurt anybody.'
I do what's necessary
what people
like Peter Declan need.
If what you're doing
isn't wrong..
...then why are you
hiding your face with a hood?
To protect the ones
I care about.
That sounds lonely.
It can be.
But not today.
[intense music]
[elevator dings]
I've got one question.
Why am I being fired?
- Ms. Smoak, isn't it?
- Yes.
And I am without a doubt
the single most valuable member
of your technical division,
that's including
my so-called "Supervisor."
Letting me go would be
a major error for this company.
I agree, which is why
you're not being fired.
Uh, I assumed when
you brought me up here
it was because..
It's because I wanted you
to look into something for me.
The variance of $2.6 million
on a failed investment
from three years ago.
It was authorized by my wife.
I was hoping you could find out
some of the details
of the transaction for me.
- Find out...
- Dig up, discreetly.
I'm your girl.
I mean, I'm not your girl.
I wasn't making a pass at you.
Thank you for not firing me.
[door opens]
[car beeps]
[grunts]
What the..
[groaning]
Matt Istook.
You're him, that hood guy.
You're the guy that's been
terrorizing the city.
Peter Declan, your lies helped
put him on death row.
Now, either it's time
to tell me the truth
or it's time for the 10:15
to Bludhaven.
Oh!
Okay, okay, I-I..
Brodeur paid me t-to say
that Camille never spoke to me
but-but I didn't have anything
to do with her death.
Oh, God, please.
I-I'll do anything.
- Y-you can have the file.
- What file?
Camille gave me a file of
evidence against Jason Brodeur.
- Where is it?
- Let me go, and I'll tell you.
'Wait! Wait! Wait!
Don't go!'
Wait! Wait! Wait!
Don't go! It's in my desk!
The file, it's in my desk
at the office!
You can have it!
Get me out of here!
[train horn blaring]
What is that?
I'm so hungry.
It smells really good.
[screams]
[sighs]
Hey, fine. Don't share.
Hey.
[bird chirping]
(Yao Fei)
'Shengcun.'
I'm not gonna kill the bird.
Shengcun.
(Arrow)
'Compliments of Matt Istook.'
- What's in here?
- Leverage on Jason Brodeur.
'Enough to help save
Peter Declan's life.'
As an attorney, I never would
have gotten a file like this.
I always thought the law was
sacred, it, it fixed everything.
And now, Laurel?
Now what do you think?
I think there's
too many people in this city
who only care about themselves.
People who are selfish.
I think they need someone
who cares about the lives
of other people.
Someone like you.
♪ God give me your shelter ♪
[instrumental music]
Oh, my God.
- What is wrong with your face?
- What do you mean?
There's something
really weird on it
like this thing with your mouth
it, it looks like
it's in the shape of a smile.
- That's cute.
- So why are you grinning?
I took your advice with Laurel..
...to be myself.
- And..
- It's helping.
Got mad relationship
skills, bro.
Let me know if you need
trendy places to propose.
I think you're getting
a little bit ahead of yourself.
- Mm.
- Little bit.
Rob.
You gotta keep up.
[instrumental music]
Hey, you look busy.
'Is that the Declan case?'
'You know, it was a funny
development on that'
Matt Istook, he, uh,
filed a police report.
He said the Hood
harassed him last night.
'And that's funny, because'
I gave my daughter
Istook's name.
- Dad...
- He's a vigilante.
He's a damn criminal.
And you working with him,
that makes you an accessory.
I am trying to save
an innocent man's life.
No.
You're breaking the law.
Well, I wouldn't have to,
if the police would have done
their job right in
the first place.
I asked you
how you got this case.
You lied to me,
straight to my face.
Eh?
I thought you and I
didn't do that.
Guess I was wrong.
Your Honor, the mere existence
of the file proves that
Mr. Istook perjured himself
for Jason Brodeur's benefit.
That's slander.
Jared Swanstrom, Your Honor.
I represent Jason Brodeur
and Brodeur Chemical.
The interest of justice
requires you to stay
the defendant's execution
pending exploration
'of the newly discovered
evidence.'
Ours isn't a court of justice,
Ms. Lance.
'It's a court of law.'
And under the law,
I don't think your evidence
is sufficient to warrant
a stay of execution.
'Your motion for
habeas corpus is denied.'
This isn't over.
I've got the loose end now
and no matter what happens,
I am going to pull on it
until your whole world unravels.
(Jason)
Declan's lawyer is
pulling me into this.
I'm gonna go to prison
if not for murder, then
this-this this dumping thing.
That won't happen.
There are steps we can take.
You saw her.
She's going after me.
She's gonna want to meet
with her client
after what happened
in court today.
'We have friends
up in Iron Heights.'
Prison can be a dangerous place.
We're not done yet.
I'm an attorney. Trust me.
We're done.
What do you need
to free Peter Declan?
At this point
nothing short of a signed
confession from Brodeur.
- Where are you going?
- To get a confession.
The company Mrs. Queen,
or Steele.
Mrs. Queen-Steele.
She hyphenate?
She seems like a woman
who would hyphenate.
[clears throat]
Right, the company she invested
in doesn't exist.
- I don't understand.
- There was no investment.
The money was used to set up
an offshore LLC called Tempest.
I don't recall
that name being under
the Queen Consolidated banner.
'Cause it's not,
there's nothing registered
with the Secretary of State.
'No federal tax records'
'no patent applications filed.'
But, in 2009
Tempest purchased a warehouse
in Starling City.
[dramatic music]
- Enough moping.
- Mm.
You quit. It's done.
My advice would be to move on.
Uh, if it were only that easy.
Except it is.
Personal security is dangerous.
Your nephew already
lost his father.
He can't lose his uncle too.
Does it ever bother you
they never caught the guy
who killed Andy?
You know,
when I was in Afghanistan
I had a job, and I did it.
And when I could, I would help
out the people there
so that, in some small way,
when I left
I could believe
I left it a better place.
But ever since I've been home
all I do is protect punks
and spoiled one percenters.
Yeah.
I miss feeling like I'm making
a difference in the world.
Then get out
of personal security
and go do something
you believe in.
- Yeah, what if it's wrong?
- John.
If you believe in something
how can it be wrong?
- 'Jason Brodeur'
- What do you want?
You're gonna confess
that you arranged
to have Peter Declan's wife
murdered.
What, so I can take his place
in prison?
So you can avoid
the death penalty.
Except if I'm dead.
Well, then, you've got no one
to pin Camille's murder on.
'You need me
to exonerate Peter Declan.'
Maybe you could try to force me
to sign a confession
or something.
[screams]
That might be difficult.
[telephone ringing]
'My hand!'
[groaning]
Just answer it.
- What?
- 'It's Ankov.'
'It's going down, one hour.'
What's going down in an hour?
What?
Let's just say..
...Peter Declan's execution
it's getting moved up.
[grunts]
(Laurel)
'Okay, you have to
listen to me.'
We still have a shot.
Do you remember
the friend that I mentioned
the one who believes in you?
He is working on something.
[dramatic music]
I told you
Jason Brodeur is powerful.
Time to unlock the cages.
I've been here before.
These lawyers, holding out
these little nuggets of hope.
[siren blaring]
[indistinct chatter]
What?
(male #1)
'Secure all corners
in cell block C.'
The warden's setting up
a secure perimeter in C block.
'Stay here, Ms. Lance.'
Wait!
[indistinct chatter]
[instrumental music]
[grunting]
[panting]
[screams]
Let's go.
Go, go, go!
Ah!
[grunting]
[panting]
- Open up the generator area.
- Area clear.
Laurel.
(male #2)
'That's right. Stay back.
Area secured.'
(male #3)
'Movin' out.'
[indistinct radio chatter]
Oh, Laurel.
Sweetie.
What are you..
- I'm all right.
- You sure?
I'm sorry about
what I said to you.
You were right, Brodeur's
bodyguard just confessed
to Camille Declan's murder.
We got the wrong guy.
Now, listen to me, Laurel.
I'm right too about him.
He's dangerous.
- He's outside the law.
- I know.
He's a killer.
He would have killed that man.
'I looked in his eyes.'
'It's like he had no remorse.'
Hey.
Please.
I'm starving.
I never killed anything before.
[bird chirping]
[dramatic music]
I'm sorry.
[bird shrieks]
(Quentin)
'Let's get you home, sweetie.'
How'd he get into
that prison anyway, huh?
A grown man in an outfit,
and a hood
that kind of stands out
a little, doesn't it?
He actually wasn't
wearing the outfit this time.
He was in a prison-guard uniform
and a ski mask.
- What?
- 'Nothing.'
I just had an idea.
'Get in the car.'
[door beeps]
[door opens]
[instrumental music]
Okay.
Here's the security footage from
the Exchange building shooting
but I've already scrubbed
through all of it.
Yeah? Well,
we're gonna do it again.
So, listen, when you went
through the camera
security tapes,
you were looking for a guy
in a green outfit
and a green hood, right?
What do you want me to look for
a man in a wig and a tutu?
I want you to look for anything
that's out of the ordinary.
Okay? Just look.
Hey, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Wait. Wait. Go back ten seconds.
What is that?
'I'll be damned.'
Play that again.
- Thank you, Laurel.
- Don't thank me.
Thank Brodeur's bodyguard
Ankov for flipping him.
'I think there's someone
that wants to see you.'
Izzy.
(man on TV)
'At least five federal, state,
and local agencies'
'are seeking millions of dollars
in fines'
'and environmental
cleanup costs'
'from Brodeur Chemical.'
'New facts have come to light'
'that Brodeur Chemical employee,
Camille Declan'
'had discovered Brodeur
was illegally disposing waste'
'and had collected
a file of evidence'
'against her employer,
before her murder in 2007.'
'Peter Declan, who was
convicted of killing his wife'
'has been released,
and the case has been reopened.'
Shengcun.
Yeah.
Bird. I know.
Shengcun not mean "bird."
Shengcun mean "survive."
You speak English?
You want survive this place
bird not last thing you kill.
And forget her.
'You look at that all day'
you not survive this place.
[dramatic music]
You wanted to see me?
You look nervous, Moira.
Do I have a reason to be?
We all do.
A modern-day Robin hood.
What, are you worried that your
net worth makes you a target?
Jason Brodeur.
Adam Hunt.
Warren Patel.
Tell me you see a connection,
Moira.
He's not targeting the rich.
'No, he's not.'
He's targeting the list.
(Oliver)
'You here
for the bodyguard position?'
'Cause the new guy just quit.
No, I'm not.
I'm here about
the other position.
Just to be clear..
...I'm not signing on
to be a sidekick.
But you're right.
Fighting for this city
needs to be done
and you're gonna do this
with or without me.
Yeah.
But with me,
there'll be fewer casualties
including you.
Diggle, I'm not looking
for anybody to save me.
Maybe not..
...but you need someone
just the same.
'You are fighting a war, Queen'
'except you have no idea
what war does to you'
how it scrapes off
little pieces of your soul.
And you need someone
to remind you
of who you are
not this thing you're becoming.
- 'Oliver Queen.'
- What is this?
- You can't just barge in here.
- Yeah?
Well, I got a badge and a gun
that say different.
- What the hell's going on?
- Oliver, what's happening?
You're under arrest on suspicion
of obstruction of justice.
- Aggravated assault...
- Walter, stop them!
Trespassing,
acting as a vigilante..
Are you out of your mind?
...and murder.
You have the right
to remain silent.
'If you give up that right..'
[theme music]
(male #4)
'Greg, move your head.'