My name is Oliver Queen.
After 6 months in hell,
I have been released from
prison and returned home
with only one goal...
To save my city,
but things have changed.
Instead of operating outside the law,
I am now working alongside the police.
I am no longer inmate 4587.
I am once more...
The Green Arrow.
Previously on "Arrow"...
There's always gonna be another Dante.
There's always gonna be a
logical reason to compromise,
but I'm not doing that anymore.
- Walking away is not the answer.
- Well, I'm not walking away.
I'm gonna call my own shots.
I went to go check your
midterm results online,
and I didn't come
across any test results
because you didn't take the exams.
- Why?
- Because I got expelled.
CONNOR: So you found this place
by watching that documentary?
BLACKSTAR: Vigilantes were
the death of Star City,
and they got exactly what they deserved.
We now have unfettered access
to the Archer Program's
entire security interface.
Let's find those bombs.
_
[BEEP BEEP]
- Heading home soon?
- Not quite yet.
I'll see you in the morning.
_
What's it say?
Nothing.
Just some punk kid pulling a prank.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
FELICITY: You ever get in
trouble with your parents?
Uh, yeah. All the time. Why?
Because William doesn't need pancakes.
William needs to tell
us why he got expelled
and why he's been lying to us.
- After pancakes or...
- No.
Okay.
- Ready to talk?
- About what?
Why you got expelled.
Come on, Will. You know you can talk
to us about anything. Please.
It's not a big deal. I
just got into a fight.
I thought you'd be proud of me.
I went for the nose
just like you told me.
When did you tell him
to go for the nose?
That was over a year ago,
and it was a lesson in
self-defense, thank you.
Buddy, it's not like
you to get into a fight.
Why do you guys even care?
Every time that we
spoke, you're telling me
how much you love your school,
about your new friends and your classes.
What am I missing here?
Maybe you should have
asked how I felt for once,
but you don't ask other
people for their opinions.
You decide everything on your own
just like you decided to go to prison
rather than take care of your family!
I don't think that's fair, but okay.
William, you got expelled,
and, young man, you need to understand
that in life you have
to accept responsibility
for your actions.
Yeah? I'm over this.
W-William. Hey.
William, we're not done here.
[SIGHS]
That went well.
Damn it! Still no luck figuring out
where Felicity planted those bombs.
Well, I'm pretty sure
hitting that thing harder's
not gonna make it work better.
Makes me feel better, though.
The Archer Program's
supposed to see everything,
but what good's that when
there's nothing to see?
[FOOTSTEPS]
About damn time.
Your algorithm kind of sucks.
Ah. Nice to see you, too. Give it to me.
Archer's not helping us, and that means
Blackstar's our only lead
on finding those bombs.
You guys have any
luck tracking her down?
Uh-uh. I spent the last few
days searching the entire city,
but she knows how to be a ghost.
Pretty easy to do with
the way the city is now.
Okay. My algorithm isn't the problem.
The Archer Program was
designed to monitor The Glades,
but Star City is 10 times the size
with half the technological
infrastructure.
So less eyes covering a larger area.
Even if that's the case,
that bomb plan was massive.
We should have found something.
Well, not if the bombs
haven't been positioned yet.
I mean, maybe Felicity stockpiled them
somewhere off the grid,
somewhere no one would
ever think to look.
I think I might know a place.
ZOE: This is definitely off the grid.
WILLIAM: God. I used to
think this place was so cool.
DINAH: I can't believe
it's still standing.
I can't believe my dad
used to call this home.
Yeah. Well, no one's called
this home for quite some time.
Someone's been here.
[DARTS WHOOSHING]
Unh!
BLACKSTAR: Someone's still here.
I told you this wouldn't end well.
What's that, some A.R.G.U.S. fan mail?
No, not exactly.
Oh. This is some "I know what
you did last summer" creepiness.
- You want me to run a DNA trace?
- No. Already on top of that.
Besides, that's not the reason
why I called you in here.
How's the search for Dante coming?
Good. We were able to backtrace
the number Diaz called.
It belongs to Dante's contact in
Egypt, a guy by the name of Virgil.
If we're able to bring
him in, we'll have Dante.
Fantastic! And we would
have you to thank for it.
Excellent work, Curtis.
Too bad I might not be
around for my victory lap.
What are we talking about here?
There's no good way to say this,
but I've been offered a job at the
Kohler Humanitarian Institute in D.C.
I would be able to create
tech that would be able
to help people all over the world.
Curtis, I know you're not
happy with the Ghost Initiative,
but I was hoping that
we could get past that.
Besides, the work you're
doing right here at A.R.G.U.S.
is already helping
people all over the world.
I know you believe that, John.
I'm just not sure that I do.
The key is to maintain eye contact.
Your assailant's gonna
focus on your weakness.
In this case, it's that injury.
So you draw them in,
and as soon as they're
close enough, strike.
Yeah! That's very good.
Eh, you're a natural.
Thanks for teaching me, aunt Dinah.
It's so cool learning how to
kick ass from the Black Canary.
RENE: Keep kicking the
crap out of that shield,
and Captain Drake's gonna
have to deputize you, too.
How about you keep practicing
your kicks in your room?
- Okay.
- Good job.
I saw the way you looked
when Zoe mentioned the Black Canary.
You still adjusting to being outed?
Well, it was one thing when all
the people in our Inner Circle
knew about my secret identity,
but now everybody knows,
the cops at SCPD, everybody.
I don't know. Maybe I'm just worried
people are gonna treat me differently
now that the secret's out.
Yeah. Well, maybe it's a
good idea that me and the team
are gonna be hanging
out at the SCPD for now
in case I got to crack some heads.
Oh. Thanks.
Hey. Ever since you became captain,
you've been busting your ass
to earn their trust and respect,
so you keep doing what you're doing
and don't sweat the haters
because they're gonna hate
like... whoever left me this.
- When did you get this?
- Last night.
Figured it was some punk-ass pranking me
for working with you and the SCPD.
- Oh, damn.
- What, did you get one, too?
And so did Laurel. We've been
trying to track down who did it.
We thought maybe it was about
a case we worked together,
but if you're getting them, too...
Who knows who his next target is?
[FLOORBOARD CREAKING]
Ohh!
Get back!
What the hell? I can't move.
Oh. Stop! Please just stop.
I'll give you anything you want.
Why are you doing this?
_
Wow! This is a lot of blood.
I thought Kullens was
in jail for helping Diaz.
JOHN: Yeah. Well, apparently,
he had a very good lawyer
because he got out a month ago.
Any chance this connects
with the two body drops
we were looking at last week?
Kullens did have his throat
slit, same as the other two.
I mean, the only
difference is that Kullens
was the only victim to leave
behind one of these notes.
Look familiar?
I spoke to the families
of the other victims,
and they did get notes, as well.
- They just didn't turn them in.
- Right.
This is turning out to be one
hell of a first day on the job.
Yeah. Look at us,
working together again,
being targeted by a homicidal maniac.
Feels like a Monday.
What about Laurel?
You said that she got a note, too.
She did, but she's fine. She's
at a conference in D.C. all week.
JOHN: Okay. So wait. You, me,
Laurel, Rene all got notes.
- Curtis and Oliver didn't.
- Oh, don't worry about me.
I'm definitely not feeling FOMO over it.
Well, we already know this killer's
not only targeting people on the team.
Kullens was against vigilantes,
and we didn't even know
the other two victims.
There has to be a connection.
We just... be patient,
and we'll find it.
Maybe this will help.
- Kullens' autopsy report.
- DINAH: Thank you.
Tox screen is clear.
No defensive wounds.
So he didn't fight back.
This M.O. feels very familiar.
When I was undercover in Central City,
the guys in homicide were
chasing after a serial killer
with a very similar pattern...
Throat slash and victims
who didn't fight back.
I'm gonna give Captain Singh a call.
Wakey, wakey, money bags.
Unh!
[COUGHS, GASPS]
Touch me, I'll bite your hand off.
Almost makes me forget
that you're nothing
but a pampered girl from The Glades
playing vigilante dress-up.
WILLIAM: What do you want?
The access codes to Archer.
ZOE: Go to hell.
Well, let's try this another way.
Wait! Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
The access codes now.
Keep your mouth shut, William.
So that's your name.
All right, William. What the
hell are you even doing here?
Funny. I was just about
to ask you the same thing.
Ooh. Is that a backbone I'm seeing?
Even if we give you the codes,
you're just gonna kill us
just like you killed Felicity
and just like you're gonna
kill the rest of the city,
so what is the point in talking?
Someone is trying to blow
up the city, but it's not me,
and I sure as hell didn't kill Felicity.
Then who did?
About what you said,
about wanting to do something different.
Okay. Suddenly, I'm getting
nervous about where this is going.
No need.
Just talked with Lyla, and we both agree
that, Curtis, we cannot afford
to lose a talent like yours,
so A.R.G.U.S. wants to make you
the head of its science
and technology division.
You want me in charge
of the entire division?
The entire division.
You'll be shaping the future
of A.R.G.U.S., Curtis,
and you can make all the
decisions just like you wanted.
- I don't know what to say.
- Say you'll do it, man.
Just stay here in Star City.
You can keep working with the team.
I think it's the best of both worlds.
Think about it.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Captain Singh, thank you
for getting back to me.
I'd have done it sooner,
but some new metahuman freak
sent a bunch of Central
City's finest to the hospital
before the Flash and his
team were able to stop them,
not that there's anything
wrong with metahumans.
No disrespect intended, Dinah.
Well, none taken. Heh.
And here I was just starting
to feel like I had a handle
on this whole captain thing.
Do you remember when
Blockbuster and his gang
tried to expand their operations
from Blüdhaven to Central City?
And almost started a turf war
with all the major crime families?
- Yeah.
- But it didn't,
all because one undercover cop
had the balls and the brains
to infiltrate their ranks
and prevent a citywide bloodbath.
If anyone knows how to win
hearts and minds, Dinah, it's you.
You just have to have faith in yourself.
I certainly do.
So about that case file.
Your father is gonna make
his famous chili tonight.
Does he really think making
dinner is gonna solve everything?
I mean, it's his chili
we're talking about.
I'm pretty sure it
could solve world peace.
- Let me see that.
- It's impossible.
Actually, solving a
Rubik's Cube is a lot
like running an algorithm.
In fact, my favorite pattern is a cube
within a cube.
- That's pretty cool.
- Yeah. Thanks.
COMPUTER: The Green Arrow has
entered through the front door.
Heh heh heh.
- The Green Arrow?
- You know, I thought I'd give
the security system
a little personality.
Hey, buddy.
Help me unpack these bags.
I'm good.
Okay. Give you two a moment alone.
Give me those. Thank you.
William, I understand why
you were mad at me before.
You have every right
to be mad at me, okay?
You're a tough kid.
And I forget sometimes
that you are just a kid...
That's lived in 4 different
cities over the past 2 years.
That's tough. One of the many reasons
why Felicity and I think
that you should come back here
and live with us.
COMPUTER: Warning, warning.
Unidentified person at the front door.
Did you...
Mr. and Mrs. Clayton?
What are you doing here?
Our grandson called us.
Okay. I apologize. I
understand and appreciate
why after everything that's happened
you two might be worried,
but we can assure you
that... that going forward
things will be better
and more stable, okay?
- They will be...
- Right.
Because we're taking him with us.
We're filing a suit for guardianship.
No. You can't do that.
William, we need to speak
with your grandparents alone.
Oliver, it's an open-and-shut case.
You're a convicted felon.
You were absent for most of his life,
and then once you showed up... heh...
He's kidnapped, he's sent
into hiding from a mob boss.
I'm his father, Frank.
By blood maybe,
but you are not fit to
be William's guardian,
either of you.
We should have done
this a long time ago.
FRANK: Yes, dear.
It's what Samantha would
have wanted for him.
William is my son. Felicity treats
and cares for him like a son,
and nobody...
is gonna take him away from us.
No one.
ROY: I hate tranqs.
Where are the others?
Hey, you! Where are our friends?
They're with Blackstar.
Hey. She's got questions to ask.
What about us?
I already know everything
I need to about you,
and you guys should
have stayed out of this.
Wait. I recognize you.
You know him?
And so do you. You're Connor Hawke,
John Diggle's son.
[THUNDER]
Thank you, Dinah.
Call me if you need anything, okay?
All right.
Can I speak with you for a moment?
Why? Sounds like you got
to go save the city again.
William, get over here and sit down.
[THUNDER]
[SIGHS]
What?
Your grandparents are trying
to take you away from me.
There is no chance that
that's gonna happen,
but I cannot... I cannot
have you phoning for backup
every time that you're mad at me.
It's the only thing
that got you to listen!
You think I'm not listening?
I have heard and felt
every single terrible thing
that you've said to me
since you've been back!
Come on. I'm... I'm trying my best.
That's the problem because
whenever you're around,
things always get worse!
You want to give me a normal life?
Yes! That's all I've ever tried to do!
That's why I... That why I've asked you
to come back here and
live with Felicity and I.
That isn't a normal life! I want
to go live with my grandparents!
Eight murders over
the course of 2 months.
And this is definitely the
same guy we're dealing with?
Yeah. Analysis of the wound
confirms the same angle of entry
in all the murders here
and in Central City.
The question is why pack
up and bring the fun here?
Yeah. That really is the missing
piece of the puzzle, isn't it?
Doesn't seem to be
any obvious connection
between the victims.
Actually, maybe there is.
They all had elevated levels
of magnesium in their blood.
But their tox screens came back clear.
Well, that's because increased
magnesium alone isn't a red flag,
but if you combine that with
decreased levels of red blood cells,
then you have a drug called mivacurium.
It's a neuromuscular blocking agent.
Captain Singh said it looked like
the victims had been immobilized.
It's because they had been drugged.
Mivacurium is extremely rare.
In fact, there's only been
one shipment in the past month
to Star City to a condemned
house in The Glades
addressed to a John Doe.
[THUNDER]
- Hey, don't, Curtis.
- Why not?
RENE: What if someone spots
that thing flying around?
Might as well have a freaking neon sign
that says, "Hey, murderer. We're here."
[SLAM]
You were saying, Rene?
Curtis, Rene, you take upstairs.
Me and Dinah will secure down here.
Split up? What? Have you guys
never seen a horror movie before?
Wait, Rene!
[FLOORBOARDS CREAKING]
[THUNDER]
[PLAYS LOW NOTE]
[GASPS]
[THUNDER]
[DOOR SQUEAKS]
[MUSIC BOX PLAYING]
Rene.
Don't sneak up on me like that!
Sorry. What was that?
Our psycho was at Slabside?
[DOOR SQUEAKS]
[THUNDER]
[CLATTER]
Hyah!
Unh!
[GAGGING]
You should have listened to me.
- JOHN: Dinah.
- CURTIS: Dinah, where are you?
JOHN: Dinah, I need you
to copy. Can you hear me?
Dinah, where are you?
- RENE: Oh!
- CURTIS: Oh, my God.
Dinah. Have to stop the bleeding.
RENE: We have to call an ambulance.
They won't get here in time.
You're gonna be fine. D!
It's too deep. There's nothing I can do.
- RENE: What?!
- CURTIS: Maybe there's something I can do.
I've been working on a new prototype...
Mid-infrared lasers that might
be able to cauterize the wound.
- Might or will?
- I don't know,
but the only way to bond the
cut is by burning it first.
- I've never tested it, though!
- Do it! Do it!
Okay.
- Tell me when.
- When.
[GROANING]
Okay. Done.
There's a pulse.
You did it.
Be strong, Dinah.
[THUNDER]
[SIGHS]
I take it by the way that
you're treating the chili
that your talk didn't go so well.
He wants to go live
with his grandparents.
- And you think that's...
- I think it's ridiculous
because we're his family and
we are what's best for him!
Sorry.
Well, we've all grown and changed a lot
since you got out of Slabside,
and I've been thinking
that maybe you and I
need to think more
about what William needs.
You need to tell me...
If you honestly believe that he
would be better off away from us.
I think that now that you're working
with the SCPD and Team Arrow again
that we don't exactly provide
a life of normalcy and...
I just want to be a better father
for him than my father was for me.
You already are by giving him
the life that he deserves...
Even if it breaks our hearts.
[THUNDER]
If you didn't kill
Felicity, then who did?
No one. Felicity's still alive.
How do you know that?
I just do.
It's why I need Archer...
To find Felicity.
Don't listen to her. She's a liar.
She'll say anything to...
You didn't need to do that.
No, but I enjoyed it.
[SCOFFS]
Now... how about those codes?
Only after you tell me why
you're looking for Felicity.
Let's just say we owe each other.
What I don't get is you.
You're no hero wannabe
like the rest of them.
You're obviously well off,
enough to not slum around Star City.
So what are you getting out of this?
Honestly... I don't know.
Closure maybe, to ask Felicity
why she disappeared from my life
only to contact me now out of the blue.
What, did you guys date or something?
God, no. I'm gay, and she's my mom.
Stepmom.
Oliver Queen is your father?
Did you get anything out of them?
You're supposed to be
watching the others.
Unh! Agh!
Hyaaah!
[GRUNTING]
CONNOR: Hyaaah!
- Brace yourself.
- What?
Aah!
Roy!
- Ugh!
- Drop the bow.
WILLIAM: You first.
[COCKS GUN]
JOHN: Called the ambulance.
They're on their way.
They'll be here any minute.
- Shh, shh, shh.
- D., D., relax.
Help's on the way.
You don't have to talk.
[GASPING] Oliver. Ohh. Oliver.
Oliver.
What the hell?
Slabside. We found a uniform
upstairs in the closet.
This guy must have been
in prison with Oliver.
So all of this, the
notes, the murders...
[THUNDER]
It's about Oliver.
Mmm. Sure beats our suppers
in Hope Springs, hey, William?
Except when we ate there,
I could actually see my food.
Yeah. I'm sure they're working
on getting the power back on soon.
This storm is crazy.
I thought my chili
was your favorite, bud.
- It's too spicy.
- What are you talking about?
It's perfect. It's absolutely delicious.
In fact, I will have seconds if
you could pass me some more, please.
I can't.
Felicity...
I can't really move.
FELICITY: I can't either.
What's that sound?
[GAS HISSING]
Dad, what's going on?
[THUNDER]
Don't worry, Oliver. It's me.
I'm just really happy
to see you guys again.
It's so nice to meet you, William.
I'm Stanley Dover.
I'm your dad's best friend.
Stanley, don't hurt my son.
Hurt him? I don't want
to hurt any of you.
I... I just need to talk.
That's why I gave you the medicine...
So you would listen to me.
What kind of medicine?
Don't worry. Its effects are temporary.
I used to take this stuff
all the time when I was a kid.
My dad was a doctor.
Said you want to talk, Stanley.
What do you want to talk about?
I just have to warn you
because those people, they
don't understand you like I do.
You can't believe
anything that they said.
Which people?
The people that call
themselves your friends.
I've been sending them warnings,
but they haven't listened.
FELICITY: Warnings?
What kind of warnings? Like, notes?
Yeah.
You're the Star City Slayer.
Err! Don't call me that.
I'm... I'm sorry. Oliver, I'm sorry.
I just really hate that name.
Look. No tricks this time, okay?
I just really need you to listen to me.
Okay. All right, Stanley,
but this is between us...
So I need you to let my wife and son go.
I can't because there's people
out there that want to hurt you,
who want to hurt all of you.
If you knew the things that
I had to do to protect you.
But I know that you would
do the same thing for me.
I... I like that you're
working with the police.
Not everybody does.
There's people out there that are saying
bad things about you.
They want to hurt you.
Like that councilman
that works with Diaz.
Some people don't deserve to live.
Come on, Stanley.
My teammates would never hurt me.
But they're still bad for you,
worse even because they
don't understand you,
they don't understand you like I do,
and I only had time
to correct one of them.
"Correct" them?
The police captain.
The Black Canary.
What did you do to her?
It doesn't matter
because we're together now,
and we can go somewhere
new and be a new team!
But I don't know about her
because I don't think
that she's been listening.
OLIVER: Hey, Stanley!
She's... she's listening.
Just a little scared, all right?
Sure. I used to be scared
when my dad gave me medicine.
He gave me medicine whenever I was bad
or I didn't listen,
and so when I couldn't move
and when I had to listen,
then he would correct me.
Your dad used to hurt you?
He was just doing what he
thought was right for me.
My mother thought so, too.
My older brother, he
tried to protect me,
tried to take my punishments for me,
but it only made it worse.
I couldn't take it anymore,
and I gave my parents some medicine.
I corrected them.
Everybody's got to get
back at their parents
sometimes, right, William?
Right, buddy?
Stanley, you said your brother.
Where's your brother now?
When he found out what I did for him,
he got upset.
I don't know why.
He wanted to send me to Arkham Asylum,
so I had to give him some medicine, too.
I needed to correct him.
You killed your own brother?
I didn't have a choice.
If he just listened to me,
then I wouldn't have had to do it,
and none of this would have happened...
But I'm starting to think
that you're not listening
to me either, Oliver.
I can tell!
And you should have... You
should have apologized to me
for being mean to me at Slabside,
but you haven't, so
I'm starting to think
that you're just like everybody else
and you don't deserve
my... my protection.
[THUNDER]
I'm sorry that you
feel that way, Stanley.
FELICITY: You're exactly
like your father, Stanley.
You're wrong. I'm nothing like him.
You're right, you're right.
You're worse.
You're the Star City Slayer.
I told you I hate that name!
William.
Agh!
Are you all right?
We are now.
[GROANS]
Hey. Dinah's in surgery now.
Doctors say she'll be fine,
although they're not too
sure about her voice yet.
Dover's been picked up by SCPD.
They're transferring him
back to Slabside tomorrow.
FELICITY: How many
times has he done this?
At least 3 that we know of.
It always involves some
older brother figure,
someone he admires.
Stanley starts off by
killing those he thinks
are bad for them and not just enemies
but friends, as well.
Tries to impress them,
tries to endear himself,
and when that doesn't work,
they become his next target.
You guys okay, though?
So far, so good. If there's any trace
of the drugs left in our
system, the doctors will find it
in the gallons of blood
they just siphoned from us.
I'm gonna go check on William
and get him discharged.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
This is A.R.G.U.S. We have to go.
Actually, John, uh...
You are taking the position in D.C.
Look. I know that A.R.G.U.S.
does a lot of good,
but I'll never agree with
them on how they do it.
You have to do what's right for you,
but I am gonna miss you, Curtis.
I'm gonna miss you, too.
Sorry I didn't tell you. Just
with everything going on...
Eh, Rene already gave you up.
I was kind hoping more for "Boo-hoo.
I'll miss you so much.
You're my other half
I'll never replace."
Yeah, but I'm really happy that you're
finally doing what you want.
I think it's time you do the same.
- Yeah.
- I talked to my lawyer.
They're gonna draw up
some legal documents.
I'm signing over sole
ownership of Helix to you.
You don't have to do that.
I want to.
Helix was your idea,
and I love working with you,
but it feels like you're struggling
to find your purpose, too.
Yeah.
Maybe this is it.
Maybe this is how Felicity
Smoak will change the world.
Well, you are right.
I am really gonna miss you.
[SNIFFLES]
Hey.
Are we going home?
Well, that depends.
Do you want to go home?
What do you mean?
I mean you were right
that I never asked you what you wanted.
So I'm asking now.
Would you like to come home
and live with us?
Or do you want to go and
live with your grandparents?
I just want a normal life.
I want that for you, too.
I thought I could...
Provide that for you...
Especially since, um, you know,
I've been unmasked.
After what happened
tonight, I see that, um...
Normal may never be a real possibility.
I don't want you to stop being a hero.
I know the city needs you.
I just think for at least now,
it might be better for
me to be in Central City.
Okay.
Then that's what we'll do.
It gets really cold there in the winter,
so I'm gonna send you, like, 3 coats
and mitts and a hat.
You're definitely gonna need a hat.
Ohh.
I'll miss you so much.
I'm gonna miss you, too.
Listen here, young man.
Wherever you are, I'm
always gonna be your dad.
So we'll talk all the time... ahem...
And I promise to come and visit
whenever it's cool with you
and with your grandparents.
[SWALLOWS]
You just have to promise that you...
You will call me...
If you need anything,
anything, you will call me, okay?
- I will.
- You have a home
with the two of us in Star City forever.
I love you, William.
I love you, too, dad.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Hi. Dr. Schwartz, is everything okay?
Oh, good. I thought it was
gonna be one of those calls
where you say, "Everything
spread to the liver," and...
I'm what?
You can't win this.
ZOE: Drop the damn knife.
Come on! Don't give me a
reason to pull this trigger.
You're not gonna shoot me.
[KNIFE CLANGS ON FLOOR]
You sure about that?
Yeah...
Because my name is Mia Smoak.
I'm Felicity's daughter
and your sister.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --