My name is Oliver Queen.
After five years in hell,
I returned home with only one goal,
to save my city.
Today, I fight that war on two fronts.
By day, I lead Star City as its mayor.
But by night, I am someone else.
I am something else.
I am the Green Arrow.
Previously on Arrow...
Zoe's in a foster home.
A good one, it looks like.
She shouldn't be anywhere near me.
I don't agree with that. I have
a lawyer friend who doesn't, either.
I'm worried about you.
Because you're into something,
and you don't want to
tell anyone about it.
You just have to trust me on this one.
If we can produce video
that Chase is Prometheus,
that's game over for him.
That is what we needed.
Please let me be the one
to walk this into SCPD.
I'm gonna throw it up on YouTube.
There won't be anywhere
that son of a bitch can run.
Delta Team in position.
Seems our friends are here, too.
We're on site.
An A.R.G.U.S. drone confirms Adrian Chase
walked into the arcade at 0900.
Sixteen hours ago.
That's a lifetime for Chase.
Yeah, but no one has entered
or exited since.
We got the bastard.
We have to move right now.
See something?
Yes. This is Maximum Force. It's vintage.
We cannot let anything happen to this.
I'm more worried about
something happening to me.
Will you two focus?
Incoming!
Is everybody okay?
It was vintage.
Looks like we found our guy.
Chase escaped the arcade by using
a secret tunnel that led to Port Newark.
Homeland Security's placed him
on a no-fly list.
No, he's not gonna leave the country.
He isn't done yet.
How do you know?
Call it a hunch.
"A hunch"? Mayor Queen,
this city deserves better than a hunch.
Excuse the interruption.
I can't hold them off any longer.
All right, I will take a few questions.
Yes?
You worked side-by-side
with Adrian Chase for months.
How could you not know that you had
a serial killer in your administration?
Well, Mr. Chase's secret life
came as a surprise to us all.
I can say that we are currently
following up some very promising leads.
Are you saying
you have no idea where he is?
No, I'm saying that the details of
an ongoing investigation are confidential.
Yes?
I spent the afternoon
speaking with Gay Eked's father.
What do you have to say to him
and the families
of all of Prometheus' victims?
Well, I would say to them
what I'm saying to you.
We are doing everything
that we possibly can
to bring Mr. Chase to justice.
Do you have anything for us
other than canned platitudes?
Better question is, do we have anything?
Manhunts aren't exactly
in Helix's wheelhouse, Felicity.
Yeah, you helped me unmask Chase.
Now I need your help
trying to find the bastard.
Well, from what you've told me,
they've got Homeland Security,
the FBI, and A.R.G.U.S. working on this.
Yeah, and last night,
Chase played them like Maximum Force.
I used to love that game.
I know, I did, too.
Apparently, it's seen better days.
Point being, I was expecting you and Helix
to come up with a fresh perspective.
Maybe pull out some new trick,
something Chase isn't gonna anticipate.
Well, it would help not having to
waste time reinventing the wheel.
You wanna know what intel
they're working with?
Getting into Homeland Security
and the FBI is easy.
Their cyber sec is a bad joke.
But breaking into A.R.G.U.S.' network...
Allow me.
The intel of Chase being in New Jersey
came from an A.R.G.U.S. drone.
Okay. So?
So, the information was then sent
to an unsecured phone.
Seems like a big-time breach
in operational security.
- Wait.
- "Wait," what?
What if Chase has a buddy
inside A.R.G.U.S.?
Someone who tipped him off,
who pinged the unsecured cell phone?
Yeah.
- Mr. Mayor.
- Hi.
Could you give us some space?
Let's go.
Chase probably knew Agent Pierce
was part of our operation in Jersey.
This could be payback.
Okay, Lyla, what killed him?
Cause of death
looks like blunt force trauma.
Felicity, Curtis, we have a camera.
Roger, Roger. We have clearance, Clarence.
What is our vector, Victor?
Guys, focus, please.
That's evidence.
A.R.G.U.S. evidence.
All right, I got the video.
Streaming back to your phone now.
- Here we go.
- You guys seeing this?
Well, we're seeing it.
It looks like a meta.
An invisible meta?
Or psychokinesis.
Though, some prefer telekinesis.
I don't think so.
Check out what the elevator's doing.
Yeah, guys, Curtis is right.
According to the elevator activity logs,
the car accelerated upwards at...
Oh, my God, nine Gs.
And then it just dropped into a free fall
for 40 stories.
Death by elevator.
This doesn't feel like Chase.
No. At first, I thought Chase was
trying to tie up loose ends,
but I couldn't find
any connections between them.
He had his A.R.G.U.S.
security key still on him.
Why enter the elevator if not to take it?
Maybe to confirm the Kill.
Guys, how do we manipulate
an elevator like that?
Remotely. I mean,
everything's computer-controlled.
All right. However this happened,
let's just find whoever did it.
We are on it.
Huh. Looks like the elevator
was hacked in real time.
Pulling up the rootkit now.
Oh, my God.
"Oh, my God," what?
Nothing. There's a line of code here
I'm not quite getting.
But I think I know someone at Helix
who can help.
Hey, don't you need to show them the code?
Yeah, that's a good idea.
Yes, thank you. Very helpful, Curtis.
I'm sorry, Mr. Eked, but the specifics
of the investigation into Adrian Chase,
they're just not open to the public.
The mother of my children is dead,
and you can't tell me anything?
I can assure you that the SCPD
and the Mayor's office
are doing everything in their power
to apprehend him.
We're gonna catch that scumbag.
Oh. Instead of working
shoulder-to-shoulder with him? Huh?
Sorry. It's just...
Things may not have worked out
between Gay and me,
but she was always there for the kids.
She loved them and they loved her.
And now she's gone.
Please find him.
Gay didn't deserve dying like that.
And no other family deserves this pain.
We will find him.
And he'll know
the true meaning of justice.
Thank you.
How many other victims' relatives
do we have today?
He was the last.
God, I don't think I could handle another.
These people are grieving, Rene.
I'm not saying they're not
entitled to their grief, hoss.
I'm saying hearing about it
all day long's a real buzzkill.
You know, I'd have thought
someone in your situation
would've been a little more...
Sympathetic?
- My situation?
- Yeah.
Curtis might've told me about your wife
and your daughter.
Curtis talks too much.
I don't disagree.
But while he was talking,
he also mentioned that he offered
to set you up with a lawyer
to help get your daughter back.
And that was over two months ago.
I'm just not ready, hoss.
A polymorphous worm
concealed by a kernel rootkit.
Are you trying to talk dirty to me?
I have the code, Alena. I know your work.
You hacked that elevator,
you killed that A.R.G.U.S. agent...
- Just slow down.
- Yes or no?
- Kind of.
- "Kind of"?
I didn't mean to kill him, I swear.
I'd never knocked anyone out
with an elevator before,
- and apparently, there's a learning curve.
- Alena.
I need you to hear me out for one second.
You murdered someone.
Accidentally, and for a good cause.
I can't believe I'm hearing this.
Cayden James.
He's the most skilled hacker
the world has ever known.
If he was, I would've heard of him.
No, you wouldn't have,
because he's just that good.
He's a ghost.
He's also the person that formed Helix.
What does that have to do with...
Eight months ago,
he was scooped up by A.R.G.U.S.
Not arrested, not charged, just taken.
And now he's being held without cause.
Being tortured, who knows what else.
And I had to take this off
that A.R.G.U.S. agent so we can free him.
Alena, you killed someone.
Before you get too judgmental,
know you're gonna help me free Cayden
from where A.R.G.U.S. is holding him.
Why would I do that?
Because before he was taken,
Cayden was working on a biometric tracker
that could recognize a heartbeat.
Powerful enough to scan
anywhere in the world.
Anywhere Adrian Chase is.
We have a problem.
- What is it?
- The problem.
After Damien Darhk
took my security implant last year,
I instituted new protocols to prevent
any sensitive A.R.G.U.S. information,
or location
from being accessed by a single person.
Access now requires
two of these security keys.
But Agent Pierce's key wasn't taken.
You found it on him.
- I found a very sophisticated copy.
- Smart.
Extremely. I almost didn't catch it.
If those keys have been compromised,
then they have to be reprogrammed.
The whole point of having the keys
is for them to be unhackable.
Reprogramming takes about 24 hours.
Lyla, clearly,
A.R.G.U.S. security is under attack.
But this doesn't feel like Chase.
And, quite frankly,
that is where we have to keep our focus.
And I sympathize.
But I've got almost all personnel
with keys in lockdown at A.R.G.U.S.
- "Almost"?
- Agent Ditkoff is 20 miles out,
near Port Talbert.
I was hoping your team
could escort her back to A.R.G.U.S.
Oliver, I know you wanna get Chase.
So doll.
But A.R.G.U.S. has always had our backs.
Yes, they have.
Let's call Curtis and Dinah.
Please let Felicity know
where we're going.
Copy that.
Just let me talk
to my friends at A.R.G.U.S.
Maybe we can negotiate
for Cayden's release.
Sorry. It's just funny, you know?
"Negotiate with A. R.G.U.S."
Seriously, I really think they will.
Just hold off on taking the second key.
A.R.G.U.S. won't even admit
they have Cayden.
Besides, plan's already in motion.
What did you do?
Don't worry.
I hired professionals this time.
"Professionals"?
One casualty was enough
for this girl's conscience.
Like mercenaries?
You really can buy anything
on the Internet.
Well, are your Internet thugs
headed to Port Talbert?
Because they're about to
have some company.
Over Terrific here. Or Mr. Watch.
Or Watch Terrific.
Anyway, it'll come to me.
We're on our way.
Right. Seven-hundred feet ahead,
three bogies. Please hurry.
Dinah and I
are a few blocks away.
Hey, John,
I know you have to protect that agent.
We're on our way.
I know you have to protect her,
but I need you to let those guys
get away with her security key.
Wait, what? What?
Hey! Don't move!
Oliver, we have a situation.
I need you to let tango
get away with that security key.
- Why?
- Felicity has information
that we don't have.
Oliver, I need you to stand down.
What the hell was that?
Felicity said we had to.
Why?
To catch Prometheus.
It's the only way to catch Chase.
No, it's not.
But even if it were, at what cost?
Agent Ditkoff could've been killed.
No, the team was there to make sure.
She could've been killed,
just like Agent Pierce.
I told you, that was an accident.
And now, two keys are in the wind,
and A.R.G.U.S. is vulnerable.
What the hell were you thinking?
That we need to catch
this son of a bitch, no matter what.
Guys, a little support here.
Might be crossing a line, Felicity.
Well, you're the last person on Earth
that gets to give that lecture, Oliver.
Or second to last.
And don't tell me that you don't make
morally questionable choices
so that I don't have to. I have to.
No, you don't, Felicity,
you don't have to.
Lyla's right. There are better ways
for us to find Chase.
Chase has been in the wind for a week.
He was trained by Talia al Ghul.
He knows how to stay in the wind.
What other leads do we have?
How else are we gonna
bring Adrian Chase to justice,
unless A.R.G.U.S. lets go of Cayden James?
- Not a chance.
- Then my only choice is to help Helix.
Your only choice?
Felicity, I thought
we're on the same side.
No, John, I'm on the side
that's gonna put Chase away,
so that he can't hurt anyone ever again.
Hey, Felicity.
Let her go, man. Now is not the time.
You wanted to see me, hoss?
Yeah. First, close the door.
Second, what have I told you
about calling me "hoss"?
- Don't.
- Right.
Yeah.
Just sit down.
Are you firing me?
Rene, there was a time when
I would've loved to hear you ask me that.
But no, I am not firing you.
I wanna talk to you about...
Zoe.
Yeah, your daughter.
Yeah, I know her name, hoss.
I thought I told you
I don't wanna talk about her.
Well, that's too bad,
'cause you happen to be working
for a guy who would give anything
to be with his daughter again.
What do you want from me, man?
An explanation.
I looked into your case.
You have full visitation rights
as long as you're accompanied
by a court-appointed guardian.
And there's no record
of you ever visiting.
Please...
Just leave this alone, man.
I think we both know I'm not gonna.
So why don't we just skip to the part
where you tell me
why you do not wanna see your daughter?
Okay.
When Curtis told me about
his lawyer friend, I got excited, okay?
Yeah, yeah, all right.
And then what happened?
I remembered why they took Zoe
away from me in the first place.
Yeah, sure, I could visit her
with a court-appointed guardian,
like you said.
You wanna know why that is?
'Cause I'm bad news.
- Yeah, you're an acquired taste, for sure.
- I hurt her!
What do you mean, you hurt her?
I was reheating some soup for her.
It's just about all I could make her.
And it was on the stove,
and I passed out drunk.
Poor Zoe, she's trying to grab it,
and pulls it down,
and it burns her hand real bad.
And it was her crying that woke me up.
Zoe deserves better than me.
End of story.
Rene. Rene. Get back...
Meet prisoner 38085, aka Cayden James.
What are you holding him on?
He's a person of interest.
So, no crime,
I'm guessing no trial, either.
Do you have something
you wanna say to me, Johnnie?
Not right now, Lyla.
There's something
we're not considering.
What if Felicity is right?
She might be right.
We give James a terminal,
we make him find Chase,
and then we hand him back to Helix.
I know you want Chase
off the board, Oliver,
but Cayden James
is as dangerous as a loose nuke.
I can't put him back in play.
Helix has compromised your security.
And now they have hired mercenaries
that are gonna go after A. R.G.U.S.
to get James out.
Which means we go after them first.
Curtis has intel as to where
their base of operations is.
And we'd be going in completely blind.
We have a greater chance of success
if we let Helix come to us.
Wait, Lyla.
You wanna set a trap for Helix
and use James as the bait?
I don't think I need to tell either of you
how dangerous Helix is.
This is our chance to take them down.
This is happening
with or without your help.
I'll let you boys
wrap your head around that.
We have to get Felicity out of Helix.
We can't let her get involved in this.
You mean any more involved.
We knew she was into something.
We knew it was bad.
We just let her get in deeper.
Oliver, grief can make people
do crazy things.
No one knows that better than you and me.
But I'm not the one she was gonna marry.
What's your point?
My point is...
Oliver, look. Maybe we should've
talked her out of Helix.
Maybe not. I don't know.
But the point is, we're here now.
And you're the only one
she will listen to.
I'm not sure how much credibility
I have with her.
You both wanna catch Chase, right?
You have that in common.
Which tells me you are the only one
who can pull her back from the brink.
Oh.
- Hi.
- Hey.
Nice of you to use
the front door for once.
May I come in, please?
Actually, I was just leaving.
I can see that.
Sure.
Looks like you're not sitting
behind a keyboard for this one.
- Can you blame me?
- No.
I, more than probably anyone else,
understand what it's like
to be willing to do whatever it takes
to stop Chase.
Then let me do it.
Let me just tell you
how I'm seeing things.
You're willing to do whatever it takes
to stop Chase
because I was willing to do
whatever it takes to save this city...
And that created him.
Okay, so it's ironic. That's what it is.
It doesn't have to be.
You see, we can think of
another way to find him,
and then we can find
another way to stop him.
Okay, how? The SCPD tip line?
No, that's not gonna work this time,
Oliver. We both know that.
Look, this is our only chance.
And this is me asking you.
Don't do this.
For the past four years, I have
watched you do whatever you had to,
whatever it took,
to stop the people threatening this city.
How can you stand there
and not ask me to do the same thing?
Because over the past four years,
you, more than anyone else,
has seen the toll that it has taken on me.
- And I told you...
- And I understand, I agree
that I should not shelter you
from making hard decisions.
But you wanna talk irony? Fine.
You are willing to sell your soul
to destroy a threat that I created.
How did...
One of the reasons I fell in love with you
is because you're always willing
to do what was right,
no matter what the cost.
Even if it's unbearably hard.
It's what makes you, you.
So how can I be any different?
You have sacrificed your soul
for the team, for the city, and for me.
You don't have to
carry that burden any longer.
Let me do it.
Felicity, I...
I can't.
Then you'll have to stop me.
This facility has eight ingress points.
I've got six-man teams stationed at each,
perimeter squads keeping watch,
and drones flying surveillance.
Helix has to be ready for all of that.
That's why we're here.
Added support and the element of surprise.
You think Felicity will be surprised
that we're trying to stop her?
Actually, I am kind of surprised.
I mean, you and her have a history.
Just kind of like,
"We're against each other."
Let's have you and Dinah
patrol the southwest.
Stay on comms, okay?
- Quick question.
- Mmm-hmm.
What do we do if she shows up tonight?
We stop her.
Logistics calculates a 46% likelihood
they'll try to breach through here.
Okay. Then we'll be ready for them.
We're not expecting Helix
for another seven minutes,
so would you like to use that time
to tell me what I've done
that's got you so pissed off?
Lyla, I'm not pissed off.
But I am concerned.
What did Felicity mean
when she made that crack
about you crossing a line?
I can't even begin to fathom
the amount of crap
that Helix has put
into Felicity's head, Johnnie.
But Lyla,
holding Cayden James without due process,
that's not a bunch of crap.
Cayden James is 20 times
more dangerous than Snowden.
We caught him trying to hack
an A.R.G.U.S. transponder.
If he got in, every NOC agent we have
could be at risk.
That sounds a whole lot
like Amanda Waller.
Waller's decisions seem a lot less wrong
from this side of the desk, Johnnie.
You can't judge me for that.
I'm not judging.
I'm just worried.
Felicity Smoak is one of
the best people I've ever known,
and she's gone over to the dark side.
I don't want that to happen to my wife.
I've done a lot of illegal things,
but none of them
ever required heavy weaponry.
Or any weaponry.
You know, I found the transition
between hacker to vigilante
to be surprisingly straightforward.
You're gonna do great.
Besides, you have enough
firepower here to invade Russia.
Well, hopefully, we won't have to.
I think we might.
They know we're coming.
I'm not worried.
In case you need them.
No.
I mean, even if we do, I'm not using that.
A.R.G.U.S. will have guns.
I thought you said
no one was gonna get hurt.
If we do this right, no one will.
Wait for my signal.
What's so important, hoss?
I was gonna call it a night.
Daddy!
Sweetheart.
I told you.
Hey, you're not the only one around here
that doesn't listen to orders.
Who's he?
This is Quentin, Quentin Lance,
Daddy's friend.
But I call him "hoss."
He arranged this little visit.
Thank you, hoss.
- I missed you.
- I missed you so much.
I missed you more.
Dang, girl, you're getting so big.
Look at you.
Pretty soon you're gonna be
driving Pops to the games.
Isn't that right?
Tell your daddy what you're doing
at school now, Zoe.
I made the hockey team.
What? No way. What position you playing?
- Goalie.
- That's my girl.
Just like your pops.
Oh...
That's so good. I'm proud of you.
Can we go home now?
I'm sorry, sweetheart, but not today.
Why?
Sweetheart, last time you were with me,
you got hurt, baby.
It was an accident.
When can I go home to Daddy?
I don't know, sweetheart.
Soon, peanut.
There's a lawyer friend
Daddy's friend knows.
And Daddy's decided
he's gonna talk to him,
and you're gonna come home with me.
I promise. Okay? I promise.
I thought you were
standing post with Lyla.
Seemed like a good idea
to put some space between us.
Felicity isn't the only lady
who thinks the ends justifies the means.
When Lyla and Felicity Smoak
are willing to cross the line...
Makes you wonder
if there even is one, right?
We got incoming.
Tango's in the field.
Copy that.
What's that?
Think of it as a weaponized tablet,
preloaded with Address Resolution
Protocol Spoofing.
The A.R.G.U.S. site is protected
by microchipped gun turrets.
Right. This will shut them down?
You sure you're ready for this?
Let's do this.
Bogie's on site. Want us to intercept?
Negative. Draw them in closer.
Identification, please.
It's not them.
Lyla, sitrep.
The van checked out. It wasn't Helix.
We have a problem.
Wait, this isn't A.R.G.U.S.
No, it is. Just not the site
A.R.G.U.S. expected us to hit.
What problem?
Helix is about to extract Cayden James.
- How? They're not here.
- Neither is Cayden James.
And you didn't tell us?
I didn't think it was necessary.
Where is he?
At an off-the-books black site,
12 miles away.
Damn it, Lyla, you should've
let us in on the plan.
Helix wasn't supposed to know
about the black site. No one was.
That's because it's illegal.
I'm not discussing this, Johnnie.
Get your head in the game.
You're two minutes out.
Where has this tablet
been all my life?
I made it special for you.
So much better than a friendship bracelet.
How are we gonna find Cayden James?
I know he's inside
one of these containers,
but I don't know exactly which one.
Can you check to see
if there's a site map?
Mmm-hmm.
Okay.
Whatever A.R.G.U.S. is keeping in there,
they wanna keep secure.
Or whoever.
Two air-gapped, unhackable keys.
It's beautiful tech, really.
Free Cayden James now.
Admire A.R.G.U.S. tech later.
Right.
- One...
- Two...
Three.
Cayden?
Hey. Hey. It's okay, this is a rescue.
We gotta move.
Team Arrow will be here any minute.
I doubt that very much.
They have no clue we're here.
Do not say "I told you so."
Meet us out back in five.
Where are we going?
We're gonna go say hi to your friends.
Don't grab a woman
unless you have permission, dumb-ass.
Freeze!
I've got Felicity's friend.
I have a name, you know.
Turn around. Put your hands on your head.
- Do it!
- Okay. Turning.
You wanna see what else they can do?
Next one goes in his head.
Then it'll have to go through me. Go!
Get out of the way!
You know I can't do that.
I was really hoping you wouldn't!
Oliver, don't move.
That is a 30-kilowatt spectral beam laser.
It'll cut you to the bone.
Curtis will let you out.
I'm sorry.
I am. I'm really hoping that you're gonna
understand after we get Chase.
Don't count on it.
On the bright side, we were suited up.
I mean, I'm glad Cayden James
doesn't know that, you know,
we were trying to keep him in prison.
Because if he did, I would be scared
of my refrigerator, my car,
my alarm clock.
And could we talk
about elevators for a second?
Because I think I'm gonna be
taking the stairs for a while.
It's just better for your health.
Also, on the bright side, you know,
so, just think about that.
This wasn't a prison, Curtis.
This was an illegal black site
on American soil led by my wife.
Also, no A.R.G.U.S. casualty...
No A.R.G.U.S. casualties.
All the mercs used rubber bullets, so...
What do you wanna do about Felicity?
There is nothing to do.
She put herself in front of a bullet
in order to take down Chase.
Until that happens,
I don't know what to say to her.
In the meantime,
we drink to her speedy success. I mean...
In the meantime, I think we go home.
Why? There's more glasses in the bunk...
You wanna drink by your... Okay.
Yeah, right. I mean, yeah.
Thank you both very much for tonight.
Yep.
You're working late.
Well, I thought I'd stick around
for my thank you.
You had that coming, for sure.
Along with an apology.
Here I was, thinking you didn't know
what an apology was.
I guess you can
teach a dog some new tricks.
Even wild ones.
I spoke to Curtis' lawyer friend.
I put things in motion.
Good for you.
You know, that Zoe,
she's a hell of a little girl, and...
You know, she deserves her dad.
You know, father to father,
I gotta tell you,
her dad deserves to be with her.
Thank you.
That's what I was waiting for.
All right, how about
a celebratory club soda?
I'm buying.
Hey, hold on a second, hoss.
How about something stronger?
You keep calling me "hoss,"
I'll show you something stronger.
Hello?
Hey, Felicity.
Hi. Where are you? Are you okay?
We're safe.
Thank you for all of your help.
But here's the thing.
Your connection to the Green Arrow
and his team, it's a liability.
Yeah. Well, once we get Chase,
he'll see all the good Helix can do.
I'm sorry, but we just can't risk it.
Especially not with
Cayden back in the fold
and A.R.G.U.S. looking for him.
I loved getting to work with you.
Meeting your heroes,
it turns out it's not so bad after all.
But we left something for you. Look down.
Up a little bit.
Little bit to the right.
This?
What is it?
Some on-the-fly coding from Mr. James.
Told you he was the best there ever was.
Take care, Felicity.
Yeah, you, too.
Johnnie.
We need to talk about this.
I don't think that's a good idea, Lyla.
- I could say something I might regret.
- John.
When you said that you were
taking over for Waller,
you said you wouldn't become her.
I told you.
It's more complicated when you're sitting
on the other side of the...
What the hell is more complicated?
You're holding someone
with no lawyer, no trial, no justice.
And the world is safer for it.
It could be safer.
But it's not better.
The woman I love could never do this.
Lyla, this job has changed you.
Maybe.
But maybe the world's changed.
It's gotten even worse, Johnnie.
It's gotten worse and uglier,
and we do what we can
to protect the people we love.
I am not ashamed of what I did.
Of what I'm still going to do.
We've been down this road before,
haven't we?
We know where this fight takes us.
So let's stop it.
Move forward.
I don't know if I can.
- Is that it?
- Yep.
James' magic tracker to find Chase?
Biometric tracker, yes.
Nobody from A.R.G.U.S.
was seriously injured,
in case you were wondering.
Helix froze me out.
It's over.
I'm sorry.
I thought you weren't ever
gonna lie to me again.
I'm not lying.
I'm sorry.
I know that they gave you
a sense of belonging
- that maybe I haven't...
- No.
You didn't back my play.
I was worried.
You don't trust me.
After all these years,
all of the times that I supported you,
even when I didn't agree,
you couldn't do the same for me.
What's that?
Tracker's honing in on Chase's location.
Where is he?
Chase. He's here.
English - SDH