Previously on "Arrow"...
Galaxy One has us
outmanned and outgunned.
You want to even the
odds, you get out there
and you fight the hell back.
Hyah! Hyah!
Uh!
Dinah sent you.
Give this to Felicity.
You military types
are like Swiss watches.
Youse are always on time. Show me.
Show me what you got.
Where's Emiko?
Well, if I told you that, Mr. Queen,
she'd have me head. Ha ha!
And, frankly, that's a
part of me I'd like to keep.
- Uh!
- Yah!
That Virgil is damn slippery.
At least now we know what
he's trying to acquire.
A.R.G.U.S. vault drive,
triple-level encryption
for eyes-only documents.
If someone at the agency's leaking
classified intel to the Ninth Circle...
Right. But if we have some indication
as to what they're planning finally,
it might help me find Emiko.
And you said you didn't need any backup.
Yeah. Well, we lost Virgil,
but we got what he was after.
This drive feels like our
best lead at finding Emiko,
at least until Archer's back up.
Alena is pulling all-nighters
to get Archer back up and running,
and once it is, we will
be able to find Emiko.
And finally tell her that
Dante killed her mother.
And, hopefully, she'll
come to her senses
about the Ninth Circle.
Well, that would be enough for me to
turn myself against
the evil organization
that raised me as a child.
- Crap!
- What's that? What's wrong?
The drive has a security fail-safe
that fried all the
files, probably to prevent
someone like me from trying to do
what I am trying to do.
But these aren't
A.R.G.U.S.-encrypted protocols.
Someone else must've written the
security program for this drive.
Wait. If it's not A.R.G.U.S., who is it?
Well, I have hacked enough
government servers in my day
to know that this is the
Department of Defense.
Not that I do that anymore,
because I work with the SCPD.
But this branch is the D.I.A.
What would the Ninth Circle want
with the defense Intelligence Agency?
We need to find out.
You're married to the A.R.G.U.S.
Director. Maybe she can help.
Yeah, well, any inquiries to
A.R.G.U.S. will send up red flags,
paint an even bigger target on
Lyla's back than there already is.
I think I might have an
old contact at the D.I.A.
A General.
The General will be
right with you, gentlemen.
Hey. What's... What's going on?
You're acting like we're being sent
to the principal's office.
This guy can be a real hard-ass.
Just let me do the talking.
Okay. How do you know him?
Ah. I must say, I was surprised
to hear from you, John.
Well, sir, I wouldn't have made the call
unless it was very, very important.
No, I imagine you wouldn't have.
You must be Oliver Queen...
The legendary Green Arrow.
I'm General Stewart.
A pleasure to meet you, General Stewart.
Thank you for taking the time.
I'm not gonna lie, son.
I wasn't always a fan.
But since you got out of prison,
you seem like a changed man,
- and I respect that.
- Thank you, sir.
Sir, we made the call
because we were hoping
you could tell us what was on this.
Ah. Where'd you get it?
We intercepted a handoff
between an A.R.G.U.S. agent
and a man that works for a
group called the Ninth Circle.
The terrorist financiers.
I heard they were just a rumor.
No, sir, they are very real.
And we have reason to suspect
they are planning something.
We were hoping you had
intel that you could give us
and the SCPD.
I'm afraid I can't. Heh!
But even if I did, John, you know
I can't just hand over classified intel,
not without proper clearance,
which you no longer have
since you left A.R.G.U.S.
Of course. But, sir, we
were still hoping that maybe
you could, uh...
You were on a path
destined for the Pentagon,
maybe even a post with the joint chiefs.
Now where are you?
Working with the cops,
playing vigilante?
That's no career. That's a dead end.
No offense.
I wasn't even sure you
were keeping tabs on me.
Sir, I had my reasons
for leaving A.R.G.U.S.
You left to protect your wife.
I know you better than you think.
And I'm sorry to say you lost your way.
I didn't leave A.R.G.U.S. for my career.
I left to protect my family.
And that's not something you
would understand, is it, sir?
John, we should probably go.
Again, thank you for your time, General.
I always have time for my family.
Excuse me?
Oh, John didn't tell you.
I'm his stepfather.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
Frak! Ugh!
Well, I guess I don't have
to ask how this is going.
Well, as glad as I am that
you both got to meet Laurel,
her cry really did a
number on this helmet.
How did it go at the bunker?
Good. The bombs we stole from
Galaxy One are now secure.
Roy and Dinah are setting up a perimeter
in case they ever come looking for them.
And William is making sure
they can't be detonated
unless, well, we say so.
Although maybe he'd be more useful
helping you out with this?
The helmet is inlaid
with this highly advanced circuitry mesh
and retinal display,
and I will not be able
to figure out why until
I get it up and running.
What do you think you'll find?
Hopefully, whatever Galaxy
One has planned next,
if they haven't stopped from
making the city go boom-boom.
Well, can't we just ask
our man on the inside?
No. We can't come in contact with Rene
until we get the go-ahead from Zoe.
They're at Glades City Hall now,
and we don't want to blow their cover.
Okay, so how do we get this
piece of junk up and running?
The power module is comprised
with an alloy proprietary to Galaxy One.
I've been trying to work around it,
but I can't without the real thing.
Wait. I thought this helmet was
a one-of-a-kind prototype.
As far as we know. But
the power module is not,
which means we need to find one.
All right, public enemy
number one, sit tight.
I know where to go. Be back in an hour.
Anyone dealing in secret weapons tech
won't be friendly.
You need backup.
Better safe than sorry.
Keep up.
Felicity Smoak now entering Smoak Tech.
Ohh. I have missed your sweet voice.
You know she's not a real person, right?
Of course she's not.
No. I am just so glad that we were able
to start building the program out again.
It feels wrong confining
Archer to just one tablet,
even temporarily.
She deserves to spread her wings
right after we find
Oliver's evil half-sister.
Speaking of spreading wings, um,
I think I've found a way to
help Smoak Tech really soar.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah. There's someone
interested in buying the company.
It's just you, me, and Archer.
I mean, who would be interested in that?
Dr. Will Magnus.
What? Huh. The Dr. Will Magnus?
- Mm-hmm.
- The world's foremost authority
- on robotics engineering.
- Mm-hmm.
When I was CEO of Palmer tech,
he wouldn't even return my calls.
My friend at Magnus
Labs says that Archer
could really help Doc Magnus with
these new A.I.S he's building.
I could set a meeting.
Magnus Labs is the gold standard
in tech R&D.
Oh, my god. With their backing,
we could expand Archer to be
more than just a genetic tracking system
or surveillance for the SCPD.
I mean, it could be a bigger and
better Overwatch system. I mean...
It's a chance to change the world.
Uh-huh.
Warning. Intruder alert.
Tick-tock, lads. In and out.
Look for the device
drawing the most power.
Ohh. Ohh.
Hidden on a tablet. Ha! Crafty.
Put the tablet down, call your men off,
and I'll let you live.
Felicity!
Sorry, love. No can do.
Pistol beats keyboard, darling.
Who the hell are these guys?
You're safe now.
They weren't after me.
Oh, my God. She's gone.
They couldn't have
gotten her, could they?
The Ninth Circle has Archer.
Then this crazy Irish
guy came busting through,
and Alena and I tried to fight them off,
but then the D.I.A. came crashing
through the ceiling
and took them all out.
- What about Archer?
- Virgil made away with it.
We'll get it back. I'm glad you're okay.
How did they find out about Archer?
I'll give you one guess... Emiko.
I'm sorry my men weren't
there sooner, Ms. Smoak.
It seems the Ninth Circle was
a step ahead of us as well.
You must be General Stewart,
A.K.A. the stepfather that John
hasn't told his closest friends about.
So this is where you people work.
Impressive.
How did your men end up
at Smoak Tech, General?
Several months ago, the D.I.A. got wind
of Ninth Circle mole inside A.R.G.U.S.
Since then, we've made it a point
of tracking their activity, including
the theft of that drive, which led us
to your friend Virgil.
Wait. Wait. Wait. I thought you
said you didn't know anything.
I said I couldn't tell you anything.
A lie of omission is
still a lie, General.
I'm sorry, John, but it was classified.
What was on the drive?
A list of assets we have in the field...
Special operatives with
high-level security clearance.
That's why Emiko took Archer,
so that she could hunt them down
and then gain access to what they know,
which she could pretty much do
with anybody now that she has their DNA.
It's only a matter of time before
they find everyone on that list.
We need to make sure
those assets are secure.
We have protocols in place.
I'll call my assets to a safe house.
This is General Stewart. We
need to start evacuations.
Uh...
Oliver, before you get started,
I'm fine, man.
The second time that you've
broken the chain of command
with a 4-star general.
That's not like you, John.
You expect me to say
"yes, sir" to that man?
I... you know, I... I'd
like to know why you won't.
And...
I would like to know why you never...
Never mentioned that
you had a stepfather.
I didn't see much of a need to.
That man has not been in my life
since I left home and
joined the military.
Ok. I just met him.
All I have is my first impression,
and my first impression is that
he doesn't seem like that bad of a guy.
Oliver, when I first met the general,
he was a lieutenant,
my father's CO on a covert military op
to quell an insurgency in Vlatava.
The op went bad.
The unit was pinned down
with heavy gunfire from insurgents.
My dad stayed behind to hold them off.
Saved the whole unit.
Stewart made it out.
My father didn't.
So do you blame him
for your father's death?
It was his op. He
should've stayed behind.
Six months later,
he's coming by the house for dinner.
Six months, Oliver.
I didn't know.
It was bad enough that, uh,
he just appeared in our lives, but...
Once he and my mom got married,
he had me and Andy running
spartan survival drills he
learned as a recon marine.
I mean, how long could
we be out in the cold
trying to find our way out of
the woods without a compass.
He called it "tough love."
Said he didn't care
how we felt about him
as long as it made us strong.
I don't know. If he was so strong,
how could he just abandon
the first rule of the corps
and leave my father behind?
- Thanks. Owe you one.
- You got it.
You get a lead?
Finally, someone not afraid to talk.
There's a guy here trading Galaxy merch.
The only problem is
he's in Deathstroke territory.
Well, that won't be a problem. Trust me.
Trust you?
Funny.
Okay. Are you ever gonna
let me off the hook?
Huh. Doubtful.
Great. Well, you should
let me handle this.
You're backup, remember?
So back me up.
Hey. There's a vendor back
there we need to talk to.
And I'm just gonna
let you in because why?
'Cause I'll kick your ass if you don't.
Okay. That won't be necessary.
I got the mark.
- From who?
- Your boss.
Check it.
How you know JJ?
You just need to know that I do.
We good?
Hey.
Who the hell was JJ?
He's my brother... John Jr.
Ha ha! John Diggle has
one son in Knightwatch
and another who's leader
of the Deathstroke Gang.
That must make family
dinners interesting.
Well, he grew up hating my parents,
and the expectations they put on us.
That's why I'm glad that
you finally figured out
the truth about your family.
Look, I've wanted to tell you
the truth for a long time.
What else don't I know about you?
How long you got?
I don't think that gun's gonna
get any cleaner than that.
I just want to be prepared.
I can't slip up with the Ninth Circle.
- And Emiko?
- What about her?
Well, I know you two were close,
and you haven't said a thing
about her since she went all evil.
I'm not so sure she's all evil.
When we were at the airfield,
there was a moment when Emiko and I
were alone, and...
She had the upper hand.
I thought I was dead.
I mean, I should have been dead,
but she let me go.
And that tells you what?
I don't know, but it can't be as simple
as her being all bad.
I mean, we've all gone through paths
where we've come to regret.
Hell, if Laurel can redeem herself,
then maybe Emiko can do the same.
We got a problem, people.
What's going on?
I just got off the
phone with intelligence.
All of our assets have been
accounted for, except one...
An undercover agent by
the name of Julian Sison.
He should be at a safe house,
but there's been no response
since the call came in.
Where is the safe house?
30 miles northeast of here.
We'll get into it.
I'll check with the other
assets, see if there's been any...
I'll come with you.
Somebody needs to keep an eye on you.
You think I'm trying to mislead you?
"Fool me once," right?
That's not very fair, John.
It's okay. You can come.
Follow my lead.
This place is a pigsty.
Either he's messy as hell...
Or someone made it that way.
Overwatch, any sign of our guests?
I'm getting 3 heat sigs further in.
Come on, people!
What the hell's going on?
- Are you Julian Sison?
- Yeah.
Then why didn't you
answer your transponder?
'Cause I'm in the middle of an op,
and you three just blew it.
Overwatch, there is no sign of Emiko
or the Ninth Circle.
If this guy isn't the
target, then who is?
Those are my assets.
Overwatch, we have men down.
The Ninth Circle knew we were coming.
Uh!
General, we've been looking for you.
I'm trying to track John's
spartan helmet, but it's offline.
Clearly this was an elaborate
play to draw General Stewart.
We need to find he
and John, and quickly.
I'll put a bolo out for both of them.
I'll put the word out around The Glades
in case Emiko shows up in the old 'hood.
Or we just find Emiko and end all this.
We will. We have found
people without Archer before.
We will find John and his stepdad,
and then we will find your sister.
Kidnapping a 4-star
general is a risky move
for the Ninth Circle,
especially if the Pentagon's on to them.
So why? Why do it?
I don't know. We need to
find out more about who he is,
what makes him so important.
I'd imagine his files are
really, really classified.
"Really, really classified"
sounds really, really fun.
I'm on it.
General?
John, are you all right?
Yeah. You?
I've taken worse hits than this.
Where do you think we are?
I don't know.
Maybe a Ninth Circle
safe house. I don't know.
They must've found out
I was looking into them.
Agh! We got to get the hell out of here.
You're not going to will those
things into breaking, John.
Do you not remember
anything I taught you?
How could I forget?
I know I was hard on you, son,
but I wanted you to be prepared.
It paid off.
Look at you now.
Really? We're captured,
probably gonna die in here.
We're not dead yet.
Uh! Uh!
What about your helmet?
Yeah. Yeah, that could work.
If we could get to it, I could
send a signal to the others,
tell us our location.
Time for us to have a
little chat, General.
- Hey.
- Yeah.
- Oh, good work.
- Thanks.
All right. Anything in the file
that will help us find them?
No. But, uh, plenty on why the
Ninth Circle would want him.
Okay.
Thrice-decorated commander
of the 1st recon battalion
during the Khandaq conflict, after which
he was appointed commandant
of the marine corps,
then chairman of the
joint chiefs of staff.
I mean, the guy is a real
bona fide American hero.
Not to John. John blames General Stewart
for his father's death during a mission
they were both on in Vlatava.
Oh, yeah. That would
be enough to alienate
someone like John, and why he
wouldn't have told us about him,
but it's not true.
Which part?
According to the
Pentagon's official account,
the vlatava mission
was so successful that
the general was actually,
for a stint of time,
appointed head of DARPA.
But if... if the mission was a success,
why would he lie to John about it?
To protect him?
It's been a long time since we've
seen each other, Agent Diggle.
Go to hell.
Hold that thought.
I want the codes to project Cygnus X-1.
My name is General Roy Stewart.
Serial number 498003145,
United States marine corps.
Yes, yes. The military's
trained you well,
but you'll break eventually.
Leave him alone! Leave him alone!
Now let's try it again, General.
The codes, project Cygnus X-1.
My name is General Roy Stewart.
Serial number 498003145...
Enough! I guess we're
gonna have to do this
the hard way.
Leave him alone.
This has nothing to do with him.
Give me the codes or...
Don't tell him anything.
Stop. Stop it! I'll tell you. Stop.
5693016.
Now, was that so hard?
You all right, John?
Why did you give him the code?
A thank you would be good enough.
What the hell is Cygnus X-1 anyway?
Something we don't want the
Ninth Circle to know about.
Now, let's get out of here.
There's a box cutter on the table.
I got something better.
What the hell are you doing?
You really don't remember
anything I taught you, do you?
With enough pressure
applied at a steady pace,
a shoelace can saw through plastic.
Damn. There's no power.
How about we give it a boost?
John's helmet just came back online.
Morse code... SOS. Location?
Warehouse in the meatpacking district.
Call the team.
Clear.
You know, you could be court-martialed
for giving up that info to Dante.
It was a necessary risk.
You don't leave a man behind.
Sooner or later, they're gonna
send someone looking for us.
Let's get you the hell out of here.
That's got to sting.
Yeah, I've been through worse.
What'd the Ninth Circle
want from you, General?
Access to an experimental
weapon I oversaw
during my tenure at DARPA...
Cygnus X-1.
The project was shelved
because it was too dangerous
and unstable.
The goal was to genetically
engineer bacteria
to consume the by-product
of nuclear fission.
So it's a biological weapon
that can literally eat through anything.
That's terrifying.
A weapon like that falls in the
hands of the Ninth Circle, we're...
It won't. We're gonna stop them.
The problem is I don't know where it is.
Archer.
Great.
They are going to use
the intel they get from the assets
to locate the DNA of the
people involved in Cygnus X-1.
That DNA can lead them
to exactly where that weapon is.
If I can piggyback off Archer's signal,
I'll be able to...
Lead us right to them.
It's like we're tracking
the DNA of a DNA tracker.
This is so meta.
We need to be ready the
moment they reactivate Archer.
It's the only way to
locate her signature.
Yeah, like one of those FBI movies
where you have to keep the kidnapper
on the line to trace the call.
Yeah, except the kidnapper
is the tech I invented,
which almost makes me wish I hadn't.
What happened to Archer
putting Smoak Tech on the map?
Well, that was before I realized
all the bad that she could do.
I wanted to invent something
that would help save the city,
and instead I made something
that can destroy it.
Oh, my God. I'm a mad scientist.
Oh, my God, no. It's
so much worse than that.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. I'm my dad.
I am your friend who has
some real-life experience
working with evil geniuses,
and you need to trust me on this one.
You are not one of them, okay?
Okay.
You gonna tell me what's
really bothering you?
I love Team Arrow, but it is not enough.
I need to do something separate.
I need to do something separate
that can still do good,
and that's what Archer
was supposed to be.
You know, my way of making
my mark on the world,
and not as Overwatch.
As me.
Well...
It can still be that.
We just need to get Archer back,
and when we do, you
just need to figure out
how to make sure that
your beautiful creation
is used exactly the way you intended.
You got this, Smoak.
Normally I'm the one off by myself
staring into nothing.
That's usually true.
Usually I'm the one with
the father-son issues.
Oliver, people's lives are in danger
because my stepfather
couldn't be honest with me.
It j... it just surprises me
that you don't see his position.
You know, he's at the top
of the chain of command.
The John Diggle that I know,
he would have done the exact same thing.
Oliver, it sounds like
you're on his side, man.
I'm on your side, but I'm
looking at a guy over there
who cares for you, who
was trying to protect you.
Frankly, he deserves a
little bit more of your trust.
What is this?
Those are the unredacted files
from the Vlatava mission.
Your father didn't die saving his unit.
According to that, he died
because he was negligent.
And he took two marines with him.
The only reason that
anyone got out of there was
General Stewart.
That's not possible.
It's all in there.
I'm sorry to be the one
to tell you this, John.
One Galaxy One power module.
I guess there are perks to having
a gang leader black sheep brother.
Hmm. Sounds like my kind of people.
When do I get to meet him?
I don't know. I haven't
seen JJ in a year,
maybe more.
Funny thing is he used
to be my best friend.
What happened?
Ah, he and my dad started butting heads.
Guess I got caught up in the middle.
And this Deathstroke thing,
that was just a way to rebel.
I just thought one day, he'd outgrow it.
But I tried to reach him.
In the end, I think I just reminded him
of everything my mom and
dad expected him to be.
I'm sorry.
Ain't your fault.
No. I just...
Got so mad at you for
lying to me that I...
I never thought about
how much it must've sucked for you,
and not having anybody
to share things with.
You know, this life.
It was unfair to both of us.
Hey.
JJ has a message for you.
Hey!
This way. Run!
Get back!
Ahem. It's time to go.
Hey, guys, we found the weapon.
Well, technically, the Ninth
Circle did using Archer.
Felicity and I rode their coattails
right into the secure facility,
where it's being stored.
Yup, that's definitely
a secret weapons depot.
Okay, well, now that we
know where we're going,
we just have to figure
out how to get past Archer.
The moment you set foot on-site,
the Ninth Circle will
know that you're there.
So we lose the element of surprise.
I'll call my team.
No. Wait.
We got this.
Copy that.
Let's move.
Perfect.
Perimeter breach detected.
Scanning intruders' DNA. Identifying.
It's your brother and his friends.
Stop them.
Overwatch, do you have a bead on Emiko?
I'm hacked into the exterior cameras,
but she must already be inside.
Without Archer, it's
like I'm flying in blind.
Isn't that what these boosters are for?
Yes. Once you've planted
the signal boosters,
I will be able to take back
control of Archer and find Emiko.
Go find your sister.
We'll plant the boosters.
Oliver, you have company.
Archer has our positions locked.
Where are we with the boosters?
Boosters are in place and activated.
Good to go, Overwatch.
We have uplink.
It's not working.
I can't get through their firewall.
Wait. They locked you out
of your own program? How?
I don't know, but whatever they did,
I can't get back control of Archer.
Get down!
We need an exfil route now! Now!
Most black-level facilities
follow the same blueprint.
There should be a
door near your position
that leads to an access tunnel.
Are you sure?!
Trust me.
Let's move! Move!
We're clear, General. Thanks.
Emiko is headed to the
parking garage with the weapon.
What the hell are you doing?
I'm infecting it with a
self-destruct protocol.
Those boosters were the only reason we
were able to access Archer.
If the Ninth Circle
gets their hands on it,
we may never be able
to access Archer again.
Well, what about all your
hard work, your legacy?
I guess I'll just have
to build a new one.
Archer's gone down.
It doesn't matter. We
got what we came for.
Take the weapon and go.
Me and my brother have
unfinished business.
Emiko!
You need to listen to me.
You need to hear this.
Dante's been lying to you.
He killed your mother.
Liar.
Aah. Ugh.
Hyah!
Listen to me.
He set all this in motion.
He used the Ninth Circle's
resources to cover it up.
He misled you. He
doesn't care about you.
I do.
Emiko.
I told you to go.
And I told you I won't leave you.
We're currently in a tie
between good news and bad news,
the good news being
that I destroyed Archer,
which I can't believe
I'm counting as good news.
The bad news is the Ninth Circle
got away with a very
dangerous biological weapon.
How did things go with Emiko?
I told her that Dante killed her mother,
and it didn't make any difference.
I guess bad news wins this round.
We need to plan our next move.
What is our next move?
Start by figuring out
what the Ninth Circle
intends to do with Cygnus X-1.
I should take this to the D.I.A. brass.
Thank you.
I'll walk you out.
Hey.
I know how much you wanted
Oliver's plan to work.
Maybe I should be
grateful that I can finally
get to see Emiko for who she really is.
Maybe.
It doesn't make it hurt any less.
Hey, I, um, ahem,
wanted to say thank you.
I know this...
I know I haven't made it easy for you.
This is the most time
we've spent together
since you turned 18.
As hard as it may be to believe,
I'm grateful for it.
Yeah, I'd prefer a round of golf
to kidnapping and... And torture.
I know you might not feel the same way,
but you will always be a son to me.
Oliver told me the truth about Vlatava,
about my father.
Why did you let me believe a lie?
You let me hate you.
Every child deserves to believe
that his father is a hero.
And believing it, you became one.
If he could see you today,
I know he would be so proud of you.
If I'm a hero...
It was all because of you...
Sir.
- John.
- Yes, sir.
Call your mother.
I figured out the silver lining
to the whole torpedoing
our only viable product is
that we are gonna save
so much money on servers
because Archer was a power suck.
Not even a chuckle.
I guess I'm not really in the mood
for the whole dark humor thing,
what with our only viable
product being destroyed and all.
I'm sorry I destroyed our golden goose.
Golden egg. Goose?
You know, we could rebuild.
Make it better, less stealable.
Heh.
When you were uploading
the self-destruct code,
I copied Archer's root code.
But with that and your
notes, we could start over.
No. I appreciate that.
But as long as Archer's out there,
it could fall into
the wrong hands. And...
I don't know what my
legacy's going to be,
but it can't be that.
Well, that sounds like someone
who hasn't heard Doc Magnus' offer.
Relax. I know.
Legacy trumps payday.
Oh, I'm really glad you're
the CTO and not the CFO,
because the CFO wouldn't be so chill
about me deleting our only, only asset.
I have a question. Do we have a CFO?
No. Quick question, do we need one?
Hmm, I think we should probably focus
on coming up with our next project,
one that makes us a lot of money.
Yes. One that can help people
but also not lead to mass destruction.
Ohh, if we have to.
Yes, we do. We must.
Hey, for what it's
worth, being Overwatch
won't be your only legacy.
It'll be whatever you do
next here at Smoak Tech.
Because it's not Archer that
was destined to change the world.
It's you... Felicity Smoak.
Thank you.
Heh.
All right, madame helmet,
let's see what you're hiding.
Here goes nothing.
It seems like it worked.
That's not possible.
What is it?
This helmet is a satellite
to a much larger network.
Galaxy One was able to expand Archer.
Hold on. I know big
brother getting bigger
isn't exactly great, but isn't
Archer just a surveillance program?
No, not if you weaponize it.
Wearing one of these would be like
wearing an A.I. powered sixth sense.
Pair that with tech-enhanced
strength and agility.
One of those troopers
was able to take out
half the Canaries.
A whole army of them,
they'll be unstoppable.
Acquiring that weapon
was a great victory,
but Oliver Queen is still a threat.
You need to deal with your
brother before he jeopardizes
the last phase of the plan.
I couldn't agree more.
But first things first.
You lied to me, you betrayed me,
and you killed my mother.
No.
Emiko, you don't understand.
Stop lying...
- Uh!
- And tell me why.
She was the last reminder
of your former life.
Your mother was making you weak
just like your father did.
And I needed you strong
to lead the Ninth Circle.
She was the only family I had.
No, we are your family.
Don't you see? I did it for you.
Uh!
This is for my mother.
Rot in hell.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --