My name is Oliver Queen.
After 6 years
of being a vigilante,
the only way to achieve my goal
and save my city was to confess
to being the Green Arrow.
Now my family and friends must
carry on my mission without me.
I am no longer a hero.
I am inmate 4587.
Previously on Arrow...
I am Dr. Jarrett Parker.
I'm here to conduct your
psychiatric evaluation.
- What is your name?
- My name is Oliver Queen.
Laurel: You kidnapped
and imprisoned the silencer?
Felicity: She's gone.
Laurel: How'd you know she was gonna take the belt?
The RFID chip I installed
in it is gonna lead us straight to Diaz.
- Where is Diaz?
- I don't know,
but I know who does.
Everything that goes on here
goes through the Demon first.
What will you do
after you find this person?
I will use them
to stop Diaz.
Still resistant.
Agh!
Parker: What is your name?
My name is inmate 4587.
[Footsteps]
[Beeping]
On your feet, 4587.
- Who are you?
- Your new best friend.
Now, on your feet.
Hold out your hand.
This will be
on you at all times
to ensure the safety
of yourself
and the other prisoners.
[Beep beep]
Where's Dr. Parker?
He said you're ready
for phase two,
which means you belong
to me now.
- Move.
- Where are you taking me?
Down the rabbit hole.
Welcome home.
Man on P.A.: Inmate 10-13.
Inmate 10-13.
Man: No, no.
No, please, please.
No, no.
Oliver: Where are they
taking him?
Pray you never find out.
Your wife is dead.
Guard: Friend of yours?
No.
Is there a problem?
No. No problem.
Good. Keep it that way.
When's visitation?
There's no visitation
down here.
No... what do... what
do you mean?
It's probably best
that you forget
about anyone
on the outside.
They'll eventually
forget about you.
Bell: I read through your
mission report
from the Switzerland op.
Director Michaels
signed off,
but I noticed a few
abnormalities.
Sir, if this is regarding
the 23 minutes
of unaccounted time
in our field log,
it is because we took
a pit stop
for chocolate.
When in Rome, right?
Do you want some?
You should have some.
- Actually, I'm diabetic.
- Oh, OK. Don't have some.
And I was referring to the
intel we got from that mission.
This is Malcolm Byrd,
a black market arms dealer
specializing in chemical
weapons trading.
The data we pulled
from the bank
tipped us off to
an ongoing transaction
involving a gentleman...
Dr. Nyambi Somto,
biochemist.
Two weeks ago, Somto
went missing
along with a cache
of nerve agents banned
by the Geneva protocols.
We believe that Somto's
trying to sell
these chemicals to Byrd.
Bell: Fortunately, A.R.G.U.S.
already has Somto in custody.
So mission accomplished.
Yay.
Not exactly.
Byrd still believes the buy is going on,
which means we can
catch him.
That's where you
come in, Holt.
Why is there a mock-up
photo of me
I.D.ed as Dr. Somto?
John: We need
an undercover operative
to impersonate Somto
and make contact
with Byrd.
Somto claims he and Byrd
only interfaced online,
never face to face,
thus the mock-up.
Uh, why does it
have to be my face?
We need someone who can pull
off a convincing charade.
You have 14 phds,
including one
in biochemical engineering,
and you're fluent
in 5 different languages,
including Somto's
native tongue.
6, actually.
Nowadays, I'm more
of a chill in the back
of a van,
surrounded by monitors
kind of a guy.
Curtis, we don't
need you to engage.
Just put eyes on Byrd.
Me and my team
will handle the takedown
and package retrieval.
Also...
It's an order.
[Sighs]
[Speaking French]
Remember me?
I need to talk to you.
Oliver: Hey.
I know it was the Demon
who hired you to attack me.
Stop talking to me.
Tell me
who the Demon is.
- Leave me alone.
- Hey. Hey.
Ugh!
It was an accident,
I swear.
[Crackling]
[Grunting]
Looks like you're
having a relapse.
We warned you
about this.
You know what
happens now.
I'm sorry.
It won't happen again.
[Crackling]
[Groaning]
Get him up.
Prisoner: No!
Not through there, please.
[Whimpers]
[Door slams shut]
[Computer beeping]
The tracker is now paired with
a facial recognition program,
targeting all CCTV
and traffic cameras
within a 5-mile radius of the silencer's
location, updating in real time.
So when the silencer
finally finds Diaz,
we'll get
an immediate alert?
Yeah, as long as you don't
adjust any of the inputs,
change any of the settings,
or click any buttons.
I mean, basically,
don't touch anything,
and, yeah, we will be...
we will be... we will be just fine.
I'm not sure I needed
an in-person tutorial
on how to watch
a blinking dot blink.
Sorry. I'm just
really anxious, you know?
We're so close
to getting Diaz,
and the last time I saw
Oliver was a while ago,
and it didn't end
so well.
Relax. Visiting your
husband is not gonna cause
our operation
to fall apart.
[Computer beeps]
Although when the
blinking dot disappears,
that's not good,
is it?
- Crap!
- Hey. I wanted it noted
for the record I did not
touch anything.
- Is the signal dead?
- No. It's just faint.
It's still pinging,
but I'm gonna need to boost the signal
to get a secure lock
on her exact location,
which may take a while,
so maybe I should stay here,
keep an eye on the
program, you know, just...
you can keep an eye on the
program from the road.
OK, but the moment...
the signal comes back online,
you want me to call you.
Yes. Look at us,
you know, finishing
each other's sentences.
- Really...
- go.
Mm-hmm.
If not for Oliver's sake,
at least for my own.
[Sliding]
I understand you've been
looking for the Demon.
Talia?
You survived the explosion
on Lian Yu.
- How?
- You know I'm not so easily defeated.
What are you doing
here?
Oh. I ran afoul
of an old foe in Gotham.
What surprised me was to see you here,
a prisoner.
I believe I taught
you better than that.
Oh, you taught me
many things,
including how
to manipulate people.
So the attack
in the shower,
brick's mind games...
you pushed every button
and pulled every string
just to get me down here.
You always were
a quick study.
Where's Ricardo Diaz?
- I don't know.
- Liar.
I'm many things,
but a liar is not
one of them.
You asked how
I survived Lian Yu.
The answer is barely...
And only with the help of a
drug supplied by your Mr. Diaz,
so in exchange,
I facilitated an attack
on the man who murdered my father,
left me for dead.
More than a fair trade.
There was a time,
Talia,
when aligning yourself with
a man like Ricardo Diaz
would have been
beneath you.
I do what it takes
to survive.
Another lesson you
seem to have forgotten.
I taught you to separate
the man from the monster.
Instead, you exposed
your true identity
for all the world to see
and became the monster you
always feared you were.
What do you want from me?
There is a way out
of slabside,
and I need your help
to escape.
You expect me
to help you
after all the pain
and the suffering
that you inflicted
on my family?
What does it tell you that I
would even ask for your help
after what you've
done to mine?
You don't understand what
they do to people down here.
They reform criminals.
They destroy them.
You and I once stood
on the same side.
We can do it again.
You stood on the same side
as Adrian Chase...
And my son lost
his mother,
so now I'm here,
trying to save
what's left
of my family
because I'm stuck
in a cycle of violence,
and I have been stuck there
since the moment
you told me what to do
with my father's list.
You don't honestly
believe that, Oliver.
There's no Oliver in here.
I'm inmate 4587,
so I'm asking you, however
you broke into my cell...
Get out.
[Indistinct chatter]
[Door opens, keys jingle]
Uh, excuse me.
My husband is Oliver Queen,
and as your colleagues have
already triple-checked,
I am definitely
on his visitor's list.
It's been 20 minutes,
and he's not here.
Inmate 4587 has had his
visitation privileges revoked.
What? What happened?
What are you talking about?
I'm not at Liberty
to say, ma'am.
I'm his wife.
I have a right to see my husband.
I'm afraid you don't.
- You're Oliver's wife.
- Yeah.
I recognize you from the picture
he looks at all the time.
You know Oliver.
I'm kind of
his sidekick in here.
Can you give him
a message for me?
Can you tell him that
I have a lead on Diaz?
- He'll know what it means.
- I know what that means.
He'll be so excited,
but I can't give
him that message.
Why not?
Because he got sent
down to level two.
What's level two?
It's bad,
it's really bad.
It's where they send
the worst of the worst.
But Oliver isn't
It's kind of a long story,
but he got set up,
and then he had to
stab a guard or two.
It all kind of
happened fast,
and there was
a lot of blood.
No. Oliver... Oliver
would never...
he would never do
something like that.
I don't know
if you've noticed,
but the guards aren't exactly
on the side of good in here.
- I should go.
- Wait just one second.
Sorry about
your husband.
He's the best.
Target sighted.
Heading into the sketchy
loading dock to confirm.
OK, Curtis. Once you get
firm confirmation,
we'll move in but not before,
so keep it cool, OK?
Sure. That will be easy
to do in wool pants.
[Speaking French]
John: We still don't
have eyes on Byrd.
Find out why.
Uh...
You do. Yes,
you do, Curtis.
[French accent]
Yes. Yes. I do.
You speak English.
Bring you entire supply
to the mandrake gallery
tomorrow, 8 P.M.
Monsieur Byrd
will be waiting.
You'll get your money then.
Wait.
A second meeting was not
a part of our agreement.
Do we have a problem,
Dr. Somto?
John: What are you doing?
Just agree to the meeting.
Curtis!
No. No problem
at all.
What the hell
was that?
You said this was
a one-time deal...
meet the guy,
get out, done.
Getting roped into the sequel
was not part of the plan!
We're in the field.
Sometimes, plans
change in the field!
You, of all people,
should know that!
Look. My days
in the field were over
the day Oliver went
to prison.
I would like to
keep it that way.
Curtis, we still need
to nail Byrd.
We can't do that
without you!
Well, then you better hope I have
a twin or a clone or something
because I am not
doing that again!
I'm out!
That doesn't make
any sense.
Mr. Queen has
two hours
of visitation
left this month,
so I suggest you get
it straightened out,
or I will have the U.S.
attorney so far up your ass
that you'll have to turn
your head to the left
and cough.
Whew! I mean, no offense
to Black Siren,
but I actually think you're
scarier as an attorney.
Black siren gets results.
All the D.A. got
was stonewalled.
Prison authorities
insisted that Oliver
already maxed his visitation
allowances this month.
How? I've only
been there once. I...
something's wrong.
Obviously.
Sorry. Empathy's
a word I'm learning.
It's a work
in progress.
The prisoner that knew
Oliver said
they took him somewhere
called level two.
We need to figure out
what that is.
We?
Consider it a lesson
in empathy.
OK. I'm accessing
the federal slabside records...
employment,
inmate sentencing,
infrastructure.
I don't know what's
more amusing...
the fact that you just broke
6 laws in front of me
or that you're forcing me to
feel empathetic about it.
What? What's wrong?
Wherever they took Oliver is
completely off the books.
There's no record of anything
at slabside called level two.
[Door sliding open]
Oliver: What the hell
happened to him?
You don't recognize
a dead body?
What goes on
in that room?
That's where they
reform you.
Therapy doesn't kill
people, Talia.
You have a surprising
amount of empathy
for a man
who assaulted you.
He's dead because
of whatever happened
behind those doors.
Then he's one
of the lucky ones.
- What?
- Those who walk out alive
suffer much more.
You have no idea what your doctor
is really doing down here.
Come on.
Dr. Parker's behind this?
Not so quick
a study after all.
You fell
for Parker's lies.
That's what happens when you fail
to keep your two sides separate.
You become weak.
Whatever is happening,
we need to stop it.
These people are
criminals
the likes of which you've spent
the past 6 years putting away.
I'm surprised you
want to help them.
But you were the one who pushed
me towards helping others,
towards fighting
for justice.
You had honor then.
That was
a long time ago.
Now all I care about
is getting out of here.
Are you prepared
to help me with that?
Then we have nothing
further to discuss.
I need to see Dr. Parker.
That's not how it works.
I need his help.
I'm having a relapse.
Hey, Dinah.
Do you have a sec?
Yeah. Uh, is this
about the Hudson case?
Because I would like to
get 3 counts if we can.
Felicity: Hi, Dinah.
Hi. Wow. OK.
Since when are you two friends?
Well, we decided to start a support group
for women who've been attacked by Diaz.
Laurel: Or his assassins.
Do you care to join?
Dinah: Uh, thanks,
I'll pass,
but, hey, maybe you
should get back
to witness protection
and you should head
on back to Earth Two
before you both remember
you hate each other.
OK. Real talk. We're working together,
and we need your help.
- We?
- It's called empathy, Dinah.
I'm about 100% sure that's not
what we're dealing with here,
but what is going on?
Slabside is denying
Felicity access to Oliver.
Felicity: They're keeping him
somewhere called level two,
but there's no record
of anything at slabside
called level two,
so we dove into the employee records,
- and we found something.
- Yes. A psychiatrist by the name
of Dr. Jarrett Parker
with a "p."
We need you to check to see if
there were any complaints made
to the SCPD about Parker
during his private practice.
Surprised you didn't just
hack into SCPD yourself.
Oh, I did. There was just
nothing in the digital records.
I was hoping to do this
the old-fashioned way
and go through the hard
copies in the SCPD archive.
Dinah: OK, but what makes us
believe this Parker guy is shady?
Slabside doesn't have a psychiatric
program for their inmates.
Felicity: Whatever Parker is
doing is not being reported.
Please. If Oliver is in trouble,
we have to help him.
Surprised to see
you here.
Thought you'd be out.
Well, still have
a job to do,
you know, the one
that doesn't involve
possibly dismemberment
and/or death.
Since when have you been
afraid of any of that?
- Since always.
- You know what I mean.
You always ran the risk
of dying with Team Arrow.
Why is it any different
now with A.R.G.U.S.?
It just is.
Let's leave it at that.
No. We can't just
leave it at that.
You're sidelining yourself.
I want to know why.
I just don't have it
in me anymore.
What the hell is that
supposed to mean?
Oliver's in prison.
Even he couldn't outrun the risk
that it takes to be
out there fighting.
This life has cost
me my marriage,
gotten me stabbed,
and people I love shot.
Maybe you and Lyla
and everyone else has
what it takes
to cope with it,
but I can't keep
lying to myself.
Being Mr. Terrific...
It's just not
me anymore.
John: I've been at war,
seen the faces of men who are done.
Curtis, that is
not you.
Yeah. I am pretty sure
that is me.
[Scoffs]
14 phds, fluent
in multiple languages,
genius, bronze medal
decathlete.
Mr. Terrific isn't just an
alter ego you can lay aside.
It's who you are,
Curtis.
The only real risk you're running
is denying the truth in that.
Now, I respect your decision
to sit out this mission.
Just make sure
it's the right one.
When did you notice
the rage happening?
When I saw the inmate with
the grim reaper tattoo.
Interesting. Why do you think you
responded so negatively to him?
He was among the group who
attacked me on level one.
Hmm. Well, the good news is you didn't
give in to your violent tendencies.
You came here.
That means the treatment is working.
Dr. Parker, the main reason
that I didn't do anything was
he was dead.
I...
I saw him being w-wheeled out of the room
with the blue door.
Unfortunately, some
inmates don't respond
as well as you
to the process.
When you're breaking
new scientific ground,
setbacks are inevitable.
It seems like a... ahem...
prisoner dying is
a little bit more
than a setback.
Look at what we've done
together,
h-how we've eliminated
that part of yourself
that was trapped
in a cycle of violence.
Imagine that
on a grander scale.
The world would be
a much safer place.
Right, but people
are dying.
What about them?
That sounds like something
the old you would say, 4587,
the hero who insisted on
righting the wrongs of strangers
at the expense of the
safety and well-being
of the people he loves.
I thought you weren't
that person anymore.
I'm not.
Good.
You need to continue
focusing on yourself,
on the man you
need to be
for the sake
of your family.
If you're unable
to do that,
we'll be forced
to pursue some
other treatment options.
Felicity:
Why is an arrest report from 1985
in the same box as an
employee file from 2002?
It doesn't make
any sense!
I know, after the department
switched to computerized files,
they just stopped taking
care of this place.
You mean, the SCPD is
late to the digital party?
Wow! Shocking.
Felicity, there may be
some other options.
Now I still have friends
in the FBI.
- I can call...
- because the FBI is known
for their speed
and efficiency?
Do you have
a better idea?
Yes. I asked the U.S.
attorney to file a motion
compelling slabside to
release all their records.
Oh, and you think
my way is slow!
That could take weeks,
months.
Oliver may not have weeks,
he may not have months!
He may not even have days!
We don't know where he is.
I had no idea what his life
had become in there,
the things that
he's had to do.
Laurel: Felicity, you've been focused
on catching a homicidal maniac.
If anybody understands
that, it's Oliver.
Dinah: And Oliver's the one
who decided to go to prison.
This isn't on you.
And I was pissed
about that decision.
I should have
visited him more.
I should have been
able to prevent this.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Look. I get it, OK,
but trust me,
there is nothing
you could have done.
You have to stop
blaming yourself.
I thought that the worst
thing that could happen
was me losing my
husband to prison.
Well, what if I lose
him permanently?
Ahem. If you still want to get out of here,
we go tonight.
Well,
I'm glad you've finally come to your senses,
though I suspect
your willingness
to conspire comes
with... Conditions.
I need you to help me expose
the truth about Dr. Parker.
And how do you
propose we do that?
The evidence we need is
behind those blue doors.
We break in, we get it,
we escape.
That would be unwise.
You've seen what happens to
people who go into that room.
They come out
in body bags.
Talia, we are doing
this my way,
or we're not doing
it at all.
You'd risk both our lives
to help these prisoners,
despite knowing
that every last one
is a murderer or worse?
These people are being treated
like they are disposable.
- No one deserves that.
- Tell me, did you feel
that same compassion when you rammed
a sword through my father's chest?
No, because back then,
I still allowed the monster
that you helped unleash
take over.
Don't insinuate that my father's
death was somehow my fault.
I... Ra's' death
was my fault.
I couldn't see past what he
intended to do to my city,
so I didn't stop and think
about his family,
and for that,
I am truly sorry.
I know you hate me...
But I was
your student once,
and we trusted
each other completely.
We need to find
that trust again
because it is the only way
both of us will get
what we want.
John: Remember, the area surrounding
this meet is densely populated.
Byrd will not hesitate to leverage
this if he suspects something's up.
Dismissed.
But he won't, right,
as long as you all send
me in there alone?
Curtis, that's the hope,
but don't worry, man. You got this.
Right. I just need to turn off the
part of my brain going, "aah!"
OK. Ready.
What's the plan?
We're gonna give him
exactly what he wants.
The chemical will be
housed in this.
The case contains
a hidden targeting system.
Use it to scan the building
and locate the hostiles.
That way, we'll know exactly
where to hit and how hard.
[Scanner beeping]
Once you locate Byrd, hand
off the case and get clear.
We'll launch the attack
on your go.
Dr. Somto.
[Speaking French]
Targets acquired.
Make the exchange
and get clear.
[Guns cocking]
[French accent]
A binary chemical bomb.
I didn't take you for someone
as crude as a terrorist.
What you call crude
I see as lucrative.
All I needed was
a fall guy,
and you were
far too perfect a mark.
Perhaps you are forgetting
you are standing
right in front
of the bomb.
You've heard of remote detonation,
haven't you?
For someone so smart,
are you really this dumb?
[Normal Voice] Well, actually,
if I wanted to do something
super-dumb, I'd probably
do something stupid like
tackle you to the ground,
take that tablet,
and shove it
down your throat.
That's our mark.
Get ready to move.
[Laughs]
Still a sense of humor.
Quite impressive for
someone about to die.
Guess I'm just
ready for it.
I do have one
request first.
Can you give me a countdown
before you kill me?
First time I've
heard that one.
I wasn't talking
to you.
[Beeping]
Too bad for you
I am pretty damn smart.
The bomb's disarmed.
Byrd's down.
- Are you all right?
- I don't know.
Do I still have my legs?
I got so much adrenaline
going right now,
I can't even tell.
Come on, Talia.
Come on, come on, come on.
Hey!
Stop!
About time.
You know, they say
the mark of a great teacher
is when her pupil
finally surpasses her.
Unh!
What... what
are you doing?
What I should have done
from the beginning...
let you perish.
- Brace yourself.
- God, I could use a nap.
[Electricity crackling,
both groaning]
That's enough of that.
Take them to the room.
Ugh. Yeah. Felicity,
I hate to say it,
but I think we might need to
try a different approach here.
It's not that we're
giving up.
It's just that we need to
figure out another way to...
found him.
During Parker's
private practice,
he was also a defendant
in 3 malpractice cases,
all settled
out of court.
Dinah: Check this out.
Robert Goodman.
It's one
of his patients.
22-year-old male referred
to Parker back in 2015
after experiencing
several violent outbursts.
Parker promised the parents he
could make their son docile.
Instead, Goodman began suffering
spontaneous bouts of amnesia.
What the hell was this guy
doing to these people?
It's not clear.
Some sort of experimental treatment.
Looks like Parker's
making a career out of it
because I am looking at
about 8 different cases
that are exactly
like Goodman.
Oh, my god!
Felicity, what is it?
"As Goodman's amnesia
became more frequent,
"he eventually lost all sense
of identity and was"...
this is what they're
gonna do to Oliver.
They're going to
erase him.
I'm disappointed
in you, 4587.
It's always so unfortunate
when a study doesn't work out,
but this failure is
especially painful.
You're a monster.
[Bangs table]
We could have done
such great things together,
helped so many people.
Oliver: This isn't
helping people!
I misjudged you.
I thought after
our work together,
you were committed to breaking
your family's cycle of violence.
My father pushed
people away.
He kept secrets,
and I made
those same mistakes,
but if I choose
to break the cycle,
I'm gonna do it
my way.
I suggest you hold
very still, 4587.
Unh!
My name is Oliver Queen!
[Bones crack]
Talia: Well, it seems
like you've picked up
a few new tricks
without me.
These things are
so barbaric.
[Alarm blaring]
Must have
an anti-tampering alarm.
Man on P.A.:
Lockdown procedure initiated.
All inmates should return
to their cells immediately.
I've got the key card.
I've got the file.
We got to go.
We'll not be able
to go quietly.
[People shouting]
Guard: Hey!
Where the hell
are you two going?
We're on lockdown.
You're supposed to be
in your cells.
I said, get
back to your cells.
[Clicking]
Straight ahead.
[Heavy footsteps]
Talia: Do you think they
realized they're outmatched?
I think
they're about to.
[Guards groaning]
[Beep]
This goes down
to the water.
Right. The only way out
is through the morgue.
Shameful way to
treat your dead.
Guard: They went this way.
Over here!
They won't be long.
We must go.
I need you to give
this to Felicity.
If you stay,
you will die.
If I leave, I'm
a fugitive forever.
I won't do that
to my family.
All those years ago,
you were wrong.
Giving the monster an identity
didn't contain the darkness.
It just gave it power.
Separating
into two selves,
hiding in the shadows...
That was never
the answer.
[Bang against door]
Guard: Someone
barricaded this.
Get something
to break this down.
I will make sure
your wife gets this
and that she knows her husband
is as stubborn as ever.
[Crash]
I'll hold them off.
[Bang against door]
[Bang]
[Footsteps]
Time to go, inmate.
Where are you
taking me?
This whole place is
getting shut down.
You're going back
to level one.
Bethany Snow: Despite official
denials of the allegation
of prisoner abuse
a t slabside penitentiary,
documents provided by SCPD
detailing the cruel
and unusual practices
of Dr. Jarrett Parker,
a suspect
in the cold case death
of Robert Goodman,
appear to connect
the controversial therapist
to the prison, bringing
those denials into question...
Whoo! One
for team Felicity.
I'm still workshopping
the name.
Question is which
guardian angel do we
have to thank for this
little baby?
Oh, don't know,
don't care.
Oliver is back
sleeping soundly
in his regular maximum
security prison cell
with no evil scientists
trying to fry his brain.
This, plus what we got
from the records room,
is enough to earn Dr. Parker
his own cozy
little prison cell.
You know, slabside's got a real PR
nightmare on their hands right now.
What if we could use that for more
than just shutting down level two?
We can use this to appeal
Oliver's conviction.
We can use it to get
Oliver out of prison.
[Car alarm is disarmed]
[Electricity crackling]
You suffering
from a relapse, doctor?
Allow me to provide
the cure.
No!
[Splat]
You haven't made it
home yet?
Ah. Wanted to get the
mission report wrapped up,
make sure there were no
abnormalities for bell to find.
Yeah. Well, mission reports don't
usually take all night.
Besides, this was
an on-the-books op.
Shouldn't be any
abnormalities.
- Then why'd I find one?
- What's this?
Something I lifted off Byrd
before he went into custody.
- Why?
- Lyla copied the bank data
because she suspected A.R.G.U.S.
has something to hide.
That data led us
to Byrd.
If there's a deeper
connection that A.R.G.U.S.
Doesn't want
anyone to find,
I figure we should
know first.
- Worth the risk, right?
- Did you find anything?
Check it out.
It's a painting?
It took you all night
to decrypt
a single image?
Do you realize how many decryption
algorithms I had to run
just to get the drive
to boot up?
This thing's security
had security.
All right. Looks like someone
doesn't want us to see this.
- What's the origin?
- Well, this painting is
from the 19th century by a French
artist named Jean-Lon Grme.
The title is "Dante,
he hath seen hell."
- Hidden meaning?
- Pfft. It's art.
There's always
a hidden meaning.
We just need to find out
what it is.
[Bars clattering]
[Indistinct chatter]
Guess the morgue isn't the only
way out of level two after all.
I'm just glad I made it
out of there.
Felicity will be, too.
What do you mean?
She came looking
for you in visitation.
I told her
about level two.
Was she OK?
Yeah. She asked me
to give you a message.
What message?
She's got a lead
on Diaz.
She's close to getting him.
That's good news, right?
Well, all this saving
of your husband crap has...
well, it's made me
very hungry,
so I'm gonna go
get a pizza.
- OK.
- If you...
Want to come or if you're hungry.
I don't know.
Are you asking me out
on a friend date?
- No.
- [Cell phone chirps]
Power boost is complete,
which means
we have a signal.
Laurel: Wha t is the silencer
doing there?
[Silence]
[Silence stops]
Get what you came for?
Diaz: Yup.
Just making good
on an old promise.
[Grunting]
Isn't that right,
Anatoly?
Huh?
Man: Greg, move your head!