PREVIOUSLY ON "ARROW"...
THIS PLACE LOOKS
EXACTLY LIKE IT DID
WHEN I WAS 13.
OLIVER: WE HAD PLANNED
TO COME BACK HERE
WITH BOTH OF YOU.
MIA: YEAH. THAT DIDN'T
REALLY WORK OUT.
BECAUSE I DIED.
HAVE YOU COME TO DOUBT
YOUR COMMITMENT
TO THIS MISSION?
OLIVER: IT MIGHT HELP
IF I ACTUALLY KNEW WHY.
MONITOR: THE RECOVERY
OF YOUR UNIVERSE
WILL REQUIRE
A SINGLE TASK.
YOU MUST BETRAY
OLIVER QUEEN.
LAUREL: IF SAVING IT MEANS
GOING BACK
TO THE PERSON
THAT I USED TO BE,
THE WHAT THE HELL
IS THE POINT?
I'M SORRY.
[TRANQUILIZER DARTS FIRE]
SPORTS ANNOUNCER:
TARK DRIVES THE LANE.
KICKS IT TO ALDRICH
IN THE CORNER FOR 3.
BINGO! COUNT IT AND THE FOUL!
THAT'S AN 8-0 RUN
BY THE COMETS,
WHO HAVE STORMED
ALL THE WAY BACK
TO TIE IT UP HERE
IN THE FOURTH QUARTER.
MIA: NO WAY.
IT TASTES THE SAME.
CONNOR: I'M TELLING YOU
THIS BIG BELLY BURGER'S
JUST BETTER.
WILLIAM:
I THINK HE'S RIGHT.
THIS IS PRE-GWESPIN
FOODS MERGER.
MIA: DAD, WHAT ARE YOU
STILL DOING HERE?
OLIVER: HOW DID WE
GET HERE?
WHAT DO YOU
MEAN?
UH, I WAS ON A ROOF
WITH JOHN AND LAUREL,
AND WE WERE TRANQED.
YEAH. BY LYLA.
DAD SAID IT WAS
ALL JUST A BIG
MISUNDERSTANDING.
AHEM. WHAT DID WE DO
WITH BUROV'S PLAN
FOR THE WEAPON?
YOU SAID WE DIDN'T
NEED IT ANYMORE.
WHY? THE MONITOR'S
STILL OUT THERE.
HE'S STILL A THREAT.
DAD, ARE YOU OK?
YOU...YOU LOOK LIKE
YOU DON'T REMEMBER
ANY OF THIS.
I...
I NEED TO TALK TO JOHN.
CONNOR: THAT SHOULD
BE EASY.
HE'S WAITING
FOR YOU AT THAT
FANCY FUNDRAISER.
WHAT FUNDRAISER?
THE ONE YOU'RE
VERY LATE FOR.
I MEAN, YOU DO REMEMBER
YOU'RE OLIVER QUEEN, RIGHT?
[ELEVATOR DINGS]
[JAZZ PLAYING]
[WOMAN LAUGHING]
MAN: HEY, QUEEN,
WHAT'S THE DIFFERENCE
BETWEEN A COP
AND THE GREEN ARROW?
A COP DOESN'T NEED
TO PLAY DRESS-UP
TO DO HIS JOB.
HA. YEAH, SURE. WHOA!
-I'M SO SORRY, MR. QUEEN.
-IT'S FINE, IT'S FINE.
JOHN: THERE YOU
ARE, MAN.
THE PARTY STARTED
AN HOUR AGO, OLIVER.
DO YOU REMEMBER
GETTING TRANQED
LAST NIGHT?
YEAH. UH, LYLA
FEELS AWFUL
ABOUT THAT.
BY THE WAY,
THAT WASN'T LAST NIGHT.
-THAT WAS TWO DAYS AGO.
-WHAT? NO.
NO, NO. THAT...
JOHN, THAT IS THE LAST THING
THAT I REMEMBER
BEFORE WAKING UP
IN MY APARTMENT
EARLIER TONIGHT.
YOU OK, MAN?
NO. THIS IS...THIS...
IS THIS THE...
THIS IS THE MONITOR.
-OLIVER.
-YOUR WIFE IS WORKING
WITH THE MONITOR, JOHN.
WHAT...
LYLA: I THOUGHT WE
ALREADY SETTLED THIS.
I HAVE BEEN WORKING
WITH THE MONITOR
BUT AS A DOUBLE AGENT,
WHICH I TOLD YOU
ON THE ROOF.
I DON'T...I DON'T
REMEMBER THAT.
I'M NOT REMEMBERING
ANYTHING.
OLIVER, LOOK. JUST
MAYBE YOU SHOULD
GO HOME, MAN,
GET A LITTLE SLEEP, OK?
OLIVER, THERE YOU ARE.
MAYOR'S LOOKING
FOR YOU. COME ON.
WHAT?
-WHAT HAPPENED THERE?
-OH.
CAN'T GIVE A SPEECH
WITH A STAINED SHIRT.
GIVE A S...WHAT SPEECH?
I'M GIVING A SPEECH?
VERY FUNNY.
YOUR JOINT REMARKS
WITH THE MAYOR.
RENE, UM,
SERIOUS QUESTION.
WHEN DID PALMER TECH
GET REBUILT?
YOU REALLY NEED TO DROP
THIS AMNESIA ROUTINE QUICK.
THIS FUNDRAISER IS
OUR ONLY CHANCE TO TAKE
THE SCPD VIGILANTE
PILOT PROGRAM GLOBAL.
THE MAYOR NEEDS YOU
TO BE ON POINT.
-HE'S WAITING FOR YOU.
-HE WHO?
ISN'T...ISN'T
POLLARD THE MAYOR?
QUENTIN:
IN HER DREAMS MAYBE.
WHAT'S THE MATTER,
OLIVER?
YOU LOOK LIKE
YOU SEEN A GHOST.
SO LISTEN. I WAS
THINKING ABOUT MAKING
A FEW CHANGES
TO THE SPEECH,
SO I FIGURED I SHOULD
RUN IT BY YOU FIRST.
THIS IS NOT POSSIBLE.
THIS IS...
WHAT? DON'T TELL ME
YOU'RE SCARED
OF A LITTLE LAST-MINUTE
MEMORIZATION, OLIVER.
IT'S BEEN A WHILE
SINCE I'VE SEEN YOU.
COUPLE OF DAYS MAYBE.
YOU'RE LOOKING AT ME
LIKE IT'S BEEN YEARS.
NO. YOU'RE RIGHT.
A COUPLE DAYS.
RIGHT. SO LISTEN.
I WAS THINKING
ABOUT ADDING A LINE
ABOUT, YOU KNOW,
ME TELLING YOU IT
WAS A BAD IDEA
TO UNMASK,
BUT, YOU KNOW, MAYBE
A JOKE ABOUT HOW
YOU'D RATHER TAKE IT
TO SUPERMAX
THAN TAKE MY ADVICE.
HEH. YOU KNOW?
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
YOU KNOW THAT I WENT
TO SLABSIDE?
UH...YEAH.
WHAT'S THAT,
YOUR WAY OF SAYING
I SHOULD HAVE COME
VISIT MORE OFTEN?
QUENTIN, RIGHT BEFORE
I TURNED MYSELF IN...
DIAZ SHOT YOU, RIGHT?
OH. YEAH.
THAT SON OF A BITCH
ALMOST KILLED ME.
ALMOST DIED IN THE O.R.
YOU DON'T REMEMBER?
I REMEMBER IT DIFFERENTLY.
WELL, THE DOCTORS
CALLED IT A MIRACLE.
I WAS WITHOUT OXYGEN
FOR SO LONG,
I SHOULD HAVE BEEN
6 FEET UNDER.
FELT LIKE I ESCAPED
MY FATE OR SOMETHING.
RENE: HEY. THERE'S
SOMETHING YOU NEED TO SEE.
SO...THERE'S
A HOSTAGE SITUATION
AT THE SCPD.
THE LEADER'S DEMANDING
TO MEET WITH THE MAYOR.
NO. NO. YOU CAN'T
GO DOWN THERE.
RENE: WE'LL CALL IN
A SPECIAL-OPS TEAM.
I'M THE MAYOR. NOBODY
DOES MY DIRTY WORK FOR ME.
GIVE MY APOLOGIES
TO THE GUESTS.
I'M...I'M GONNA COME
WITH YOU.
OK, BUT YOU MIGHT WANT
TO BRING A CHANGE OF CLOTHES
BECAUSE SOMETHING TELLS ME
WE'RE GONNA NEED
THE GREEN GUY.
[SIRENS, HELICOPTER FLYING]
GET THE FEDS ON THE LINE.
TELL THEM I NEED BACKUP
HERE NOW, RIGHT NOW.
QUENTIN: WHAT'S
THE SITUATION, CAPTAIN?
ARMED MERCS STORMED
MY PRECINCT,
TOOK A DOZEN
OF MY GUYS HOSTAGE.
HOW'D THEY GET
BY YOUR MEN?
IT'S A LONG STORY
THAT I DON'T HAVE
TIME TO TELL.
THE ONLY DEMAND WAS TO
SPEAK TO THE MAYOR.
ALL RIGHT. WELL, I'LL
GO TALK TO THEM.
I APPRECIATE THAT,
BUT THERE IS NO WAY
I'M SENDING YOU IN THERE.
LISTEN. I WORE THE BLUES
A LONG TIME
BEFORE I WORE
THIS MONKEY SUIT, OK?
-I CAN HOLD MY OWN.
-I KNOW, SIR.
IT'S NOT THE POINT.
SHE'S RIGHT.
IT'S TOO RISKY.
SAYS THE MAN WHO RISKS
HIS LIFE EVERY DAY
FOR THIS CITY?
GIVE ME A VEST.
I'LL GO IN THERE,
I'LL DISTRACT
THE SON OF A BITCH,
AND IN THE MEANTIME,
YOU SNEAK AROUND THE BACK
AND DO YOUR THING, OK?
THE LONGER
THIS DRAGS ON,
THE WORSE IT GETS.
LET ME DO THIS.
I'LL HAVE
HIS BACK.
I WANT YOU ON COMMS
THE WHOLE TIME.
SURE.
THIS IS MAYOR
QUENTIN LANCE.
I'M UNARMED.
I'M COMING IN.
-THAT'S FAR ENOUGH.
-ALL RIGHT.
JUST...JUST TAKE
IT EASY, OK?
TAKE IT EASY.
OLIVER ON COMMS:
I'M IN POSITION.
KEEP HIM TALKING.
YOU ASKED FOR ME.
HERE I AM.
WHAT DO YOU WANT TO
TALK ABOUT WITH ME?
YOU'RE THE MAYOR.
YOU'RE A GUY
WHO CAN MAKE THINGS
HAPPEN.
WHY DON'T YOU LET
A FEW OF THESE
GUYS GO WHILE WE TALK?
SO I CAN GET STORMED
BY THE COPS?
NO, THANKS.
I'M NOT STUPID.
BUT IT WOULD SHOW
THAT YOU DON'T WANT
ANYBODY TO GET HURT
BECAUSE IF ANYBODY
GETS HURT,
YOU'RE
IN REAL TROUBLE.
ACTUALLY, I THINK
YOU'RE ALREADY
IN TROUBLE.
I'M THE ONE HOLDING
THE GUN.
OLIVER: NOT FOR LONG.
PUT IT DOWN.
MAN: AGH. ERR.
OLIVER: THIS...IS...OVER.
THIS ISN'T OVER
UNTIL YOU STOP IT,
OLIVER.
THAT'S THE ONLY
WAY OUT.
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
-NO!
-QUENTIN!
[EXPLOSION]
AHH!
SPORTS ANNOUNCER:
TARK DRIVES THE LANE.
KICKS IT TO ALDRICH
IN THE CORNER FOR 3.
BINGO! COUNT IT AND THE FOUL!
THAT'S AN 8-0 RUN
BY THE COMETS,
WHO HAVE STORMED
ALL THE WAY BACK
TO TIE IT UP HERE
IN THE FOURTH QUARTER.
88 APIECE. WHAT A COMEBACK
FOR THE COMETS,
AND THERE'S A TIMEOUT...
MIA: NO WAY.
IT TASTES THE SAME.
CONNOR: I'M TELLING YOU
THIS BIG BELLY BURGER'S
JUST BETTER.
WILLIAM: I THINK
HE'S RIGHT.
THIS IS PRE-GWESPIN
FOODS MERGER.
OOH, DAD. WHAT ARE YOU
STILL DOING HERE?
I'M LATE
FOR A FUNDRAISER.
YEAH. REALLY LATE.
WILLIAM: YOU WANT A BURGER?
THOSE THINGS NEVER
HAVE GOOD FOOD.
DID SOMETHING HAPPEN
AT THE SCPD HEADQUARTERS?
LIKE WHAT?
NEVER MIND.
[DING, JAZZ PLAYING]
[WOMAN LAUGHING]
MAN: HEY, QUEEN.
WHAT'S THE DIFFERENCE
BETWEEN A COP
AND THE GREEN ARROW?
A COP DOESN'T NEED
TO PLAY DRESS-UP
TO DO HIS JOB.
HA HA HA!
-OOH! NICE REFLEXES, MR. QUEEN.
-THANK YOU.
THERE YOU ARE.
YOU KNOW THE PARTY STARTED
AN HOUR AGO, RIGHT?
I NEED TO SPEAK
WITH YOU.
UH, THIS IS GONNA
SOUND CRAZY.
UM...I HAVE BEEN
HERE BEFORE.
SO HAVE YOU.
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
ABOUT THE MONITOR DROPPING
ME INTO SOME SORT
OF ALTERNATE REALITY
T-T-TIME LOOP
OR SOMETHING,
WHERE EVERYTHING
IS DIFFERENT,
WHERE LANCE IS
STILL ALIVE.
OLIVER, LANCE HAS
ALWAYS BEEN ALIVE.
NO, HE HASN'T.
YOU JUST DON'T REMEMBER
BECAUSE THE MONITOR
HAS DONE SOMETHING
TO PEOPLE'S MEMORIES,
BUT I...I THINK I KNOW
THE WAY OUT OF THIS,
BUT I...I NEED TO STOP
A BOMB AT THE SCPD.
OLIVER, WILL YOU JUST
CALM DOWN, MAN?
IF THERE WAS A BOMB,
WE WOULD KNOW ABOUT IT.
LYLA WOULD KNOW
ABOUT IT.
LYLA'S A PART OF THIS.
LYLA: PART OF WHAT?
JOHN: OLIVER SEEMS TO
THINK THAT HE'S CAUGHT
IN SOME SORT
OF TIME LOOP.
IF WE'RE TRAVELING
BACK IN TIME,
I'D LIKE TO REVISIT
MY 20S.
I...I NEED TO SPEAK
WITH QUENTIN.
THE MAYOR'S WAITING
FOR ME.
YEAH. HOW'D YOU KNOW?
MR. MAYOR.
OH. HEY, OLIVER.
LISTEN.
I, UH...I MADE A FEW
LAST-MINUTE CHANGES
TO THE SPEECH, SO...
-WE NEED TO TALK.
-SURE. LET'S.
UH, YEAH. I WANTED TO
RUN THESE CHANGES
BY YOU ANYWAY.
YOU WANT TO ADD
A JOKE ABOUT SLABSIDE,
ABOUT HOW I WOULD
RATHER SPEND TIME
IN A SUPERMAX
THAN TAKE YOUR ADVICE.
YOU STEAL A COPY
OF MY SPEECH
OR SOMETHING?
WE'VE HAD THIS
EXACT CONVERSATION ALREADY.
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
FULLY AWARE OF HOW
THIS IS GOING TO SOUND.
QUENTIN, I'M TRAPPED
IN SOME SORT OF...
TIME LOOP,
WHERE THE SAME EVENTS
JUST KEEP REPEATING
THEMSELVES.
LIKE "GROUNDHOG DAY."
SURE EXCEPT THIS ONE
ENDS A LOT OF PEOPLE DEAD,
INCLUDING THE TWO OF US.
OK. HOW CAN I HELP?
DO YOU ACTUALLY
BELIEVE ME?
OLIVER, I'VE SEEN
ONE DAUGHTER DIE
AND COME BACK
TO LIFE TWICE.
I'VE SEEN ANOTHER
COME FROM SOME
OTHER EARTH.
I'VE SEEN A GUY
IN RED RUN SO FAST
HE CAN REVERSE TIME.
THIS IS NOT EXACTLY
OUTSIDE THE NORM,
IS IT?
ALSO, I'M DONE
LEARNING MY LESSON
ABOUT DOUBTING YOU
BECAUSE THAT
ALWAYS BITES ME
IN THE ASS. HEH.
[SIGHS]
WHAT HAPPENS NOW?
VERY SHORTLY, WE ARE
GONNA LEARN THAT
THERE IS A HOSTAGE SITUATION
AT THE SCPD.
THEY'RE GOING TO INSIST
THAT THEY TALK TO YOU
AND ONLY YOU.
AND HOW DOES IT
GO SOUTH?
THERE'S A HIDDEN
EXPLOSIVE DEVICE
THAT I DIDN'T KNOW ABOUT
THE FIRST TIME THROUGH,
AND JUDGING FROM THE BLAST,
IT'S UNDERNEATH THE BUILDING.
OK. SO YOU FIND IT,
YOU KEEP US
FROM GOING BOOM.
-WHAT THEN?
-I BREAK OUT OF THE LOOP.
GREAT.
OUT OF THE LOOP.
HERE YOU ARE.
THERE'S SOMETHING
YOU NEED TO SEE.
[SIRENS, HELICOPTER]
GET THE FEDS
ON THE LINE.
TELL THEM I NEED
BACKUP NOW.
WHAT'S THE SITUATION,
CAPTAIN?
ARMED MERCS STORMED
THE PRECINCT,
TOOK A DOZEN
OF MY GUYS HOSTAGE.
THEY HAVE A BOMB.
WE ALREADY
DID A SWEEP OF
THE ENTIRE BUILDING.
IT'S NOT IN THE BUILDING.
IT'S UNDERNEATH IT.
HOW COULD YOU
POSSIBLY KNOW THAT?
I TRUST HIM.
INSTINCT THING.
SO WHAT DO YOU
WANT TO DO?
THIS IS
MAYOR QUENTIN LANCE.
I'M UNARMED.
I'M COMING IN.
STOP RIGHT THERE.
OH. IT'S YOU.
WOULD YOU RELAX?
WE ARE BOTH HERE
FOR THE SAME THING.
HEY. HOW DID YOU KNOW
TO COME DOWN HERE?
I MAY HAVE LEARNED
ABOUT THE EXISTENCE
OF THIS PLACE AS A PART
OF A FORMER CAREER.
HOW DID YOU KNOW
ABOUT THE BOMB?
YOU WOULDN'T BELIEVE ME
IF I TOLD YOU.
WELL, ACTUALLY, SINCE
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO
REMEMBER ANYWAY,
THERE IS A CRAZY SPACE GOD
WHO HAS ME TRAPPED
IN A TIME LOOP.
YEAH? ME, TOO.
IT'S MY SECOND
TIME THROUGH.
SAME. I WAKE UP
IN THE BUNKER.
I WAKE UP
IN MY APARTMENT,
SO CLEARLY,
THE MONITOR IS
DOING THIS.
-YOU MEAN PUNISHING US?
-YEAH.
WE ARE THE TWO PEOPLE
WHO HAVE ROYALLY
PISSED HIM OFF THE MOST.
IN RUSSIA,
I DISOBEYED HIM,
AND YOU...YOU TRIED TO
DESTROY HIM.
AT LEAST WE'RE IN IT
TOGETHER NOW.
I THINK DISARMING
THAT IS THE WAY
OUT OF HERE.
HOW LONG DO YOU THINK
UNTIL THIS THING
GOES BOOM?
OH. YOUR GUESS IS
AS GOOD AS MINE.
QUENTIN'S UPSTAIRS
BUYING US SOME TIME.
-QUENTIN...HE'S HERE?
-YEAH.
[BUZZING]
I THINK WE JUST
ACTIVATED SOME KIND
OF FAILSAFE.
LOOK. WE NEED MORE
TIME WITH THE NEXT
LOOP, LAUREL.
IT WOULD PROBABLY
HELP IF WE FOUND EACH
OTHER FASTER NEXT TIME.
THERE'S A PARTY
AT THE PALMER TECH
BUILDING.
-MEET ME THERE.
-ARE WE TALKING FORMAL WEAR OR...
SPORTS ANNOUNCER:
TARK DRIVES THE LANE.
KICKS IT TO ALDRICH
IN THE CORNER FOR 3.
BINGO!
MIA: NO WAY.
IT'S THE SAME.
CONNOR: I'M TELLING YOU.
THIS BIG BELLY BURGER
IS JUST BETTER.
GUESS YOU REALIZED
YOU'RE LATE.
SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
[DING, JAZZ PLAYING]
[WOMAN LAUGING]
MAN: HEY, QUEEN.
WHAT'S THE DIFFERENCE
BETWEEN A COP
AND THE GREEN ARROW?
COP DOESN'T NEED TO PLAY
DRESS-UP TO DO HIS JOB.
SORRY.
MR. MAYOR.
HEY, OLIVER. LISTEN.
I MADE A FEW
LAST-MINUTE CHANGES
TO THE SPEECH.
AND YOU FIGURED YOU SHOULD
RUN THEM BY ME FIRST.
YEAH, EXACTLY.
HEY, BABY GIRL.
I DIDN'T THINK YOU
WERE GONNA MAKE IT.
ME EITHER.
YOU OK, HONEY?
I'M JUST REALLY
HAPPY TO SEE YOU.
OH. I'M HAPPY
TO SEE YOU, TOO.
THOUGH I GOT TO SAY
I'M GLAD YOU LEFT
THE BLACK LIPSTICK
AT HOME TONIGHT.
YOU KNOW THAT I'M
EARTH-2 LAUREL.
WHO ELSE WOULD
YOU BE?
LOOK. I'M REALLY SORRY
TO INTERRUPT,
BUT YOU AND I
NEED TO GO.
YOU'RE COMING WITH US.
WE NEED YOUR HELP.
[SIRENS, HELICOPTER]
WHAT DO YOU MEAN
THERE'S A BOMB?
OLIVER: I KNOW
HOW TO STOP IT,
BUT YOU HAVE
TO TRUST ME.
I'M GONNA NEED
A VEST.
NOT THIS TIME,
QUENTIN.
THIS IS
MAYOR QUENTIN LANCE.
YOU WANTED TO TALK.
LET'S TALK.
THE DETONATOR OPERATES
ON AN OSCILLATING FREQUENCY.
IF WE CAN FIND
THE RIGHT ONE,
WE SHOULD BE ABLE
TO DISRUPT IT.
QUENTIN: VINCENT,
LISTEN TO ME.
I KNOW YOU DON'T
REALLY WANT TO DO THIS.
VINCENT: AND I KNOW THAT
IF YOU DON'T GET IN HERE
THESE MEN ARE
GONNA DIE.
I HAVE AN IDEA.
[CANARY CRY]
WE DID IT.
OK. FINE. YOU DID IT.
WE STOPPED THE BOMB.
WHAT THE HELL ARE WE
STILL DOING HERE?
I DON'T...I...
WE MUST HAVE
MISSED SOMETHING.
-NO!
[GUNSHOT]
LAUREL: NO! NO!
SPORTS ANNOUNCER:
TARK DRIVES THE LANE.
KICKS IT TO ALDRICH
IN THE CORNER FOR 3.
BINGO!
[JAZZ PLAYING]
ALL RIGHT.
QUENTIN'S DEATH
IS THE RESET POINT,
WHICH MEANS THAT
SAVING HIM MUST
BE THE KEY.
WHAT KIND OF SICK GAME
IS THE MONITOR PLAYING?
I DON'T KNOW.
WE NEED TO FIND OUT
WHO IS BEHIND THIS
HOSTAGE SITUATION.
IF IT'S JUST ABOUT
KILLING QUENTIN,
THEN WHY PLANT A BOMB?
IT SEEMS LIKE A LOT
OF EXTRA WORK.
MAYBE WHOEVER IS
BEHIND THIS WANTS
THEIR INVOLVEMENT
KEPT A SECRET.
DO YOU REALLY THINK
THERE'S A LARGER
CONSPIRACY HERE?
THOSE WERE
MERCENARIES, LAUREL,
WHICH MEANS THAT
SOMEBODY HAD TO
HIRE THEM.
GREAT, AND I'M SURE
THEY'RE GONNA BE REALLY
EASY TO FIND, TOO.
ANY IDEA
WHERE TO START?
LET'S GET QUENTIN
OUT OF HERE.
WHY DON'T YOU TAKE
HIM TO THE BUNKER?
WHAT ABOUT YOU?
[SIGHS]
I'M GONNA GO TAKE
A LOOK AT THAT BOMB.
LAUREL, I DIDN'T THINK
YOU'D MAKE IT TONIGHT.
I AM REALLY NOT
IN THE MOOD
FOR SMALL TALK
WITH THE MONITOR'S
BESTIE.
-EXCUSE ME.
-IT TURNS OUT TRANQ DARTS,
THEY DON'T
FEEL SO GOOD.
I TOLD YOU THAT WAS
A BIG MISUNDERSTANDING.
WELL, UNDERSTAND THIS.
THE SECOND I GET OUT
OF THIS SADISTIC
"EDGE OF TOMORROW"
REBOOT,
I AM GOING TO MAKE SURE
TO TELL EVERYONE
EXACTLY WHAT KIND
OF TRAITOR YOU
REALLY ARE.
LAUREL, I TRULY HAVE
NO IDEA WHAT YOU'RE
TALKING ABOUT,
BUT WHATEVER IT IS
YOU'RE FEELING
TOWARD ME,
THAT'S ON YOU.
THANK YOU FOR
THE ADVICE, DR. PHIL,
AND NOW HERE'S
SOME FOR YOU.
THE NEXT TIME
YOU DECIDE TO
DOUBLE-CROSS SOMEONE,
DON'T PICK A WOMAN
WHO SPECIALIZES
IN REVENGE.
YOU'RE THREATENING ME.
YES. YES, I AM,
BUT DON'T WORRY.
YOU WON'T REMEMBER
ANYWAY,
AND BY THE WAY,
I PULL OFF
THE SHORT HAIR
WAY BETTER
THAN YOU DO.
WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE?
WELL, WORD CAME DOWN
THAT THE GREEN ARROW
CALLED IN A BOMB THREAT,
SO I THOUGHT TO MYSELF,
"HOW DID HE KNOW ABOUT THAT,
AND WHY DIDN'T
HE CALL ME?"
BECAUSE THE MONITOR
HAS ME TRAPPED
IN A TIME LOOP.
ALREADY TOLD YOU THAT.
OK. DEFINITELY NOT
THE ANSWER I WAS
EXPECTING,
BUT IF THE MONITOR'S
INVOLVED, ANYTHING
IS POSSIBLE.
ANY IDEA
HOW TO BREAK OUT?
I HAVE TO SAVE
QUENTIN'S LIFE.
I THOUGHT THAT THIS
WAS THE KEY TO IT,
BUT I'M NOT FINDING
ANYTHING.
WELL, HAS TO BE SOMETHING.
NO CASE IS UNSOLVABLE.
THIS MIGHT BE
IMPOSSIBLE.
WELL, YOU'LL
FIGURE IT OUT.
I DO WISH I WAS
AS SURE AS YOU ARE.
YOU WANT TO KNOW WHAT
MAKES ME SO SURE? YOU.
YOU, OLIVER.
YOU ALWAYS FIGURE IT OUT.
YOU NEVER STOP FIGHTING.
YOU NEVER GIVE UP.
YOU ALWAYS KEEP AT IT.
WHY SHOULD THIS BE
ANY DIFFERENT?
WHATEVER VERSION
THIS IS OF YOU,
YOU STILL GIVE
THE BEST ADVICE.
-YEAH. I'M FLATTERED.
-WELL, A.R.G.U.S. HAS
SOME MORE SOPHISTICATED
ANALYTICAL EQUIPMENT.
ANY CHANCE YOU CAN
GET ME IN THERE?
YEAH. I BET I CAN MAKE
A FEW CALLS.
SO YOU'RE TELLING
ME WE'RE IN SOME KIND
OF A ALTERNATE REALITY
BASED ON THE PLOT
OF A BILL MURRAY MOVIE?
WELL, I WAS GONNA GO
WITH A TOM CRUISE FLICK
BUT BASICALLY.
ALSO JUST REALLY GLAD
THAT YOU BELIEVE ME.
WELL, IT'S NOT
THE CRAZIEST THING
YOU EVER TOLD ME.
I MEAN, I'M JUST
GLAD THIS MONITOR GUY
JUST KEPT ME
AS MAYOR, YOU KNOW?
WHAT?
WHAT'S THAT LOOK?
IT...IT'S JUST THAT, UH,
IN MY WORLD
OR IN THE REAL WORLD, UH,
YOU'RE NOT MAYOR ANYMORE.
REALLY? OHH. POLLARD.
SHE ALWAYS HAD IT
IN FOR ME. HEH.
THERE SOMETHING ELSE?
LAUREL. SWEETHEART,
I ALWAYS KNOW WHEN YOU'RE
HIDING SOMETHING
FROM ME.
PLEASE TELL ME.
WHAT IS IT?
IT...IT'S A YEAR
AND A HALF AGO
WHEN DIAZ...
WHEN HE SHOT YOU
IN...IN THE REAL REALITY
OR WHATEVER,
YOU...YOU DIDN'T
EXACTLY, UM...
[SIGHS]
I DIDN'T RECOVER.
NO. NO. YOU DIED
TO SAVE ME.
BEST WAY I COULD
HAVE GONE.
WHAT?! I'M SORRY.
I BASICALLY JUST
TOLD YOU YOU'RE A GHOST,
AND YOU'RE COMPLETELY
OK WITH THAT?
IT DOESN'T...IT DOESN'T FAZE YOU?
YOU'RE COMPLETELY CALM?
I ALWAYS FELT LIKE
I CHEATED DEATH
WITH THAT ONE.
GUESS THAT'S
BECAUSE I DIDN'T.
FATE'S JUST TRICKY
LIKE THAT.
[CELL PHONE VIBRATING]
-IT'S OLIVER.
-YEAH?
HE FIGURE OUT WHO
WANTS ME DEAD?
NOT YET, BUT HE DID
FIGURE OUT THE LOCATION
OF THE MERCS' HIDEOUT.
OK. SO WE BETTER GO.
[BANG]
HOW'D YOU FIND
THIS PLACE?
UH, WE ANALYZED
THE BOMB
AND TRACED
THE CHEMICAL
SIGNATURE
BACK TO THIS
BUILDING.
INTERESTING.
WHAT?
YOUR MOUTH
BUT FELICITY'S WORDS.
IT STILL DOESN'T TELL US
WHO HIRED THESE BOZOS.
MAYBE THIS WILL HELP.
[COMPUTER BEEPING]
[TIMER BEEPING]
BOMB!
OHH.
LYLA, WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU DOING?
HELPING YOU. YOU'RE MISSING
THE POINT, OLIVER.
-WHAT?
-YOU CAN'T FIGHT THIS.
OLIVER: LYLA!
SPORTS ANNOUNCER:
TARK DRIVES THE LANE.
KICKS IT TO ALDRICH
IN THE CORNER FOR 3.
BINGO! COUNT IT AND THE FOUL!
[JAZZ PLAYING]
NO SIGN OF LYLA
ANYWHERE. YOU?
JOHN JUST TOLD ME
SHE GOT CALLED AWAY
ON A LAST-MINUTE
A.R.G.U.S. MISSION,
MEANING SHE'S NEVER
EVEN BEEN HERE.
MAYBE THE MONITOR DELETED
HER FOR GOING ROGUE.
[BABY VOICE]
HEH. WOULDN'T THAT
BE SO, SO SAD?
SHE'S CLEARLY HELPING HIM.
THERE'S NO REASON FOR HER
TO SWITCH SIDES RIGHT NOW.
SO WHY REVEAL HER HAND?
IT MAKES NO SENSE.
YOU SPOKE
WITH HER.
WAS THERE ANYTHING,
ANYTHING AT ALL
IN THE CONVERSATION
THAT STOOD OUT?
SHE SAID HOW I FEEL
TOWARDS HER WAS ON ME
LIKE IT'S MY FAULT THAT
I'M STUCK HERE.
I TOLD YOU THE MONITOR'S
PUNISHING US.
I'M NOT SO SURE.
WE'VE HAD TO WATCH
QUENTIN DIE OVER
AND OVER AGAIN,
AND WE CAN'T SAVE HIM.
IF I HAD TO DESIGN HELL,
THIS WOULD BE IT.
BUT RIGHT BEFORE
LYLA DISAPPEARED,
SHE TOLD ME SHE WAS
TRYING TO HELP ME.
SHE ALSO TOLD YOU
YOU CAN'T FIGHT THIS.
IT SEEMS PRETTY CLEAR
TO ME THAT WE'RE NOT
SUPPOSED TO WIN.
THE FIRST TIME
THAT I MET MAR NOVU,
IT FELT...IT FELT
THE SAME.
IT WAS LIKE I WAS
PUT IN A SITUATION WHERE
THERE WAS NO WAY OUT,
BUT IT WAS A TEST,
LAUREL.
IT WAS A TEST
JUST LIKE I THINK
THAT THIS IS.
-A TEST OF WHAT?
-I DON'T KNOW,
BUT THERE IS
A WAY OUT OF HERE,
AND I'M GONNA FIND IT.
-YOU JUST NEVER GIVE UP, DO YOU?
-NO, I DON'T.
ARE YOU WITH ME?
FINE.
WHAT'S OUR PLAY?
WE GO BACK
TO THE MERCS' HIDEOUT.
WE KNOW WHERE THE DANGER
IS THIS TIME,
SO WE CAN DO THINGS
DIFFERENTLY.
YOU GRAB QUENTIN,
AND I'LL MEET
YOU THERE.
OK.
QUENTIN: SO YOU'RE TELLING
ME WE'VE BEEN HERE ONCE
AND STILL CAME BACK
FOR MORE?
AT LEAST NOW WE KNOW
WHAT NOT TO DO.
OK.
THAT SHOULD DISABLE
THE BOMB.
WELL, I CERTAINLY HOPE SO
BECAUSE I AM GETTING
SICK AND TIRED
OF GETTING BLOWN UP.
OK. SO NOW WHAT?
WE FIND OUT WHO HIRED
THOSE MERCS TO KILL YOU.
MONEY LEADS TO A MAN
NAMED ANDERSON WHITE.
NEVER HEARD OF HIM.
LAUREL: LOOKS LIKE HE'S
BEEN ACCUSED
OF NOT TOO MANY
NICE THINGS...
MONEY LAUNDERING,
RACKETEERING.
DOESN'T EXPLAIN WHY
HE'D WANT ME DEAD.
WELL, THAT'S WHAT WE'RE
GONNA FIND OUT.
CEO OF A COMPANY
NAMED GLOBAL SOLUTIONS.
THEY HAVE A WAREHOUSE
DOWN BY THE DOCKS.
LET'S GO.
WE NEED TO FIND
WHITE.
[GUNSHOT]
NO! NO!
-COME ON, COME ON.
-I GOT YOU. IT'S OK.
[QUENTIN GROANING]
OLIVER: I'LL TAKE CARE
OF THE REST.
[MOANING]
ERR! UGH.
OH, I'M SORRY, BABY GIRL.
LOOKS LIKE WE LOST
THIS ROUND.
NO. NO! I AM NOT
LETTING YOU DIE AGAIN.
-IT'S TOO LATE.
-NO.
IT...IT'S...IT'S TIME
TO SAY GOOD-BYE.
I'M NOT GIVING UP
ON YOU, QUENTIN.
QUENTIN, I AM NOT
GIVING UP ON YOU.
YOU NEVER GAVE UP
ON ME.
YOU BELIEVED IN ME
WHEN NOBODY ELSE DID.
WELL, THAT'S WHAT
DADS DO. THEY BELIEVE.
I WANT YOU TO KNOW
THAT YOU
ARE THE REASON
THAT I'M TRYING
TO BE A HERO.
IT'S BECAUSE OF YOU.
SWEETHEART...
YOU ARE A HERO.
YOU ARE.
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU. I NEVER
HAD THE CHANCE
TO TELL YOU
HOW MUCH YOU
MEAN TO ME.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
-WELL...
-THANK YOU.
I THINK YOU JUST DID.
[GASPING]
I LOVE YOU. I LOVE YOU.
GOOD-BYE.
DAMN IT.
ALL RIGHT. OK.
ALL RIGHT, LAUREL.
WE FIX THIS NEXT TIME.
WE'LL FIX IT.
I CAN'T DO THIS AGAIN.
I'M DONE, OLIVER.
ALL I HAVE EVER WANTED
WAS A CHANCE
TO SAY GOOD-BYE
TO QUENTIN.
NOW I HAVE.
SPORTS ANNOUNCER:
TARK DRIVES THE LANE.
KICKS IT TO ALDRICH
IN THE CORNER FOR 3.
BINGO! COUNT IT AND THE FOUL!
LAUREL?
LAUREL!
SHE'S NOT HERE.
-WHERE IS SHE?
-GONE.
WHAT DID YOU...WHAT
DID YOU DO, LYLA?
I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING.
LAUREL GOT WHAT SHE
NEEDED FROM THIS.
I DON'T HAVE TIME
FOR THESE GAMES, LYLA,
SO WHATEVER THIS IS,
GET ME OUT OF HERE
RIGHT NOW!
I CAN'T DO THAT,
OLIVER.
MAR NOVU NEEDS YOU
TO UNDERSTAND
NO GOOD WILL COME
FROM STRUGGLE.
THE ONLY WAY TO WIN
IS TO ACCEPT
THE INEVITABLE.
I HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT THAT MEANS.
LEARN THAT,
AND THIS WILL END.
LYLA!
SO IF ME DYING
IS THE PROBLEM,
MAYBE BRINGING ME
INTO THE LION'S DEN
ISN'T SO SMART.
COULDN'T THINK
OF A BETTER WAY TO
KEEP YOU SAFE.
YEAH.
THAT MAKES SENSE.
HUH!
AH-AH-AH-AH.
UNLESS YOU WANT
A HOLE FOR A HEAD.
OLIVER: ARE YOU
ANDERSON WHITE?
YOU REALLY THINK
MR. WHITE WOULD
BE HERE?
HE ORDERED A HIT
ON MY FRIEND. WHY?
[ALARM BLARING]
QUENTIN: I GUESS
THE CLOCK'S TICKING.
LOOKS LIKE A LIST
OF HITS.
AND CLIENTS.
CODED AND ANONYMOUS.
WHITE'S JUST
THE MIDDLEMAN.
A CEO WITH A HEALTHY
SIDE BUSINESS BROKERING
HITS FOR WEALTHY ASSHATS.
ALL RIGHT. WE'RE BACK
TO SQUARE ONE.
WE HAVE NO IDEA
HOW DEEP THIS
RABBIT HOLE GOES.
WE GOT TO GET GOING.
UNH!
GET DOWN! GET DOWN!
HEY. YOU OK?
YOU ALL RIGHT? OK.
NO TIME. COME ON.
[GROANING]
COME ON.
HEY, HEY, HEY, HEY.
WHOA!
[GUNFIRE]
GO, GO, GO,
GO, GO, GO!
GO, GO, GO.
THERE'S TOO MANY.
COME ON.
GET DOWN, GET DOWN!
OVER THERE!
OHH. OH, IT'S
THE LAST ONE.
HOW MANY ARROWS
YOU GOT LEFT?
NOT ENOUGH.
OH, BOY. AREN'T WE
THE COUPLE?
WE ARE GONNA FIND
A WAY OUT OF THIS.
THERE HAS TO BE
A WAY TO FIX IT,
AND WE ARE GONNA
FIND IT, QUENTIN.
IT DOESN'T MATTER
HOW MANY TIMES.
WE'RE GONNA FIND IT!
HEH HEH. YEAH? SURE.
WHAT'S IT GONNA BE,
60 TIMES, 100 TIMES?
IT'S GONNA BE HOWEVER
MANY TIMES IT TAKES!
YOU KNOW, GETTING
HUNTED LIKE THIS
IN A SPACE LIKE THIS
IS KIND OF LIKE
WHAT I WAS DOING TO YOU
ALL THOSE YEARS AGO.
REMEMBER?
[SIGHS]
[GROANS]
OHH. OOF.
SORT OF MAKES SENSE
I'D GO OUT LIKE THIS
NOW, DON'T YOU THINK?
WOULD YOU PLEASE JUST
SAVE YOUR STRENGTH.
[EXHALES]
FOR WHAT?
OLIVER, YOU TAKE CARE
OF THESE GUYS,
THERE'LL BE MORE
BEHIND THEM,
THERE WILL BE MORE
BEHIND THEM.
THERE IS NO SAVING ME
FROM THIS!
OK? YOU EVER THINK
THAT'S THE POINT?
MAYBE YOU'RE NOT
SUPPOSED TO.
I'M NOT GIVING UP...
AND YOU'RE NOT
GIVING UP EITHER.
OH, NO, NO, NO.
I'M NOT GIVING UP.
MAYBE I'M GIVING IN.
YOU SEE, I'VE BEEN
OUTRUNNING DEATH
FOR A WHILE NOW.
THE SIEGE, THE ISLAND,
BUT WHEN DIAZ SHOT ME,
THAT FELT DIFFERENT
LIKE I WAS FINALLY
AT THE END,
AND I MADE MY PEACE
WITH THAT.
AND MAYBE IT'S TIME
YOU DID, TOO.
IT LOOKS LIKE FATE'S
KNOCKING.
JUST...JUST...
YOU JUST GET READY
TO MOVE.
I'LL SEE YOU
ON THE OTHER SIDE, OLIVER.
QUENTIN.
[EXPLOSION]
SPORTS ANNOUNCER:
TARK DRIVES THE LANE.
KICKS IT TO ALDRICH
IN THE CORNER FOR 3.
BINGO! COUNT IT AND THE FOUL!
THAT'S AN 8-0 RUN
BY THE COMETS,
WHO HAVE STORMED
ALL THE WAY BACK
TO TIE IT UP HERE
IN THE FOURTH QUARTER.
88 APIECE, WHAT A COMEBACK
FOR THE COMETS.
MIA: NO WAY.
IT TASTES THE SAME.
DAD, WHAT ARE YOU
STILL DOING HERE?
OLIVER: HEY, GUYS.
I'M JUST HEADING
OUT THE DOOR.
WANTED TO LET YOU KNOW,
ALL OF YOU KNOW
WHAT A...JUST WHAT
A GIFT
GETTING TO KNOW
YOU ALL HAS BEEN.
DAD, YOU'RE GOING
TO A FUNDRAISER.
IT'S NOT LIKE YOU'RE
GOING INTO WAR.
HEH HEH.
ALTHOUGH I GUESS I CAN
SEE THE SIMILARITIES.
I THINK HE'S TALKING
ABOUT CRISIS.
I'M JUST REALLY
PROUD OF ALL
YOU GUYS.
I'M REALLY PROUD.
I GOT TO GO.
DAD...
YOU'RE GONNA BE FINE.
SO ARE YOU.
ALL OF YOU WILL BE
WHATEVER HAPPENS.
[DING, JAZZ PLAYING]
[WOMAN LAUGHING]
MAN: HEY, QUEEN.
WHAT'S THE DIFFERENCE
BETWEEN A COP...HEY!
QUENTIN, EXCUSE ME.
YEAH.
WHAT'S THE MATTER,
OLIVER?
YOU LOOK LIKE YOU'VE
SEEN A GHOST.
MAYBE I DID.
MAY I SPEAK WITH YOU
FOR A SECOND?
SURE.
UH, YEAH, YOU WANT TO
GO OVER THE SPEECH?
BECAUSE I WAS THINKING
ABOUT ADDING A FEW LINES.
I HAVE A QUESTION
FOR YOU.
SURE.
BACK WHEN I WAS
RUNNING AROUND
AS THE HOOD,
YOU WERE TRYING TO
ARREST ME.
-YOU REMEMBER THAT?
-HEH HEH HEH.
AH. YEAH. THE GOOD, OLD DAYS.
HOW COULD I EVER
FORGET?
THE QUESTION IS...
WHAT MADE YOU DECIDE
THAT I WASN'T
YOUR ENEMY ANYMORE?
WHAT CHANGED
YOUR MIND?
HEH. OH, YOU KNOW,
MY DAUGHTERS FOR ONE.
BECAUSE I DIDN'T
RAISE DUMMIES,
AND, UH, YOU KNOW, IF
THEY WERE OK WITH YOU,
THEN I FIGURED
I SHOULD BE, TOO.
-YEAH.
-THEY TRUSTED ME,
AND YOU TRUSTED THEM.
YEAH. THEY GOT ME TO LISTEN
TO WHAT I ALWAYS KNEW
IN MY GUT, THAT WE WERE
ON THE SAME SIDE
AND FIGHTING
FOR THE SAME GOAL,
AND IT JUST TOOK ME
A WHILE TO GET THERE.
SORRY.
IT'S OK.
OLIVER, IS THERE
ANY PARTICULAR REASON
FOR THIS TRIP
DOWN MEMORY LANE?
YEAH.
GOD, I'VE BEEN
HANGING ON
TO SOMETHING.
SOMEONE TOLD ME
JUST RECENTLY THAT,
UH...IT'S ABOUT
TIME I MADE
PEACE WITH IT.
OK. SOUNDS LIKE
A SMART SOMEONE.
YEAH.
OH, I SHOULDN'T HAVE
TO SAY GOOD-BYE
TO YOU AGAIN.
GOOD-BYE?
EVENING'S JUST
GETTING STARTED.
YEAH.
THANK YOU, QUENTIN
FOR EVERYTHING.
RENE: MR. MAYOR.
WE'RE GONNA SEE
EACH OTHER AGAIN,
OLIVER.
RENE: MR. MAYOR!
[WHISPERING]
AHEM.
I HOPE SO.
LYLA: CONGRATULATIONS,
OLIVER.
NOW YOU UNDERSTAND.
I COULDN'T CHANGE
QUENTIN'S FATE.
I CAN'T CHANGE
MINE EITHER, CAN I?
NO. I'M SORRY.
WHY DID THE MONITOR
GO TO ALL
OF THIS TROUBLE
JUST TO...
JUST TO PROVE
A POINT?
YOU'VE ALWAYS BEEN
A MAN WHO NEEDED TO
SEE THINGS FOR HIMSELF.
TELLING YOU WOULDN'T
HAVE BEEN ENOUGH.
HOW LONG HAVE YOU
WORKED FOR HIM?
A WHILE.
YOU LIED TO US,
LYLA.
YOU...
YOU LIED TO JOHN.
KEEPING THIS FROM JOHN
HAS BEEN
THE HARDEST THING I'VE
EVER HAD TO DO.
THEN WHY DO IT?
THE SAME REASON YOU LEFT
FELICITY AND MIA
IN THAT CABIN...
TO PROTECT MY FAMILY.
DO YOU HONESTLY
BELIEVE THAT WORKING
WITH THE MONITOR
IS THE BEST WAY
TO DO THAT?
IT'S THE ONLY WAY.
THE CRISIS IS COMING.
THERE IS NO STOPPING IT.
ALL WE CAN DO IS
TRY TO SURVIVE IT.
OK. HELP ME OUT
HERE, LYLA.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT IT IS.
I KNOW,
BUT YOU WILL...SOON.
WHAT I CAN TELL YOU
IS THERE IS AN EVIL COMING
THAT IS GREATER
THAN ANYTHING WE'VE
EVER HAD TO FACE.
CAN WE STOP IT?
I DON'T KNOW...
BUT YOU ARE THE ONLY
CHANCE WE HAVE.
SO EVERYTHING
I'VE DONE
FROM THE MOMENT
I LEFT THAT CABIN,
THIS HAS ALL BEEN
SOME...
BIGGER PART
OF A TEST?
HE NEEDED TO BE SURE
YOU WERE READY.
HE'S JUST BEEN SENDING
ME ON USELESS MISSIONS.
THEY WEREN'T USELESS.
THE DWARF STAR PARTICLES,
DR. WONG,
EVEN THE ANTIMATTER
WEAPON,
THEY ALL HAVE A PURPOSE,
JUST NOT THE ONE
YOU WERE EXPECTING.
WHY DID HE INVOLVE
MY CHILDREN?
TIME IS A GIFT.
WHAT NOW?
YOU COMPLETE
YOUR FINAL MISSION.
I'LL SEE YOU THERE.
[WIND BLOWING]
OHH.
WHERE ARE WE?
YOU OK?
I HAVE
A KILLER HEADACHE.
THE LAST THING
THAT I REMEMBER
IS QUENTIN...
DYING IN
THAT WAREHOUSE.
I WAS WEARING THESE
ON THE ROOF
WHEN WE GOT TRANQED,
SO DOES THAT MEAN THAT...
WE GOT OUT.
HOW?
WE LEARNED OUR LESSONS.
I GOT OUT
AFTER I SAID GOOD-BYE.
WHY WOULD THE MONITOR
LET ME SEE QUENTIN
ONE LAST TIME?
IT WAS A REWARD
FOR NOT BETRAYING ME.
DIDN'T REALLY
THINK REWARDS
WERE HIS BRAND.
NO. WE WERE WRONG
ABOUT HIM.
AND LYLA WAS RIGHT?
THAT'S ANNOYING.
SO WHY DID YOU
HAVE TO LEARN TO
LET LANCE GO?
BECAUSE DEEP DOWN,
I STILL BELIEVED
THAT I COULD FIGHT
MY FATE.
NOW I KNOW I CAN'T.
LYLA SAID WE HAD
ONE LAST THING TO DO,
ONE FINAL MISSION.
I CAN'T WAIT
TO FIND OUT
WHAT THAT IS.
[SIGHS]
WHERE THAT IS.
WE'RE NOT
IN STAR CITY.
MIA: DAD.
YOU OK?
WHERE THE HELL
ARE WE?
WE'RE ON LIAN YU.
MAN: GREG, MOVE YOUR HEAD!