This is Delta two-three-seven
en route to Star City Bank.
We are under attack
and need immediate assistance.
(BRAKES SCREECHING)
(BLACK CANARY SCREECHING)
(BIKES REVVING)
(GUNSHOTS FIRING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
The Ghosts. They're back to
knocking over armored cars.
Yeah, it's just like old times.
(GROANING)
-There are guards in the back.
-All right, we'll get them.
Go!
(GRUNTS)
They burnt all the money.
They didn't need it.
The federal government sent this
to prop up Star City Bank.
HIVE just wanted to make sure
that didn't happen.
I've heard of having money to burn,
but stealing money to burn, that's new.
Darhk's not kidding.
He really wants this city to die.
Yeah, but why? I mean, what does
HIVE have to gain from any of this?
A base of operations.
They have to be able to
operate out of somewhere.
What better spot than a dead city?
With almost a dead police department.
Any luck from that tooth
we got off the HIVE member
that we took down?
Only that the deterioration
of the DNA markers
was most definitely not natural.
Which means it was caused by what?
Curtis and I have been trying to
figure that out for the past month.
Maybe Ray will have better luck.
I will ask.
Hey, you got a sec?
Yeah.
-Where'd you get this?
-I got that from Lance.
Who got it from Damien Darhk.
-John, this...
-Is pretty definitive evidence
that HIVE had Andy killed
because his criminal operations
conflicted with theirs.
That doesn't track at all
with what you've told me about Andy.
Oliver, that doesn't track
with what I knew about Andy.
But I guess I really
never knew him at all.
-There's got to be some explanation.
-Oliver...
-Maybe he was undercover.
-No, man.
Listen, it's all right there.
The facts are the facts.
All I'm saying, Andy was your brother,
and he deserves the benefit of the doubt.
Trust me, things aren't always
what they seem.
Yeah. Yeah.
Reiter's not gonna like this.
Not one bit.
Vlad was a good worker.
And they listened to him.
I didn't have a choice.
He was gonna kill me.
Doesn't sound like something he'd do.
Maybe... Maybe he didn't
have a choice either.
Maybe someone put him up to it.
Maybe it was revenge.
Revenge for what?
For Taiana.
That drug-stealing bitch you choked out?
Vlad was her brother.
(KNOCKING)
Ah!
Thank you for coming by
on such short notice.
Oh. Happy to have something to do.
To be honest,
I'm feeling at a bit of a loss
of what to do with my newfound freedom.
And height. (CHUCKLES)
Is everything always this big?
If you're looking for something to do,
why not try,
I don't know, declare yourself undead,
try getting your company back?
You said you had something
that you needed help on?
Don't change the subject.
I'm not.
I'm a recently undead billionaire CEO.
My time is at a premium.
What can I do for you?
Thanks. I was wondering
where my tooth went.
John pulled this off of a Ghost.
It's their cyanide retirement plan.
We tried pulling DNA off it, but...
But half of the genetic markers
are missing. That's impossible.
You mean like a guy who can shrink to
the size of a French fry impossible?
Do you have any equipment?
I'm fresh out of chromatographs.
Take that.
Can we circle back to why
you won't come back to Palmer Tech?
Your return is exactly
what our stock price needs, and...
That's incredible.
The genetic code has been
selectively degraded.
We know. We think it's to
scramble their DNA markers
so they can't be ID'd. But how?
Looks like it was done
with a synthetic compound.
Like a chemical CRISPR/Cas9.
Lastrapium trioxide.
Wolfman Biologics has a patent on it.
Thank you.
Okay, tomorrow night,
Patrolmen's Benevolent Association Gala.
It's black tie, so you need a tux.
Which one? He's got, like, 50.
Uh... (CHUCKLES)
Maybe back in the day. I don't have a tux.
Get a rental. It doesn't really matter.
Every mayor in the history of Star City
has attended the PBA.
I secured a spot for you
on the dais with the brass.
We need to make sure
that your keynote is on point.
Which means we need to find a way to say
that the police need our help without...
-Throwing them under the bus.
-Right.
I thought you failed civics class?
A D-minus, thank you.
Alex has a way of making this interesting.
(CELLPHONE RINGING)
(SIGHING)
Sorry, wrong number. What were we saying?
Uh... Moving on to Oliver's platform.
I got your e-mail about
cleaning up Star City Bay.
-Yes.
-Yeah, it's, you know,
with everything
this city's facing right now,
a hippie-crunchy program...
A hippie-crunchy program
that will add hundreds of jobs,
help gentrify
the surrounding neighborhoods,
and encourage outside investment.
And put voters to sleep.
-We need to focus on crime and jobs.
-(CELLPHONE VIBRATING)
Which this program will address.
Hey, I will put out
a press release tomorrow.
-I got to take this.
-Okay.
I think your brother is onto us.
No. No, and even if he was,
it's not like he's the boss of me.
-No, he's the boss of me.
-I know.
I'm really glad
your brother's not a killer.
-Oh.
-Speedy. Speedy.
Uh...
Thea. Sorry, it's a nickname.
We have to go.
Felicity called about the thing.
The dental problem.
(STUTTERING) Uh, yes, yeah.
Sorry, um, our friend has
this tooth issue. Yeah.
Good work.
(MACHINE BEEPS)
On site.
We're clear for entry.
All right, Felicity, what's next?
We need a sample of the chemical.
With it, Ray can unscramble
the DNA markers
and we can have a shot at
ID'ing some of our Ghosts.
Where do we find this thing?
According to their
recently hacked computers,
second floor, northwest corner.
It's a yellow liquid.
Incoming. Four Ghosts. North entrance.
I'm on it.
-(GROANING)
-(GRUNTING)
DIGGLE: Felicity, we're in.
Looking for the compound.
Got it.
(GROANING)
FELICITY: Green Arrow
and Speedy need assistance.
-Thanks.
-You should go. Get out of here.
-What about you?
-I've got this. Go.
Felicity, I'm going for an ID
on the Ghost that shot at us.
Stand by.
(GASPS)
Andy?
(GROANS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Well, even death's not permanent anymore.
I'm sorry.
No, no, it's okay.
Nothing seems to make sense anymore.
Andy... I can't believe this.
It's obvious that HIVE faked his death.
-Maybe it was part of his recruitment.
-You saw the file.
You saw what kind of man my brother was,
what kind of man he is.
We don't know anything.
Not until we hear it directly from Andy.
And how are we supposed to do that?
We get him out of HIVE.
Oliver, how can you still be giving him
the benefit of the doubt?
Because he's your family.
You said he was a good man,
maybe a part of him still is.
-I don't know.
-FELICITY: I do.
Last month, at the lumber yard, a Ghost
had a chance to kill you, but didn't.
I remember thinking how weird that was.
Unless that Ghost was Andy.
So, what, he had a chance to kill me
and he didn't,
so I'm just supposed to
forget he's a killer?
No, but you should still remember
he's your brother.
I can't square that circle, Thea.
That HIVE member was
nothing like my brother.
The man who was my brother's dead.
He's dead.
-What brother?
-OLIVER: The brother of the prisoner
that stole the drugs.
But only because he put him up to it.
You're crazy. That prisoner attacked you
'cause what you did to his sister.
That's a lie.
It's a hell of a lot more believable
than me putting him up to attacking you.
You know what? You have had it in for me
-ever since you found that knapsack.
-Enough.
I have a means of divining the truth.
Why did you kill that prisoner?
Because he attacked me.
Oh, come on, man.
This isn't the place for
your hocus-pocus crap.
Did you have that prisoner
attack Mr. Queen?
Hell no.
You're lying.
According to what? A bunch of twigs?
No, Reiter, don't do this.
You got to hear me out.
It's him. He's the problem.
He's the problem! Hey!
What are you gonna do to him?
Nothing.
I believe the wronged
should make things right.
So, you wanted to see me?
So polite. That's a bit atypical.
Well, a guy gets slapped down
enough times, he learns who's boss.
Apparently not.
I'm sorry, what are you talking about?
After our meeting last week,
I had an unpleasant encounter
with the Green Arrow and his compatriots.
My security personnel
are under the opinion
that you called that meeting so as to
create an opportunity to have me followed.
So your security guys don't trust me,
but what about you?
Trust is an orchid.
Beautiful but delicate.
Requiring ideal conditions
in order to thrive.
Without those conditions, it dies.
Tread carefully, Quentin.
Believe it or not,
the death of your daughter
is not the most terrible thing
that I can threaten you with.
(CELLPHONE RINGING)
I don't want to talk to you.
MALCOLM: Then why are
you answering the phone?
Because I...
I would have told you I was stopping by,
but you weren't taking my calls.
What do you want?
To help you.
Those men you killed in Nanda Parbat,
the effects of those deaths
must be wearing off by now.
I'm fine.
The bloodlust has returned, hasn't it?
I have it under control.
You can't control it, Thea.
Who's Lawrence Tanner?
A pedophile.
Multiple accusations, no convictions.
Lives three blocks down.
The world needs one less pedophile,
and you need at least a month of peace.
Look, I'm gonna go out. Okay?
And when I come home,
you better not still be here,
or I am calling the police.
Hey.
Alex hired a security detail,
if you want to sit this one out.
Yeah, I'm gonna be at the bar.
Well, this has to be a better way
than how you usually spend your evenings.
Dressing in leather and tying people up.
There he is.
They're waiting for you on the dais.
Ready for this?
About to find out.
Evening.
It is our great privilege
to be here tonight
to honor the Star City Police Department.
These are a group of men and women
who risk their lives for us
on a daily basis.
Never been an easy job.
And it has certainly
never been more difficult
than it is right now in our city.
These are the people
that keep our streets safe,
who watch over us.
They protect us.
For that, I'm grateful,
and so is the rest of Star City.
(OLIVER CLEARS THROAT)
Not bad.
Not quite as powerful
as the Green Arrow's, but not bad.
Yeah? Maybe I should get him
to endorse me.
I need a favor from you.
Relocation of
one of Darhk's foot soldiers.
Could be a little difficult.
Darhk called me
into his office this morning
for a little chat about
how he doesn't trust me anymore.
Wait, wait, wait. Are you in danger?
I hope not.
But listen, when I was there,
I saw something on his desk.
Something about Slip 52 down at the docks.
Now, if the Ghosts are there,
maybe the one you're looking for
will be there too.
-Okay. Thank you.
-All right.
Hey, honey. How are you?
-Here you go, miss.
-Thank you.
Club soda?
Yeah, it has to be.
Can't have the candidate's bodyguard
getting hammered.
Do you want to talk about it?
Resurrected siblings are
kind of in my wheelhouse.
This ain't quite the same thing, Laurel.
(EXHALES)
Sara wasn't really a...
A member of an organization of killers?
I'm sure there are a million things
going through your head right now.
All I'm saying is, make one of them
an appreciation for the fact
that your brother is actually alive.
Well, why?
Why, so I can hold out some kind of
false hope that he might be decent?
He doesn't deserve that.
No, he probably doesn't, but you do.
After Andy died, a part of you died, too.
And now, now is your chance to heal.
How am I supposed to do that?
I had to look my nephew in the eye
and tell him that
he was never gonna see his daddy again.
(CRYING)
And the months after Andy died
were the darkest times in my life.
I would've given anything,
anything to get Andy back.
I would've sacrificed my life
to have him back
with his wife and his son.
I would've traded my life for a stranger.
-Mr. Queen, it's so nice to meet you.
-Thank you.
Do you think you can get
more funding for the SCPD?
Well, that's certainly a top priority.
-That's great news. Thank you.
-Sure.
Mr. Queen. Huge fan.
Thank you, Mr...
Darhk.
I have some ideas on
how I might contribute to your campaign.
-Do you have a minute?
-Of course.
Well, it's not just about
financial support.
I have strong relations
in the business circles.
Media outlets as well.
This is all well and good,
but I am running unopposed.
So I don't totally understand
how you could help me win.
Oh, it's not about winning.
It's about how much we could accomplish
if we worked together.
Right.
And not to be indelicate, but
a lot has changed in Star City
since your parents held sway here.
The levers of power have changed.
And not understanding that is
what doomed Jessica Danforth's bid.
Hmm.
What do you want, Mr. Darhk?
I read the press release
about your new project.
"The restoration of Starling Bay."
Reconsider your plans.
Leave the Bay as it is.
What if I refuse?
Well, then you'll no longer be unopposed.
Mr. Queen.
Mr. Darhk.
Leaving to fight Ra's on a mountaintop,
going undercover
with the League of Assassins,
dating the Huntress...
-What are you doing?
-Oh.
I'm just listing all of the terrible ideas
you've had over the past three years,
of which throwing in with Damien Darhk
has got to be the worst.
I'm not throwing in with Damien Darhk.
I am using him to get at HIVE.
Isn't Lance already our man on the inside?
Lance has lost Darhk's trust,
making this the only way...
To get yourself killed.
You remember the last time
you tried to take down
an evil organization from the inside?
-This is different.
-Why?
Because you'd be doing it as Oliver Queen?
Yep.
What about your mayoral campaign?
You cannot be an effective candidate
for mayor and Darhk's undercover stooge.
(CLEARS THROAT) Taking
down Darhk is more important.
Especially now that we know
that he has Andy under his thumb.
First, there's a whole long list of things
that we don't know about Andy.
Second, you didn't decide
to run for mayor to take down Darhk.
You did it to give this city something
that the Green Arrow can't give them.
Hope. Inspiration.
Don't lose sight of that.
Not even for John.
(GROANS)
This man betrayed us.
He sent an innocent man,
a useful man, to his grave.
He conspired against me, you,
all of his brothers.
Baron, please.
REITER: His punishment won't come from me,
but from the one he sought to hurt.
CONKLIN: Oliver, please.
Don't do this.
I'm begging you.
Come on, Queen.
Please! Look, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for everything.
Please, don't do this.
(SCREAMS IN PAIN)
Harder.
(SCREAMING CONTINUES)
(LAUGHING)
So, I'm sorry.
Your friend was reunited
with his brother after eight years?
It's crazy, right?
Yeah, crazy.
So have you given him your crown yet?
I mean, you held the record with
five years thinking Oliver was dead, so...
Ah. (CHUCKLES)
I can't imagine how tough
it must have been for you, Thea.
-(CELLPHONE RINGING)
-I'm sorry.
-You know, I should probably take this.
-Okay.
This is Alex. (WHISPERING) Sorry.
Yeah, what's up?
Hi, there. What're you drinking?
Maybe I can buy you another.
I don't think my date
would like that very much.
Well, I don't see him here.
You look like the kind of girl
where "no" means "yes."
Come on, baby.
(GROANS)
(THEA GRUNTING)
Thea! Stop! What the hell are you doing?
Can't do it?
I can't believe that Andy's back.
How am I supposed to tell Carly?
She has a right to know, Johnnie.
She's better off thinking he's dead.
I'm not sure that's your call to make.
I'm not sure about anything.
You know, when I first found out
about the Flash,
and Lazarus Pit, and what it did for Thea,
I began to daydream about Andy being back.
I would just play with that idea,
"My brother's back."
I never thought it would actually happen.
(WHISPERING) I know.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
I'll get it.
Hi, Lyla.
Hi, Oliver.
-May I come in?
-Sure.
-I'll give you two a minute.
-Okay.
(CLEARS THROAT)
How are you holding up?
Uh, I guess as good
as can be expected, right?
Nothing really to compare this to.
At least not this week.
-Lance has some intel for us.
-Mmm.
Slip 52 at the docks.
Felicity checked it out,
and that whole area has been
shut down for the entire night.
You think the Ghosts have
something planned there?
And maybe your brother.
Every time we face the Ghosts,
it's Russian roulette.
I'm not risking any of you for Andy.
You're not. We're offering.
Okay. But just us.
Thea and Laurel sit this one out.
-Okay.
DARHK: Gentlemen, you've all
come here from different walks.
Different paths.
But all burdened with the same knowledge,
that this world is diseased.
Fortunately, there is a cure
for this pestilence.
That cure, gentlemen, is HIVE.
Those little yellow pills you swallowed,
they do a few interesting things,
including making you cooperative.
Now I understand you all volunteered,
and that's just swell,
but I think we can all agree
that in any chain of command,
there can never be too much compliance.
Perhaps a demonstration.
Kneel.
The people of this city,
well, what's left of them, at any rate,
they call you "Ghosts."
They have no idea how right they are.
-GHOST 5: Up there!
-(GUNSHOTS FIRING)
Kill the green one.
(GRUNTING)
(BEEPS)
(GROANS)
(BEEPING ACCELERATES)
This isn't on you, John. It was my call.
(CLEARS THROAT)
And I never should have let you make it.
Felicity, can you give us a second?
No, I think I should stay.
But I just remembered I got that thing
in the whatever with the what's it.
Oliver, let this go, man.
I have.
And you almost got yourself killed.
I've been a lot closer to "almost killed."
Andy made his choice.
You don't know that.
John, you saw what was going on tonight.
Those men were under
the influence of something.
Whatever pill is scrambling their DNA
is also making them susceptible
to Darhk's suggestion.
All right. Just because you have
a blind spot for your family,
don't expect me to as well.
-That's not what this is about.
-The hell it's not.
Family is exactly what this is about.
Criminal or not,
under the influence or not,
Andy let his son and his wife
believe he was dead,
for eight years, Oliver.
(LOUDLY) Eight years!
And there's no excuse for that!
-None.
-John, I'm... You don't know.
Oliver, you don't know.
You have this inexplicable way of
excusing everything
just because it's family.
Oh, it's not "inexplicable."
I'm asking you... (GRUNTS)
I'm asking you to hold out hope for Andy
because I need that hope.
I need to believe that
no matter what happens in our lives,
no matter how much darkness infects us,
I need to believe
that we can come back from that!
DIGGLE: And it was exactly that thinking
that led you to the League last year.
Doesn't seem like
you learned much from that.
Felicity told you.
Getting in bed with Darhk, Oliver,
I don't see how you can even consider it.
We are gonna take this guy down.
And no idea is off the table.
Look, you're doing things
differently, Oliver.
Fighting Darhk from the inside
is just fighting Darhk in the shadows.
You want to do things differently?
You want ideas? Fine.
Let's take this son of a bitch down
in the light of day.
Hey.
Just in time.
For what?
Roasted lizard with a little bit of
coriander and sea salt.
I've gotten better at removing the skin
with a sharp rock.
I ate already.
Thank you.
Are you all right?
Had a hard day.
Taiana, I have to...
I have to tell you something
about your brother.
Vlad?
Is he all right?
No.
I'm sorry.
What do you mean?
-Is he...
-Taiana, I'm very sorry.
(TAIANA CRYING)
-Hey.
Sorry, I had Curtis grab some more toys
so I could keep working on your tooth.
That's okay. I don't think
we're gonna be using that
table for eating tonight, anyway.
Oliver and John are busy fighting over
John's not-so-dead-after-all brother.
Do I even want to ask?
Let's just say you no longer
corner the market
on not being as dead as people think.
Though in John's brother's case,
he does have a pretty good excuse.
Unlike some people. Have you seen anyone?
Of course not, I've been busy here
working on your tooth.
You're stalling.
Ray, when you come back from the dead,
you're supposed to start living again.
What's going on?
I've been catching up
on the past six months.
My company, my city, my life.
And I feel like Tom Sawyer
watching his own funeral.
Except in my case, nobody really cares.
That is not true, Ray.
Renaming Starling "Star City" is nice.
But then, take a look
at what's happened to the place.
And my company, this thing I built
that was supposed to outlast me,
is now on life support.
Because it needs you.
To do what?
The same thing I was doing
before I "died"?
Obviously, that didn't amount to anything.
Self-pity is not a good look on you.
Yeah. I don't think it's self-pity.
I think it's self-reflection.
If I'm gonna come back to life,
I have to figure out
what it is that I'm living for.
Okay.
I played around with your bicuspid a bit.
The compound definitely broke down
the residual DNA on the tooth.
It's pretty inventive, actually.
Is there any way to reconstitute the DNA,
so we have a shot at ID'ing these guys?
No. Once the alleles are decomposed,
they're gone for good.
-Yeah.
-So, since that was a dead end,
I took another look at the polymer
the fake tooth was made of.
Uh... I found
faint traces of sodium fluoride.
Like, from water?
There's no way that the
concentration could be high enough
to leave behind any sort of residue.
It would if there was an unusually high
sodium fluoride count
in the drinking water.
Like, say, at a facility that was
closed down for that very reason.
Muller Psychiatric Center.
You gotta admire the irony.
Damien Darhk keeping his army of bad guys
in a defunct loony bin?
Not bad for a guy who thinks
his life didn't add up to anything.
Yeah. Never gonna outlive that one.
Everyone clear on the plan?
You know, I wasn't the first 80 times
we went over it,
but now I think I got it.
What's going on, guys?
Felicity found a probable location
for the Ghosts' base of operations.
These guys are not
gonna be easy to take out.
How are you feeling?
We're not trying to take down the Ghosts.
We don't have the manpower.
We're going after Andy.
Guys, Oliver nearly got himself killed
trying to help Andy.
I'm not letting you do the same.
I'm sorry,
but it's not really just up to you.
I did everything that I could
to bring my sister back,
and I think your brother
deserves the same.
No, no. That's just it.
I don't think he does.
I don't know what Oliver told you...
FELICITY: He told them
the only two things that matter.
Andy's under Darhk's influence,
and we need to get him out.
I can't let you risk your lives for
someone who does not deserve it.
That's your call. But we've made ours.
Let's move.
-OLIVER: We're on site.
-Uh...
Satellite's reading a hell of a lot
of activity for 3:00 in the morning.
I'm guessing 50 or so Ghosts,
plus who-knows-how-many recruits.
Wait. If the Ghosts are wearing
their usual Halloween costumes,
then how are we supposed to tell
which one's Andy?
That's what your fancy
new cameras are for.
A little gift from Curtis.
The infrared lenses should
virtually unmask our Ghosty friends.
Sick.
Okay. Ready?
I'm in position.
In position.
This isn't just a base of operations.
It looks like a staging area.
-For what?
-Equipment.
Military crates marked "G-six-five."
Does that mean anything?
Maybe they're playing Bingo.
Let's assume that's not it.
-Deadly Bingo.
-No. (CLEARS THROAT)
We need to get an ID on Andy.
When you do,
you wait for my signal before engaging.
Yeah, I might not have that option.
OLIVER: Speedy?
She's been spotted.
Third floor. Southwest building.
LAUREL: I've been spotted too.
-(GRUNTING)
-(GROANING)
(GUNSHOTS FIRING)
(THEA GRUNTING)
Be able to get a visual on our target.
Waiting on confirmation.
That's him. You got him.
The one on your right.
(STRUGGLING) Yeah, actually, he's got me.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
I've got him.
He looks pretty heavy, though,
-so I could use a hand.
-LAUREL: I'm on my way.
It's Merida.
Aren't you out
a little bit past your bedtime?
I've seen something
of your fighting style.
You were trained by Ra's al Ghul.
Tell me, how is Malcolm doing these days?
(GASPS)
It usually works.
(GRUNTING)
Black Canary's got Andy,
but she needs help reaching the exfil.
-I got this!
-You sure?
Go!
(GUNSHOT)
It's, uh, nice of you to show up.
My brother needed me.
The green one.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you, all of you.
-Palmer, even you, thank you.
-My pleasure.
It feels good to do something useful.
It's been a while.
Does that mean
I can expect to see you at work tomorrow?
Ah... No.
I can't keep doing the same useless,
ineffective things, you know?
I gotta do something different.
I'm gonna take some time
and figure out what that is.
But it'll still include the occasional
super-heroics, whenever you need me.
Where are you going?
Well, I have a long overdue chat
with my brother.
I hope you were right.
Me too. You were right.
-About what?
-Darhk.
I thought about what you said,
and how to fight him.
-I'm gonna do it in the light of day.
-Good.
What did you have in mind?
You'll see.
TAIANA: (CRYING) We never should have
gotten on that damn boat.
Reiter's men hijacked a yacht
that we were working on.
I was a dive instructor.
Vlad was a deckhand.
They killed everyone on our charter,
and they brought us here.
What happened? With Vlad.
Conklin.
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
Taiana, wait. Wait. Listen to me.
-I'm going to kill him for what he did.
-Listen to me.
Conklin is terrible,
but he's not the problem.
-He's just a pawn.
-A pawn for what?
For Reiter's plan.
What is this?
This is a map of Lian Yu.
And I think that it leads to
whatever Reiter is looking for.
Can you follow it?
Not without a detailed
survey map of the island.
Where will we get something like that?
Oh. I had an idea.
It's a long shot, but it's worth a try.
To get there, I'll need your help.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Thank you for coming.
Are you sure you don't have the SCPD
waiting for me in the kitchen?
Don't be so paranoid.
You did threaten me with arrest
the last time I popped by.
So, did you reconsider my advice?
Yes.
But I'm still not gonna take it.
Look, I think I might have found
a different way for me
to control my bloodlust.
One that does not include killing people.
What does it include?
Damien Darhk.
Last night, we went after HIVE,
and I ran into Damien.
I've seen what he can do with his powers.
But when he tried to use them on me,
it completely backfired.
And my bloodlust was gone.
I mean, at least for a little while.
So what I want is for you
to help me figure out a way
to make that permanent.
Andy, I don't even know where to begin.
Andy, I need to understand.
Can you help me understand?
Is what's in this file true?
Andy, answer me.
It's true. All of it.
Boy, this is quite a lot of media for a...
What'd you call it?
-"Hippie-crunchy program."
-That's right.
Always happy to admit when I'm wrong.
-Good luck up there.
-Thank you.
Hi. Sorry I'm late.
You're fine. We're just getting started.
So I haven't been arrested
for battery, yet.
I keep thinking, you would have
killed him if I hadn't stopped you.
I just had a really bad night.
I guess I'm just asking if maybe
you could be a little patient with me?
Thank you all for coming.
My campaign adviser
doesn't think that saving the Bay
is the right fight
given the state the city is in.
But I'd like everyone to know that I'm not
blind to Star City's problems.
And I wouldn't be here today
if I wasn't confident that this program
could help solve them.
And the reason I chose the Bay
is because it's in the center of the city.
It's out in the open, for everyone to see.
The fight to save Star City isn't gonna be
fought in the shadows.
It's gonna be fought in the light of day.
And I promise you,
all of you,
that I will never stop fighting
to save this city.
(ALL APPLAUDING)