Previously on Arrow...
Four years ago,
The Hood took down Justin Claybourne.
You told me that Claybourne
didn't have any kids.
There's no record of the kid's name.
He'd be about 30 today.
Just old enough to put on
a hood and a mask.
Old enough to want revenge on the man
who murdered his father.
Evelyn? Why?
You're a fraud.
This city needs to be saved from you.
Hey.
Johnny, I need you
to come to the Safe House.
- Something's wrong with J.J.
- Lyla?
Did you find Billy?
I didn't know it was Billy,
I couldn't have known.
Hi, Ollie.
I saw you die.
I was saved. I saw this white light and...
It's... It's just like they say.
This angel, she reached out to me,
but she wasn't an angel.
She was my sister.
What?
Sara, she had me teleported
to the Waverider.
They have this technology
that fixed the embolism.
I was there.
Everyone was there.
Nobody saw a white light,
and you didn't go anywhere.
That's because she hadn't done it yet.
Ollie...
Ollie, I asked her.
I asked her to bring me to your present.
She gave me the same gift that I gave her.
She gave me a second chance.
It's a miracle.
Laurel?
Hi, Felicity.
Laurel? Oh, my God!
Oh, my God!
It's a miracle.
Oliver said the exact same thing.
I thought Sara and the Legends
were against changing history.
Sara said that they figured out a way
to bring me back without causing a, uh...
An Aberration?
Yes, that.
Are you okay?
Fine.
Yeah, I just wished the Legends
could bring back everybody we wanted.
What happened? What did I miss?
We'll talk about it later.
The important thing is
that you're back from the past.
Which they brought you back
from months later,
and they just dropped you here.
So weird.
Time travel, am I right? Wow.
Do you guys want coffee?
I am gonna get a decaf,
probably, 'cause...
It's nice to see some things
haven't changed.
Ugh. I have to call my dad.
He's gonna kill me for coming here first.
Laurel, after you...
Your dad left with Donna
and it didn't go well.
- He's drinking again.
- He's in rehab.
But, he's getting better.
He's getting the help that he needs.
Wow. Nine months.
I guess I have a lot of catching up to do.
Which is why I'm going to
tell everyone to come to the party.
What party?
The party that we're gonna throw
for Laurel tomorrow night.
That sounds great.
I mean, I would love to see everyone.
Thea and John...
Oh, my... John! Oh...
I came here to tell you
and I totally forgot.
What's going on with John?
I can't believe she's back.
I walked into the bunker,
and she was just there.
Like nothing had happened.
Like it was some kind of gift.
How much does she know
about what's happened?
We're easing her in.
There's a lot to process. The recruits...
Prometheus.
The fact that you killed his dad.
Felicity and Lyla are working on
finding his mother.
What happened with the dude
who trained the two of you?
Well, she doesn't stay
in one spot for very long.
But, I'm working on finding her.
In the meantime, we need to work
on a way of getting you out of here.
Yeah, well, we did that, remember?
And here I am, right back on the inside.
- Well, John...
- No, man. No more running.
It's time I faced this head on,
and fight these trumped-up charges.
That's an improvement from last time.
Roger that.
I'm gonna show Walker that he picked
the wrong soldier to screw with.
We need to have some kind of plan.
I'm gonna need one hell of a lawyer.
I might know a guy.
My captains warned me
that you would be a risk.
An American Bratva?
But I thought that you could be useful.
I did what you asked me to do.
I tried to blow up Kovar's casino.
All that you were interested in
was killing Konstantin Kovar.
But not for the Bratva.
For yourself. For a woman.
Kovar told me everything.
Kovar is a government agent.
And the deal that you made with him
betrays the Bratva.
Your vendetta betrays the Bratva.
My deal with Kovar
benefits our brotherhood.
And, in any case, I am Pakhan.
My decisions are the law.
And I will get obedience from you,
even if I have to beat it into you.
Is this why you joined Bratva?
To get to Kovar?
Because you had some promise to her?
Hmm?
You don't have to drop everything
and fly home, Thea.
I'll still be here
when the conference is over.
And the way Oliver describes it,
you're the one that's doing all the
heavy lifting at the mayor's office.
I guess spontaneous resurrection
is as good as any reason for a party.
But...
But we haven't even buried
Detective Malone yet.
It feels weird to be celebrating?
It doesn't feel weird to you?
Yes, weird, yeah.
Weirder. I guess.
After the past four years it's just
hard for me to accept good news.
It's weird, man. She was dead.
Now she's not.
Well, that's time travel for you.
Well, I don't mean Laurel being back
is what's weird.
It's how you all reacted to it.
Like it's happened before.
It's happened before?
The Lance sisters have a habit
of coming back to life.
Wait, what?
Yo, Curtis. Come back inside.
We're gonna make a toast.
It doesn't feel right
to be gathered around like this.
Detective Malone is dead.
Evelyn betrayed us.
And Prometheus is still out there.
We should be trying to find him.
Making him pay for everything.
A little over a year ago,
I stood right here,
and I remarked that I wished
it wasn't just the dark times
that brought us together.
With all of the loss
that we have suffered,
I think it's important,
that we embrace the miracles, too.
And that we remember
they are still possible.
Welcome home, Laurel.
Cheers.
Hey.
- Sorry?
- God!
I wasn't expecting anyone here. It's late.
I don't sleep much. Or at all.
Side-effect of wearing haunted rags,
I guess.
So, I figured I'd train. What's that?
- It's nothing.
- It's my Qmail.
You know, my Face-Chat, Snapbook stuff.
All the kids are doing these
new, crazy social media things...
- You're running a DNA analysis.
- Yeah, I am. On Laurel's glass.
That... What, you took from the party?
Oh, if by "party" you mean
my brilliant ruse to collect her DNA,
then, yes, you are correct.
- Wow.
- Yeah.
You know, there's looking a gift horse
in the mouth and then there's...
Being driven by paranoid delusions
to run comparisons on genetic base pairs?
- Yes, I'm aware. Thank you.
- Yeah?
Yeah. Yeah.
- Well?
- DNA matches.
- Okay, so, we can relax, Shapeshifter.
- Yeah.
Ooh, what about an evil twin?
Oh. No.
Okay, I was joking.
No. No, no, no, no, no.
She actually has an evil twin.
- Seriously?
- Yeah. She's locked up in S.T.A.R. Labs.
I'll explain later.
Right now we have to call Cisco...
Finally!
It's about time someone figured it out.
You know, I am so sick and tired
of playing this weak, vulnerable Laurel.
She's such a pill. It's pathetic.
You know, the one problem with my ability
is that I can never hear
my poor little victims scream.
Laurel!
Hey, are you hurt?
I'm gonna be okay. But...
That's not our Laurel.
So, that Laurel's from
an alternate reality?
Technically, she's from
a parallel universe.
We're on Earth-1.
The lookalike Laurel
is from another Earth, Earth-2.
Over there, we all have doppelganger
versions of ourselves
who could be very similar
or incredibly different
based on an infinite amount of variables.
I'd love to see what I'm like
on Earth-2.
Oh, God! What if I'm straight?
Okay. One thing I don't get...
Well, you know,
there's a list of things I don't get,
but the top is, this fake Laurel
seemed to know, like, everything.
- How's that possible?
- Prometheus.
Cisco just sent this over.
It is from three days ago.
Nobody knew
because no alarms were tripped.
It's like he's a dybbuk.
Yeah, I don't know what that is.
- One question.
- Just one?
Prometheus breaks into S.T.A.R. Labs,
gets not-Laurel,
Henry-Higgins her into coming off
as real-Laurel.
That's a lot of hoops.
Why not just kill you?
He told me he doesn't want to.
He's proving to me
that I will destroy myself
and everyone close to me.
Well, he's gonna be disappointed,
because we are gonna put Black Siren
back in her cage.
"Black Siren"?
Every meta gets a nickname.
Let's hit the streets.
She is not leaving the city
until this is over.
What are you gonna do?
John needs my help as mayor.
I will be on my cell.
Let's see if I understand.
You carried this girl with you
through all of your trials
and tribulations on some island.
Lian Yu -Yes.
And yet, when you get off this island,
you do not return home.
No.
Instead, you come to a country
where you know just one person,
you join my organization,
pass all of our tests,
and all of this so you can avenge
the death of a different woman?
Woman in that photo's name is Laurel.
And I didn't return home
because after everything
I've been through,
everything I've done,
she wouldn't recognize me.
Now I see.
You think that you've been made
into a monster?
Better a monster than a sell-out.
How much did Kovar pay you
to betray your brothers?
Your failure is unacceptable.
You should have let me kill them
instead of some stupid role-playing idea.
It is not your place
to question my agenda.
Your freedom, your life is contingent
on following my orders.
Do you understand?
Hey, thanks for coming in.
No problem.
I wanted to talk with you as well.
Okay. Uh, the file that I sent you...
John Diggle is my former bodyguard.
And current friend.
And facing a court-martial
for espionage, murder,
escaping a federal prison,
and attempted theft of a WMD.
He's innocent.
So why did he escape a federal prison?
Because he's innocent.
The man who framed him
is a three-star General.
John did not think that he would
get a fair trial in the court system.
Which is where you come in.
Oliver, I'm a city prosecutor,
not a military defense attorney.
That's why I thought of you.
John needs someone outside
of the military infrastructure.
This is the only way
for justice to get done.
- He doesn't even know me.
- John Diggle is a good man.
He's better than the both of us
put together.
Getting the Judge Advocates
to even authorize me
to pro hac in would be a miracle.
Sounds like a "yes."
Eh, more like a, God, help me.
And your friend.
Hey, I will owe you one.
This is worth more than one.
Um, actually, hey... As if we don't have
enough on our plate,
have you heard about the circumstances
surrounding the death of Detective Malone?
No.
He was wearing Prometheus' outfit
when he was Killed.
His mouth was taped shut,
a sword taped into his hand.
There was a wireless speaker
found on the scene.
What are you saying?
That it looks like Malone was set up.
That it looks like the Green Arrow
was manipulated into killing him.
By Prometheus.
I made sure the cops who caught the scene
won't say anything,
and I'm handling the coroner.
I just wanted to let you know.
Yeah, that you're gonna cover this up?
If the city finds out
that a member of the Anti-Crime Unit
was Prometheus,
there's gonna be panic.
If the Green Arrow killed a member
of the Anti-Crime Unit,
there's gonna be panic.
- Either way.
- Gotta keep this quiet.
It's the only way to see justice done.
This is Mayor Queen.
Oliver, it's me. Laurel.
Don't you say her name.
I'm sorry. What I did was unforgivable.
But, but he made me do it. Prometheus.
What do you mean, he made you?
He threatened to kill me.
You have to help me. Please.
Can you meet?
Where?
The Black Canary statue.
I'll be there soon.
Wait...
Any sign of Black Siren?
Not yet. But everyone's
gonna stand down and do not engage...
Yeah, we get it.
Yeah, well, I say take her down.
Overwatch.
You heard the boss.
This is an eyes-only operation for you.
I have eyes on.
Boys, I just put you
on a separate channel.
Uh, why?
So, if Black Siren looks like
she's about to double-cross,
and trust me, she will,
you have it on my authority
to light her up.
Thank you for meeting me.
You don't believe me.
Prometheus threatened to kill me.
You're a very convincing liar.
I deserve that.
According to S.T.A.R. Labs,
you'd help Prometheus
even if he wasn't threatening anyone.
That's what they think.
What do you think?
I can help you track him.
Take her out.
I told you not to engage.
We know, it's just...
She, um, spooked us.
You guys are terrible liars.
I told them to move on her.
Since when are they taking orders
from you?
I don't know. But I kind of like it.
- She had something in her hand.
- She had her phone in her hand.
Well, it didn't look like her phone,
and I don't trust her,
so I told them to move.
I had the situation under control.
She told me that
Prometheus forced her to do this.
Now whether or not that is true,
she was going to give us
valuable intel on him.
She's playing you, Oliver.
I understand that you're
suspicious of her.
And I know this Laurel
is from another Earth,
that this is not our Laurel.
But we don't know why.
We don't.
I told you. Blinders.
Hey, you good?
Why wouldn't I be?
I just got my ass kicked
for the bazillionth time.
So, basically, I'm trading a cell
in Central City
for a cell in Starling City.
Actually, on this Earth,
we call it "Star City."
I'm sorry about the cell.
I told you
that Prometheus was going to kill me.
And that is why I did what I did.
Your history on Earth-2
would suggest you had other reasons.
- You don't trust me?
- Can you blame me?
No. Because on my world,
you've been dead for 10 years now.
I moved to Central City for a fresh start.
That's where this happened.
And from then,
it was just one bad choice after another.
And I guess
once you let the darkness inside,
it never comes out.
And now I am trapped
in a parallel dimension,
telling my sob story
to the doppelganger of the man that...
That I loved.
So stop running.
Face the darkness.
How does that work?
First, you need to tell me
everything that you know about Prometheus.
Everything.
And then we keep you safe.
And you're willing to do that, why?
Why, because I look like someone
you used to know?
Someone once told me that a circumstance
could make something poison or nectar.
What they meant was
that we get to choose what we are.
We get to choose who we are.
So tell me...
Who are you?
Hey, yo, hold up!
I'll walk with you. Hopping the L-line.
- You taking the subway?
- No, I'm just gonna walk.
By yourself?
You do have a tendency
to get your ass kicked.
Did you just come all the way
out here just to insult me?
I'm just going home,
but that was merely a product of...
I'll see you tomorrow, Rene.
Damn, you soft!
I thought you had some wit, man.
What, the Black Siren kicked that
out of you, too?
Not now, man. Not now.
What, did I hurt your feelings?
Just let me be, man.
What's your damage, hoss?
I mean, ever since the party,
you've been off.
You're supposed
to be the happy one, remember?
Like what? Like this?
What the hell's gotten into you?
I've been stabbed, shot at, put in a coma,
had magic powers used on me,
superpowers used against me, and for what?
What difference does it make?
All it's done is cost me my blood,
my sweat...
And my Paul.
It cost me Paul.
That's your husband, right?
Was. He left me.
'Cause of you being Mr. Terrific?
Because of me trying.
But I'm never gonna make it,
because I don't have what it takes.
So now I don't have anything.
Hey, keep your wrist straight.
Just so you don't jam it.
Mmm.
- I spoke to Laurel.
- When did she become Laurel?
She's not Laurel. Not Laurel Laurel.
She's not our Laurel, okay? Not...
Okay, Felicity, I can't pretend
to understand parallel worlds.
But if I'm gonna believe in them,
and I kind of have to now,
then I need to believe
that differences
are caused by circumstances.
So why can't we change
this Laurel's circumstances?
You think that you can save her.
- After she's thrown in with Prometheus...
- Under duress.
I just...
I think I can reach her.
When did you find the time
to get a PhD in psychology?
I'm a quick study.
My name's Adrian Chase,
Star City District Attorney.
John Diggle. Convict.
You here to add to my charges?
Not exactly. I'm representing you.
Your friend Oliver's persuasive.
Plus, he's my boss.
General Walker,
the guy who wants you out of the picture,
- you know who his boss is?
- The President.
So you can imagine how difficult
this is about to be.
Mr. Chase, MP officers are here to remand
the prisoner into their custody.
Wait, I thought
I was supposed to stay here for now.
You're under their jurisdiction.
The trial...
The trial? Man, there won't be a trial.
As soon as I'm out of here,
Walker will concoct some reason
to put a bullet in my head.
Sergeant Diggle.
Good to see you again.
Have Sergeant Diggle cleared out of here
and ready for transport ASAP.
We got a long ride back
to Langham ahead of us.
So tell me,
what happened between you and Oliver?
Did he find someone else?
Or were you not tall enough?
Do you have a sister?
Because I hear he loves sisters.
Oliver seems to think that
because you look like Laurel,
that you could become her.
And what do you think?
I think...
You should get used to living in cages.
There's a part of him
that blames himself for Laurel's death.
It's who he is.
So when he looks at you,
he doesn't just see Laurel.
He sees his shot at redemption.
Wow, it must be really frustrating
that he doesn't listen to you.
No, I'm used to it.
How'd she escape?
The power went off
and the dampener along with it.
And Goldilocks huffed and puffed
and blew the door down.
That's not exactly how her power works.
Was there something wrong
with Cisco's specs?
Because didn't we just replicate
the Pipeline's security system?
We did. I let her go.
- What?
- Damn, blondie.
I'm sorry. But, everyone, just relax.
I put tracking nanites in her water,
- the same ones we used to find Malcolm.
- Well, that makes everything better.
Isn't that exactly how you used Anarky
to find Darhk last year?
- Could we have the room please?
- Seriously? This is getting good.
Rene, Rory, come on, guys.
You could've been hurt.
What ever happened to
"if we change her circumstances"?
You risked your life to get a line
on Prometheus because of Billy.
Well, now that you're killing again,
I thought why not put it to use?
You know,
we're gonna get justice for Billy.
But first,
we need to take care of your ex.
Who's not even your ex.
There's a part of him
that blames himself for Laurel's death.
It's who he is.
So when he looks at you,
he sees more than just Laurel.
He sees his shot at redemption.
It's like I said,
you know me better than almost anyone.
I failed Laurel before.
I can't fail her again.
I don't have to
remind you that this isn't her.
I know.
Our Laurel's gone.
She's the last chance that I have.
Okay?
Billy is my responsibility.
And we will get justice for him.
I'll let you know
when the trackers metabolize and go live.
You've been here for just few months
and already you think you know everything.
Did it not occur to you
that I could be playing Kovar?
- I don't believe that.
- Of course, you don't.
Because you don't understand
that circumstances are
what makes a thing poison or nectar.
You believe
your fool's errand to kill Kovar
because you think that you are responsible
for this darkness that's inside of you.
Like a baby blaming himself for being
left out in the cold by his mother.
If it weren't for that island,
you would be
that harmless American douchebag
that you pretended to be
in Kovar's casino.
So I guess I'm just supposed to
listen to you instead?
I can give you family.
One that does not see a monster,
but a brother.
All I'm asking in return
is your obedience.
- Or else?
- Hmm.
Or else...
You don't leave this room alive.
So Mom and Dad
are going 12 rounds upstairs.
They're just having a discussion.
Look, I know that I took the teasing
too far earlier.
I can be an acquired taste,
but I'm sorry to hear about Paul
and that I made you feel worse about it.
Thanks.
- That's really big of you.
- So what are you doing down here?
Well, since the Black Siren's cry works on
a more powerful frequency than Laurel's,
these are useless.
So, I was trying to see if there was a way
to make the dampener portable
- so the next time we go up against her...
- You can take her powers away.
That's awesome.
Yeah, well, ideas are one thing,
executing them is another.
- You don't get it, do you?
- Get what?
That maybe instead of beating yourself up
about what you can't do,
take a moment
and appreciate what you can do.
'Cause it's pretty bad-ass.
General Walker. Sorry, General,
but I cannot let you take John Diggle
without the proper paperwork turned in.
- Excuse me?
- Forms I-55 and W-67.
And the completed transfer assignment
signed by the Langham warden.
Never seen a D.A. get involved in military
matters. And on the defense side.
I'm expanding my practice.
Anything else?
It's not common for someone of your rank
to personally supervise
a prisoner transfer.
I make exceptions for traitors
and terrorists.
I'll need a district judge
to ratify the transfer papers.
That could take a few hours,
maybe even a few days.
Do you have the Attorney General
on speed dial? I do.
And she owes me a favor.
I can have you disbarred in 15 seconds.
I expect the prisoner to be
in my custody in 24 hours. Am I clear?
Mmm-hmm.
Tracker's live.
- Where is she?
- The nanites just metabolized.
I'm triangulating them
with a keyhole satellite feed.
Remind me to upgrade our Internet
tomorrow. Got it.
1400 block, Brand Boulevard.
Pulling up keyhole now.
I think I have something that'll help.
A mobile version of the dampener
from S.T.A.R. Labs.
- "Think"?
- I might need some more time with it.
The circuitry is pretty complex
and I'm feeling a lot of pressure...
Felicity can come with and help you.
Hold up. I'm not getting a good enough
reading off the thermal imaging.
There's no way to tell if Black Siren
is actually with.
Prometheus, and the whole point of doing
this is to catch that son of a... bitch.
We need to wait until we get
visual confirmation of Prometheus.
We are not waiting for anything.
We're gonna bring her in right now.
Get on board with this. Suit up!
This is private property.
Ma'am, what are you doing here?
I'm just waiting for a friend.
She's here. Create a perimeter. Go!
- Did you hear that?
- Hear what?
Kidding. I think people in Florida
heard that. We need to hurry.
- She was crazy. She could scream.
- Run away and call the police.
Don't move, Trinity.
Oh.
I thought you'd be someone else.
Disappointing.
- This should do it.
- Are you sure?
No, but we're out of time.
Prometheus.
Diazepam. That should slow you down.
Diazepam.
You could say I have a tolerance.
But you shouldn't be worrying about me
right now.
Ah, Felicity.
I'm so sorry, but I think it's about time
that I kill you.
Felicity or me!
Laurel!
Don't do this.
There's no coming back for you.
If you kill Felicity,
then you're killing that part of yourself
that existed before you lost your family.
If you end this now,
we can find that person again,
together.
She was never there.
You really need to shut your damn mouth.
Hey, pumpkin.
Hey. Kept my wrist straight.
You turn me over, I'll be dead before you
get back to your office.
I believe you.
You know, when I woke up,
I didn't think that I'd be pissing off
one of the most powerful men
in the military.
Hit me.
What?
- What the hell is going on here?
- Your prisoner just decked me.
- Unsatisfied with your legal counsel?
- Who knows?
But we are in Starling County,
and the County Code Section 47.15
specifically states
that the District Attorney, me,
can supersede transfers
to other jurisdictions
if the suspect commits a secondary crime
within my jurisdiction.
Attacking a city official
is a very serious offense, Mr. Diggle.
I think I'm gonna have to
prosecute this one myself.
It could take a while.
Fine. I'll be back with a writ
signed by the President.
Can't wait.
I've always wanted her autograph.
You know how people say,
"Il hate to say I told you so"?
I don't hate it. I freakin' love it.
You really weren't kidding
about that acquired-taste thing.
It's like shooting fish
in a barrel with you.
It's cool. I can take it.
You were right, Rene.
I need to start embracing
what I can do for the team,
instead of what I can't.
That's what I'm talking about.
More tinkering and less fighting.
Well, I wouldn't exactly
call it "tinkering".
- Oh, one more thing.
- Yeah, what's up?
You put your hands on me like that
one more time, and I'll kick your ass.
Oh. Good talk.
God! This is why I usually leave
the punching to you guys.
- It was a memorable punch.
- Mmm-hmm.
Yeah, well, typing is going to be a bit of
a challenge in the next couple of days.
Serves me right.
Because I let Black Siren go,
one of those guards could have
gotten killed.
We almost got Prometheus.
Your plan worked. He was there.
No, if it worked,
we'd be putting cuffs on him right now.
We'll get there.
We'll get him.
I'm sorry she wasn't her.
I know.
I'm sorry about Billy. He was a good man.
Like you.
So I'm guessing that Laurel is
on her way back to Central City then?
Secure lockup at A.R.G.U.S.
I'm keeping her close
because if there is anything left
of the real Laurel in there,
I'm gonna find it.
You know what?
I could really get used to
this newfound optimism of yours.
I'm done asking. Follow me or die.
Find out what's happening.
Hello, Mr. Queen. My name is Talia.
I've been looking for you.
This doesn't feel right.
They're just taking it away like this.
We should build a new one.
- I think we can do better.
- Yeah? What are you thinking?
I haven't kept my promise to Laurel.
You're gonna train a new Black Canary?
I think that somewhere out there, there is
a woman worthy of Laurel's legacy.
Now all we've gotta do is find her.
You boys want another round?
No. I was thinkin' of ordering
somethin' that's not on the menu, huh?
Where you goin', baby?
Seriously, could you two be
any more of a cliché?
Don't worry, sweetheart.
There's plenty of me to go around.
I thought people like you
only existed in the movies.
You know, two guys trying to
overcompensate for their lack of manhood
by taking it out on a defenseless woman.
What are you gonna do about it?
That.
English - SDH