My name was Oliver Queen.
For three years, I worked to save my city.
But to save my sister,
I had to become someone else.
I had to become something else.
Previously on Arrow:
You can still save her, Oliver.
Take your rightful place as heir to the demon
and Ra's al Ghul will bring your sister back.
I have fulfilled my end
of our arrangement.
I suggest you begin
to make peace with yours.
The only way I'm gonna survive this
is if I know that you're out there...
...living your life happy.
Oliver Queen is dead.
And for now, only the Arrow...
...Al Sah-him shall
remain heir to the demon.
Oliver Queen is alive
only in the past. He is forgotten.
Oliver Queen is alive only in the past.
He is forgotten.
You are Al Sah-him.
You have made great progress
in three weeks...
...Al Sah-him.
You no longer flinch
upon hearing your new name.
Oliver Queen is alive only in the past.
He's forgotten.
Indeed. You are Al Sah-him.
You are Wareeth al Ghul, heir to the demon.
My lord...
...I apologize for this interruption.
We captured this intruder.
Why then is he still yet alive?
He is known to Al Sah-him.
What the hell is going on?
Clearly, he made another attempt
to free Al Sah-him.
Well, then it falls on Al Sah-him
to deal with him.
Oliver, they're lying to you.
I never made it home.
They've had me here prisoner for weeks.
My oath of mercy on your friends
was premised by your fealty. Prove it.
No, Oliver, listen to me.
They're lying to you-
We can get out of here. You and me
working together. There's still a chance.
Remove his chains.
Give him your sword, Sarab.
I will not kill an unarmed man.
That's the way this is. You've been here
for a few weeks and you forget who you are.
Remember when you brought me
into your crusade?
I told you I would be here to remind you
who Oliver was...
...if you ever became something else.
I haven't given up on that promise.
Fight.
The past three weeks, you've
been exposed to a rare herb, centuries old.
Causes one's conscience
to come to the forefront of their mind...
...so it's the only thing they see.
The herb's effect is
different for everyone.
Some people see family and loved ones.
Others encounter trusted
friends or teachers.
What did you see?
Very well.
There is something else
I wish you to see. Come.
Where?
The past.
A place now home only for the dead.
I had the vial in my hand.
What's happening is not your fault.
- Shrieve is to blame. This is his doing.
- I can't get through.
Everyone's calling the police.
We're all inoculated, remember?
I want to get back to my son.
I've not been back to this
place since I pledged myself to the League.
What happened here?
When I joined the League,
I was conscripted with another man...
...Damien Darhk.
We would become the prized agents
of Ra's al Ghul.
We were his horsemen.
And he molded us into warriors
the likes the world had never seen.
We were as brothers.
What happened to him?
He believed himself worthy
of becoming heir to the demon.
But I was the one chosen.
So you had to kill him.
Yes.
But, you see, I hesitated.
With that hesitation,
he found an opportunity to escape.
Taking with him his loyalists
and water from the Lazarus Pit.
And he has vexed me ever since.
And you.
- I don't follow.
- Damien continues the League's ways...
...but through his own organization
filled with a hive of agents...
...devoted to his own agenda.
Last year, he tried to purchase
Malcolm Merlyn's earthquake generator.
He gave Gholem Qadir safe haven
to Markovia...
...and he hired Mark Shaw to steal
a secret file from A.R.G.U.S.
This was all the work of one man?
The list goes on.
Many lives have been lost,
others endangered.
And all because I was slow
to swing a vengeful sword.
And I will not have my heir...
...haunted by the same mistake.
What is it you wish me to do?
There is a rival who claims to be heir
to the demon.
You must eliminate this threat
from your reign.
And you must do so without mercy.
Didn't you hear?
Masks aren't wanted in Starling no more.
Tell that to the woman you mugged.
You underestimated your opponent again.
I should've known he had a knife.
- He didn't have a knife.
- What the hell...?
He had two.
Shall we continue your training?
I'm starving.
There's a diner near here that serves the best
black-and-white milkshakes in Starling City.
What is a black-and-white milkshake?
I never understood your country's need
to fry everything.
That's because everything
tastes better that way.
This is more oil than potato.
Dip it in your milkshake.
I sense you mocking me.
Heh. I'm serious.
Here, dip it in your milkshake.
I have to admit, it's fun
seeing you like this.
- Like what?
- Like a normal person.
I am a normal person.
I can't believe you said that.
Mm.
That's actually not bad.
And the student becomes the teacher.
You have a point.
For me, normal is a world
where only the strong survive.
One without simple pleasures.
Thank you, Laurel.
I was alone and adrift.
And you have shown me kindness.
I'm only returning the favor.
Isn't that what you did for Sara?
There's little comparison
between my situation...
...and Sara's after her time
with Oliver on Lian Yu.
What's wrong?
It's about Oliver.
There's something that I haven't told you.
He's in Nanda Parbat.
I don't understand.
He's accepted your father's offer
to become the next Ra's.
You should not have kept that from me.
I'm sorry, it's just...
it's just that you seem so happy, and
after what happened with your father, I...
And here comes the CAT-5 prong
into the Ethernet port.
Even if she knew what that was,
even if I knew what that was...
...I think Sara is still young
for chicken cacciatore.
My mom used to feed me nachos from the bar
at The Grand before I was off the bottle.
- And I turned out normal.
- lsh.
John, what's the house rule?
No Glocks on the dinner table.
How did it go out there tonight?
Your intel was spot-on.
Caught four Halcones at the docks
trying to unload a shipment of M16s.
Well, I'm especially proud
you didn't get yourself killed.
That was my favorite part too.
If you're gonna keep going out,
we should design you some sort of...
Do not say "costume."
Okay. Identity concealment.
Eventually we're going to have to figure
out a new status quo, a working one...
...now that...
Ollie's gone.
How are you doing?
Having never been resurrected before, I don't
really have anything to compare it to.
- I mean, about Oliver being gone.
- I don't know.
Mornings are the worst.
I can't really leave the loft, so...
It's nice to be able to come here.
You are always welcome in our home.
I just miss him.
The fact that he's gone because of me...
He wouldn't want you blaming yourself.
The military, they have a saying for a
soldier that makes the ultimate sacrifice:
Gone but never forgotten.
Liling's apartment
is just a few more blocks north.
Waller said there wasn't a cure.
The United States Army. Shrieve's men.
That's not a cure
they're giving those people.
It's the virus.
Shrieve's leaving nothing to chance.
Wants to infect as many people as possible.
We have to stop him.
Hey! Get away from there.
Move. Move.
Tatsu, the truck.
I had him.
- What do we do now?
- Destroy it.
All of it.
I'm sorry I didn't tell
you about Oliver earlier.
It was your right to know.
I just... Things were
going so well for you.
You seemed happy. I didn't wanna upset you.
I still shouldn't have kept it from you.
Were I so inclined...
...I'd question why your first instinct
is to always keep matters secret.
Even after doing so cost you your
relationship with your father.
But I have much greater concerns.
What's going on?
You should go.
No.
I'm not leaving.
Friends don't do that to one another.
Now that Oliver has ascended to his
position as heir to the demon...
...he will come for me...
...with as many men as it takes
to see me dead.
Tonight, Nyssa al Ghul faces justice
for her betrayal.
Wait a second, Oliver wouldn't.
I don't see how.
What she's trying to say is Oliver
would never do anything to hurt you.
The only reason he joined the League
is to protect people he loves.
And what you need to understand
is that Oliver Queen is dead.
He's a memory.
Apparently, the League
has some of their recruits...
...undergo a process of reprogramming.
Like brainwashing? Oliver never said
that he was signing on for brainwashing.
The League's ways are shrouded
in ritual and ceremony.
- Oliver would not know it was happening.
- I don't care. Oliver, he is stronger than that.
I did not come here to debate.
Laurel insisted
that I bring this news to you myself.
But I can see all I'm doing
is damaging your memory of him.
Perhaps it is better for you to not think
of what Oliver has become.
You can have that luxury.
- Wait, where are you going?
- To face him. And if necessary, my destiny.
I will not cower in the shadows
waiting for death.
Great. Now what are we supposed to do?
Nothing. No offense, but Nyssa is insane.
Oliver is still Oliver.
Nobody knows the League
better than Nyssa.
Did you see her face? She was terrified.
I didn't think that was possible.
- Even if Nyssa's right about Oliver...
- She isn't.
Getting between her and the League
isn't an option.
Since when does Ra's' daughter
become someone we stick our necks out for?
I know you're furious with Ra's
for what he's done to Oliver. We all are.
But Nyssa...
...she saved my sister's life.
She gave her a home. She's a good person.
In spite of everything
that she grew up with.
And the last time I checked...
...protecting good people,
that is what we do.
Fine. Nyssa does seem to have an idea
where we can find Oliver and the League.
We shouldn't have let Nyssa leave alone.
No, it's fine.
I just put a tracking device on her.
This isn't my first day.
Everybody, get back!
Away from the truck!
No more virus.
We have to get back to Akio.
Come on.
- Anything?
- Nyssa hasn't stopped moving.
- I'm still getting a strong signal.
- Copy that.
Radio check every five minutes.
- What?
- If anything happens with Nyssa...
...let me handle it on my own.
- We're talking about the League of Assassins.
- I know that. I just...
Oliver. You were closer to him
than any two people I've known.
- You should not have to...
- What, fight him?
Kill him?
Laurel, it's not gonna come to that.
Look, I'm with Felicity.
There's nothing that Ra's al Ghul can do that
can turn Oliver against the people he loves.
Right.
Nice secret headquarter upgrade.
Does Mr. Palmer know
you guys are in here?
Yes. He's out of town,
and how did you get in here?
My dad's a super villain
and you left your doors unlocked.
Right.
I've been distracted.
Because you and Mr. Diggle
are trying to save the city by yourselves?
Look, I've been thinking.
Um, maybe rather than
me sitting at home alone, miserable...
...maybe I could be out there
helping you guys.
I mean, you seem like you're shorthanded
one and vigilante skills run in my blood.
Thea, this might actually be
the worst week ever for this conversation.
- What's going on?
- I can't.
Felicity, I cannot be handled right now.
It's possible, and I stress "possible,"
that Oliver is back in town.
With the League.
I don't understand.
Why would Ollie come back here?
- They're after Nyssa.
- Ollie would never...
Nyssa thinks he's under some sort
of League mind voodoo.
But it's gonna be fine.
We're handling it.
You are a terrible liar.
That is true.
You know where he is?
Maybe I could just talk to him.
I don't know what doctor's orders are when
someone gets brought back from the dead...
...but I'm sure getting into a fight
with the League goes against them.
I can get through to him.
Please, Thea.
Oliver wouldn't want you involved.
He did what he did
so that you would stay out of harm's way.
Yeah, well,
sounds like Ollie is not here anymore.
This is where my beloved spirit
departed this world.
Do you even remember Sara?
Or has my father already obliterated her
from your memory?
I'm here to bring you back to Nanda Parbat.
To face justice?
If so, for what crime?
To face vengeance?
If so, for what offense?
You told me...
...vengeance is justice.
And you bested me in battle.
That won't happen again.
Do it. If I would die,
I would have it on the same ground as Sara.
Oh, my God.
We can't let you hurt her, man.
Oliver.
You should not have interfered.
Well, I am sorry...
...but I have lost a sister,
a father, Oliver...
There's no way
that I was about to lose you too.
You don't understand.
You already have.
I was marked for death the moment
Oliver accepted my father's offer.
Laurel, these past few weeks...
...they've enlightened me...
...to live a life outside
of my father's rule.
To be someone else even for a little while
brought me great happiness.
But I am daughter of the demon.
Happiness is not something
that was ever meant for me.
I've known Oliver my entire life.
We've been friends since childhood.
- But tonight I did not recognize him.
- I told you...
...he has been changed.
Well, if he can change, then why can't you?
How's Nyssa?
She's with Laurel. She's gonna be okay.
How are you?
Same as you, probably.
Neither one of us believed Nyssa
when she said Oliver had been turned.
I'm still not sure I believe it.
I've heard about this kind of thing.
Guy gets captured by the enemy...
...he gets broken.
I just never imagined Oliver...
Still can't imagine that Oliver would...
He's the strongest man I've ever known,
Felicity.
When Oliver stayed,
when he agreed to join the League...
...he never could have known
this was what he was agreeing to.
Only way I've been able
to get out of bed these past weeks...
...is because I knew
that Oliver was still alive.
He is alive, Felicity.
We thought that Oliver
was just giving up his life to Ra's...
...but he gave up his soul.
There was doubt you would return.
But not from me.
What happened?
Nyssa had friends.
I warned you not to face her alone.
These friends of Nyssa's...
...were they friends of yours?
They'll be protecting her now.
We need to draw her out.
Thank you for coming
Suffice it to say,
I was surprised to get your call.
I need your help.
That couldn't have been easy
for you to say.
I need to know.
Is Ollie back in town?
Is he going after Nyssa?
According to my sources,
he intends to eliminate her...
...as a threat to his ascension to Ra's.
Well, I need to stop him.
He is Wareeth al Ghul now, Thea.
Heir to the demon.
He is my brother. It's one thing to let him join
the League and run off to Nanda Parbat, but...
Another to let him kill?
What did you think he would be doing
in the League of Assassins?
Felicity told me that
he's been brainwashed.
I know what it's like to kill
while under the influence of someone else.
Your brother didn't sacrifice everything
for you to go to war with the League.
- That's what Felicity said.
- And she was right.
No.
I couldn't stop him
from trading his life to save mine.
But this? This, I can stop.
You are a warrior, Thea.
Long before I trained you.
You have always had an incredible strength
inside you...
...and your brother knows that too.
Now...
...what do you need from me?
Are you sure this is okay?
Yeah. With Oliver and the League
running around, it's best we stay close.
Especially if something...
John?
Something's wrong. Lyla?
Where's Lyla?
- John.
- Oliver?
First, let me assure you
that no harm will come to Lyla...
...if you do exactly as I say.
Bring Nyssa to the warehouse at Fullerton
and Halsted, and I'll let your wife go.
Oliver, I swear, if you
do anything to Lyla...
You have 30 minutes.
Laurel.
- What happened?
- Oliver and his new friends took Lyla.
- What? Where's Sara? Is she okay?
- With John's neighbor.
- What's wrong with you?
- Hey, it is not Nyssa's fault.
No, just her people.
You call yourself warriors?
You claim to have honor?
If you knew the meaning of the word...
- ...there are lines you do not cross!
- John, back off.
You back off!
I am truly sorry. I never meant for any
harm to come to you or your family.
Yeah, Nyssa?
Then prove it.
Hand yourself over to the League.
What? We're just gonna negotiate
with them now?
Are we just gonna give in?
Turn over an innocent person?
She's not innocent.
She's the daughter of the demon.
- She's killed hundreds of people.
- Enough.
Only thing that matters
is getting Lyla back.
- I don't care how we do it.
- Yes, you do.
Trading one person's life for another?
We're better than that.
It's all right.
You should exchange me for your beloved.
- I won't see an innocent life taken for mine.
- What? No.
I'm not gonna let you commit suicide.
Don't you remember what you said?
These past few weeks
have been some of the best of your life.
I remember.
And I remember telling you
that happiness is something denied to me.
Where is the exchange to take place?
No. There has to be another way.
Another way to save Lyla
without turning Nyssa over to the League.
And if there isn't,
even if you get Lyla back safe and sound...
...Oliver won't be the only one
who lost his soul.
What happened to you?
Johnny told me,
but how could you become this?
Quiet. It'll be over soon.
No. I genuinely wanna know.
How could the man
who stood up at my wedding do this?
How could the man...
...who's been like a brother...?
Quiet!
You know, when John's brother died...
...a part of him died too.
His guilt and the emptiness from the loss
outweighed everything.
I tried my hardest to help him.
But no one seemed to be able to comfort him
or fill that void...
...until he met you.
You gave him hope and purpose again.
It's time.
Aki0.
- Aki0.
Liling's sick.
It's gonna be okay.
- We have to leave Hong Kong.
- Shrieve and his men...
- Have enough to worry about.
- Tatsu's right.
The chaos will give us cover.
It could be our only chance.
They're here.
Search them.
Where's my wife?
You son of a bitch.
Whatever Ra's did to you...
Don't you dare touch me.
Oliver, this isn't you. Look at me.
I know you're still in there somewhere.
Bind her.
You're free to go.
- Johnny. I thought they were going for Sara.
- It's okay.
Everything's fine. Sara's fine.
I told Felicity, this is just like Jakarta.
- Kneel before the true heir to the demon.
- I kneel before no one.
Laurel.
Nyssa.
You're still Oliver.
I don't care if the hood is black or green.
You're still you.
Get away from him.
Get away from him
or the next one goes in your eye.
Lyla's got Sara. They're
headed out of town.
- There is no straightening this out.
- I don't know.
I can't see past tomorrow right now.
They're gonna kill Nyssa.
- Oliver or her father, they're gonna kill her.
- I'm sorry, Laurel.
It's not fair.
No. No, it's not.
I'll ask it...
...to ask it.
There is no way of getting him back?
He's gone, Felicity.
No one wants to believe that less than me.
But he's gone.
There's only one thing left of him now.
And what's that?
Us.
Gone but never forgotten.
There are no more threats to my reign.
Your fealty continues to impress me,
Al Sah-him.
You truly are Wareeth al Ghul.
And yet my daughter
still does not approve of my choice.
Fortunately, what I require from you
is not your approval.
- Did you search her?
- It does not appear to be on her person.
Bring me her weapons.
You know, as a young child...
...Nyssa displayed the panache of a thief.
Always stealing extra qatayef after meals
and then stowing them away in her quarters.
She would grow to learn
that there is nothing she can hide from me.
Her exploits of late...
...seem to have clouded that memory.
I will remember you
as the warrior you once were...
...and not as this shell
that stands before me.
All my life, I've lived in fear of you.
But now as I stand before you
ready to leave this earth...
...I want you to know...
...I am not afraid.
Do what needs to be done, my heir.
And take with it the satisfaction
that your reign will be unchallenged.
I can see now you do not require a culling
to solidify your reign.
You have broken your rival, Al Sah-him...
...something I wasn't able to do as heir.
Spilling her blood now
would only serve as gluttony.
And perhaps her blood
could be of another purpose.
As a means to unite our families.
You as husband.
And you as wife.
I would rather die
than become his betrothed.
Well, your wishes were no longer my
concern from the moment you betrayed me.
So you will marry Al Sah-him...
...and you will become bride of the demon.
Come on, come on, come on.
We need a vehicle.
Oliver.
- Let's get out of this place.
- It's okay. We're safe now.
Thea?
The door was open.
Sorry to interrupt your staring
into nothingness.
He should have let me die.
That was never an option.
It's why I love him.
I didn't know...
...about you and my brother.
Yeah, well...
It was complicated.
But I did love him.
Despite everything, I still do.
I do too.
How is that even possible...
...after what he's...
Become?
I don't know.
But I think John's right. I think we have
to remember the best parts of him...
...and we have to move on.
Are you trying to convince me or yourself?
Both of us.
I don't know how,
but we have to go on living.
That's what Oliver...
Ollie would want for you.
To move on.
To live.
To be with the one that you love
while you still can.
Roy's gone, so...
You've had a lot on your plate.
And I've been trying to think of
the right time to tell you this.
Roy's alive.
We faked his death. It's a long story...
...as most fake death stories are.
We were gonna tell you, I promise.
You were busy being mostly dead,
Oliver signed on to become Darth Oliver...
- Wait, I don't...
- He's starting a new life.
One that hopefully includes you.
If you want it.
When my daughter left Nanda Parbat...
...she absconded something critical
to both our futures.
Do you recall the village I showed you?
The one where only the dead remain?
- It was your home.
- It was.
And I was obligated
to unleash death upon it.
It has been this way
ever since there has been a Ra's.
You see, it is the final
act of ascension...
...the transformation to Demon's Head...
...the erasure of one's former life...
...former home.
Now, my predecessor, he wiped away
Alexandria, Egypt with cholera in 1609.
Today you will do the same.
Do you recognize this?
The Alpha and Omega bio-weapon.
Beginning and the end.
Now, Nyssa stole this to prevent my heir
from doing that which you will do today.
You will unleash this on Starling City.