For the past five months,
You've been waiting for things
to go back to the way things were.
.:.SubTown.:.
Subtitle Team
Represents
.::. WwW.Film2MoVie.biZ .::.
A shark that does not swim, "drowns".
If you don't move forward, you "die".
I'm recruiting a new "team".
The people that we're looking at
have some experiences on the street.
You have the farthest
way to go.
I'm an "Olympian".
It takes more than a few medals and
a mask to take on these streets.
They were "Bronze".
Our Channel in Telegram:
@moviesicim
Hesam0884@gmail.com
Hessam_hmz
The "Green Arrow" cannot be stopped,
Unless we all work together.
Subtitle & Sync
Soroush_abg
What about "Oliver"?
"Ollie" can take care of himself.
"Arrow"