HUNT:
This is a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity.
Look, all I'm doing is looking
to get something going again.
Yeah, I know.
I know, but this time...
[CLATTERING]
I'm gonna have to call you back.
What?
What, you come back
for another pound of flesh?
You're gonna be disappointed, pal.
Thanks to you, I'm...
[GRUNTING]
-Nice. Picking up the pace.
-Could say the same thing about you.
You crossed three names
off your father's list this week.
Some of these guys are just giving it up.
All I gotta do is pay them a visit.
Seems the vigilante's reputation
is beginning to precede him.
Ah! Ugh.
Another round?
No.
Gotta take my nephew to the mall
so he can let Santa know...
-...what he wants for Christmas.
-Christmas.
[CHUCKLES]
I didn't even realize.
Because you've been logging so many hood
hours ever since that thing with Helena.
I meant...
...there were no holidays on the island.
There just... Every day was:
"How do I stay alive?"
And to do that, you had to forget things.
Like Christmas.
My dad threw a party every year, heh...
...and he would put a Christmas tree
in every room.
The whole mansion smelled like...
It smelled like Christmas.
Maybe give the list a rest
and enjoy the holidays with your family.
Besides,
I hear St. Nick has a list of his own.
I'd wager you're in the "nice" column.
Go home, Oliver.
[ROCKS GRINDING]
You not dead.
Good.
Where the hell have you been?
I ran out of food and water days ago.
Hey. Hey. Where you going?
You.
YAO FEI:
Stop.
He's the one who tied me up and had me
tortured all because he was looking for you.
He would've killed me
if you didn't show up.
Then you kill him.
Or he can take you home.
What?
YAO FEI:
He has a plane.
A way for you off this island.
Hey.
You look very pretty.
What's the occasion?
Mom and Walter are having a dinner party
with some big muckety-mucks.
-Phew.
-Best night of my life.
Thea, why aren't there any decorations up
in the house?
What do you mean?
No wreaths. No trees.
Everyone's just been really busy lately.
I'm sure they haven't gotten around to it yet.
Does Mom at least have
some of those boxes of candy canes?
Remember we used to race
to see who would finish first?
-Yeah, I always won.
-No, you cheated.
Well, she went sugar-free last year.
So I doubt you'll be seeing
any of those around.
The thing that people forget
is that Robin Hood was a criminal.
And stealing from the rich to give to
the poor is really the job of the Democrats.
[ALL CHUCKLE]
All joking aside,
crime is down for the first time in five years.
That's because of the changes
my department has implemented.
Or because the vigilante's activities have
had a chilling effect on the city's criminals.
[MURMURING]
What are your thoughts, Oliver?
I think the vigilante needs a better code
name than "the Hood" or "the hood guy."
[ALL CHUCKLE]
I agree. How about "Green Arrow"?
Lame.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
[WALTER SIGHS]
Forgive me.
It's the office.
Excuse me.
I'm in the middle of a dinner party,
so I hope this is of some importance.
FELICITY: That depends
how you define "important."
See, most people would consider
finding a list of names...
...written in subsonic, ultraviolet,
invisible ink important.
But I already know about that, don't I?
Did you know seven of the names
on the list...
...are guys the vigilante has had
in his crosshairs?
That is if bows had crosshairs,
which they don't.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
But it is a rather long list, Felicity,
so I would expect there to be some overlap.
Like Doug Miller.
Head of Applied Sciences
at Queen Consolidated. What of him?
Miller may end up getting an arrow
in his stocking, because he's on the list.
So important or not?
[WHISPERS INDISTINCTLY]
I'm sorry. Something's come up.
Is everything okay?
The vigilante has struck again.
[MURMURING]
[CELL PHONE BUZZING]
I really do need to take this call.
It's my contractor. Excuse me.
LANCE: Well, the daughter came over,
used her key, found Dad.
Hat trick to the chest.
The hood guy.
That's what I thought at first, but these
black arrows aren't consistent with his M.O.
Neither is the fact that the Hood took Hunt
for $40 million a few months ago.
Doesn't make sense to kill him now.
Something doesn't add up.
We're dealing with a copycat.
Who would kill Adam Hunt with an arrow?
I mean, other than you.
A setup, maybe.
Someone looking to cover up killing Hunt
by making it look like the work of the Hood?
Whoever he was, he's good.
The grouping on Hunt's chest was tight.
It's a compound bow, most likely.
The guy is a...
The guy's a legitimate archer.
So someone who would be particular
about his arrows.
We get an arrow, we get a bead
on where he purchased them.
So, what are you gonna do?
What anyone does when they need help.
Call a cop.
DELIVERY MAN: Quentin Lance?
-Yeah.
Sign here, please.
-Thanks.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
-Lance.
ARROW: I didn't kill Adam Hunt.
-You.
ARROW: You call me "the Hood."
It's not a great nickname.
You told Commissioner Nudocerdo
you might be dealing with a copycat...
...another archer, which makes me
your best bet to take him down.
But I need your help.
I need one of the arrows from his murder.
We're good at pulling down leads
off evidence.
ARROW:
Not like I am.
I can do things the police can't.
Go places they won't.
Like I said, I don't even know who...
If this archer doesn't stop with Adam Hunt,
we both have a problem. Think about it...
...then call me.
Number's programmed in.
[DOOR OPENS]
Doug. Thanks for coming.
Of course.
How's construction coming
on the Applied Sciences Center?
Over budget and behind schedule.
Exactly as expected.
Is that what you wanted to see me about?
Adam Hunt...
...he was murdered last night
by the vigilante.
-I read about that.
-I've been concerned by the idea...
...that the vigilante might target
an employee or officer of this company.
Security red-flagged you.
Me?
Why would this guy go after me?
That's a point I was hoping
you could shed light on.
From what I've read, this vigilante
only goes after white-collar criminals.
Well, let's just hope he doesn't decide
to branch out.
[CHATTERING]
I think there should be a national holiday
for the guy who invented french fries.
Or at least a statue or something.
There is no Christmas party...
...is there?
Thea, Dad threw one of these every year.
Did people think
I just wasn't gonna notice?
SHANE: Hey, Thea.
-Hi, Shane.
-Uh, this is my brother, Oliver.
-Nice to meet you, Thea's brother.
Bet the food on that island's better
than the stuff here.
You'd lose that bet.
We're heading down to the bay,
if you wanna come.
Thanks, but, uh, I'm spending the afternoon
with my brother.
SHANE:
Another time.
See you.
-How do you know that Shane guy?
-We rob banks and smoke crack together.
Heh, that's funny.
I have a feeling I'm not gonna be a fan.
You don't even know him.
Let's change the subject.
Fine. You were gonna tell me why we're not
having the annual Christmas party.
[SIGHS]
When you and Dad disappeared...
...by the time Christmas rolled around...
...none of us felt much like celebrating...
...so we kind of skipped Christmas that year.
Every year.
And it's really fine, so...
No.
No, it's really not.
We're celebrating Christmas.
I went five years without it...
...then Thea tells me you didn't have it
either and I'm the reason. So maybe now...
...I can be the reason
we have Christmas again.
I thought I would throw
the Queen Christmas party.
[CHUCKLES]
You?
I know that I haven't been the son
or the stepson...
...or the brother that all of you deserve,
especially lately...
...but this feels like the right moment
to start making up for lost time.
What do you say?
-I say yes.
OLIVER: Yes. Okay.
I will take care of everything,
you don't have to do anything.
Just show up, look fantastic,
and bring some Christmas cheer, okay?
Okay.
Fine.
You're a good man, Oliver.
FYERS:
You're a good man.
I can see it.
Well, beneath the privileged upbringing
and the wealthy veneer.
I saw it when my man tortured you.
You wouldn't give up your friend.
Not even a friend, really.
Someone you just met.
Shut up.
What do you know about him, hmm?
Nothing, I suspect.
Do you even know
what this island really is?
It's a prison.
I mean this literally.
Until eight years ago,
the Chinese military...
...operated this island as a penitentiary...
...for criminals deemed so dangerous...
...they couldn't be safely incarcerated
on the mainland.
When the military
shut the program down...
...my unit came in
and disposed of all the inmates.
With the exception of two.
Your friend was one of them.
-Who was the other?
-You met him.
He presided over your interrogation.
He tortured me.
You had information I needed.
What would you do in my position?
What would you do to capture the man
who'd slaughtered dozens of people?
Douglas Miller came to see me today
quite concerned.
He said your husband interrogated him.
That his questions suggested a knowledge
he shouldn't have...
...of the list.
Let me talk to him.
I think we're past the point of conversation,
Moira.
A month ago you came to me and told me
to stay away from your family, and I did.
But your family
isn't staying away from me...
...which means
something must be done about it.
-Don't you agree?
-Yes, I do.
And I'll handle it.
I guess what I'm wondering is whether
it's time for our associate to handle it.
Hell yeah, I returned the money.
Seventy-million dollars isn't worth
getting an arrow through the chest.
And you can tell him,
if he's got a problem with that, he can...
LANCE:
Commissioner, this is Nelson Ravich.
The Hood hit him earlier this week.
Ravich wired back the money he embezzled
less than five minutes later.
All right.
We tell the press the Hood did this.
Hunt's murder is a Page-10 story, at best...
...but Ravich makes this
a serial-murder case.
We can't let the public get wind of the idea
that there are two of these nutjobs around.
You want me to ignore a serial killer?
Just catch one of these psychos.
I don't care which one.
That is a direct order
from your commanding officer.
Well, you can forget it, then.
Fine. It's forgotten.
And you're off this case, sergeant.
Effective immediately.
[PHONE DIALING]
[BUZZING]
Don't bother trying to trace this.
You'll never make it through the encryption.
There's a heating vent on the corner
of O'Neil and Adams.
You'll find what you're after there.
ARROW: It'd be a mistake
to set a trap for me, detective.
I'm trading away everything I believe in.
It's the only way to get this bastard.
You've got till Christmas,
and then, copycat or not...
...I'm coming after you.
So your friend Lance gave you
a Christmas present after all.
OLIVER:
Mm-hm.
Teflon-coated titanium blades.
Serrated to split the bone.
Shaft is some type
of specialized polymer...
...which is stronger
than your typical carbon fiber. This...
This is a custom job.
Lance gave in after the other archer dropped
another body.
Nelson Ravich.
Which is another name
you crossed off your dad's list.
So is this guy trying to frame you
or call you out?
Either way, I need to find him.
Hey.
-Don't you knock?
-Felicity, this is the I.T. Department.
-It's not the ladies' room.
-Heh. Right.
-What can I do for you?
-My buddy Steve is really into archery.
Apparently, it's all the rage now.
I don't know why.
Looks utterly ridiculous to me.
Mm-hm.
Anyway, it's Steve's birthday next weekend
and I wanted to buy him some arrows.
Thing is, he gets these special,
custom-made arrows...
...and I have no idea where he gets them.
I was hoping you could find out
where this came from.
-Careful.
-Yeah.
The shaft's composite is patented.
And that patent is registered
to a company called Sagittarius.
-That's Latin for "the archer."
-Really?
Could you find out where and when
this was purchased?
According to Sagittarius
company records...
...that particular arrow
was part of a bundle shipment.
Two hundred units...
...sent to this address.
Felicity...
...you're remarkable.
Thank you for remarking on it.
And Merry Christmas.
I'm Jewish.
Happy Hanukkah.
NUDOCERDO [ON TV]: ...significant resources
of the Starling City Police Department...
...it is clear that this vigilante's cycle
of violence has escalated.
I'm asking our citizens to keep a close eye out
and to report anything suspicious.
A tip line has been set up
and a reward will be offered...
...to anyone who aids the authorities
in the capture of this madman.
It isn't him, is it?
NUDOCERDO:
We are all frustrated with the crime...
The man in the hood,
he didn't kill those people.
NUDOCERDO: This violence has gone on...
-You're the one that said he was a monster.
Yeah, but he was protecting me,
it's different.
...the apprehension of this so-called Hood
that has been terrorizing our city.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
-As police commissioner...
-It's probably Joanna.
She said she was gonna come by
with some files.
Merry Christmas, sir. How are you?
Proficient with firearms.
-Dad?
-Yeah.
I told you I wanted to spend the holidays
with my dad.
Right, because of Sara.
Because it makes the holidays a tough time.
But when you are with someone,
as I wanna be with you...
...then there aren't tough times,
there's just times.
Something is holding you back.
The Queens are having
a last-minute Christmas party...
...and I would like for you
to be my plus-one.
I, um, was looking through
some old photographs...
...and I found this.
Merry Christmas.
[DOOR CLOSES]
Bad enough you're friends with this guy, D,
now he's your what?
I don't know what he is,
but he's not wrong.
Something is holding me back.
Right. Keep listening to that something.
I try to stay out of your personal life,
but Merlyn, Queen, they're selfish.
They think they can treat people
any way they please.
-It's you, me and Sara.
-What?
[LIQUID SPLASHING]
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLING]
[CHATTERING]
[BAND PLAYING JAZZ MUSIC]
-I see the halls are decked.
-You okay?
I'll manage. Ahem.
Is everyone having a good time?
You sure you wanna do this, man?
Maybe now is not the best time
to be Martha Stewart's elf.
My family needs this party, Diggle,
which means that I need it.
[DOOR OPENS THEN CLOSES]
Hey, dude.
Uh, Thea invited me, I hope that's cool.
These are for your mom.
Smooth.
Good luck, kid.
-Thank you for coming.
-Oliver.
You guys look great. Merry Christmas.
ALL: Merry Christmas.
-Let's get a holiday photo.
I've already sent out
our Christmas cards, Oliver.
-Let's get a picture just for the four of us.
-Of course.
SHANE:
Excuse me, Mrs. Queen?
-These are for you.
-Well, thank you.
Uh, I'll go put those in water.
WALTER: Is everything all right?
-You and I should talk. Alone.
THEA:
I'm really surprised.
-Everything okay between the two of you?
-Yeah. I'm sure it'll work itself out.
So glad that both of you could make it.
-Merry Christmas, pal.
-Merry Christmas.
-Hi.
So how long do you think it'll be
till this isn't so weird?
-You know, the three of us.
-It's not weird at all.
[ALL CHUCKLE]
You lied to me.
An odd accusation coming from you.
When you came home, you said you were
through investigating Robert's death.
Robert was my oldest friend.
Do you take me for a man who wouldn't
avenge his best friend's murder?
[SCOFFS]
I thought I could forget about it,
go back to the way things were...
...but you told me too many lies, Moira.
You embezzled money
from the company.
Salvaged the Queen's Gambit.
Why, Moira?
What was it all for?
-For leverage.
-Against whom?
-People you've made very angry.
-Well, then let me help you fight them.
-I can't fight them.
I am them.
I have tried so hard
to convince myself that I'm not.
And loving you...
You were my salvation.
Moira.
Moira...
...whatever you've done,
and whoever these people are...
...the time for lies is over.
You need to tell me what's going on.
Let's just get through the party...
...and I promise I will tell you everything.
[WALTER CHUCKLES]
Tommy, do you mind
if I talk to Oliver for a minute?
Yeah, I'll go grab us a couple of drinks
and drink them both.
[OLIVER CHUCKLES]
I know it's probably not easy for you
to see Tommy and I together.
The invitation said "plus one,"
not "minus Laurel."
I've been wanting to move forward with him,
but something's been holding me back.
I keep making these excuses
that it's my dad, it's my work...
...when really...
...it's you.
But for five years, I was emotionally off...
...because you had died.
And the truth is...
...the last person that I expected
to make me feel again, has.
I'm happy...
...for both of you.
Thank you.
Thea, I have something to tell you.
Oliver.
Hit the road.
What are you doing?
Funny, I was gonna ask you
the same thing...
...because there's a party going on
downstairs that I threw for you.
I told you I didn't want a party,
but you didn't care.
Because you came down
with the holiday blues.
I've been trying to get you
to open up for months.
All this party is doing is bringing back
memories I've been trying to forget.
Thea.
Why would you wanna forget?
No matter how fancy
the party is you throw...
...things will never be the way
they used to be in our family, ever again.
DIGGLE:
Oliver?
What is it now?
That other archer moved to the next level.
He's taken hostages.
This just hit the news.
[WHIMPERING]
"Happy holidays, Starling City.
For the past three months,
this city has been laid siege by a vigilante.
But the police have been unable
to bring him to justice...
...because they lack the will
to do what justice demands.
[SOBBING]
I will kill one hostage every hour
in the name of this vigilante...
...until he surrenders himself
to my authority."
Police are on the scene.
Let them handle this.
Those people are there because of me.
I have to end this.
Oliver, this guy...
This guy, he's very dangerous.
There wasn't anything on the island
that wasn't twice as dangerous as this...
...and I survived there for five years.
Call your people.
Tell them to bring the plane.
There's no need, Yao Fei.
My people will be here shortly.
Do you not think it convenient
you captured me so easily?
YAO FEI: Go.
-What?
Run!
NEWSMAN: Starling City holds its breath
as the hostage crisis unfolds.
Police have attempted
to enter the structure in the Glades...
...but found explosives preventing them
from doing so.
At the moment,
there has been no sign of the vigilante...
...as his one-hour deadline nears.
BOMB TECH: I count three thresholds, each
wired via mercury switches to Semtex charges.
Can you defuse one for HRT
to use as a breach point?
That's gonna take a while. He's gonna
know which way we're coming.
You got a better idea?
Now would be a lovely time.
[CLANGING]
[GLASS BREAKS]
ARROW: Where is he?
WOMAN: I don't know.
ARROW:
It's gonna be okay. Follow me.
Get up on the roof.
-What about...?
-I'll handle him. Move.
Hostages.
You got five hostages on the roof.
Repeat, five hostages on the roof.
ARCHER:
Thank you for coming.
After the warehouse, I knew I'd have to do
something dramatic to get your attention.
-What do you want with me?
-What any archer wants...
...to see who's better.
[YELLS]
ARCHER:
First Hunt, then Ravich, and now you.
[GRUNTING]
I know about the list.
The man who authored it wants you dead.
They call you the Hood,
let's see what you look like without it.
[ARCHER GRUNTS, THEN GROANS]
[GRUNTING AND GROANING]
[HELICOPTER WHIRRING ABOVE]
[GRUNTS]
[COUGHING]
Dig...
...help. Help.
DIGGLE: Hey, relax.
OLIVER: Ugh.
Relax, relax, relax, you're safe.
You're in the hospital.
What happened?
I back-traced your signal,
cleaned you up and got you out.
You have a pneumothorax,
broken ribs and a concussion...
...but the doctors say you're gonna be fine.
Some people are here to see you.
-Are you all right?
THEA: Oh, God, you look terrible.
Thank God you were wearing your helmet.
I told them how you were on a bike
and the semi pulled in front of you.
-What were you even doing out?
-You bailed on your party.
It seemed like the right move.
I mean, like you said,
it wasn't the best timing.
[SIGHS]
Okay, but when I was saying that,
that was me being a bitch.
No. The truth is,
I don't think any of us were at our best.
The real truth is, you wanted to have a party
to bring us closer together.
Well, here we are.
[CHUCKLES, THEN GROANS]
We're gonna let you get some rest.
So we never got
to the exchanging-presents part.
[CHUCKLES]
I don't think I deserve a present.
Look, I know that I've been hard on you...
...about being different
from the way you were.
But the truth is, Ollie...
...I'm not the same person
I was five years ago either.
So maybe we can just accept each other...
...not for who we were...
...but for the people we are now.
Yeah.
Oh.
No cheating.
-You're on.
-Come here.
Thank you, Felicity.
It was good of you to call,
but Oliver's gonna be fine.
-He's already on the mend.
FELICITY: Good. I'm glad to hear it, sir.
I'm stepping into an elevator,
so I'll probably lose you.
I'll call you straight back. Hi.
MAN: It's done.
-And he won't be harmed.
Nor will he ever discover your involvement.
You have my word.
-Forgive me if I don't find that comforting.
-You were warned, Moira.
I told you to get Walter under control
and you couldn't. Steps had to be taken.
That's what you said
to justify Robert's murder.
-And you wonder why I don't trust you.
-Quite a bit of judgment coming from...
...a woman who had her son kidnapped
and tortured.
To prove to you
that Oliver didn't know anything.
And what does it matter now?
-What's done is done.
-No, Moira.
It's just beginning.
In six months, the organization's vision
of what this city should be will be complete.
And you won't feel a thing, will you?
Thousands of innocent people will be dead
and you'll feel nothing.
That's not true.
I'll feel a sense of accomplishment.
And you'll have Walter back.
[OLIVER GRUNTS]
OLIVER:
You know, Dig...
...when I confront somebody on the list...
...I tell them that they failed the city.
But tonight, it was me who failed.
Oliver, five hostages are home tonight
with their families enjoying the holidays...
...because of you.
This guy, the other archer...
...he'll get his.
And you'll give it to him.
We might have a bigger problem.
The other archer told me
that somebody compiled the list.
I always assumed it was my father...
...but what if it wasn't?
What do you mean?
I think there's someone else out there.
Someone who's more of a danger
than the archer.
And I am gonna take him down.