MY NAME IS OLIVER QUEEN.
FOR 7 YEARS, I HAVE FOUGHT
WITH ONLY ONE GOAL...
TO SAVE MY CITY,
BUT NOW A NEW THREAT
HAS EMERGED,
A DANGER SO SEVERE,
IT HAS FORCED ME
TO LEAVE MY FAMILY
IN ORDER TO FACE IT,
AND IT WON'T BE ENOUGH FOR ME
TO JUST BE THE GREEN ARROW.
TO PREVENT THE CRISIS
THAT'S COMING,
I AM GOING TO HAVE TO BECOME
SOMEONE ELSE.
I AM GOING TO HAVE
TO BECOME...SOMETHING ELSE.
PREVIOUSLY ON "ARROW"...
TURNS OUT CONNOR
DOESN'T KNOW HIS BROTHER
AS WELL AS HE THINKS.
WE'RE ALL STILL
ALIVE, AREN'T WE?
WHICH MEANS WHAT EXACTLY,
THAT YOUR BROTHER'S NOT
SUCH A BAD GUY?
WHAT DID YOU DO?
JJ: YOU ARE NOT
GONNA TOUCH ME.
OH, MY GOD.
BECAUSE IF YOU DO,
THE MEN WHO ARE
STORMING YOUR BUNKER
RIGHT NOW
WILL KILL YOUR BROTHER.
OLIVER: I IGNORED THE ORDERS
OF A COSMIC BEING,
AND AS A RESULT,
I WATCHED
AN ENTIRE WORLD
DISAPPEAR.
JOHN: WE'RE FACING
THE DESTRUCTION
OF EVERYTHING?
THAT'S THE VERY
DEFINITION
OF ALL
HANDS ON DECK.
A LOT OF PEOPLE
HAVE DIED ALREADY
FOR THE SAKE
OF THIS MISSION.
I OWE IT TO ALL OF THEM
TO FIND OUT WHO
THE MONITOR REALLY IS.
SO WHAT'S THE PLAN?
I'M GOING TO NANDA PARBAT.
[WHOOSH]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
OLLIE?
HI, SPEEDY.
WELL, I'M GUESSING
MIA'S FOR MOM
AND NOT MY CORTO MALTESE
ALIAS.
GOOD GUESS.
SHE'S BEAUTIFUL, OLLIE.
WHERE'D YOU GET THAT?
ATHENA.
I WASN'T EXPECTING TO
FIND YOU HERE ALONE.
WHERE'S NYSSA?
THAILAND, I THINK.
I DON'T KNOW.
AFTER WE DESTROYED
THE LAZARUS PITS,
SHE SAID SHE HAD SOME
LEAGUE BUSINESS
TO TAKE CARE OF.
YOU DESTROYED
THE PITS.
WHY DIDN'T YOU
COME HOME?
PITS MAY BE GONE,
BUT THE THANATOS GUILD ISN'T.
I HAVE TO TAKE THEM DOWN
AFTER WHAT THEY DID TO ROY.
THAT'S FAIR.
HAVE YOU SEEN HIM?
HE CAME BACK HERE
AFTER STAR CITY.
HE TOLD ME WHAT HAPPENED,
HOW HE KILLED
THOSE MEN AND...
HE'S DEALING
WITH HIS OWN DEMONS.
HE'LL BE BACK.
[SIGHS]
I MISSED YOU.
I MISSED YOU, TOO.
BUT I'M PRETTY SURE
I'M NOT THE REASON
WHY YOU CAME HERE.
LAST YEAR, I MADE
A DEAL
WITH A COSMIC BEING
NAMED MAR NOVU.
RECENTLY, HE CAME
TO COLLECT HIS DEBT.
HE ASKED ME TO
HELP HIM,
BUT HE'S NOT VERY GOOD
AT SHARING INFORMATION
WITH THE PEOPLE
HE'S WORKING WITH.
SOUNDS LIKE
SOMEBODY ELSE I KNOW.
I NEED TO BE 100% SURE
THAT I CAN TRUST HIM.
I KNOW IT'S A LONG SHOT,
BUT I WAS HOPING
THAT NYSSA COULD TELL ME
WHAT, IF ANYTHING,
THE LEAGUE KNOWS
ABOUT HIM.
OK. WHAT ARE YOU
NOT TELLING ME?
HE'S SEEN THE FUTURE.
HE'S SEEN ME DIE.
IT'S SOON, SPEEDY.
AND?
TAKE AS MUCH TIME
AS YOU NEED TO BE UPSET.
OLLIE, COME ON.
YOU'VE CHEATED DEATH
MORE THAN ANY OF US
HAVE BY THIS POINT.
THIS IS FUNDAMENTALLY
DIFFERENT THAN ANYTHING
THAT WE'VE EVER DEALT
WITH BEFORE.
OK.
WELL, LET'S TRY TO
FIGURE OUT WHAT WE'RE
DEALING WITH,
BUT LIKE I SAID,
NYSSA'S NOT HERE.
SARA HASN'T BEEN ABLE
TO HELP EITHER.
WE'VE KIND OF KILLED OFF
EVERY LEAGUE MEMBER,
HAVEN'T WE?
I CAN THINK
OF ONE MORE.
[ALARM BLARING]
WILLIAM?
CONNOR: WILLIAM?
FRAK!
[CONNOR COCKS GUN]
WILLIAM!
WHERE IS HE?
-AAH?
-OH. IT'S YOU.
I'M HERE. I'M OK.
I REMEMBERED HOW MOM
HARDWIRED
THE BUNKER'S POWER GRID
THROUGH THE FLOOR.
GAVE THOSE GUYS THE SHOCK
OF THEIR LIVES.
GUYS.
THIS IS WHY JJ WAS
GOING AFTER WILLIAM.
HE'S TARGETING
ALL THE MEMBERS
OF THE STAR CITY
UNIFICATION MOVEMENT.
THE ONES THAT ARE
STILL ALIVE ANYWAY.
THIS WAS A CITY-WIDE
ASSAULT.
THERE'S 10
CONFIRMED DEAD.
AND NOW THAT JJ KNOWS
WHO THEY ALL ARE,
IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF TIME
BEFORE HE WIPES OUT
THE ENTIRE MOVEMENT.
WILLIAM: UNLESS
WE TRAP HIM FIRST.
ALL WE REALLY NEED
IS THE RIGHT...LURE.
YOU WANT TO USE
YOURSELF AS BAIT?
NO WAY.
IT IS TOO DANGEROUS.
CONNOR: LOOK. I KNOW
YOU DON'T WANT TO
HEAR THIS,
BUT THE DEATHSTROKES
HAVE BEEN 5 STEPS
AHEAD OF US
THIS WHOLE TIME.
WE NEED TO GAIN
THE UPPER HAND.
WHICH IS WHY WE
ARE GOING
TO BRING
THE FIGHT TO THEM,
TAKE THEM OUT
IN ONE FELL SWOOP.
ZOE: HOW? IT'S NOT
LIKE WE'RE GONNA WALTZ
BACK INTO THEIR
HEADQUARTERS.
UNLESS THAT'S
YOUR PLAN.
CONNOR: MIA, THAT
DIDN'T WORK OUT
TOO WELL FOR US
LAST TIME.
RIGHT, BUT WE'VE
BEEN THERE BEFORE.
WE KNOW THE LAYOUT.
WE CAN USE THAT
TO OUR ADVANTAGE.
I THINK THIS IS
A MISTAKE.
I'LL REMEMBER THAT.
GET READY TO MOVE OUT.
[SCOFFS]
SOMETHING WRONG
WITH THE UPLINK?
JOHN: NO, NO. IT'S
OUR TIMING THAT'S OFF.
JJ ALREADY WENT
TO SLEEP.
WELL, WE CAN CALL HIM
BACK, WAKE HIM UP.
NO. LITTLE MAN'S
GONE THROUGH
ENOUGH ALREADY.
BESIDES, I NEED TO
KNOW WHAT MISSION
WAS SO IMPORTANT
THAT YOU WANTED ME
HERE INSTEAD
OF NANDA PARBAT.
BEN TURNER IS CURRENTLY
ON A DEEP COVER OP,
SO I'VE BEEN KEEPING
AN EYE ON HIS FAMILY.
SANDRA HAWKE HAS NEVER
MISSED A CHECK-IN
UNTIL YESTERDAY.
SO YOU THINK
SOMETHING HAPPENED
TO SANDRA AND CONNOR?
I KNOW IT.
[TYPING]
THESE PICTURES WERE TAKEN
AT AN AIRFIELD IN KASNIA.
KASNIA? THAT'S FAR
FROM HOME.
ANY CHANCE SANDRA
AND CONNOR ARE
MEETING UP WITH TURNER?
KASNIA'S NOWHERE CLOSE
TO ANY OF TURNER'S MISSIONS
PAST, PRESENT, OR FUTURE,
AND THEN THERE'S
THIS MAN.
ABDUL NARDOC.
HE OWNS THAT PLANE.
NARDOC BILLS HIMSELF
AS A PHILANTHROPIST,
BUT INTEL SUGGESTS
THAT HE HAS TIES
TO LOCAL TERRORISTS.
-HMM.
-HE'S THROWING A FUNDRAISER
TOMORROW AT HIS HOME.
ODDS ARE GOOD THAT
SANDRA AND CONNOR ARE
BEING HELD ON SITE.
WE NEED TO INFILTRATE
AND GET EYES ON THEM.
WHY NOT JUST TAKE
AN A.R.G.U.S.
RECON TEAM?
I'VE SPENT THE PAST
FEW MONTHS TRYING TO
UNTANGLE THE WEB
OF CORRUPTION AT A.R.G.U.S.
UNTIL I ELIMINATE IT,
I CAN'T TRUST THIS
WITH ANYONE.
I NEED YOU WITH ME, JOHN.
HMM. MUST BE
REALLY IMPORTANT
IF YOU CALL ME
JOHN.
GUESS I NEED A SUIT.
I ALREADY PICKED
ONE OUT.
HMM.
I THOUGHT YOU GUYS
WERE FRIENDS NOW.
WELL...NOT EXACTLY.
OK. WELL, THIS PLACE
ISN'T THE LEAST
BIT CREEPY.
[SWORD SCRAPES]
TALIA: HOLD!
LEAVE US.
YOUR STUDENTS USED TO
ASK QUESTIONS FIRST.
I HAVE LEARNED
THAT HESITATION
OFTEN PROVES FATAL.
YOU SHOULD NOT HAVE
COME TO THIS PLACE.
YOU OWE ME A DEBT.
I'M HERE TO COLLECT.
YOU COME HERE
AT GREAT PERIL.
ESPECIALLY YOU.
WORD OF YOUR EXPLOITS
HAS TRAVELED FAR.
HOW IS MY SISTER?
SHE'S GREAT.
VACATIONING,
WORKING ON A TAN.
I SEE YOU SURVIVED
PRISON.
MM-HMM. DR. PARKER DIDN'T.
HEARD HE WAS KILLED
WITH A SWORD.
HE RECEIVED
THE JUSTICE
HE DESERVED.
SO NOW YOU'RE BACK
TO YOUR OLD EXPLOITS?
WITH THE LEAGUE GONE,
THE REGION HAS BECOME
QUITE UNSTABLE.
AND YOU THINK TRAINING
A BUNCH OF ASSASSINS
IN A PLACE LIKE THIS
IS GONNA STABILIZE IT?
I THINK IT A WISER
COURSE OF ACTION
THAN DECLARING
A ONE-WOMAN WAR
ON THE THANATOS GUILD.
MUCH AS I WOULD LIKE
TO HAVE A DEBATE, TALIA,
I NEED TO KNOW WHATEVER
THE LEAGUE MIGHT KNOW
ABOUT MAR NOVU.
THAT'S AN UNUSUAL NAME.
I'D REMEMBER IT.
IF IT HELPS, HE'S
APPARENTLY SOME KIND
OF COSMIC KNOW-IT-ALL.
WELL, SUCH BEINGS
OFTEN GO BY
MANY NAMES.
IF I HELP YOU,
I CAN CONSIDER
MY DEBT PAID?
YES.
IF THE LEAGUE HAS
ANY INFORMATION
CONCERNING THIS MAN,
IT WILL BE FOUND
UNDERNEATH THE KARAN SHAH.
THE LEAGUE'S STRONGHOLD.
IT HAS SINCE
BEEN DESTROYED,
BUT MY FATHER KEPT
THE LEAGUE RECORDS
IN THE CATACOMBS,
SO WITH ANY LUCK,
THEY'RE STILL THERE
WAITING TO BE FOUND.
WE LEAVE AT NIGHTFALL.
SHE'S STILL FUN.
[COUGHING]
MIA: YOU GOOD?
WILLIAM: I'M FINE.
I THINK I JUST...ACK...
GOT SOME DUST IN MY MOUTH.
ACK! WAS IT THIS
DUSTY LAST TIME?
IT WAS WORSE.
ARE YOU SURE THIS
IS GONNA WORK?
IF I CAN TAP INTO
THE OLD GALAXY ONE CAMERAS,
WE SHOULD BE ABLE
TO SEE EVERYTHING,
INCLUDING JJ AND HIS
DEATHSTROKE MANIACS.
CONNOR: PSTT. HEY.
SOMEONE'S COMING.
GUYS, THERE'S AN OFFICE
JUST UP HERE I CAN USE.
OK. SYSTEM'S GONNA NEED
A MINUTE TO REBOOT
BEFORE I CAN ACCESS IT.
LOOK. I KNOW YOU THINK
THIS IS A BAD IDEA.
THE 4 OF US TAKING
ON ALL OF JJ'S
FORCES
ON THEIR HOME TURF?
WASN'T MY
FIRST CHOICE.
THANKS FOR COMING ANYWAY.
WE'RE A TEAM.
I JUST...
I HOPE YOU'RE DOING
THIS FOR THE RIGHT
REASONS.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
I'M PISSED THAT JJ
TRIED TO KILL
WILLIAM, TOO,
BUT WE CAN'T LET FEAR
DICTATE OUR STRATEGY.
I'M NOT AFRAID OF JJ
OR HIS IDIOT GOONS.
I KNOW, BUT YOU ARE
AFRAID OF LOSING
YOUR BROTHER.
[TABLET BEEPS]
WILLIAM: BAD NEWS, GUYS.
SYSTEM'S IN WORSE SHAPE
THAN I THOUGHT.
I'M GONNA NEED
MORE TIME.
CONNOR: WE SHOULD GET
INTO POSITION.
I'LL STAY WITH WILLIAM
UNTIL HE'S DONE.
LET US KNOW WHEN
YOU'RE UP AND RUNNING.
YEAH.
[JAZZ PLAYING]
JOHN: SEE A LOT
OF UNFRIENDLY
FACES HERE.
HOW YOU LOOKING?
JUST WAITING FOR
THE SECURITY FEEDS
TO FINISH UPLOADING.
HMM. DANCING UNDERCOVER'S
LIKE DEJA VU.
THERE'S NARDOC.
WHAT DO YOU SAY WE
TAKE A CLOSER LOOK,
FIND OUT WHO
HIS FRIENDS ARE?
YOU'VE COME A LONG WAY
SINCE AFGHANISTAN.
HEH HEH HEH.
YEAH. WELL, SOMETIMES,
I WISH WE WERE STILL
ON THAT TOUR.
LIFE WAS A LOT LESS
COMPLICATED.
BUT WE WOULDN'T
BE MARRIED.
HMM. THAT'S TRUE.
OR DIVORCED.
OR REMARRIED,
AND WE WOULDN'T HAVE
OUR BEAUTIFUL BOY.
ALL THE FEEDS ARE
COMPLETE.
COPY THAT.
SANDRA AND CONNOR ARE HERE.
THEY'RE BEING HELD
IN A ROOM
IN THE NORTHEAST CORNER.
GOOD. WE'LL
EXFIL THEM OUT
BEFORE NARDOC KNOWS
WHAT HIT HIM.
I DON'T THINK IT'S
GONNA BE THAT EASY.
-WHY?
-WE JUST GOT A HIT ON ONE
OF NARDOC'S FRIENDS.
THE MAN IN THE BLACK SUIT
AND BLUE TIE...
FARZAD QADIR.
GHOLEM QADIR'S SON.
-WHO BEN TURNER KILLED?
-TO SAVE ME.
I DOUBT HIS FAMILY'S
KIDNAPPING IS A COINCIDENCE.
THEA: WOW. LOVE
WHAT THEY HAVEN'T DONE
WITH THE PLACE.
ASSUMING THE KARAN SHAH
HASN'T BEEN PLUNDERED,
WE'RE LIKELY TO FIND
WHAT WE'RE LOOKING FOR
IN "THE CHRONICLES
OF AL-FATIH."
HE WAS THE FIRST
RA'S AL GHUL.
ACCORDING TO LEGEND,
HE WAS BESTOWED
PRIMORDIAL KNOWLEDGE
BY ONE OF THE SKY GODS.
NOW MY FATHER KEPT
A SECRET ROOM
WITH HIS MOST VALUED
POSSESSIONS,
INCLUDING INFORMATION
ON AL-FATIH.
[THUNK]
[ROCK SCRAPING]
OLIVER: LOOKS LIKE
WE'RE TOO LATE.
TALIA: NOT NECESSARILY.
HEH HEH HEH.
"THE CHRONICLES
OF AL-FATIH."
SO THE LOOTERS
JUST HAPPENED TO
LEAVE BEHIND
THE ONE THING
WE'RE LOOKING FOR?
BECAUSE THE THIEVES
DID NOT CONSIDER IT
TO BE OF VALUE.
RIGHT. WHAT'S IT SAY?
"THE PHOENIX IS
REBORN IN THE FIRE.
THE PATH TO YOUR
DESTINY FOLLOWS ME."
SPEEDY, YOU JUST
READ ARABIC.
YOU SPEAK RUSSIAN.
YES, BUT WHAT DOES
IT MEAN?
TO JOIN THE LEAGUE,
YOUR OLD SELF MUST DIE
SO THAT YOUR NEW ONE
MAY BE REBORN.
OH.
WE NEED TO BURN
THE SCROLL.
THE SCROLL IS
CENTURIES OLD.
YEAH.
AL-FATIH TOOK GREAT PAINS
TO HIDE HIS SECRETS
LEST HE BE BETRAYED.
I BELIEVE THIS LEADS
TO AL-FATIH'S TOMB.
IT STANDS TO REASON
THAT HE WOULD ATTEMPT
TO TAKE HIS SECRETS
WITH HIM BEYOND THE GRAVE.
SO IT'S A SCAVENGER HUNT.
IT WOULD APPEAR SO, YES.
WHY CAN'T EVERYTHING
JUST BE EASY?
ATHENA: ACTUALLY, YOUR
SITUATION IS MORE
DIFFICULT THAN YOU THINK.
-ATHENA.
-YOU HAVE ALWAYS BEEN
TREACHEROUS, TALIA,
BUT BRINGING OUTSIDERS
INTO OUR SACRED HEART
IS A BETRAYAL
OF THE HIGHEST ORDER.
I'LL TAKE THAT.
RELINQUISH IT OR PERISH.
AS YOU WISH.
ATHENA: ATTACK THEM!
ATHENA SHOWING UP
RIGHT WHEN WE DID
CAN'T BE AN ACCIDENT.
NO, AND NEITHER WAS
HER GIVING ATHENA
THE SPHERE.
IF YOU'RE ACCUSING
ME, I'D LIKE TO
POINT OUT TWO THINGS.
FIRST, ATHENA AND I
ARE BLOOD ENEMIES.
AND SECOND?
SHE WAS LIKELY
TRAILING YOU.
THE WOMAN WHO'S
DECLARED WAR
ON HER.
STILL, I DON'T SEE
WHY ATHENA WOULD GIVE
A CRAP ABOUT A RUSTY,
OLD SCROLL BURIED
WITH AL-FATIH.
SHE WOULDN'T.
SHE WOULD GIVE
A CRAP
ABOUT WHAT ELSE
IS BURIED WITH HIM,
NAMELY HIS SWORD
AS REVERED
AS THE RING OF RA'S.
WHOEVER WIELDS IT
COMMANDS ABSOLUTE
DEVOTION.
CLEARLY ATHENA WANTS
TO USE IT TO RESTART
THE LEAGUE
OF ASSASSINS.
YEAH. WELL, NOW SHE'S GOT
THE MARBLE OF DESTINY
OR WHATEVER.
ACTUALLY, IT'S A MAP.
THE MARKINGS ON IT
WERE CONSTELLATIONS
INDICATING
THE TOMB'S LOCATION,
BUT WE DON'T NEED IT.
I'VE MEMORIZED THEM.
OLIVER: WHAT?
-YOU MEMORIZED THEM?
-YOU DIDN'T?
OK. LISTEN. I'M GONNA
GO HEAD WITH TALIA.
I'D LIKE YOU TO GO
BACK TO HER CAMP
AND WAIT
FOR US THERE.
YOU CAN'T BE SERIOUS.
I WILL GIVE YOU TWO
A MOMENT.
OLLIE, I THOUGHT
WE WERE WAY
PAST THIS
OVERPROTECTIVE
BROTHER THING.
IT'S NOT ABOUT THAT.
YOU CAME TO ME
FOR HELP.
I CAME TO YOU
FOR ANSWERS.
I WASN'T COUNTING
ON GETTING ATTACKED
BY ATHENA.
ATHENA AND I WERE
FIGHTING LONG BEFORE
YOU SHOWED UP HERE.
I CAN TAKE CARE
OF MYSELF.
I KNOW YOU CAN TAKE
CARE OF YOURSELF.
IF ATHENA IS TRYING TO
RESTART THE LEAGUE
OF ASSASSINS,
THAT MAKES YOU
HER CHIEF RIVAL.
-I DON'T CARE.
-I CARE, THEA.
IF YOU WANT TO HELP ME,
JUST...JUST LET ME
HANDLE THIS.
QADIR MUST BE USING
TURNER'S FAMILY
TO LURE HIM OUT.
OK. THEN WE HAVE TO
GET OUT OF HERE
RIGHT NOW.
WHAT? WHAT ARE
YOU TALKING ABOUT?
IF BEN TURNER'S A TARGET,
THEN SO ARE WE,
AND EVERY SECOND
WE STAY HERE,
WE RISK BEING MADE.
WHAT ABOUT SANDRA
AND CONNOR?
CALL AN A.R.G.U.S.
TEAM, LYLA.
-EXIFL THEM.
-IT WOULD TAKE A TEAM
AT LEAST AN HOUR
TO GET HERE.
A LOT CAN HAPPEN
BETWEEN NOW THAT THEN.
OK, FINE, BUT WE
CAN'T RISK DOING
THIS ALONE.
-WE HAVE TO DO SOMETHING.
-THEN YOU LEAVE.
I'LL GET SANDRA
AND CONNOR MYSELF.
JOHNNY...
WHAT'S REALLY
GOING ON HERE?
YOU'VE NEVER BEEN ONE
TO SHY AWAY FROM RISK.
I'D NEVER SEEN A WORLD
JUST DISINTEGRATE
IN FRONT OF MY FACE.
I KNOW WHAT WE DO
REQUIRES RISK.
I'VE ALWAYS
ACCEPTED THAT,
BUT THIS IS
DIFFERENT, LYLA.
SEEING A UNIVERSE
JUST DISAPPEARING,
I DON'T KNOW, IT'S
LIKE...
LIKE LOOKING
INTO THE EYE OF GOD.
IT CHANGES YOU.
IT CHANGED ME.
I CAN'T RISK
LOSING YOU.
I CAN'T RISK THAT.
NO ONE KNOWS THE FUTURE.
ALL WE CAN DO IS
ENJOY THE TIME WE HAVE
WITH THE PEOPLE WE LOVE
AND MAKE OUR CHOICES
FROM A PLACE OF STRENGTH,
NOT FEAR,
AND IF THE WORLD
ENDS TODAY,
THERE IS NO ONE I'D
RATHER HAVE BY MY SIDE.
HOW MUCH FURTHER?
PATIENCE. YOU REALIZE
YOUR SISTER IS INVOLVED
IN THIS WHETHER YOU
WANT HER TO BE OR NOT?
SHE'S A DAUGHTER
OF THE DEMON.
SHE HAS A CLAIM
TO THE SWORD.
SHE'S CARRIED ENOUGH
OF MALCOLM'S BURDENS.
FATE DOES NOT CARE
WHAT WE BELIEVE
WE'RE OWED.
YOU'RE VERY FAMILIAR
WITH THAT.
ISN'T THAT WHY
YOU'RE HERE?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
YOU CARRY YOURSELF
WITH A HEAVINESS
I'VE NOT SEEN
SINCE RUSSIA.
THIS IS THE PLACE.
I'VE BEEN HERE BEFORE.
YES. WHEN MY FATHER
VANQUISHED YOU.
HOPEFULLY YOU HAVE
BETTER LUCK
WITH THE MOUNTAIN
THIS TIME.
[CLANG]
[CREAKING]
DOWN!
THE PHOENIX UP THERE,
TRIGGERING THE SPEARS.
HERE'S AN IDEA.
[CREAKING]
THE KEY TO THE CRYPT
OF RA'S.
LOOKS LIKE THE ENTRANCE
RIGHT THERE.
YES.
AGH!
WH...WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I AM SORRY, OLIVER.
I CAN'T LET ATHENA
GET TO THE SWORD,
BUT I CAN'T LET YOU
GET IT EITHER.
LOOKS LIKE YOU'RE DOWN
ONE EVIL COMPANION.
HMM.
I THOUGHT I TOLD YOU TO
STAY AT THE CAMP.
YOU DID. LOOKS LIKE
I DIDN'T IGNORE YOU
SOON ENOUGH.
HEY. I DON'T HAVE TIME
FOR AN I TOLD YOU SO.
ALL RIGHT.
SO TALIA WILL TAKE
THE TRAIL TO THE SUMMIT.
IT'S SAFER,
YOU CONSERVE ENERGY,
BUT GOING UP THE FACE
OF THE MOUNTAIN IS FASTER.
THOUGHT YOU SAID
IT WAS HARDER.
YEAH. I'VE DONE IT BEFORE.
OK. IF YOU CAN DO IT,
I CAN DO IT.
-THEA.
-OLLIE, JUST STOP IT.
START WALKING.
MIA: TELL ME YOU'RE
ALMOST DONE HACKING
THOSE CAMERAS.
YOU EVER HEAR
THAT THING ABOUT PATIENCE
BEING A VIRTUE?
SINCE WHEN HAVE
I EVER CARED
ABOUT VIRTUE?
ALL RIGHT. SERIOUSLY,
HOW MUCH LONGER?
OK. I JUST ACTIVATED
THE NORTHWEST
QUADRANT CAMERAS.
I JUST NEED A FEW MORE
MINUTES TO GET THE REST
OF THEM UP AND RUNNING.
MIA: HOW MANY
IS A FEW?
LOOK. I KNOW WHAT
I'M DOING, OK,
SO JUST TRUST ME.
[SIGHS]
I DO.
I D...I JUST...
WILLIAM, THIS HAS
TO WORK.
IF WE'RE GONNA
BRING STAR CITY
AND THE GLADES
BACK TOGETHER,
WE HAVE TO TAKE OUT
THE DEATHSTROKES
FOR GOOD THIS TIME.
WELL, WE COULD HAVE
IF YOU'D LET THE TEAM
USE ME AS BAIT.
NO. THAT IS TOO RISKY,
AND YOU KNOW IT.
WELL, HOW MANY TIMES
HAVE YOU RISKED YOURSELF
FOR THIS TEAM?
HOW MANY TIMES HAVE YOU
BEATEN UP A GUY
10 TIMES YOUR SIZE
TO PROTECT SOMEONE
YOU CARE ABOUT?
-THAT'S DIFFERENT.
-WHY? BECAUSE I'M NOT A FIGHTER?
NO. BECAUSE
YOU'RE MY BROTHER.
YOU ARE THE ONLY FAMILY
I HAVE LEFT.
MIA...LOOK.
I...
I APPRECIATE YOU
LOOKING OUT FOR ME. I DO,
BUT OPERATING
FROM A PLACE OF FEAR
IS NOT THE WAY
TO PROTECT EACH OTHER.
WE NEED TO TRUST EACH OTHER.
IT'S THE ONLY WAY
WE'LL SURVIVE.
[TABLET BEEPING]
FOUND THEM.
OH, BOY. THAT IS A LOT
OF DEATHSTROKES.
YOU SURE ABOUT THIS?
MIA: CONNOR, ZOE, WE HAVE EYES.
ZOE: ROGER THAT.
MIA: GET READY TO MOVE.
ZOE: ON IT.
MIA.
BE CAREFUL.
I WILL.
OH, AND IF YOU TELL
ANYONE
ABOUT THIS CONVERSATION,
I WILL KILL YOU
MYSELF.
ERR!
THOUGHT YOU SAID
THIS WAS THE HARD PART.
DON'T GET COCKY.
OK. WHAT IS GOING
ON WITH YOU, OLLIE?
YOU WERE NEVER THIS
OVERPROTECTIVE
WHEN I LEFT STAR CITY.
THINGS HAVE CHANGED.
I LEFT MY FAMILY BEHIND,
SPEEDY,
AND I MISS THEM.
AND EVERY DAY, I WRESTLE
WITH WHETHER OR NOT
I MADE THE RIGHT DECISION
BECAUSE MAYBE I DIDN'T,
AND...
I SAW AN ENTIRE WORLD
WIPED OUT OF EXISTENCE,
A WORLD THAT
YOU WEREN'T IN, BY THE WAY,
BECAUSE I WASN'T AROUND
TO PROTECT YOU.
I'M SORRY, THEA,
BUT THE ONLY WAY
THAT I CAN BEAR THIS
IS IF I BECOME 100%
CERTAIN
THAT MY SACRIFICE,
THAT MY DEATH...
WILL PROTECT
THE PEOPLE I LOVE.
I NEED MY FAMILY
TO BE SAFE.
YOU KNOW, I'VE BEEN
THINKING A LOT
ABOUT MOM AND DAD
LATELY,
WONDERING WHAT THEY
WOULD THINK
ABOUT THE LIVES
WE'VE CHOSEN.
ALL THE MISTAKES
THEY MADE,
ALL THE...LIES
THEY TOLD
IN THEIR OWN
VERY, VERY
MESSED UP WAY.
THEY THOUGHT THEY
WERE PROTECTING US.
THEY WEREN'T.
THEY DIDN'T.
NO, BUT...IT DID
HELP US BECOME
THE PEOPLE WE ARE
TODAY.
THEY TURNED US
INTO HEROES.
WE CAN'T CHANGE
THE FUTURE, OLLIE.
THE PAST TEACHES US
YOU MIGHT AS WELL
NOT BOTHER TRYING TO.
HEH.
WHEN YOU'D STOP BEING
MY BABY SISTER?
NO. I NEVER DID.
I JUST GREW UP
A LITTLE BIT.
NOW CAN WE PLEASE GET
OFF THIS MOUNTAIN?
YEAH.
[SIGHS]
WE'RE NOT ALONE.
[FOOTSTEPS]
APPARENTLY, THIS DAY
IS NOT GOING THE WAY
EITHER OF US
HAVE PLANNED.
SURRENDER YOUR WEAPONS.
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
THE ROUTE TO AL-FATIH'S
CRYPT WILL BE DANGEROUS.
ALWAYS GOOD TO HAVE A FEW
SACRIFICIAL LAMBS
TO TELL US
WHERE NOT TO STRAY.
AFTER YOU.
UNDERGROUND IN NADA PARBAT.
WHAT COULD POSSIBLY
GO WRONG?
WELL, INDIANA JONES
MADE THIS LOOK
WAY MORE FUN.
"TO SURVIVE DEATH,
YOU MUST EMBRACE IT."
OLIVER: WELL,
HOW DO YOU
EMBRACE DEATH?
THE COFFIN.
COME ON.
GO ON.
OK.
[GROANING]
[BONES CRACK]
I MISS WATCHING
YOU KICK ASS.
THIS WAY.
MUST BE
PASSCODE-PROTECTED.
THIS SHOULD BE ABLE
TO CRACK IT,
BUT IT'LL TAKE
A FEW MINUTES.
WE MAY NOT HAVE
IF THIS IS QADIR
AND HIS MEN,
HE'LL RECOGNIZE US
THE MINUTE HE SEES US.
MAYBE WE CAN USE THAT.
I WAS STANDING NEXT
TO GHOLEM QADIR
THE NIGHT THAT TURNER
KILLED HIM.
I CAN DISTRACT FARZAD.
LYLA THAT'S
TOO DANGEROUS.
IT'S OUR ONLY OPTION.
HEY. JUST BE CAREFUL.
PARDON ME.
WAIT.
YOU KNOW, USUALLY,
I DETEST PARTY CRASHERS,
BUT I'LL MAKE
AN EXCEPTION FOR YOU...
LYLA MICHAELS.
[BEEPING]
[LOCK CLICKS]
HEY. SHH, SHH, SHH, SHH.
IT'S OK. IT'S OK.
MY NAME IS JOHN DIGGLE.
I'M A FRIEND OF LYLA MICHAELS
AND BEN TURNER.
I'M HERE TO HELP YOU.
I CAN GET YOU OUT OF HERE,
BUT YOU HAVE TO MOVE QUIETLY.
COME ON, COME ON.
SHH, SHH SHH.
DID YOU KNOW I WAS THERE
THE NIGHT MY FATHER DIED?
I WAS SUPPOSED TO
STAY IN MY ROOM,
BUT I WANTED TO
HEAR THE MUSIC.
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
WHAT IT'S LIKE TO WATCH
YOUR OWN FATHER
BE MURDERED?
I WAS JUST A BOY.
I'M SORRY YOU HAD TO
SEE THAT,
BUT YOUR FATHER WAS
A CRIMINAL.
SO HE DESERVED
TO DIE?
I WILL HAVE
MY VENGEANCE.
[MUFFLED GUNSHOTS]
YOU ALL RIGHT?
I'VE GOT SANDRA
AND CONNOR.
LET'S GO HOME.
ATHENA:
PRISONERS FIRST.
WATCH YOUR STEP.
THEA: OLLIE,
A PHOENIX.
ALL RIGHT. CRYPT
MUST BE THROUGH THERE.
OK.
THEA!
THANK YOU.
YEAH.
TALIA: "ALL BEINGS BURN,
BUT A PHOENIX RISES
FROM THE ASHES."
OK. I THINK WE
NEED TO USE
THE PHOENIX TILES
TO GET ACROSS.
ATHENA: AFTER THEM!
YOU HOLD THEM OFF.
I'LL GET TALIA.
-THEA!
-JUST TRUST ME.
THEA: TALIA?
YOU'RE TOO LATE.
AS HEIR TO THE DEMON,
I HAVE THE RIGHT
TO CHALLENGE YOU
TO COMBAT.
YOU WISH TO FIGHT ME?
VERY WELL. I ACCEPT.
I HOPE YOU PROVE
TO BE A WORTHY OPPONENT.
YOUR BROTHER
TRAINED YOU WELL.
PITY THE TOOLS
YOU LEARNED FROM HIM
HE LEARNED FROM ME.
LESS TALK,
MORE FIGHTING.
[RUMBLING]
YOU WERE A FOOL
TO THINK YOU COULD
DEFEAT ME.
ACTUALLY...
YOU'RE RIGHT
WHERE I WANT YOU.
UNH!
[GAGGING]
DO YOU YIELD?
[GROANING]
[GASPING] I YIELD.
[GASPS]
AHEM. WHAT'S IT SAY?
IT SAYS AL-FATIH
WAS VISITED BY A GOD
WHO POSSESSED THE POWER
TO SEE ALL THAT IS
AND ALL THAT WILL BE.
HE BELIEVED THAT
IF HE FAILED TO KEEP
THE BALANCE
BETWEEN GOOD AND EVIL
THIS GOD WOULD
BRING FORTH
THE END OF TIMES,
THE ANNIHILATION
OF ALL THINGS.
OLLIE, IF THAT'S TRUE,
THIS MEANS THAT...
IT MEANS MAR NOVU
IS NOT TRYING TO PREVENT
WHAT'S GOING TO HAPPEN
BECAUSE HE'S GONNA BE
WHAT CAUSES IT.
[FOOTSTEPS]
YOU'RE LEAVING?
TALIA: I HAVE
BETRAYED MY HONOR
AND THE SACRED
TRADITIONS
OF THE LEAGUE.
THE SWORD WAS DESTINED
TO BE YOURS,
DAUGHTER OF MERLYN.
I AM SORRY
FOR THE PAIN I'VE
CAUSED YOU BOTH.
WHAT ABOUT
YOUR STUDENTS?
I'VE RELEASED
THEM.
THEY WILL FOLLOW YOU
IF THAT IS WHAT
YOU WISH.
IT'S NOT.
YOU'RE THEIR TEACHER.
THEY NEED SOMEONE
TO FOLLOW.
IF I WAS MEANT
TO LEAD THEM,
I WOULD WIELD
AL-FATIH'S SWORD,
BUT YOU DO,
SO THE HONOR
AND THE BURDEN
ARE YOURS.
YEAH. HARD PASS.
IT IS YOUR DESTINY.
YEAH, BUT, SEE,
ABOUT THAT.
I DON'T REALLY BELIEVE
IN THE WHOLE FATE,
DESTINY THING.
WE CAN ALL MAKE
OUR OWN CHOICES.
MEANING?
MEANING I DON'T THINK
THE WORLD NEEDS
ANOTHER LEAGUE
OF ASSASSINS.
IT COULD USE LEAGUE
OF HEROES.
IT WOULDN'T BE
A ONE-WOMAN JOB.
YOU'D EXTEND ME
THAT HONOR
DESPITE
MY BETRAYALS?
YOU MADE A MISTAKE.
WE'VE ALL MADE MISTAKES.
NOT ONE BUT
TWO WOMEN TO WIELD
MY FATHER'S SWORD?
HE WOULD BE AGHAST.
HEH.
I ACCEPT.
NEW PHONE,
BETTER ENCRYPTION,
AND A ONE-WAY
TICKET HOME
VIA HONG KONG.
NO ONE WILL BE
EXPECTING THAT.
I CAN'T THANK YOU
ENOUGH FOR ALL
YOUR HELP.
I MEAN, WITHOUT
YOU TWO I'D...
JOHN: NO, NO.
IT'S THE LEAST WE
COULD HAVE DONE,
AND YOU WERE VERY BRAVE.
YOUR FATHER WOULD BE
PROUD OF YOU.
THANKS, MR. DIGGLES.
CALL ME DIG.
SANDRA: LET'S GO GET
OUR THINGS.
HEY. THEY'RE GONNA
BE OK.
YEAH...AND SO
ARE WE.
THE WORLD'S GONNA
KEEP COMING FOR US.
THERE'S NOTHING
I CAN DO TO STOP IT.
NEITHER CAN YOU,
BUT YOU WERE RIGHT.
WE JUST HOLD ON
TO EACH OTHER,
WE'LL BE FINE
LIKE SANDRA AND CONNOR.
WHAT? WHAT IS IT?
JOHNNY, PROMISE ME THAT
NO MATTER WHAT HAPPENS
YOU'LL ALWAYS REMEMBER
THE GOOD TIMES.
I WON'T HAVE TO
BECAUSE I'M NOT
GOING ANYWHERE,
AND NEITHER ARE YOU.
I LOVE YOU,
LYLA MICHAELS.
I LOVE YOU.
I LOVE YOU, TOO.
ALWAYS HAVE,
ALWAYS WILL.
I'M SORRY YOU DIDN'T GET
THE ANSWERS YOU WERE
LOOKING FOR.
GOT TO SEE YOU.
-HERE'S WHAT I DON'T GET.
-OK.
IF MAR NOVU CAUSES
WHATEVER'S GONNA HAPPEN,
WHY DOES HE BRING YOU IN
IN THE FIRST PLACE?
I DON'T KNOW.
LOOK. I JUST...
I KNOW THAT IF HE
ENDS UP BEING
ON THE WRONG SIDE
OF THIS...
I'M GONNA STOP HIM.
IF YOU'RE GONNA TAKE ON
A GOD, OLLIE,
YOU'RE GONNA NEED ALL
THE HELP YOU CAN GET.
PRETTY GOOD ON HELP
ACTUALLY.
I HAVE JOHN,
I HAVE LAUREL...
BELIEVE IT OR NOT.
SEEMS TO ME YOU HAVE
YOUR HANDS FULL
REBUILDING THE LEAGUE
OF ASSASSINS
INTO A LEAGUE OF HEROES.
YEAH.
I CAN'T BELIEVE I'M
SAYING GOOD-BYE
TO YOU AGAIN.
WELL, YOU'RE NOT.
THINK OF IT AS A...
"SEE YOU LATER,
AND PLEASE DON'T DIE."
ONE OF US IS GONNA HAVE
TO LET GO FIRST.
-SAME TIME?
-MM-HMM.
NO HOZEN THIS TIME?
UH, FELICITY GAVE
IT TO WILLIAM.
I'M GONNA MISS YOU.
EVERY DAY, I MISS YOU.
GOOD-BYE, SPEEDY.
BYE, OLLIE.
TONIGHT IS THE NIGHT THAT
WE HAVE ALL BEEN WAITING FOR,
THE NIGHT THAT WE DESTROY
THE UNIFICATION MOVEMENT.
THE CITY WILL BE OURS,
AND THERE IS NOTHING
ANYONE CAN DO TO STOP IT.
MIA: ACTUALLY, I THINK
THERE IS.
YOU JUST DON'T KNOW
WHEN TO QUIT.
[CANARY CRIES]
DAMN. WHAT AN ENTRANCE.
MIA!
[GRUNTING]
YOU KNOW, THE HUMAN BODY
HOLDS AN AVERAGE
OF 5 LITERS OF BLOOD.
LET'S SEE HOW MUCH
YOU HAVE, HUH?
ZOE: HYAH!
[GASPING]
ARE YOU OK?
THANKS.
[GASPS]
ZOE!
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLES]
MIA: ZOE.
JJ!
STAY WITH ME.
WE'RE GONNA GET YOU
OUT OF HERE.
TELL...TELL MY DAD...
JUST TELL...TELL HIM
THAT...
I'M SORRY
ABOUT EVERYTHING.
THAT I LOVE HIM.
HEY. HEY. YOU'RE GONNA
TELL HIM YOURSELF, OK?
YOU ARE BECAUSE WE ARE...
WE'RE GONNA GET YOU SAFE.
OK? I GOT YOU.
ZOE, I GOT YOU.
ZOE?
NO. NO, NO, NO, NO.
NO. ZOE.
[MIA CRYING
OVER COMMS]
CONNOR: AAH!
YOU DON'T HAVE THE GUTS,
DO YOU, HUH?
YOU'RE WRONG.
[BOTH GRUNTING]
WHAT IS THIS?
OLIVER?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
THAT'S A VERY GOOD
QUESTION.
DAD?
MAN: GREG, MOVE YOUR HEAD!