My name
was Oliver Queen.
For three years,
I worked to save my city.
But to save my sister,
I had to become someone else.
I had to become
something else.
Previously, on "Arrow"...
You can still
save her, Oliver!
Take your rightful place
as heir to the Demon.
Ra's al Ghul will bring
your sister back.
I fulfilled my end
of our arrangement.
I suggest you begin
to make peace with yours.
The only way that
I'm going to survive this
is if I know that
you're out there
living your life, happy.
Oliver Queen
is dead, and for now,
only the Arrow,
Al Sah-him, shall remain.
Heir to the Demon.
Oliver Queen
is alive only in the past.
He is forgotten.
Oliver Queen
is alive only in the past.
He is forgotten.
You are Al Sah-him.
You have made great progress
in three weeks.
Al Sah-him.
You no longer flinch
upon hearing your new name.
Oliver Queen is alive
only in the past.
He's forgotten.
Indeed. You are Al Sah-him.
You are Wareeth al Ghul.
Heir to the demon.
My lord.
I apologize for this
interruption.
We captured
this intruder.
Why, then, is he
still yet alive?
He is known
to Al Sah-him.
Oliver, what the hell
is going on?
Clearly he made another attempt
to free Al Sah-him.
Well, then it falls on Al Sah-him
to deal with him.
Oliver, they're lying to you.
I never made it home.
They've had me here
prisoner for weeks.
My oath of mercy
on your friends
was premised
by your fealty.
Prove it.
No, Oliver.
Listen to me--
they're lying to you.
We could still get out of here;
you and me working together.
There's still a chance.
Remove his chains.
Give him your sword,
Sarab.
I will not kill
an unarmed man.
That's the way this is?
You've been here
for a few weeks
and you forget
who you are.
Do you remember when
you brought me into your crusade,
I told you that I would
be here to help remind you
who Oliver was, if you ever became
something else.
I haven't given up
on that promise.
Fight.
The past three weeks,
you've been exposed
to a rare herb centuries old.
It causes one's conscience
to come to the forefront
of their mind
so it is the only
thing that they see.
The herb's effect
is different for everyone.
Some people see family
and loved ones.
Others encounter
trusted friends or teachers.
Who did you see?
Very well.
There is something else
I wish you to see. Come.
Where?
The past.
A place now home
only for the dead.
I had the vial
in my hand!
What's happening
is not your fault.
Shrieve is to blame,
this is his doing.
I can't get through.
Everyone's calling the police.
We're all inoculated,
remember?
I want to get back
to my son.
Have not
been back to this place
since I pledged myself
to the League.
What
happened here?
When I joined the League,
I was conscripted with another man.
Damien Darhk.
We would become
the prized agents of Ra's al Ghul.
We were his horsemen.
And he molded us into warriors
the likes the world
had never seen.
We were as brothers.
What happened
to him?
He believed himself worthy
of becoming heir to the Demon,
but I was the one chosen.
So you had
to kill him.
Yes.
But you see, I hesitated.
And with that hesitation,
he found an opportunity
to escape,
taking with him his loyalists and
water from the Lazarus pit.
And he has vexed me
ever since.
And you.
I don't follow.
Damien continues
the League's ways,
but through his own
organization filled
with a hive of agents
devoted to his own agenda.
Last year, he tried to purchase
Malcolm Merlyn's earthquake generator.
He gave Gholem Qadir
safe haven to Markovia.
And he hired Mark Shaw to steal
a secret file from A.R.G.U.S.
This was all
the work of one man?
The list goes on.
Many lives have been lost,
others endangered.
And all because I was slow
to swing a vengeful sword.
And I will not have my heir
haunted by the same mistake.
What is it you
wish me to do?
There is a rival who claims
to be heir to the Demon.
And you must eliminate
this threat from your reign.
And you must do so
without mercy.
♪ Arrow 3x21 ♪
Al Sah-Him
Original Air Date on April 29, 2015
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Did you hear?
Masks aren't wanted
in Starling no more.
Tell that to the woman
you mugged.
You underestimated
your opponent again.
I should have known
he had a knife.
He didn't have a knife.
What the hell?
He had two.
Shall we continue
your training?
I'm starving.
There's a diner near here
that serves the best
black and white milkshakes
in Starling City.
What is a black
and white milkshake?
I never understood
your country's need
to fry everything.
That's because everything tastes
better that way.
This is more oil than potato.
Dip it in
your milkshake.
I sense you're mocking me.
I'm serious.
Here. Dip it in
your milkshake.
I have to admit...
It's fun seeing you
like this.
Like what?
Like a normal
person.
I am a normal person.
I can't believe
you just said that.
Mmm.
That's actually not bad.
And the student
becomes the teacher.
You have a point.
For me, normal is a world
where only the strong survive.
One without simple pleasures.
Thank you, Laurel.
I was alone and adrift,
and you have
shown me kindness.
I'm only
returning the favor.
Isn't that what
you did for Sara?
There's
little comparison
between my current situation and Sara's
after her time with Oliver on Lian Yu.
What's wrong?
It's about Oliver.
There's something
that I haven't told you.
He's in Nanda Parbat.
I don't understand.
He's accepted your father's offer
to become the next Ra's.
You should have not
kept that from me.
I'm sorry,
it's just--
it's just that
you seemed so happy,
and after what
happened with your father, I...
And here comes the Cat-5 prong
into the Ethernet port!
Even if she knew what that was,
even if I knew what that was,
I think Sara's still a little young
for chicken cacciatore.
Well, my mom used
to feed me nachos from the bar
at the Grand  before I was
off the bottle,
and I turned out normal.
Ish.
John...
What's the house rule?
No Glocks
on the dinner table.
How'd it go
out there tonight?
Your Intel was spot-on.
Caught four Halcones
at the docks
trying to unload
a shipment of M16s.
Well, I'm especially proud that
you didn't get yourself killed.
That was my
favorite part, too.
If you're going to keep
going out into the field,
Do not say
"costume."
Ok.
Identity concealment.
Look, eventually we're going
to have to figure out
a new status quo,
a working one,
now that...
Ollie's gone.
How are you doing?
Having never been
resurrected before,
I don't really have anything
to compare it to.
I mean about Oliver.
Being gone.
I don't know.
Mornings are the worst.
I can't really...
leave the loft,
so it's nice to be able
to come here.
You are always welcome
in our home.
I just miss him.
The fact that he's gone
because of me--
He wouldn't want you
blaming yourself.
In the military,
they have a saying
for a soldier
that makes
the ultimate sacrifice.
Gone...
but never forgotten.
Gone, but never forgotten.
Liling's apartment
is just a few more blocks north.
Wallace said
there wasn't a cure.
It's United States
Army. Shrieve's men.
That's not a cure
they're giving those people!
It's the virus!
Shrieve is leaving
nothing to chance.
He wants to infect
as many people as possible.
Come on, we have
to stop him.
Hey! Get away from there!
Tatsu, the truck!
I had him!
What do we now?
Destroy it.
All of it.
I'm sorry I didn't tell you
about Oliver earlier.
That was your right to know.
I just--
things were going
so well for you.
You seemed happy,
and I didn't want to upset you,
but I still shouldn't
have kept it from you.
Were I so inclined,
I'd question why your first instinct
is to always keep
matters secret.
Even after doing so
cost you a relationship with your father.
But I have much
greater concerns.
What's going on?
You should go.
No.
I'm not leaving.
Friends don't do that
to one another.
Now that Oliver
has ascended to his position
as heir to the Demon,
he will come for me,
with as many men
as it takes to see me dead.
Tonight,
Nyssa al Ghul
faces justice
for her betrayal.
Wait a second!
Oliver wouldn't.
I don't see how.
I think what
she's trying to say
is that Oliver would never do anything
to hurt you, Felicity.
And the only reason why
he joined the League
is to protect
the people he loves.
Now what you need
to understand
is that Oliver Queen
is dead.
He's a memory.
Apparently, the League
has some of their recruits
undergo a process
of reprogramming.
Like brainwashing?
Oliver never said that he was
signing on for brainwashing.
The League's ways are shrouded
in ritual and ceremony.
Oliver would not even know
what's happening to him.
I don't care!
Oliver, he is stronger than that!
I did not come here to debate.
Laurel insisted that I bring
this news to you myself,
but I can see all I'm doing
is damaging your memory of him.
Perhaps it is better for you to not think
of what Oliver has become.
You can have that luxury.
Wait, where
are you going?
To face him,
and if necessary, my destiny.
I will not cower in the shadows
waiting for death.
Great. Now what
are we supposed to do?
Nothing. No offense,
but Nyssa is insane.
Oliver
is still Oliver.
Nobody knows the League
better than Nyssa.
And did you see the look on her face?
She was terrified.
I didn't even think
that was possible.
Even if Nyssa's
right about Oliver...
Which she isn't.
Getting between her
and the League isn't an option.
And since when
does Ra's daughter
become someone we stick
our necks out for, Laurel?
I know you're furious with Ra's
for what he's done to Oliver.
We all are.
But Nyssa, she saved
my sister's life.
She gave her a home.
She's a good person.
In spite of everything that
she grew up with.
And the last time
I checked,
protecting good people,
that is what we do.
Fine.
Nyssa does seem to have an idea
where we can find Oliver and the League.
Well, then I guess we shouldn't have
let Nyssa leave alone.
No, it's fine.
I just put
a tracking device
on her.
This isn't
my first day.
Everybody, get back!
Away from the truck!
No more virus.
We have to get back to Akio.
Come on.
Anything?
Nyssa
hasn't stopped moving.
But I'm still getting
a strong signal off the tracker.
Copy that.
Radio check every five minutes.
What?
If anything happens
with Nyssa,
let me handle it on my own.
Laurel, we're talking
about the League of Assassins!
I know that, I just--
Oliver. You were closer to him
than any two people I've ever known.
You should not have to--
What, fight him?
Kill him?
Laurel, it's not going
to come to that.
Look, I'm with Felicity.
There's nothing that
Ra's al Ghul can do
that can turn Oliver against
the people he loves.
Nice secret
headquarter upgrade.
Does Mr. Palmer know
you guys are in here?
Yes. He's
out of town.
And how did you
get in here?
My dad's a super villain
and you left
your doors unlocked.
Right.
I have been
distracted.
'Cause you and Mr. Diggle are trying
to save the city by yourselves?
Look, I've been thinking.
Um, maybe, rather than me
sitting at home,
alone, miserable,
maybe I could...
be out there helping you guys.
You seem like
you're shorthanded one,
and vigilante skills
run in my blood.
Thea, this might
actually
be the worst week ever
for this conversation.
What's going on?
I--I can't.
Felicity, I cannot be
handled right now.
It's possible--
and I stress possible--
that Oliver
is back in town
with the League.
I don't understand.
Why would Ollie
come back here?
They're after Nyssa.
Ollie would never--
Nyssa thinks
he's under some
sort of League mind voodoo.
But it's going
to be fine.
We're handling it.
You are a terrible liar.
That is true.
Do you know
where he is?
I mean, maybe
I could just talk to him.
Thea, I don't know
what doctor's orders are
for when someone gets
brought back from the dead,
but I am pretty sure getting into a fight
with the League of Assassins
goes against them.
I can get through
to him.
Please, Thea.
Oliver wouldn't want you
involved. He did what he did
so that you would stay
out of harm's way.
Yeah, well.
It sounds like
Ollie's not here anymore.
This is where my beloved spirit
departed this world.
Do you even remember Sara?
Or has my father already obliterated her
from your memory?
I'm here to bring you back
to Nanda Parbat.
To face justice?
If so, for what crime?
To face vengeance?
If so, for what offense?
You told me...
Vengeance
is justice.
And you bested me in battle.
That won't happen again.
Do it! If I would die,
I would have it on
the same ground as Sara.
Oh, my God.
We can't let you
hurt her, man.
Oliver!
You should not
have interfered.
Look, I am sorry,
but I have lost a sister,
a father, Oliver--
there is no way that
I was about to lose you, too.
You don't
understand.
You already have.
I was marked for
death the moment
Oliver accepted
my father's offer.
Laurel, these
past few weeks,
they've enlightened me.
To live a life outside of my
father's rule;
to be someone else,
even for just a little while,
brought me
great happiness.
But I am daughter
of the Demon.
Happiness is not something that was
ever meant for me.
I've known Oliver
my entire life.
We've been friends
since childhood.
But tonight,
I did not recognize him.
I told you...
He has been changed.
Well, if he can change,
then why can't you?
How's Nyssa?
She's with Laurel.
She's going to be ok.
How are you?
Same as you,
probably.
Neither one of us
believed Nyssa
when she said Oliver
had been turned.
I'm still not sure
I believe it.
I heard about
this kind of thing.
Guy gets captured
by the enemy.
Gets broken.
I just never imagined Oliver--
still can't imagine--
that Oliver would.
Strongest man I've ever
known, Felicity.
When Oliver stayed behind when
he agreed to join the League,
he never could have known that
this is what he was agreeing to.
The only way
that I've been able
to get out of bed
these past few weeks
is because I knew that
Oliver was still alive.
He is alive, Felicity.
We thought
that Oliver was
just giving up his life to Ra's.
But he gave up his soul.
There was doubt
you would return.
But not from me.
What happened?
Nyssa had friends.
I warned you not
to face her alone.
These friends
of Nyssa's--
were they
friends of yours?
They'll be protecting her now.
We need to draw her out.
Thank you for coming.
Suffice it to say, I was surprised
to get your call.
I need your help.
That couldn't have been easy
for you to say.
I need to know--
is Ollie back in town?
Is he going after Nyssa?
According
to my sources,
he intends
to eliminate her
as a threat to his
ascension to Ra's.
Well, I need to stop him.
His is Wareeth
al Ghul now, Thea.
Heir to the Demon.
He is my brother.
It's one thing to let him join the League
and run off to Nanda Parbat, but--
Another
to let him kill?
What did you think
he would be doing
in the League
of Assassins?
Felicity told me
that he's been brainwashed.
I know what it's like
to kill while under the influence
of someone else.
Your brother didn't sacrifice
everything for you
to go to war
with the League.
That's what Felicity said.
And she was right.
No.
I couldn't stop him
from trading his life
to save mine,
but this, this I can stop.
You are
a warrior, Thea.
Long before
I trained you.
You have always had an incredible
strength inside you,
and your brother
knows that, too.
Now...
What do you
need from me?
Are you sure this is ok?
Yeah. With Oliver
and the League running around,
it's best we stay
close. Especially if something...
John?
Something's wrong. Lyla?
Where's Lyla?
John.
Oliver?
First, let me assure you that
no harm will come to Lyla,
if you do exactly as I say.
Bring Nyssa to the warehouse
at Fullerton and Halstead,
and I'll let your wife go.
Oliver, I swear, if you
do anything to Lyla...
You have 30 minutes.
Laurel!
What happened?
Oliver and his new
friends took Lyla.
What?! Where's Sara,
is she ok?
Yeah, she's with
John's neighbor.
What's wrong with you?!
Hey, it is not
Nyssa's fault!
No, just her people.
You call yourself
warriors.
You claim to have honor.
Well, if you knew
the meaning of the word,
you would know
there are some lines you do not cross!
Ok, John, back off.
You back off!
I am truly sorry.
I never meant for any harm
to come to you or your family.
Yeah, Nyssa?
Then prove it.
Hand yourself over
to the League.
What?!
We're just going to
negotiate with him now?
Are we just going to give in?
Turn over an innocent person?
She's not innocent!
She's the daughter
of the Demon.
She's killed
hundreds of people.
Enough!
The only thing that matters is
getting Lyla back.
I don't care how we do it.
Yes, you do.
Trading one person's
life for another--
we're supposed to be
better than that.
It's all right.
Of course you should
exchange me for your beloved.
I won't see an innocent life
taken for mine.
No.
I'm not going to let you
commit suicide.
Don't you remember
what you said?
These past few weeks have been
some of the best of your life.
I remember.
And I remember telling you that
happiness is something denied to me.
Where's the exchange
take place?
No. There has
to be another way.
Another way to save Lyla without
turning Nyssa over to the League.
And if there isn't, even if you get Lyla
back safe and sound,
Oliver won't be
the only one who lost his soul.
What happened
to you?
Johnny told me,
but how could you become this?
Quiet.
It'll be over soon.
No. I genuinely
want to know.
How could the man who stood up
at my wedding do this?
How could the man who's
been like a brother to--
Quiet!
You know...
When John's brother died,
a part of him died, too.
His guilt and the emptiness
from the loss
outweighed everything.
I tried my hardest
to help him,
but no one seemed to be
able to comfort him or fill that void.
Until he met you.
You gave him hope
and purpose again.
It's time.
Akio!
Mother!
Liling's sick.
It's going
to be ok.
Akio. Hao Ba.
We have to leave Hong Kong.
Shrieve
and his men--
Have enough to worry about!
Tatsu's right.
The chaos
will give us cover.
Could be our only chance.
They're here.
Search them.
Where's my wife?
Where's my wife?!
You son of a bitch.
Whatever Ra's
did to you...
Don't you dare touch me.
Oliver, this isn't you.
Look at me.
I know you're still
in there somewhere.
Bind her.
You're free to go.
Johnny!
It's ok, I'm here.
I thought they were
going for Sara.
Everything's fine,
Sara's fine.
I told Felicity
this is just like Jakarta.
Kneel before the true
heir to the Demon.
I kneel before no one.
Laurel!
Nyssa!
Aaah!
You're still Oliver.
I don't care
if the hood is black or green.
You're still you!
Get away from him.
Get away from him,
or the next one goes in your eye.
Lyla's got Sara.
They're headed out of town until
we can get things straightened out.
There is no straightening
this out.
I don't know, Felicity.
I can't see past tomorrow right now.
They're going
to kill Nyssa.
Oliver or her father,
they're going to kill her.
I'm sorry, Laurel.
It's not fair.
No. No, it's not.
I'll ask it to ask it--
there is no way
I'm getting him back.
He's gone,
Felicity.
No one wants
to believe that less than me.
But he's gone.
There's only one thing
left of him now.
And what's that?
Us.
Gone, but never forgotten.
There are no more
threats to my reign.
Your fealty continues
to impress me, Al Sah-him.
You truly are
Wareeth al Ghul.
And yet my daughter
still does not approve of my choice.
Fortunately, what I require from you
is not your approval.
Did you search her?
It does not appear
to be on her person.
Bring me her weapons.
You know, as a young child,
Nyssa displayed
the panache of a thief.
Always stealing
extra atayef at her meals
and then stowing them away
in her quarters.
She would grow to learn
that there is nothing
she can hide from me.
Her exploits of late...
seem to have
clouded that memory.
I will remember you
as the warrior you once were
and not as this shell
that stands before me.
All my life, I've lived
in fear of you.
But now, as I stand before
you ready to leave this earth,
I want you to know--
I am not afraid.
Do what needs to be
done, my heir.
And take with it
the satisfaction
that your reign
will be unchallenged.
I can see now,
you do not require
a culling to solidify
your reign.
You have broken
your rival, Al Sah-him.
Something I was
unable to do as an heir.
Spilling her blood now
would only serve as gluttony.
Now, perhaps...
her blood could be
of another purpose.
As a means to unite
our families.
You as husband...
and you as wife.
I would rather die than
become his betrothed.
Well, your wishes
were no longer my concern
from the moment
you betrayed me.
So you will marry Al Sah-him.
And you will become
bride of the Demon.
Come on,
come on, come on!
We need a vehicle.
Oliver!
Let's get out of this place.
It's ok.
You're safe now.
Thea?
The door was open.
Sorry to interrupt
your staring into nothingness.
He should have let me die.
That was never
an option.
That's why
I love him.
I didn't know...
about you and my brother.
Yeah, well...
It was complicated.
But I did love him.
Despite everything,
I still do.
I do, too.
How...
is that even possible?
After what he's become.
I don't know.
But I think John's right;
I think we have
to remember
the best parts of him,
and we have
to move on.
Are you trying
to convince me
or yourself?
Both of us.
I don't know how,
but we have to go on living.
That's what
Oliver...
Ollie would want
for you--
to move on.
To live.
To be with the one that you love
while you still can.
Roy is gone, so...
You've had a lot
on your plate,
and I've been trying to think
of the right time
to tell you this...
Roy's alive.
We faked his death.
It's a long story,
as most fake death stories are.
We were going to
tell you, I promise.
But then you were busy
being mostly dead,
and then Oliver
signed on to become Darth Oliver.
I don't--
He's starting...
A new life.
One that hopefully
includes you.
If you want it.
When my daughter
left Nanda Parbat,
she absconded something critical
to both our futures.
Do you recall
the village I showed you?
The one where only
the dead remain?
It was your home.
Was.
And I was obligated to
unleash death upon it.
It has been this way
ever since there has been a Ra's.
You see, it is
the final act of ascension,
the transformation
to Demon's Head.
The erasure of one's former
life, former home.
Now, my predecessor,
he wiped away
Alexandria, Egypt,
with cholera
in 1609.
Today you will
do the same.
Do you recognize this?
The Alpha and Omega
bioweapon.
Beginning
and the end.
Nyssa stole this
to prevent my heir from doing that
which you will
do today.
You will unleash this
on Starling City.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Greg!
Move your head.