[GRUNTING]
SARA:
Dinah Laurel Lance.
Selfish bitch.
You're not a hero.
You're a liar. A fraud.
And an addict.
Sara.
Sara, please. Please. I'm your sister.
Then why are you trying
to take my place? Unh!
What the hell do you think you're doing?
Your job, apparently.
-I told you that I didn't want you out here.
-And I told you that it wasn't your call to make.
Think for a second about what it would do to
your father if something happened to you.
What you're doing is selfish.
Fighting for your city isn't selfish.
It's what a hero would do.
You're not a hero.
Maybe it's best if we stay
out of each other's way.
How'd it go out there?
OLIVER:
We ran into Laurel. Again.
Diggle, how could you sign off
on her doing this?
You might not notice, but she's not lobbying
for anyone's permission.
-She has yours.
-Well, not at first.
-But she can definitely hold her own out there.
-You have a visitor.
Or as I like to call him, your new BFF.
-I see things are running smoothly down here.
-What do you want?
It's been a week since your return.
I thought it past time we spoke.
Nanda Parbat is remote.
But I wouldn't delude yourself
into thinking that Ra's al Ghul missed...
...your televised return to Starling City.
Your point, Malcolm?
We can't merely wait
for Ra's to mobilize his forces.
It's time to bring Thea into the fold.
She's not ready to know my secret.
I disagree.
But in any case...
...if we are to protect Thea...
...and to defeat the League...
...the three of us need to join forces.
I don't see how we can do that
if she is to believe...
...that her brother is a reformed playboy
and failed businessman.
I told you before, if Thea finds out
you've been lying to her all this time...
...you will lose her. Forever.
OLIVER:
How's Tatsu?
She'll be better when we're far away
from here. Your bow.
Want anything else, take it quickly.
We're leaving in five minutes.
-We're not coming back.
-We can't just run.
Waller knows I tried to steal the virus
to get Tatsu back.
Even if she didn't...
...Chien Na Wei knows where we live.
We have to go.
-Look, Maseo...
-If you stay, Waller will torture you to find us.
Contact your family, contact the press.
Once the world knows Oliver Queen
is still alive...
...it will limit A.R.G.U.S.' options.
Make it more difficult for Waller
to assassinate you.
That's reassuring.
What are you gonna do?
I'll take Akio and Tatsu on the ferry
to Shanghai.
From there, we will disappear.
You saved us.
Now save yourself.
[CROWD CLAMORING]
MAN 1:
Mr. Zytle. Vertigo. Mr. Zytle.
-How many have your drug killed?
WOMAN: How many have you killed?
MAN 2:
Reaction to sentencing, Mr. Zytle?
The Roman governor, Porcius Festus,
maintained that the accused...
...has the right to face their accuser.
Now, where is my accuser?
I speak, of course, of the Arrow.
Excuse me, Mr. Zytle
has no further comments.
ADA Laurel Lance. Take him to the van.
Thank you.
[CROWD CHATTERING]
Stay back. Stay back!
[GUNSHOTS AND CROWD SCREAMING]
Where's Zytle?
CHASE:
Hey.
So you still haven't told me,
what did you think of my set last night?
Fan girls on Vine called it "epically epic."
More like "epically profitable."
CHASE: It's kind of hot when
you talk business and numbers.
Chase. God, if you ever really
wanna kiss me again...
...you're gonna have to work on your game.
Later, princess.
Ollie.
Hey, Speedy.
THEA:
I'm so happy you're home.
What?
I have to show you something.
-Where are we going?
-The basement.
I thought that you said that it was flooded.
[BEEPING]
I lied.
Ollie, what's going on?
You're kind of making me nervous.
I know that this isn't gonna mean much...
...and I've given you no reason to believe me
when I say it...
...but I lied all of this time to protect you.
You're...
You're him.
Yeah.
That night with the Hoods...
...and the woman in black, that...
That was Ra's al Ghul's daughter.
That was you.
All those times I got so mad at you
for being a flake...
...or telling me something I knew
that had to be a lie...
...you were saving someone's life.
Thank you.
THEA: You know how many times I've wished
that I could thank the Arrow...
...for things he's done for this city?
Probably as many times as I've wished
we could have this conversation.
Did Mom know?
The night that she died, she told me...
...that she'd known for a while.
I was worried that you'd be angry.
Only because you broke my window.
Although I did kind of kick your ass.
You didn't.
-But you did have a good teacher.
-You were looking for Malcolm that night.
We know about each other.
Wait, Malcolm knows that you're the Arrow?
I am amazed that he didn't tell you.
And why did you tell me?
Why now?
[DOOR OPENING]
Because Ra's al Ghul is coming for us.
All of us.
And the only chance that we have to survive
is to work together.
To trust each other.
He's right.
THEA:
No.
No. No, he's not.
I turned my back on everyone I know.
Including my own brother.
Because you told me there was nobody
I could trust.
I was only trying to protect you.
By driving a wedge between me and Ollie?
You manipulated me.
-Thea.
-Let her go.
[PHONE RINGING]
Yeah.
[PHONE LINE RINGING]
[RECORDING] You've reached Moira Queen.
Please leave a message.
Mom, it's me.
I'm alive. I'm... I'm in Hong Kong.
I know it sounds crazy...
...but I'm alive, I'm in Hong Kong,
and I need your help.
I want you to call Ned Foster, you tell him
to issue a press release. Tell everyone.
You tell Thea.
I'm coming home. I love you...
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLING
AND OLIVER GRUNTING]
OLIVER:
What do we know?
Apparently the federal marshal guarding
Werner Zytle just started shooting...
...while Zytle waltzed off in the panic.
This is my favorite part.
It's pretty convenient. Guy decides to wig out
and Zytle takes advantage.
It's planned.
Those are the effects of his Vertigo.
Zytle was in a full set of restraints.
-How did he manage to dose a federal agent?
-He didn't. One of the reporters did.
What's wrong?
Was my form off?
She's right. About the reporter.
-We need a name...
-And address on our clumsy reporter. I'm on it.
OLIVER:
What do you think you're doing?
-I'm coming with you.
-You're not.
I just gave you your only lead.
Talk to you for a second? Alone?
I know what you're gonna say. But I risked
my life for this city while you were gone.
-That should earn me respect.
-This isn't about respect.
And it's not about you risking your life.
I understand that you miss Sara.
And I understand that when you go out there
like this...
...all of that pain goes away.
-It's the only time it ever does.
-That relief isn't real.
It's a drug.
-If you're implying...
-You are an addict.
Just like with booze and pills,
that high you're chasing every night...
-...is endangering your life.
-Go to hell, Oliver.
You don't get to play that card with me.
Ever.
And if there is anyone who's using adrenaline
to hide the pain of real feelings and real life...
...it's you.
ROY: Oliver. Felicity tracked down
the reporter's work address.
ARROW:
Anthony Walker. Where's Werner Zytle?
-He's not... He's not here.
-You helped him escape today.
Zytle threatened my wife.
Said he could get to her,
that he'd kill her if I didn't do this.
Do what?
Kill you.
-I'm so sorry.
ARROW: Anthony.
Give me the detonator.
He'll kill my wife.
We can protect her.
Promise.
Now, hand me the detonator.
God forgive me.
[BOMB BEEPING]
I will weep for thee.
[PHONE BEEPING]
THEA:
Ollie?
I'm sorry. Did I wake you?
THEA:
Can't sleep.
Apparently insomnia is a common side effect
of finding out your brother's a vigilante.
OLIVER:
Heh. Right.
You smell like smoke.
-Korean barbeque?
-C4.
Yeah.
Nice that we can tell each other
this stuff now.
OLIVER:
It is, actually.
You always had the lamest excuses.
Lame excuses are sort of
an occupational hazard.
What was tonight's hazard?
Roy and I were looking for the man
that escaped from the courthouse earlier today.
We found a bomb instead.
Yeah, I don't know how you do it.
Just risk your life out there
for people every night.
It's my job.
It is my job...
...to keep the people of this city safe.
And that includes you too, Speedy.
Listen to me.
I'm always gonna hate Malcolm Merlyn.
But right now, he is a necessary evil.
-We can take care of ourselves...
-Not against Ra's al Ghul.
You have to trust me on this.
I do.
But I don't trust him.
I can't.
And I won't.
WALLER:
Ten minutes.
I'm impressed.
I know Special Forces
who can't last longer than three.
Eventually, though, everybody breaks.
Tell me where the Yamashiros are
and it will stop.
My family's gonna be looking for me.
Everyone is gonna be looking for me.
Because your mother issued
a press release?
We erased your message
before she could hear a word of it.
Be glad.
If she had heard it,
your mother would be dead right now.
You would never risk the exposure.
WALLER:
You're right.
Your mother's too public a figure.
But your sister on the other hand...
What's her name?
Thea?
Did you know she's developed something
of a substance abuse problem...
...since you've been gone?
I guess the strain of losing two family members
must have been too much for her to bear.
One day, someone may just find her
in the back of a car...
...dead with a needle in her arm.
Poor Speedy.
You stay away from my sister.
I will. If you answer one question.
Where are the Yamashiros?
The ferry to Shanghai.
LANCE:
Knock, knock.
Hey.
You know, half the department is still talking
about the way you clocked that marshal.
Those boxing lessons look like
they're paying off.
Yeah, I guess so.
Are those the cargo manifests
for the whole city?
Yeah. Although, I gotta ask.
What do you need these for?
Just a RICO case that I'm second chairing.
Right.
-Dad.
-Yeah. Sorry, I just...
Have you heard from Sara lately?
No. Why?
I ran into her a few weeks back.
And something just felt a little off.
Then I ran into that friend of hers.
You know the one with the, uh...
The boy hair?
-Sin.
-Yeah, Sin. That's it.
She said something strange.
She said that the woman in black
isn't Sara.
-That doesn't make any sense.
-No.
I mean, look, I just wanna talk to her,
you know? Sara or not.
But look, don't worry.
I said I'd start taking it easy, I meant it.
I'll get out of your hair.
You know, I've been wondering.
How do you decide between the red hoodie
and the one with the mask?
I'm glad you know.
I felt pretty lame not recognizing my own
brother just because he's wearing a hood.
I can't believe you knew before I did.
He saved my life, Thea.
He saved a lot of people's lives.
-He thinks we need Merlyn's help.
-Hm.
And what do you think?
I think I wanna get as far away
from Malcolm Merlyn as I possibly can.
Well, there's your answer right there.
OLIVER:
Hey.
Sorry. May I borrow him for a second?
Apparently he's been more yours
than mine lately, so...
What happened?
One of our trackers sent a signal
from the docks.
Except we don't have any tracking devices
in the field.
Unless we do.
It's Laurel.
-You tagged Laurel with a tracer?
-If she's gonna be reckless...
-...I need to know what she's doing.
-She's definitely doing something.
Just not exactly sure how reckless it is.
I ran the manifest on these shipping
containers you see here.
One of these leads back
to Zytle's old supplier.
-Looks like Vertigo's back in business.
-She's gonna get herself killed.
Suit up.
MAN 1:
Hey! Unh!
MAN 2:
Come on.
ZYTLE:
Wonderful seeing you again.
Ooh, I fancy the new outfit.
[GRUNTING]
Feeling my Vertigo, dear?
Wonderful to...
Dinah Laurel Lance.
Selfish bitch.
You're not a hero.
You're a liar.
A fraud.
And an addict.
[GRUNTING]
Sara.
Sara, please. Please. I'm your sister.
Then why are you trying to take my place?
ARROW:
Get away from her.
ZYTLE:
You should be dead.
I salute your persistence.
LAUREL:
Help me.
Help... Help me.
Help me. Help me.
OLIVER:
We need an IV.
Watch her head.
FELICITY:
It's gonna be okay.
-Why did I have to die?
-Sara.
If you wanted to be me, you could have.
I didn't have to die.
I am so sorry.
I'm so sorry, Sara. I'm so...
[GRUNTING]
THEA:
Ollie.
I'm sorry. I just wanted to talk.
Thea, go back upstairs.
-Now!
-Hey. Don't talk to her like that.
You don't have the right to kick her out.
I'm not.
-I'm protecting her.
-By telling her what to do?
Work with Malcolm Merlyn,
let him get his hooks deeper?
-Enough. She's my sister.
-She makes her own choices, Oliver.
It's okay. We can talk later. I just...
Just... is Laurel okay?
Is she a part of this too?
She's gonna be fine.
I promise. Just...
Please go back upstairs.
What the hell was that?
You're the only person
who can stand up for Thea?
I'm trying to figure out why
you're standing up to me.
All right,
maybe we just need to throttle back.
No. We need this. Oliver, you were gone.
Dead. At least we thought you were.
And we had to go on with our lives.
And doing that...
-...meant not doing things your way.
-Fine.
-I'm back now.
-That doesn't mean that we can go back.
And you do not have the right to come back
here and question everyone's choices.
Just let me know if there's any change
in her condition.
Hey. How's it going?
What's that for?
My life has been really complicated lately,
so I just need something simple.
This seat taken?
It's a free country.
Apparently.
The first time that we went after Zytle...
...I told you that this was my crusade.
-Doesn't seem to be the case anymore.
-You're right. It isn't.
-You know, I get that I was gone...
-No, you weren't gone. You were dead.
And all of us, including me,
we were ready to hang it up.
Why didn't you?
Because we realized we weren't just fighting
for you, we were fighting for ourselves too.
That includes Roy.
And yes, that includes Laurel.
She's not a soldier.
-Neither were you.
-It's not the same thing and you know that.
What I know, Oliver,
is that you started something.
Something strong enough
to live on past you.
Question is...
...can you live with what it's become?
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
Oliver, are you all right?
I told them you were on the ferry.
I'm sorry.
-They tortured you.
-I sold you out.
No, you didn't.
Because we were never going to Shanghai.
I lied. A precaution just in case
you were captured.
Then how'd they find you?
They didn't.
When I found out you'd been taken,
I came back.
You're an idiot.
Maybe. But I will not let you face
Waller alone for my actions.
Now we're both gonna get tortured.
Or worse.
Great plan.
I must speak with Agent Waller.
OLIVER:
Hey! Why'd you...?
FELICITY:
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hey.
Hey, hey.
-Hey.
-How are you feeling?
When Zytle hit me with Vertigo, I...
I saw Sara.
She was alive.
And she was calling me a fraud.
I was crazy to think that I was fit
to wear Sara's jacket.
So much as follow in her footsteps.
You're right.
I hope I'm not out of line here...
...but I think Sara wore her mask
just as much to hide her demons...
...as she did to help people.
And I don't see that with you.
You have a light inside of you
that Sara never had.
So maybe you should stop trying to be Sara.
And just be yourself.
Thank you.
[COMPUTER BEEPING]
What's that?
One of the chemical drums Zytle stole
tonight sent out a GPS signal.
[BEEPING]
Why?
Because he just opened it.
I dig your place.
I'm sorry I interrupted the tour.
Pretty sure you saw everything
you needed to.
-You want a drink?
-Sure.
This was nice.
I almost took it personally
when you said I was simple.
Well, I never said that you were simple.
What?
Nothing, it...
It's just something my father once said.
We were sitting in this little taberna
in Corto Maltese...
...drinking this amazing Carménère...
...and he said that for centuries...
...noblemen had been using
the rich aroma of red wine...
...to cover up a very different scent.
Cyanide.
Tell me who you are
and what you think you're doing here.
Serving my master, Ra's al Ghul.
-Please.
-Don't struggle.
I can do this so you won't feel a thing.
Get away from her.
DARK ARCHER: If you beg forgiveness for trying
to harm my daughter, I'll grant you a quick death.
I'd never give you the satisfaction, Al Sa-Her.
DARK ARCHER: You're unarmed
and you have nowhere to run.
But there's someplace I can go
where you won't dare to follow.
[CHASE GRUNTS]
Daggett Pharmaceuticals. 5th and Kingsley.
Looks like Zytle found a place to change
those chemicals into Vertigo.
And he's got hostages.
-Where's Roy?
-I can't reach him.
[BLEEPING]
Laurel.
Oliver.
There isn't anything that you can say to me
that I don't already know.
Actually, there is.
I must once again thank you...
...for letting us use your laboratory
this evening.
And my sincerest apologies
to your colleague here...
...but mistakes will not be tolerated.
Werner Zytle.
-This ends now.
-As you wish.
May I suggest a grand finale?
Chlorine trifluoride.
Oliver, I'm registering an enormous spike
in thermal activity.
-The whole place is gonna blow.
FELICITY: You have to get out of there.
Not yet.
Go. Run! Now!
Unh!
I'm surprised.
Usually women don't return
for a second go with me.
-Hi, sis.
-You're not her.
You're not real.
Oh, I'm quite real.
You lied to me, Laurel!
Straight to my face! My own daughter!
Sara was my daughter.
I deserved to know. I had a right.
To grieve! To mourn!
And who do you think you are
to take that away from me, huh?
Who do you think you are?
-I'm sorry.
-I know you are.
She said she's sorry,
but she would do it again.
You keep my own daughter's death a secret
because you think I'm too weak for the truth?
You think you can wear my mask?
You think you can be me?
No.
And I'm done trying to be.
[LAUREL GRUNTING]
FELICITY:
Oliver, are you there?
-It's over.
-No, it's not.
You have to get home.
It's Thea.
MAN:
Okay, all good.
-Hey.
-Is everything okay?
Oh, yeah, just the usual insurance policy
search and seizure.
Seems like I'm a high-risk case.
Wonder what gave them that idea.
What's the matter? You okay?
Um...
There's, um...
There's something that I have to tell you.
And I didn't tell you...
I didn't tell you before
because I was worried about your health.
But I realized...
...that you deserve to know.
I already know it.
Sara's off God knows where, and yet there's
another blond in a mask running around...
...tuning up the bad guys,
and it's you, isn't it?
Sweetheart, come on. It's all right. It's okay.
It's okay, honey.
I mean, look, I am pissed as hell,
but, you know, we'll figure it out.
-We figure out everything.
-No, no. No, Daddy, that...
That isn't what I was gonna tell you.
What I was gonna tell you...
...is about Sara.
No.
Dad.
-No.
-Dad.
Not again.
-Daddy.
-Not my baby. Not again.
Sweetheart.
[BOTH SOBBING]
I can't do this.
OLIVER:
Thea?
It's okay. You're okay.
I thought that I was stronger.
I thought that I could keep myself safe.
-Who was he?
-One of Ra's' agents.
Roy...
...can you give us a minute?
I really hope you're not expecting
a "thank you."
No parent needs gratitude
for saving their child.
I didn't ask to be a part of this.
I didn't ask for any of this.
Maybe you were right.
Maybe we can't do this without him.
But I am never gonna forget
the things you've done.
-Or the person that you are.
-Understood.
But before we can begin...
...there's something that only the two
of you can do.
Ra's al Ghul preys upon the fears
of his enemies.
Conquer your own fear...
...and you eliminate that critical advantage.
For you...
...there is only one place on earth
uniquely suited...
...to doing that.
FELICITY:
So you're leaving again?
She's got a point, man. You just got back.
It's just for a few days.
Ordinarily, I wouldn't do this.
But it's for Thea.
And if you've shown me anything,
it's that this city...
...is more than safe in your hands.
All of your hands.
Thank you.
Ollie told you we're heading out for a bit?
You cool with it all?
After the whole Chase thing,
I think it's gonna be a little while...
...before I'm cool with anything.
What was that for?
Take your pick.
Saving my life or standing up to Oliver
about Malcolm.
I should get going.
Come on, Speedy, we have four more miles
to make before nightfall.
THEA:
Ugh. God.
I get that Malcolm wants to whip us into shape
so we can face the League...
...but don't you think
this is a little bit excessive?
[THEA PANTING]
We've been here for two hours.
Are you complaining already?
I started thinking it after the first 10 minutes.
Well, give it time.
Eventually, this place will feel like home.
It does not look like home.
It was for me. For other people,
this is purgatory.
WALLER: You're not dead,
if that's what you're wondering.
Once again, you have the good fortune
of being uniquely qualified to help me.
Me?
Why?
Chien Na Wei has left Hong Kong.
We've tracked her here.
Here?
Where are we?
WALLER:
Welcome home, Mr. Queen.