My name is Oliver Queen.
For 5 years,
I was stranded on an island
with only one goal--
Survive.
Oliver Queen is alive.
Now I will fulfill
my father's dying wish--
to use the list
of names he left me
and bring down those
who are poisoning my city.
To do this, I must
become someone else.
I must become
something else.
Previously on "Arrow"...
Hi, I'm looking for Detective Hall.
I was told he works in Vice.
Oliver?
McKenna Hall.
I live to surprise.
I want to find Walter.
My stepfather.
I'll help you rescue
him, but that's it.
That's my offer.
Ok.
Jerry.
Jerry, you ok?
Yeah.
You look a little
peaked, man.
I'm fine. It's, uh,
Mrs. Hill wants us
to move the Sherwood
into the vault.
Now? It's mid-day.
I know. She says
it's a security threat.
It's, uh, all
the robberies lately.
Right, right.
Take this thing
off me, all right?
I got it
like you asked.
Here.
Take it off me!
Were--were you--
were you bluffing? I mean,
would the thing have detonated?
Violently. Don't worry, though.
You did exactly as I asked,
so it's just
unconsciousness for you.
Unconscious?
You might want
to take it easy
if you plan on taking
someone off that list tonight.
This is me taking it easy.
So who's our
lucky guy tonight?
Ken Williams. His pyramid scheme
stole millions.
People didn't just lose their homes.
Their lives are ruined.
Why don't you call it
in early tonight,
I'm not expecting
much trouble.
Felicity!
Did you just...
Computer override
your lock.
Maybe a little.
What are you doing?
I pulled up some information
on Mr. Williams.
Did you know he's a widowed father
of a 10-year-old boy?
I told you.
I'm only in this
to help Walter.
Not to be an accessory
to orphaning little kids.
I'm just giving him a warning.
Has it ever occurred to you
you could do some
real good in the city?
Beyond just recovering
people's stock portfolios
and their saving accounts.
You're not the only
one who knows how
to reboot my system.
I made a mistake.
Getting in my way?
I don't disagree.
No.
Signing on with you.
Even provisionally.
Hey. Hey.
Drink.
That tastes like dirt.
You got to stay
hydrated, ok?
Hydration is not my problem.
My problem is getting
a bullet dug out of
my arm with a dull blade.
Let me take a look.
It's infected.
Go figure.
Yeah, uh...
I got to stop that
before it spreads.
When you swing past the
drugstore for those antibiotics,
you want to get me
a copy of "Maxim",
or maybe a "Sports Illustrated"?
Yao Fei had these super
herbs back in the cave
that'd heal anything.
I'm going
to go get them.
You're not going to last
an hour out there.
Well, I guess you
better hope I get back
in 45 minutes, then.
♪ Arrow 1x15 ♪
Dodger
Original Air Date on February 20, 2013
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Ahh.
Thank you for coming.
It is so good
to see you, Frank.
Ohh.
It's been far too long.
Yes. My interests in China
have kept me away
more than I'd like.
But with The Undertaking
approaching,
I thought a return
to Starling City was in order.
Hmm.
Actually, Frank,
it's The Undertaking
that I wanted
to talk to you about.
I want to get out.
Is this because of what
happened to Walter?
With Walter,
with Robert.
Last week the Vigilante
nearly made my children orphans.
I've reached my limit, Frank.
That's, uh,
a lot to confide in me, Moira.
Robert did.
I know
he reached out to you;
whether I was supposed
to know it or not.
He had misgivings.
He sought you out because
he knew you did, too.
But then he was murdered.
And that should be
a cautionary tale for both of us.
Yes, I know. And I've
gone along with this
for as long
as I can stomach it.
We started this
to fix the Glades,
Frank.
To cure the city,
not lay it to waste.
You got into this
because of what happened
to your daughter.
Frank...
What would Amanda
want you to do?
Well.
Maybe we should
come back later.
No, maybe we should wait,
Oliver. This is really serious.
What if her next attack
of conscience
leads her right to the police?
Oh, she won't
say anything.
I know I had to make
the same calculation
when you found out
about me.
Mm-hmm. And what would you
have done if you were wrong,
and I decided to make
a call to detective Lance?
I would have put
an arrow in you.
Ha!
Really--really--you really
would have done that, really?
Hmm.
I had a bet
going with myself
on how quickly
you two would visit.
Tell me not
to reveal your secret.
Looks like I won.
Actually, Felicity,
I was hoping
that I could get you
to change your mind.
I was worked up on
adrenaline last night,
and I didn't exactly put
my best foot forward.
I was hoping you'd
give me the opportunity
to do that now.
How about you start
with Ken Williams?
Did he also get to enjoy
your adrenaline last night?
No, he returned
the money that he stole
just in time
to put his son to bed.
Like I said, Felicity,
just a warning...
At this time,
we'd like to remind the public
that we are coordinating
our efforts with Interpol
as the Dodger operates
primarily in Europe,
and they have advised us
to warn the public
that he is to be considered
armed and extremely dangerous.
You know, I heard about this guy.
They call him the Dodger
because he avoids
getting his hands dirty.
He uses hostages to do
his stealing for him.
How?
Puts a bomb collar
around their necks.
Last year, a guy
in Madrid didn't steal
what the Dodger told him to,
and it took his head off.
Literally.
And now the psycho's
in Starling City?
It's too bad his name's
not in your notebook.
You know, not all the people
that I target are on the list.
Every once in a while,
I make an exception.
A hostage-taking jewel
thief, for example.
So, why don't you help us
take him down?
He's late.
Never.
I maintain a Swiss account
for financial transactions.
Here's the number.
Thanks.
I'll wire you the money.
Assuming I don't
misplace the numbers.
My bookkeeping method
is a little sloppy.
Really?
Clearly you're under
the impression
that you can have the
Sherwood Ruby for a steal.
Well, you're new
here in town.
We're not as refined
in Starling City.
I'm getting that impression.
Don't worry.
Your men are merely unconscious.
In about 17 minutes,
they'll wake up
with the ability
to tell every other
fence in this town.
That I am not to be trifled with.
What about me?
I don't know.
What about you, indeed.
So to catch this guy,
we need to either
figure out where he is,
or where he's going to be.
Is this really how you guys figure
out how to get your target?
Over burgers and shakes?
Sorry it took me so long.
I'm waiting on a bunch
of particularly
rowdy customers.
You need me to handle that?
I appreciate it,
but I'm a pro by now.
I'll be here if you need me.
Girlfriend?
No, it's my sister in law.
Hmm.
Sort of.
Carly was married
to Dig's brother.
And he passed away.
Hmm. Well,
looks like
she's hot for you.
Ah. Can we get back
to crime fighting, please?
Actually, Dig,
I was thinking,
you probably should
ask her out.
Really?
Mm-hmm.
I'll do that just five minutes
after you ask out McKenna.
Ooh, the detective
on the Dodger case.
You have a thing for her?
Yes.
I don't see you
asking Carly out.
Felicity, this guy,
he's targeting a very specific
type of jewel.
We figure out why,
and that'll give us
the how to catch him.
I have an idea.
Mm-hmm?
Your crush object with a badge
said they were
working with Interpol.
Yeah.
Why don't I work
a couple of little tech,
you distract her
with a little flirty flirt,
slip said tech onto her phone.
It'll turn into
a micro transmitter,
and boom, we'll learn
everything she knows.
Hmm.
It's not how I typically get
my information.
How do you typically do it?
I find the person.
And then I put the fear of God
into them until they talk.
But we can try your way.
You know, Carly,
I don't want this to, um,
you know, to come off
weird or anything,
it's just...
Would you like
to have dinner?
How about tonight?
Tonight?
What...
We haven't waited long enough?
Mmm.
Who knew street meat
could taste so good?
I had a feeling you needed
a break from the office.
Hank was
my first client.
I kept his son
from being sent away
for a mugging
that he didn't commit.
And how did that not
score you free hot dogs for life?
CNRI gives low income people access
to the legal system.
Without them, his son could have
gone to prison forever.
I could have gone
to prison, too.
He couldn't afford a dream team
of super lawyers.
So I'm supposed to feel guilty
because I'm lucky enough
to have a rich family?
No. You are lucky.
And hopefully CNRI
will show you that.
Hey!
Give us the purse,
and we won't press any charges.
Yeah, you're right.
I really do feel lucky.
This got snagged
as he bolted over the fence.
Looks like a chain
from his wallet.
I thought you gave up crime fighting.
What?
Well, the business
with your sister. I figured...
Ohh.
You'd stay out of police precincts.
Yeah, I...I saw you
on the news
and I realized that
I never thanked you
for everything
that you did, so.
Thank you.
So you got promoted.
Major Crimes.
Wow.
And they assigned me
to the Dodger case.
He extorts people
into stealing for him.
How's that going?
Slow.
Well...
It was nice
seeing you
the last time
that I saw you.
Yeah. It's good
seeing you, too.
It was like old times.
Except the PG version.
How do you mean?
Well, you and I always knew
how to have a fun time.
Something that's been
missing from my life lately.
So how about a drink?
Not now.
Would you maybe--
I'll take you for a--
would you like to have dinner
with me, McKenna?
I don't know
if you heard,
I was on a deserted
island for five years
and I am totally out of practice
with this whole...
Hmm. Well--well,
dinner would be nice.
In fact, I can make
myself free tonight.
Yeah.
Great.
So I'll grab you
at eight?
That's perfect.
All right.
Ok.
I'm lingering. I'm going to go.
Who's there?!
Help me.
Lance.
Sergeant,
it's Detective Hall.
I have an update
on the Dodger case.
A body was found in an
art gallery shot point blank.
There were
three other men there,
all rendered unconscious
by a highly focused
electric current to the heart.
Same M.O. as that
guard at the museum.
Got an ID on the vic?
His name is Cass Derenick.
Pause.
Who's Cass Derenick?
Arrest, possession
of stolen goods.
Arrest, conspiracy.
Conviction, attempted
sale of stolen goods.
This guy's a fence.
The Dodger's looking to unload
the Sherwood Ruby.
Which means he'll be
in the market for a new fence.
One he hasn't,
you know...killed.
So we find the fence
and we find the Dodger.
Anyway, I saw online
that you sell
a chain wallet with
an eight ball on the chain.
I was wondering
if you could give me
a name of one of your customers
if I gave you a description?
Yeah, sure, you can
call be back.
Like every other used clothing
and leather good store
I've called today.
What was that about?
What's up with the fancy fancy?
What? Oh, um,
I have a date.
Contrary to popular opinion,
I do have a life.
Then why do you seem
so nervous?
Is it obvious?
Just be your charming
and brooding self.
I mean, the girls
seem to dig that.
This girl is different.
She knew me before the island,
before I was...
That's CNRI.
I've got to take this.
I'm working on a very important
purse snatching case.
Yeah.
Hello?
Yes, I called you this morning.
Yeah, he might have been
wearing a red hoodie.
Kind of Abercrombie-looking.
His face, not the hoodie.
Really?
You wouldn't happen
to have his name?
Thank you so much.
Hey, Laurel.
Does your dad still
like arrest people?
I found the dirt bag.
His name is Roy Harper.
I can't remember
the last time I was here.
It's so beautiful.
Yeah, this was the place
to take a girl in high school.
Hmm, I was never
lucky enough to experience that.
I had braces and terrible bangs
back then.
I'm sure you looked amazing.
I'm glad we finally
got around to doing this.
Me, too.
You know, Andy set
a pretty high bar
when it came to first dates.
Hmm.
You know, he'd face down
armed gunmen for a living
but I've never seen him
as scared as he was before
that first date with you.
Ohh, Carly, I'm sorry.
That wasn't good
first date etiquette, was it?
Bring up Andy when we are having
a romantic night?
Probably not.
Look, Carly, this is
difficult and complicated.
It's not like there's
a manual, you know?
You know...
For a moment,
I--I felt like
a girl who likes a boy,
and nothing else
mattered.
But if this is
too hard for you,
or too complicated,
then please,
just get out now,
because I've already
been hurt too much.
Carly, listen, I'm sorry--
Can you just please
take me home?
Mmm.
No, no, no, no,
it is not possible
for something
to be this good!
Right?
Ohh!
So you must have
missed soufflés.
What do you mean?
Five years on an island,
away from civilization.
Ah, what did you do?
What did you eat?
Where'd you sleep?
How did you make it?
McKenna...
Sorry.
Didn't mean to drill you.
It's ok.
It's just I haven't
had a conversation
with a guy in a while
without it resulting
in me reading him
his rights.
So. Yeah,
but those years,
they must have
changed you.
From a guy I used
to party with to who you are now.
Yeah.
Because I had to make
some tough choices.
You're right.
It changed me.
What kind of
tough choices--
I don't want to talk about
those experiences, McKenna.
Saved by the cell.
Hall.
Ok, put what the C.I. told you in
the warrant application.
I'll be right there.
It's work, I got to go.
Felicity, listen, please.
I need you to activate
the bug in McKenna's phone.
I think the police
just got a lead on the Dodger.
Ok.
Who are you?
My name is Alan Durand.
I'm an exchange student.
I was on a fishing
excursion with my class.
We got lost and our boat
caught fire.
It was some mechanic malfunction.
We had to jump ship.
When?
Two days ago.
It was awful.
I thought I was
going to die.
Where are the other students?
Where's the boats crew, huh?
I think I'm the only one
who made it.
I managed
to get to shore.
I thought I was
lucky, but...
What? Somebody found you?
Soldiers, or...
Yes!
Yes.
They had these masks on
and they attacked me
and beat me.
They left me here!
Who are they?!
You can untie me
at any point, by the way.
Nice place
you have here.
Oh, thank you.
Tell me.
Does every fence
in this town hire muscle?
I did
as soon as I heard
about what you did
to Cass Derenick.
Oh, yes, Cass.
God rest his soul.
He wasn't
a very nice man.
He tried to steal from me.
Oh.
I've heard that you have a better
sense of judgment.
And that you have no
trouble in moving this.
Well, it's only a recession
for some people.
I take a 15% commission
off the top.
Let's call it
at 12, shall we?
Obviously I don't
have to remind you
about what what happened
to the last person
who tried
to screw me over.
SCPD! Grab the floor!
Come quietly!
I'm afraid
I'll have to decline.
Then I'm afraid
you won't be going to jail.
I heard on the news
the Dodger got away.
Hopefully the night
wasn't a complete waste.
Your dates.
How'd they go?
Great.
Awesome.
You two suck
at lying.
The police and I busted it up
before the Dodger
could get himself paid.
Don't change
the subject.
Is your hacker chip
still working?
You two
are no fun.
Yeah.
Still getting
a strong signal.
You should pull up
the police records.
Everything the Dodger's
stolen so far.
What are you thinking?
We know the Dodger has a taste
for a very specific
type of antiquity.
Yeah.
These all look like
they're from the ominous decade.
The last ten years
of King Ferdinand's reign.
And she says
we have no lives.
Are there any other
places that sell
or display items
from the ominous thing?
Decade.
Not really.
I guess people
in Starling City
prefer the Elizabethan era.
The Starling City
Cancer Society.
It says right there
they're holding
a fundraising auction
tomorrow night.
We could lure him
out into the open.
With what? A fake?
No. The Dodger clearly has a
trained eye for this sort of thing.
He's not going to fall for anything
less than the genuine article.
Where are we
going to get our hands
on a rare Spanish antiquity?
You really have no idea how rich
his family is, do you?
Roy William Harper Jr.
Where's senior?
Norris cemetery.
Sorry to hear that.
You and an army of bookies.
Can I go?
No. You've been
IDed as a suspect
in a purse snatching.
It's quite a résume
you've compiled here.
Petty theft, B&E,
robbery,
petty theft.
Stolen car. Well, it's nice
to change things up
once in a while.
And petty theft.
You got something
against banks?
Well, it is hard to run with one
under your arm.
Well, maybe you'll learn a few
new skills in prison.
Look, I don't want to steal.
Ok? I don't have
any other choice.
My mother, she...
She has a problem.
Yeah, her son's a moron.
No.
Vertigo.
She got hooked
on Vertigo last year.
She kicked it,
but I guess
she'd done enough that...
It messed her up.
Hmm.
She hasn't been the same,
and her medical bills--
look, I'm...I'm just trying
to help her get out from under.
Look, we're not privileged enough
to have as much as other people.
Ok?
Fine.
Let him go.
It's just a damn
purse, right?
They'll meet with you.
It has been arranged.
Thank you for this.
There's one more thing
I need you to do for me.
Malcolm's the only one
who knows where
Walter's being kept.
I just...I just need a clue.
Some lead to follow.
If our plan works,
I can't let it damn
Walter to hell.
No.
That's the fate that's in store
for us, I'm afraid.
The police
are here, too.
Your bait's attracted them,
at least.
That's not exactly
who I'm looking to catch.
So I'm getting a good
signal from the GPS
I put in
your family's broach.
I can track it on my phone.
Speaking of,
have you given any thought
to what might happen
if this doesn't work
and the Dodger absconds
with your family jewels?
I'm sorry, that
came out very wrong.
Let's just keep our eyes
open, Felicity.
Hey, isn't that...
You can just follow him
over there, ok?
Mm-hmm. I would rather take my
chances with a deadly jewel thief.
Right.
Hey!
That broach was donated
by the Queen family.
If you want it,
you're going to have to bid.
Actually, love,
I thought
I'd just take it.
Maybe I should
check out front,
see if the security
guards had any problems.
That's a good idea. I'm going
to go check on the bait.
I think I have a problem.
Get away from me!
If this thing blows...
Not going to happen.
The Dodger said if I called
the police, he'd--
I'm going to get decapitated,
aren't I?
The tracker's on the move.
If I find him, I can
get him to disarm it.
Talk me in. Stay calm.
Too late.
Go. Just go. Go, go, go.
Talk to me, Felicity!
Ahem.
Heading towards
Adams and O'Neil.
At the clip he's going,
he's got to be in a vehicle.
Hey. I need
your bike.
Are you kidding me?
No.
I'm mobile.
Where is he?
Talk to me, Felicity.
Come on.
First time anyone's ever been
grateful for traffic cameras.
He's one block
from your position.
If you cut through Harris Plaza,
you'll end up right behind him.
Where is he now?
Got it.
I got him, I got him.
Gray sedan driving north.
At the light ahead of you.
Ok, hard right.
Hey!
Don't do anything stupid.
I had the foresight
to collar up
a particularly
inquisitive blonde.
I assume she's
a friend of yours.
Touch one hair on my head
and she loses hers.
You've got quite
the choice to make, don't you?
Not this time.
Your median nerve's
been severed.
You couldn't push
that button if you tried.
Oh, thank God.
Why are you doing this?
I'm exactly like you.
I only steal
from the rich.
I'm not Robin Hood.
I don't know when
these men are coming back!
You have to believe me.
Untie me, please!
What, do you think
these men,
they planted me here,
some kind of trap or something?
I...Well, why'd they
tie you up like that
and then just leave you?
Huh? Why not just kill you?
They were going to!
They got called away
at some--some altercation
somewhere else
on the island.
If they come back,
they will kill both of us.
Please! You have
to believe me.
Please.
All right, turn--
all right, turn around.
Thank you.
I'm sorry...
But I can't.
What? Why?!
Why not?
Because I don't know you.
Are you out
of your mind?!
Please!
You can't do this!
You can't just leave me here!
You know, last night
all I could think about
was how pissed off
Andy will be;
how hurt he'll be
if he saw us together.
But that's nothing
compared to how he'd be
if I did something
to hurt you, Carly.
Believe me when I tell you
that war is easier than dating.
In a war, you act
or you die.
No time to think, no time
to second guess yourself.
Maybe that's
your problem.
With me,
you're thinking.
Not feeling.
You're right.
How did you know
where I live?
A little thing
called the Internet.
Look, could we not
do this with a door between us?
So I guess you're not
pressing charges
'cause you feel like--
you feel like you can change my life?
And so you can run and tell your rich
prep school friends
what a Saint you are and how
you're helping the disadvantaged?
You don't know
a thing about me.
Thea Queen.
Trust fund brat.
Totaled her car, which she got
as a birthday present.
Loves designer labels
and is usually in the tabloids
for partying too much.
Did I--did I leave
anything out?
Yeah.
Dead father,
missing step dad,
damaged brother,
and almost served
jail time for that car accident.
Plus, she really
wants her purse back.
You know, you showed some
real sack coming down here,
the Glades in the middle
of the night.
You must not know the value
of a vintage purse.
Don't worry,
it's all there.
Except for these. Ahh.
You know, it's a really
filthy habit you got there.
Yeah, tell me about it.
Hey, can I give you
some advice?
First, stay out
of the Glades.
And second?
Don't fall
for every sob story
a guy like me
tells the police.
You have
a great evening now.
Do you ever take time off?
I do.
In fact, last night
I went on a date.
The guy was
kind of a jerk.
Really?
He might have
had a reason.
McKenna,
I didn't just lose
five years
on the island.
I lost the part of
me that enjoyed...
Being alive.
Listening to music
and, uh...
eating a soufflé
with a beautiful girl.
It's the easy things.
But when you asked me
about the island,
it reminded me
of all the hard things
and the hard choices that
I had to make that
still stay with me.
Made me question
how I can trust,
and even
if I'm worthy of...
being with anyone.
You are.
Mmm. Hmm.
Can I take you
to a dinner?
That I promise not
to cut short.
Um...
Throw in a soufflé
and you're on.
McKenna!
Glad you're still here.
Queen.
Mr. Lance.
Actually, I was just leaving.
Is everything ok, sir?
Yeah. I'd like you
to, uh,
work with me on
the Vigilante investigation.
Thank you, sir.
Well, don't worry,
we'll bring him in.
Oh, yeah.
Ah. Ready to go?
Yep.
Ok.
Ahh. It tastes like an ashtray.
But it does the job.
I owe you one.
You didn't get into
any trouble out there, did you?
Hmm?
No. Not a bit.
Frank Chan recommended you.
He said you could
help us with our problem.
He appreciates you
agreeing to meet with me.
Anything for a friend.
So...
How can we be of assistance?
Malcolm Merlyn.
I want you to kill him
for me.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==