[Oliver] My name is Oliver Queen.
After five years in hell,
I returned home with only one goal,
to save my city.
But I couldn't honor that commitment
and honor the promise
I made to the mother of my son.
So I asked the best man I know to help.
His name is John Diggle
and he is the Green Arrow.
[Oliver]Previously onArrow...
Pollard. She's using last night's
disaster as a pretext
to introduce her anti-vigilante
legislation to the council.
I'm invoking chapter nine
of the city charter.
That would convert
Councilwoman Pollard's bill
to a citywide referendum.
What do you want?
To operate without interference.
So you can keep killing people.
You don't seem to know that this is a war.
The intel that you gave me on my son,
Joe, panned out...
So I'm heading to Calgary.
Good luck, Slade.
[indistinct chatter]
Miss Pollard, Captain wanted you to
see the latest COMPSTAT.
Thanks, Lieutenant.
Sniper!
[clamoring]
[gunshots]
[policeman] Officer down. Code three.
Officer down.
Well, I'm just glad no one
was seriously hurt.
How do you want to handle this?
I'd like you to
issue a statement on my behalf.
On your behalf?
I have an old friend in town
that needs my help
and I might not be back in the office
for a few hours.
Do we have any idea
who the shooter was targeting?
We're working on it.
Good. Be the Mayor until I get back.
For real?
No. It's a figure of speech.
Just don't make any laws while
I'm out of the office, okay?
Fine.
And don't worry about the shooter.
We're gonna nail his ass.
I know you will.
Sorry. That was work.
Don't apologize.
I appreciate the meeting.
You helped me find my son.
The least I can do is help you find Joe.
He doesn't go by that name anymore.
He changed his name?
It was his mother's idea.
Her maiden name. He goes by "Kane" now.
What happened to him?
I tracked him to Calgary,
but by then he had gone.
So, I followed him to Ibiza,
and then Mombasa.
Mombasa?
The kid took after his father.
While we were stuck on Lian Yu,
he went down and joined
the Australian Intelligence Service.
And a week ago, in Kasnia,
a mission went south.
He was dealing in arms,
some locals caught him.
Supposedly, he didn't
have a fair trial and now he's...
Serving a life sentence.
Like a rat in a cage.
Okay, Slade, what do you need?
I need you to help me find my son.
Last we met, you told me
that I couldn't live in two worlds.
I'm not asking you to come back in.
Strangely enough,
what I need is diplomacy,
which means I don't want Green Arrow,
I need Oliver Queen.
For what?
Can I ask you just to trust me
on this one, kid?
I've organized transport to Kasnia.
Wheels up at 2200.
I'll understand
if you don't want to join me.
But if you do,
I'll meet you out front at 2100.
Okay, kid?
Okay, bring that stuff over here.
Sorry.
Hey, don't worry.
It's only tent poles.
It's not like we're gonna
stick around long enough to use them.
Why'd you say that?
You're always leaving. I can't
believe we even made it this far.
Listen, you know
that I work for Australian Airlines
and I have to travel.
But I promise you,
this weekend, it's just about you and me.
Father and son. Out in the wild.
Come on. Go find some flat land,
and pitch a tent.
Got him.
I didn't get him, get him,
but I've identified him.
-Identified who?
-Our sniper.
I thought your T-Spheres
could track his visor.
Well, that was then.
This is apparently now.
He must have hacked the tracer.
Or got a new visor.
It's not like they sell 'em
at Walmart, Felicity.
Guys, update time. I think
our vigilante's back in town.
He's the shooter?
I saw him coming out of the sniper's nest.
CSU's here.
I don't know how much evidence
we'll be able to pull.
[Curtis] Why don't we work
with what we have?
Mainly, the Vigilante seemed to be
targeting Councilwoman Pollard.
"Seemed to be" being the operative word.
Well, Pollard's the one who's
championing the anti-vigilante bills.
Seems like a guy named "Vigilante"
wouldn't like her much.
[John]Yeah. But martyr her?
That'd get this bill passed faster
than you could say "obstruction."
If it passes, I'm gonna
have to consider arresting myself.
Excuse me. What are you doing here?
You're not SCPD.
No, he's not.
And this is not a federal case.
Still doesn't explain what John Diggle,
who works personal security for
the mayor, is doing at a crime scene.
I have relevant experience, and...
the mayor thought this could use
a fresh set of eyes.
What type of experience?
Sniper.
I don't recall
reading that in your military file.
I'm sorry, tell me again, why you're
reviewing my service jacket?
Mayor Queen didn't
mention he was under investigation?
Of course he did,
it has nothing to do with this.
But you've been working with him
for the past six years.
Which makes us overdue for a chat.
I can wait for a subpoena if you prefer.
No. I'm an open book.
Step into my office.
Uh-uh.
Private conversation.
Hey, William.
Hi.
How are those quadratic equations going?
I hate them.
Yeah, those were the days.
Where's your dad?
In his room.
Huh.
Do you remember
when our biggest problem in life
was solving a quadratic equation?
Mmm-mmm.
I mean, I never really worried
about them, but no.
Well, now, we have metas crashing
bachelorette parties, so...
Wow. Slade invited you on
a romantic getaway?
Something like that.
Where? Don't say Aruba. That's our spot.
[sighs] Kasnia.
Wow!
His son is in some trouble.
The kind of trouble you need
to get in more trouble to fix it?
Well, Slade says that
he has a diplomatic solution
that requires my name
and not me in a mask.
I'm worried that if I don't go,
he will take a more aggressive approach.
So the empty bag, is that second thoughts?
Or can't decide what T-shirt to pack?
Because I'm out.
I made a promise to my son and I'm out.
It sounds like
you made a promise to Slade, too.
You think I should go?
It's not like you're
going back to your old life.
I wanted you to tell me not to go.
Look, Slade is not
my favorite person, but...
I mean, it's not about Slade.
It's about his son.
If you don't go, you're just gonna
beat yourself up about it.
If, when, it veers from diplomacy,
and I have to break
my promise to William, I will beat
myself up over that too.
-Then tell William what you're doing.
-What?
Spare him the details of,
you know, Slade being Slade
and tell him that you are
helping a friend.
He'll understand that.
-You sure?
-Yeah, I'm sure.
He's his father's son.
[breathes deeply]
[sirens wailing distantly]
How long is this flight?
It's about 12 hours.
Thanks for coming, kid.
Let's go get your boy.
[lock beeps]
SCPD!
Hey!
[sonic scream]
Stay down.
[gasps]
It's you.
[gate rattles]
Got your 9-1-1. Is everything okay?
Look at her face.
That is not an "okay" face.
Dinah?
Vigilante made another move on
Councilwoman Pollard tonight.
I almost got him.
It's cool, D. We'll nail that bastard.
I hit him with my cry.
I shattered his visor
and he took off his mask.
I saw his face.
Can you ID him?
His name is Vincent Sobel.
He's my old partner.
I'm sorry. When you say partner,
do you mean partner,
or do you mean, "partner"?
Both.
Now I'm confused.
Dinah, I thought you said
your partner died in the line.
He was shot in the head
right in front of me.
No!
Okay, well, I know you believe
you saw what you saw tonight,
but it was night, probably dark.
It was him, Felicity.
It was Vincent. I know it.
I know it sounds crazy.
Dinah, this doesn't change anything.
We have to find him
before he hurts anyone else.
I know.
I know. Where are you
with the shell casing John found?
The casing appears to be magnetized.
Bullets aren't magnetic.
They can be if they are stored
in an environment
with a strong magnetic field.
You think it's something you can trace?
I like your optimism.
It's not optimism, Felicity.
It's faith.
Dinah said that you had a chat
with our FBI BFF?
Oh, yes. She's tough,
but I pushed back pretty hard.
Can we put that to bed?
-[phone ringing]
-Good.
Hello?
Special Agent Watson...
Yes, sure. I can come by tomorrow,
no problem.
All right, see you then.
Definitely not put to bed.
So where's your point of contact?
I don't know.
His name's Nylander.
A foreign associate of mine
from back in the service days.
He was a bit of a jackarse
and never on time.
[Nylander] He's not that bad.
[chuckles] Slade Wilson.
The Terminator.
I haven't heard that name in a while.
So, you're running later than usual.
Yeah, I was with a girl.
Forget about it. Look at you.
Mirakuru did you wonders.
Now what? You're not sensitive
about that shit, are you?
You were quite the madman, I hear.
You promised me something.
Did you bring it?
Or did I waste my time
traveling 7,000 miles
for you to screw with me?
Truth be told,
I'm glad you got your marbles back.
So who's this?
He's a friend of mine.
Don't worry about him.
With you, I always worry.
This should work.
Thank you.
That's it? Just thank you?
No extravagant dinner? No pints?
Maybe next time,
when my son's not
rotting in a third-world prison.
He's lucky to have you as a father.
My son wouldn't be in this mess,
if anybody else was his father.
Just be careful, comrade.
Your boy was snooping around
some private-op mercenaries.
Some not-so-nice guys.
Under certain circumstances,
I'm not so nice a guy.
Yeah, not so big in the decoration,
are you?
I'm less enthusiastic for people
wasting my time.
Okay.
You're seeing Oliver Queen again.
Yeah. These new prescription glasses
are really working wonders. [chuckles]
Just a little FBI interrogation
humor, you know.
You are Mr. Queen's alibi
for certain evenings where
the Green Arrow was active.
If you say so.
My point is, are you prepared to
testify under oath,
under the pains and penalties of perjury,
in support of those alibis?
Yeah. Absolutely.
100%.
Super ready.
[phone chimes]
Everything all right?
Mmm-hmm.
Yeah. I'm just late for a coffee date.
-So, I'd like to...
-Go.
Go.
Thank you. This was pleasant.
I call this play Liberty Watch.
A famous American mayor comes
to small war-torn Kasnia,
to fight for the release of a man
who has been wrongfully accused.
This is very clever.
Like I said, it's a "diplomatic solution."
Well, Slade, still. I don't think
that they're gonna free your son,
just because I give him a photo op.
No. The photo op is just to gain entry.
Of course, they'll need a reason
to release him.
And here are 50,000.
Assuming this works,
where do we meet?
When you pick up Joe,
go straight to the airport.
Here is an alias passport for him
and tickets for you both
to London.
You're not even gonna see him?
I need you to promise me
that you won't tell him I helped.
No. I'm not gonna lie to your son.
It's better this way.
For him or for you?
Wait, are you...
Are you afraid that he's gonna
see you as Deathstroke,
and not the man you were? The...
The man I think you are now.
I gave up my right to be his father
when I stepped out of the light
into shadows,
and became this monster.
Your son will forgive you
the way that my son forgave me.
Joe knew
that I was coming to look for him,
so he contacted his mother
and she sent me a message
to stay away.
You got your second chance, kid.
And I'm happy for you.
Some fathers aren't that lucky.
So, tell me this is not the freshest
fish that somebody's caught for you.
I don't even like fish.
Not all fish are the same.
Trust me, kid.
Are you really a pilot?
Of course, I am.
Stop lying.
Why are you being like this?
We never get free trips.
My friend Nick's dad flies for Ferris Air.
They get free trips all the time.
-[woman] Here, honey, keep up.
-[boy] Okay.
Unfortunately, I work
for a cheaper airline
that doesn't allow for free vacations.
Whatever. I'm not hungry.
Don't walk too far.
[Dinah Drake] This place
used to house MRI machines.
[Green Arrow] We are in the right place.
That's all that matters.
Hey, guys, sorry I'm late.
How was it with Watson?
Terrifying.
We knew she was planning
a case against Oliver,
but I'm starting to think her net
is widening to include us.
She hasn't contacted me yet.
Wait, why hasn't she?
[Wild Dog] How about
we not worry about this
while we're in the lair
of a psycho-killer?
-Sorry.
-[Green Arrow] Here.
There's enough ordinance here
for a small war.
You don't need this many bullets
for one councilwoman.
When you called Vince
a psycho-killer, you weren't wrong.
Mr. Queen...
Thank you for taking the time.
It is not every day I meet celebrity.
I'm not famous.
I saw you on news once.
You punched man with camera.
Yup, I sure did.
They also say you are quite good
with bow and arrow.
Oh, don't believe everything
that you see on TV.
Okay, okay.
I understand you are
with organization in hopes to...
To request the release
of one of your prisoners.
Kane Wolfman.
[sighs]
I wish you come earlier.
[door opens]
What're you doing back here?
Where is my son?
[sighs]
There was a... A fight in the prison yard
that Joe tried to break up.
Someone pushed, and he hit his head...
He's gone.
[Slade] He never knew.
Never knew what?
[shuddering]
That I loved him.
I'm sure he did, Slade.
I don't remember the last time
I told him...
Well, you were his father.
Trust me, he knew.
I should have come with you to the prison.
I know it wouldn't have
made any difference, but...
at least I could have seen him...
Say goodbye.
Well, you still can.
You can still say goodbye.
Joe! Good catch.
Come on.
We are not here to mope around.
[chuckles]
Excuse me,
could you take a photo of my son and I?
Sure.
[camera clicks]
I'm Slade.
Darryl. Nice to meet you.
This is my son, Joe.
-Hey, Joe.
-Nice to meet you.
[John] Don't burn yourself out, Dinah.
We need you for the long haul, remember?
There's no long haul.
We're putting this bastard down.
Remember, this bastard was
your partner and your boyfriend.
I don't need you
to remind me of that, thanks.
[chuckles] No, you don't need me
to remind you of that.
But you do need someone
to point out the fact
that perhaps a part of you
should be happy to have him back.
John, when Vince died, I did
my absolute best to kill myself.
I became somebody I didn't even recognize.
To avenge somebody
who I don't even recognize anymore.
Somebody who kills innocent people.
You and Vince went through
something horrific.
You did some things you regret.
Maybe there's a part of you
that's putting that on him.
John, he's a psychopath.
It doesn't change the fact that
he's someone who needs help, Dinah.
Just like you did.
Sorry to interrupt, but we've got
two new problems.
Pollard's headed over
to do a sit-down with Channel 52
to talk about
the anti-vigilante referendum.
Wait, no, that station is not secure.
SCPD cannot protect her there.
That's why I said we've got a problem.
-What's the second one?
-Agent Watson's subpoenaed me.
I gotta go, right?
Yeah. That's usually what
a subpoena means. You have to go.
I'm gonna head to the news station,
see if I can get Pollard
some extra protection.
-Dinah, if Vince tries anything...
-I know, John, I got it.
Mr. Queen,
I was not expecting a return visit.
Warden, this is Kane Wolfman's father.
He wishes to see his son's body.
I'm afraid that won't be possible.
Why?
You said he passed only days ago.
-Yes, but...
-Warden. Where's the body?
It is no longer in my possession.
Where is my son's body?
Hey. Easy. Easy.
He's lying.
Do you want me to contact Liberty Watch?
Do you want me to cause
an international incident?
Because I'm prepared to do both.
The situation is complicated.
-Well, un-complicate it.
-Hey.
Trust me on this one.
Don't make this man angry.
[sighs]
They're called the Jackals.
The men your son investigated.
When they discovered his arrest,
which was merely him being
in the wrong place at the wrong time,
they broke into prison. Take him.
Why did they take him?
Torture. Your son is spy.
In his head, secrets worth millions.
They threatened reprisal on my family
if I spoke about it.
Slade. Slade.
When the Jackals took my son, they
didn't count on who his father was.
Okay. Every single person
in that line is ID'd twice.
You got it?
I don't care if it's your mother.
And I want two officers
at every emergency exit
and I need somebody to move this car.
Lieutenant Drake. Good to see you again.
All right. We're nearly ready to move
on the news station.
Dinah's already on site.
Copy.
Emailing Oliver?
Yeah, I'm just sending Oliver
some info he asked me for.
You know, for his adventures with Slade.
Are you having as much trouble with
Oliver working with Slade as I am?
No.
Having a lot more.
Rationally, I know that it was the
Mirakuru that made him a jerk, but...
But he wasn't on Mirakuru
when he left us on Lian Yu.
Exactly.
It's ironic that Oliver has more
honor than the man he's helping.
Ironic isn't the word I would use.
[Dinah Drake]Guys, we've got a problem.
If I had a nickel for every time
I heard that...
Listen, I'm gonna need you to
stand down. Okay? Do not come here.
Dinah, we're not standing down.
We are not leaving you out there alone.
I'm not alone.
Agent Watson is here.
And she brought friends.
She's hoping the Green Arrow will show up.
You guys stay put, okay? I got this.
I asked Felicity for any intel
she could find on the Jackals.
She hacked the databases of every
major intelligence agency
in the world.
-And what did she find?
-Nothing.
These guys are ghosts.
That's no help.
This is.
Using closed circuit-cameras in the prison
and surrounding areas,
she got their escape route,
the license plates and then
using keyhole satellite technology...
She tracked them to one location.
Yes. She did.
She's brilliant. How did you get her?
I ask myself that every day.
What's in there for me?
Nothing.
I promised you.
Your only part in this was talking.
Circumstances have changed.
Not for you.
You've got your feet planted in one world.
-And you should keep them there.
-Slade!
These Jackals are the best of the worst.
All right? They're stone-cold killers.
And what do you think I am?
I think that you're outnumbered.
And quite frankly, I think
that you're out of practice
and I am not letting you do this alone.
[groans]
Alone is what I do best, kid.
Go ahead.
Tell me the truth.
Not bad.
[laughing]
I have to go to the bathroom.
I'll be back soon.
[Deathstroke] You are Xien Ming, an agent
for the Ministry of Defense,
People's Republic.
I'm looking for an agent
who you black-bagged.
Called Yao Fei.
You have 10 seconds
to tell me where he is.
Purgatory.
[twig cracks]
[grunts]
Hey. He's with me.
Excuse me. He's with me. Let him through.
You guys make sure that perimeter
is secure over on the side there.
I thought I told you to stand down.
Don't worry. I left the hoodie at home.
Well, then, what are you doing here,
John? I told you I got it.
But I realized, you're not exactly
in your right head.
My head is fine.
Thank you. Your little pep talk
really got through to me.
Dinah, you're a lousy liar.
He didn't always make bullets.
Vince.
He used to make this matchbox art,
with a tiny little paper rose
on the inside.
He made me one the morning
Sonos found out we were undercover.
There is nothing left of that man
anymore, John.
Dinah, earlier this year,
when he attacked Oliver's limo,
he had the chance to kill you,
and he didn't.
-Your point?
-My point is
that maybe there's something
left of the man you used to love.
If there isn't,
I'm going to put him down.
And this time, he'll stay dead.
-Dinah, will you just...
-You better get out of here,
before Watson sees you.
Three. Two.
Good evening. I'm Jane Wood.
Sitting tonight with Miss Emily Pollard.
-Welcome, Councilwoman Pollard.
-It's my pleasure.
[Jane] And we're going to hear thoughts
on the anti-vigilante referendum.
Status?
Pretty quiet, Lieutenant.
The place is locked tight.
He's not getting in here.
What we need is legislation
to deter others
from joining this vigilante movement
in the future.
We need to take those vigilantes
off the streets.
You don't think they serve a role?
Cops serve that role.
The department's been full of
corrupt cops in the past.
And on top of that, we're shorthanded.
All I know, Lieutenant,
is if people take the law
into their own hands,
we've got anarchy.
[Jane] John, can we have the lights
back up, please?
Guys, check the power!
[indistinct chatter]
Don't move and it'll be quick.
Killing me won't prevent
the referendum from passing.
If anything, it'll make sure it does.
But there will be one less
corrupt politician.
[grunting]
Run!
Let's talk, Vince.
Just talk.
[cop] Freeze!
Get down on the floor.
-You have three seconds.
-Easy.
One. Two.
-Put the gun down.
-[distorted] Three.
[thuds]
Call an ambulance.
Do it now!
[groans]
[whimpers]
How?
You're not the only one
dark matter did something to.
Everything heals now.
I thought you were dead.
You let me believe it
for four years, Vince.
I'm sorry. I couldn't let myself...
Be human?
Distracted.
Distracted? From what?
My mission.
We were cops for 10 years.
What did we ever accomplish?
A lot.
Not enough.
Not nearly enough.
This is the only way.
You've lost your mind.
I'm not the only one wearing a mask.
[sirens wailing distantly]
The police are coming.
And the FBI.
You should go.
[John]Black Canary, what's happening?
-We're getting reports that...
-Pollard's safe. She's secure.
What about Vigilante?
He got away.
[gasps]
[groans]
[phone vibrates]
Hey, buddy.
I just wanna check in. Is this a bad time?
It's never a bad time.
Are you coming home?
As a matter of fact, I am.
I wish you were here already.
Raisa's been making me eat granola
all weekend.
[chuckles] Raisa knows her stuff.
Granola's good for you.
Were you able to help your friend?
No, I wasn't.
I really hope he finds his son.
Yeah.
I do, too.
Is there anything else you can do for him?
War.
-[grunts]
-[Deathstroke] Who's in charge?
[men groaning]
[clanging]
[man yells]
[groaning]
[guns cocking]
[Nylander] Stop it, stop.
Damn it, Slade.
You're going to ruin my new shoes.
And I just bought them, brother.
Nylander.
This man is a legend.
So no pulling triggers...
Yet.
Truce? Let me explain.
I knew you'd be involved, Nylander.
But you're too stupid
to run this organization.
So, where's the boss?
You know, I had really hoped
prison would be your dead end.
But no.
You just had to keep on coming,
didn't you?
We've got a great thing going here, Slade.
Lots of killing. Lots of money.
And your son, what he knows? Priceless.
You like burning bridges.
[chuckles]
So says the man who nearly
burnt down a whole city.
[gunshot]
Be smarter than that, comrade.
[strains]
Where is my son?
Why do you ask?
Hmm?
Do you wish to join him?
-Did you have a good time?
-Yeah.
Just close this up.
[Samanda] Busy night.
Yeah.
Guess we're lucky you and your agents
were there to provide backup.
Councilwoman Pollard says she was
saved by the new Black Canary.
Mmm. Yeah, I heard that.
[Samanda] Helluva thing.
Pollard's saved by one
of the vigilantes she's gunning for.
From what I understand,
it didn't change her position.
What about you?
I try to stay out of politics.
No, I mean where were you tonight?
What do you mean? I was right there.
Not when the lights went out.
When it went dark, you were gone.
And the Black Canary was there.
You think I'm the Black Canary?
I think a lot of things.
But I focus on what I can prove.
Have a good night.
[grunting]
I'm curious, Slade.
What was your plan?
Kill us all and save your boy?
Kind of reductive, no?
I like to keep things simple.
Things rarely are, brother.
Well, this is.
I will join the Jackals
as long as you let my boy go.
[Nylander] It's like I said.
Things aren't so simple.
We need your son.
After all, he's our boss.
Hello, Father.
It's been a long time.