Previously on Arrow:
- Where's your mother?
- The white-haired woman, she took her.
Deliver Sara's killer or citizens of Starling
will see what the League is capable of.
I will tell Ra's this was you,
that Thea was under your control.
And he Will still kill her.
She fired the arrows.
- There's nothing I won't do to protect you.
- What does that mean?
I killed Sara. By League law, I have the
right to challenge you to a trial by combat.
You covet death that much?
Shots fired. Units in pursuit
of a van across the causeway.
I want air support.
These bastards, they shot one of our own.
That cop was just asking for my license,
man. You didn't have to shoot him.
Shots fired.
Get me closer.
Come on. Damn it.
Nice.
It's him.
I thought he was green.
This bike is sick.
Not supposed to be having fun right now.
- Sorry.
- No, sorry is what you'll be...
...when Oliver finds out
you took out his motorcycle.
I've got him headed your way.
Aim for the engine block.
There's the green one.
Suit's too tight.
They make it to the tunnel, we lose them.
You're not helping.
I thought he was supposed to be good.
Who the hell are you?
I'm more of a Glock kind of guy.
I didn't say anything.
One caught, one got away,
but even Oliver bats .500 sometimes.
- Any luck finding Oliver?
- Not yet.
But I have every reconnaissance satellite
I could hack looking for him.
So the second he steps outside, we'll know.
If he steps outside.
- It's what we were all thinking.
- I'm not. It's only been three days.
I have to head to my
other office for a bit.
Okay, I know it's only been three days...
...but how much longer
before we actually have to start worrying?
I expected this kind of blunder
from Mr. Queen, but not from you.
You should have checked with me
before abducting that scientist.
We were just following the trail for Omega,
like you ordered us to.
I ordered you to be cautious.
That's how you protect yourself
and your loved ones.
We need an extraction team to free my wife.
From where? We don't know
where Chien Na Wei is located.
- We have more pressing concerns.
- She has the Omega.
We find her, we find Tatsu.
We get them both out of wherever they are.
If only it were that simple.
We've learned that the bioweapon
is actually comprised of two components.
The Omega she has is harmless
without its counterpart, Alpha.
And where's that?
Currently in the possession
of the Hong Kong military.
- So it's safe.
- Far from it.
The only way to secure
the counterpart Alpha is to destroy it.
And by the time we do,
my wife will be dead.
Alpha is being kept here
in a PLA military laboratory.
The two of you with backup will break
into the facility and recover the vial.
It's tagged with a GPS tracker, which
you'll need to disable before extraction.
And what about Tats-u?
- Stop ignoring me.
- I'm not ignoring you, Mr. Yamashiro.
I'm merely focusing on the task at hand...
...which, at the moment,
is not recovering your wife.
Ah. All right.
This will be gauntlet pulse test 37 Alpha.
Two-second burst at 800 volts.
In five, four...
...three, two, one.
Damn it.
- Clowns?
- Practice targets.
- Clowns freaked me out as a kid.
- Well, you're showing them who's boss now.
I would be, if I could figure out how
to modulate the stress energy tenser.
Ray, I've been thinking.
- About overclocking the magnetic coils?
- No.
About what you're doing
and about me helping you do it.
Save the city, you mean?
Risk your life.
I know you think you're going to be safe
inside that suit of armor.
I know there's, like, a gajillion movies
that make it look easy.
Well, the Arrow and his partner go out
there every night, without armor.
And one night...
...hopefully very far off in the future,
they're not gonna come back.
I don't want that to happen to you.
Let's not get ahead of ourselves.
Start small.
Just see if you can get the nanite chip
to function.
Dad, I will do what I can.
Here he comes.
The cop he shot, doc says he may never
walk again, and that's if he makes it...
...because right now, he's 50-50.
All right, Miss Lance, you're up.
The People v. Jermaine Fisher.
Mr. Fisher is charged with 41 counts
of attempted murder...
...including 16 counts of attempted murder
of a police officer.
So no bail is what you're saying?
Vigorously, Your Honor.
Just as the defendant vigorously moves
to dismiss all charges.
Mr. Fisher's apprehension was not affected
by the police, but rather by vigilantes.
The circumstances of Mr. Fisher's arrest
are irrelevant.
Produce the Arrow as an eyewitness,
and we'll find out.
That won't be necessary.
We have the weapon with Mr. Fisher's
fingerprints all over it, Your Honor.
Motion to dismiss, denied. Bail, denied.
Please remand Mr. Fisher into custody.
How'd it go at A.R.G.U.S.?
Lyla tapped all of her worldwide contacts.
No sign of Oliver.
- No idea where he could be.
- He'll tell us when he gets back.
Until then, we should focus
on keeping the lights on.
The shooters we took on last night, I've
been trying to find the one that got away.
Jose Anton. Anton is attached
to a new crew working the Glades...
...the head of which is this gentleman.
I know that guy. That's Danny Brickwell.
His street name's Brick.
- But I thought he was in Iron Heights.
- He was until a week ago.
And then the case against him imploded...
...by which I mean every single witness
suffered some sort of fatal accident.
Three guesses as to who the police suspect.
Jermaine Fisher
and the guy who got away last night.
Jose Anton.
So they kill witnesses in order to get Brick
out of prison, then shoot a cop to do what?
- That's what we have to find out.
- I'll hit the streets.
You have that look you always get right
before you tell Oliver something sagely.
Yes, and this is about Oliver.
You think I'm in denial?
I think Oliver challenged
the world's greatest assassin to a duel.
He survived Lian Yu...
...and Hong Kong,
and God knows what else.
He defeated Malcolm Merlyn...
...and Slade Wilson.
- You have to believe in him.
- Oh, I do believe in him, Felicity.
It's just I'm preparing myself
for the possibility...
...that things didn't go Oliver's way.
Not this time.
You need to prepare yourself too.
Please, Oliver, where are you?
Y'all best step off.
Brick is a friend of mine.
You're more than a friend, Anton.
You're like a brother.
Always had my back, always loyal.
Stand up.
So when they told me
someone ignored my orders to lay low...
...when they told me
one of my crew shot a cop...
...I beat the man who said it was you.
I'm sorry.
Danny, that cop...
...it was a mistake.
What we're planning here
requires two things.
No mistakes
and the cops not knowing anything.
They still don't.
Fisher's not gonna say anything.
Was this side job his idea or yours?
It doesn't have to be like this.
Bro.
I dropped my first body with that piece.
You know the deal.
You take me down first, you walk out alive.
He actually tagged me. Ha, ha.
All yours, boys.
Your attorney doesn't
have your best interests at heart.
- Otherwise you'd be walking out a free man.
- Yeah, more like a dead man.
You think you scare me
more than Brick does? Think again.
You have a real nice day now.
No, he didn't flip.
He likes breathing too much.
When your opponent is the mountain,
you must be the sea.
When he's the sea,
you must be the mountain.
- Poetic.
- Switch your attacks.
Never do the same move
more than twice.
Otherwise, your opponent will learn
to read you.
Something like that?
Well, I wouldn't recommend texting
during a real fight.
Sorry, I thought it might be Ollie.
He hasn't been home, he hasn't
returned any of my calls or texts.
Didn't realize his absence
was weighing on you.
Not weighing, it's worrying.
If you like, I could have some
of my old associates...
...look into Oliver's whereabouts.
Would you?
Of course.
He's family.
According to Laurel, Fisher's lawyer called
Brick. With the time and place of the call...
Can you trace that call back
to where Brick is?
At least where his phone is.
His burner phone, to be exact.
It's at a warehouse in the Glades.
We'll check it out.
I'm gonna have to talk you in
from Palmer Tech. I'm crazy late.
- This is the only vulnerable entrance.
- Because it's not actually an entrance.
Not until we make it one.
I'll shoot out the glass.
You get in and find the Alpha.
You won't have much time
once we breach.
Two minutes max
before alarms draw the police.
Head directly for the lab.
We'll be right behind you.
You Okay?
Waller said when we get this done,
she'll get Tatsu back.
She's lying.
- On the move. Thirty seconds.
- Copy that.
I've got eyes on the target warehouse.
No signs of life.
- Felicity, you seeing something?
- The warehouse doesn't have cameras.
Someone disabled the traffic cams
on that block.
Which means you're in the right place.
Sure ditching the Arrow suit
was a good idea?
Only if I need to move or shoot.
In position.
Clear.
Hey, I got something.
- It's not big enough to be Brick.
- Yeah, I know.
What's this?
- They burned their burners.
- Yeah.
Torching evidence. Tying up loose ends.
Evidence of what?
I don't know. These just look like numbers.
I found this.
Looks like some industrial blueprints.
Hmm.
These numbers look completely random.
I can run a pattern recognition algorithm.
Oliver?
Could you put the gun away?
They don't scare so much as annoy me.
I've only come here to talk.
Would it be possible to do that?
- Talk about what?
- Oliver.
- I need to know, is he still alive?
- He's alive.
Have you heard from him
since he went off to face Ra's al Ghul?
He's alive.
If he were,
you would have heard from him by now.
Unless Ra's took him prisoner.
The Demon's Head
does not take prisoners.
What are you doing?
I'm running the pattern analysis
on that list of numbers you guys found.
No, I mean, what's the point?
Malcolm Merlyn didn't tell us anything
we don't already know. Nothing has changed.
You're right, Felicity.
He didn't tell us anything new.
But he may have been right.
I know you think I'm in denial, but if
there's one thing Oliver taught me...
...taught us, is that sometimes
all you can do is keep pushing forward.
All right?
- I've got the ME's report.
- Did they ID the body?
Jose Anton.
Career criminal
with ties to Danny Brickwell.
I think Brick severed those ties
pretty thoroughly.
Is everything okay?
Where's Oliver?
He went to fight the head
of the League of Assassins.
What?
- Haven't heard from him since he left.
- And something else.
Malcolm Merlyn stopped
by for a little chat.
He says Oliver's dead.
- And you guys believe him?
- Look, Laurel, Merlyn said...
There isn't one thing Malcolm Merlyn
can say that any of us should believe.
This isn't the first time that I've heard
that Oliver was dead.
He's been back before.
He'll be back again.
I'm in.
Foundit
Hong Kong military?
The Triad. Chien Na Wei's men.
Any luck?
The number pattern is consistent
with cataloging numerics.
- What kind of catalog?
- If I knew, I would be telling you.
I'm sorry to interrupt.
- We really need to change the locks.
- What do you want?
The League conducts
matter of significance such as duels...
...on grounds sacred to its beliefs.
I went there...
...and found this.
It's Ra's' custom...
...to leave behind the
instrument of death...
...as a memorial to honor the fallen.
Merlyn, did you see Oliver's body?
He fell into a ravine.
His remains are unrecoverable, I'm afraid.
Then how do we know
that's Oliver's blood?
Because after I leave, you'll test it.
And after you confirm
that it is his blood...
...you'll exhaust yourself
with conspiracy theories...
...as to how I planted it
or how it's all a lie.
And after enough time passes...
...you'll be left with one inescapable
truth that Oliver Queen is dead.
This is your fault.
Oliver went there because of you,
because of what you did to Thea.
You made her a target for the League
so he would have to challenge Ra's...
...just to save her.
You killed him.
You are right.
And I will live with that guilt
for the rest of my days.
I'm truly sorry.
- I can see how much you loved him.
- Save it, Merlyn.
You're enjoying this.
Miss Smoak is correct.
I orchestrated the matter...
...to eliminate the death
warrant Ra's placed on my head.
Oliver was that weight.
His death means my own.
Good.
What's that?
The blood analysis on the scimitar.
It's Oliver's.
99.997 percent match.
If Merlyn's lying,
he's being thorough about it.
Felicity.
Thanks for not saying "I told you so."
- I gotta go to work.
- You really don't.
It's fine.
Glad we know now.
Run for the exit. I'll cover you.
- What about you?
- You need to get the Alpha out of here.
- But...
- Away from them. Go.
No.
You had him. Why didn't you take the shot?
We need to get out of here now.
You know, it's weird. I don't think
I've ever actually seen you drink alone.
Are you okay?
Yeah. I just got some bad news
about a friend.
Anyone I know?
How are you doing?
Still freaking out, actually.
Worried about Ollie.
I was gonna ask you a favor,
but it doesn't seem like the right time.
Well, it depends. What's the favor?
You and the Arrow, you're close, right?
I mean, that's you I've been seeing
on the news in the red hood.
- Thea...
- Look, I haven't seen him.
I haven't heard from him.
He's not answering any of my phone calls.
I'm actually starting to
get really worried...
...so I thought maybe the Arrow
could look for Oliver.
I just thought maybe if you saw him,
you could ask.
Thank you. You're the best.
I better go check the stockroom.
Thea just asked me to talk to the Arrow...
...about finding Oliver.
- What'd you tell her?
- What else? I lied.
- Oliver didn't want Thea to know.
- That was then.
But now, what's the point?
I keep asking myself
the same question, Roy.
Then why do you keep combing over
the case evidence?
Because it helps me
keep my mind off of Oliver.
Doing this without him, while we're waiting
for him to come back, is one thing.
But doing all this without him, without
him, that's a whole other situation.
What do you want me to tell you?
I can only see one inch in front of me.
And this is the only thing
in front of me right now.
I keep looking at this file and...
- Something about it feels familiar.
- Yeah.
Felicity did say Fisher and Anton
were connected with Brick.
No, it's more than that.
I've seen this file somewhere...
...else.
- What are the chances that's a coincidence?
- Only one way to find out.
What are you doing?
Bringing up the case numbers
on all the guys...
...who were put away
over the past eight months.
- Some of these are guys that we caught.
- Yeah.
And others were apprehended
by the authorities.
There's a pattern here.
All these guys are awaiting trial
for assault...
...assault with intent to murder,
attempted murder.
Street enforcers. Muscle.
Why would Brick have a list
of these case numbers?
I'm sure you're wondering
if I ever go home.
Unfortunately for my assistant,
the answer is no.
Any luck with our nanite problems?
- No.
- Yeah, it's the transplex interface, isn't it?
I knew my designs were off.
It won't work.
- Yeah, you've only been at it for a day, so...
- Not the chip.
Not your suit.
Your plan.
It won't work.
You make it sound like
using an enhanced exoskeleton...
...to fight crime and save the city
is a Looney Tune idea.
It won't bring her back.
Anna.
Your fiancée.
- I know who she is.
- She's not coming back.
When we lose someone...
...when someone dies...
...they're gone...
...forever, and there is nothing...
There is nothing...
...nothing that we can do
that is going to bring them back.
So you have to stop.
You have to stop because
it's not what Anna would have wanted.
- It's...
- You're upset, I can see that.
And if you want, we can talk about it.
But never tell me again
what Anna would have wanted.
You don't get to do that.
I am sorry.
I shouldn't be here right now.
- What?
- We got something on Brick.
The blueprints we found,
they're schematics...
...for the warehouse where the police store
all physical evidence.
And Brick has a list of case numbers.
He might be looking to steal or destroy
evidence to get those cases thrown out.
Yeah. I'll call Lance, tell him.
A lot of these cases are guys
we've put away over the past eight months.
This is everything we've been doing
since we took Slade down.
This is everything Oliver was working for.
I'll be right there.
Three minutes.
Seal off every exit.
Give me a two-block perimeter.
John, shooter at your 5.
I'm out.
Here.
Use mine.
So here's the deal.
You take me down, you walk out alive.
I don't fancy your chances, though.
Smart man.
Nobody thinks about going for a head shot.
Shots fired.
I need an ESU and backup here now.
Felicity, where's Diggle? I'm pinned down.
Felicity.
Any last words?
Or are my hands too tight
around your neck?
I guess arrows work a little better
on this guy than bullets.
You Okay?
Yeah, I will be
after we find the son of a bitch.
Damn it.
Oh, my God, John.
It's okay. It's all right, I'm fine.
I'm fine.
- Brick?
- Got away.
They put one guard in the hospital,
but he's gonna pull through.
If that door hadn't shut,
we would've had him.
It's just our bad luck.
Unless it wasn't.
You were pinned down. You both were.
They were gonna kill you.
- Felicity.
- You did that?
They had machine guns.
You had a bow and arrow.
You let him get away?
I saved your lives.
Felicity, it wasn't your call to make.
It wasn't my call to let Oliver go challenge
Ra's al Ghul to a fight to the death either.
Brick has who knows how much evidence,
Felicity.
And it was either that or the two of you, my
friends being killed, so I made my choice.
I chose not to let anyone else
I care about die.
We've been in tough spots.
We've always managed to come out.
No.
Oliver did.
But he's not here anymore...
...because he's dead.
Okay.
The point is,
if we're gonna do this without Oliver...
...Felicity, we have to trust each other.
You don't get it.
There is no "this" without him.
It's done. I'm done.
I'm sorry...
...but I had no one else to turn to...
...and he needs your help.
I was out of line.
And I'm sorry.
You wanna tell me what had you so upset?
I lost a friend of mine.
He was more than a friend, actually.
He was...
I'm not sure what we were...
...but he's gone.
I'm sorry.
And three months ago,
another friend of mine died.
I'm 25 years old.
I'm over my quota
where losing friends are concerned.
And you're a friend.
So if you wanna go out there...
If you want to commit suicide,
I can't stop you.
But I don't have to help you.
Eight months to put them away...
...eight minutes to set them loose.
I'm sorry.
I tried.
Without the evidence,
the judge had to let them go.
He's not coming back.
Oliver.
I know you don't wanna believe it, Laurel.
God knows I don't, but...
He's not coming back.
Are you?
Are you coming back?
I don't know.
For the first time since
I met Oliver Queen...
...I don't know what happens next.
I know it's silly, but I...
...still like to think of myself
as Oliver's bodyguard.
I just couldn't protect him.
It's funny. He was worried
something would happen to me.
I could have killed you.
Heh. It's cute that you think so.
Did you hear anything about Ollie?
I'm afraid not.
Then what are you doing here?
We're in danger, Thea.
We need to leave Starling City
and never return.
Thank you all for coming.
But seeing as I'm the reason none of you
are sitting in a prison cell right now...
...I figure it's the least you could do.
And I'm the guy that made
all the evidence against you go away.
But as you can see...
...it didn't go too far.
You are all part of my crew now.
And if any of you
have a problem with that...
...I can send a gift-wrapped package
to the DA.
Together,
not only will we make a lot of money...
...we will make history.
Together,
we are gonna take over the Glades.
You think Brick's crazy?
Take over a whole section of town?
I know he's crazy.
I don't know what he's got planned,
but whatever it is, I'm in.
Who the hell are you?
I'm the justice you can't run from.
Well done, Mr. Queen.
I'm glad to know my investment in you
hasn't entirely been for naught.
Although I was disappointed to read
Agent Pearson's after action report.
You let one of Chien Na Wei's men
get away.
- I hesitated. It was a mistake.
- It really was.
Now we have no one to interrogate.
You mean, torture. Right?
I saw you with that man.
You didn't hesitate.
You chose not to shoot him.
I put the GPS from the file in his pocket,
and now he is gonna lead us right to Tatsu.
We are gonna get her back, Maseo,
I promise.
Oliver...
...what you've done...
...I will be forever in your debt.
Don't move. You'll pull out the sutures...
...Oliver.
Tatsu.
- How?
- I asked her to come here...
...so she could bring you back to life.