GREEN ARROW [IN NORMAL VOICE]:
Roy.
Where'd you go?
-Sorry.
-Get your head in the game.
We're in position.
So is the Culebra Cartel and their heroin.
They all showed up about 30 minutes ago,
haven't moved from your location.
GREEN ARROW:
Got it.
No sentries outside.
If we're gonna do this, we need to do it now.
I've got north entrance,
Dig's got south. Roy...
-East.
-The roof.
You're on overwatch.
The Culebras get their weapons
from the Bratva. All military grade.
I've got your backs.
Let's do this.
South's clear.
Nobody's home.
Roof's clear.
-North's empty too.
-Doesn't make sense.
They all showed up half an hour ago
and never left. They are in there somewhere.
Looks like somebody beat us here.
That's at least a few million dollars'
worth of heroin.
[SPEAKING IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
"He took Paco."
Whoever did this ignored the drugs...
...took a gang member.
This was personal.
Yeah, more than that. Whoever did this
was trying to send a message.
I think I know what it is.
"Guilty." Well, yeah. The Culebras
are the bloodiest gang in Starling.
The second bloodiest?
Culebras have a long-standing rivalry
with the Los Halcones.
-You said this was personal, not business.
OLIVER: And Paco?
There are only 86,000 Pacos in Starling.
Give or take 5000 for a few nicknames.
Something tells me the Culebras' rivals
will narrow that down for us.
We find Paco,
he'll be too dead to say anything.
I'm not looking for him,
I'm looking for whoever did this.
I will handle this. Take the rest of the night.
-I'll back you up.
-Not dead on your feet, you won't.
I'm sorry. I've been a little out of it recently.
Don't be sorry, be rested. I wouldn't be much
of a teacher if I let you get killed...
...because your reaction time is slow, okay?
Dig.
There are a lot of Halcones members
in Starling City.
How about I take the ones north
of 10th Street?
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
OLIVER:
You know, we've been waiting here an hour.
After walking around the block five times.
We need to work on your patience.
Where is this guy, all right?
More importantly, how is he gonna help us
find out what this China White person is...?
Chien Na Wei.
Whatever. How is he gonna help us find out
what she's doing in Hong Kong?
Waller hasn't been able to locate
Chien Na Wei because she avoids using...
-...any traceable forms of communication.
-What, so he's the target now?
He's her delivery guy.
Her courier. But he's not a target.
-Waller doesn't want you to kill him.
-That's refreshing.
He'll use a dead drop, leave behind
information for Chien's network.
-Information we'll intercept.
-I see him.
Stay on Bluetooth.
I'll be right behind.
What was that? Did he make you?
Yeah, I think he did.
[MAN YELLS]
[HORN HONKS THEN TIRES SCREECH]
He's gone.
-Where is it?
-Where's what?
The envelope. The message.
We need it. He stashed it somewhere
while you were chasing him.
-I didn't see him stash anything.
-Yes, you did. You just don't know it yet.
-That's not bad.
-It's better than "not bad."
[GRUNTING]
What the hell was that?
Today's lesson. Fighting's about
being surprised and not getting rattled.
You look rattled.
-Try angry.
-Another lesson, then.
It's not about you getting knocked to the mat.
It's if you get up.
Okay, fine.
Then let's go again.
Not tonight, all right? I gotta close up shop.
And you need to get some rest...
...let those muscles recover. Make sure
you get some protein within the hour, all right?
Yeah, egg whites. They're my new BFF.
That's disgusting.
No, no, no. Two blocks from here.
-Korean tacos.
-Korean tacos?
Trust me, they're heaven.
Come on, I'm buying.
-Hey, can I ask you a question?
-You just did.
Kidding. What?
-You know how to do a blood test, right?
-I know just enough to make me dangerous.
And, well, me holding a syringe,
well, that makes me more dangerous.
Why?
I need you to test my blood.
For what? And don't say STD's
because that would be crossing a line.
ForMirakuru.
I don't need to check you
for traces of Mirakuru.
-You were cured.
-I know, I...
If this is about your sleep problems, Mirakuru
makes people crazy strong and "crazy" crazy.
-It doesn't make it hard to get eight hours.
-Could...?
Are you okay?
I mean, besides
the whole not-sleeping thing.
Totally.
I'm fine. I'm just looking for reasons
to help me sleep, you know?
Okay.
[ALL GROANING]
I'm looking for a Culebra member
named Paco.
-Emilio?
-Paco!
That's what they call him, ése.
-Paco's his street name.
-Whose?
Emilio.
Emilio Ortega.
Thank you.
Felicity, I have a name.
Emilio Ortega.
Pinging his cell's GPS.
He's in the Glades, 9th and Hasen.
[DOOR OPENS]
[IN DISGUISED VOICE]
Why'd you kill all those men?
-What the hell are you talking about?
-What are you doing?
Get out of here.
Oh, my God.
-Now, Laurel.
-No.
Ted didn't do this.
Ted's been with me for the past two hours.
He trained with me
and then we went for dinner. And that...
He wasn't here when we left.
[WHIRRING]
Okay, that is 10 minutes of my life
I am never getting back.
-I'm clean?
-Your cholesterol is a little high...
...for someone of your age
but absolutely zero Mirakuru serum.
Congratulations.
-Thank God.
-Okay.
You're acting like I just told you
that the biopsy came back negative.
What is going on?
It's stupid.
You just had me test your blood for a serum
you were cured of six months ago.
I already knew it was stupid.
The reason I haven't been sleeping...
...is because I've been having dreams.
And not normal ones.
It was like I was remembering
the time I was out, you know?
When Slade OD'd me on the Mirakuru?
What do you remember?
Nothing much, just a feeling.
A feeling of being not me.
Of being strong...
...and out of control, but here's the thing:
In those dreams...
...I killed Sara.
This really had you worried.
Because the dreams, they didn't feel
like dreams, Felicity. They felt like memories.
I actually remembered
throwing arrows into her.
Crazy. Right?
Yeah.
Crazy.
LANCE:
So that's it?
LAUREL:
I was with him the whole time.
You can put me on the box if you'd like.
If I wanted to give my daughter a polygraph, I'd
have done it back when you discovered beer.
So listen, what's the story
with you and this guy anyway?
-He's my trainer.
-Who you went to dinner with?
As friends. But I know him,
and he would never do something like this.
We gotta hold him
till the coroner's findings come back.
And then if they're consistent
with his story, we'll cut him loose.
[TALKING INDISTINCTLY]
-[IN NORMAL VOICE] Well?
-Well, it's like I said, he didn't do it.
Why would a mass murderer
string up a body in his gym?
Ted caters to a pretty rough clientele.
A lot of career criminals, gangbangers.
He runs afoul of one now and again. He thinks
someone was trying to send him a message.
-Who?
-He says he doesn't know.
I wanna talk to him.
About this case, or me?
Two weeks ago,
I said I wouldn't train you to fight.
Now you have a trainer.
Who's training me to box.
To let off some steam. I think I have
a pretty good reason to have some.
-Keep your eyes open with this guy.
-He didn't do this.
Just the same.
Why are you sitting like that?
I'm concentrating.
Why?
-Because I need to remember something.
-Why?
Try this.
Pay attention.
Remember where the matching one is?
See? Your memory is fine.
MASEO:
He needs your help.
You need my help.
You know I don't like your friend.
This gaijin, he is trouble.
Well, I need him to remember what he saw.
When we capture Chien Na Wei,
my debt is paid.
All I care about is us getting home.
Then help me.
I love you.
You know that, right?
-Oh, come on, you must be cheating.
-I'm just better at this than you.
-Heh.
TATSU: Akio.
[IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
[YELLS IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
We're just playing a game.
[IN ENGLISH]
Mr. Queen...
...I will house you,
feed you and clothe you...
...but my son is off-limits.
Fine.
Stay.
What are you doing?
I'm helping you.
Now, do exactly as I say.
Ever heard of this Ted Grant?
Yeah, I saw his title fight
a few years back on pay-per-view.
Called him Wildcat. He was the real deal.
The body in his gym was strung up the same
way the bodies in the warehouse were.
Like punching bags.
-What if Laurel vouches for him?
-I don't think Laurel is seeing clearly on this.
If Grant's our doer, he's more than a boxer.
I hacked CSU's files
on the warehouse murders.
Culebras were armed to the teeth...
...but the killer, the psycho,
mass murder guy, never fired a shot.
-They were beaten to death by brass knuckles.
-That's a pretty specific MO.
Matches one murder six years ago.
Same. Culebra drug dealer.
Trauma consistent with brass knuckles
worn by a left-hander.
-Let me guess, Ted "Wildcat" Grant's a lefty.
-They called him the Starling Southpaw.
Well, S.C.P.D. never put that together
because Ted was never arrested.
[COMPUTER BEEPS]
He's moving.
You dinged him with a tracer?
Just because Laurel trusts him
doesn't mean I have to. Talk me in.
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[IN DISGUISED VOICE]
Second time I've found you with a body.
I've never killed anybody.
-I'm being set up.
-Why should I believe you?
Because I used to be a vigilante.
I used to be you.
The city has been hurting
long before you showed up.
I've never heard
of another vigilante in Starling.
It was six years ago.
I wasn't news. I stuck to the Glades.
And these are supposed to convince me?
Masks are also useful for serial killers.
Says the guy currently wearing one.
Who's that?
I don't know.
I've never seen him before in my life.
But this was hung around the body
that was found in my gym.
The key is to the storage locker.
-He's leaving me a trail to follow.
-Who is?
Whoever's setting me up.
Look, I've never killed anyone.
Except for that drug dealer
that you beat to death six years ago.
That was a mistake.
I may have avoided jail...
...but I have lived with the guilt of that
man's death every single day of my life.
I gave it all up after that.
I locked this place up
and I swore I'd never open it again.
-Who else knows about the locker?
-No one.
This is where I kept my supplies.
A safe place, separate from my day job.
-As I'm sure you've got one just like it.
-Mine's bigger.
Look, we're both trying to find out who
the hell's doing this. We could help each other.
LAUREL:
His name's Albert Mancini.
No criminal record,
aside from a few unpaid parking tickets.
-Grant doesn't know who he is.
-You believe him.
I haven't decided yet.
Do you know
that you're training with a vigilante?
Former, apparently.
And, no, I didn't. I didn't.
So you also didn't know that six years ago
he beat someone to death?
How many more reasons am I gonna have to
give you before you stay away from this guy?
Okay, are you guys just about finished
with your little private chat?
The guy from your storage unit...
...he has no criminal record.
He was a magician.
Magician's assistant, more accurately.
He worked with a local act before getting
cut loose. Mancini hasn't worked since.
Culebra Cartel, magician's assistant.
What's the connection?
TED:
Their act was at the Zanzibar.
Zanzibar's where the dealer was murdered.
You mean the person you beat to death?
I told you, whoever's doing this
is leaving me a trail to follow.
-Then we follow it.
-We need another minute.
How do you two know each other?
We used to date.
You cannot be serious.
-I am not on your team. I don't work for you.
-Exactly.
-You're untrained.
-Oh. Whose fault is that?
Does he know what's driving you?
I told him that Sara's gone.
But does he know that you wanna follow
in her footsteps?
You're playing
a very dangerous game, Laurel.
-I can handle it.
-No, you can't.
Because you haven't realized
that it's not actually a game.
Let's go.
-What about Laurel?
-She's not coming.
-Oliver has a 20 on our killer.
-I thought Oliver was tracking Grant.
Looks like things changed.
Suit up, he wants us to provide backup.
-Roy can't go.
-What?
-I need to talk to you. Something important.
-It can wait.
No, it can't. John?
I'll take care of it.
-What the hell was that about?
-We need to talk.
You made that clear.
Before we buried Sara, I scanned her body
using portable magnetic resonance imaging.
-You're really starting to freak me out.
-I basically created a virtual autopsy.
It's not as good as a regular autopsy...
...but like one, I can use it to determine things
an autopsy would...
...like angle of attack, trajectory
and the force of the arrows.
Felicity, what are you saying?
Things about the forensics
I couldn't reconcile with.
Specifically,
the angle and velocity of the arrows...
...were not consistent with a normal bow
or archer of normal height.
But if the arrows were thrown
with Mirakuru force...
What if there was some residual Mirakuru
in your system, would explain the forensics.
The angle and force of the arrows.
-But you said I tested negative for Mirakuru.
-There isn't any in your blood today...
...but if one last Mirakuruepisode
burned out any remnants in your system...
Episode?
You mean me killing Sara?
-I'm on site.
-Copy. Keep watching the perimeter.
-How many partners do you have, anyway?
-The Culebras, the body in your gym.
Body in your storage locker.
Someone's gone to a lot of trouble
to frame you and bring you here. Why?
What does all this have to do
with one killing six years ago?
Hello, Ted.
I see you got my messages.
Arrows.
Brass knuckles. I never knew why we
couldn't just use a gun the way they did.
We're better than they are.
At least, we're supposed to be.
That's almost ironic coming from you.
I trusted you.
OFFICER:
S.C.P.D.!
You're under arrest
for multiple counts of homicide.
What are you talking about? I didn't do this.
Yeah? Tell that to the stiff
we found in your locker.
Let's go.
DIGGLE: He got past me. He knew an exit out
of the building that wasn't on the blueprints...
-...that Felicity hooked me up with.
-You had Ted Grant arrested?
Your father's men found him at a crime scene.
A body was found at a storage locker...
...that he owns, along with evidence
of past vigilantism.
-No. He's innocent.
-I know.
-I saw the person who's doing this.
-Who is it?
He was wearing Ted's old gear.
Full face mask. Let's go.
Clearly Grant knows who's behind the mask.
Oliver, Laurel.
-I...
-What's up?
I have to...
Roy, don't.
-Let's just...
-I need to tell you something.
Okay.
I...
I killed Sara.
That doesn't...
You're not making any sense.
Why would you kill Sara?
It was the Mirakuru.
Roy had no memory of the attack.
No real memory, at least.
But he's been recalling fragments
of his Mirakuru exposure last year.
That, and suppressed memories
often resurface in dreams.
What...? This is insane.
Laurel, I'm so sorry.
-I'm really...
-Don't...
-Wait, Roy, where do you think you're going?
-Let him go.
I thought he was cured.
What we know about Mirakuru
is vastly outweighed...
-...by the things we don't know.
-What does that even mean?
That Roy killed my sister
and it's not his fault?
The arrows that killed Sara,
we pulled DNA off of them, didn't we?
I tested it against the sample of Roy's blood.
First thing I did.
And?
The results were inconclusive.
I can't process this right now.
Hey. Hey, look at me.
Focus on what you can process.
Ted knows who we're coming after.
I need you to find out who it is.
I can't. I can't. If Roy killed Sara...
If Roy killed Sara...
...then we will deal with it.
But right now, I need you to deal with Ted.
Okay?
Okay.
How sure are you?
There's other forensic evidence.
A virtual autopsy. In light of what Roy's
described, it sounds incriminating.
That, and his trouble sleeping
started right when Sara was killed.
My husband says you're having problems
remembering what you saw earlier today.
That's the problem.
I didn't see anything.
You see and hear far more than you think.
Hidden truths,
buried deep in your subconscious.
You saw something,
but your head is too busy.
You need to quiet it.
Close your eyes.
Take a deep breath.
In through your nose,
out through your mouth.
In...
...and out...
...and again.
You're floating in nothingness.
All that exists is your breath.
Any thoughts you have are clouds.
They just drift away.
I remember.
Sixteen murders.
Seventeen,
counting the one from six years ago.
That's more than Son of Sam,
less than Bundy.
Probably worth a miniseries, huh?
Maybe a book.
You became a defense attorney?
Can I talk to him for a minute?
[LANCE SIGHS]
You sure can pick them.
You okay?
I'm not the one facing a lifetime in prison.
-Who framed you?
-I don't know.
I can't help you
if you're gonna keep lying to me.
The Arrow saw you with him.
He knows you know who it is.
Hey.
If the DA's office refuses
to seek an indictment...
...the police have to release you.
But first, I'm gonna need you
to be straight with me.
Who is the man behind the mask?
His name is Isaac Stanzler.
Six years ago, the Culebras ran the Glades.
I thought it'd be a good idea
for families to live there...
...without worrying
about their kids getting shot.
So I decided to do something about it.
You became a vigilante.
Just like your friend in the green hood.
Without the green hood.
And what about Stanzler?
You know the guy that Arrow's been
running around with lately? The one in red?
Stanzler was my guy in red.
I guess you could call him my apprentice.
One night, we decided to go after this drug
dealer that was pushing crank near the school.
We tracked him
all the way to this nightclub...
And what happened?
That drug dealer...
...Isaac got to him first.
That murder from six years ago,
that wasn't you.
That was him.
-I hung it up after that.
-And what about Stanzler?
What happened to Isaac Stanzler?
I told him to get the hell out of Starling.
That I never wanted
to see his face ever again.
I cut him loose.
That's why I've been lying to you
this whole time, Laurel.
Everything that's happening is my fault.
No word from Laurel?
Not yet. According to S.C.P.D. e-mail traffic,
which I may or may not have hacked into...
...they are dropping the charges
against Ted Grant.
Let me go after Roy.
If he's experiencing side effects...
-...we can't leave him running around.
-So you bring him in, then what?
Oliver, this crusade of ours,
it's supposed to be about justice, right?
If that's supposed to mean something,
we can't have two sets of rules.
One for bad guys and one for us.
I'm the one who brought Roy
into this crusade.
And maybe it's time for you
to cut him loose.
-Are you telling me to abandon him?
-Yes, Oliver.
If that's what it takes
to find justice for Sara.
So, what do you think
Stanzler's next move is?
Framing me didn't work. I'm afraid
to think of what he might try to do next.
ISAAC:
What I should've done from the start.
After you abandoned me
the Culebra found me.
They wanted payback for the man they lost.
They tortured me for months
before I escaped.
Isaac, I'm so sorry. I didn't know.
[GUN COCKS]
But, come on, let's talk about this.
Oh, don't worry, we will.
There's so much I have to say
before I kill you.
-Where are we going?
-Just drive.
Hey, your beef is with me.
Okay, you got me. Let her go.
Taking innocent people hostage?
Man, I taught you better than that.
-They're not people, they're criminals.
-Albert Mancini wasn't.
You still strung him up in that nightclub.
You taught me that there are no innocents
when you abandoned me to the Culebras.
You gave me direction, purpose.
And then when things got tough,
when I really needed you...
...you weren't there.
[RINGING]
It's Laurel.
-Put her on speaker.
ISAAC: I hated you so much for that.
-That voice, that's him.
-I was just a kid, okay?
You were supposed to know better.
Call's coming from Laurel's cell.
Moving fast, 45 miles an hour.
They're in her car.
-They're headed north on Route 17.
-Keep that line open.
Isaac, I'm sorry.
I had no idea.
Eyes on the road.
Don't stop.
-Who was that, huh? Who was it?
-I don't know.
The only friend I ever had was you.
Hey.
TED:
Another vigilante.
Looks like we started a movement.
Go, go, go!
[TIRES SCREECHING]
GREEN ARROW: Get Grant.
TED: Get Laurel.
[BOTH GRUNTING]
Don't you get it? He's using you.
You're not a human being to him.
You are just another weapon in his arsenal.
And the second you do something wrong,
he'll turn his back on you.
He will abandon you.
I'm not you.
Don't abandon me.
Never.
[FOOTSTEPS]
You planning on hiding
in the shadows all night?
That's a good trick.
Used it once or twice myself back in the day.
Thank you.
[IN DISGUISED VOICE]
Thank me by doing something for me.
-Name it.
-Stay away from Laurel Lance.
She's in a vulnerable place,
and I don't want her getting hurt.
Did you bother to ask her what she wants?
Because that's her choice.
-If she stops coming, that's fine.
-She'll stop coming.
You know, you did me a solid, so let me
repay you with a little hard-won advice.
Learn from my mistake.
What I did, what you do...
...this playing judge and jury...
...it messes with people's heads.
It messed with Isaac's. I just waited
till it was too late to cut him loose.
Don't make the same mistake
with that kid you're running around with.
Ted, your mistake wasn't cutting him loose.
It was losing faith in him.
OLIVER: Hi.
-Hi.
How you feeling?
Worst part about sobriety
is having to pass on the pain meds.
Right. Thought maybe
you could use a ride home.
And an "I told you so"?
I don't think that I owe you one of those.
When I said I wouldn't train you,
I was trying to protect you.
But a homicidal former vigilante apprentice
was not what I had in mind.
I know you were trying to protect me, Ollie,
but I'm not helpless.
I've never seen you that way. But, Laurel,
I'm always gonna watch out for you.
It's not because I think you're helpless.
It's because I care about you.
And what about Roy?
Do you trust me?
I'm gonna miss this.
I feel like I was just starting to get good at it.
OLIVER:
You are getting good at it.
That guy...
...he said I was just another weapon
in your arsenal.
Well, maybe that's what
we should call you, then.
Arsenal.
I don't know why you would ever
let me suit up after what I did.
It doesn't matter anyway,
because I'm gonna be turning myself in.
[SIGHS]
Okay.
There's something you need to know, Roy.
Something that your mind
has been trying to tell you.
And I think it best...
...if you help me let it.
With a candle?
With meditation.
To clear your thoughts, find hidden truths.
[SIGHS]
This is weird.
You're hurting.
But it's not for the reasons that you think.
And I've been afraid
that if I just came out and told you...
...it would only make the hurt worse.
-Do you trust me?
-Always.
Good. Close your eyes.
And focus on your breathing.
In through your nose...
...out through your mouth.
[BREATHING DEEPLY]
In, out.
Floating along, weightless.
And the only thing that exists is your breath.
Now your thoughts are like clouds.
They drift away.
[GASPS]
Let go, Roy.
I killed him.
-The police officer. Why didn't you tell me?
-You were overdosed on Mirakuru...
...you didn't remember.
And I was hoping you never would.
But Felicity told me you had a dream
that you killed Sara and I realized...
It was a memory.
I think because of the way
Sara was murdered...
...the fact they used arrows...
...brought it to the surface.
-So I didn't kill Sara?
-No.
But I am a murderer.
-Roy...
-No, I just need to be alone for a while.
This is it.
This is the dead drop.
What kind of a message is this?
MASEO:
Have you ever heard of steganography?
Is that the dinosaur
with the plates on its back?
It's the art of concealing a message
within another message.
In this case...
...within an image.
"Li Kuan Hui."
-Who's that?
-I do not know.
But if Chien Na Wei is interested in him,
so are we.
Hey, it worked.
-Thank you.
-I don't want your gratitude.
There's only one thing I want from you.
Name it.
Get out of our lives as soon as possible.
Sign says closed. Learn to read.
LAUREL:
I thought you might make an exception.
Yeah? And why would I do that?
Because I just made sure your past vigilantism
fell under the statute of limitations.
No new charges will be filed.
Much obliged.
But you still shouldn't be here.
No, this is exactly where I should be.
Last night, when Isaac had me at gunpoint,
when he was shooting at my friends...
...I should have been so scared.
Rattled.
But I wasn't.
I saw what needed to be done, and I did it.
Because you taught me.
I've just been teaching you
how to throw a proper jab.
And your pal Robin Hood
doesn't want me even doing that.
I want you to give me the tools
to avenge my sister's death.
I want you to teach me
to get justice outside of a courtroom.
I took on an apprentice once...
-...didn't work out so good.
-Well, it's like you said...
...it's not about how you get
knocked down to the mat.
It's about whether you get up.
-Yaah!
-Uhn!
Who the hell are you?
I'm Cupid, stupid.
[ARROW WHIZZING]