My name is Oliver Queen.
After 5 years in Hell,
I returned home
with only one goal--
to save my city.
But I couldn't honor that
commitment
and honor the promise I made
to the mother of my son,
so I asked the best man I know
to help.
His name is John Diggle,
and he is the Green Arrow.
Previously on "Arrow"...
Could you tutor me
some more before the test?
See you soon.
She's pretty cool.
His life will be better
with you in it
just like mine.
Cayden James--he's the most skilled hacker
the world has ever known.
8 months ago, he was
scooped up by Argus,
and now he's being held
without cause,
being tortured,
who knows what else?
Helix is about to extract
Cayden James.
-1...
-2...
3.
Bad Laurel--
she wasn't dead
when we found her
back on Lian Yu.
Buy you a drink?
Whiskey, neat.
Are you waiting
for someone?
Is it too cheesy
if I say you?
I'll let it slide
this time.
What about you?
Let me guess.
You're a numbers guy.
You sit in front
of a computer all day,
and you came here
to blow off some steam.
You got me pegged.
I think the bartender
forgot your order.
I have a better idea.
Uh-oh. Looks like
I know your dirty, little secret.
Oh, it's...
Shh.
I won't tell
if you won't tell.
All right. You know
my secret. Now...
Tell me one of yours.
Ok.
Only if you promise
not to tell anyone.
Cross my heart
and hope to die.
♪ Arrow 6x04 ♪
Reversal
Original Air Date on November 2, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Well, William did an
excellent job picking out your tie.
Yeah. He was
very excited.
He wanted to come
to dinner.
I told him that Raisa
was his date tonight.
Oh. Well, she's
a lucky woman.
Has it, um,
really been 3 years
since the first time
we did this?
Yeah. Let's just hope
that this date goes
better than that one.
I think it will.
Don't jinx it.
Masked gunmen could
come through the door,
and it would have been
better than our first dinner.
Only because we were
not being blown up.
Well, you know, also
because I wasn't ready,
not the way I am now.
Well, now the time
is right.
Yeah.
Mr. Mayor.
- Yes?
- I--I'm sorry to interrupt.
I just wanted to say
that I'm voting
against that awful
anti-vigilante referendum.
Oh, that's
very nice to hear.
Are you two
back together?
Such a sweet couple.
Uh, well, enjoy
your dinner.
Thank you. Don't forget
to vote, ok?
You pay her
to say that?
I had absolutely nothing
to do with that.
Hmm. Well, I am the mayor's
girlfriend now,
so does that get me
a break on my taxes
or maybe a pass
on jury duty?
I mean, I--I was gonna
offer to bring you
to a fundraiser.
Ehn.
I can not tell you
what it is
if you're gonna keep
making that face.
No. Sorry.
It's just, you know...
With Overwatch
and the startup
with Curtis
and, you know, our old
but new relationship,
maybe we could...
Ease into
some of the things.
Of course, of course.
I love rolling
to those things solo.
Yeah, you're lying.
I'm kidding.
I'm--I'm really happy
that you're busy,
and I'm especially excited
for--for this thing
with Curtis
because it--
truth be told,
it is important that
you have something
in your life that is not
just the--
The team.
Yes.
No. I mean...
The team.
This is how it felt
to be you, isn't it?
Oh, yeah.
I'm sorry.
Go.
What's going on?
Body dropped outside
of a bar.
Dinah's on the scene
with SCPD.
The Vic was
dead on arrival.
Paramedics are calling it
internal hemorrhaging,
but I'd recognize this kill
from a mile away.
Sonic scream did this
an inch from his ear.
- Ouch.
- Laurel.
Witnesses saw the Vic
leaving with a woman, a brunette.
Maybe Laurel got
a wig.
According to witnesses,
they were very handsy
with each other
on the way out.
What do you guys think?
Black Siren turned
black widow?
You know, because she
mates and then kills.
Mm-hmm.
Dinah, thanks.
We'll take it from here.
Victim was an accountant
named Jackson Klimavich.
No criminal record,
boring job,
really boring
Upswipz profile.
Well, he was married,
so maybe not so boring.
Boring and scummy.
Sorry. Had to help Lance
finish up the polling analysis.
Star City stands
at 70% against
the anti-vigilante
legislation.
That's 70%
for us, accounting
for the double negative
you just used.
Yeah, but after everything this team
has done for the city--
- You'd think it'd be higher.
- Yeah.
What'd I miss?
Evil Laurel seduced
a guy
and then killed him.
Why?
That's what we
have to figure out,
but first,
we have to find her.
Laurel's been in the wind
way too long.
We're on it.
Speaking of being on it,
did you mail out
our articles
of incorporation? Heh.
For our startup.
The documents required
to, you know,
start it up.
Oh, my God. They are
in a Manila envelope
on my countertop
with every intention of mailing them.
I was just telling Oliver how
I'm being stretched too thin.
Wait a minute.
What do you mean by just?
We were at dinner, and
then I got your text.
- Felicity.
- No. It's the job. It's ok.
No, no, no.
This is all on me.
I 911ed you over
one dead body.
Can you still make it
out to dessert?
Well, no. We have to
find evil Laurel.
No, no, no. I will find
evil Laurel.
You go out there
and take your ass back
and get your man.
- Are you sure?
- Are you kidding me?
I was, like, you guys'
bigger shipper.
I feel like the reconciliation
taking effect
is, like, kind of
on me.
- You're amazing.
- All right. I'm terrific.
- Well...
- Is that getting old?
- I kind of like it.
- You like?
- Yeah. Oh, I need this.
- Still cool. All right. Go, go.
Finally. I thought you were gonna
keep me waiting here all night.
Patience is how wars
are won, miss Lance.
Well, first battle's
already over.
Hmm.
Look. I don't know
if this is your first
clandestine meeting,
but at this point,
most people would say "thank you."
For foe item
or for leaving a body
for the police to find?
Better than a witness
to question.
Any reservations,
concerns about what
comes next?
Of course not.
This one shouldn't
be a problem.
Glad to hear it.
Till we meet again.
I'm so sorry that I had to
bail on dinner,
but I'm--I'm home now
if you want to, uh, come by
for some dessert.
Yes. Yes. That was
intentionally suggestive.
Ok. Uh, well, good.
I'll see you soon.
Nice try,
but I wasn't born--
- Alena.
- You always announce
your attacks
like that?
What are you doing
in my apartment?!
You think a computer
hacker would know better
than to install
a smart-lock on her door.
I mean, what are you
doing...here?
I need your help.
You you
or--or Helix you?
- Does it matter?
- Let's pretend for a second
that it does.
Who gave you that?
Cayden James.
He's working
on something terrible,
something that will hurt
the entire world,
and I need your help
to stop him.
I helped you break
Cayden James out
of Argus custody.
I went against my friends,
I went against my team
because you told me
that Cayden James was a good man.
You did it because Cayden could
help you find Adrian Chase,
and he delivered.
So at what point did he become
a criminal mastermind?
I don't know.
At some point
during his 8 months
in Argus custody.
They held him in a glorified
shipping container, Felicity.
Nutrition withholding,
sensory deprivation.
They broke him.
Well, in that case,
he should be
in a funny farm
somewhere.
He shouldn't be planning
the end of the world.
Actually, how do I know
that you being here
isn't part of his plan?
Because I could never
go along with what
I suspect he's planning,
Felicity.
I am a hacktivist,
not a monster.
You say he has plans
to hurt the world? How?
I don't know exactly
what he is planning,
but I saw
a casualty estimate,
and the most conservative
estimate is 4% collateral damage.
4% of what?
The world population.
That's almost
300 million people.
If we try and hack
his servers,
we might be able to
figure out what he's planning.
Ok. Where is he now?
Corto Maltese,
but I came here because...
I didn't know who else
to reach out to.
Will you help me?
We set Cayden James
loose, Alena.
Of course
I'm helping.
Looks like the same M.O.
Did Laurel also
make out with this one first?
It's a legitimate
investigatory question.
Cause of death was the same.
This was
definitely Laurel.
Yeah. Victimology
was similar, too,
insofar that this woman
is just as boring as the first guy.
College librarian
may even be more boring.
Maybe Laurel's
killing for sport.
Doesn't sound like her.
Black Siren's not the Laurel you
remember, remember?
Any word on
tracking her down?
Nothing useable
from the CCTV cams
we found on either
crime scene.
Forensics is
a dead end, as well.
- And Felicity?
- I tried texting her,
but she hasn't
hit me back.
Fine. Let's hit
the streets.
Someone has to be
able to help us find Laurel.
What about me?
Um, I want to hit the streets, too,
and maybe a couple
of bad guys.
Curtis, with Felicity AWOL,
we need tech.
Keep working
that angle.
I--I've been working
Another dead end.
Did you try spoofing
the subarray?
- Yeah.
- Ok. What about the--
Yeah, but these
firewalls are crafted.
I mean, the protection
protocols are just...
- Art.
- Well, I was gonna say
impenetrable,
but yeah, that, too.
Cayden'd be the only one
who could get onto Cayden's system.
Oh, my God.
You're a genius.
We need to convince
Cayden's system that we're him.
That's like saying
all we need is a trillion dollars.
No, no, no. We have to work
off Cayden's system.
I told you he's
in Corto Maltese.
Yeah, but Helix
is right here.
We cleared the place
out, Felicity.
- It's sanitized.
- But what about the wiring,
the digital
infrastructure?
That's proprietary,
Cayden's own design.
We left that in place.
That'll work.
Let's get the gear.
Does that include
a ghost drive
because we're gonna need that to get
into Cayden's system.
I know a guy.
Whoa! What's all this?
Oh, just some stuff
for a startup
that Curtis and I are
trying to start up.
Oh, good for you.
You guys are funded?
Well, seed money
from our reputation
of being geniuses at Palmer Tech,
though I'd feel
more like a genius
if I knew what we were starting up.
We're thinking something
in the smarthome area.
- You're joking.
- No.
You left Helix--
I was kicked out
of Helix by you.
To make home appliances?
I thought you wanted
to change the world.
to change the world,
and look where you
ended up.
Sorry. That's--
I didn't--
No. We should go.
We should go.
Ok. We good?
Mm-hmm.
Oliver!
Hi. What are you
doing here?
You invited me.
That's right.
What is she
doing here?
Hi. Heh.
I'm just gonna
go over there.
Ok. Come in.
I know how much you love
to say, "I told you so"--
- No, that's you.
- So consider this
an early Christmas gift.
Cayden James is
a bad person,
and he's planning on
doing a bad thing.
Are you sure that
you can trust her?
I wouldn't exactly
use the word "trust."
Then wherever you're
going, I'm going, too.
No. This isn't your life
anymore. No.
At least tell the team
what you're doing.
I will tell them.
I will call them on my way,
and then when I am done,
we can finish dinner, starting with dessert.
Alena!
Didn't you know you guys
were back together.
Sure are.
Excuse me.
Ohh!
Here you go.
I'm such a klutz.
Don't worry. Me, too.
I love your shoes.
They're so cute.
Custom-designed.
Girls can rock limited edition
kicks, too, right?
Absolutely.
I'm Dinah, by the way.
Jenny.
It's really nice
to meet you.
I don't know why
I didn't think of this sooner.
Laurel's cry resonates
in the terahertz range,
which can be triangulated
according to geography.
Was I supposed to
understand a single word of that,
or are you talking
to yourself?
Sorry. Short version is
I think I figured out a way
to find evil Laurel
by tracking her Sonic cry.
Meaning if we she uses
it we can find her.
Yeah, only problem
being it means someone's
probably in trouble--whoa!
Talk about timing.
Yeah. So that means
she just used it, right?
- Mm-hmm.
- Where?
A parking garage
between Marleau and Hainesly.
- I'll tell John and Rene.
- Mm-hmm.
Nothing on level C.
D is clear.
A is empty,
except for a sweet-ass Corvette
someone left overnight.
Guys...
We're too late.
Actually,
you're right on time.
My mistake for dawdling,
I guess.
It's just--it's just
she's so, so pretty.
I really wanted to
hold her hand
until the end came.
You are one
twisted bitch.
That really
hurts my feelings.
Unh.
- She's gone.
- Good work tracking her down.
Don't give me points
for being late.
Call it in.
Ok. You couldn't have
told me to change?
Well,
you look great.
We here for a GMD or
an acid trip-techno freak show?
Both if you want.
Ok. So the dealer's
name is Amnesiac,
but I have no idea
how to find him.
Well...
Whoa! Ok. Rude.
Maybe that door guarded by the 3
scary dudes with chains for brains.
They look friendly.
Hello.
- You lost?
- No. We're here to see...
- Amnesiac.
- Mm-hmm. Yep.
Now.
Ok! That turned!
I don't think we
should go in here.
Hands off!
Easy, chrome dome!
Forgive
my thuggish compatriots.
I pay them to uphold
a certain aesthetic.
You're Amnesiac?
Your shock is exactly
what this establishment
aims to cultivate.
Now what brings you here?
We need a ghost
mirror drive.
- What for?
- That's our business.
And selling
illegal tech is mine,
and I only get to stay
in business by avoiding
legal entanglements.
Everything about you two
screams narc.
Well...
No, no, no!
Don't shoot. It's me!
Oliver?
Are you ok?
No! What the hell
are you doing here?
Trying to keep you safe.
I saw the guys take you!
Yeah. Those guys
were taking me to this guy,
who was gonna give us
what we needed to stop Cayden James,
but now they won't because you kicked
the crap out of them.
God.
You screwed up
everything.
He said he thought
you were police.
You know, me not
wanting your help tonight
doesn't have to do with me
just needing to do this alone.
It has to do with me
wanting to protect you.
I was trying to
protect you.
You are under
24/7 surveillance
from the FBI right now.
What if somebody
saw you?
I can handle it!
What I cannot handle
and will not stand for
is you going off
after a criminal without backup.
I get that,
but I don't need that right now.
What I need...
What I need is
a ghost mirror drive,
and I need to get Alena out of here
before they all come to.
- Felicity.
- We will talk about this later.
Another boring
person.
Disrespect
the dead much?
He's right. No connections,
no money to speak of,
no apparent benefit
to killing 3 different people at random.
They weren't random.
Autopsies finally came
back on all 3 victims.
Apart from all 3
being thoroughly unremarkable,
they had one other
thing in common.
All 3 had traces
of Dimotex 75 on their hands.
Dimotex is
an adhesive polymer.
It's used on the streets
to rip off fingerprints.
Laurel was stealing
fingerprints.
Why would
somebody want to collect
the fingerprints
of 3 nobodies?
And I disrespect
the dead?
They're not nobodies.
They're invisible.
Boring jobs,
no connection
to community.
What makes them remarkable
is just how
unremarkable they are.
What are you saying,
Hoss--I mean, boss?
What if these people's
backgrounds are just a cover?
They're boring
by design to be invisible.
So you're saying they're all
some kind of covert operatives?
They could be anything,
but whatever they're
dealing with is big enough
that they needed a cover.
Be nice to know.
Then we could figure out
who Laurel's going
after next.
Anybody got
a crystal ball?
I might not be able
to figure out where she's headed,
but I might be able
to figure out where she was.
Now, Sonic cries leave
ripples in the air.
I might be able to
backtrace where Laurel's been
and maybe even find out
a pattern,
maybe even determine where
she's operating out of.
I heard two mights
and two maybes, but I'll take it.
In the meantime,
I'll try to raise Felicity.
If anyone can hack
through these covers
to these people's
real identities, it's her.
Wow. Love what you
haven't done with the place.
The cat-5 hookups are
there and back there.
Yeah. One sec.
Hey, John.
Hey. Did you decide
to take a vacation?
Uh, no. Sorry. I just
have a situation here.
Yeah. Well, Curtis
told me about the startup.
No. This isn't
about the company.
This is about Cayden James,
and I don't have time to talk to you about it
right now,
but you were right,
and I was wrong about
breaking him out of Argus.
- Felicity, listen.
- I'm in Helix right now.
I'm just gonna clear up
the situation real quick.
I will be back at the bunker
before you know it, I promise.
All right, but get back here
soon. We need you.
I'm on it.
Got it! The mights
and maybes have paid off.
Ok. Backtracing Laurel's
sound waves produced
a probabilistic curve
of geolocations, which I canvassed
by means of cameras
of various sorts.
Curtis, less how,
more what.
I found
a probable location
for Laurel's
base of operation.
Tasking
a keyhole satellite.
When was this?
10 seconds ago.
Anybody know that guy?
How about that one?
Never seen him
before.
I have. We should go.
Felicity's in trouble.
Every file
in here is labeled Arclight.
Must be a code name
for whatever James is planning.
Now the question is,
what is the plan?
You're supposed to
be in Corto Maltese.
This is Cayden James?
No, miss Smoak.
I'm Cayden James.
Very nice to finally
make your acquaintance.
In case you're curious
about why I'm here,
it's not nostalgia.
It's you. We never
finished our conversation
in Corto Maltese,
which is
where you thought I was,
because you've been
pinging my cell.
I was hurt, truly.
Not the betrayal
so much as the naivete
of someone I thought
had potential.
I'm sorry, miss Smoak.
I'm afraid you're what's
known as collateral damage.
Horrible waste
of talent.
Make it as humane
as possible.
One shot.
You won't even know.
Get down!
Get down.
How'd you guys
know we needed you--
not that I'm complaining.
Felicity.
Oh! Alena!
Call an ambulance!
Stay with me.
Alena.
It's bad.
It's really bad.
Alena!
How is she?
Stabilized.
The next couple hours
will tell her story.
Um, I air-gapped
her IC room just in case.
If Cayden
tried to kill her
by hacking her
hospital equipment, he can't.
Hey.
You all right?
Am I all right
that I broke
a genius madman
out of prison
who's apparently working
with the psychopath
version of Laurel?
Am I ok that I didn't
see what was right in front of my face
and now Alena
might die?
What the hell
do you think?
Sorry. It's not you
I'm mad at.
I know that,
but right now, we need you.
I know. Curtis.
All set. Did everything just
like you told me.
I softened the beach, so now you can,
you know, do your thing.
Well, I couldn't do that before
because of Cayden.
All right.
I'm in.
Oh, John was right.
They were hiding
their identities
because they are
really important.
John thought they were
some kind of spies or something.
More like something.
All 3 are access managers to the IDND,
International Domain Name Directory.
Let's just pretend
for a second
only you and Felicity
know what that is.
The Internet is run
on domain names.
You start messing
with them,
and you start collapsing
whole parts of the Internet.
So Laurel's stealing
fingerprints?
To gain access, I guess.
But why steal 3 sets
of fingerprints?
Wouldn't one
do the job?
No. The Internet is
divided into sections
so not one person can
take it down all at once,
and each manager
controls a section.
And all 3 would be needed
to access the master vault,
which oversees
all sections.
All right. So Cayden James wants to
take down the Internet.
Can he actually do that?
If you destroy
the vault, yes.
And then what,
I can't send an e-mail?
I mean, so what?
No. The Internet controls
everything now--
electricity, water supply,
hospital equipment.
Also planes, trains,
and automobiles.
Alena said that Cayden's
casualty estimate was
300 million people.
Actually, that sounds low.
Yeah. I don't disagree.
This is all my fault.
All right.
Let's keep our focus here.
So James and his
people want to hit this vault.
Do we have
a location on it?
The location is
so classified
that they don't even
have a word for how classified it is.
Be that as it may,
I have a hack running
that will give us
the location soon.
Good, which
means you can get home,
take a shower,
clear your head maybe.
I'm fine.
It's not a request,
Felicity.
- Hey.
John told me
what happened.
Hmm. So I'm guessing
this little visit
is his idea
of therapy.
Actually, I'm thinking
that he probably
wanted you to speak
to one of the world's leading experts
in guilt and regret.
Hmm.
What's happening now
is not your fault.
Is that what I sounded
like all these years?
No. You sounded
smarter.
How did you do it?
How did you balance
being the Green Arrow,
the mayor, a boyfriend,
a brother?
How did--
How did you do it
all by yourself?
I--I d--I didn't
do it all by myself.
I had you.
Yeah. Well, I know
you're just saying that
to get boyfriend points,
and it's working.
I'm being serious,
Felicity.
Even if we weren't
together,
you were always
there with me,
always there to talk
me out of stuff,
to help me being
the Green Arrow.
You were literally
in my ear
every second
that I was in the field,
and that's why I
followed you
to the club tonight--
because I--I wanted
the chance to be there
for you
the way that you've
been there for me.
Well, then what
would I say to you
in this situation?
You would tell me
that when I--you--
ahem--freed Cayden James,
"I did it" because
at the moment,
at that time in your heart,
you thought it was right.
Yeah.
But you would tell me
not to live in the past.
You would tell me
to make it right in the present.
to trust myself.
Well, I am very smart,
apparently.
So smart.
Sorry. This is
becoming a habit.
It is, and I am
incredibly proud.
Please.
I have a wife
and two little girls.
Shh. I know.
I had a family once.
I appreciate your zeal,
miss Lance,
but we just need people
down, not dead.
Do I question
your method?
Oh, a little
gratitude, please.
Were it not for me,
you would have either starved
or bled to death
on Lian Yu.
The pre-Socratic philosopher
Thales of Miletus,
known as the father
of science,
believed that
for any event
there was a natural cause,
even if we couldn't see it...
And he thought that
with perfect knowledge
man could control
anything...
everything.
You're just full of surprises,
aren't you?
Oh, I'm just beginning.
Welcome
to the inner sanctum.
He's gone.
Biometric hand scanners.
So cool except
for the dead body part.
Stay sharp.
This place
is huge.
Yeah. Well, it has
to be big to hold,
you know,
the whole Internet.
This way.
Cayden's overclocking
the vault CPU.
- English, Felicity.
- He put a virus in the system
that's gonna make
the whole thing explode.
That's a bit
too much English.
How much time do we have
before the vault goes boom?
6 minutes. I think
I can stop the virus.
I just need-- I just need one--
I just need one minute.
There's no way Cayden James and Laurel
are gonna let you
just stand there
and do that.
You weren't wrong.
Your men have
engaged the targets.
Our men, miss Lance.
This partnership is
a democracy after all.
Oh. Miss Smoak just
appeared on the server.
Clever girl.
Her ingenuity
never disappoints.
I'm coding a little
something to occupy her...
While I take my leave.
Do the same
for her friends, would you?
No, no, no, no, no.
"No" is not what we
want to hear right now.
Cayden just used the processor's
firewall to block me out.
I can't take down
the virus remotely now.
I'm gonna have to do it on site before
he turns this whole place into an ashtray,
not to mention, you know,
the Internet.
- Where's the processor?
- Northwest quadrant.
Fine. We'll cover
you. Delta formation.
Fall back!
We're
outgunned here.
We've got you covered.
Can you handle this?
I can handle it. Just keep
them off me for 4 minutes.
Go, go, go, go, go!
Maybe doing this solo
wasn't such a good idea.
Good thing you're
not alone.
- Oliver?
- Well, technically,
if I'm in this chair,
that makes me Overwatch.
- You're in the bunker?
- I am. You ok with that?
I am all right with that.
I am so all right with that.
I'm epically
all right with that,
especially if you have
eyes on this complex.
I think I do.
You've automated the system
to the point that William could
basically operate it.
Do you see the room
in the far northwest quadrant?
I do, but I also see
10 hostiles between you and it,
so let me put you
on the safest path.
Take the corridor
to your left.
Are you sure
about that?
Sorry. Right. Right.
My left. Your right.
There's a little
bit of a learning curve here.
Overwatch, sitrep.
Overwatch, what's
your situation?
She's fine.
Stop.
Go right.
Under the door.
3, 2, 1.
Coast is clear.
Good.
I'm in.
Cayden's not here.
Time to get to work.
Company,
nine o'clock.
I knew you would be
around here somewhere.
Well, I couldn't
stay away from you
except for you've
changed something about yourself.
I just can't quite put
my finger on it.
Here. Let me
help you with that.
So it's a crossbow.
That's cute.
Two more hostiles inbound.
Ohh!
Oh! Thank you for that!
Just wanted to give you
a little time.
Yeah. Well, I'm gonna
need it.
I have to break
through the processor's
protective firewall to stop
Cayden's virus,
and the fact that the processor
is exponentially overclocking
and he's disabled
the cooling system.
Did not understand
a single word that you just said.
Oh, well, you understand
blaring noises
and really scary
lights, right?
I know this.
You can do it.
I believe in you.
Time to go.
- Thanks.
- No problem.
If this place is
gonna go boom,
let's not be here
when it does.
Overwatch, how we
doing?
Overwatch?
Good job.
And we're not dead.
Told you.
You know, if this whole
role reversal thing sticks around,
you're really gonna have to
adopt my saying
of not saying
"I told you so."
You tell me
you told me so.
Yeah, but not
all the time. Heh.
Thank you.
Well, I'm just glad
I found a way to help.
Heh. You always do.
Thank God we saved
the Internet.
My fantasy football team
was killing it this year.
So this new
partnership--
is it permanent?
Certainly hope not.
I think mayor Queen's
probably too busy
to be moonlighting
as tech support.
Besides, after all
those years in the field,
it'd be a shame if you
went down for carpal tunnel.
All kidding aside--
ahem--
we need to focus
on why Laurel has aligned
herself with Cayden James.
Those operatives,
they were the same ones
that we took out
last month.
Sorry. Old habits.
I will leave you to it.
I'll come with you.
Gonna go tell Alena
the good news.
Thank you.
No, no. No need
to thank me.
Saving the world is
kind of what we do,
that and fixing
our mistakes.
None of this is
on you, Felicity.
I vouched for Cayden.
You were just
backing my play.
Yeah. Well, like you
said, he changed.
Yeah.
Now that you're
no longer working
for an evil uberhacker--
I'm just assuming--
Mm-hmm.
Do you know what you're gonna do
when you get out of here?
Oh. I'm gonna
take some time
and gain some
much needed perspective
and then maybe,
if you'll have me,
come work
for you at your startup.
Yeah. That'd be great.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, you should.
I mean, maybe
in a year or two,
Curtis and I will actually have an idea
of what to develop.
Oh, I actually--I have
a pitch for you on that.
- Yeah?
- Mm-hmm.
Why did you get fired
from Palmer Tech?
Well, besides me being
lousy at balancing my time
and working
with the team,
the board actually
violently resisted my--
efforts to replicate
your spinal implant.
Yeah.
You've been looking
for something to work on,
something that
would change the world,
and you've literally been sitting
on the right idea this whole time.
I couldn't figure out
a way to affordably
mass produce the implant
at Palmer Tech.
Now you have Curtis
and no board oversight.
You know, Curtis and I
have actually had a really hard time
coming up with a name
for the company,
almost as hard of a time
as we've had for a concept,
so I was wondering
how you would feel
about me appropriating
the name Helix?
Well, I think you don't
generally need to worry
about criminal hackers
coming after you
for trademark
infringement...
That's true.
And I think it
would be really nice
to see something good
come out of that name.
Helix Dynamics.
That rolls off
the tongue nicely.
Cool logo possibilities,
easily engravable on a Nobel medal.
Funny. Those are
Curtis' criteria, too.
- Heh heh.
- It's possible.
A reward for a job
only half done?
A means of preventing them
from tracking you
by way of your
Sonic scream,
and the job was done
to perfection.
I thought the objective
was to take down the Internet.
No. The objective was
to take down the firewall
protecting the vault,
and miss Smoak was
most adept in complying.
Why couldn't you
find a way to do it yourself?
I've been doing this
too long to leave trails, miss Lance.
Much safer to have miss Smoak's
digital fingerprints
on the processor,
not mine,
and once she had
taken down the firewall,
I was able to upload
a critical piece of code
to Arclight.
What happens now?
We take the next step.
Mmm. Dinner went
better than expected.
Can't believe we got
through the whole thing, no interruptions...
No armed assassins...
I, um...
I still have room
for dessert.
So do I.
Wait.
That's ok.
- Oh, sorry.
- It's ok.
- Sorry.
- That's ok.
- Ok. Oh!
Sorry. Not mine.
- Thank you.
- Oh.
- One sec.
- Yep.
Ok.
Hello.
Hi.
Ok.
I'll be there.
Uh-uh. All right.
That didn't sound like
John or the team.
It wasn't.
What's going on?
That was Slade Wilson.
He needs my help.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Greg!
Move your head.