MOIRA: I'll need the Unidac merger
finalized by the end of the week.
We're on something of a clock here.
[BEEPS]
[MOIRA GASPS]
Moira Queen, you have failed this city.
Stand still.
Please don't kill me.
Do you know anything
about your husband's disappearance?
-What?
-Is Walter Steele still alive?
I don't know where my husband is.
I swear.
Do you know anything about the Undertaking?
I said don't move!
I... I'm a mother.
I have a son, Oliver. A daughter.
Her name is Thea.
She's just a teenager.
Please don't take me from my children.
They've lost their father.
They can't lose me too.
Please, whoever you are, please.
Okay.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
[GUNSHOTS]
[CELL PHONE DIALING]
This is Moira Queen.
I'm on the 39th floor. I need help.
There's an intruder.
Please.
[CAR ALARM CHIMES]
[ENGINE STARTS]
[GREEN ARROW GRUNTS
THEN FELICITY GASPS]
GREEN ARROW:
I'm not gonna hurt you, Felicity.
How do you know my name?
Because you know my name.
Mr...
Oliver. Oh. Wow.
Everything about you
just became so unbelievably clear.
-You're bleeding.
-I don't need to be told that.
-You need a hospital.
-My...
My father's old factory in the Glades.
No, you need a doctor,
not a steel worker.
Felicity, you have to promise me
that you are gonna take me...
...to my father's factory
and nowhere else.
Yeah, promise.
Something tells me bloodstains
are not covered under my lease.
MAN [ON TV]: So far,
the police are unwilling to comment...
...but unsubstantiated
eyewitness reports claim...
...the Starling City vigilante
attacked Mrs. Queen...
...in her office earlier tonight.
She was unharmed in the assault.
FELICITY:
Excuse me.
Can you help me? He's really heavy.
Oh, damn it. He just missed a carotid.
It's a zone two wound. Press there.
-I should've taken him to a hospital.
DIGGLE: No.
That's why he asked you
to bring him here.
He knew the police would wanna know
how and why he got that wound.
I'm guessing "how" and "why"
are Oliver Queen's least favorite questions.
Yeah, well, there's also "when" and "where,"
he's not too fond of.
-If we can't bring him to the hospital...
-We are bringing the hospital to him.
-Is that...?
DIGGLE: Yeah.
His blood. He stored it for a rainy day.
And I say right now, it's pouring.
FELICITY: Mm.
DIGGLE: I got it. Over there.
Do you know what you're doing?
Yeah, I had some medical training
in the Army.
I just hope it's enough.
Remember playing Operation
when you were a kid?
Yes. Heh.
-It never made me want to throw up.
-Hey, Felicity, listen. Trust me.
He'll be fine.
He's been through a lot worse than this.
[GRUNTING]
SLADE:
Dead.
[GRUNTING]
How did you survive here
for six months?
I know Girl Scouts
who have more fight in them.
Fighting Girl Scouts now, Slade, huh?
Aah!
-What the hell?
-Listen, kid.
We have 10 days
until the supply plane lands.
Ten days to turn you
into at least half a soldier.
So start taking it seriously.
[GRUNTING]
Aah! What is the point of this?
These soldiers don't carry bamboo!
They have guns!
So, what am I supposed to do
if one of them jams a gun in my face, huh?
Threaten them with my stick?
Jam this in my face.
Do it.
[GRUNTING]
I give up. I give up.
There is no giving up to these guys!
No crying or buying your way
out of it!
You have two choices.
Escape or die.
So choose.
Escape.
Then let me show you how not to die.
[OLIVER GRUNTS]
Lian Yu.
It's the name of the island, I know.
It's Mandarin for "purgatory."
It is? Wonderful.
Is that the airstrip?
ASIS took satellite images
of the whole island.
This is Fyers' main camp,
where I was held for almost a year.
Do you think that's where Yao Fei is now?
We can get a message to him.
-Tell him we found a way off the island.
-Forget about him.
This is the airstrip.
And these infrared images show...
...there are at least 10 soldiers
guarding the perimeter.
-Too many of them for you?
-No.
My problem is the guy here
in the tower.
It's a PATC.
A portable air traffic control tower.
The U.S. government set up these
for disaster zones...
...like Thailand after the tsunami.
So, what's the problem?
The glass is bulletproof.
I can't take out the tower guard
with my sniper rifle.
And if he suspects anything's wrong,
he'll radio Fyers and we're cancelled.
It'll be up to you to take him out.
Up close and personal.
Are you ready for that?
Do you think I'm ready?
What I think is there is only one
supply plane every three months.
We leave tomorrow,
or we die soon afterwards.
I pick leaving.
So get some sleep.
We leave at 0600.
Don't worry. You'll be back
with your girlfriend soon enough.
Morning.
Please don't hate me.
Why would I hate you?
For cheating on you with Sara.
Did it hurt, Ollie?
-Did what hurt?
-When they killed you.
[THUDDING]
SLADE:
Rise and shine.
Come on.
We're moving out.
All clear.
Hey, can we, uh...?
Can we rest for a second?
You can rest on the plane.
Yeah, well, really looking forward
to that in-flight movie.
[CLICKS]
-Oh, God.
-Don't move.
Is it a mine?
-Yeah.
-The soldiers mined the island?
No. It's probably Japanese.
Left over from World War II.
Still active. Impressive.
Can you disarm it?
Without disarming you?
[MEN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
Soldiers.
OLIVER:
They're gonna see us.
They're going to see you.
Wait. Stop.
SOLDIER:
What are you doing so far from camp?
OLIVER:
I got separated from my unit.
SOLDIER:
Come with us.
OLIVER:
I can't.
I'm kind of having a bad day,
you know?
[SLADE YELLING]
[GRUNTING]
Be still.
Thanks.
[CHATTERING]
Yao Fei. Come in. Sit.
Now, the first time I saw you
with this contraption...
...I thought you looked
utterly ridiculous.
That is, until you took out
three of my best men with it.
Twenty-five compound bows...
...will be arriving
on tomorrow's supply plane.
I'd like you to train a few of my men
on how to use them.
Archery can take years to master.
I trust you will be
a proficient instructor.
That will be all.
I hope you are steadfast in your
commitment to our cause, Yao Fei.
For her sake.
I am.
-Obviously you were never a Boy Scout.
-Yeah? What tipped you off?
We better hurry.
The wolves come out at night.
There are wolves here?
Right. Of course there are.
Because what would the worst place
on Earth be without wolves?
Well, the only thing
that will keep them out is fire.
Well, you know,
you're welcome to help.
Seriously?
I've been working on this
for two hours.
I know, I was watching.
Thank you for the entertainment.
You're gonna wear that thing out
just by looking at it.
Don't worry.
She'll be waiting for flowers
when you get back.
I doubt it.
Remember how I told you
I was shipwrecked here?
Her sister was with me
when the boat went down.
That's funny.
I never took you as being the bad boy.
You seem to lack the spine.
That's why I've gotta get home.
To make this right.
Do you think you can sleep
with your girlfriend's sister...
...and still make it right?
You're dumber than I thought.
And believe me when I tell you,
that is saying something.
Yeah, well, you don't really strike me as
the type of guy who accepts apologies, so...
Everybody is in this life
for themselves.
Learn that at Australian spy school?
No.
I learned that here.
Do you remember I told you
that I had a partner?
Yeah.
You remember the guy
who tortured you?
[SCREAMS]
That...? That freak show
was your partner?
-His name's Billy Wintergreen.
-Oh, okay.
Our mission was to exfiltrate Yao Fei...
...find out why Fyers and his men
were interested in him.
Our bird got shot out of the sky
before we even saw the airstrip.
That's where I found you.
When Fyers took us prisoner,
he asked if we would join him and his men.
Billy accepted Fyers' invitation...
...and I declined.
He was the godfather to my son, Joe...
...and yet he turned his back on me
without even thinking twice about it.
Everybody is in this life
for themselves.
If you let him radio camp, we're done.
-What about the others?
-You worry about your one.
I'll worry about my 10.
[INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER]
[BEEPING]
FELICITY:
Good job.
I think.
His heart rate's elevated,
but at least the bleeding's stopped.
Thanks for your help.
You kept your head on.
Well, I always wondered
how I'd react...
...if I found my boss shot and bleeding
inside my car.
Not that I helped
because he's my boss.
I'd help anyone who was shot
and bleeding in my car.
I was thinking all of this
would be more of a shock.
-You saying you called this all along?
-I'm not saying anything.
Except Oliver brought me a laptop
with bullet holes...
...had me trace a black arrow...
...and research a company
involved in armored car heists.
I may be blond, but I'm not that blond.
Yeah, Oliver's not too great
with cover stories.
FELICITY:
Neither are you.
The two of you with that whole
energy drink hangover cure?
Please.
What was really in that vial anyway?
Vertigo.
I knew it.
I didn't know it was Vertigo for sure...
...but I knew it wasn't something
that can cure a hangover.
Yeah, we needed it analyzed
so we could take down the Count.
-That was you and Oliver?
-And you, Felicity.
Without you, we never would've found him.
But why come to me?
Hard as it probably is for him to admit,
even Oliver needs help sometimes.
[GUNSHOT]
[GUNSHOTS]
[GUN CLICKS]
Damn.
[OLIVER GRUNTING]
[BEEPING]
-What's happening?
-There's a syringe labeled Ativan.
It should stop the seizure. Go.
[EKG FLATLINING]
His heart stopped.
FELICITY:
I'm calling 911.
No. Wait, you can't.
-You know how to use one of those?
-We are about to find out.
[DEFIBRILLATOR BEEPS]
You didn't say clear.
[DEFIBRILLATOR WHINES]
I heard the charge. That's good news.
-How's that?
-Might not be the machine.
It could be the wiring.
Come on, come on, come on.
FELICITY:
Try again.
DIGGLE:
Clear.
[BEEPING]
[DIGGLE SIGHS]
What the hell did you do?
I've been building computers
since I was 7.
Wires are wires.
What do we do now?
Pray we don't have a heart attack
ourselves.
[GUARD GRUNTING]
One job to do
and you manage to screw up even that.
I'm gonna make sure
everything is clear.
Stay here. Keep the door locked.
Do not let anybody in except for me.
-You got that?
-Yeah.
SLADE:
Here. Keep this.
And try not to shoot yourself
by mistake.
[LINE CRACKLES THEN DIAL TONE]
[DIALING]
[LINE RINGING]
LAUREL [OVER PHONE]:
Hello?
Is anybody there?
Have you lost your mind?
They might be monitoring the calls.
MAN [OVER RADIO]:
Island Tower.
This is Skyhawk 801 Foxtrot.
We are 700 kilometers
southeast of your position.
ETA, three hours, 22 minutes, over.
Island Tower, Skyhawk 801 Foxtrot,
acknowledged.
Skyhawk 801 Foxtrot, acknowledged.
MAN: Of all creatures that breathe
and move upon the Earth...
OLIVER: What is that?
SLADE: It's a challenge code.
They're trying to verify our identity.
Skyhawk 801 Foxtrot, please repeat.
MAN: Of all creatures that breathe
and move upon the Earth...
-Wait.
SLADE: What?
Wait, I know this.
I know this.
They picked the one book
that I read in college.
-What the hell are you talking about?
-It's a quote from The Odyssey.
Uh...
Of all creatures that breathe
and move upon the Earth, nothing...
Nothing is born
that is weaker than man.
Are you sure about this?
If you're wrong,
this plane will turn around.
OLIVER:
Yes. I'm positive.
Nothing is born
that is weaker than man.
Say it.
Wait. Wait, wait, wait.
It's... Sorry, sorry, sorry.
Bred.
Not born. Bred.
Nothing is bred
that is weaker than man.
That's it.
Nothing is bred
that is weaker than man.
MAN:
Roger that. See you in a few hours. Out.
-The Odyssey?
-Yeah. It's a...
Well, it's a story about a guy
who's trying to get home, so...
Well, after a few days
at Landstuhl Air Base...
...you'll be on your way home.
You sound like
you're not coming with me.
I'll be coming with you.
After I radio in an air strike
on this location.
I'm going to send Fyers and all his men
straight back to hell.
Wait.
You can't blow up the island.
Yao Fei is still out there.
-He is not my concern.
OLIVER: Really?
He's the only reason you came here.
Rescuing him was your mission.
The mission has changed.
Edward Fyers is a mercenary
and he is not on this island by mistake.
He has plans for Lian Yu
that involve Yao Fei.
And whatever they are,
they must end.
Yao Fei saved my life.
That is your debt to repay, not mine.
Where are you going?
All my life...
...all that I've ever thought about
is myself.
I took my family for granted.
I betrayed people that I loved.
And I'm not gonna be that person
anymore.
I can't leave Yao Fei here to die.
I won't.
The plane leaves in three hours.
If you and your friend are not on it,
I am going to leave without you.
If I don't make it back in time...
...and you get out of here...
...I want you to call my family.
Call my family.
Sure, kid.
[EKG FLATLINING]
-He's going into cardiac arrest again.
-No.
Ah, the leads just came loose.
[EKG STOPS]
DIGGLE:
Aah!
It's less stressful
when he's jumping off rooftops.
Yeah.
This bow has put arrows
in quite a few people.
Yeah, bad people.
That doesn't bother you?
Because...
And I mean this in a good way.
...you seem like the kind of guy
it would bother.
When I was in Afghanistan,
my unit was tasked...
...with protecting this local warlord.
Gholem Qadir.
Qadir was less than human.
He sold opium.
Sold children.
One day, we were accompanying him
to Mosul...
...when my convoy was ambushed
by insurgents.
We had them outgunned.
Firefight didn't last more than a minute.
When the smoke cleared...
...I moved in on their position.
They were all dead.
I knew which one I had killed.
When I pulled off his keffiyeh, I could
see it was just a kid, no more than 18.
Shot him in the throat.
I killed this kid
to protect this human piece of garbage...
...and I thought, "Am I still good?
Am I still a good man?"
Doing this with Oliver...
...doing what we do, I feel good again
for the first time in a long time.
And that's worth
all the collateral damage?
Haven't killed anyone,
if that's what you're asking.
But he has.
Unfortunately,
there are always casualties...
...when you're fighting a war.
-How did you...?
-Let's go. I'll explain on the way.
-Stupid. You should not have come back.
-I found Slade Wilson.
And he has a way off the island.
-But we have to go right now.
-No.
-What? What do you mean, no?
This is our chance. What reason could you
possibly have for staying here?
Not what.
Who.
Now, Mr. Queen, I think it's past time
you left this island.
Permanently.
MAN [OVER RADIO]:
Island Tower, this is Skyhawk 801 Foxtrot.
We are 5000 feet and holding. Over.
Skyhawk 801 Foxtrot,
this is Island Tower.
You are clear to land.
MAN:
Roger that.
Simply to satisfy my own curiosity,
why aren't you already dead?
-I saw Yao Fei choke you to death.
-I guess he's not as strong as he looks.
[SOLDIERS LAUGHING]
Still, you returned for him.
So you're either a fool...
...or is it possible
you now think yourself a hero?
-I'm not a hero.
FYERS: No, of course not.
It's not possible to be a hero
when there's nobody worthy of saving.
Is this what you want?
-You want me to fight him again?
FYERS: Oh, no, Mr. Queen.
I'm sorry, you're mistaken.
This is not a match.
It's an execution.
YAO FEI:
I'm sorry.
It's Wintergreen, right?
Bill Wintergreen?
I know all about you.
I know you worked
for the Australian government...
...and that you used to fight
for your country.
You used to stand for something.
Whatever he's paying you, I'll triple it.
-How many of them are there?
SOLDIER: Go, go, go!
[SOLDIERS YELLING]
DEATHSTROKE:
Slade. Come back to die?
[GRUNTING]
Was it so easy to betray me, Billy?
Well, Billy...
...you always had a good kick.
[KNIFE SQUELCHES]
[THUDS]
[GUNSHOT THEN SLADE GRUNTS]
-Come on, come on, come on.
-Aah!
[SOLDIER GRUNTS]
[AIRPLANE MOTOR HUMMING]
SLADE:
There goes our ride.
[GRUNTING]
I'm impressed.
-You didn't puke.
-I swallowed it.
You can untie me now.
Why did you want me to tie you up
in the first place?
A man in pain is unreliable.
I was afraid I might kill you.
Thanks.
[CHUCKLES]
What?
I'm trapped on an island...
...and my only friend is named Wilson, so...
What now?
We hope my fireworks show
set Fyers back...
...maybe enough for those
who hired him to call things off.
Hired him?
Well, Fyers is a merc.
He follows the money.
So he's on this island
under someone's employ.
And what do we do?
We have to make sure that neither
of us dies on this godforsaken island.
I thought you said
if we didn't get on the plane...
...we weren't gonna make it.
Well, that dumb kid that I trained...
...he would never have made it.
You?
You might just have a chance.
Yup, it's Fyers.
MAN [OVER PHONE]: Satellites show multiple
heat blooms on the island. What's happening?
There was a complication.
MAN: Slade Wilson?
-I'm handling it.
MAN: Handle it better.
I've worked too hard and planned for too long...
...to have complications
close to the end.
I assure you, it won't happen again.
MAN: What of Yao Fei?
-I've ensured his cooperation.
MAN:
Good.
I've paid you a lot of money, Fyers.
I expect a return on my investment.
You sent for me?
I'm a man of my word.
You made the right call,
turning in your young castaway.
And for that,
I'll grant you five minutes.
Shado?
Shado? Shado?
SHADO [IN MANDARIN]:
YAO FEI [IN MANDARIN]:
Shh, shh, shh.
I guess I didn't die.
Again.
Cool.
It's not bad.
So how am I gonna explain this one?
Hickey gone wrong?
The police collected a sample
of your blood at Queen Consolidated.
I just hacked the crime lab
and ordered the sample destroyed.
Oops. Heh.
I hope it's all right.
Your system looked like it was from the '80s...
...and not the good part of the '80s,
like Madonna and, well, legwarmers.
It's a lot of work.
Does that mean you're in?
You mean "in"
as in I'm going to join your crusade?
You're practically an honorary member
of the team already.
Hm, so Mr. Diggle said.
-No.
-Then why'd you upgrade my system?
First, because seeing a network
that poorly set up hurts me in my soul.
DIGGLE: Ahem.
-And second...
...I want to find Walter.
My stepfather.
He was nice to me.
And Mr. Diggle told me
the notebook you use...
...to fight crime is the same notebook
that got Walter abducted.
I'll help you rescue him, but that's it.
Then I want to go back
to my boring life of being an IT girl.
That's my offer.
Okay.
So I've been meaning to ask...
...is there a bathroom?
Because I've had to pee since I got here.
-It's upstairs to the left.
FELICITY: Great.
Felicity.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Oliver,
I know you don't wanna hurt this girl...
...and you didn't have any choice
in telling her who you were...
...but we're asking her to get involved
in dangerous stuff.
-We can protect her.
-How?
Your mother just shot you, Oliver.
You can't even keep yourself safe.
She was scared.
She was defending herself.
Or she was hiding something.
Like maybe her involvement
in Walter's disappearance or worse.
Diggle, we don't always know
why people do what they do.
But what I do know
is when I was standing in her office...
...with an arrow aimed at her heart...
...she begged me to spare her,
all on behalf of me and Thea.
Now, I've taken down a lot
of bad people.
-None of them brought up their kids.
-She had the list.
Now, she may not be in charge
of whatever it is...
-...but she's definitely involved.
-Involved in what?
We don't even know what it is.
And until we do, she is off limits.
Am I clear?
DIGGLE: But, Oliver, are you saying this
because you truly believe she's innocent...
...or because you don't wanna face the fact
that your mother might be guilty?
MOIRA:
Six-one and a deep voice. I...
Hey. What's going on?
Where have you been?
I've been calling all night.
At the club.
I get zero reception in there.
-It's time you invest in a landline.
-Thea.
Your mother was attacked last night.
-By the vigilante.
-What?
He came after me at the office.
-Did he hurt you? Are you okay?
-She hurt him.
She shot him point-blank
with a gun hidden in her office.
That should help with your investigation.
You get any evidence? A blood sample...?
There was a screw-up at the lab.
That's too bad.
Mm.
We'll be in touch.
-Thank you.
-Yeah.
-Oh, sweetheart. I was so scared.
OLIVER: I'm just glad you're okay.
I thought he was gonna kill me.
I promise you...
...he's never gonna bother you again.