Now is not the time for panic.
We let him rot in prison.
Clearly, you overestimate
Darhk's capacity for forgiveness.
Which is to say that he has any.
Should Damien prove to be unreasonable,
I have implemented contingencies.
(DOOR OPENS)
My buddies. Long time no see.
I brought my posse, I hope you don't mind.
What happened to Ian and Judy?
They come down with that nasty little flu
that's been going around?
Some were wary of this meeting,
given that...
You all abandoned me to my imprisonment?
I visited.
Someone should teach
this evil organization
a lesson in helping their fellow man.
I'm sure it's all
just a simple misunderstanding.
After all, why would I rely solely
on the word of Malcolm Merlyn?
-He can be so underhanded.
-Cute.
And our illustrious council has worked
together for such a very long time.
I'm glad that we still have your trust.
Of course. I had a lot of time to reflect
while I was in prison.
Mostly about religion and Bundt cake.
But after much thought, I realized that...
Oh, almost forgot.
Did my little incarceration
delay Genesis at all?
(GRUNTS) Of course not.
Genesis is much bigger
than just one person.
(CHUCKLES)
Gold star for you.
Where was I? Oh, that's right.
My jailhouse epiphany.
If I could escape prison
without your help,
what do I need any of you for?
(GUNSHOT)
Milo, you really have not been
paying attention, have you?
(GROANS)
-(DARHK LAUGHING)
-(PHAEDRA GROANS)
Anyone else care to do something stupid?
No takers?
Pity.
Ladies and gentlemen
and recently deceased,
it is time to begin
the final phase of Genesis.
Milo Armitage. SCPD found him
in an alley outside Ellendale.
And across town...
-(KEYBOARD KEYS CLACKING)
-Phaedra Nixon.
-Okay, so, what am I missing?
-They were both HIVE.
You probably don't recognize
Phaedra and Milo now that they're dead,
or maybe you were too busy
running for your life, but...
They were with Darhk
when he held us hostage.
And now they're dead.
Wait, so you think
crazypants Lonnie Machin's back in town?
No, his grudge is against Darhk, not HIVE.
You think Darhk is cleaning the house?
Well, HIVE didn't lift a finger
to break him out of Iron Heights.
That was all Andy and Merlyn.
Okay, well, if Darhk is settling scores,
then now might be the time to hit him.
We have seen how powerful he is.
I can't risk losing anyone else.
We just can't sit on our hands, Oliver.
We're not just sitting on our hands,
but before we do anything,
we need to know
that we can counteract his magic.
Well, is that even possible?
I think it might be.
I was finally able
to get in touch with Constantine
and he put me onto someone
who he thinks may be able
to teach me how to defend
against Darhk's magic.
Okay. Well, I'm not just saying this
because I love Harry Potter,
but why are we not all taking
those lessons?
Well, it is easier said than done,
and apparently quite dangerous.
So, I have to go to Hub City
for a day or two.
Okay, in that case,
can I take the weekend with Alex?
Kind of wants to go away, clear our heads.
That sounds like a good idea,
I think that...
Actually, I think
everyone should take a little time.
Lay low, but stay available,
and we will deal with Darhk
when I get back.
THEA: Okay.
(BUZZING)
Let him in.
(DOOR CLICKS)
Mind stepping out?
Hey, you? How you holding up?
(BOTH KISSING)
-You've looked better.
-(SCOFFS)
Considering I've spent two weeks
in a bomb-proof tungsten-encased bunker,
-I think I look pretty good.
-Hmm
You hungry?
Mmm, how long have those been there?
That was lunch.
It might have even been today's.
-Yeah, I think I'll pass.
-(CHUCKLES)
Oliver is leaving tonight
on some Magical Mystery Tour,
he wants me to stay put and do nothing
until he comes back.
Magical Mystery Tour?
Yeah, it's a long story.
But the point of it is,
that he thinks it's too dangerous
for any of us to go after Darhk or Andy
until he gets the right magical know-how.
-I can see you're thrilled about that.
-Hmm.
If you think you have it bad,
try remembering you're not the one
being held prisoner in a metal box.
Sweetheart.
We've talked about this.
Andy has been inside of A.R.G.U.S.
He's been inside of our home.
It's too dangerous for you to be
either place right now.
(SIGHS)
I don't want you in either place, either.
Oh, I got you. I got you.
(GRUNTS AND KISSES)
Let my agents see what they can find.
Yeah. (KISSES)
And, as much as you don't wanna hear it,
-Oliver has a point.
-Hmm.
HIVE is too dangerous for you
to go off half-cocked, John.
Well, it's always serious
when you call me John.
Well, John,
why don't you make yourself useful
by grabbing some diapers while you're out?
We're running low
and I hate asking my people to get them.
-You got it. (KISSES)
-(GRUNTS)
(KISSES)
Back in an hour?
Or less.
(BEEPING)
-Goodbye, Daddy. Honey, say bye.
-(KISSES)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(CLATTERING)
You've been living down here?
Seemed to make the most sense.
Where's all your stuff?
It's just in storage.
You know me, I don't need much.
Maybe, like, a plant?
Like a fern or something.
They thrive in places like this.
How could I forget?
(ZIPPING)
Come to see me off?
You were pretty stingy on the details
about this "magic tutor"
Constantine referred you to.
That is sort of my MO.
Don't talk to me like I'm other people.
What has you so worried?
Darhk's idol.
The type of magic that he's using,
I've seen it take good people.
(EXHALES)
And turn them dark, soulless
and almost inhuman.
And you're afraid
that's gonna happen to you?
There's an argument to be made
that I'm already there.
-That's not funny.
-I am not joking.
There is no length that I will not go to
to avenge Laurel.
To stop Darhk
from hurting anyone ever again.
And I honestly don't know
where that path will lead.
I'm coming with you.
Felicity...
Just because we're not together
doesn't mean you have to do this alone.
And I've already
chartered the company jet.
Mr. Dennis is furious.
And I've booked us a room... Rooms.
With points.
Should I even try
and talk you out of this?
(CHUCKLES)
No. You've met my mother. Same DNA.
(CELL PHONE BEEPING)
(BEEPING)
(CRASHES)
(SIGHS) Did you see anyone else here?
Which way? Get out of here, now.
(CRACKLING)
What the hell?
-Sorry, man.
-(GUNSHOT)
But I'm not playing anymore!
ANDY: Whoo!
-You still got those quick reflexes, John.
-(GUN CLICKS)
Too bad they couldn't save your partner.
Don't you dare say anything about her!
Well, you got a gun. Make me!
(GUN CLICKS)
(CELL PHONE BEEPING)
Hey, honey, it's a little tough
for me to talk right now.
You'll wanna hear this.
Satellite track just picked up Andy.
-(GRUNTS)
-(GUNSHOT)
Let me guess, he's somewhere south of Main
between Grammercy and Addison, right?
How do you know that?
Because I'm trading shots with him
right now.
-Johnny.
-Yell at me later.
Just send backup.
He's at the Grammercy Power Plant.
-(GUNSHOTS)
-JOHN: How soon can your men get here?
-(KEYBOARD KEYS CLACKING)
-Five minutes, 10 tops.
-That's too long.
-(GUNSHOT)
LYLA: Johnny, you need to wait.
You have no tactical advantage in there.
Lyla, I can't wait. If I do, he gets away.
I can't let that happen. Not again.
Your judgment is compromised.
Maybe it is.
But it doesn't mean I'm wrong. Get here!
(GUNSHOT)
-LYLA: Johnny!
-(GUNSHOT)
Johnny!
So, what exactly are we looking for?
-High-roller room.
-(JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING)
When you said that you had found someone
to teach you magic,
I was thinking, like, a mountain top
or a hidden temple,
not Hub City's
premiere underground casino.
Well, with Constantine,
I have learned to expect the unexpected.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
I'm betting on Fortuna.
(CHIPS CLINKING)
Now, he was a little bit vague
with the specifics. He just said,
"Pitch game, first base, mate.
See if you're worthy."
Wow. Okay, pitch game.
Blackjack, uh, dealer using
up to two decks.
First base,
first seat on the dealer's left.
I think we're in the right place.
I'm not so sure that finding this guy
depends on gambling.
It's not gambling when I play.
(SIGHS)
Alex?
(CLATTERING)
Hello? Alex?
Alex?
(CHUCKLES) Hey, morning.
And here I thought
you were gonna sleep past breakfast.
(CHUCKLES) I... I almost did.
(YAWNS)
Head's so foggy.
Yeah, you were exhausted.
You passed out
five minutes after we left the city.
Oh.
Guess I was really tired.
See, it just proves how badly
you needed this trip. We both did.
Hey, you ready for some
famous eggs Benedict?
You poached eggs?
Hey, I'm not just
a cutthroat political operative.
-I contain multitudes.
-Mmm-hmm.
And you also wear a very mean apron.
Well, you should see
what I have on underneath.
(GRUNTS AND CHUCKLES)
(KISSES)
I forgot how good you were at this.
Ah, like riding a bike.
Rough beat.
Indeed. I should probably head home soon
before they take my shoes.
Oh, well, you never know
when your luck's gonna change. Trust me.
That's so kind. Muchas gracias.
De nada.
Oh! Boom. Come to mama.
(CLEARS THROAT) I mean...
What?
I'm starting to think
that this guy's gonna be a no-show.
Right.
It's because he's not a guy, amor.
Esrin Fortuna.
Tell John Constantine
he still owes me money.
(ANDY PANTING)
(GUNSHOTS)
Stay right where you are,
you son of a bitch.
It's funny.
I was gonna tell you the same thing.
(GROANS)
(GUN CLATTERS)
-Bravo, John.
-(GROANS)
You played the script out perfectly.
What the hell are you talking about?
Don't worry about it.
I'll explain everything.
After you wake up.
(GRUNTING)
(COUGHS)
Sorry this place isn't as fancy
as the cage you kept me in
for three months.
Where the hell am I?
You've got bigger worries.
Mr. Darhk is on his way.
To do what?
Well, he's not coming here
to play gin rummy.
I'm supposed to prep you.
(EXHALES)
Glad to see you're picking up
your psycho boss' old habits.
I'm sorry,
but is the man that locked me up in a cage
and beat me half to death
questioning my savior's orders?
Damien Darhk is no one's savior.
He's a liar and a monster.
The Romans said the same thing
about Jesus.
Just do whatever you gotta do, man. Do it!
(CHUCKLES)
Wow. There's that temper I remember.
You know, it's a good thing
that Sara's not gonna
have to grow up with it like I did.
You keep my daughter's name
out of your mouth!
How could you do this to everyone again
for a second time?
Oh.
I know what you're doing.
You're referring
to my former wife and son.
I left that life a long time ago, John.
You can't even say their names.
Carly, Andy Jr.
They were your family.
They still are.
My family
is HIVE.
(GROANS)
(GROANS AND SCREAMS)
Okay, so since Oliver
doesn't seem to want to ask it, um...
Why is an immortal shaman
playing blackjack
in Hub City's premiere underground casino?
(STUTTERS) Excuse me. Immortal?
-You see any wrinkles on my face?
-And shaman?
A shaman is someone who has influence
in the world of good and evil spirits.
Blackjack is just a hobby. This way.
You're planning on teaching me magic
in the back room of a casino?
You want to learn
the dark arts, Mr. Queen?
We cannot do that here.
This is, by far, the coolest high-roller
room I have ever seen. (CHUCKLES)
We've left the casino behind, amor.
And that plane of existence.
I've been in a chamber like this before
on an island named Lian Yu.
Yes, Lian Yu is a place of nexus.
Just like your home.
Star City?
There's a nexus chamber there as well.
Wait, you didn't think
it was a coincidence
that Damien Darhk chose that city?
-You know Darhk?
-(SCOFFS)
(CHUCKLES) I wouldn't be much of a shaman
if I didn't.
(GASPS) A special brand
of nasty loco that one is.
So, if you know Darhk,
why haven't you tried to end him?
That's not the way of things.
We immortals tend to stay out
of the affairs of men.
Unless someone owes you money.
(CHUCKLES)
Recognize this handsome gent?
(SIGHS) Darhk has a similar idol.
It gives him his power.
Mmm-mmm. It only channels it.
Darhk's power comes from...
Death.
The more people he kills,
the more powerful he becomes.
Not just a pretty face, this guy.
Yeah, except Oliver's not gonna go kill
a bunch of people
just to be on the same level playing field
as Darhk.
(CHUCKLES)
All things have their opposite.
Darhk draws his power from fear and death.
Its opposite is light and hope.
La luz del alma.
Light of the soul.
If you can channel la luz del alma,
you will be able to repel Darhk's magic.
Then that is what I'm here to learn.
I wish it were just that easy.
If the darkness inside you
outweighs the light,
instead of repelling Darhk's magic,
you'll end up fueling it.
You will only make him more powerful.
Are you getting a signal?
Nope. It's one of the benefits
of being on vacation.
(GRUNTS) Just wanted to call my brother.
You okay?
Seem to be having trouble relaxing.
Yeah, no, I'm...
(SIGHS)
You're probably gonna think it's stupid.
I can pretty much guarantee that I won't.
(SIGHS) It's...
(SMACKS LIPS) It's this place.
-It just seems too perfect.
-(BOTH CHUCKLING)
Well, it sounds like it's been
way too long since you've left the city.
Yeah, maybe.
Do you hear that?
Yeah, I think people call that nature.
(CHUCKLES) No. That's...
That's not it. It...
I, uh...
I don't know, maybe...
Maybe I'm just tired, but it...
It sounds like everything
is on a loop right now.
Does that sound crazy? That...
That's crazy.
Only a little, yeah.
Like, I think this is just the last bit
of you trying to fight this vacation.
-Yeah.
-Hey,
let all that go. Just be happy, okay?
(SIGHS) Okay.
I sure am.
-Okay.
-All right.
ANDY: It's time.
I know this feels personal, John.
But it isn't. What's happening
is just what has to happen.
(CHAINS CLINKING)
(GROANING)
-(GRUNTS)
-(GROANS)
-(GROANING)
-(GRUNTING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Do it.
Do it for Laurel.
She'd be so disappointed in you.
The only reason why you're still breathing
is because one of us is still human.
(GUN CLICKS)
-(GRUNTS)
-(RATTLES)
I'll hit you with a low dose
of Darhk's magic,
and then we'll take it up from there.
(GRUNTS) Don't I need an idol or a totem?
The tattoo Constantine gave you
does many things.
Are you ready?
Yeah.
I'm sorry. I...
I just thought that these magic lessons
would have, you know, more
lessons.
Magic is a manipulation
of primordial energies.
Primordial as in pre-linguistic.
You'll probably want to take
a few steps back, amor.
Hmm? (GRUNTS)
(SIGHS) Two sides of you.
Darkness. Light.
Focus on the light.
Good.
But that might be,
as they call, beginner's luck.
So, let's kick it up a notch or two. Hmm?
FORTUNA:
The darkness and light are within you.
In truth, you're only fighting yourself.
(GRUNTS)
The friends you've failed,
the people you've killed.
They have no place in this.
(GROANS)
Don't give in. Cast aside your doubt.
Resist your darkness.
(GRUNTS)
(CHOKES)
(GUN CLICKS)
(GASPS)
-What happened?
-He's not ready.
I'll get it. I'll get it.
Now, let's go again.
I could give you an infinite number
of tries, it wouldn't change a thing.
What? No, I can do this.
I told you, if the darkness within you
is greater than the light,
you will only make your enemy stronger.
You've seen what's inside of you.
Now, tell me,
what could I possibly teach you
that would change what you saw?
Wait, so that's it? It's over?
There's nothing I can do for him.
It's not even getting dark out.
What's that?
It's 8:00 and it's raining outside,
but it's still light out.
Yeah, we're up north and...
Seriously. What's gotten into you?
You never even told me
where we were going.
And... (CHUCKLES)
How can you not hear that?
Thea, come on, we've been over this.
Seriously, listen, there's three chirps,
then a bark, then four chirps,
and then it just
keeps repeating itself twice.
Okay, I think what's happening here
is you're beyond stressed...
No, okay. Alex, I am not stressed out.
Just listen.
There's gonna be a bark right
now.
(DOG BARKS)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
Since when did you start taking vitamins?
Now you're worried about my vitamins?
Where did you get those?
Ruvé. She said I needed to stay healthy.
(SHUDDERS)
Alex?
Where are we?
Is...
Is the reason that I don't remember
anything because you...
Did you drug me?
-Thea, now you're talking crazy, okay?
-No.
Where are you going?
-Thea!
-(DOOR CLOSES)
-(BEEPING)
-(DOOR OPENS)
What the hell, Johnny?
I told you to stand down!
I know. I know. But, I couldn't...
You could've been killed!
I couldn't stand down,
not after what he did.
Then you are going to make
an orphan of your daughter,
because you are not seeing straight.
That's why tonight went south!
(BABY SARAH CRYING)
(LYLA SHUSHES)
-It's okay. Sweetheart, it's okay.
-Lyla, listen I know, I...
I know I messed up
and I know my head isn't on right, but...
But he's my brother.
And Laurel, she was like a sister.
I know. And it's horrible.
But right now, Johnny,
you are not acting like the man I married.
You're the man I divorced.
Lyla, look... I just wanted to help him.
To bring my brother back.
Then bring him to justice.
But do it the right way.
I will.
I will. (SIGHS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
We'll find someone else
to teach you magic.
Someone with more patience
and less smelly incense.
She was right, you know.
It's not about the magic, it's about me.
If she didn't see anything worthy
inside you,
she never would have dealt with us.
She didn't deal with us.
She dealt with you.
She didn't reveal herself
until you offered her your chips.
That has always been the way
with us, Felicity.
You are the one who brings the light.
You know? I told you that I've seen
magic that's turned good people dark.
But all Fortuna did
was show me who I really am.
Don't do this.
Every time you face a setback,
you throw yourself a pity party.
It's not a "pity party." It's acceptance.
You said it yourself. No matter what I do,
I'm always gonna revert back
to the person I became on the island.
Yeah, when I said that I was hurt.
I was going through one of the most
painful experiences of my life.
Oliver, you are not perfect.
None of us are.
Good news is that all of us can change.
DARHK: Hmm!
(SMACKS LIPS) Poor widdle Andy Diggle.
Did your big brother knock your noggin?
(CHUCKLING)
Bravo. Your performance was pitch perfect.
Thank you, sir.
I assume the tracker's in place.
We've already locked in on his location.
Well, then I believe it's time
for one last family reunion.
(GROANS)
Oh, come on.
You're a bigger baby than Sara.
Ouch!
Is there anything else you can tell me
about their lockup?
Yeah, the place could've really used
some central heating.
It was strange. Torture just didn't
seem like the right play.
Why not just kill me?
(ALARM BEEPING)
-What's that?
-Proximity alarm.
Sweetheart, make sure
Sara's strapped in really tight.
(GUNSHOT)
(EXPLOSION)
(JOHN GROANS)
-How's Sara?
-She's okay.
(COMPUTER BEEPS)
It's Director Michaels.
We have a code black.
(GUNSHOTS)
-(EXPLOSION)
-(GROANS)
(GUNSHOTS)
We have two more bogies.
How the hell did they find us?
It's me. Andy let me go.
He probably tagged me with a tracker.
You can blame yourself
after we get out of this.
You mean, if we get out of this.
Where's your backup?
(CELL PHONE BEEPS)
HIVE has them engaged elsewhere.
A.R.G.U.S. headquarters.
Where's your team?
They're not answering.
So much for "stay available."
We're on our own.
-(GUNSHOT)
-(GROANS)
(GUNSHOTS)
This rig was designed
to withstand just about anything.
Does that include magic?
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(GRUNTS)
It's me he's after. I'll draw him out.
No.
If you were Darhk's objective,
he already had you.
He wanted you to lead him to me.
What are you talking about?
-You need to get out of here now.
-Lyla, I'm not leaving you.
Johnny, I am not Amanda Waller.
If they use you against me,
I will give them whatever they want.
I need you both safe.
(GUN CLICKS)
-(GUNSHOT)
-(GROANS)
(ENGINE REVVING)
Well, that's was a fun bit of business.
Get him.
(ENGINE STARTING)
(CLICKS)
(EXPLOSION)
(GUN CLICKS)
-(GUNSHOTS)
-(GROANS)
(GRUNTS)
(GASPS)
(GROANS)
You are a feisty one, Ms. Michaels.
You've had your fun.
It's time for me to have mine.
(TIRES SCREECH)
(GRUNTS)
(DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES)
Oh, it's been a while since I've hit
anybody with this thing.
I didn't think you got my message.
Sorry we're late.
Oliver's on Lyla and Darhk.
-Baby Sara.
-Oh.
-Hey, hey, little one.
-Yeah.
-JOHN: You got her?
-FELICITY: Yeah, yeah.
Okay. (KISSES)
All right.
Okay.
(TIRES SCREECH)
-It's a small world, isn't it?
-(PANTING)
Your brother in-law
being my loyal servant.
Thanksgiving at your home
is gonna be so interesting this year.
(GROANING)
(GRUNTS)
(THUD)
(PANTING)
(DAHRK GROANS)
(CLATTERS)
You seem like a likable guy, Oliver.
I bet you've got a lot of friends.
I'm going to enjoy killing
every last one of them.
No. Never again.
(JOHN GRUNTS)
-(GRUNTING)
-(GROANING)
(GUN CLICKS)
Bet you regret not pulling
that trigger the first time around.
(GUN CLICKS)
What are you gonna do, John?
(GRUNTS)
(GROANING)
After Laurel, I left you alone to grieve.
I was being nice.
You have no idea
how much I hate being nice.
(GRUNTS)
-(JOHN GRUNTS)
-(GROANS)
It isn't over.
You haven't been paying attention, Andy.
Darhk got out. I got out.
I'll get out again.
That mobile safe-house you've got
looked really homey.
Bet it gets cramped once Sara gets older.
Shut up.
She's gotta go to school eventually.
And Lyla, well, you can't watch her 24/7.
I said to shut your mouth, Andy.
Shut your damn mouth!
You're the one
who's obviously not payin' attention.
Because this is war.
And women, children,
they're expendable in your war?
Genesis is coming, John.
Lyla and Sara won't be
the only women and children who die.
Tell me, how's it feel
knowing that you had no problem
pulling the trigger
to protect a bunch of Afghanis
that you never knew,
but you don't have the guts
to do what's necessary
to protect your own wife and child?
-(GRUNTS)
-(GROANS AND GASPS)
(CLATTERS)
How's Lyla?
Um...
She's fine. She's, uh...
She's unconscious, but she's fine.
Felicity's taking her and Sara back.
Darhk is...
Darhk's in the wind.
John, what happened?
He was never gonna back off, Oliver.
My family,
they were never gonna be safe.
FELICITY: Hey.
Hi.
-Did you get in touch with Thea?
-Not yet.
-You okay?
-(SIGHS)
Earlier, with Darhk, it worked.
He tried to use his magic on me
and I was able to repel it.
That's incredible.
How'd you do it?
(SIGHING)
I heard your voice in my head.
You were reminding me
of all of the good things
that I have in my life.
I heard Thea, I heard John.
I heard Laurel.
Just telling me to keep fighting,
to never give up.
Just telling me to have hope.
(KISSES)
Hey.
-Sara? Where's Sara?
-No, no, no, she's fine.
She's fine. Felicity took her to Donna's.
She's okay.
(SIGHS)
But something's wrong.
I, um...
I had to put him down, Lyla.
Andy.
I had to kill my baby brother.
He wasn't a brother to you, Johnny.
Not in the ways that really matter.
What happened?
He reached for my gun. (SIGHS)
I didn't have a choice.
Oh, no.
-No, no, no, no.
-What? What?
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
It's gone. Darhk took it.
Took what?
Rubicon.
I thought Rubicon
was being stored at A.R.G.U.S.
It was,
until Shadowspire tried to steal it.
After Waller's death,
-I had it moved for security reasons.
-To where?
It was under your skin?
A sub-dermal implant. Darhk ripped it out.
Lyla, you need to tell us what Rubicon is.
A ballistic launch override protocol.
Designed to prevent any country,
even our own,
from firing a nuclear missile.
Something tells me
Darhk's plans aren't so benign.
LYLA: With some work and the right
expertise, Rubicon could be corrupted.
Instead of controlling nukes
to prevent them from being launched...
Oh, my God.
Darhk would control
the world's nuclear stockpile.
To what end?
I don't mean to apply logic
to a bad guy's plot here,
but Darhk destroys the world, then what?
He'll be ruler of nothing.
Unless he wants to rebuild.
-Andy told me that Genesis was coming.
-I don't think so.
Phil Collins said they'd never tour again.
The Old Testament, the Book of Genesis.
God wanted to give the world a do-over
so he destroyed it.
He destroyed it with a flood.
Rubicon is Darhk's flood.
FELICITY:
So, nuclear annihilation is Darhk's flood.
What's he planning on building as his ark?