My name is Oliver Queen.
For 7 years, I have
fought with only one goal--
to save my city,
but now a new
threat has emerged,
a danger so severe
it has forced me
to leave my family
in order to face it,
and it won't be enough for
me to just be the Green Arrow.
To prevent the
crisis that's coming,
I'am going to have to
become someone else,
become...something else.
Previously on "Arrow"...
We see the wall coming
down as an opportunity.
For the criminals
of Star City to
-rob the Glades blind.
-To reunite the city.
Ever since we brought
down the wall, your bro--
the Deathstroke gang--
has really upped their game.
They've amassed more territory
and power than ever before.
Your brother hates you. That
makes things unpredictable.
Vasquez is one of the
Glades' wealthiest citizens.
Maybe the Deathstrokes
plan to extort him.
A crisis is coming, John.
- What are you doing here?
- Reminding you
what you are doing here,
which does not include
interfering in the
events of this Earth.
-The city's under attack.
-By who?
A crisis is imminent.
Someone is coming,
someone far, far more
powerful than myself.
We have to get
the hell out of here.
I missed you, buddy.
‘Cause we found
ourselves in each other.
You're never without me.
Beautiful boy.
What's happening?
Oliver!
Survive.
I warned you not to interfere.
You didn't bring us here?
No. I discovered what
had transpired on Earth-2,
that you intervened
to save Laurel Lance.
I redirected you.
What...the hell
happened back there?
A herald of what is to come,
an entire world
erased from existence.
Where's my mother?
Where's--where's Tommy?
Where's--where's
Rene, where's Dinah?
They are no more.
Did you hurt John and Laurel?
They are alive and nearby,
but now you know
that if we fail to stop
the coming crisis,
what you witnessed will occur
on infinite Earths across
the expanse of time.
How did I fail? Your dwarf
star particles are right there.
You disobeyed my instructions
to avoid entanglements
on a parallel Earth.
You confronted Tommy Merlyn.
You altered the
fate of Laurel Lance.
I watched her die once.
Ok. I wasn't prepared
to do it again.
You are not a man
accustomed to following orders,
but the survival of
the multiverse requires
that you obey mine.
Where are we?
Your home Earth,
where you will
complete your next task.
There's a man named
Dr. Robert Wong.
Bring him to me.
Why? Now, that
is not your concern.
Do not fail me again.
Oliver, we have to
get out of here...now.
“Who are they? -Local gang.
I think we busted up a deal.
Nice of you to show up.
Where the hell are we?
We're in Hong Kong.
It's--it's not possible.
There's no way
that my entire Earth
is just-- is just gone.
You saw what happened
to the SCPD, right,
that energy wave,
people just disappearing?
That doesn't mean it
happened everywhere.
The Monitor told me that it did.
-The what?
-His real name is Mar Novu--
Oh. You call that a real name?
He's the one that
has asked me to be
on this mission.
He is trying to
prevent a crisis--
Oliver, just stop.
Hand me the breach device.
Give it to me. I'm going back.
Laurel, back where?
To my Earth
to look for any survivors.
-It's not working.
Probably damaged
on our jump through the portal.
We don't have time to go
all the way to S.T.AR. Labs.
I--I have to find
somebody local.
I'm sorry, but we need
to focus on the mission.
First of all, there
is no we here,
and the only mission
that I care about
is saving what's
left of my Earth.
Laurel. Laurel!
There's no one left to save.
The only thing that
we can do right now
is prevent this from
happening again
by doing what the
Monitor tells us--
screw the Monitor, Oliver,
and screw you, too.
None of this would have happened
if you hadn't shown up on
my Earth in the first place.
All of those people
that you saw die,
they weren't real to you.
They were just copies of
the people that you love...
but that is my home,
and those people,
those are real people
who are counting on me--
Adrian, my sister.
I just got my life back,
and I am not giving
it up without a fight.
Let her go, man.
She's wasting her time, John.
She's processing her grief,
and if we have a new mission
and the multiverse
depends on it, Oliver,
we have to get going right now.
Anyone want to fill me in
on what happened out there?
I almost got my throat slit.
Turns out Connor doesn't know
his brother as well as he thinks.
Hey, we're all still
alive, aren't we?
Which means what exactly,
that your brother's
not such a bad guy?
All I'm saying is JJ could
have killed you, and he didn't.
Wow! That is
some serious denial.
To answer your
question, nothing good.
What about Alberto Vasquez?
He's safe, but he'd already
given JJ what he was after.
- Which was?
- Access codes
to the private vault in
Vasquez's penthouse.
Yeah. Well, we
went to the vault,
but by the time we got there, it had
already been trashed and emptied.
This is all that was left.
Flash storage from the
vault's security mainframe.
Yeah. Don't get too excited.
It's totally fried. Not to brag,
but totally fried is
kind of my wheelhouse.
If I can fix it, I'll
be able to extract
the vault's security log.
Finding out what the
Deathstrokes stole
could help us figure out
what they're planning next.
We already know
what they're planning.
♪ wants to take over the city.
He needs the cash to do it.
Well, Vasquez did say the
vault was full of valuables--
jewelry, cash.
So we figure out where
JJ's gonna sell, take him out.
I know exactly where you'd
go to move that kind of product.
You're not the only one
around here with street smarts.
Ok. We'll find JJ,
take him out of play.
Stay here. Fix that
useless piece of junk,
and, you, next time
I see your brother,
don't get in my way.
Harbinger sends her regards.
Oh. This would have
come in handy 10 years ago.
Well, it helps to be
married to Lyla Michaels,
who is en route
even as we speak.
John, I didn't even want
to get you involved in this.
I know, but if what
you told me is true,
which is that we're
facing the destruction of...
well, hell, man, pretty
much everything,
then to me that's the very
definition of all hands on deck.
Check this out.
Now this machine is hooked
up to AR.G.U.S.'s intranet,
$0 we can access all the
information it has on Dr. Wong.
You want to tell me
what that face is all about,
or are you gonna make me guess?
Laurel. She was right.
The Monitor warned
me not to get involved,
and, I don't know,
if I'd just found
a way to get the
dwarf star particles
without trying to stop
Tommy's Undertaking, then--
Oliver, what were you supposed
to do, just sit back and let it happen?
l ignored the orders
of a cosmic being,
and as a result, I watched
an entire world just
disappear, so...
I'm just trying not to make
the same mistake twice.
Well, if this cosmic
being wanted
someone willing to watch the
mass murder of innocent people,
then...he picked the wrong hero.
Shouldn't blame yourself, man.
Well, what about my
behavior over the past 7 years
has given you the
impression that I would?
Got him. Good.
Dr. Robert Wong,
renowned biophysicist.
Won the Nobel
Prize in the specialty
of complex proteins
and antibodies.
First the dwarf star particles,
now a mysterious scientist.
Can't the Monitor just snap
his fingers and get both?
Well, he's not the biggest
fan of sharing information.
Ok. Looks like Dr. Wong
might not be that easy to find.
He's been missing a week.
This is the last-known photo.
Wan Chai University.
He's a professor.
That's where we start.
We need to do things
quietly, stay under the radar.
Too late.
Agh!
Tatsu?
You will be safe here.
So who were those men, Triad?
Shu gang, their rivals.
Why are you in Hong Kong?
I thought you were
with the Crescent Order.
I was until I gave
Nyssa the Lotus cure
to save your sister,
and they called for my head.
So you decided to
become a vigilante?
My son died in this city.
No more Akios will die here
as long as I'm here
to protect them.
That explains
what I'm doing here.
It's all you, man.
Right. We're looking for a
scientist named Dr. Robert Wong.
Why? -There's a crisis coming
that...quite literally
threatens the entire universe.
A man--something like a man
has asked me to
help him stop it.
-You mean Mar Novu?
You've heard of him?
When I was with
the Crescent Order.
A being who
transcends universes,
a crisis brewing.
He believes Dr. Wong
can help him stop it.
And you believe him?
I have to.
Then how can I help?
Tatsu, what we're
doing is very dangerous.
I--I can't ask you
to be involved.
You're not asking. I'm offering.
Dr. Wong was seen
last leaving his classroom
at Wan Chai University.
That was a week ago.
We're trying to figure out
why he would have left town.
I don't think he has.
Those pins, they're only worn
by the Security Wing,
Hong Kong version
of the secret police.
With a very healthy
reputation for
silencing political
enemies of the state.
Yeah, but why would they
be going after Dr. Wong?
We need to find out.
Johnny told me you were
about to do something stupid.
He called you all the way
to Hong Kong to follow me?
How nice. He thought
you could use some help.
Clearly, he was right.
Clearly, he needs to
mind his own business.
He said you're
looking for an old friend.
Doesn't seem like the
kind who's too friendly.
His name is David Chin.
I met him a few years ago
through Cayden James.
He said he could help
me get back to Earth-2
so maybe he still can.
Do you have any idea what
you're about to walk into?
Nothing that I
can't handle myself.
You'll need backup.
What the hell?
I wouldn't.
Hello, David. It's been a while.
Black Siren?
David, I'm gonna need your help,
and if you don't help me,
then I am gonna hurt
you very, very badly.
What do you want?
Whoa? Is that an
interdimensional extrapolator?
If that's nerd talk for
breach device, then yes,
and I need you to fix it.
That's not really
my area of expertise.
Okay, okay.
I'l do it.
Good. I'm so glad
you reconsidered.
So this is, what,
like a black market?
More or less.
♪ wants to find a buyer,
this is where he'll be.
11 got a number, I gota name?
I1got a target, it has a face ♪
I'll check the back.
See, I still don't get it.
Your dad was Bronze Tiger,
and you turned out okay.
I mean, kind of.
Gee. Thanks.
John and Lyla were
basically saints.
Yeah. Well, they spent all
their time worrying about me.
♪ got shortchanged.
Hey. You think ♪ turned
out this way ‘cause of you?
No. JJ made his own choices.
I know you want to
believe that deep down
there's still some good in him.
There is.
♪ wasn't just my brother, okay?
He was my best friend.
That was a long time ago.
Come to have a drink
with me, little bro?
-This is over, JJ.
<l don't think so.
-Put down your
weapons. You first.
Maybe there's a better
way that we can resolve this.
No, no, no. We can resolve this
by you coming with us.
You know, I wish
that I could. I do,
1 do, but I got
business to attend to.
1 would settle for a
friendly chat with my brother.
What you think?
I think that's never
gonna happen.
Fine.
You want to talk, we'll talk.
That looked like that hurt.
Knowing you has changed my life.
We're gonna be fine.
I spoke to contact on
Hong Kong police force.
As soon as I mentioned
Dr. Wong's name, he stopped talking.
-He seemed afraid.
+I think we know why.
It seems that Dr. Wong
has been working
on a top secret project for
the Chinese government.
Exactly, which means
the Security Wing
wasn't kidnapping him.
It was trying to help him.
He must be in
protective custody.
Safe house in the
Wan Chai district,
but they're planning on moving
him out of the city tonight.
Then we better get moving.
Don't hurt me.
Triad.
We can't let them get
away with Dr. Wong.
We won't, Go, go, go, go!
Out of the way! Out of the way!
Welcome back to Hong Kong.
Hyah! Hyah!
Agh! Ugh!
-Hyah!
-Unh!
Gah!
It's gas. Got to get
these people out of here.
We can't lose the doctor.
No sign of Dr. Wong.
Triad must have taken
him deep underground.
I thought China White
was in AR.G.US. custody.
Yeah, Well, so did I, and
as far as I know, Lyla did, too.
Well, our situation just got a
whole lot more complicated.
You seemed ready to let
those people die back there.
I knew you had it handled,
and you knew that
Dr. Wong was the priority.
You sound like
someone l used to know--
you nine years ago,
single-minded
about your mission.
Tatsu, with due
respect, if you had seen
what I have seen,
you would understand.
The Monitor is our best
chance at preventing it
from happening again.
I've seen that blind faith
in you before, as well,
with Amanda Waller.
That wasn't blind faith.
She threatened my family, Tatsu.
Right now, the stakes are
every family in existence.
Guys, I really hate
to interrupt this,
but none of this
matters if we don't find
this missing scientist, right?
Why does the Triad want him?
His work does not seem harmful.
Yeah? Well, innocent
men don't work
on secret government projects.
We need to know
what this project is.
Then we'll know why
the Triad is after him.
I don't like this.
He's stalling.
Hey. Hey!
What's taking so long?
-It's done. <Great.
So you won't mind
if we test it out.
Itisn't working.
Well, it should be.
Then where's the portal?
You want to go to
Earth-37, Earth-14?
I want to go to Earth-2.
Earth-2...
is gone.
It registered at first, but now
I see that it's like a shadow.
There's no sign of life.
That doesn't make any sense.
You're lying. Fix it! Fix it!
I'm telling you I did.
1 can fix tech. I
can't bring back
awhole friggin' universe!
I'm so sorry, Laurel...
but they're gone.
Let's get out of here.
Laurel!
Now!
There's nothing in any
governmental databases
of the project Dr. Wong
was working on.
-So we're back to square
one? No, not exactly.
An AR.G.U.S. mole
led me to a paper trail,
some equipment that
Dr. Wong purchased.
He shipped it to this address.
Well, it's his lab. It has to
be. We need to get in there.
That may not be $0 easy.
I know this place.
It's a PLA garrison.
Oh. Those garrisons
have a reputation
for being almost impenetrable.
Almost but not quite.
There are certain
vulnerabilities.
Yeah. Well, even if we
could get in that place,
it's gonna be heavily fortified.
That's never stopped us before.
Ow.
I'm almost at the sublevel.
The elevator will take
you straight to the lab.
Most likely will be guarded.
All right. I've
definitely been made.
You only have a few minutes.
I'm starting the upload.
What? What is it?
I know what the Triad is after.
Dr. Wong has been
trying to re-create
the Alpha-Omega virus.
He's not trying.
He's already done it.
After what happened
last time, you'd think
the Chinese government
would have learned its lesson.
The Alpha-Omega
is a powerful weapon.
Yeah, and the Triad
could already have it.
If they had it, they wouldn't
have any need for Dr. Wong.
It's just a matter of time before
they make him re-create it.
Which means, Oliver,
that we have a ticking clock
and absolutely no plan.
-We have this.
-You stole the virus?
This is what China White wants,
this is what I'm gonna give her.
Oliver, you more than anyone
else knows how dangerous this is.
Which is why I'm not actually
gonna give her the virus.
We're using this as
bait to draw her out.
My husband tried this
gambit once already,
and you're the one who
told him he made a mistake.
This is different.
Maseo had every intention
of actually giving the
virus to China White.
-l don't. t's too risky.
It's riskier to do nothing.
If anyone has a better idea,
I'm all ears.
I'll start making arrangements.
Here. It'll help
with the swelling.
I don't have anyone here who cares
if I come home with bruised knuckles.
I'm here. I care.
You barely even know me.
I know what it's
like to lose people.
Do you know what it's like
to lose an entire universe?
No.
Then you don't know how I feel.
You didn't know them.
My sister, Adrian,
they're my family,
they're--they're good people.
They don't deserve to be gone.
To think that I'm the one
who's done such awful things.
But you're trying to be better.
Everyone deserves
a shot at redemption.
Well, then maybe this
is where I deserve to be.
When I was in Afghanistan,
my unit got sent out on patrol
on a day I drew base duty.
It was a routine op.
We'd done it a
hundred times before.
Only this time, there
was an IED in the road.
None of them made it back.
I used to lie in bed at night
asking myself,
"Why them?
Why not me?"
And I made every
deal I could think of
with any god I
thought might listen.
And did it work?
Not exactly.
So you're right.
I don't know what
you're going through,
but I do know something
about survivor's guilt.
Does it get any easier?
No.
All we can do is try
and move forward.
How am I supposed
to move forward
when everyone I've
ever loved is gone?
By not giving up.
By doing the right thing.
We honor the dead
by fighting for the living.
This world needs you, too.
You're not talking
me out of this.
4 know. -Trust me, Tatsu.
1 will not let China
White get the virus.
-And what if you fail?
-I'm not gonna fail.
Nine years ago, you
failed to stop the virus,
and my son died.
And I regret it every day.
You must remember it
because of what happened after.
I tortured General Shrieve.
Your grief, your anger,
your guilt over the failure,
it stole your humanity.
This is different.
I'm not angry.
I'm simply doing
what has to be done.
How do you know that?
It is said that Mar Novu believes
order comes through chaos.
So he's bringing us order?
But first may be chaos.
He's asking you
to bring him a man
who re-created a
deadly virus. Why?
How do you know he won't use it
for something worse than the Triad?
I don't know,
but I have to believe him.
I have no other choice.
Even if that is true,
he does not seem to care
who he hurts along the way.
Sometimes, the mission
is not worth the cost.
You know that,
so why are you still
doing what he asks?
Because if I'm wrong--
if 'm wrong, then all
of this is for nothing.
Do you understand, Tatsu?
1 left Felicity.
I left my children,
§0 if--if--if the-- if the
Monitor can't fix this
and if he is not here to help,
then all of these things
that I've sacrificed
and all the things that
so many other people
have already sacrificed
will have been for nothing.
I need my family to live,
which means that
I need this to work.
You're risking too much.
There's no other choice.
There's always another choice.
You seem stressed. Relax.
You said you wanted to talk,
so talk.
Still can't believe that you
decided to become a vigilante.
You know you always
have a place here with us.
You do have the mark.
You know why I got it.
That's right. You and
Dad's brilliant plan
to save me from the dark side.
I got it because I
wanted my brother back.
You remember when I
was in middle school?
Remember when those guys
tried to get me to run their drugs?
Not really in the mood for a
trip down memory lane, Con.
When you found
out, you were the one
that told me that I
was better than that.
Yeah. My favorite
part of that story
is when you didn't listen
and I got grounded.
Dad held me responsible.
You want to hate me?
You want to hate Dad? Fine. Ok.
That--that's fair.
Don't throw your life
away because of it.
When I look at you, I still see
the kid who'd take on
somebody twice his size
just because he
was messing with me.
Yeah. I'm not that
kid anymore, Con.
Yes, you are,
and you can try-- you can try
to snuff it out, to
cover it up with a mask,
but I know who you are,
and it's not too late.
And we can fix this...together.
You're late. I thought perhaps
you changed your mind.
Deal's a deal.
Thank you for meeting me.
Anything for a friend.
Now I have the virus.
“Where's Dr. Wong? -He's nearby.
I was surprised
when I got your call.
Well, I'm surprised that you're
not in an AR.G.U.S. prison.
Well, apparently the
government doesn't like
when agents put
bombs in people's necks.
You know what else
they don't like? Bad press.
So they bought your silence.
It's a shame your
friend Mr. Diggle
had to lose his job over it.
I assume he's here, too.
Perimeter's clean.
Tatsu, any sign of Dr. Wong?
Not yet.
I don't think he's here.
Wait. Someone's coming.
Oliver, keep her talking.
You and I...
we have been enemies
since the very beginning,
but there's something coming.
It's bigger than us.
It is something that threatens
our entire Earth.
-Let me see him.
-Give me the case.
Tatsu, we have to move now.
I see him. I'm going in.
Wait. He's wearing
some kind of vest.
It looks like explosives.
China White must
have a detonator.
It's real.
That vest is not part
of the agreement.
I had to be sure you weren't
gonna do anything stupid.
I'l deactivate it once
I'm safe in the car.
Until next time, Mr. Queen.
There's not gonna
be a next time.
Now.
Hyah!
Damn it! I'm going
after the virus!
Chien Na Wei.
Tatsu Yamashiro.
You really think this will
go better than the last time?
Ihave Dr. Wong.
Hi, honey.
Virus is secure.
I can't remove the
vest without triggering it.
We need that detonator.
Unh!
The detonator.
You better kill me now.
I have the detonator.
Tatsu?
Unh.
Looks like I'm not the only
one who needed backup.
Tatsu's resting
in the infirmary.
She'll be in pain for a
few days, but she'll be fine.
She would have been dead
if you hadn't have come
back and fought with us.
1 don't know if I'll ever
get over what happened
on Earth-2, but...
I'l help you make sure
it never happens again.
Well, at least we
accomplished our objective.
“How's Dr. Wong? He's fine.
In a secure location.
The virus is, too.
And so what-- what, do we text
the Monitor or whatever, letting
him know we have his guy?
Don't think he texts.
I don't want to hand
over Dr. Wong just yet.
I want answers, and if he is
not gonna give them to me,
I'm gonna find them
somewhere else.
Oliver, what are
you talking about?
Tatsu...
she told me that I had to be
absolutely sure that I was
making the right choice.
She almost died, John.
Alot of people have died already
for the sake of this mission.
1 owe it to all of
them to find out
who the Monitor really is.
And, Oliver, what if we don't like
the answers to those questions?
What do we do then?
We find another way to stop it.
There's always another way.
Oliver, so what's the plan?
I need to apologize
to a friend of mine first.
So...what do you say?
How about you and
me leave together?
It was a nice speech,
but once again,
you have managed to
make everything about you.
This isn't about you or Dad.
Yeah, you both have
this misguided idea
about duty and
family, civic pride.
You fail to see
the bigger picture.
I have vision.
What are you talking about?
Did you really not think that
I knew you'd show up here?
Yes. Worthless
piece of junk, my ass.
What the hell did the
Deathstrokes want with this?
What did you do?
What did you do?!
Oh. Hey, hey. I
knew that you thought
that I'd be after the
valuables in Vasquez's safe
and that Zoe
would lead you here,
the one shady trading post
that she knows about, right?
You were never after the money.
Why cripple the system
when you can rip its heart out?
Oh, my God.
Once the unification
movement is gone,
the power vacuum
is ours to fill.
- think we're done
here. Not even close.
You are not gonna touch me.
Oh, yeah? And why is that?
Because if you do,
the men who are storming
your bunker right now
will kill your brother.
William?
William, do you copy?
Like I said, I think
we're done here.
If you hurt my brother,
I swear I will kill you.
JJ...please.
You were wrong
about me, brother.
It was never a mask.
Think the doctors would have
preferred you stay in the hospital.
I have survived worse.
Brought you something.
Herbs.
-There's a rumor going around
they help with healing.
I have seen many battles.
For a moment, I
believed this was my last.
I saw Akio and Maseo,
but...this was not my time.
Tatsu, you almost
died because of me.
I'm sorry.
Well, you were right
when you said that
some missions
aren't worth the cost,
s0 I'm gonna make
sure that this one is.
So where will you go?
You heard a rumor about the
Monitor and a coming crisis?
I doubt the Crescent Order
will have the answers you seek.
Thankfully, there are
organizations on this Earth
far, far older than
the Crescent Order.
I'm going to Nanda Parbat.
You should have told me what
was going to happen on Earth-2.
John was there. He
could have been killed.
The destruction of that Earth
was a necessary sacrifice.
And what about Laurel Lance?
Her friends, her family--
Countless more
like them will perish
if we do not ensure that
Oliver Queen is prepared
for what is coming.
Were you successful?
Yes. I have Dr. Wong.
Then let us proceed.
Greg, move your head!