My name is Oliver Queen.
After 5 years in Hell,
I returned home
with only one goal--
to save my city.
Today, I fight that war
on two fronts.
By day, I lead Star City
as its mayor,
but by night,
I am someone else.
I am...Something else.
I am the Green Arrow.
Previously on "Arrow"...
You cost me
something dear to me--my son.
We decided to go
our own way.
Good luck.
It's our new lair.
Helix used to
operate out of here,
but it's not like they're
using it anymore.
So we've got them
fighting with each other
instead of fighting us.
Vincent's working
with them, too.
Oliver saw him
with James and the rest.
You don't understand.
You lying
son of a bitch.
You were the Green Arrow
for my dad.
That's right, William.
I'm sorry you
had to step in,
and I'm sorry you had
to lie to your son.
I don't want to lie
to him,
but I can do it
if it's temporary.
I may have solved
the glitch in my chip.
It worked?
Looks like we're not
as undermanned as we thought.
Yes! Ha!
I'm a city councilman!
I deserve some respect!
Hey. Didn't your shift
end at 6:00, Doc?
That's what I keep
asking myself, Gilbert.
- Hey, man.
- Hey.
Joe and I are
gonna watch the game tonight
if you want to
join us, Frank.
I wish I could.
Today's gonna be
a long one.
Aah!
All right, everybody.
Stay calm.
Oh. What was that?
What's happening?
Back away
from the walls.
Everyone, back
away from the walls.
No, no. We got
to get out of here.
No, no, no, don't!
♪ Arrow 6x11 ♪
We Fall
Original Air Date on January 25, 2018
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Bull's-eye!
Indeed it was,
young man.
- Try again, please.
- Ok.
Yes! Ha!
These things are--
you win...Again.
Well, you must be
out of practice
since you quit being
the Green Arrow.
That must be it,
yeah.
You all ready
for your field trip, yeah?
- Yeah.
- Ok.
It's the Coastal
Biology Center, right?
Yeah. There's a prep sheet
for the trip,
and I tried one
of the extra credits.
Hold on.
Will you take
a look at it?
Yeah, of course.
I meant Felicity.
Sure you did.
Yep.
I'm sorry.
It's a math problem about
hyperbolic geometry
in marine organisms
like coral.
I do know what coral is,
but that's ok.
This is
a high-dimensional math problem
most people don't get
until they're
in 12th grade AP,
and it's perfect.
Well,
congratulations.
Take your flash
backpack
and don't miss your
bus, all right?
- Ok.
- That's fine. Get out of here.
Go learn something.
- I know what coral is.
- Mm-hmm.
- Good morning.
- Morning.
Heh heh.
I think we've reached
maximum-level domesticity.
Oh, God. I certainly
hope not.
- What's up?
- Councilman Grovner is dead.
- What?
- So are 6 people in the hospital
and 5 more electrocuted
by an elevator.
- In an elevator?
- By an elevator.
What? That doesn't
make any sense.
Yeah. Quentin.
We got
a problem. An elevator--
Electrocuted 5 people.
Yeah. How do you know?
I just know.
Look. Grab Thea,
and I will meet you
at the SCPD, ok?
Oliver, one
of the casualties,
it's Frank Pike.
Oh.
Ahem.
I will see you
soon.
Frank Pike is dead.
Can you get your stuff,
can you go to the bunker?
Can you find out what's
going on, please?
- Mm-hmm.
- Thank you.
Hey. That chip's
really working.
- Yeah. I never felt better.
- That's great.
Or stronger.
- Everything all right?
- No. Not even close.
The city is under some
sort of electronic attack.
- Cayden James?
- You got to figure.
I mean, cars, cranes,
life support systems,
even elevators are
killing people all over town.
Yeah. Hacking electronics
I always thought
was a bit of a bank shot
when you have
a thermobaric bomb
and amplifier.
- And control of the port.
- Right.
It's Oliver.
Hey. I'm on with John.
What do we know?
"Hack-cidents" are happening
all over the city.
Size of this attack,
you got to think
it's Cayden James,
but to what end?
Well, should I get
William home,
or should I be happy that he's
heading out of the city?
Oh, for sure
the second one.
Let's think about looping in Dinah,
Curtis, and Rene.
We may have gone
our separate ways,
but we have
the same goals.
Do it. We need all
the help we can get.
Mr. Mayor.
Quentin, I'm--I'm
sorry about Frank.
He was a good cop,
and he was a better man.
Yeah, yeah.
He sure was,
but he wouldn't want us
standing around here grieving, right?
Listen. 911 is
on overload,
and now we got no one
here to run the show.
Yes, we do.
Just when I thought
I was out.
Can you catch me up
on the status here?
Yeah. Well, the, uh,
status keeps changing,
but I can tell you
what we know so far.
Ahh. Not bad for one
week's worth of work.
I would rather have
a team I can trust
than any kind
of technology.
Word.
It's Felicity.
She isn't bugging us
again, is she?
No.
I'll do a sweep.
- Hey.
Cayden is attacking
the city with a series
of coordinated hacks.
He just crashed
a plane.
Yeah, I know.
I mean, he can hack anything
that is connected
to the Internet,
which is practically
everything these days,
so I was thinking that
our teams,
our two separate teams,
could share information.
Yeah.
Uh, that's a good idea.
We'll share any and all
information that can help.
Ok. Thanks, Curtis.
I'll, uh, send you what I've got so far.
I hope that was
all right, guys.
I mean, I know we looked
at each other,
but we didn't actually
verbalize.
Oh, we agreed,
Curtis.
Frank Pike is dead.
What?
He was killed by one
of Cayden James' hacks.
Is Felicity
doing this?
Wait. That--
that can't be.
You know what?
The last time I saw it
doing this, it was tracking
vigilante's visor.
I know,
but he modified
his electronics to block
our signal,
but this is real.
It's locking on to him.
Because your balls
never malfunction?
Really?
Not this time,
all right,
but, I mean, could he
have messed up?
Did he forget
we could track him?
No way.
He's too devious.
I thing the son of a bitch
is trying to draw us out,
trap us.
I say we trap him.
You all in?
1, 2, 3.
Suit up!
Yeah. I don't think we
should say "suit up" all together.
It'd be really cool
if we did, though.
I don't think it would
be really cool.
I mean, let's just be
different than OTA.
Let's be, like, NTA
and say it together.
But we are NTA, and we're
cooler without having to say "suit up"...
Just saying this is
kind of what Oliver was always doing.
I'm just saying
we should just try it one time.
I'm sorry I'm late. There was
an airplane crash on State Street.
It's awful. Is this
the Cayden James
that you've been
talking about?
Most likely. Look. Quentin can bring
you up to speed.
I've asked him to run
things here with your help.
- Absolutely.
- Yeah. Listen.
We've taken SCPD
systems offline.
We're setting up
communication trees
so officers can talk
in person.
Ok. Cool. It's just
like the old days.
I'm not that old.
Look. I think it's
a great idea.
We should take everything in the city's
government on analog,
and that way, we're
out of James' reach.
In the meantime,
we need to do everything
that we can to
minimize panic.
Why don't we
set up libraries,
uh, gyms, and civic centers
with SCPD protection?
- Yeah.
- We can take them
completely off-grid,
people can come, feel safe.
Safe zones are a good idea.
Now I have to get
back to city hall
with the death
of councilman Grovner.
- No. Go. Don't worry.
- Go. Go, go, go, go. We got it.
- Ok.
- Good luck.
I got nothing
in the alleyway.
Same
for the parking garage.
Zilch here.
Back to base?
What was that?
The comms are breaking up.
Yeah. I'm getting some interference
on my side, too.
Can you guys
hear me?
No,
they can't.
You're jamming us.
I'll be brief.
I'm on your side.
Cayden James is
my target, too.
I'm undercover
with his organization.
You think this "T" on my face
stands for gullible?
You know what I mean.
I tried telling
Dinah last week,
but she didn't
give me the chance.
Right now, James is
killing dozens of people.
By tonight, it will
be hundreds.
I need your help.
Why should I trust you?
Go to the subway tunnels
where the red line
and the gold line cross
an hour from now.
You might be able to
save some lives.
Or I could lead
my teammates into a trap.
I could have trapped
you here,
but I didn't.
Harold Grovner was
a dedicated civil servant,
who always wanted
what was best for this city,
and we will not
forget that,
but with everything
that is happening,
we don't have the time
to mourn at the moment,
so, please, let's get
back to work.
Becky, I need councilmen Gattis,
McCaskill, and Kullens.
In that order, please.
Your 10 am is here.
I don't have a 10 am
on my schedule,
and even if I did, I--
I think you'll find
this one's rather important.
Ben Gale. Pleasure
to meet you, Mr. Mayor.
Thanks for making
the time.
Thank you, Becky.
I'll let you make
the usual threats in a minute,
but before we get
to that, you should know
that my colleagues
are expecting to hear from me in 6,
and if they don't,
well, you would be remiss
in forgetting
the thermobaric explosive
that remains
in my possession.
What...Do you want?
I've already told you.
Vengeance for my son.
I cared for him,
protected him, loved him
just as you do this city,
but now...your city's
entire infrastructure
is under my control--
buildings, institutions,
even people,
all under my dominion.
These are innocent
people.
And you can save them...
by wiring $10 million
into that offshore account
no later
than 11:30 tonight...
And every night
until further notice.
That will bankrupt us!
Well, I certainly
hope so.
Please don't imagine
that I've gone
to these lengths
for money.
No. This is for you
so that you'll suffer.
I didn't kill your son.
Yes, you did.
One year ago
this very day
right here
in Star City,
you missed your
intended target,
but your arrow found
its way into my boy.
Well, if you're
seeking vengeance,
if you want revenge...
Why haven't you just
outed me
as the Green Arrow?
If my understanding
is correct,
that's already
been done.
Star City will not
negotiate with a terrorist.
Oh, spare me
the political claptrap, Mr. Queen.
By tonight, that will sound hollow,
even to you.
Come on.
You ok?
I have tried
every trick
to counter-hack what
Cayden is doing,
and I am completely
boxed out,
so I contacted Alena to
help me figure out why,
and the answer is,
is that it's my fault.
Felicity, what are you
talking about?
When we stopped Cayden and Laurel
from blowing up the Internet vault...
Uh-huh.
That was all a ruse.
Cayden just wanted us
to think that people
were in trouble so
that I would break
through his firewall,
but instead
of blocking him,
I was actually just
helping him plant a virus,
and now he has complete
control of the entire city.
A hack-cident is
killing one person every 18 minutes,
and I have no idea
how to stop it.
I do
thanks to Cayden James,
who was kind enough to pay
me a visit at city hall.
- What'd he want?
- He wants $10 million a day.
That is not
the actionable part.
He told me the details
of his son's death.
He was killed one year
ago today.
Cayden thinks that he was
collateral damage
from a fight that I had
in Star City.
It's not possible.
You were in Hub City
recruiting Dinah.
Yep.
If Cayden James is
motivated by revenge,
maybe we can get him
to stand down.
Well, I like that idea
because I have no way
of stopping him my way,
and I have no location
for you to find
him your way.
Felicity, we need
incontrovertible proof.
Yeah. I know.
I'm on it.
I can't believe we
didn't catch Vincent.
He had a 20-minute
lead on us.
- Where have you been?
- Long story.
I need to check
on something.
- Hey.
- Hey. If we're still sharing
Intel, I need you
to check on something for me.
- Yeah. Shoot.
- The subway system,
specifically where the Red
and Gold line meet.
I'm trying to stave off
a disaster.
Yeah. The automatic
track signals just went offline.
- How'd you know?
- Lucky guess.
- You want backup?
- Felicity, I appreciate
the Intel, but we're
not working together anymore.
My team can handle it.
Handle what?
Cayden James is gonna attack
the subway
in less than an hour.
I'd say "suit up,"
but we already are.
Let's go.
Hey, guys.
Take a look at this.
This is the city's
transportation system,
and these are all the accidents that
have happened so far.
A lot
around the edges.
The train lines
and the freeways.
He's laying siege
to the city.
That's probably why he
wanted the port.
It's exactly
what he's doing.
He wants to block off
all the exit routes.
And stop all the reinforcements
from the outside.
Any roads he
hasn't hit yet?
Yeah. There's one exit
left out of the city,
and it's the tunnel.
William.
I saw your new mom
on TV.
She's pretty hot.
Heh heh.
She read you
bedtime stories?
Well, at least she can read,
unlike your mom.
This field trip,
it's gonna be fun.
- You sure you're good?
- Yep. Never better.
Had Cisco put
this together.
You ok?
Yeah. Yeah.
Suit up!
Let's go save your son.
Careful around
these metal lines.
Sometimes, they can
be electrified.
I know that, T.
I'm not 6.
I didn't know that.
Hey. These tracks
are set to cross.
The trains are
gonna collide.
That could be
the switch, that lever.
Pull it.
Uh! It's stuck.
These switch boxes
are locked, though.
All right. Stand back.
There we go.
Ok. Well, plan B--
actually, there is no plan B
because Cayden James
has completely overwritten
everything we
could do here.
- Maybe plan C will be--
- Guys.
We could literally
just start pulling things out
till we get
the right circuit.
Guys!
Pull it all out,
pull it all out.
It's not working.
Hurry!
Hey. What's plan D?
- There is no plan D.
- What?
Yes, there is!
Whoo!
All right. I'm gonna go
see what's going on.
You kids stay put.
I'm bored, Clayton.
Read us a story.
We have to get
out of here.
Everyone stay calm
and follow me.
We have to get
out the back!
We can still make it out.
Ok. Come on.
Move it, move it!
You two,
help them out!
Hurry, hurry!
Donnie.
We need to get out of here.
Come on, come on.
- I can't, I can't.
- We need to go! Go!
I need you to go. Go!
William!
Where's William's bus?
Go. I'll take care
of everyone else.
Go for the door,
go for the door! Move!
Come on, come on!
Get to the door!
Move, move!
Through here,
through here.
Go, go, go, go,
go, go, go!
Come on.
Where's William Clayton?
He's stuck
behind the sign.
Go, go!
Come on!
William, William.
You ok?
Dad?
We got everyone
out safely.
Unfortunately, that tunnel
was the last way out of the city.
So this is your
secret hideout?
Yeah.
You said you weren't
the Green Arrow anymore.
John did take
over for me,
but he got injured.
He's not injured
anymore.
No, he's not.
We've lost the other members
of our team, William,
and I can't have him
out there on his own right now
with everything
that's going on.
Listen, buddy.
I promise--
You've promised before.
I need to go
meet your aunt Thea.
Could you please
hang here?
Damn,
that was on fire!
Hey, man. New team Arrow's
kicking ass.
You know what?
I really have to say
that I think we should
change our name.
Like, what do you guys
think about The Outsiders?
Ooh. Um, I think it was
a really awesome book.
You know, guys, talking
to Felicity actually was a good idea.
I mean, if she hadn't
given us that Intel,
those people
would be dead.
About that.
I got that information
from Vincent Sobel.
I'm sorry. What?
I didn't trust him
at first either, ok,
but I called Felicity
to confirm
if his Intel checked out,
and it did, clearly.
And that's why you were
late getting back here earlier.
You were talking to him?
So you didn't
bother telling us?
How very
Oliver Queen of you.
I had to get
all the information first
before I looped
you guys in.
Then once I did have
all the information,
we had to stop
a subway collision,
but we did,
and now here I am,
telling you guys.
Telling us what?
Why would Vince
help us?
He says he's
a double agent working
to take down Cayden James
from the inside.
I mean, that
does track.
I mean, the guy used
to be undercover.
Which makes him
a professional liar.
He has had so many
opportunities to tell me
he is a double agent.
Why hasn't he?
He just somehow
forgot to mention it?
He says he tried to.
That is absolute crap.
Maybe, but if he
turns out to be legit,
he could offer
a tactical advantage
that we can't
turn down.
Well, I can, because
I will never work
with him again, ever.
Well, obviously,
Curtis and I disagree, so...
So nothing.
We all have to agree,
don't we,
or are we just
screwing consensus now?
Ok. So maybe
you can get some of your officers
and have them stand
over there.
- You bet.
- That'd be great. Thank you.
Thought that would
put a little extra pep in your step.
You are my savior.
What, me
or the coffee?
Why can't it
just be both?
- Hey. How are things going here?
-Hi.
Well, it's not good.
No. We got no customers at all.
There's so much
happening right now
that people are too scared to
even come to the safe zones.
And worse still,
I got cops standing around here
doing nothing when
they could be out there helping people.
I would like
to redeploy them.
No. If--if we get
people here,
then we don't need to
worry about protecting them out there.
We have no idea where Cayden James is
going to attack next.
The best thing that
we can do for the city
is to get people
to the safe zones.
Could you please call
the press?
I have an idea.
Ok.
- Yes!
- You got something?
A bull's-eye. Alena
remembered that
last May, Cayden received a package
from Corto Maltese,
and she thinks that
in that package was the evidence that
made Cayden think that
Oliver killed Owen.
And how exactly
is that a bull's-eye?
Because we know Oliver
didn't kill Owen,
so whatever was in that package,
that evidence--
That evidence had to
have been faked somehow.
- Bull's-eye! Boom.
- Right.
You ok?
Yeah. Yeah, it's just--
just stupid.
Well, you don't
do stupid, so...
I don't know.
I was just hoping that
since the implant was
working so well that maybe--
You'd be putting
the hood back on?
- Yeah.
- I'm sure you will,
you know, once this
whole Cayden thing is dealt with.
I hope so.
I hope so
for his sake.
Oh, man.
He just found out
that his father's
been lying to him for a month.
I've been trying to work up the courage
to talk with him,
but, like, step-mom
in training over here.
You'll do fine, Felicity.
Mr. Mayor.
Mr. Mayor...
Hey, Will.
Your dad's on TV.
What is happening
to this city?
Are we under
some kind of attack?
Ahem. A hacker--
goes by the name
Cayden James--
has taken over the electronic
infrastructure of Star City.
In his hands, anything--
anything that is connected
to the Internet
can be used as a weapon.
Now, sadly, this has
already led
to a number of casualties,
including our police captain,
Frank Pike,
and councilman Harold Grovner.
But Mr. James has
made his demands,
but make no mistake,
he is a terrorist,
and Star City does not negotiate
with terrorists, period.
Instead, we are gonna focus
on the safety and well-being
of our citizens.
In that spirit, the SCPD
has set up safe houses throughout the city.
These locations are
entirely analog,
and you will be safe there.
I promise you, you will
be safe there.
Mr. James, Star City has
survived far worse than you.
We will band together,
we will be united,
and we will survive this.
Thank you very much.
So predictable.
Almost takes the fun
out of it.
Time to proceed
to the next phase.
Nice speech,
and it worked.
Safe zones are filling up,
they're completely offline,
and hack-cident free,
and in other news...Yeah--
I might have a thing
on our other thing.
On Cayden James' son?
So Alena thinks that Cayden believes
that you killed his son
because of something that arrived
in a package from Corto Maltese in May.
Through a pretty cool
sequence of hacks on the mail systems
of several different countries--
not that you need to know
about it, but it was,
like, really intense and really cool,
and I did it, and it was really hard,
but you don't need
to know about those.
In that package was a USB drive,
and we actually have that USB drive's
serial number, so Alena's just working
on trying to find the computer in Corto
Maltese that uploaded
the information onto that drive that
Cayden received,
the information
that made him think
that you
killed his son.
You see how I came full circle
on that, right?
- 100%.
- Awesome.
You should go
talk to him.
I will.
- Dinah.
- Hey.
If you don't want
to work with him,
we won't.
We do it by consensus
like we agreed.
Hey. Look.
I--I acknowledge
that Vince is
a complicated variable, ok?
Well, let's
break it down.
You know, pro/con style.
All right.
Pro--he's really good,
and he gets deep
into his assignments.
Con--on our last assignment,
he got in too deep.
He can forget
what side he's on.
Pro--he's in with Cayden James
and his crew,
and his last Intel
worked.
If you didn't know
Vincent,
if you could remove
this history with him,
if, as a cop, he came to you
with some Intel,
what would your
gut tell you?
Do we have new Intel
from him?
No.
Well, then I'm not
gonna answer that yet.
You know, there's, um,
a study I was reading
that was saying that
actually talking to a child
is one of the most
effective parenting techniques.
- No kidding?
- Yeah.
- That true?
Well, I've learned
several times the hard way
that sometimes kids just
want to be left alone.
I know I have to
talk to him.
I'm just trying
to respect that.
Ok. And I might totally be
projecting here
because my dad was
a, you know, supervillain
evil hacktivist,
but he did a lot
of things
that I didn't like
or approve of,
and the way he chose
to live his life,
that's not the part
that bugged me.
Ok. What bugged you?
The lie.
All I ever wanted
was for him
to tell me
the truth, you know,
and that's all
William wants.
All he wants to
know is the truth--
the good, the bad,
the ugly.
He just wants to
know the truth.
William knows the truth,
or he--he knew
the truth,
and he decided that
he didn't want me
in situations
where he might lose me.
Ok, but here we are,
and everything
that's happened
with John
and everything
that's happened with the team,
and everything that is happening right now
with Cayden James.
Here we are,
and you know what
I think?
I think William
can handle it.
- I don't know.
- I do
because, you know,
genetics.
Aren't you ready yet?
We're moving out.
I'll be right there.
- What's going on?
- Vincent's using the link
to my T-sphere
to send a message.
Morse code.
Clever.
What does it say?
"Attack...
"Oak...
"Street...
Now."
I'm assuming that's a warning,
not a directive.
Oak Street is one
of the safe zones
Oliver and Quentin
set up.
What do we do?
Suit up.
Officers marching,
guns out,
city under siege.
It's like
"Escape From Detroit."
I don't know whether
to correct you
or to just embrace
your attempt
at referencing one of my
favorite John Carpenter films.
- Huh?
- I think the point
is that people
are scared.
It's not good.
They should
be scared.
That's why they need us.
When you say, "us,"
do you mean just you
and it's a passive dig
at our team--
no pun intended--
or do you mean
all of us and you recognize our own team
as being independent--
Curtis, we got
your message.
Thanks for
reaching out.
So what are we dealing
with here?
We have it
on good authority
this place is
Cayden James' next target.
- How do you know?
- We know.
That's all that matters.
Not to spoil the really
awkward team reunion,
but you have incoming.
Whoa. You have lots
of incoming.
We need to
move out right now!
Is dad gonna be ok?
Yeah, he's gonna be fine.
Look. I know you're not
all that happy with your dad right now,
but this--this is what
he does best,
and nobody does it
better.
But everybody
makes mistakes.
Things go wrong.
He can't plan
for everything.
Yeah, you're right.
What your dad does,
it's---it's very dangerous,
and heroes don't
always make it home.
I never forget that.
But, you know,
I've loved your dad
from the first time
he brought me
a bullet-riddled computer.
Remind me to tell you
about that one.
That was
a long time ago,
which means I've loved
him for a long time,
which means I've worried about him
for a long time,
and he--he hasn't
always been truthful.
He's lied,
he's kept secrets.
He's not perfect.
This life, it's--
it's not ideal--heh--
but he makes
his sacrifices,
so we have to make ours.
I sometimes think to myself that that's
what makes this love
deeper than other kinds
of love.
You know, it sounds
cheesy,
but it does because
we can't take things for granted.
We have to live with the fear
and the uncertainty
that everything can be taken from us
in an instant...
Traitor! I'm taking
you to hell with--
Because that's
the price we pay
for choosing the people
that we love.
Everything he does
he does for a good reason
or what he thinks is
a good reason,
so you can worry
about your dad,
but you have to believe
that he's going to be ok
because that's the only
way that this works.
Ok?
Ok. Now watch.
Now after he takes
these two down,
he's going to spin,
disarm him...Kick.
He's probably gonna
use the arrow right here!
Oh! Ooh. Wow!
You probably should not
have been allowed
to watch that.
That's definitely
in parenting 101.
Good work.
Doesn't change
anything, Hoss.
Come on.
Wow. He's--he's
pretty--
Amazing, yeah.
Well, I was gonna
say badass.
Badass.
Well, for two teams
that do not trust each other,
you guys worked
together pretty well.
Well, except for the fact
that they never shared
with us where they got
their information.
What's happening?
Cayden's shutting down
all communications--
e-mail, TV, cell phones,
Internet traffic, everything.
We didn't meet
his 11:30 deadline.
Can you please talk
to Alena and tell her
that we are running
out of time?
I already did. She's working
as fast as she can.
What are we gonna do?
I need to go talk
to my son.
You saved Rene's
life tonight.
Thank you.
I'm on your side, D.
I wasn't so sure before.
So...What now?
When I was growing up,
if something happened,
my dad would call
a family meeting
so that we could all
talk about it.
And I know we've already
both talked to you separately,
but we just thought
we'd all get together
and just sort of talk it out,
put it all in the open.
I'm terribly sorry
that I lied to you.
There is no excuse for it,
and I'm new at this
whole dad thing,
but that's not
an excuse either.
I've just--I've...
Been trying to work
my way through it,
and I've hit more bumps
in the road
than I thought
that I would, as you know,
but no more secrets
and no more lies,
and, William, if you need me
to stop being the Green Arrow...
I will.
Felicity showed me
what you did tonight.
I got to say it was--
it was really cool.
The city needs you,
and I get that now.
Are you sure?
Yeah. I mean, I was
worried before
that I'd become
an orphan,
but it's
different now.
I have Felicity.
I understand why
you have to go out there.
I'm gonna get
to bed.
Sleep well, William, ok?
What he said
was touching.
It was kind of
awful, too.
I think that's
the actual definition of bittersweet.
Ok. Well, don't let
it get to you.
- I mean, it's--it's not.
- Oliver.
It's not. It's--
if I've learned one thing
about parenting so far
that I'm sure of...
you can't win them all.
Hmm.
It's Alena.
She went through
all the computers in Corto Maltese.
She didn't find
anything. I'm sorry.
I've got to get
to city hall.
What are you
gonna do?
Wire the money.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man