[NICKI MINAJ'S "VA VA VOOM"
PLAYING OVER SPEAKER]
Hey, mister.
You feel like a dance?
SABATONI:
Absolutely.
Tonight your first night? Hmm?
First. And last, Gus.
[SABATONI GROANS]
-Helena?
-I'm looking for my father.
I figure if anybody knows where he is,
it would be his attorney.
I don't.
Ow. Whoa!
Helena, I swear I'd tell you
where the FBI is keeping Frank...
...but after your father and I
made his plea deal to testify...
...the feds,
they stopped telling me anything.
Please. You have to believe me.
I do.
Hey, Gus, song's over, man.
You still in there?
[ENGINE REVS]
Oh, my gosh.
It looks amazing.
[OLIVER CHUCKLES]
Yeah.
Steve Aoki's gonna DJ right there.
-What? How did you get Steve Aoki?
-I dated his sister.
-A million years ago. A million years ago.
-Okay.
So will you be my date tomorrow night?
-Is a club opening a proper date?
-I certainly hope so.
-Is that a yes?
-No.
That's a yes.
Laurel, I'm glad you called.
Two months is too long for us
to go without talking.
LAUREL: Dad, I have to tell you...
-No, listen.
Before you say anything,
I got to apologize.
I should never have used you
to catch the archer and I'm sorry.
-Laurel, I'm just... I'm sorry.
-Thank you.
-I owe you an apology too.
-For what?
DINAH:
Hello, Quentin.
How are you?
You look well.
What are you doing here?
Why are you here?
I'm here
because I believe Sara's still alive.
What?
-Dad. Sit.
-What is going on?
Just hear Mom out. Sit.
-What's going on?
-Start from the beginning.
Oliver was found on an island
called Lian Yu in the North China Sea.
There are hundreds,
thousands of deserted islands in this chain.
What if Sara had survived too?
Nobody would know
if she'd washed up in any of those.
So you don't actually have any proof
that she's alive?
I have proof.
A tourist took this.
-Could be anybody.
-Doesn't it look just like Sara?
Our daughter's a survivor, Quentin.
You have some nerve. Three years,
no phone calls, no e-mails, nothing.
-You just show up with an old photo... No.
-Dad, please.
Please, you listen to me, okay?
Sara died on that boat.
Why are you making me re-live this?
Why you doing this?
LAUREL: Dad...
LANCE: No.
So I told Chris and Shane
they could be our plus ones tonight...
...to Oliver's club, if they're lucky.
We both have plus ones, right?
Uh...
I don't know. Hold on just a second.
I didn't know purse snatchers
took coffee breaks.
For a stuck-up rich-bitch,
you spend a lot of time here in the Glades.
My job's around here.
-You have a job?
THEA: Yeah.
You should try it.
Instead of hanging out on a street corner
waiting to boost somebody's handbag.
Sounds good. Know anyone hiring
high-school dropouts with a couple priors...
...no references and a history of violence?
Actually, I might.
You know that new club opening
in the Glades? Verdant?
My brother owns it.
I think they might be hiring
valet attendants.
You think it's a good idea,
me taking the keys to strangers' cars?
I think it's time you put up or shut up.
Talk to your brother.
OLIVER:
Yo.
Hey.
-Where you been?
-I thought I'd give myself a rare morning in.
Don't look at me like that.
The club is opening finally.
McKenna and I are going on date
number six tonight which is...
It's significant. And, uh, I don't know.
It seemed like a good day
to give the bad guys a rest.
Well, it's the bad girls
that I'm worried about.
-Helena.
-Yes, or as I like to call her...
...your psycho ex-girlfriend.
This was taken at Alley Cats, the strip joint.
The police report lists the stiff's name
as Gus Sabatoni.
That's Bertinelli's lawyer.
Why would she come back just for him?
Not like he did a good job. Her father's
serving consecutive life sentences.
Come on, we both knew
this was just a matter of time.
You tried to help her, you couldn't.
Now the only question is how long
before she drops a dime on you...
...me, this whole operation.
Okay. I want you to get in touch
with our contacts in the Bratva.
Talk to anyone on the street, figure out
where Helena is, why she's back.
-Okay, but Oliver...
-If she's here, she's here for a reason.
If that's not Frank,
need to know what she has planned.
Okay.
[WOMEN LAUGHING]
-Speedy?
THEA: Oh, we're in here.
Look who's back.
She was just telling me
about your guys' first date at Russo's.
Hello, Oliver.
Ollie, I kind of have this pseudo friend
that's looking for a job.
-I was wondering if the club's still hiring?
-Yes. Of course. Talk to Tommy.
As a matter of fact, you can go upstairs
and call Tommy right now.
Great. You rock.
Where have you been?
Um...
Barcelona.
Monaco. Budapest.
I just needed to forget who I was.
And how much I missed you.
Do you mean like you missed
Gus Sabatoni?
I thought you were done
with your father's organization, Helena.
Because he's serving consecutive
life sentences in Iron Heights prison.
You got your revenge.
He just cut a deal
with the Justice Department...
...to testify against the East Coast Family.
In 48 hours, Witness Protection
will give him a new name, a new life...
...and he'll be off the grid forever,
untraceable.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
My father doesn't deserve
a second chance, a second life.
And I can't take on a phalanx
of U.S. Marshals.
-Not without help.
-No.
That's murder. It's not justice.
MOIRA:
Oh, there you are.
I have a question
about your opening tonight.
-Hello.
-Hi.
Oliver, who is your friend?
Oh. Mom, this is Helena.
-Helena, this is my mother.
-Hi. Nice to meet you.
-Helena was just leaving.
-Yes.
I have a family engagement.
OLIVER: Excuse us for a minute.
MOIRA: Of course.
I guess I will just have
to be more persuasive.
Fortunately, you have a family too.
She was in my house.
She made a not-so-veiled threat.
I want extra security
around my mother and sister.
-Way ahead of you, man.
-Thank you.
-It's my job.
-For not saying "I told you so."
Night's young.
Where you been?
The club's opens in four hours.
-I've been dealing with the vendors.
-No, you haven't.
Tommy.
We need to talk.
I'm sorry.
But I kept this a secret to protect the people
that are closest to me.
Do you think that's what I care about?
What, that my feelings are hurt?
You're a murderer. A killer.
You were my best friend in life,
but now it's like I don't even know you.
You're right. I've changed.
Listen, buddy, now I can explain to you.
-I can explain to you how and why...
-What'd be the point?
I wouldn't believe a word of it anyway.
One of those missiles has an effective range
of up to 2400 kilometers.
We're not going anywhere
until we figure out what Fyers is planning.
Wild guess? He's planning
on blowing something up.
Well, one of those could do that job.
But this?
This is about starting a war.
-With who?
-What does it matter?
We have to stop Fyers before he kills
thousands of innocent people.
There are a ton of soldiers.
Even if we get through all of them,
we can't just steal a whole missile launcher.
Well, who said anything
about stealing it?
So, what's the plan? Ambush?
Impossible. Can't take out six
without one radioing for backup.
It'd be good
if we could get all the soldiers in one place.
You're right.
What is...? Damn thing.
-What did the stapler ever do to you?
-What is it?
I'm busy. The Hood's girlfriend's back.
Dad, I'm sorry about this morning.
But if I told you the real reason to come
see me, you wouldn't have shown up.
You're damn right I wouldn't.
So you really believe this garbage
about Sara being alive on fantasy island?
I mean, no.
But what would it hurt to take
a look at everything that Mom found?
Even if it's just to set her straight.
You know how long it's taken...
...to get to a place where Sara isn't the first
thing I think about every morning.
Dad.
[SIGHS]
Tell your mom
I'm not making any promises.
[CLUB MUSIC PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
[CROWD CHEERING]
MOIRA:
To Verdant.
I know I haven't always been
supportive of this venture...
...but I have to admit this nightclub
is quite an accomplishment.
I'm proud of you.
Your father would be too.
-Thank you.
-Yeah, congratulations, Ollie.
-Your club doesn't totally suck.
-Thanks, Speedy.
Thank you very much, all of you,
for coming.
There you are.
This place is amazing.
I'm so proud of you and Ollie.
Thanks.
Is everything okay?
I'm great.
Well, breakfast was a disaster.
Breakfast with my parents.
Right. That was this morning.
-Sorry.
-Are you sure everything's okay?
Because you seem completely off.
I'm fine. I promise.
-Tommy. Tommy. Did you call Roy yet?
-I left him a message.
He starts tomorrow. Which reminds me,
I have to go check in with the office.
Excuse me.
Hey, Tommy. Remember me?
-I'm sorry to bother you.
-Your timing is perfect. I can't dance.
They said it was urgent.
-You okay?
OLIVER: Yeah.
-We ran out of Cristal. I'll be right back.
-Oh.
Dig?
Let him go.
He has nothing to do with this.
-I told you. Oliver, I warned you.
-Helena, this isn't you.
My father is a mobster and a murderer.
It is not like you haven't killed men
like that before.
And I tried to teach you
to obtain your objective without killing.
By applying leverage.
By exploiting someone's weakness.
[TOMMY SCREAMING]
There is a whole club full of leverage
above our heads right now.
Please.
Oliver, don't make me do something
that both of us will regret.
Okay. Okay, I... You win.
I'll help you. Let him go.
Let him go.
[TOMMY SCREAMS]
-Don't say it.
-Okay.
Then let's talk about Helena.
Oliver, if you didn't have feelings for this girl,
you would have a different solution...
...than letting her extort you
into killing.
What do you want me to do?
-You want me to kill her?
-I think you would have...
...if she looked like me
instead of the T-Mobile girl.
-She's a stone-cold killer, Oliver.
-She's not evil.
She's been lost since her father
killed her fiancé in cold blood.
And are you gonna sit there...
...and tell me that you don't know
what it's like to want revenge?
What would you do, hmm?
If Floyd Lawton
was standing right there?
Nothing that would involve
blackmailing you into hunting him down.
You're right. Okay? I can't kill her.
And I can't take her to the police
and risk her exposing all of this.
But at least if I'm involved,
I can contain her, all right?
I can minimize the collateral damage.
Sorry, am I interrupting something?
We were just talking about you.
And here I thought
you didn't care much for me.
Still don't.
I haven't been able to locate
where the FBI is keeping your father.
I can help. I've been dying to hack
into the FBI's security system.
Get out. Get out.
This is a private thing, Felicity. Please.
Oh. Okay.
See you. I guess.
How many girlfriends
do you have exactly?
Like I said, we don't know
where the safe house is.
What we know is that the Marshall
service is taking your father...
...to a hearing
at the Justice Department tonight.
There's a problem, Helena.
There are two vans.
-And one of them's a decoy.
-Well, it's a good thing there's two of us.
-It's not too late to call this off.
-I think you know me better than that.
I don't take prisoners.
OLIVER:
Hey!
I found an intruder
while I was circling the perimeter.
It's Wilson.
SOLIDER:
You killed a few of my friends, son of a bitch.
And I'm gonna kill a few more.
I'll talk to one of our lawyers
and have them call you right back.
Cut yourself shaving?
-Hi.
-Hey.
-You got a minute?
-Sure.
-How was Roy's first day?
-Kid never showed.
Um...
I just, uh... I came by
to apologize for last night.
Instead of an apology,
why don't you try the truth?
You can start with your wrist.
I got into a fight with a blender at the club.
It was stupid.
I thought I asked for the truth.
I know something's up.
Why won't you tell me what's going on?
-Because I can't.
-Why not?
I can't tell you that either.
I wish that I could.
Laurel, I'm sorry.
So am I.
I really need you right now, Tommy.
My mother shows up
saying my dead sister is still alive...
...and my father is furious with me
that I'm even listening to her.
And I don't know who to believe.
I feel like I'm falling apart.
-Laurel, I'm still here for you.
-No, you're not.
You're a million miles away and the worst
part is, I don't even know why.
I'm sorry.
Wow.
Stalker much?
-You didn't show up for the job.
-Yeah, I had second thoughts...
-...about parking your brother's Bentley.
-Being a valet is beneath you?
No. But accepting charity
from some rich girl is.
Why are you so obsessed with the fact
that I have money?
You know, money isn't everything.
Spoken like someone who's got it.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I need to get back to my life of crime.
[SIGHS]
Yo. Can you help me out? I think I'm lost.
-Where's downtown at?
-I don't know.
Maybe you can give us some directions.
Or, better yet, some money.
You okay?
You're bleeding!
Yeah, you know, that's what happens
when you get stabbed.
[GROANS]
Just your father. Anyone else gets hurt
and I'll put an arrow into you.
That's sweet.
Now I know how you charmed
your cop girlfriend.
[POLICE DISPATCHER SPEAKING
INDISTINCTLY OVER RADIO]
[POLICE SIREN WAILING IN DISTANCE]
[CAR HORN HONKING]
Give me Frank Bertinelli!
[POLICE SIREN WAILING]
LANCE:
Your father's not in the van.
But he sends his regards.
Where's the Hood?
McKENNA:
Helena Bertinelli...
...you have the right to remain silent.
Damn it.
McKENNA: Anything you say can and will
be held against you in a court of law.
You have the right to an attorney.
Paul Copani. Nick Salvati.
Gus Sabatoni.
You are quite the hunter, Miss Bertinelli.
Well, I guess
I should make that "huntress."
You've been taking down everyone
in your father's criminal organization.
When Gus Sabatoni turned up dead...
...we knew it was just a matter of time
before you tried to murder your old man.
-Do you want to tell us why?
-Not particularly.
You should reconsider.
We got you, but the vigilante got away
before ESU could move on him.
You know who he is. Who he really is.
Don't you?
[LANCE CHUCKLES]
Ms. Bertinelli, you're going away for all day.
We can't change that.
But things can be better.
Or they could be worse.
You tell me his name,
I will do everything I can to make it better.
Oliver Queen.
You're dating him now, right?
I saw you at the opening of his club
last night.
Did he mention
that we used to be lovers?
We want to know about the Hood,
not Oliver Queen.
Let me let you in on a little secret.
It's not gonna work out between you two.
You see, Oliver has a particular talent.
He uses people.
He used me.
He used the detective here's daughter.
Excuse me, daughters.
I would get out of it
before you get yourself hurt.
Last chance.
His name.
"The Hood."
[BELL RINGING]
-What the hell is going on?
McKENNA: I don't know.
Let's go.
MAN 1: Get out of here.
MAN 2: Can't see anything.
LANCE:
Freeze!
[DART GUN FIRES]
DOCTOR:
Sounds like quite the daring rescue.
You're very lucky to have a friend
like Roy, Thea.
-Oh, don't I know it.
-We're not friends.
Well, let me get you stitched up...
...and then you two can decide
what you are or aren't.
You are such a jerk.
Roy, what's the matter?
Nothing.
I just don't see why I need a shot.
Oh, don't tell me a tough gangbanger like
yourself is afraid of a tiny little needle.
-It doesn't look so tiny.
-Well, just think about something else.
-Besides the needle.
-Like what?
Okay, now this could sting a little.
Done.
Now, that wasn't so bad, was it?
Thanks for the save.
-I couldn't risk you telling police about me.
-Is that the only reason?
Why can't you just admit
that you still have feelings for me too?
-What is it?
-A plane ticket to Rome and a passport...
...so you can start a new life
somewhere else.
The police know
you're tracking your father, Helena.
You'll never find him.
So get out of my city.
Place these around the launcher.
Do it quickly.
Their backup will be arriving any second.
SOLDIER [OVER RADIO]:
We are 60 seconds out from the launcher.
Set your final charges and we'll blow it.
I think I have a better idea.
What are you doing?
I'm taking the circuit board. Computers
won't work without them. Neither will this.
Leverage.
-I'm sorry. I should've called.
-No, it's okay.
Come on in.
-Are you sure?
-Yeah, yeah.
-Thank you.
-I'm surprised, but I'm happy.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
-Everything okay?
-I had a really rough night.
I just wasn't anticipating,
with my work and the club...
...I feel like I'm letting everybody down.
My family and Tommy and you.
I feel like I'm letting you down.
You're being too hard on yourself.
We both have demanding jobs.
That's no excuse for hurting
the people closest to you.
No, but when you believe in what you do,
you find a way to make it work.
How?
Well, the first thing you do
is you find yourself someone...
...you never have to apologize to.
[PHONE VIBRATING]
Hey, I was multitasking
and intercepted a police report.
A local sporting goods store just got
robbed of one high-powered crossbow.
Now, could be a crazy coincidence
or your psycho ex-girlfriend...
Dig's words, not mine.
...is still in town.
I'll let you know if I learn anything more.
In the meantime, just watch your back.
Hi. I don't think we had a chance
to be properly introduced this morning.
-Felicity?
FELICITY: Oliver. Oliver.
OLIVER:
I'm here.
Are you okay?
Hey. Hey.
You okay?
Got your call.
-What happened?
-Helena.
She wanted the address of the safe house
where her father's kept.
She made me hack the FBI database.
-I'm sorry, Oliver.
-Hey, it's not your fault.
-Oliver, what are you gonna do?
-What I should've done in the first place.
Helena!
DISPATCHER [OVER RADIO]: Code three,
shots fired at the Bertinelli safe house.
This is Hall. I'm on-site.
LANCE [OVER RADIO]:
Wait for backup, detective. That's an order.
You won't shoot me.
-You're not a murderer, remember?
OLIVER: But you are.
And if I let you go,
that blood will be on my hands.
I'm sorry.
I practiced that move.
I had a feeling I might need it someday.
You would have killed me.
[BOTH GRUNTING]
Enough!
Freeze!
Put it down. Turn around.
Slowly.
No!
McKenna.
[KNOCKS ON DOOR]
-Hey.
How you feeling?
Ah, numb.
-Hey, don't move.
-Okay. Okay.
I met your doctor. He's a nice guy.
-He says you're lucky to be alive.
-Yeah.
He also said I have a shattered femur...
...and it's gonna take at least a year
to rehab.
-I loved being a cop.
-Oh, come on. McKenna.
You're still a cop.
You have one more surgery, go home...
-I'm not going home.
-What?
Moving to Coast City
to live with my sister.
They have the best physical therapy facility
in the country there.
I'll visit.
-I told you, I'm a billionaire, right?
-Yeah.
I'll move to Coast City.
That's very sweet,
but your club just opened.
-And your work is here.
-Don't worry about me.
-It's my responsibility to worry about you.
-Just stop, okay?
Listen, you know how I feel about you.
Please don't make this harder
than it already is.
Okay.
Okay. It's, uh...
It's whatever you need.
[SIGHS]
-Cleaning out your desk?
-No. A friend's.
Um...
You asked to see me?
Take a seat.
I'm ready to listen now.
Thank you.
TOMMY:
Hey.
I, uh, heard about McKenna. You okay?
Not really.
Look, I know
that I have been a jerk lately.
I just couldn't understand how you could
keep such a huge secret from me.
But I never considered the toll
it must take on you.
Lying to the people
that are closest to me.
It's the hardest part.
I get that.
[SIGHS]
I was wrong
to think that I could have it both ways...
...that I can do what I do...
...and still have a normal life.
-With anyone.
-Except if you're alone...
...you're never gonna be happy.
Maybe not.
But me being happy
isn't what's important right now.
Your plan. Your call.
Fyers.
Mr. Queen, I thought
I might be hearing from you.
We have the circuit board.
You are making a grave mistake.
My men are scouring the island for you
as we speak.
And when they find you,
they will kill you.
Very slowly, I'm afraid.
If your men kill us,
you'll never find the circuit board.
After that, we both know all you'll be left with
is a really ugly piece of modern art.
Then what do you propose?
-A trade.
FYERS: I see.
And what do you want in exchange?
I want a way off the island.