Previously on
"Arrow"...
I'm the one who's
testifying against you.
In a shocking fall
from grace,
the Star City council
has voted to impeach
mayor Oliver Queen
and remove him from office.
I'm thinking about
moving up your trial.
I got a lot of friends
at the courthouse.
Speculation
that the former mayor is
secretly the Green Arrow
has multiplied
in recent weeks
after his decision
to terminate two city
officials investigating him
led to his impeachment.
If convicted, Oliver Queen
could face
a life sentence.
His fate now rests
in Star City's justice system.
John.
I'm getting you
out of here.
Ha ha! What the hell
are you doing here?
I need your help
in Star City.
*ARROW*
Season 06   Episode 21
Episode Title: "Docket No.11-19-41-73"
Mr. Queen, do you
know who the Flash is?
What about the identities
of the other vigilantes
working with the Green Arrow?
Mr. Queen, how long
will this trial last?
Will you be acquitted?
And the media wonders
why everyone hates them.
Thank you,
officer.
You can wait
outside.
I'm right where
Mr. Diaz wants me.
I need to have
a privileged conversation
with my client.
Nobody's stopping you.
Since you fired
district attorney Armand,
the D.A.'s office has
brought
an outside counsel
to prosecute.
Ok, well, that
could be a good thing.
I mean, someone who's
not in Diaz's pocket.
Have you heard of
Alexa Van Owen?
Should I have heard of her?
She took down Intergang
and Bruno Mannheim.
She's prosecuted CEOs
and serial killers,
and she has CIA-caliber
investigators that say
they can find anything
and everything.
Her conviction rate is 99%.
She called me
last night,
and she offered
a plea.
Single count of first-degree
manslaughter.
That doesn't sound so bad.
With a 15-year
minimum sentence.
That sounds bad.
We're not taking that, right?
We're not taking any deal.
Look, Van Owen isn't
in Diaz's pocket,
but we have every
reason to believe
that Judge McGarvey is.
I mean, this whole
system is against you.
No deal.
Get me an acquittal.
I'm not doing it,
Rene.
I'm not playing
make believe with you.
It's a mock trial,
not make believe,
and we got to get
our stories straight.
Well, I'm planning
on pleading the fifth.
Did you have a different
amendment in mind?
We can't plead the fifth
without looking guilty.
We are guilty,
we are vigilantes,
and we know Oliver
is the Green Arrow.
Which is why we got to lie
through our teeth,
and we got to be convincing.
We got to have
our stories straight.
Hoss, you want
to weigh in on this?
You've been
real quiet.
Why? It's not like I'm
gonna have to testify.
Curtis, please don't
tell me you have FOMO
because you weren't
subpoenaed.
Yeah, I have major FOMO.
Don't I rate?
You know, maybe you are
just so much better
at maintaining your
secret identity than the rest of us.
Guys, can we be real
for a second here?
I mean, Oliver's facing
life in prison.
Yeah, and I guess
I'm just a little
bit surprised
that you care,
not that I think
you actually want Oliver to go
to prison, Rene, but come on.
Oliver's a jerk. My position
on that hasn't changed.
But what also hasn't changed
is the position
that he's in right now.
He's in it because of me.
You're right.
And I think
we can all agree
no matter what
our feelings are about Oliver,
none of us want him
to go to prison.
Am I right?
Damn right.
From where I'm sitting,
it's pretty simple.
They've got
the wrong guy.
Oliver Queen isn't
the Green Arrow
any more than I am.
And for the record,
I'm not the Green Arrow.
There appears to be
a fair amount of evidence
to suggest the former
mayor is guilty.
What evidence?
That photo from several months ago,
that was doctored.
And I don't know who
they're gonna find
to say "Oliver's the Green Arrow,"
but they'll be lying.
- You sound pretty sure of that.
- I am.
I'm the guy that arrested Oliver
6 years ago, remember?
I watched him pass
a polygraph.
He's not
the Green Arrow.
Do you know who is?
I got a few guesses.
Thank you, Mr. Mayor.
You're welcome.
Oh, hey.
Sorry. They told me
I could come in here.
Uh, no, that's fine,
right? We're finished.
Actually, maybe we could
just get some b-roll.
As the Black Canary,
you have to know who
the Green Arrow is.
I do.
And I'll testify to it
if they subpoena me.
Happy? Got your
sound bite? Good.
This looks bigger
than the O.J. trial.
How would you know?
You were in, like, fourth grade.
Yeah, but I watch
"American Crime Story."
I guess John decided
not to show.
I knew he was pissed, but
I didn't know he was that pissed.
Guys. Hey.
Thank you so much
for coming.
Well, you know,
they were subpoenaed.
But we also wanted
to show our support.
Yeah, we have
your back.
Thank you.
Really, thank you.
Hey.
So many reporters
outside.
Yeah, I know.
I'm sorry. You ok?
I always thought the worst thing that
could happen to dad
is he'd get hurt.
I know.
Ok. He's been through
something like this before.
I mean, not exactly like
this, but something and...
It's gonna be ok.
All rise.
Docket number 11-19-41-73,
"The People
vs. Oliver Jonas Queen."
Status of the parties?
Ready for trial.
Then let's begin.
Oliver Queen is a hero.
He is.
He's saved this city
more times
than anybody can count,
but he's done it all
from behind a mask
so that he could take
the law into his own hands.
In fact, he's taken
as many lives as he's saved.
So, yes, Oliver Queen
is a hero,
but that doesn't mean he's
not also a criminal.
3 weeks ago,
Oliver Queen was mayor
of this city.
In that time, he has gone
from being under indictment
to impeachment
to being on trial.
How? How could everything
go wrong so quickly for him?
I think intuitively you know
the answer.
Corruption. It runs through
this city like a cancer,
compromising some city officials
while discrediting others,
like... like the defendant.
Even the anti-vigilante law that
he's being charged under is
the work of the corrupt
men and women
who are holding our city
in their grip.
This may sound like
a conspiracy theory,
but at the conclusion
of this trial,
I'm going to ask you what is
most likely,
that our city's government
has been compromised
or that we elected a superhero
as our mayor?
Ms. Van Owen, please
call your first witness.
The people call John Diggle.
Where is he?
A bench warrant will
issue for Mr. Diggle.
If he's not made to
appear within one hour,
he'll be held in
contempt of this court.
Is your next witness
ready?
Yes, your honor.
Please state
your name and occupation
for the record.
Dr. Elisa Schwartz.
I'm an attending
physician
at Starling General
Hospital.
Thank you, Dr. Schwartz.
And you've had an occasion
to treat the defendant?
- Yes.
- For various suspicious
injuries. Is that correct?
I can't say without
violating
doctor-patient
confidentiality.
I understand.
Then let me direct your
attention, please,
to an incident when
Mr. Queen was not a patient.
On the night of
April 6, 2016,
the Green Arrow brought in
the Black Canary.
And according to your
records,
she had been stabbed.
Objection. Is there
a question in our future?
Yes. That night,
you were close enough
to the Green Arrow to
determine his identity.
So my question is, whose
face did you see that night?
I was focused on saving
Ms. Lance's life.
I wasn't the least
bit concerned
with who
the Green Arrow was.
Concern or not, whose face did you see
underneath that mask?
Well, it's not bad.
Oliver might just pull this one off.
You want to put
money on that?
Diaz wants Oliver
in prison.
You think he'd
want to kill him.
I mean, at least try.
What, so the Green Arrow
can become a martyr?
Diaz is smarter
than that.
I have to go.
Diaz yank your leash?
Something like that.
You know, you don't
have to go.
The first step to
standing up to him
is to stand up to him.
Sounds like
the first step
to getting
myself killed.
Not for nothing,
but apart from your face,
there is one thing
you've got in common
- with my Laurel.
- And what's that?
Neither of you would let
somebody else tell you
what to do or have
you running scared.
You think your Laurel
would stand up to Diaz?
I know it.
Well, maybe if she
were a little smarter,
she wouldn't have gotten
herself killed.
It's been one hour.
Mr. Diggle having not yet appeared,
he is hereby in
contempt of this court.
I'm sorry I'm late,
your honor.
I had some business to take
care of out of town.
Oliver Queen is not
the Green Arrow.
I can't make it any
plainer than that.
How can you be so sure?
From 2012-16, I was
his personal bodyguard.
If he was running around
with a bow and arrow,
I would've known it.
But would you admit
knowing it?
Why wouldn't I?
Because you were aiding
and abetting a vigilante?
I absolutely was not.
In fact, I had very limited interaction
with Oliver Queen.
How can that be?
You were head of his
security at city hall.
And my job was to keep
him safe.
And that included not
jumping off of rooftops.
Well, Mr. Diggle, you can't
even keep yourself safe.
I mean, in the past 4 years,
you've been abducted by
Damien Darhk,
your own child was
also kidnapped.
You were hospitalized
for nerve damage caused
by severe trauma.
Mr. Diggle,
either you travel
in some very dangerous
circles,
or you have
the worst luck ever.
Who was Sean Sonus?
Objection. Relevance.
- Overruled.
- Your honor?
I said, overruled.
Answer the question.
He was a drug dealer
I investigated
while undercover in the Central
City police department.
And he was shot and killed
in Hub City last year.
Your honor, I renew my
objection as to relevance.
Well, if Ms. Drake
is a murderer,
it would certainly
undermine
her credibility,
now, wouldn't it?
Objection overruled again.
Sit down, Ms. Loring.
So you were not
with the Central City police department
when Mr. Sonus was killed.
Is that correct?
- That's right.
- Did you murder him?
Your honor!
Answer the question.
I'm exercising my
fifth amendment right
against
self-incrimination.
You beckoned?
I saw something
interesting on TV.
And I'll testify to it
if they subpoena me.
Is there a problem?
Not yet,
there isn't.
You know, this would move
a lot faster
if you would stop
talking in circles.
You were given the
gift-wrapped opportunity
to say that Oliver Queen
was the Green Arrow.
You didn't do it,
baby.
I was unaware
I was supposed to.
Well, that's why
we're here
having this
little meeting,
so we can set
expectations.
The prosecution
is holding you
as a rebuttal
witness.
So when they call you,
you're gonna be
the final nail in the coffin.
If I go in and try
and convince a courtroom
that I'm Laurel Lance,
I'm gonna get made.
Maybe you're right.
You don't have
a poker face.
For example...
The way you've been
acting lately, hmm?
Ever since I torched
Fredericco
on that rooftop,
you've been keeping
your distance from me.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
It's ok.
You're ok.
I just want to be
a little clearer.
When you take
the stand,
I want you to give
the jury
a much better
performance
than the one
you're giving me.
You know what I'm
talking about now?
Good.
That's a good girl.
Got to go
to the courthouse.
It's not going
too good, is it?
Hey. No, it's going fine.
It's fine.
That was just
the prosecution's turn.
So when it's our turn, we're
gonna kick some major ass.
That's a legal term.
Why don't you go and get
yourself something
that's not too unhealthy from
the vending machine, ok?
Ok.
What will happen
if Mr. Oliver goes to jail?
He's not going
to jail, Raisa.
He's not
the Green Arrow.
I think we both know better.
I tanked it.
I did exactly
what you said not to do.
The lawyer's
good, D.
Don't worry.
I'll bring it home.
How? You got immunity
from the prosecution.
If watching every episode
of "Law & Order" ever
has taught me anything,
it's that you can't
plead the fifth.
If you get cornered and you
refuse to testify,
you could go to jail, Rene.
Well, then I'll go
to jail, Hoss.
But I'm not screwing
Oliver over again.
Hey, guys, the clerk
is calling court
back into session.
I worked in the mayor's
office close to a year,
side by side with
Mr. Queen
every single day.
If he was running around
pretending to be
Robin Hood,
I would've known.
And did you know it?
Mr. Ramirez?
Mr. Ramirez, did you have
occasion to determine
whether Oliver Queen was
the Green Arrow?
Rene.
He's the Green Arrow.
Oliver is.
And you know
this because you were
a member of his vigilante
team, weren't you?
Yeah.
And as a member
of that team,
did you ever see
the defendant
kill or maim anyone
as the Green Arrow?
Yeah.
How many people did he
kill or maim?
I don't know.
Ballpark it for me.
It's too many
to count.
Order. Order!
The prosecution
rests, your honor.
Are you ok?
Are you hurt?
I'm fine. He picked
me up from school.
He was with
a police officer.
They said you were hurt.
He was here, and we
just let him walk?
We're not
letting him walk.
Let's get out of here.
Hey, look at you.
Maybe you don't care
about people
finding out
the truth about you.
That's right. I don't care.
Whatever it takes
to stop you.
How about taking on
the entire police force?
How does that sound
to you?
You want us to
light 'em up, boss?
That depends
on them.
My man.
What do you want us
to do with them?
Nothing.
If they had
an accident
I'd have to testify,
and it'd be awkward.
Hey.
Smile. It's your
lucky day, baby.
Ok. Is this as bad
as it looks?
Arguably worse.
Can... can we prove
that, uh, Diaz was putting
pressure on Rene?
No, no, no.
I mean, even assuming
we could, the jury has
no idea
who Ricardo Diaz is.
Conventional wisdom says
you never ask a client
if they are guilty
because the more I know,
the more it might tie
my hands,
but I am gonna ask.
Are you the Green Arrow?
Yes.
Then I'm gonna propose
a new strategy.
Ok.
- Jury nullification.
- Hmm?
You're going to admit to
being the Green Arrow.
We are then going
to highlight
every single thing you
have done for this city,
all the times you have
saved it.
We will argue you do not
deserve to go to prison.
This is a legitimate
chance, Oliver.
I can't do it.
Why not?
I'd be putting a target
on my back,
on my wife and son's back.
I have been the Green Arrow
for 6 years.
I didn't plan on doing it
forever.
I thought that one day,
my mission would end
and I would finally,
after all this time,
get a chance to actually
live my life.
That will never happen...
If I tell the whole world
that I'm the Green Arrow.
You don't have
to testify.
Jean doesn't have
to call you.
Yes, she does,
and I want to testify.
I don't want you
in a position
where you perjure
yourself because of me.
Oh, well, let me just add it
to the long list of felonies
I've already committed
for you.
Look, John has
something planned.
You don't have
to take the chance.
I will take any chance
if it keeps you
from being taken away
from me and William.
Court is back
in session.
Here we go.
I graduated
Summa Cum Laude
from the Massachusetts
Institute of Technology
with master's degrees
in Cyber Security
and Computer Sciences.
From 2015-16,
I served as the CEO
of Palmer Tech,
Incorporated.
Thank you.
The defense moves to have
Ms. Smoak accepted
as an expert witness.
I don't see the point
of this, Ms. Loring.
I want the witness
testify
as to the validity of
this photograph.
Fine, but make it quick.
Ms. Smoak, this appears
to be a photograph
of your husband,
Oliver Queen,
dressed as
the Green Arrow.
Yes. The key words
being "appears to be."
This photo
has been doctored.
A pixel level analysis
will show
almost undetectable
light shifts
and resolution
inconsistencies
that would not be present
in a natural photo.
Objection, your honor.
What is the point
of showing us
an allegedly doctored
photograph at all?
The better question
would be who,
and why would they
doctor a photo
to make Oliver Queen look
like the Green Arrow
if he were the Green Arrow?
I mean, which he's not. He's
my husband. I would know.
No further questions.
When was Mr. Queen arrested?
November 21, 2017.
And when were
the two of you married?
November 28th.
- Just a week later.
- Yes.
Is it possible that you
rushed the wedding
so that you could claim
spousal privilege
just in case you had to
testify against Mr. Queen?
I have been in love
with Oliver for 6 years.
Trust me, it felt
anything but rushed.
Let's change the topic.
Your father's Noah Kuttler,
the alleged Calculator.
- Objection.
- Overruled.
He's reformed.
But before he was,
did you know that he was
a notorious computer hacker
and cyber criminal?
No. I had no idea.
Doesn't say much about your
ability to see criminality
in people close to you,
does it?
- I w...
- And under the heading
"apples falling from trees,"
have you yourself ever
engaged in cyber crime?
No, I haven't.
Good luck proving
otherwise, Ms. Van Owen.
Roy Harper is not
a vigilante.
He sacrificed himself
to protect the identity
of a man that the city
at the time
referred to as the Hood
or the Arrow.
I've since come to learn
that the Green Arrow is
the same person.
But that's not you.
It's absolutely not me.
And do you know who it is?
Yes, I do, but I will not
reveal his identity...
Not even if it sends
me to prison.
Pass the witness.
Well, that's convenient.
You're not the Green Arrow.
You know who is
the Green Arrow,
but you're not saying.
Well, I keep my promises,
Ms. Van Owen.
When did you meet
this mystery man?
Shortly after I returned
to Star City.
As you know, I was
marooned for 5 years
on an island named Lian Yu.
This photograph was taken
during that 5-year period.
I'm just curious.
Why does Lian Yu look
a lot like Russia?
- Objection.
- Overruled.
We obtained this photograph
from a reporter by the name
of Susan Williams.
I have not been
entirely forthcoming
about that period of time
in my life.
Parts of it were spent
in Hong Kong,
and, yes, parts of it
were spent in Russia.
So you lied repeatedly
and publicly.
You lied about being on
Lian Yu,
and you lied about
5 years of your life,
which begs the question,
Mr. Queen,
what else have you lied about
lied about?
Quiet! Quiet,
or I'll clear the courtroom.
Please state
your name for the record.
Thomas Merlyn. Tommy's
fine if you want.
Mr. Merlyn,
you were declared dead
May 15, 2013.
That night,
my father destroyed
a large portion
of the city.
With the heightened
scrutiny on my family,
I took the opportunity
to fake my own death
to protect my identity
as the Hood.
Three years ago, Roy Harper
confessed to being the Hood.
To protect me.
And then he was
attacked in prison.
I have lived with
that guilt for 3 years.
I am not about to let
Oliver take the blame
for me the same way
that Roy did.
And that's why
I'm here...
To set the record
straight.
Thank you. Your witness.
If you're the Green Arrow,
how come Rene Ramirez
testified under oath
that Oliver Queen is?
Well, I would suspect that
he was being pressured to.
Are you saying he
perjured himself?
Well, I don't know.
I'm not a lawyer.
I'm just
the Green Arrow.
And I am telling you
I am the only man
that has ever worn
this hood.
Mr. Merlyn,
you're under arrest
on suspicion of
murder, assault,
and violation of the
anti-vigilante act of 2017.
The bailiff will remand
Mr. Merlyn into custody.
Objection, your honor.
It's the people's contention
that Mr. Merlyn here is
not the Green Arrow.
Be that as it may,
I can't just let him walk
out of my courtroom.
You know, if it's
any consolation,
my team is
going to extract me
before I ever get
to prison, so...
Get him out of here.
Your honor, the defense
moves for a dismissal.
Nice try, but it's
the jury's job to sort out
this kind of mess,
and that's what
I'm gonna let them do.
Guys, on the way
to Iron Heights,
you think we could stop
at a drive-through?
I am starving.
We're not going to
Iron Heights.
Mr. Diaz really wants
to meet you.
All right. So where did we
land on the drive-through?
It's my treat.
Ha ha ha!
You know,
6 against one.
That's not
really a fair fight.
You should've brought
backup. I did.
You're cutting it a little close there,
aren't you, John?
What's your
exit strategy?
Sitting right there.
Well, let's go.
- Thanks for doing this.
- My pleasure.
I always wanted to say,
"I am Spartacus."
Christopher Chance.
Rene Ramirez.
Hey, I think I bought
you a perjury charge back there, Rene.
A small price to pay
for a clear conscience.
You think it worked?
At the very least,
we've created
some very serious
reasonable doubt.
Yeah. Let's hope so.
So...
When you said
I didn't have
to take the chance of
lying, that was a pun.
- I don't do puns.
- Well, that was Christopher Chance
I did just see in
there, right?
Yes. I'm sorry that
I couldn't loop you in.
We had officer Parks
listening
to every word that
we said, and I...
I didn't know Chance was
gonna use Tommy's face.
Well, yeah, I mean,
I guess they were thinking,
"What's more compelling
than a testimony from
a dead guy," right?
Excuse me.
- Mr. Mayor.
- We've got a problem.
Not anymore.
Chance just saved our bacon.
Laurel told me.
She also told me
that Diaz is making
her testify as
a rebuttal witness.
He's sending her
in there
with Chance's
entire CIA file.
She will be telling
the jury everything
about what you guys
just pulled in there,
or Diaz is going
to kill her.
How does Diaz
even know about Chance?
Because Diaz has access
to everything
that Cayden James learned
from his...
It's the bug in the bunker.
I'm sorry, Oliver.
We'll think of something.
I'll give you guys
some room.
Ok. Ok. So...
Ok, what's the something
that we're gonna think of?
Jean suggested that I just
admit I'm the Green Arrow
and we go for some sort
of jury nullification,
but I explained to her
that I would like
to have a life after
being the Green Arrow,
but, more
importantly, I...
I cannot put a target
on you and William.
Let me worry
about me and William.
Let me at least
take that off your plate.
That's not
how wedding vows work.
Well, we didn't
exchange vows.
But if we did, exchange
means "goes both ways."
So we fight for
each other, Oliver.
We protect each other.
We're gonna save each other.
I can't save anyone
from behind bars.
We'll get you out,
just like we got John out.
I could break out of
prison, Felicity,
but then what,
you know?
I... I'm not abandoning
the two of you.
I can't make the two
of you fugitives.
Oh, we're gonna be ok.
John and I have been
talking,
and, uh, if I go
to prison, I need...
You and William
to go
into A.R.G.U.S.
protective custody.
Oliver...
We're not...
We're not there yet.
We cannot live in
denial, all right?
We have to have a plan.
I can handle
losing my freedom.
I cannot handle losing
you and William.
I solemnly affirm
to tell the truth,
the whole truth, and
nothing but the truth.
Ms. Lance,
the defendant here
has publicly acknowledged
that you were
the vigilante known
as the Black Canary.
Is it fair to take
Mr. Queen at his word?
On that, at least.
And being that
the Black Canary is
a known associate of
the Green Arrow,
is it fair to say you know
his true identity?
I do. I know who
the Green Arrow is.
Good girl.
Over the course of this trial,
we heard Rene Ramirez testify
that Oliver Queen was
the Green Arrow, but a man
calling himself Tommy Merlyn
claims that identity.
Ms. Lance,
if you would, please,
just help me out here.
Who's telling the truth?
I got an idea, Hoss.
Help me out?
Let's go.
Ms. Lance...
Who is the Green Arrow?
Tommy Merlyn.
Oliver Queen is not
the Green Arrow.
Order!
Testimony being closed,
we'll take a short recess
and resume
for closing arguments.
No comment. No comment!
Hey, back up. Give her
a break, please.
Hey, hey. Listen...
Are you ok?
Until Diaz gets a hold
of me, yeah.
I thought you said you
were gonna bury Oliver.
That was the plan.
Well, what made you
change your mind?
You did.
"The first step to
standing up to him
is to stand up to him."
You can't stay in town.
Don't worry.
Thanks to you, I now know
exactly what I have to do.
Earlier, Judge McGarvey said
it fell upon you, the jury,
to sort out what he deemed
to be "a mess."
True, we have contradicting
witnesses.
And, yes, we have
conflicting testimonies,
but that is not a mess,
ladies and gentlemen.
That is the textbook definition
of reasonable doubt.
15 minutes after being taken
into custody, Tommy Merlyn
was freed by members of
the Green Arrow's team.
Now, you might take that
as evidence
that he is, in fact,
the Green Arrow,
but I would like to offer you
a much more
plausible explanation,
and that is Oliver Queen
has people and resources
at his disposal to do whatever
it takes to keep his secrets.
And don't think that
doesn't mean
someone falling out of the sky
into this courtroom
with a false face
and a made-up story.
Because Tommy Merlyn is
just another Roy Harper.
He's just another man
willing to go to prison
to cover up the crimes that
that man committed.
Don't let him get away with it.
Not again.
Not ever again.
What happens now?
It's up to the jury.
Yeah, but what if Diaz
got to them, too?
Dad!
Hey. Ha ha!
William, I love you
very much.
I love
both of you very much.
And whatever happens,
nothing is
gonna change that.
What do you mean?
I mean that the man who
wants me in prison
controls the judge,
and we think it's a pretty
good bet that he has
a strong influence
over the jury.
What does that mean?
It means I might be
going to prison, ok?
If that happens, Felicity
has assured me that she
is going to make sure
you grow into the man
that I know you can be.
I don't want you to go.
I don't want to go either.
Ok? I don't...
I wish it was up to me,
but it's not.
You are strong like me,
stronger even.
So whatever happens
and wherever I am...
You need to know that I am
always right here with you.
- What is it?
- The jury's back.
They have a verdict.
Will the defendant
please rise?
Please publish the verdict.
In the matter of the
"People v. Oliver Queen,"
on all 26 counts
of the indictment,
we find the defendant
guilty.
Members of the jury,
the court thanks you
for your service.
You're dismissed.
The defense moves
for judgment notwithstanding
the verdict.
Ms. Loring,
as you know,
the standard for granting
a JNOV requires a verdict
that no reasonable jury
could arrive at.
I find
such a circumstance here.
Your honor...
The evidence presented
was so conflicting
that it created
reasonable doubt.
The defense motion
for a judgment
notwithstanding the verdict
is granted.
Mr. Queen, see probation.
Then you're free to go.
Oh, my God. How
is this possible?
I don't know.
Congratulations, man.
Thank you.
I'm surprised Judge McGarvey had
it in him, you know?
I totally thought
he was in the tank for Diaz.
I absolutely am.
And Mr. Diaz isn't
the forgiving type.
Surprise.
Wait. Wait, wait.
When did you...?
During jury
deliberation.
You know, the judge
can argue that he got rolled,
but no one's gonna
believe him.
Thanks again, man.
I owe you another one.
Yeah, well,
after Kasnia,
let's just
call it even.
Chris...
Thank you.
Yeah. Always happy
to help.
Just try not to
need me again
for at least
another year.
That was a brilliant move.
Thank you.
Well, I wish I could
take the credit, Oliver,
but it wasn't my idea.
Dad, you might want
to close your eyes for this part.
Th... that was just one time
I was scared.
That's not cool.
That's not cool at all.
Go to your room
and lock the door.
- Is it the guy from the courtroom?
- I said, go now.
You can take a shot
at me if you want to.
Just, it's gonna ruin
me saying thank you.
You can't be too safe.
Thank you.
Don't mention it.
When I rolled over on you
last November,
I was thinking about my kid,
even though I knew it meant
it'd take you away
from yours.
I'm really sorry.
Apology accepted.
Look, I'm sorry if I...
made you feel like you
couldn't come to me
when Watson put you
in that position.
I'm very sorry
for everything that
happened afterwards.
It wasn't me.
I never did it.
Listen to me. It wasn't...
Uh!
It wasn't me, I swear.
The only law
that I abide by
is following through
on my word.
You failed at that.
So what would you
have me do?
These two men, they broke
into my chambers.
They knocked me out.
You have to...
The legal system
in this country,
it's going to hell.
You really must be
stupid,
showing your face...
After the crap
you pulled in court.
No. I'm smart enough to know
there's no place I can run
where you can't find me.
I am so sorry, Ricardo.
Fool me once.
Couldn't get it out
in time.
Come on.
I had a plan.
Get Oliver Queen
discredited,
imprisoned.
I worked for months
to make that happen.
I'm so sorry
to disappoint you.
Oh, I'm not
disappointed, baby.
I'm moving on
to plan B...
Killing
Oliver Queen...
And anyone and everyone
he cares about.