This is a duel, Oliver.
With one of the most dangerous men alive.
I wouldn't do it if I didn't think I could win.
I don't worry that you can beat him.
I am terrified you won't kill him.
That's not who you are anymore.
And I'm afraid that Ra's is gonna use
your humanity against you.
You're right.
-I'll stay.
-Really?
-Are you sure?
-I'm sure of one thing.
I love you.
[SCREAMS]
[GASPS]
[GRUNTING]
TATSU:
Oliver.
Drink this.
-More herbs?
-Penicillin.
For the infection.
-You saved my life.
-The snow and cold helped.
And your will to live. You should be dead.
Did you know Maseo would bring me here?
He was the one who told me
to meet you at this cabin.
I didn't realize
that the two of you were still in contact.
We are not.
[DOOR OPENS]
-Maseo.
-You're in no condition to stand.
Help me.
[GRUNTS]
I'm glad you stayed.
Then you'll be disappointed.
When the storm passes,
I'll return to Nanda Parbat.
Maseo.
If Ra's finds out that you saved me,
betrayed him...
...he's gonna kill you.
Don't waste your breath or worries on me.
Your concern should be for your home,
and what has become of it in your absence.
GIRL:
Help.
MAN: You picked the wrong alley.
You see, this one cuts off here at Carlyle.
You pick the next one,
and you're free and clear to Reimer Avenue.
Now, you wanna do this the hard way?
Or the harder way?
CANARY:
Hey.
Run.
[GRUNTS]
Heard rumors about a mask
used to protect girls around here.
Well, I guess you ain't her.
This is Brick's town now.
I think we should talk.
ROY:
This is gonna hurt a little.
Just one more.
Sorry. I warned you it was gonna hurt.
You said a little.
Yeah, well. Dig taught us how to suture.
I guess Felicity got the hang of it
quicker than I did.
-Where is Felicity?
-Let's talk about you.
-What do you think you're doing out there?
-Same as you.
I've had training from Oliver
and years on the streets.
You have a law degree.
Look. Heh.
I get it. Heh. This?
This isn't how you deal with grief, Laurel.
This is how you get yourself killed.
Laurel, what the hell?
-I'm fine.
-You are certifiable...
-...if you wear your sister's mask.
-Yeah, you're right.
But Oliver...
...the Arrow.
He's gone now.
And like it or not,
the Canary sends the same message.
-They fear her.
-No, Laurel.
They fear your sister.
Yeah.
She's not here anymore.
Hey.
What are you doing here?
Meeting's not for another three hours.
I convinced Mayor Castle
it might be a good idea to move it up.
What with a murderer
running amok in the city.
-Isn't that what the police are for?
-Well, she wanted to speak to city leaders.
And I'll help in whatever way I can.
And by help,
you mean money and counsel...
...not a suit powered by dwarf-star alloy
that fires lasers at people?
Well, they aren't lasers.
That'd be ridiculous.
They're compressed hard-light beams.
And they don't actually fire
because I can't get anyone...
...specifically you,
to help me fix the nanite chip.
I already told you, Ray, I'm not interested
in helping you with your suicide mission.
And there's nothing you can say or do
that is gonna change my mind.
Are you ready to go?
Hey, what are you doing here?
With Brick running around the Glades...
...I shouldn't leave my gear
anywhere he'd find it.
What are you doing here?
This neighborhood isn't a safe place
to hang out now.
Uh, I'm not hanging out,
I'm just doing my job.
Are we cool?
It just seems like you've been avoiding me
ever since we had that moment.
Moment?
You have a very high opinion
on your kissing skills.
Judging from your response,
you've got a high opinion of them too.
-Unless you need a reminder.
-No, not right now.
But, um, I'll see you later?
What are you doing here?
Went by your apartment see how packing
is going, only to discover that it's not.
I can't leave.
Not without knowing where Oliver is.
I thought I made it clear
that leaving was not optional.
No, actually,
you didn't make anything clear.
You just ordered me to uproot my life
and didn't even give me a reason why.
All you need to know is we're in danger.
Every day we remain in Starling,
the danger grows greater.
-Now get in the car, Thea.
-No.
Not until you tell me the truth.
You're not ready for the truth.
Then I guess I'm not ready
to leave Starling City.
-Yeah, I know. Yeah. Okay, I'm on it.
-Hi.
-Hey.
-Sorry I'm late.
You're not late. Castle's still hashing
things out with her people.
Um, you heard from your sister?
No. Why?
Well, she's, uh, back in town.
A girl came into the precinct
a few hours ago.
Claimed a blond in a mask
and a black leather jacket saved her life.
Thank you, everyone, for coming.
-Please take your seats.
-Yes, ma'am.
As you know, over the last week...
...a criminal organization
headed by Danny Brickwell...
...has been on a crime spree
unlike anything since Al Capone.
Which begs the question:
Why don't you arrest him?
We sent in an ESU team to do just that.
Most of those men are in the hospital now.
Now we don't know where he is.
Maybe if we had more men,
but that means more money.
Uh, I've got a few bucks. Heh. Sorry.
In fact, Palmer Technologies just made
a large donation to the S.C.P.D.
But it'll take time for that equipment
to do any good.
We need to consider calling in
the National Guard.
[GUNSHOTS AND SHOUTING]
I've always wanted to meet the mayor.
Bring her and the aldermen.
And kill the rest.
Laurel.
[GRUNTING AND SHOUTING]
See? That's why I need a technosuit.
Is Mayor Castle secure?
Yeah.
What about the aldermen?
Brick's got them.
Your penicillin tea taste like penicillin.
[OLIVER COUGHING]
We can't let him go back to the league.
It's not our choice.
Maybe we could have
changed Maseo's mind.
But not his.
Not Sarab's.
"Sarab" is just a name
that Ra's al Ghul calls him.
He's still your husband.
Thank you.
Maseo blames himself for what happened.
It wasn't his fault.
The line between grief and guilt
is a thin one.
Sometimes, death is preferable
to the agony of life.
[DANCE MUSIC PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
Track is in there.
Looks like a VIP area.
Probably where they're holding Tatsu.
-There's a lot of muscle in front of that door.
-This club is a Triad front.
-It will be heavily guarded.
-Will you do anything to get her?
Yes, I would.
I told you it would be heavily guarded.
You're late.
-That's funny.
-I wasn't talking to you.
-I was addressing your partner.
-What?
Did you bring the item?
What is she talking about?
I wanna see my wife.
I said, I want to see my wife.
Once I know she's alive,
then you can have the Alpha.
I'm sorry, Oliver.
Maseo.
What are you doing?
Hey.
-How's your heart?
-Uh...
Still beating. You okay?
Couldn't help but notice nobody
in a green hood showed up to save the day.
That's because he's gone.
-What do you mean gone?
-It means we're on our own.
That doesn't make any sense.
The Arrow's gone, but Sara's back.
Wait.
-What are you talking about?
-She's been taking out Brick's men solo.
I've been getting reports.
Blond, masked, bo-staff.
You didn't know?
I've sort of been living
under a rock these days.
Ask her to give me a call.
Yeah.
Will do.
Jim Huffman, 34, eight arrests...
...no convictions.
Grand theft auto, B and E, drugs.
You did pretty well flying solo.
What made you decide
to start working for Brick?
I'm not telling you anything.
Sure about that?
I still have another heel.
Kidding.
You don't wanna talk about Brick?
That's fine.
Then let's talk about something else.
Why would you murder...
...Julio Salazar?
Salazar?
Head of Los Halcones?
I had nothing to do
with him getting popped.
Well, that's not what your file says.
See?
What kind of game is this?
You just wrote that down.
You making this stuff up.
Actually, I can charge you
with whatever crime that I want.
Of course, then they'd have to keep you
in custody until the trial.
Good news, Bell Reve, it's a lot
more comfortable than Iron Heights.
Bell Reve's where the Los Halcones
are locked up.
They'd think I offed Salazar.
I won't last two seconds in there.
Tell me where I can find Danny,
and you won't have to.
He'll kill me.
-Charges filed by Dinah Laurel Lance...
-Stop. Stop!
I'll tell you where you can find Brick.
If you're looking for Thea...
...she's not here.
I know.
-I came to see you.
-Ha, ha.
Following me, Mr. Harper?
You need to stay away from her.
I don't know why you want her to leave,
but I'm not letting her go with you.
Well, thank you for that.
I was in need of some humor.
I wasn't joking.
You're a poison.
You put her in Ra's al Ghul's gun sights?
You had her kill Sara?
Thea knows nothing about Sara...
...and she never will.
That's where you're wrong.
I know her.
She'll get to the truth,
no matter how well you're hiding it.
And when she does find out you've
been lying, you're gonna lose her forever.
Trust me, I know from experience.
[CHUCKLES]
This is a family matter, Mr. Harper.
And you are not family.
-Sit.
-Okay.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Armed gunman attacking you, that had
to have brought back a few bad memories.
Yeah, when it started...
...all I could think about
was the night Anna died.
But when that gunman charged us,
all I could think about was...
...saving you.
[CHUCKLES]
[GRUNTS]
You were right.
I've been going about this all wrong.
When I started the A.T.O.M. Project,
it was all about avenging Anna.
But what it has become about
is protecting the people I care for.
-You mean the city?
-No.
I mean you.
You sure you wanna use that?
We have other weapons here.
-It was Sara's.
-Roy.
I thought we're on the same page.
That was before Brick
kidnapped three aldermen.
Laurel knows where they are.
We put their location in Felicity's
program, but Brick's moving them.
We can take him out en route,
but the window's closing.
Laurel, monitor us from here.
Talk me and Roy in.
No. That's not how this is gonna work.
Are you trying to get yourself killed?
You're not your sister.
You think I don't know that?
You lost a brother.
If there's anyone who I thought
would understand, it would be you.
Stay close to her.
We should have got the mayor.
That was a loss.
[GRUNTS]
You'll never get me, masked man.
Come on, throw everything that you got!
[BOMB BEEPS]
Let's go.
Laurel. Laurel, watch your 6.
[GRUNTING]
Lucky for you, I don't like hitting women.
Go, go, go!
Bad choice.
This one's on you.
No. No.
No.
Danny Brickwell is still at large tonight
after abducting three aldermen...
...from city hall earlier this evening.
Though he's managed
to evade S.C.P.D. thus far...
-Dad.
-Hey, you okay?
-Yeah.
-Two vigilantes associated with the Arrow...
...the Red Arrow and the woman in black...
...in pursuit.
Reports now trickling in
suggest a confrontation...
Your sister did her best.
Channel 52's running cell-phone footage
of her and the guy in the red hood.
Did Sara talk to you?
What? No.
Uh, she hasn't, not yet.
She must know we're seeing this.
MAN:
Mayor, there's a call for you on line one.
-Take a message.
MAN: It's Danny Brickwell.
Mr. Brickwell?
How is your evening going, Madam Mayor?
Mine's not going too well.
Because your city's vigilante problem
became mine earlier tonight.
And he's forced my hand.
Look, you have demands,
just get on with it.
No demands, just Shakespeare.
Julius Caesar.
Act five, scene two.
They stand, and would have parley.
The war stops and together they converse.
I would have parley with you.
That isn't what we're doing now?
In person. Brockton Point, one hour.
I don't negotiate with terrorists.
And certainly not in person.
You are already going to one funeral,
Madam Mayor.
If you wanna make it a hat trick,
that's your prerogative.
Me? I'll be at Brockton Point.
[DOOR CLOSES]
If you came to see
how packing is going, it's not.
No.
I came to apologize.
I don't wanna lose you, Thea.
But at the same time,
sharing the truth with you is sometimes...
...difficult for me.
Well, maybe you'll get better with practice.
-Who are we running from?
-His name is Ra's al Ghul.
Why does he wanna kill you?
Ra's has a particular code of honor
he feels I violated.
And he's marked me
and my family for death.
I fell in with Ra's because I was consumed
by the death of my wife.
And I was marked for death because
of the undertaking that killed my son.
You're all I have left, Thea.
Keeping you safe is all that matters.
Please let me.
WOMAN [ON COMPUTER]:
Alderman Richard Ford...
...was in his second term at city hall.
He leaves behind a wife and two children.
The city asks the family's privacy
be respected during this trying time.
-Though no official statement...
-Laurel? I'm sorry. I can come back.
No, it's okay. It's...
Is everything okay?
I came to ask you the same thing.
Canary.
I guess you came
to talk some sense into me.
Seems like you could use some.
I'm not sure you're gonna have to bother.
Brick, he...
He killed someone tonight.
In front of me.
I thought that being...
Being Sara would make it hurt less.
But instead, it just...
It caused more pain.
Not just for me.
So you don't have to worry.
I'm not gonna be putting on that mask again.
I'm not strong enough to fight for Sara.
Maybe you're not supposed to.
Maybe it's not about Sara. Or Oliver.
Or anyone else
that we care about who we lost.
Maybe what we've been doing...
...we've been doing it
because there are people we care about...
...that are still alive.
Maybe we're doing it for them.
I thought you quit.
CASTLE:
He's confident.
Meeting here in the open
where any police sniper could take him out.
Because he's got men who could take
the hostages out. Checkmate.
Madam Mayor.
All this for me?
I'm impressed.
What are you doing here, Palmer?
Wanna make yourself look important?
Good luck with that.
Star City.
[LAUGHING]
Seems more like Brick City to me.
The night is young.
Tough talk.
Too bad all you got is money to back it up.
But you can't fix this with money, Palmer.
I don't know.
I got a lot of money.
CASTLE: Say what you came here to say.
We can all end this farce.
Okay.
I've still got two of your men.
If you want them back, it's simple.
Get out of the Glades.
Your city servicemen,
especially the police, evacuate.
-You're out of your mind.
-You've got until midnight tomorrow.
And if I even see a hint of a blue,
your city yes-men?
They will be buried.
We won't abandon an entire district.
They did in L.A. in '92, didn't they?
Besides, you don't want every news station
in the country...
...showing footage of the murders
of the aldermen, do you?
You have 23 hours 59 minutes.
I suggest you move your sweet ass.
Captain Lance?
LANCE: Brick wants every cop out the
Glades, or he's gonna kill his hostages.
We need help. We need it now.
Look, I know you said the Arrow is gone.
Are you sure about that?
Yes, I am.
But I think I know where to find the Canary.
-The storm has passed.
-Maseo...
...you don't have to leave.
You can still have a life.
Why do you assume I want one?
Because I know you,
and this isn't who you are.
I love you.
No matter who you think you've become.
Maseo?
They found you.
Sarab, what are you doing here?
Ra's al Ghul wants Oliver Queen's remains.
I found no body, only tracks.
Which led here.
Queen is still alive.
But there is no one here.
I was just about to go.
Brothers.
We should go.
MAN:
Traitor.
MASEO:
She's the mother of my son.
-You do not get to judge me.
-Too late.
This concludes our business.
Only if the serum is genuine.
It's genuine.
Then you should have no problem
with me testing it.
It's a fake. Kill them all.
[GRUNTING AND SHOUTING]
Go, go, go!
That alderman died
because of the decision that I made.
And there's no Mirakuru
to blame this time.
Don't take that on yourself, man.
That was Brick.
What's that?
Sometimes, me and Oliver
would come down here...
...after, you know, tough nights.
He would pour this.
Look up and say:
[SPEAKING IN RUSSIAN]
What does that mean?
I have no earthly idea.
To Oliver.
We can't do this without Oliver, can we?
Felicity was right.
Actually, I was wrong.
-And I'm not wrong a lot.
-I talked to my father.
The mayor will cave
and seek control of the Glades.
-They'll evacuate police force.
-It's up to us to stop Brick.
Us? What, are you and Laurel a team now?
I was wrong
when I said Oliver's mission was over.
Because it's not just Oliver's
mission anymore. It is ours.
It's our home under attack.
For all we know, Oliver could be dead,
and Sara certainly is.
But there are people that are still alive.
People who need us.
Okay.
First, we have to find out
where those aldermen are.
-It's a bad idea.
-So you've said, repeatedly.
But it's my decision,
so do as I tell you, and give the order.
You give it. You wanna pull my men
out the Glades, fine. That's your funeral.
I don't want any part of it. Excuse me.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Hello.
LAUREL [OVER PHONE]: Hi, Daddy.
-Sara.
Where you been?
I've been worried sick about you.
I'm sorry.
I'm here.
Are you okay?
Well, yeah. I've been better.
I'm sure you have been to.
Why didn't you call me sooner?
It's complicated.
How are you doing this?
I fed recordings of Sara's voice
through a symbolic algorithm.
Daddy, I'm sorry that I've been away...
...but I don't want you to worry about me.
I'm fine.
-And I'm here to help.
-Okay. What do you need from me?
Tell me everything about the hostages.
No matter how seemingly insignificant.
I don't know how
their favorite color will help.
There has to be something.
Intel that you couldn't use
because of the mayor's orders.
I wish. The clock's running down
on these guys too.
One has a heart condition.
If his pacemaker isn't recharged soon...
...we'll lose him.
Daddy, that actually helps.
But I have to go now.
Wait, just listen to me. Be careful, okay?
I don't know what I'd do
if anything happened to you.
I'll be careful.
-I love you, sweetheart.
-I love you too, Daddy.
One alderman has a pacemaker.
-If it's remote programmable...
LAUREL: It will have a GPS.
FELICITY:
It'll take me a few minutes to log onto it.
Gear up.
This one, breakthrough. All we need's one...
-[MOUTHING] Hi.
-Yeah, hey. Just one second.
-Sorry.
-What's going on?
I need the keys to your helicopter.
How would you fly it?
I got that covered, just give me the keys.
I promise I will not crash it.
I got to be honest.
I'd feel more confident
in your aeronautic abilities...
...if you knew, for instance,
that helicopters don't actually have keys.
They don't have keys?
-No, they...
-Is it on the roof?
-Yeah, it's on the roof.
-Thank you.
I'll hold you to the no-crash promise.
You realize it's been five years
since I've flown one of these?
-Like riding a bicycle, I hope.
-We have Brick's location?
According to the last signal
from the pacemaker...
...Brick has the alderman
in a warehouse at 16th and Kent.
Not for long, he isn't.
MAN:
We got a chopper outside. Take a look.
Roger that. Checking it now.
[GRUNTING AND SHOUTING]
I guess we're even now.
Follow the hallway 20 yards.
Turn left.
Aldermen.
Come on. Don't worry,
we're gonna get you out of here.
-Let's go. Let's go.
-Go, go.
[GUNSHOTS]
Dig, I'm gonna need you
to find me a way out of here.
Copy that.
I still don't like hitting women.
But I could make an exception for you.
CANARY:
So come and get me.
You're getting warmer.
Because I will keep this city safe.
CANARY: By killing anyone
that doesn't do what you say?
Something like that.
CANARY:
Warmer.
We're not going to let you...
[GRUNTING AND SHOUTING]
It's done.
The bodies will not be found.
Okay, Maseo, I get that you wanted
to go back before, but that was before.
When Ra's finds out
that you've betrayed the league...
Maseo?
-Why the hell did you do that?
MASEO: I didn't. You did.
In a successful attempt to escape.
Or you could just come back
to Starling City with me.
[SPEAKING IN JAPANESE]
Ahem. Can I talk to you for a minute?
If you're gonna bluff
with a fake virus sample...
...let me in on it.
I wasn't bluffing.
What does that mean?
That the Alpha we stole was a fake?
That Amanda Waller knew
I would try something like this.
She must've switched the vial
before I took it.
Maseo, you were willing to risk...
...letting hundreds,
maybe thousands of people die?
For my wife.
Yes.
There's nothing I wouldn't do for my family.
Thank you.
You saved my life.
CANARY:
Dad.
[CHUCKLES]
Both aldermen are back with their families.
Nice job.
-For all the good it did.
-What does that mean?
Mayor Castle caved.
-She's pulling S.C.P.D. out of the Glades.
-But why?
Brick doesn't have the aldermen anymore.
No, but he has the home address...
...of every council member and their family
and the means to hurt them.
Played that card 15 minutes ago.
Hey, sweetheart... Hey.
How about we cry
over each other's shoulders...
...over dinner at the Chinese place you love.
I can't.
I'm sorry.
What's going on with you?
Why are you trying to avoid me?
I'll explain everything.
-Just not tonight.
-You okay?
I'm fine, Daddy. I'm fine.
-Are you ready to leave?
-No.
I'm not leaving.
Is this supposed to make up
for me missing your adolescence?
This routine of listening
and disobeying me?
Just hear me out.
You told me that we were in danger.
You even told me who was after us...
...but what you didn't tell me is why?
Yes, I did.
Because Ra's al Ghul wants us dead.
It's pretty much the case anywhere we go.
So why run?
Why not stay and fight?
Seven months ago, I asked you to teach me.
To teach me how to not be afraid
and how to not get hurt.
So why are you asking me
to be afraid now?
I am not asking you. I am telling you.
-You should be very afraid.
-Well, I'm not.
Because my father taught me not to be.
He taught me to stand my ground,
how to not give an inch in a battle.
I'm not afraid of this man,
and you shouldn't be either.
He should be afraid of us.
Then we'll stay.
FELICITY:
Your helicopter...
...is back on the roof.
I didn't crash it.
It turns out...
...it actually had keys. And this.
The reason you couldn't get
the nanite chip to function...
...is because what you actually need...
...is a quantum processor.
-The design is elegant.
-Mm-hm.
I thought you weren't gonna help me
on my suicide mission?
Well, that's the thing.
With my help, you might not end up dead.
Hey.
Thought you knew about this neighborhood
turning into a scene from The Purge.
We didn't open tonight.
I forgot my music files here,
and I've got another gig.
Are you cheating on me
with another club manager?
Well, I heard a rumor you were leaving town.
Happy to say that those rumors are false.
That's good news. For both of us.
Don't get so ahead of yourself.
My hard drive's up there.
Take your time.
[IN ARABIC]