No change?
Nope. So much blood mixed in
with so much Mirakuru.
I don't know if it's good or bad.
-We could really use that cure.
-I talked to Caitlin this morning.
We're working on it.
-No mention on Isabel Rochev's death?
-Not a thing.
I wasn't expecting a glowing obituary,
but she's a Fortune 500 CEO...
...that's been missing for a week now.
You'd think she'd have some column inches.
[THUD THEN FELICITY GASPS]
Does the fact that him lying there, freak me out,
make me a bad person?
I don't think there's a force on Earth
that could make you a bad person.
But I am starving. Dinner?
Yeah.
Uh, no Big Belly Burger though.
It's giving me a big belly.
-Sushi then.
How can you be unconscious
and freak me out at the same...
...time?
Roy?
Oh, my God.
You scared me.
-Roy?
-I forgot my phone.
[FELICITY SCREAMS]
Roy, listen.
-Dig.
-You okay?
Roy.
What's going on?
[DANCE MUSIC PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
Move, move, move.
You think Roy's okay?
Please tell me that you're not thinking
about Roy right now.
We were finally alone...
...in bed...
...in a very nice hotel room.
A hotel room that you couldn't afford.
I have something of a history
with the manager.
Mm. I can only imagine.
I think I trashed this specific room once.
But favors run out.
We should think about getting
a more permanent place.
We?
Well, you're probably getting tired
of staying with Laurel...
...and we can't sleep in the foundry
now that Roy's there, so...
But I mean, "we"?
Are you asking me to move in with you?
[CELL PHONE BUZZING]
-Hey, your phone's ringing.
-I know.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Okay, both our phones are ringing.
That's never good.
-What happened?
-I don't know. One minute, he's comatose...
...the next, he's flipping over
computer equipment.
He's a lot more out of control
than Slade was.
He looked like Roy but he wasn't Roy.
-Where do you think he's headed?
-I don't know, but we have to find him.
Despite predictions, you've managed to pull
ahead of Sebastian Blood in recent polls.
Yes. I think our message
is resonating with the voters.
The people of Starling know
that I have a vision...
...and the experienced apparatus
to make that vision a reality.
What is the main reason they should vote
for you over Alderman Blood?
Well, um...
...Alderman Blood isn't a parent.
And the soul of being a parent is making sure
that your children have a bright future...
...and I've been very lucky
to be able to do that for my own.
THEA:
Yeah, mother of the year.
Uh, we're in the middle of an interview.
I'll keep it short.
You can't have your rally at Verdant.
It's the only place I have
that hasn't been poisoned by you.
Can you give me one moment, please?
Turn it off.
Thea, I know you're upset,
and you have every right to be...
-...but we need to talk somewhere else.
-I'm done talking.
I just came by to tell you it'll be a cold day
in hell before you can use my club.
-We can't just change the venue the day before.
-I'm sure you can figure something out.
I mean, you have such
an experienced apparatus.
You signed a contract.
Huh.
Just when I thought
you couldn't go any lower...
...you threaten your own daughter.
Moira.
What's going on?
Sorry you had to witness that.
After her abduction,
I'd think the two of you'd be closer than ever.
It's a very complicated situation.
Well, my advice?
Simplify it.
You have to be either a mother
or a candidate.
You can't be both. Not right now.
You cannot split your focus.
You're absolutely right.
You're cute when you're mopey.
I'm not mopey.
Mopey's your default, Ollie.
It's part of your smoldering charm.
-I do have smoldering charm.
-Ha, ha.
But you're more-than-usual mopey.
Is everything all right?
It's fine.
Ollie?
Tommy had me out a little bit later
than maybe I should have been and...
Heh. What, I'm wiped?
Well, you want me to go?
I promised Sara I'd help her
with her trigonometry.
I don't know what that is.
You are very cute.
-Get some sleep.
-Mm-hm.
Bye.
-Good night, Mrs. Queen.
MOIRA: Good night.
-You didn't go out with Tommy last night.
-Ha, ha.
Okay. Thank you for eavesdropping on
my entire conversation, Mom. That's nice.
Sweetheart, something's bothering you.
Tell me what it is.
Dad's gonna kill me.
Your father loves you.
-I love you.
-I screwed up.
It's bad.
What happened?
I got a girl pregnant.
Laurel's pregnant?
No.
Not Laurel.
This is ridiculous. We can't just ride around
all night, hoping to lay eyes on him.
Diggle.
His place is clean.
I don't think he's been back here.
A call just went out for an ambulance
at 14th and Hobart.
There's four men seriously assaulted
by someone wearing a red hoodie.
What happened?
Guy jumped us. It came out of nowhere.
Dude is roided out or something.
Crazy-like.
MAN: See you, Sin.
-Adios.
Yo, Abercrombie.
Hold up.
Where you been, man?
I went over your place, like, 20 times.
Thea said you skipped town.
Holy crap. Have you been in a fight?
Hey!
MAN:
Hey, Sin. This guy bothering you?
No, no, no. It's chill. Seriously, just step off.
-We gonna have a problem, guy?
-Seriously? Just leave him alone. He's fine.
What, you got nothing smart to say?
[SCREAMING]
Felicity's running facial recognition
on traffic cameras.
Which could take forever. We need to take
Roy down before he attacks more people.
What part of "I want nothing to do with you"
are you not understanding?
I came by to see Sara.
And what about him? He's been stalking me.
-He's protecting you.
THEA: From what?
Slade Wilson is still at large.
-He already tried hurting you once.
-He didn't hurt me. He told me the truth.
Which I know you think is a bad thing,
but it's actually not.
It is if it cost me you.
Your lies did that.
I'm gonna go up to the stockroom,
and if I get attacked by some shot glasses...
...I'll call 911.
Thanks for taking care of her.
Lucky for me, she's not as good
at disappearing as you are.
I'll be right back.
-Have you seen Thea?
-What happened to your eye?
It's okay. I could cover it with makeup,
if I wore makeup.
-It's fine.
-Who did this to you?
SIN: It's a long story.
-I asked you who.
Roy.
But he's not right in the head.
He got injected with something, a drug,
I don't know, but it made him strong.
Like comic-book strong.
-Look, I know it sounds nuts...
-No, it really doesn't.
Sara, Roy's a friend.
He needs help, not a beatdown.
I'll have to call you right back.
You want me to stay, Mr. Blood?
Uh, no, Clinton, thank you. We'll be fine.
My new body man,
he's a little overprotective.
-Please.
-No, thank you.
I'd say this visit is unexpected
but I despise understatement.
I'm dropping out of the race. I'm making
a concession speech at my rally tonight.
You're ahead in the latest polls.
Even the most skeptical pundits are saying
you could pull this out.
I felt I owed you the courtesy
of informing you in person.
I don't, however,
owe you an explanation as well.
No, you don't.
But I'd appreciate one.
What you're doing, Moira,
as much as it benefits me...
...doesn't really make much sense.
It's my daughter.
At the moment, she needs me
more than Starling does.
Well, you're doing the right thing.
I am going to change this city, Moira.
A new day is coming.
A better day...
...for all of us.
I know things seem bleak, sweetheart,
but we're gonna figure this out, I promise.
Mom, it doesn't seem fair...
...to me.
One mistake and it...
It feels like my entire life is over.
Your life is far from over.
Are you sure it's yours?
Where there is money, Oliver,
there are people looking to take advantage.
She's not that type of person.
She's a good person, Mom. She's...
All right.
I don't know what to do. What do I do?
Heh.
We all make mistakes, Oliver.
And I'd hope that one day you'd forgive me
for any that I might make, so...
All right. Um, I'll be right back.
FELICITY: Verdant, 14th and Hobart,
and the bar Sin spotted him at.
-He looks to be moving east.
-What east?
Queen mansion.
If he still remembers where Thea lives...
Well, you used to live,
but Roy doesn't know that.
...there might be something of Roy
still in there.
Or it's a coincidence he's moving east.
I know that Sin's involved,
but don't let that cloud your judgment.
Well, don't let the fact
that this used to be Roy, cloud yours.
-Sin.
SIN [OVER PHONE]: I found Roy.
I thought I told you to go home.
Yeah, that's where I am right now.
And so is he.
Roy.
He's not here.
[GROWLING]
[GRUNTING AND SHOUTING]
It's Oliver.
It's me.
What you're doing right now...
...it's because of the Mirakuru.
You're a good person, Roy.
You have a conscience and a soul.
I need you to use those and fight this.
You can do it.
[GRUNTING AND SHOUTING]
[SCREAMING]
[TIRES SQUEALING AND SIRENS WAILING]
Drop the arrow. Drop it.
[OLIVER GRUNTS]
[SCREAMING]
No!
A full moon tonight,
that really brings out the whack jobs.
Good news is, it can't get any stranger.
My friend needs your help.
I was wrong. Gotta call you back.
Some of this damage is chronic.
The cost of jumping off rooftops, I guess.
I need to get back on my feet.
I can give you a brace, but you'll still be
in horrendous amounts of pain.
Six months ago,
this cabinet would've been empty.
The Chinese Triad was stopping
all of our med shipments...
...until someone stopped them.
Ever since, I've been looking for a way
to thank you.
If you're gonna have to follow me everywhere,
at least don't lurk, all right?
DIGGLE:
I can't let you out of my sight...
...and you're sick of seeing me everywhere you
go. Lurking seemed like a good compromise.
Yeah, well, it's not.
Family's hard.
Sometimes they're the hardest in the world.
Loving someone so much
and letting them love you back.
You know, you're right.
You should go back to lurking.
I spend a lot of time with your family.
Think that gives you the right to weigh in,
wrong.
Plus, Oliver will be out of money soon
and you'll be unemployed.
Right. Then I guess I should get this in
under the wire.
You know, your mother isn't perfect.
Her judgment definitely isn't.
There's one thing she's consistent about,
she loves you and Oliver.
And that should buy her what, in your mind?
Hell, I don't know, Thea.
But she is your mother...
...that should buy her something.
A second chance maybe?
...perpetrator of an attack that left one police
officer seriously injured and the other dead.
We have video shot by a bystander...
...but please be warned that the footage
maybe too graphic for some viewers.
Oh, my God.
-Thea?
-I have to go see a friend.
If you have to follow, follow.
These aren't gonna fix your knee.
-They'll help it heal faster.
-And until then?
-Where are we with facial recognition?
-Traffic cams can't get a clear shot.
-Now I see why you wear that hood.
-Felicity.
We need to find Roy before the police do.
Because they'll kill him and we won't?
-S.T.A.R. Labs is working on a cure.
-Which they may never come up with.
Even if they do, how many people
are we gonna let Roy kill in the meantime?
You wanted to kill Helena too.
You found another way.
That was different and you know it.
Roy has the Mirakuruin him, just like Slade.
If you had a clear shot at Slade right now,
you'd take it.
Roy isn't Slade.
Roy isn't Roy.
He's not himself anymore. He's too far gone.
I don't believe that.
Do you even hear yourself right now, Ollie?
This is the exact conversation
that we had five years ago...
...except we were freezing on Lian Yu.
OLIVER: What are you doing?
-What needs to be done.
Mirakuru won't do anything
against a head shot.
-Sara.
-Your mother's rally starts in half an hour.
I'd start getting dressed, if I were you.
[SIGHS]
She reminds me so much of me
after I came home.
When it just seemed...
It seemed impossible to believe in
anything even resembling hope.
But you did.
You did.
Eventually.
Sara will too.
THEA: Thanks for coming.
-It's chill. Who's that?
Uh, my shadow.
Uh, listen, something is going on with Roy.
I know. I saw him. He's totally crazed.
What's happening to him?
Do you remember around Christmas
when he bailed on us?
-Yeah?
-He got shot up with something, this drug...
...and it's been messing with his head.
Did you tell my brother any of this?
No. Why?
He's had this bodyguard all over me.
He must know about Roy,
think he's coming after me or something.
What are you gonna do?
THEA:
Roy?
Roy, it's me.
It's Thea.
I'm so glad I found you.
I've been looking everywhere.
This is all my fault.
I did this to you.
When you broke up with me,
it was a cry for help...
...and I didn't listen.
I should be punished.
I deserve to be punished.
Someone hurts you, you hurt them worse.
You hurt them permanently.
You should just kill me.
Kill me.
MARK:
Oliver, where have you been?
-Haven't you gotten any of my calls?
-I've been busy. What's wrong?
-It's your mother.
-She'll do fine.
No, she won't.
She's not using this event to rally the troops.
She's using it...
...to tell people she's dropping out
of the race.
Oliver.
What happened?
It's a motorcycle accident. It was stupid.
Yes, this would be the second accident
in as many weeks...
-...if my math is correct.
-Mark says you're dropping out of the race.
The truth is I should have done it
weeks ago...
...after Thea was abducted.
My complete focus needs to be
on repairing our relationship.
What's happening with Thea now isn't because
you weren't spending enough time with her.
Well, maybe not. But I have to do something,
and I'm not sure what else to do.
Thea hates you right now
because of the things that you've done.
Terrible things.
So let her see you do something good...
...as mayor.
Mom, I know a little something about...
...sacrificing the people closest to me...
...for the good of this city.
It's what you need to do now.
I know.
Good.
Oliver, I know.
I know.
I've known since last year, I suppose.
The night of the Undertaking,
everything became so clear.
It's pretty much the night I stop sleeping.
-Before you say anything else...
-There's nothing else to say.
Nothing I need to say.
Except I could not be more proud.
Can I have Raisa get you anything to drink?
Or something to eat perhaps? Please.
Where's Oliver?
He's running an errand for me.
I thought it would give us a chance to talk.
With all due respect, um, Mrs. Queen...
...what's happening,
it's between me and your son.
Yes.
What is that?
Oh, I had one of our investigators
write up at dossier on you.
I'm sorry, but it's a necessary precaution
against a fraudulent claim of paternity.
Well, the baby is Oliver's.
Oh. Of that, I have no doubt.
Our investigators were quite thorough.
But you can imagine...
...how many people my family attracts
who are looking for handouts.
Well, I'm not looking for money.
Of course not.
I told you I don't want money.
And I'm telling you
that this is my first grandchild.
And I wanna make certain
that he or she has a bright future.
Please.
This is a million dollars.
I wanna make certain
that my son has a bright future as well.
That money is yours...
...once you tell Oliver
that you've lost the baby.
What?
And another million when you return
to Central City never to speak to him again.
Can I offer you some advice,
one mother to another?
When it comes to your children,
there is no action that is inconceivable...
...there's no decision that is impossible.
You do what you must
to provide the life that they need.
And I think that $2 million is sufficient...
...to provide the life
that both our children need.
Don't you?
[CROWD CHEERING]
When I was first approached
about entering this race...
...the prospect of winning seemed a distant,
nearly impossible feat.
How could a city
that had suffered so much...
...place its faith in someone
so responsible for its suffering?
But as the weeks progressed...
...good people such as you
raised your voices in support...
...and I began to think
that I could make a difference.
I could help save this city.
But...
...recent events have changed things, and...
And now I know I can make a difference.
[CROWD CHEERING]
Should the honor become mine,
I promise with every breath I take...
...to do what is necessary.
To sacrifice what is necessary
for the good of this city.
Starling City is my home, you are my family...
...and there is nothing more important to me
than family.
Thank you. Thank you, all.
[CROWD CHEERING]
Great speech, Moira.
-A little too off-book for my liking...
-Thank you.
-...but we'll work on that.
-I thought it was perfect.
Uh, um...
Hi.
I just wanted to come up here
and say a few words.
I am so proud to have my mom here tonight.
At my club, Verdant, in the Glades.
What is she doing?
She knows this is being televised.
She's sending a message to Roy.
Trying to draw him out.
Vote Queen. Tell your friends. Thanks.
-Thea...
-That was not for you.
[GROANS]
Oh, my God, you're heavy.
Is this really all muscle?
-How many of those vitaminerals do we have?
-About 20.
-I need all of them.
-Okay. Are you sure that's a good idea?
Can you even get into those pants
with that knee?
Lidocaine, now.
FELICITY:
Okay.
-Let's see, the bottle says the proper dose...
-Is all of it.
-I don't think that's a good...
-Mm.
Oh.
Terrific speech. How did we not think
of running you years ago?
Well, thank you.
-Uh, can you give me a moment?
-Of course.
Oh, hello.
[GUNFIRE]
-We need to go now.
THEA: I can't leave without my daughter.
I'll see to the safety of your daughter.
Go. Thea, we have to go now.
No, it's Roy. I'm not leaving him.
He came here for me.
Roy.
Roy, listen to me. Listen to my voice.
I don't know what's going on...
...but I have to believe the man I fell in love with
is still inside there, somewhere.
You have to fight.
You're strong, you can fight this.
Fight this.
[GASPING]
SARA:
Roy.
Put her down.
No. Please, don't.
-He can't control it.
-That's why I don't have a choice.
SIN:
Roy.
-Get out of the way.
-Don't do this.
Kill me.
Please, kill me.
THEA:
Please, don't do it.
No one dies tonight.
You've got the police.
Go outside.
We'll get Roy the help he needs.
I promise. Go.
Tibetan pit-viper venom.
Constant dose of that
can't be good for you, right?
-It'll keep him sedated like it did Slade.
-Until when? What happens when we run out?
Not like you can buy this
over the counter, unless you're in Tibet.
Then maybe.
We'll take care of him.
I'm not ready to give up on Roy.
Anyone else crave dim sum after fisticuffs?
No? Okay, dumplings for one then.
I would've killed him.
I was ready to.
He'd be dead right now
if you hadn't have stopped me.
But he's not.
That's all that matters.
SARA:
That's not true.
I wanted to kill Roy...
...because that's what I do.
That's who I am.
I spent six years in the darkness...
...and I looked into the eyes of the devil...
...and I gave him my soul.
Let me help you get it back.
No, you deserve someone better.
Someone who can harness that light
that's still inside of you.
But I'm not that person.
-And I never will be.
-Sara.
Don't.
I'm sorry.
I just care about you too much
to be with you.
Hey.
Everything okay?
Yeah. Just had a long day.
-How's Roy?
-Well, he's alive. No thanks to me.
You know, that was brave,
getting between us.
-It took guts.
-Not really.
I knew you wouldn't really hurt him.
You're not a killer.
What's this for?
Say goodbye.
What? Wait, where are you going?
To see an old friend.
We've got every cop in this city canvassing.
We'll find this guy.
-Thank you.
-You okay?
-Fine. Where were you?
MOIRA:
He was with me.
Odd to see the two of you
are getting along again.
Thea.
You knew about Roy.
What?
That's why you had your bodyguard
stalking me.
Somehow, you knew
what was going on with him.
[SCOFFS]
I'm just trying to protect you.
By not telling me the truth.
Just like with Malcolm Merlyn.
You know, the two of you...
...you think you're protecting me
by lying and by keeping secrets.
But that's what's actually hurting me.
You're absolutely right.
-We need to turn a new page.
-It's not gonna be that simple.
-Or easy.
MOIRA: I know.
If the truth were easy for me,
we wouldn't be in this situation.
But to start...
...there's something about Malcolm
that both you and Oliver need to know.
Malcolm...
Oliver.
SHADO:
I'm dead.
[MOIRA CRYING]
Oliver?
Oliver.
I was dead the last time
you were offered this choice.
Slade.
Oliver, what's happening?
[THEA CRYING]
I often wonder how you looked...
...when he pointed the gun at Shado...
...and took her from me.
You psychopath.
Shado. Shado wasn't yours.
No, she was yours.
Until you chose another woman over her.
-That's not what happened!
-It is what happened.
It is.
She told me.
What do you mean, she?
There's nobody there.
Slade...
...you were on the island with Oliver.
I thought I had known true despair...
...until I met your son.
I trusted him to make the right choice.
Let me make the right choice now. Kill me.
MOIRA: No.
-No.
Choose me, please.
I am killing you, Oliver.
-Only more slowly than you would like.
-Don't.
-Choose.
-No, no. No.
-Don't.
-Choose.
OLIVER: Please.
SLADE: Choose.
I swear to God, I am gonna kill you.
-Choose.
-No. No.
-No.
Mom?
-Mom, what are you doing?
-There's only one way this night can end.
No.
We both know that.
Don't we, Mr. Wilson?
OLIVER:
Mom, please don't.
Both my children will live.
Mom, what are you doing?
Mom.
Thea, I love you.
-Close your eyes, baby.
-No!
No.
You possess true courage.
I'm truly sorry.
You did not pass that on to your son.
THEA:
No!
No.
There is still one person...
...who has to die...
...before this can end.
No.
THEA:
Mom?
Mom.
Well, yeah, I'm sorry too.
Well, listen, if there's ever anything
that I can do...
Hello?
Who was that?
That was, um...
She lost the baby.
She said she's sad about it.
And she's gonna go back to school
in Central City.
Apparently, she has family there.
I'm sure this has been
very traumatic for her.
But it sounds for the best.
-Sure.
-You okay?
Yeah. Yes.
I continue to be
the luckiest guy on the planet.
What would I have done if she...?
I'm just... I'm not ready to be a dad.
No.
But someday.
It's my fondest hope for you.
I'm glad I told you.
I don't think I could've gotten through this
without you.
You're never without me.
My beautiful boy.
So...
I love you.