Previously on "Arrow"...
Last night, a group
of vigilantes saved
hundreds of lives.
So if we are going to decide
on diverting
police resources
towards stopping them,
we are not going to do that
until the people
of Star City have spoken.
How the public will decide
on the issue of vigilantism
is anyone's guess.
Mayor Queen didn't mention he was
under investigation?
Of course he did.
Which makes us
overdue for a chat.
I'm not the man
you think I am.
No, Mr. Queen.
I think you are.
Cayden: I was able to upload
a critical piece of code
to Arclight.
What happens now?
We take the next step.
[Indistinct chatter]
Oliver: Thanks
very much, guys.
William: Thank you.
Oh, that's very
generous of you.
Thank you, buddy.
- Thank you. All right!
- Here you go.
Oh, cranberry sauce.
Awesome.
Ok, happy Thanksgiving,
guys. Thank you very much.
Happy Thanksgiving.
It's a nice turnout.
You having fun?
Yeah! I'm really glad
we're doing this.
Me, too, buddy.
Me, too.
Hey.
[Clicks tongue]
How do you think
Felicity's doing?
Uh, you should go
save her.
Can you comment on
speculation
Mayor Queen converted
councilwoman
Pollard's bill
into a citywide
referendum
as a distraction
from speculation
that he's
the Green Arrow?
If I was dating
the Green Arrow,
I think I would know.
Besides, the Flash is much
more my type.
Sam, she's a civilian.
Just give her a little
space, ok?
How is it that you
don't put an arrow into
one of those people?
Hey.
Oh. Did Oliver save you?
He is heroic that way.
She was doing
just fine on her own.
All right. Listen,
we're all set inside.
Um, Rene--he is a complete
pain in the ass,
but he's a very good
advanceman.
Good. Detective,
what's the tally?
Um, I got it
all here.
Good, good.
All right.
Listen, everybody.
Please gather round.
Gather round.
Mayor Queen will be making
an announcement,
and then we will be
touring
the site of the new
SCPD headquarters.
Thank you so much for
being here today, guys.
It means a ton to Felicity,
to William, to myself
that we can all gather
together as a city
and help our neediest
neighbors on Thanksgiving.
Across these various
food drives with your help,
the SCPD has collected
enough food
to feed over 1,200 families.
And it is why
I am incredibly proud
to be here today
at the unveiling
of our new precinct.
It's a top-of-the-line
facility
for a top-of-the-line
police force...
One that might
actually make
federal agencies jealous.
Ms. Watson, are you here to
tour our new headquarters?
Turn around.
We're doing this here?
Oliver Queen, you're
under arrest.
Quentin: On what charges?
Murder, assault,
burglary, and kidnapping
all stemming from your
activity as the Green Arrow.
Dad?
It's--it's gonna be
fine, buddy. I promise.
Watson: You have the right
to remain silent.
Anything you say can and will
be used against you in a court of law...
[People speaking excitedly]
Ok, the mayor's about
to come in, press in tow.
You'll give
the formal salute,
he'll say a few words, and--
I want this man
processed,
and I'm going
to need
an interrogation
room.
This is the mayor.
You can't just--
I'm a federal agent
with a valid arrest warrant.
I want this man
bound over until arraignment.
Quentin: Yes, but
you're federal. This is--
Temporary holding request.
Man: I'm going to need the ranking
lieutenant to sign off.
Then get him here.
I'm the ranking lieutenant.
Can I expect my
prisoner to be here
when I come back
for him?
Would you process the mayor
through booking, Joe?
♪ Arrow 6x07 ♪
Thanksgiving
Original Air Date on November 23, 2017
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
You did this
in front of my son.
In front of my son!
Agent Watson, when I
get out of here--
and I will--I am
going to sue you
for malicious
prosecution.
Express yourself.
In the meantime, you're
being prosecuted
for multiple felonies.
You show up after
5 years,
and the hood just happens
to show up with you?
That was Roy Harper.
Wearing the hood at
your instruction,
the same way John Diggle's
been doing
since I started my
investigation.
I've got more than you
think I have.
A confession will make
this easier on all of us.
I'd like to see William.
You're not in a position
to make demands.
I demand to see
William.
Until then, you
get nothing.
You said you weren't
the Green Arrow anymore.
I am not
Even the FBI would
agree with me there.
I--I've kept my
promise to you.
You're in jail.
I will get out of here
as soon
as I possibly can.
For now, go home
with Felicity,
and--and Raisa will
be there,
and I will be there
just as soon as I can.
Ok? I just...
I need you to be
as strong
as I know you
can be.
Ok, buddy?
Come here.
Ok, uh, this is going
to sting,
and by sting, I mean
hurt really bad.
Ok, well, as long
as it will stop this.
Well, I can't say 100%
that it will.
This is a prototype that
Felicity and I have been developing
to mass-produce
her spinal implant,
spinal, as in I'm not
sure if it'll work for your issue,
prototype as in, well,
prototype.
Let's do this.
[Groans]
God.
It took Felicity's
a while to work.
Hey, you guys need
to see this.
Dinah: Watson
just arrested Oliver
in front of basically
the entire world.
Reporter: ...Drive was
cut short.
Federal agents arrested
mayor Oliver Queen.
Accusations include several..
Son of a bitch.
Pretty much, yup.
Did she just do
all this now because she
just got through
talking to all of us?
Well, heh,
sorry.
She didn't talk
to all of us.
Heh. She actually
never talked to me.
Rene: If you got fomo about being
interrogated, don't worry.
Think you won't miss out
when we all get arrested.
I actually think we're
all in the clear for now.
Curtis: No, because cops
arrest up the food chain
in criminal
enterprises,
not to say that we're
criminal enterprises.
They don't arrest
the kingpin and his underlings.
They arrest
the underlings first.
That's how it works.
I've seen every episode
of "Closer" twice.
Well, I'm a real-life cop,
and I observed Oliver's
interrogation,
and it didn't sound like
we were targets.
That's enough.
We have to focus.
This might be the
most difficult thing
we've ever had
to face.
If people think that
the Green Arrow's in prison,
then the floodgates
will open.
Now more than ever,
we have to protect this city.
If the criminals here think that
it's open season,
then this city will
become a war zone.
You got us in here
so easily,
I didn't have a chance
to kill anybody.
Well, homicide is
not our objective here, Ms. Lance.
Two guards inside.
Laurel: What's the holdup?
Your generation's
so impatient.
Why can't you just savor
the anticipation?
[Beeping]
Cry havoc and let slip the dogs
of war, Ms. Lance.
[Dagger hits guard]
That was a literary
epigram, Ms. Lance,
not a directive.
Potato, potah-tah.
Now, what am I looking for?
The nano-thermite
device is
inside the containment
unit at the far end.
They do not have the keys.
- Wait.
- Why?
And don't say
"savor the anticipation."
Nano-thermite is
highly explosive.
Your scream will
detonate--
[Siren cry]
You do see how that could have
gone wrong, yes?
Yes, but it didn't.
Tell me what
you need.
I need some sleep.
I think I can do one
better.
FBI transfers can
get lost.
Locks can be left
open.
I appreciate that,
but if I make myself
a fugitive,
then obviously I'm
making William an orphan.
Got to do it
the right way.
Yeah. I got to do it
Ok.
Good night.
[Exhales]
The pain's feeling
a bit better.
What you got?
There was a break-in last
night at Sunderland Corp.
Why didn't we get
an alert?
Felicity has us
wired--
Up the wazoo. I know. I'm
trying to figure it out.
I mean, we're basically
the big brother of Star City,
not in a creepy way.
[Typing]
Oh, ok, this makes
more sense now.
Laurel.
Yeah, who works with
Cayden James,
who can hack
any security system
to bypass any alerts,
such as ours.
What did they steal?
Nano-thermite.
It's a metastable,
intermolecular composite,
a reactive particle.
You know, like a mint
inside of a soda. Heh!
Alone, harmless,
but together, kaboom,
as in kill lots of people, not spill
grape juice all over your cub scout--
What are they
targeting, Curtis?
I don't know.
Nano-thermite needs
to be combined
in order to be combustible,
but once it is,
there are many, many,
many possibilities.
Can you narrow it down?
No. But Felicity might
be able to.
Hey. Talk fast.
Oliver's arraignment
is in two minutes.
Laurel and Cayden James
got their hands
on a mess of nano-thermite
last night.
That means they'll
be in the market for an accelerant.
Yeah. What kind of
accelerant?
That's a really long list.
The nano-thermite heist,
did it involve a computer hack?
It involved Cayden James,
so what do you think?
I think that you can
backtrace his hack.
Maybe you can get
into his system.
But can you come back
and do this because
you're, like, way better
at this than I am.
I got to go.
Hey.
Armand: Mr. Mayor?
Sam, I didn't realize
you were joining my defense.
Can a city
district attorney--
He can't, and I'm not.
I'm sorry, Mr. Mayor,
but considering
that the charges
against you stem
from actions taken
within this city--
Is the FBI handing
you the case?
I'm sorry, Oliver.
All rise.
Docket QR2861, "State versus
Oliver Queen,"
Judge McGarvey presiding.
I understand the defense
have waived
the reading of charges
in favor of a motion.
Yes, your honor.
Defense moves to dismiss
for lack of probable cause.
The photograph with
the defendant wearing
the Green Arrow outfit
was debunked a month ago.
We're not relying
on that photo.
The FBI has provided
definitive proof
that Oliver Queen is
the Green Arrow.
Then let's see it.
Show my whole card during arraignment?
I don't think so.
Sorry, Ms. Loring,
but we're not skipping over steps here.
But, good for you, I'm going to release
the defendant on bail.
Armand: Your honor,
the defendant faces 7 counts of murder.
And he's the mayor and
sole parent of a minor.
Something tells me he's
not going anywhere,
particularly not
with a $5 million bail
and a $500,000 bond.
[Gavel pounds]
We are going to ask for
an accelerated docket
and an early
trial date.
Please tell William
not to worry.
You tell him yourself
when you get home.
I'm sorry. Do you have
half a million dollars lying around?
- Actually, I do.
- What?
The first round of
the Angel investment
for Curtis' and my
startup came through.
No. I can't let you
do that.
I can't let you not let me.
That is so not fair.
It's not supposed to be
fair, but thanks to you,
I might be able
to keep my job.
No tremor?
Almost gone.
You're a genius, Curtis.
I bet you say that to
all the geniuses. Heh!
[Computer buzzing]
What's that?
Hacker tracker.
Our friend Cayden just
infiltrated security
at Amertek, which,
as it happens,
has 20 different
possible accelerants
which could cause,
well, lots of damage.
[Inhales and exhales deeply]
Want to say it?
Call in the team
and suit up.
What's this I'm hearing about Watson
having a smoking gun?
She gave it to DA Armand.
Yeah, we need to
find out what
kind of ammunition
they work with.
No, no. I'm not risking
Felicity hacking
the FBI.
Ooh, too late.
Also, too little.
Whatever information
they have, they're keeping it offline.
Well, I can check
around the SCPD,
see if anybody's
heard anything.
Good. Quentin, let's see
if whatever it is came from city hall.
Yeah, yeah, sure.
Been a while
since I used my
detective skills.
Rene: You know, on the plus
side, you getting arrested
has done wonders
for your approval ratings.
Yeah, and it's had
the opposite effect
on the anti-vigilante
referendum, too.
There's a silver lining.
[Cell phone vibrating]
Oh, we got to go.
Well, us, not you.
There's a bad guy--or girl
who's breaking in
to Amertek.
[Quentin exhales]
I'm assuming all of
those squirrelly looks
mean that the girl
in question is what,
Laurel's evil twin?
She's working with
Cayden James,
a criminal we've been
tracking for some time.
I have been wrestling
over whether or not to tell you.
Well, I'm glad you didn't because I don't
want anything more to do with her.
Well, Quentin, now
that you know?
I will distract myself
clearing your good name.
Wow. What a warm welcome.
You really know
how to treat a girl.
'Tis the season.
I suggest keeping
your lovely singing to a minimum.
There are over a dozen
highly reactive
compounds
in this facility.
No promises.
John: Sitrep.
Ok, you got 4 turkeys
near the entrance
and 5 more stuffed in on the floor,
all puns intended.
Your window to move is now.
Copy that.
Me and Terrific have
the guys on the left,
you two--the guys on
the right. Move out. Go.
Go.
[Yelling]
[Spits]
[Groaning]
Hyah! Hyah!
Arrow!
John, what the hell's
going on?
- I'm ok.
- No, he's not.
We need to get you
out of here now.
No, you need to stop
Laurel. Go!
[Breathing heavily]
Go now! Go!
[Groaning]
The merry men are
approaching your position.
Robin Hood is laying
back for some reason.
[Gunshots]
Dinah: Take cover!
[Gunfire]
Our objective here is
the package, Ms. Lance.
[Siren cry]
Dig's been keeping this
a secret for months?
Some kind of drugs?
And he told you guys,
and then he didn't loop
me in?
It was right when
Oliver got home from Kasnia.
And he figured that
he'd be ok
after Curtis hooked him up
with that prototype thingy.
What prototype thingy?
You'll have to ask him.
Hey, speaking of,
any word from Curtis
on Dig's condition?
Stable.
They're running tests.
Feels wrong us not being
at the hospital with him.
All of us showing up
in his room
right now is the
last thing we need.
Well, Dig needs to get
back on his feet pronto,
'cause we did not exactly
shine out there without him.
[Computer beeping]
What'd Laurel steal
this time?
Only 100 pounds of
polymer-bonded explosives.
When combined with
the nano-thermite,
it--well, actually,
I don't know what happens
when they combine.
It will take
a little time
for this blood work
to come back,
but if I had to guess,
you're suffering
withdrawal from the drug
you've been taking
in combination
with Mr. Holt's
experimental treatment.
Is he gonna be ok?
I'll know more
once Mr. Diggle's
panels come back.
Thank you, doctor.
[Sighs]
I should've ran a mountain
of tests on you
before injecting you with
that prototype.
It was my choice.
Don't beat yourself
up, Curtis.
[Cell phone vibrates]
Curtis: Felicity.
Felicity: We have a problem.
We have a massively,
huge problem.
And considering it's in the same
week Oliver has been arrested.
What is it?
The nano-thermite
when combined with the explosive creates
a thermobaric weapon.
What's a thermobaric
weapon?
Felicity: It disperses
what is essentially
a cloud of fire
and then pressure-cooks
everything within 200 yards.
I'm guessing we're
giving up hope
that Cayden James has
to cook
a lot of turkeys
for Thanksgiving.
Felicity: The only good news
is that a thermobaric bomb
is extremely difficult
to make.
Yeah, well, Cayden James
can do it,
given his history,
and he'll probably
detonate it
in a populated area.
Maximize casualties.
Go help Felicity, see
if you can find out
where he's targeting.
Felicity: Hey, John...
I just heard about what's
been going on with you,
and...
I'm really sorry you've
been dealing with this.
Thank you, Felicity.
- Have you told Oliver?
- No.
I really think that
you should tell him.
Look, he just got
arrested.
I don't want to add anything
to his plate.
John, I think he'd
really want to know.
Not this week.
Thanksgiving day.
There's a million
events going on.
I mean, if you're
Cayden James,
what do you target?
Soup kitchens? Parade?
Door-buster sales.
Well, that's where
my mom took me.
Although Cayden
wouldn't guess.
He would be
logical.
He'd be calculating.
Calculating.
I saw one of his
algorithms at Helix.
It's based
on traffic patterns
and can extrapolate
to predict
population movements.
I mean, maybe if
I can re-create it.
I'm here. Uh, what
can I do to help?
You can start by telling
me what prototype you used
to treat John's condition.
Our prototype,
the one
we've been
developing
to cure paralysis.
You injected our friend
with our company's
proprietary technology,
and you didn't think to--
I don't know--
involve me in that at all?
I thought Lone Ranger
was just the way we
did things here at
Helix Dynamics.
You know, the name of
the company you picked
without consulting me.
I'm gonna work on
an algorithm over there
when I figure out
what an algorithm is.
I can't believe you just
equated a company name
to exposing a friend of ours
to an untested procedure,
one you still haven't
told me about.
It's the prototype of
your spinal implant--
well, mine, seeing as
how I'm the one who invented it,
which is why I probably
don't understand
how you get to be
so offended here.
We don't have time
for this right now.
You should
cross-reference
the crowd's patterns
with the bomb's
path of destruction.
I'll work on
a particle cloud SIM.
You could've
just told me you
didn't like the name.
It's more than just
the name.
Felicity, you picked
the product we're making.
We're working out
of your loft.
That's called being decisive,
taking initiative.
I didn't do anything
in secret.
Can we maybe fight
about this
when we don't have
a thermobaric bomb to stop?
You don't have to ask me
to do anything
because that's how you
and I work together.
It's done.
Let's hope it works.
[John exhales sharply]
I told Felicity not
to bother you with this.
Which part?
You being in
the hospital?
The experimental
steroid? Or...
The nerve damage...
that has affected
you for months?
Are you gonna be
all right?
I'll be fine.
I didn't want you
to worry, Oliver,
which is why I didn't
tell you.
No, no, John.
You didn't tell me
because you knew
I'd never let you
go out there compromised
and that I'd
certainly
never let you
compromise the team.
I've been mad at
you before, John,
but this--
is the first time
I've ever been disappointed.
Oliver, you gave up the right to judge me
when you gave up that hood.
You don't get to claim
the moral high ground here, my friend.
Oh, I'm not, Oliver,
but I apologized to the
people who I endangered--
the team,
Oliver.
The team.
My obligation begins
and ends with them.
I don't owe you
a damn thing.
For the sake of
our friendship,
I hope that's
withdrawal talking.
I put on this hood
because you asked me to.
Don't blame me for this.
I'm not blaming you, Oliver.
I blame myself...
For putting your needs,
your goals,
even your family,
above my own.
I've done that from
the very beginning.
That was my biggest
mistake.
That was your
biggest mistake?
Mine was trusting you
to be the Green Arrow.
Hey, Speedy...
I miss you.
[Chuckles softly]
I miss chatting.
They say that, um...
People in comas
can hear
other people
talking to them.
If you can hear me,
just wake up,
all right?
Please.
'Cause I need you now.
Should we order
our traditional Thanksgiving meal?
I can call Big Belly Burger.
I'm gonna crush my French fries
and pretend they're mashed potatoes.
Got it.
Maximum damage for
a thermobaric bomb
is Starling Stadium.
Today's Thanksgiving.
Yeah, we just covered that
when we talked about
ordering Turkey burgers.
Wow.
I'm saying, Billy Joel's
playing there tonight.
Sold-out crowd.
I happen to like
a wide variety of music,
and "The Stranger"
is a treasured piece
of rock and roll history.
Yeah.
Starling Stadium
seats 35,000 people.
Guess that sold-out crowd's
gonna get pressure-cooked to death.
So how do we go in
without Diggle?
We got to step it up,
fight without him.
Yeah, 'cause that went
really well at Amertek.
We have 4 hours
until showtime.
That's definitely
the place
because Cayden
already has control over the system.
What can we do about
shutting it down
or cutting the power
or something?
Tried that. Didn't work.
That's how I know Cayden has
me locked out of the grid.
Ok, I know the saying goes,
"the show must go on," but this can't.
I might be able
to help with that.
I'll declare
a state of emergency
and make them cancel
the concert.
- Did you talk to John?
- John and I spoke.
I'd like to apologize
to everyone.
I didn't know about
John's injury,
and I should have.
I will have them
shut down the concert.
I wanted to see
Billy Joel.
Like I said on the
phone, Mr. Mayor,
I'm not canceling.
The cost will
be catastrophic.
Well, so would
a terrorist attack.
You have no actionable
intelligence
or confirmation
from law enforcement.
You're asking me
to set a match
to millions of dollars
on a hunch?
Have you even brought
this to Mr. Joel?
Brought what?
You haven't given me
anything substantive.
I'm trying to save lives.
You're trying
to save your ass.
You give me some
proof--
something more than
your gut to go on--
then I'll cancel.
But without it,
we open the gates
at 7 pm.
Oh, come on.
- You all right?
- Yeah, yeah. Why you asking?
- Because you don't look it.
- Whoa!
Well, I get it.
No one wants to believe
someone that they care about
is capable of
unspeakable things.
I've been there.
[Scoffs]
Oh, yeah?
Has your daughter's
otherworldly doppelganger
been on a murder spree
lately, Dinah?
Not exactly, no,
but I did find out my
ex-boyfriend is vigilante.
What, the guy in
the ski goggles?
And I never thought in
a million years that he
had it in him.
And ever since I found out,
I've been trying to reconcile
the man that I loved
with the monster he is now.
Huh. Well, I'm sorry.
Um...Last--
last month when
Laurel attacked the bunker,
I had a chance
to stop her.
What?
Yeah. I had a gun
on her...
But I couldn't pull
the trigger,
not like I did
on Lian Yu.
Point being, you know
those people that she's been killing
you told me about?
They're on me.
That's not anywhere
close to true.
And why are you
saying that?
I'm hoping it...
Because I had a chance
to stop Vince,
and I let him go, too.
We're good people, Quentin.
We see the best in
the people we care about,
and I, for one, am not
ready to believe that
that's a bad thing.
Come back
for round 2?
No, no.
Back to apologize.
You said you put my
family in front of yours.
You did. Then I asked you
to put on the hood
to make things better
with my son, and I...
I didn't give proper
consideration to yours.
I'm truly sorry.
I was thinking about
William today, a lot,
and you getting arrested
in front of him.
How's he doing?
Oh, he's fine.
He's a tough kid,
but he is very grateful
and thankful
that you are
the Green Arrow
so I don't have to be.
Don't know how much longer
I can keep doing that,
especially
in the short-term.
You get your
test results back?
Yeah.
[Exhales]
The nerve damage
in my arm
spread to my back.
And because of
the steroid use,
I caused
permanent damage.
If I continue out
in the field,
I could end up
paralyzed.
Oh, John, I...
I really wish you hadn't have gone
to these lengths for me.
Heh. Well,
now it's my turn
to apologize to you.
I should've never
said that I
was doing it for you.
You remember last year
when the Dominators
put us into this
alternate Star City?
Yeah. Kind of
difficult to forget.
We got to see what our
perfect life would be.
Mine was being
the Green Arrow.
So you asking me
to take the mantle
was not selfish.
It was giving me
the one thing
in the world that I
never knew I wanted.
Wow.
Felicity thinks that
Cayden James is going after
Starling Stadium.
There's going to be 35,000
people there tonight.
You're the mayor.
Shut it down.
I tried. Getting arrested
is not doing a lot
for my credibility.
What are you going
to do?
I've been working on
a probable location
for Cayden's
thermobaric bomb,
but Starling Stadium
is massive.
We'll have to split up.
Still, who's going to
be calling the plays out there?
I vote Dinah.
She has the least field
experience of the three of us. No offense.
She has super powers,
tactical training, and police experience.
It's all right, Felicity.
It's all right.
We just cannot have
a repeat
of what happened
at Amertek.
Anybody have any suggestions
on how we do that?
I have a suggestion or two.
[Billy Joel singing
"No Man's Land"]
Overwatch, we're onsite.
Any luck locating
the bomb?
I'm running a code to find
the building's weakest
architectural joint--
well, targets of opportunity,
so stand by.
And I'm still trying to get
into the venue's
security system,
but Cayden has me
frozen out.
Dinah: Couldn't we
pull the alarm here,
evacuate the
stadium that way?
Rene: I'll do it.
Can't risk the SCPD spotting
you as the Green Arrow.
I have Overwatch
running interference for me on that.
If there's a cop
near you, you
will be the first
to know about it.
Still, better safe than sorry.
Joel: ♪ ...There's cable
now in zombietown ♪
♪ now we're gonna get
the closed circuits ♪
♪ now we're gonna get ♪
♪ the top 40... ♪
The bomb is definitely
down there.
I'm locking in on it.
About 400 feet up,
down corridor 52.
Joel: ♪ who remembers
when it all began ♪
♪ out here
in no man's land... ♪
Rene: Overwatch, I see
the security alarm,
but I'm not gonna pull it
like I did in high school.
[Alarm]
Felicity: I'm not seeing you on
any security cams near an alarm box.
How did you--
a magician never reveals
his secret, Hossette.
False alarm, everyone.
False alarm.
Don't worry. Go back to
your seats. Everything's ok.
Cops aren't letting anyone
out these doors.
That doesn't
make any sense.
They can't know
it's a false alarm.
Well, let's remove
any doubt.
Everybody, get
the hell out of here.
Police have locked
all the doors.
Why would cops do that?
Because they're not cops.
Get your damn hands up.
Easy. I'm just
a fan in a mask.
Overwatch, what's happening?
All you need to know
is that there's
no SCPD or FBI folks
near you.
Just focus on
the bomb.
You're, like,
super close.
Like, 50 yards.
Guys, a little help here?
Terrific, Canary, go.
Make this easy
on yourself.
It's cool, Hoss.
[Fires pistol]
[Groaning]
Overwatch,I am at the device.
The wiring's all wrong
on the thermobar--
that's not
a bomb at all.
That's a...decoy.
Freeze!
[Canary cry]
- You're welcome.
- She did all the work.
Cayden: I know
what you're thinking:
Where's the horrifically
huge bomb?
This is going to be
an incredibly insightful
evening.
Where is it?
No need to play nice.
Those jerk-wads aren't cops.
[Gunshot]
[People yelling]
Get those fans out of there.
Where is it?
Your generation is
so impatient.
Why can't you just
savor the anticipation?
[T-sphere whirs]
There is no bomb,
so relax.
And all of this?
To get your attention.
To talk, that's all.
It's not like I have
your number.
You're insane.
Thomas Szasz, the
renowned psychiatrist
and psychoanalyst,
says that there's
no such thing as
insanity.
Revenge, on the other
hand...
is very real.
Revenge.
I've never even met you.
And yet you cost me
something dear to me...
Someone very dear...
My son.
That's why I have
arranged
this little
tête-à-tête...
So that when your
city burns,
you'll know why.
[T-sphere whirring]
[Siren cry]
We ran facial recognition,
and none of those cops
are on the force.
No surprise.
Fake cops, fake uniforms,
fake bomb.
That's a lot of trouble
to go through just to have
a conversation with
the Green Arrow.
Now, did he really
lose his son?
Alena helped me
connect the dots.
There is a boy
named Owen Post,
who has Cayden James listed
as his father on his birth certificate,
but he's never been known
to live with Cayden.
Curtis: Two months
after Argus put Cayden into custody
last year,
Owen went missing.
He was never found.
H-how does this have
anything to do with the Green Arrow?
Or any of us?
You keep digging,
because even if we bear
zero responsibility,
we need to know
why Cayden James
thinks we do.
Guys, a dude I used
to code for just blasted off his link.
It's super-trending.
Yup, local news
stations are picking it up,
and, of course,
no one knows
that these cops
aren't legit.
Does anyone else find
this timing
just a little bit
too convenient, right?
The whole city is voting
on the anti-vigilante referendum today.
I guess we know
which way
Cayden James
wants them to vote.
He pulled us in to get
those videos
to sway the referendum.
That's not
all he did.
The man has
a real thermobaric bomb now.
Which he doesn't
intend to use,
at least not yet anyway.
It still sounds
pretty dangerous.
Yes, it does, but it's
a problem for another day.
How's the polling going?
It's gonna
pass, boss.
Let's prepare a statement.
Dinah: I'm right behind you.
I just need to finish up
with Lance.
Hey, you know,
if the bomb had been real,
we still would have stopped
it from going off.
Yeah, I know. Heh!
It's good to
have Oliver back in the saddle.
Yeah, that,
and you and I knew
where Cayden was targeting
because we worked on the
trace algorithm together
because we're a good team.
I'm sorry that I named
the company
without consulting you,
and I'm sorry that I picked
our first project.
And that I took the prototype
without asking you.
So there's just
one more thing
[chuckles]
That I am also sorry about.
- What?
- Um...
You know the Angel
investment we got?
Oh, wh--what?
Good evening, everybody.
I think we all would like
to applaud city officials
for conducting today's vote in such
a professional manner.
I believe in my heart
that vigilantes have worked
to make this city
a safer and better place.
I also recognize, as mayor,
that it is my duty to honor
the will of the people.
You have spoken today
and demanded the harshest
possible penalties
for anyone caught engaging
in acts of vigilantism.
Some people still believe
that includes me.
Uh, but I remain confident
that my innocence
will be proven
and I will be exonerated
at my trial.
Thank you very much,
everyone.
We'd have won
had it not been for the video.
You did great out there.
I feel like I just
kicked myself in the--
Maybe it's because
you didn't believe
a single word that
you said.
Give us a minute.
It's fine.
I'm headed back
to Washington.
Something tells me you'll
be back in time
to testify at my trial.
The time of vigilantes
is coming to an end
because how can you
idolize someone
hiding in the shadows,
who won't show his face,
who refuses to own up
to his shortcomings and culpability?
That's not a hero.
That's a coward.
What does your boy
think of you?
Leave my son out of this.
Doesn't matter what
I do, Mr. Queen.
It matters what
you do.
Are you ok, Mr. Diggle?
Well, I'm happy as hell
to be getting out of here.
And it's "John."
Oliver: William,
it's "Mr. Diggle."
And you were the Green Arrow
for my dad, right?
That's right, William.
But if you were here
last night,
who was at the stadium?
Oliver: The Green Arrow
wasn't at the stadium last night, buddy.
Just, uh, just his team.
Oh, ok.
Hey, man, let's go pull
the car around here
for Mr. Diggle.
All right.
I'm sorry you had to
step in.
And I'm sorry you
had to lie to your son.
I don't want to lie to him,
but I can do it if it's
temporary,
if I'm just, uh, subbing in
for the real Green Arrow.
What do you mean?
I mean as soon as you're
healed up,
I want you to put
that hood back on.
Oliver, I like the way
that sounds.
That makes two of us.
I'm almost ready, Doc.
Um, actually, I'm here for
Mr. Queen. It's your sister.
Something's happened.
Hi, Ollie.
Well, that stuffing
smells
a whole lot better than
this cranberry jell-o.
Oliver:
William made the stuffing.
The young man can cook.
Yeah, just like his father.
Raisa helped me a bit.
Hmm, Raisa,
as in our Raisa?
As in our Raisa, yeah.
But, uh, I have a--I have a
lot to catch you up on, so...
Yeah.
William: Uh, I'll save you
some stuffing for later
if you want, auntie Thea.
I would love that.
How did you make such
a miraculous recovery?
- Lazarus pit water.
- She's kidding.
For blast victims like Thea
in a minimally conscious state,
the trick is just to find the right drug
to literally wake her brain up.
In this case, a new form
of Zolpidem.
It's not even
on the market yet.
So more like cutting-edge
neuroscience
than--I don't know--
a miracle.
Well, it seems pretty
miraculous to me.
I missed you very much.
Felicity:
Hell of a Thanksgiving.
I've never had more
to be thankful for.
Come here. You, too.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man