My name is Oliver Queen.
After five years
on a hellish island,
I have come home
with only one goal--
to save my city.
But to do so, I can't be
the killer I once was.
To honor my friend's memory,
I must be someone else.
I must be something else.
Previously on "Arrow"...
The defendant
is found not guilty.
Hello, Moira.
What do you want, Malcolm?
Thea is my daughter.
What do these guys want
with a seven year old sub?
What's on it,
it'll save the human race.
Will it save him?
Sir, there's been
a development.
Brother Cyrus...
How do you feel?
Stronger.
What was that?
♪ Arrow 2x08 ♪
The Scientist
Original Air Date on December 4, 2013
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Mrs. Queen, welcome back
to the company.
Thank you.
You look fabulous.
Really, better than ever.
Did you do something to your hair?
Yes, I shampooed it
without eight women
and a guard
watching me.
Is it ok to laugh?
Because I was ordered
not to say anything about you being
in prison, just to avoid any awkward...
exchanges.
Like that one.
Right.
We need to drill down on these
numbers before the earnings call.
Oliver. I didn't realize
your mother was stopping by
for a visit today.
Well, it's not a visit.
This is her company, too.
Of course.
How are you, Moira?
Back, Isabel.
Mr. Queen, may I speak
to you for a minute?
What sort of message
does it send
to the investment
committee, to the city,
if we hand Queen Consolidated right
back to your mother?
She was acquitted.
By a jury.
Not by the city.
Oliver.
Stop thinking
like a son
and start thinking
like a CEO.
Oliver.
There's been a break-in.
Damn!
This door was made of expanded
reinforced titanium.
What did they use
to do this?
Not sure yet.
No sign of any explosives.
Maybe a crane,
maybe a forklift.
I'm guessing there was
at least three of them, maybe four.
And given how quick
they got in and out of here...
They were fast.
Whoa, hey, stop, wait!
You don't even
have a fare!
Any idea what these guys
were so hot to break in here for?
You didn't happen to leave
a spare earthquake machine
lying around, did you?
Sorry.
This is what we're able to
pull off the security cameras.
He was the only guy
we got on video.
The rest of the crew
must have come in after him.
Actually, it was
only one guy.
Ah, sorry I'm late.
But actually, my train was late.
Well, the second one.
The first one I did miss, but
that was my cab driver's fault.
I've got this great
traffic app, and...
But he thought
that he was right.
I'm here now,
though. So.
Great. Who the hell are you?
And do your parents
know that you're here?
I'm Barry Allen.
I'm from the Central
City police department.
I'm with the crime scene
investigation unit.
We're working on a case
with some similar
unexplained elements
in Central City,
so when the report of your robbery
came over the wire,
my captain
sent me up here.
And you think one guy ripped
through this door
like it was
tin foil?
One very
strong guy, yeah.
Uh, it takes about 1,250 foot
pounds of torque
to break someone's neck.
You see the marks
on the guard's neck?
The bruising pattern suggests
the killer used only one hand.
I'm guessing you don't know
how hard it is
to break someone's neck.
Hmm? No. No idea.
Uh, we're going to need
a list of the entire inventory here
to figure out exactly
what was stolen.
Actually, I think
I know what was stolen.
A centrifuge.
An industrial centrifuge.
Probably the Cord
Enterprises 2BX 900.
Maybe the six series.
Both have
a three column base.
Here, you can see
the three sets of broken bolts
where the thief just...
ripped it out of the ground.
And what exactly
is a centrifuge?
It separates liquids.
The centripetal acceleration
causes denser substances
to separate out
along the radial direction.
And lighter objects
move to the top.
What did you say
your name was again?
Barry. Allen.
Felicity. Smoak.
Um, you can
see the cracks
heading towards
the door. Footsteps.
One guy.
Anyway,
it's just a theory.
One backed by
a lot of evidence.
There has to be
another explanation.
Yeah. I'm sure
you're right.
You might want to fill
our mutual friend in on this.
Yeah. Don't worry.
I'm sure
he's already on it.
We need to change
directions
10 degrees north.
We need to rest.
If Ivo and any of his men
survived that blast,
they'll be tracking us.
We keep moving.
Five minutes.
You watch him,
please.
Of course.
Do you believe them?
That this Hosen will lead us
to a wrecked Japanese sub?
Ivo seems to think so.
I just hope whatever
miracle serum
they're after
is actually onboard.
For his sake.
How do you know that girl?
Sara was on
my father's boat...
with me.
What about the girl
in the picture?
Laurel?
The girl you told me
you were in love with.
Sara is her sister.
I feel like
taking a walk.
Anyone care to join me?
I guess a lot's happened
in the last year.
Oliver.
Got the final inventory
from applied sciences.
That CSI from Central City
was right.
The only thing missing
is a centrifuge.
You have to see this.
I pulled up CC traffic camera footage
from across the street
of applied sciences.
This is three minutes
after the alarm went off.
Can we help you
with something, Detective?
Oh, CSIs aren't
actually detectives.
We don't even carry guns.
Just some plastic baggies.
Uh, where should I
set up my equipment?
I'll show you.
What's going on?
Your assistant said
that you preferred
to keep
the investigation in house,
so I cleared it with my captain
to give you a hand.
What are you doing?
We need to find this intruder.
And he seems to know
more about it than any of us.
Forensic science
isn't exactly my forte, so...
I'd say we need him.
Wouldn't you?
Mm-hmm.
I'll show you around.
Why am I getting the feeling
you know more about this
than Felicity's new friend?
Pray I'm wrong.
Hi. I'm sorry
about what happened
at the office
this morning.
There are a lot of people who think
I got away with murder, Oliver.
Maybe I did.
Mom, the trial,
the Undertaking,
Malcolm Merlyn,
all of that is behind us now.
And we need everyone
to see that.
How are we going to do that?
We throw a party.
Thea.
Roy.
Did I hear you guys say
something about a party?
A welcome back to Queen Consolidated
party for mom.
I don't think so.
If things are going to get
back to normal,
then we need
to start acting normal.
Normal for us is
a lavish party.
Oh. I'm sorry, Mrs. Queen,
I can't stay for brunch.
I guess
we got to go.
Bye.
I'll take care
of everything.
What exactly
are you looking for?
Your thief's shoes
touched the ground,
which means he tracked
in dozens of clues
as to where he's been
the past few days.
Got ya.
Shouldn't take long.
So you've seen him, right?
The Vigilante?
I read that he saved you.
What was he like?
Green.
That's interesting, right?
I mean, why green?
Black would be better
for stealth,
and urban camouflage.
Me, personally,
I think that he trained
in some sort of like forest
or jungle environment,
and the green
is a nod to that.
I don't give the vigilante
much thought.
Police reports show that
he uses carbon arrows,
but if he switched
to an aluminum carbon composite,
he would have
far better penetration.
Maybe he thinks
he penetrates just fine.
Do you want
to know something else?
I think that he has partners.
Definitely someone with
a background in computer sciences.
Yeah.
Why are you
so interested in the Vigilante?
When I was 11,
my mom was murdered.
I'm so sorry.
They never caught
the guy who did it.
Maybe he would have.
The soil...there's
a crystalline structure in it.
That's weird.
What's weird?
It's sugar.
Sin, you said
this was an emergency.
No offense, but Thea,
you shouldn't be here.
In the alleyway
of the club I own?
It's my friend Max.
He's missing. I haven't seen him
for a week, no one has.
Something happened to him.
I figured you knew
someone who could help.
Roy can help you.
I thought you wanted me
to stay out of trouble.
I kind of like that you never
turn away from someone
who needs help.
I'll just get someone
to cover the club.
What do you mean?
Oh, I'm coming with you.
I hear you're
throwing a party.
I didn't get my invite.
Where exactly
should I have addressed it?
Starling City cemetery?
I know that's where you wish
I was right now.
Lying beside my son.
Am I supposed to feel sorry
for you, Malcolm?
You killed Tommy.
You killed your son.
You cannot have my daughter.
Our daughter.
I think we both
needed someone that night.
I felt so bad about betraying
Rebecca's memory
that I left
Starling.
Left Tommy behind.
That's when I made my way
to Nanda Parbat,
where I found
my new purpose.
In a way, Moira,
you made me the man
I am today.
Thea is innocent.
She loved Robert.
Please don't
take that away from her,
I'm begging you.
Thea is all
I have left.
Tell her the truth,
and tell her soon.
You found something?
We found something.
There were
trace amounts of sucrose
and a spec of dirt the killer
dragged in here on his boot.
Which got me thinking.
There is a sugar refinery
two miles from here.
The land around it
is suffused in waste sugar.
So I checked.
They had a delivery truck
stolen a few days ago.
Their truck matches
the make and model
of the truck the thief used
to steal the centrifuge.
Can you track the vehicle?
We've been trying.
What was that?
You're not going
to believe this.
The truck, it was just
used to rob a blood bank.
Are you sure?
Yeah. Our guy
just made off with 30,000 ccs
of O-negative.
What, he has super
strength, likes blood?
Please don't tell me
we suddenly believe in vampires.
We should give this information
to the local police.
I'll...take care of that.
Did you say that you were
working a similar case
in Central City?
Oh, yeah, um...
Yeah, you know,
it's similar.
Has similar
elements.
A lot of
similarities.
Right. Yeah.
I want you to look into
this Allen kid.
There's more to him
than he's letting on.
His intentions seem
pretty clear to me.
Just do it, please.
Oliver, when are you
going to tell me
what exactly
we're up against?
Yeooww!
Sorry.
Ahh.
Thank you.
You were right to ask if
I knew more than I was letting on.
I've seen men
with abilities like that before.
You have?
Where?
The island.
My second year
marooned there, we--
I came across
the remains
of a Japanese World War II
military project.
It was a serum designed
to create human weapons.
Human weapons. My God,
what's next, aliens?
This is real, Diggle.
Those five years
that I was away,
I came across things
that just...
defy explanation.
There's a doctor,
his name is Ivo,
and he came to the island
to test the serum on people.
The ones that survived,
their endurance,
reflexes and strength
were all enhanced.
And you think this Ivo's
in Starling City?
He's dead.
And so is everyone that he
injected with the serum.
The last of which...I burned.
You think someone
found the recipe.
The centrifuge
and a large supply of blood.
I think someone
wants to make more of it.
A lot more.
Why couldn't you have
been marooned on Aruba?
There's a third component--
a strong sedative.
I think I preferred it
when you left these
in people.
I need you to analyze
the blood on the arrowhead.
If we can figure out
which sedative they're using...
We can figure out
where the next robbery will be.
Barry and I will
get right on it.
I think our Miss Smoak
is smitten.
Diggle, what did you
find out about Mr. Allen?
He's not who he says he is.
How are you holding up?
I could do with
a better looking crutch.
You two seem
like you've gotten pretty chummy.
We're here.
There must be
a fissure in the island
below the waterline
for it to come that far inland.
Unbelievable.
They have nitric acid
next to hydrazine?
Permanganates
on top of acetone?
This is the definition
of dangerous.
If it's so dangerous, maybe you
shouldn't be touching them.
Barry.
I managed
to get a sample
of the perpetrator's blood
from the police department.
We need to isolate
a sedative in the blood.
It could lead us
to the thief.
How did the police get it?
Apparently the Vigilante
shot him with an arrow.
You're kidding.
You know what
this means, right?
This means the Vigilante's
working the same case we are!
Heh. Go figure.
How did you get it?
Oliver has a lot
of connections.
Wow.
Pays to work for a billionaire.
Actually my take home's
nothing special.
Especially given
I am rarely at home,
since I'm with him
every night.
Ah. Well, I didn't
realize you and he were...
Oh, no.
Work. He...and I
are not, no, I do
not like Oliver.
Um, I was invited
to a work function.
It's a party.
And I have
a plus-one.
I was thinking
you would make
a really good...
plus one.
There's not going to be
dancing, is there?
I'm not just not
too good on my feet.
Ohh.
It reeks in here.
I guess your friend wasn't too
into painting seascapes.
Max is like
any starving artist...
starving.
But I could always crash here
when I didn't have a place to stay.
Hey, this blood drive
was a week ago.
When did you say
he went missing?
That day.
It's Daily.
Someone's looking
for Maxwell Stanton.
And they should
find him.
Yes, brother blood.
Blood provides life.
Blood provides power.
And with power...
There's no limit
to what I can do.
Central City is just a day away
from making history
when the controversial
S.T.A.R. Lab's particle accelerator
is finally turned on.
Pretty cool,
right?
You know there's been
a hundred percent increase
in earthquakes since they've turned on
the Large Hadron Collider.
That data is misleading.
Oh, do tell.
You know about
misleading, don't you?
What are you
talking about?
He's not from CSI,
he's an assistant.
Whose bosses don't know
you're in Starling.
And there is no similar case
in Central City.
So tell me, Barry...
What are you really
doing here?
I told you my mom
was murdered.
By your father.
He didn't do it.
You said that the police
didn't find the man who killed her.
The police
think they did.
My dad has been serving
a life sentence.
They didn't believe me.
About what?
I was 11.
One night...
something just came
into our house, like a tornado.
A blur.
Somewhere inside The Blur,
I saw a person.
My dad went to fight it.
I tried to get 'em
when suddenly...
I was 20 blocks
away from our house.
Nobody believed me.
They thought I was trying
to cover for my father.
But what I saw that night
was real.
As real as the man
that ripped down
that metal door
with his bare hands.
That's why I look
into cases like this.
The ones nobody
believes are possible.
Maybe if I can just
make sense of one,
I might be able to find out
who really killed my mother.
And free my dad.
I am sorry I lied to you.
Better find
another plus one.
He did like about
who he really was.
And what do we do every day?
Hey.
How's everything
going in there?
Good evening,
Queens.
Can I have a word?
Yeah.
I'm sorry if I overreacted
a little bit earlier.
Oh, you think?
Look, right now you need to apologize
to your mother. Not me.
For what?
Your being wrong.
I guess these days,
I only draw a crowd
when I'm on trial
for murder.
Mom, you don't have to...
We have guests.
However few of them
there are.
This is not your fault, Ollie.
How's your mom doing?
Oh, you know us Queen women--
nothing gets to us.
You must take
after your dad.
Sorry.
Sin. What's up?
I found Max.
Where?
I'm on my way.
They find Max?
Um, no.
She just wants me
to stop by.
I can come with you.
You should stay here.
Your mom needs you.
Ok, I'll call you later.
Time for a dance?
Not really feeling like
dancing with you, Oliver.
I know.
And that is why
I called him.
Fyi--
they will card him
at the bar.
Hi.
I was serious
about not being able to dance.
But I'll hold
your hands and sway.
Sold.
Ok.
I tried to warn you.
I tried to ignore you.
I am sorry,
Oliver.
Yeah.
Oliver threw you
a lovely party.
Oliver's a good son,
if not the best
judge of character.
Is everything ok?
Everything's going perfectly.
He doesn't have long.
If this miracle drug is onboard,
then we need to find it now.
Slade, be back
in a few minutes, ok?
I'll just get comfortable.
Come on.
There.
Mirakuru.
Miracle.
I was never sure
it was real.
What happens
if we give it to Slade?
He needs a sedative
in his bloodstream first.
They might have
potassium bromide or barbital.
Ohh.
It's empty.
What happens if we give it
to him without the sedative?
Sarah!
He'll die, for sure.
He's going
to die anyway.
What was that?
Ivo and his men.
They're on the sub.
Have you made contact?
Yes.
He said to tell you that
your information was
gratefully accepted.
Thank you.
Who was that?
Nothing to worry about.
Thank you for tonight, Oliver.
It was a lovely party.
I'm so sorry that
I put you through that.
Oh, listen, I don't care
what anyone else in
this city thinks of me.
I only care
what you two think.
And I have to get
back to the office.
Excuse me.
Thea.
There's something
I need to tell you.
Sure. What is it?
I love you.
I love you, too.
Yes.
Yes, sir. I--
yes, director, I know that this is
not the first time.
Yes, sir, I do value
my job, very much.
Look, I will be on
the next train.
Mm-hmm. I'll be back
tonight. Ok.
Thank--
Well, my boss found out I don't
have food poisoning.
I need to get back
to Central City
if I still want
to be employed.
Which I do.
Tell the SCPD that
the sedative in the thief's blood
is Ketamine. It's a schedule
three controlled substance.
It shouldn't be
too hard to track.
Yeah, I'll make sure
they get it.
Thank you.
It was really nice--
thank you for--
working with you.
everything,
We couldn't have done it...
Without you.
Good-bye, Felicity.
Good-bye.
Max!
Get off, let go!
Max! Get off of me!
Hey! Let her go.
Cut it out!
Stupid cops.
They're saying
Max ODed.
Was he using?
No!
He made extra cash
donating blood.
You really think
the hospital would let him
be a donor
if he was an addict?
Hey. Can't be here, kid.
Let's go.
They found trace amounts of
Ketamine in the thief's blood.
It's a common surgical anesthesia
derived from hydrochloric salt.
Can you use that
to track him?
With the current concentration ratio
in the blood sample, there's only
one possible location with
a large enough quality of the sedative
that correlates
with the amount of blood
the stolen centrifuge
can process.
What is it?
There's no sign.
A.R.G.U.S. doesn't
like to advertise.
It's a disaster bunker.
Right on the edge of the Glades.
A.R.G.U.S. has them
all over the country.
They store relief supplies--
food, clothing...
Medicine.
I'm on my way.
Oliver...
I can't believe
I'm actually saying this.
The way this arrowhead
is bent...
It means our thief's
muscle density
is at least 120 pounds
per cubic foot.
That's almost the same
density as common concrete.
Your arrows may cut this guy,
but they will not stop him.
Well, I've beat someone like
this before, Felicity.
I can do it again.
What if you can't?
Oliver.
Now this, it could save you...
Or it could kill you.
By the looks
on your faces,
I'm going to die anyway.
Sorry.
For what?
For not telling you
how I really feel.
Do it.
No!
What?
I need your help.
A friend of mine's
friend, well,
the cops think
he ODed, but we think
he was murdered.
Why?
Well, he wasn't an addict,
for starters. And this...
This doesn't look like
any OD I've ever seen.
Stay away from that.
You know something?
What happened to him?
You're the one who told
me to be your eyes
and ears on the streets.
You know what, that is not
good enough for me anymore.
Fine. Then we're done
altogether.
I don't need you!
I have friends
that can help me.
You can't stop us.
Slow you down.
Ah!
And I thought it couldn't hurt
to add extra security guards.
It hurt them.
Badly.
Have you prepared Thea?
No.
You will not go near Thea,
you will not speak to her
and you will never
set foot in this house again.
I set you free, Moira.
Your life belongs to me.
I am through
being afraid of you.
You think
you can stop me?
Even the Vigilante
couldn't kill me.
No, he couldn't.
But I know someone who can.
Ra's al Ghul.
How do you know
that name?
Well, I didn't.
Until you mentioned
Nanda Parbat.
The League of Assassins,
however twisted their aims,
believes very deeply
in a code of honor.
Your undertaking
betrayed that code.
You told Ra's
I'm still alive?
He was so grateful to hear it.
Because he so very much
wants to kill you himself.
So my advice to you, Malcolm...
Run.
This isn't
finished, Moira.
Who are you?
Merely a follower.
Of who?!
My brother.
Did he give you
the mirakuru?
Did he inject you with it?!
No. He saved me with it.
No.
Please.
Please!
Oliver!
Is he alive?
His pulse is weak,
but it's there. Oliver!
Can you hear me?
His pupils are dilated!
What the hell
was that?
I don't know,
it's coded.
Damn it. Damn it!
I can't break into
the dispensary files.
I have no idea
what he was injected with!
Poisoned with.
All right, we have no choice.
What are you doing?
Calling 9-1-1.
Dig, wait!
Can't wait!
How are we supposed
to explain this?
Everyone's going to find out
Oliver's the Vigilante!
Which won't matter
if he's dead.
Felicity, we can't save him!
I know, you're right...
We can't.
One way to Central City.
It left
ten minutes ago.
Of course it did.
When is the next one?
In the morning.
Ahh.
Ohh.
Please save my friend.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man