Previously on Arrow...
You're probably thinking
what happened was your fault.
I'm here to tell you that it's not.
It's the fault of only one man.
And we're going to stop him.
Do you remember what I promised you?
A new beginning.
And you will have it.
I've seen
what he can do with his powers.
But when he tried to use them on me,
it completely backfired.
And my bloodlust was gone.
Help me figure out a way
to make that permanent.
One day, I will have my moment,
and I will kill you.
Take her!
Take that away as well.
The food attracts flies,
and I prefer my solitude.
The pepper came from the garden.
The garden grows strong,
even in your absence.
Please try a bite.
The mountain will be ours by morning.
We must act quickly.
The Usurper will return,
and with him, his followers.
Has the Lotus been found?
In Kyushu. It's well-guarded.
So was this place upon a time.
Good news is that the burglar
is headed straight toward you.
Bad news is that the burglar
is headed straight towards you.
Freeze!
Where'd he learn to do that?
I'm thinking Cirque du Soleil.
He's headed for the roof.
Thank you, Black Canary.
That is your cue, Green Arrow and Speedy.
- Is she...
- Overusing our code names?
Yeah. Indulge her.
We got him, Overwatch.
You have no idea
how much I love hearing that.
I think we do, actually.
Two rooftop doors.
Floor plans show that the staircase
splits a level below you.
He could come out either door.
Got him.
Speedy!
FELICITYI How's Thea?
She's okay.
She's resting at our place.
She said it was just exhaustion.
We don't believe a word of that, do we?
What else could it be?
The Pit.
The bloodlust makes her feral,
it doesn't make her lose consciousness.
- And Thea hasn't gone aggro in months.
- Exactly.
Maybe this is some sort of side-effect
of her white-knuckling her way through it.
It still seems like a bit of a leap.
Ollie, what are you thinking?
That I should have done a betterjob
of keeping an eye on her.
She told me the bloodlust came back
two months ago and I didn't even know.
I've been focused on the campaign,
and I've been...
Running back and forth
to Central City and...
How is it that you always manage to
blame yourself for everything?
That's his superpower. Guilt Arrow.
Did our thief steal anything else
from AmerTek?
A network mapper.
A piece of tech designed to scan
all nearby digital infrastructure
for potential vulnerabilities.
Do we think it's his last score?
We better hope that it is.
AmerTek's one of the last
viable businesses left in Star City.
Turns out, Palmer Tech is
one of those "viable businesses."
For now, at least.
What do you mean, "For now?"
The board, in their infinite wisdom,
decided to move the presentation of
Curtis' world-changing tech
from April to now.
And guess who gets to be the
face of that potential disaster?
Oh, well, do you want me to come with you?
A little moral support.
- No. I'll be fine. It's just a dry run.
- Okay.
Uh, in the past 30 years,
battery technology has been
at a virtual standstill,
with batteries lasting no longer than
they did in the 19703...
Damn it.
But Palmer Tech's Power Cell
represents a major breakthrough...
Sorry. I should've gone with
overhead projector.
Mr. Holt, could you give us
the room, please?
Well, actually, that's gonna be
a little difficult
seeing as how the entire building's
a property of...
I just... I'll be right outside.
Sorry.
- Felicity.
- Mmm-hmm.
May I be uncomfortably honest?
Well, you have never shown
an inability to do so before.
Right.
This company has been
flirting with bankruptcy
since before you returned to Star City.
And your injury...
Well, it didn't exactly help
our stock price.
We stake the future of Palmer Tech
on this Power Cell.
We need to put our best foot forward.
Well, that is not something
I'm exactly able to do right now.
- But...
- Sorry.
Poor choice of words.
What I mean is...
Perhaps it'd be better to let someone else
do this presentation.
And by "someone else,"
you mean someone not in a wheelchair.
This is about doing
what's best for the company.
Anything less than a perfect launch
and we are sunk.
Right. You're right.
Please let the board know.
Hey-
Just wanted to check in,
see how you were doing.
Why, I'd think the answer to
that question is fairly self-evident.
Thea's bloodlust is
the balancing of an equation.
She was given life
and now she needs to take it.
Malcolm, we know that already.
What we don't know is why...
What you don't know.
What I didn't know until Thea collapsed
is that, if the life she
owes doesn't come from taking others,
it will come from the life of the host.
Please do not refer to me as "the host."
This isn't a joke.
If you don't indulge this bloodlust,
you will die.
I don't understand. Sara wasn't like this.
John Constantine made Sara whole
and restored the balance.
Thea, I thought you were doing okay.
Because the bloodlust was
temporarily blunted.
By What?
Damien Darhk.
When we rescued Andy from HIVE,
Iran into him.
He tried to kill me
with his magic death touch thingy,
but it didn't work on me.
What it did do was stop the bloodlust.
For a time.
We need to find Damien Darhk,
and make whatever he did to her permanent.
Oliver,
even if that were possible,
even if you caught Damien
in a more cooperative mood,
he and his HIVE have gone to ground.
Or haven't you noticed?
- Yeah.
- Our sticky-fingered friend
just pulled anotherjob at Cadmus Tech.
He's two blocks east of you, headed south.
John, I can't right now.
He stole a weapon this time.
Just go.
Nothing is gonna change here in an hour.
I'm on my way.
Where am I looking?
We're working on it.
Got him!
Roy?
First Sara, then Ray,
then John's brother...
Whose shocking return
can we look forward to next?
Oliver, I'm gonna ask this just to ask it.
- Are you sure that it was...
- It was Roy. Absolutely.
Or maybe it was just somebody
who's able to
make themselves look like Roy.
Don't act like
it's the craziest possibility
after everything that we've experienced.
What's "crazy" is Roy stealing
from tech companies.
What did he take this time?
Triode capacitor bomb.
Tiny device, really huge boom.
It's Alex for the 500th time today.
OLIVER; Hey.
Hey, I was just texting you.
- How did you not...
- Oh.
- Campaign office has a secret elevator.
- What?
I'm kidding.
I came in the side to avoid the media.
Got your nine-one-one.
Everything all right?
No. Not really.
Ledger's going to press with it tomorrow,
but we got a heads up.
Someone else is
throwing their hat in the ring.
- Who?
- Political novice, it looks like.
Still working up a bio,
but she seems to have come out of nowhere
to suddenly have a campaign office
in Pennytown.
Ruvé Adams.
Do you know her from somewhere?
No. I'm just surprised
to have an opponent.
Yeah.
Well, it's pretty much a game-changer.
Yes, it is.
I've never doubted
your resiliency, Mr. Queen.
But you will tell me.
Why did you need these maps?
He can't tell you anything
if you kill him!
Get her out of here!
No!
What did your tattoos reveal, hmm?
What were you trying to find?
Hello, Oliver.
It's good to see you again.
Are you here to endorse me?
I want a meeting with your husband.
I'm not sure you would survive
another "meeting" with my husband.
No fight this time.
I have a proposition for him.
I'm listening.
Tomorrow, 10:30. Kershaw and Eighth.
Uh, we have a new problem.
I was going over the schematics
of the two pieces of stolen tech,
trying to figure out
where Roy was going to hit next...
Any luck?
No, I mean not at first.
A capacitor bomb and a network mapper,
that's like...
Ceiling fan and broccoli.
- Sounds like a messy combination.
- Combination being the breakthrough.
I stopped trying to figure out
what the two pieces of tech had in common
and started working on what would happen
if they were combined somehow.
Their components, specifically.
Tell us something good.
It depends on your definition of "good."
But I'm pretty sure that
AmerTek's network mapper
and Cadmus' capacitor could theoretically
be used to create a web-nuke.
Like a bomb?
Roy already stole a bomb.
No, lam talking about a device
that can destroy the entire Internet.
We're talking banking systems,
nuclear arsenals, power grids...
Last year,
Roy could barely spell computer.
Even assuming
he did build this device, I...
- Why hasn't he used it?
- Because it's incomplete.
A device like this needs a really
substantial power source to run off of.
And guess what company in Star City
just invented the next generation
revolutionary battery?
I don't wanna hurt you.
I don't want you to hurt me either.
Well, I'm gonna need to take that.
Oh...
I think you might have to hurt me, then.
Roy, stand down.
There's something wrong with him.
Yeah, I think that's been established.
Let's talk about this, Roy.
Drone is in position.
Roy. Roy, what are you doing?
Listen very carefully.
- Are you sure?
- Yes. Do it.
No, wait!
What did you do?
Take out the tranq, carefully.
Let's hope the Faraday cage
Cisco installed in here works.
A what?
Basically a shield for everything
broadcast and electromagnetic.
- Which eye did you see the tech in?
- The right one.
How'd you even know he had it?
Roy's eyes are blue.
I'm guessing this was transmitting
an AV signal,
probably to
whoever was picking up the tech.
Well, he can tell us when he wakes up.
- Where am I?
- It's okay.
We took out the contact. We made it
look like we killed you. You're safe.
While I'm in here, at least.
New lair. Nice.
I heard about what happened. I'm sorry.
Roy, what happened to you?
I got made.
I was in Hub City.
A new life, new name. Everything.
- And then I got an e-mail.
- Saying, what?
Steal a bunch of stuff?
Or he'll expose me as Roy Harper.
Suddenly, the Arrow's not dead anymore.
And then the police,
they'd be looking at you. Again.
Who's the blackmailer?
I don't know. I've never met him.
But he calls himself The Calculator.
This is what happens
when the bad guys name themselves.
- Roy, you should've come to us sooner.
- I couldn't.
He's right.
There's a camera built into this.
This is really incredible tech.
He could see every single move I made,
every person I talk to.
I couldn't just expose you guys like that.
We would've figured something out.
- This is my problem.
- 'Cause you were solving my problem.
Okay, well our problem is that
The Calculator now has everything he needs
to melt the Internet.
I love the Internet.
Which means we have to find him. Fast.
Can you back-trace the components
and figure out where that broadcasts to?
- Girl, you read my mind.
- Pop yourjacket off, I'll patch you up.
Man, I cannot believe you shot me.
Really?
Mei?
Shade.
Shado's dead.
I know. You're having a vision.
The result of your injuries.
You're not real?
No.
But what I've come to tell you is.
What have you come to tell me?
You need to forgive yourself
for what you've done.
Unfortunately, you're gonna
have to be a little bit more specific.
You had the chance to leave this island,
to return to your family.
They miss you terribly.
Can't go back to my family.
Not the way that I am now.
Then it's time to start changing.
The only way out is through, Oliver.
That's what Amanda Waller said.
Through what?
Through your own darkness. Let it go.
I don't know how.
Then I will teach you.
This is it.
- I see no shrine.
- The woods are the shrine, Talibah.
In times long past, the people of Japan
found their gods in all things.
Nature was their temple.
I must do this alone.
If I do not return within the hour,
tell the others...
The war is over.
Hello, Tatsu.
You look well.
Being a member of the Crescent Order
clearly suits you.
I have found my purpose.
What is yours in Japan?
I've come for the Lotus.
It is my responsibility to keep it safe.
I know.
Unfortunate.
We're evenly matched.
One of us must yield,
or this will go on for ages.
I have nowhere else to be.
I do.
In a matter that concerns Oliver Queen.
I see two options.
We keep fighting
until one of us drops from exhaustion.
Or we lay down our swords,
and you listen to what I have to say.
Maybe next time, we can
do something that doesn't involve
me getting stabbed or shot at.
Justanidea.
I'm sorry that I put you in this position.
I'm pretty sure I put myself
in this position.
Man...
I remember you not being all that happy
that I faked my death
to protect your secret.
I never should have let you.
Do you ever get tired?
You know carrying the weight of the world
on your shoulders like that all the time?
You sound like Felicity.
And Diggle.
Well, great minds.
So what are Felicity and John saying
you're taking responsibility for now?
Thea?
Oh, my God.
Am I hallucinating?
It's really you.
How are you?
I've been better. Um...
Where have you been?
What are you doing here?
How long are you... Here...
(Thea“.Thea! 4COUGHWG)
What's happening?
I don't... I don't know.
- Oh, my God...
- it's the wound. From Ra's.
- I'll call nine-one-one.
- No, doctors can't help her.
Stay with us, Thea. Stay strong.
Give it a minute. It will pass.
You're okay.
How's it going?
This tiny piece of plastic
has more computing power in it
than most high-end laptops.
I have half a mind to
reverse engineer it for Palmer Tech.
But first...
Yes, I found a tiny flaw in the O.S. code
and I'm pretty sure I can exploit it to
open a back door
into his main computer system.
Right, but wouldn't that
risk exposing us?
My pride that you understood
what I was saying is slightly undercut
by your lack of faith in me.
I have nothing but faith. Just do it.
I already did.
Well, Well...
Whoever you are, let me just say,
I am very impressed.
No one's ever been able to break through
my encryption before.
Bravo.
Disguise your voice.
Thanks.
I would take that
as a compliment
if it wasn't coming from some nut-job
who's trying to destroy the Internet.
Why would I want to take down the 'net?
Not only is it where I work,
I'm addicted to funny cat videos.
Well, if you're not trying to
take down the Internet,
what do you need a web-nuke for?
Very clever.
Keeping me talking to buy you time to
breach my firewall.
So that's a pass on telling me
your evil plan?
Let's put it this way.
If you wanna make a statement,
you don't take down the system.
You take down a city.
Damn it! He shut me out.
Not before indicating
what his plan might be.
How do you take down a...
Oh, no...
What?
Well, I've been thinking
about what would happen
if he used the web-nuke
to take down the Internet,
but if you used it right...
Overloading the electrical grid,
shutting down hospital equipment,
causing water main breaks...
He... He could kill everyone in the city.
So a web-nuke needs to be
deployed somewhere...
We need to know
where The Calculator wants to install it.
I am not calling him that on principle.
Because it is a lame codename.
Okay, Felicity,
but we still have to check...
I am conducting a review of all the nodes,
sub-nodes, and network access points
where the web-nuke
would do the most damage.
- Any luck?
- Why do you always ask me that?
If I had any luck looking for
what I'm looking for,
I would be telling you about it
instead of looking for it!
Sorry. Stressed.
In addition to our lunatic of the week,
I have Palmer Tech to look after.
Palmer Tech. Ray worked up something
last year called a battering ram,
basically something that could crash
through cyber security.
No commercial application, but...
Can you use it to get back
into The Calculator's system?
Stop calling him that. I'm serious.
Your darkness is guilt.
You've taken many lives.
The life of your love's brother
most recently.
I'm not in love with Taiana.
She helped you recover the maps
from the Amazo,
she nursed you back to health
and all she's received from you in return
is a lie.
Open your eyes.
What's this?
Curtis Holt,
have you seen the battering ram?
It's this kickass piece of tech
that Ray invented last year.
Um, cylindrical shape, titanium shell.
- I'm gearing up for a brute force attack.
- Look out for that...
And I need all the firepower I can muster.
Stool... Uh, never mind.
Hey, you've gotten pretty slick
on that thing in the last 24 hours.
What happened?
Yes! I got it.
- Thanks, Curtis. You're the best.
- I didn't do anything.
You're the one who's whipping around here
like a house on fire.
Well, that is what happens
when the entire city is at stake.
But not when it's just, say,
an entire company.
Mr. Dennis says you're no longer
presenting the Power Cell to the Board?
Well, my dry run was an epic disaster.
Yeah. I know, it was.
It was a spectacular failure.
Like, it was really bad.
- Okay.
- But it wouldn't have been
if this Felicity had come in.
You know, the one who wheels in here,
kicking ass and taking names
like you just did.
No, this is different.
No, it's not.
There's two Felicitys, Felicity.
The one in that boardroom,
whose wheelchair makes her doubt herself.
And this Felicity.
Brilliant force of nature.
This company needs the second Felicity.
Hey-
Laurel told me.
You Okay?
I'm feeling a bit better.
Hey, I'm working on something.
If it's a pedophile for me to kill,
Malcolm's already been
pitching that one hard.
You're not a killer, Thea.
That's not a way for you to live.
But it sounds like Damien Darhk might be.
Yeah, I'm sure
he's just itching to do us a favor.
We're gonna find out.
I arranged a meeting.
It's not like he's gonna be
willing to help me.
Maybe there's something that he wants.
- Something I can trade him.
- Ollie, that's insane.
Not to mention stupid. I...
I can't let you owe Darhk a favor.
And I can't let you die.
I won't.
That's not up to you.
Look, I know how you take everything on,
everyone's problems.
It's one of the things
I love the most about you.
But you can't fix this one, Ollie.
I have to try.
No, you don't.
It's my choice.
It's my life.
She's stubborn, isn't she?
Definitely something she gets
from your side of the family.
It doesn't matter.
Because you're going to go,
hood in hand, to Damien Darhk?
I am the Demon's Head.
I have my resources.
And I know how to put my ear
up against a door.
Leaving the epic stupidity
of your plan aside...
Thea's right.
This isn't either of our decisions.
Malcolm, do you want her to die?
Of course not.
Do you have any idea how badly
I wanna put a knife in her hand
and force her to slit someone's throat?
I've come this close to dragging someone
in here for her to kill.
And the reason I don't
is because that would be about
my feelings and not Thea's.
Oliver, sometimes the greatest act of love
is no action at all.
It's her life. It's her choice.
This almost feels like cheating,
using Ray's tech to beat this guy.
Got it. He's installing the web-nuke
at Flint Hill's Data Farm.
- Installing?
- Yeah. He's doing it right now.
Get Oliver.
Device is onsite.
Dandy.
Hang on a sec...
Miss me?
I have seriously missed this.
Overwatch, we're on station.
I'm trying to find the web-nuke,
but our adversary knows I'm in his system
and he's trying to kick me out.
I did get a look at his protocols, though,
and if the web-nuke goes online,
he could kill 8,000 people.
I'd say that's a conservative estimate.
Blowing the gas mains alone
will kill 3,000.
Just wait till you see what I've got
planned for the subway cars...
Ooh, good story. Write me a letter.
From prison.
The battering ram was a neat trick.
But the only way you're going to stop me
is by removing the web-nuke on site.
And I suspect that you don't come out
from behind that keyboard much.
That's what I have friends for.
Okay, so does anyone know
how to disconnect this thing?
I brought friends too.
Hired mercenaries.
It's amazing who you can find
on the Dark Web.
Always gotta make an entrance, don't you?
Sorry. It was a meeting
that I decided not to go to.
Look,
I know it's been a while for me,
but this still isn't a good thing, right?
You know, I almost feel bad
about beating you.
Rarely do I get to meet someone
with your talents.
What did you do?
Boom! I believe the technical term
is I pwned you.
Be that as it may,
I can breach through the firewall faster
than I can remove the DRMs
off a Beatles tune.
Guys, the web-nuke is hard-wired in.
Not to get too inside baseball on you,
but I need you to blow the thing up.
How much time do we have?
It's a long story, but somewhere between
I Want To Hold Your Hand and Hey Jude.
Priming the explosive.
Something's not working...
He's jamming the detonation frequencies.
Okay. We do this the old fashioned way
and manually set the charge.
Yeah, but how do we do that
and get out of here in one piece?
Someone has to stay behind.
I'll do it.
Even if you trigger the C4 with an arrow
at a distance,
you still need to outrun the blast radius.
- I can do that.
- Yeah, just because you're wearing red
doesn't make you the Flash, Roy.
I didn't say it wasn't gonna be risky.
You just got a fresh start.
I don't want you to throw it all away.
I'm the one who brought this maniac
into your lives.
I need to do this.
This is my choice. It's my life.
Okay.
See you outside, kid.
Good luck.
Hey-
You run like hell.
Yeah.
You guys might wanna get out of here.
Come on, Roy. Come on!
Just like riding a bicycle.
It's good to have you back, Roy.
You've been missed.
Oh, don't get too used to me.
And I'm gonna have to
go underground again.
Even deeper
now that The Calculator knows who I am.
What's to keep him
from posting it on the Internet?
Oh, I might've installed
a virus in his system
that wiped out everything he had on Roy.
I'm sorry I can't stay.
Not just for you guys, but for Thea.
She'll understand.
She's gonna be okay, Oliver.
Well, whatever she decides,
I'm gonna back her play.
Thank God.
I thought the fever would never break.
- I'll get you some water.
- Taiana.
I need to tell you something.
It's okay.
Whatever it is, it can wait
until you've had some water.
I lied to you.
When I said that Conklin
killed your brother, that was a lie.
I don't understand.
I have this darkness inside of me
that I've been trying to escape
for the longest time.
And I think that I found a way
but first I need to earn your forgiveness.
For what?
I didn't know that Vlad was your brother.
There are reasons but they don't matter.
They don't change what I did.
I killed your brother.
No.
I can't believe I let you
talk me into this.
You are gonna be great. Break a leg.
Sorry.
Okay.
Hmm.
Welcome.
This is a day I have looked forward to
for a very long time.
Because today, I stand...
On the shoulders of many giants.
Nikola Tesla, Thomas Edison,
Ray Palmer and, of course, Curtis Holt.
Their work has always been about
making this world a better place.
And today, we get to take another step
towards that goal.
As you know, battery technology has been
at a virtual standstill for decades,
with batteries lasting, nor charging,
any faster than they did in the 1970s.
Until now.
Today, Palmer Tech is pleased to
introduce the Power Cell.
A 100% recyclable battery.
It can charge an electric car
for thousands of miles.
And right now, it is single-handedly
not only powering
this entire presentation,
but this entire building.
She's something else, isn't she?
You have no idea.
You know, you should be a nurse
in your new life.
You're a natural.
Only problem is, I am a one-patient man.
And I am already committed to you.
Is that why you're leaving?
You know, I get it.
Star City is filled with too many people
who can recognize you.
You know, I thought about staying anyway.
For you.
You know what you could do? For me?
Go live an amazing life.
Get married, have a couple kids.
Yeah.
And get a minivan.
Just go be normal.
There's nothing in this world
that would make me happier than that.
You know,
if I could do all of this over again...
I would do every
single one of those things with you.
Me, too.
I love you, Thea Queen.
I love you, Roy Harper.
You were amazing out there.
Thanks. How's Thea doing?
I'm gonna go check on her now.
I'm just gonna debrief with Curtis,
but text me how she's doing, okay?
Okay.
Oh, my God.
Dad?
- How is she?
- Resting.
Where's your new BFF Damien?
I don't know.
Like you said, this is Thea's decision,
it's not mine.
Oliver, I know it feels wrong,
but you did the right thing.
However it feels,
I couldn't have done it without you.
Malcolm, thank you. For everything.
Oliver. It's Thea.
How long will she be in a coma?
Right now she's barely a three
on the Glasgow Scale.
The prognosis isn't good.
I'm sorry.
Thea, please, don't go.
There's only one way to prevent that.
My father once told me of an elixir
known as the Lotus.
Capable of countering
the effects of the Lazarus Pit,
a secret weapon developed by
the League's enemies.
- Do you have it?
- I do.
And I will freely give it to you
on one condition.
I want you to kill Malcolm Merlyn.
English SDH