My name is Oliver Queen.
After five years
on a hellish island,
I have come home
with only one goal--
to save my city.
But to do so, I can't be
the killer I once was.
To honor my friend's memory,
I must be someone else.
I must be something else.
Previously on "Arrow"...
I'm Barry Allen,
from the Central City
police department.
I'm with the crime scene
investigation unit.
I have friends
that can help.
This miracle could kill you.
Do it.
It was a serum designed
to create human weapons.
You think someone
found the recipe?
A centrifuge
and a large supply of blood.
I think someone wants
to make more of it.
- Oliver!
- Is he alive?
Felicity, we can't save him!
I know. We can't.
Ow!
Please save my friend.
Hold him!
He's not going
to make it.
He will. We just have
to find out what's in his system.
I--I--I usually only
work on dead people.
Barry!
All right, I can
think of four possible diagnosis
for what's causing his body
to react this way.
Make that three
possible diagnosis.
Two.
Start chest
compressions.
Got it.
He's suffering from
intravenous coagulation.
His blood is unnaturally clotting.
It's like maple syrup.
You can save him, right?
Lucky you guys
have a rat problem.
Are you kidding?
That'll kill him!
He dies if I don't.
Felicity...
Do it!
Just the right amount of this stuff
will thin his blood enough
to get it
circulating again.
Let go, Oliver.
He's crashing.
Don't fight anymore.
Oliver, stay with me!
Stay with me.
♪ Arrow 2x09 ♪
Three Ghosts
Original Air Date on December 11, 2013
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Oliver, let him go.
Oliver!
What the...
What the hell
is going on?
You were injected with
a strong-acting blood coagulant.
You would have
stroked out, ahem,
but fortunately you had
a very effective blood thinner handy.
Warfarin.
Better known as rat poison.
Kid saved your life,
Oliver.
This is the point
in a lifesaving emergency
where you thank
the person that did the lifesaving.
You told him who I am.
Yeah, I did.
That's not your secret
to tell, Felicity.
I decide who finds out
my identity.
Well, we didn't
have time to get your vote,
what with you
unconscious and dying.
What happens if he leaves here
and goes right to the police?
He wouldn't do that.
I wouldn't do that.
I trust him.
I don't!
What are you going to do,
put an arrow in him?
I am considering it.
Don't worry,
he's kidding! How is
this any different
from when your mother shot you
and you came to me for help?
Your mother shot you?
Or when you brought Dig
down here when he was
poisoned with curare.
The difference is that
I did my homework on both of you!
I don't just
tell people easily.
I'm not going
to tell anyone.
And you don't have to thank me,
but you should thank her
instead of being
kind of a jerk.
Mr. Queen.
I have to go home.
That man that I fought
in the bunker,
he has what he needs
to mass produce
the serum from the island.
And we have to stop him.
He touched your skin
when he grabbed your neck.
I was able to absorb
the residual oils from his skin,
which, when added
to a gel-based polymer,
might be able
to recreate his fingerprint.
Never meet
your heroes, right?
Mom?
Oliver, thank you
for coming home, sweetheart.
Is everything all right?
Well, I don't know.
Your sister has locked
herself in her room
and she won't
talk to me.
Don't worry, I'll talk to her.
Ok.
It's Christmas.
Yes.
But given the last
gala that we threw,
I think we're going to skip
this year's Christmas party.
Thea, it's Ollie.
Open the door.
Not--not now, Ollie.
Speedy,
open the door!
Is mom with you?
No!
What's going on?
I didn't want mom to see.
See what?
What happened to him?
Vigilante decided to use him
as target practice.
You're right--
the guy's a psycho.
Why didn't you go
to the hospital?
In this city, an arrow's
the same as a bullet
if you want the cops involved.
And mom actually
likes Roy,
but something tells me she'd revoke
his tree trimming invitation
if she found out he was
messing around with the Hood.
Uh-huh.
Hi.
Roy.
This is going
to hurt.
My anger's dulling the pain.
This will
dull it better.
Going to put
pressure on it.
Right there.
Diggle, I need you to come
to the Queen mansion.
Roy's been shot.
With an arrow.
It's a long story.
Look, just bring the first aid kit
to Thea's room.
Thank you.
Roy, my driver, Mr. Diggle,
he has medical training
from his time in the army.
He's going to patch you up.
Thank you.
It's the least I can do.
Look, I don't know what
the three of you are up to,
but maybe the vigilante
was just trying to keep you safe.
By shooting Roy?
I...I'm just saying.
Maybe you should
let this go.
So...
Are you going
to let this go?
No.
But now we're going
to do things my way.
Mom!
Hello!
Shado?
You can't be here.
I had to see you.
Had to warn you.
Warn me?
You can't fight what's coming.
Put down your bow.
Take off my father's hood.
I wear that hood
to honor your father.
And to honor you.
If you want to honor me,
stop fighting...and live.
Or everyone you love will die.
Ollie?
Who were you
talking to?
Get over there!
Mirakuru.
Take them.
Anthony...
You got what
you wanted.
You can let them go.
If you ever
cared about me.
But I do care about you, Sara.
Which is why
I won't choose to kill you.
But he might.
What are you
talking about?
Time to choose, Oliver.
Who lives, and who dies.
But pick quickly,
because in 30 seconds,
I will shoot them both.
The incubation
process has begun.
Serum will be ready
for distribution in 48 hours.
Two days.
And we will be able to create
a hundred more like you.
And the people
who run this city
will see what
real power looks like.
I knew the Vigilante
had partners.
He likes to be called
the Arrow now.
You three have messed
with some really nasty people.
The Doll Maker,
Count Vertigo,
Dodger, The Huntress.
We weren't
keeping score.
I was.
Barry.
The rat poison that you gave
me...are there any side effects?
Um, yeah, I think
hallucinations, maybe.
And excessive sweating.
Are you sweating
excessively?
You're
hallucinating?
What are you
seeing?
A girl named Shado
that was with me on the island.
Shado.
Sara.
How many women were
you marooned with?
Are you sure
this wasn't fantasy island?
You did train in a jungle
or forest environment,
hence the green.
Hey, let me draw some
blood, see what's up.
Hey, can I ask you
something?
Why no mask?
Not to tell you how to
do your vigilante...ing,
but the grease paint
thing?
It's a poor
identity concealer.
So find me a mask that conforms
perfectly to my face
and doesn't affect my ability
to aim while I'm on the run.
You should look into
a compressible micro fabric.
It could be great.
Found Cyrus Gold.
Who's Cyrus Gold?
The human weapon that left you
nearly dead the other night.
The kid did manage
to pull his print off your neck.
I've had facial
recognition software
scanning closed circuit
cameras all over town.
He's at the corner
of Delgado and 25th right now,
but we're just about
to lose him.
What else is at
that intersection?
A parking lot,
a market, a motel.
Could be where he's holed up.
I got this.
Oliver...
Why don't let me
handle this one?
It's just recon.
Fine.
But I'm going
as your back-up.
Don't worry.
I'll figure out what's
wrong with Oliver.
You'd be the first.
Secret admirer?
No, actually,
they're from my father.
What brings you by?
We need your help.
Cindy's friend was murdered,
but the police aren't
going to investigate.
They said that he ODed,
end of story.
Check this out.
He earned extra money
donating blood.
We found it in Max's apartment.
They wouldn't have accepted
his blood if he was
using, right?
Max went missing
the same day as the blood drive.
If he did
donate blood there,
maybe they at least know
something that happened to him.
I'll ask around.
Thank you, Laurel.
If you get bored, I keep a book
of crossword puzzles in the glove box.
That's not funny.
Ok, what do you see?
It's clean.
Really clean.
"Solomon Grundy,
born on a Monday."
Christened on Tuesday.
I know the poem.
It symbolizes the seven stages of life--
from birth to death.
What stage is this guy in?
Go, go, go, go, go!
He picked me up
like I was nothing.
- Felicity, call for back-up.
- On it.
This about Sara?
You heard from her?
No.
I'm sorry,
this is...
This is
something else.
Cyrus Gold.
He robbed
the Applied Sciences Division
of Queen Consolidated
last week.
Detective...
He's extremely
dangerous.
The CSI kid from Central City,
he said this guy was like
some kind of monster.
He is.
Well, what is it, steroids?
Worse. It's--
it's...
Well, assuming I believe
you, why come to me?
I've been
compromised.
What does that mean?
It means I'd be
a liability.
You have to take my word
on this, Detective.
Gather as many men
as you can,
and do not hesitate
to kill Cyrus Gold.
Because if given
the opportunity,
he'll do the same
to you.
You don't have
to do this!
You got what
you came for!
Just take it and go!
10 seconds.
You freaking
psychopath!
History will make that judgment.
Five seconds.
Time's up.
No, no!
I guess you made
your choice.
No!
Hi.
What are you
doing here?
I came by to see Thea.
Oh. Go on in.
She's upstairs
in her room.
I noticed on the drive up
that your house
wasn't festooned
with Christmas decorations.
Well, we didn't feel
very much like
festooning
this year.
I know what you mean.
I remember last Christmas,
Tommy and I came here
for your party.
It was one of the best holidays
I'd had in a really long time.
Anyway, I should probably
go talk to Thea.
I checked into
the blood drive,
and it's all legitimate.
In fact, what
Sebastian's done
has helped save
a lot of lives.
So if the blood drive
is on the up and up,
then how are we supposed
to find Max's killer?
There's one
other thing.
All of the blood
donors at the drive
were subjected
to a psych evaluation
by the Langford
Institute.
Is that, like, legal?
It's not entirely
out of the norm.
And while someone
at the institute might know
if Max was on drugs,
there's no way of finding out
without a warrant.
Which we're certainly
not going to get.
I'm sorry
I couldn't be more help.
What are you doing?
Uh, just messing around
with something.
Shouldn't you be
trying to figure out
what's causing Oliver's
hallucinations?
Sample's still being scanned.
Shouldn't be too much longer.
You're really worried
about him, huh?
He takes crazy chances.
Even when he's not
hallucinating
about beautiful
island girls.
Hmm.
The other night,
I asked you if you liked Oliver.
I told you.
I don't.
I remember.
But if you did...
I could see why.
I mean, Oliver Queen.
He is a billionaire by day
and saves the city by night.
Sounds like
you want to date him.
I just have a little experience
with liking someone
who doesn't see you
the same way.
Protests continue
into the final countdown
for tonight's ignition of
S.T.A.R. Lab's
controversial
particle accelerator.
S.T.A.R. Lab's founder Harrison Wells
promises a new era
of scientific
advancement is at hand.
I guess I won't be back in time
to see them turn it on.
I know, it sounds crazy.
Human weapons?
Look, his name is Cyrus Gold.
He's the one that broke into
Queen Consolidated last week.
He's the one that
robbed the blood bank.
And he killed
all those people.
Where are you
getting all this intel?
Oh, man, what's
a matter with you?
Talking to the Vigilante's what
got you demoted in the first place.
Look, we take a small squad.
McCarthy and Evans
from SWAT, Jones.
We can bring this guy down.
I promised Jeannie
I'd take her Christmas shopping.
Lucas.
Please.
Fine.
But you get to call
Jeanie and tell her
I'm not taking her
shopping.
Hey, sir. I don't
mean to overstep,
but could you guys
use an extra man?
Grab a vest, Officer Daily.
The police are onto Gold.
They're looking for him.
I made sure
I'm in the loop.
We are too close
to let the police interfere.
Brother Cyrus.
The police
are eager to meet you.
Introduce yourself.
So, any plans for Christmas?
Lighting my menorah.
Hey.
Hi. How are you feeling?
Fine. Just...
It's a little bit
crowded at my house,
and I wanted to come
down here to get a little privacy.
Yeah.
Come on, Barry.
We can watch the countdown
at Big Belly Burger.
Your blood analysis
is almost done.
Thank you.
What's the matter, kid?
You look like
you've seen a ghost.
Are you sure he's in?
Yes, sir. Sector car
spotted Cyrus Gold entering.
He hasn't left.
Safeties off.
This is a nice place.
It's a bit more
comfortable
than the fuselage
on the island.
You're not real.
Neither are you.
You told everyone
when you started this crusade
that it was about
making up
for your father's sins.
That was a lie.
This charade is to atone
for your sins.
You're dead.
You are not a hero.
Or a friend.
Or a brother.
You are nothing.
Do not turn your back on me,
not again.
You're gone.
Wherever I am...
It's time you joined me.
They say a coward
dies a thousand deaths.
But even that wouldn't
be enough for you.
I tried to save you!
And her.
But you couldn't.
Just like you couldn't
save this city.
The island didn't
make you strong, kid.
It revealed you to be weak.
Thank you for being
my shopping guide.
Are you ok?
Uh, yeah, it's just, um,
can I ask you a question?
It's about the blood drive
you sponsored.
Of course.
It's a wonderful cause.
Especially with the underfunded
hospitals we're dealing with.
What about it?
Hello?
What?!
Ok, I'll be right over.
What happened?
My father. Um...
He's in the ICU.
I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry, I have to go.
I'm sorry.
What happened
in here?
Did someone break in?
No.
Your blood analysis
is done. Good news.
So you know
what's in my system?
That's the thing--
your blood's clean.
There's nothing
wrong with you.
Then why am I hallucinating?!
I don't know.
But whatever
your problem is,
it's not pharmacological.
It's psychological.
It's in your head.
It's in my head.
Oh, my God.
Oliver.
Dad!
Honey.
Well, I can wiggle my toes,
it must be a good sign.
I'm all right,
honey, I'm fine.
How's Lucas, is he all right?
I--I'm sorry.
What do you mean?
I got to call Jeannie.
I got to call his wife.
No, Dad, I'll do it.
You just...stay here.
Get some rest.
What are you
doing here?
Wanted to make sure
your father was ok.
He is.
I wanted to make sure
you were, too.
How are you, Detective?
I'm alive.
Unlike most everyone else
in my unit.
I'm sorry
about your partner.
I took him in there.
Because of me.
I hate to disappoint you,
but not every death
in this city is on you.
I got this off Gold.
Hopefully you can
do something with it.
I didn't believe it
at first, but this guy,
I mean, it's like
he's not human.
He's human.
Well, then you can kill him.
For Hilton. And me.
I think those
are sharp enough.
Apparently I'm not.
Diggle, do you think
I'm losing my mind?
No more than
the rest of us.
I saw...
Slade Wilson.
Slade was my friend
on the island,
and...
like Shado,
he is dead because of me.
Mr. Lance
just told me
that not every
death in this city is my fault.
Fine.
There are plenty
that are.
When I got home
from Afghanistan, I...
saw a ghost, too.
Survivor's guilt.
Why us, not them.
I know why.
Then the "why's"
not your problem.
How'd you make
your ghost go away?
I figured out what they were
trying to tell me.
Which was?
That's for me to hear, Oliver.
You have to figure out what
yours is trying to tell you.
Guys, we got
something here.
I scanned the key
Lance gave you,
and traced its serial code
back to the manufacturer.
This particular key
fits a locked gate
somewhere on Crescent Circle
in the Glades.
Where are you going?
You can't go out there
in your condition.
I have to stop this.
Oliver, Gold
left you half dead,
which is 50 percent better than
how he left Detective Hilton.
Felicity...
I don't have
a choice.
I'll come back.
Promise me.
It's ready.
Is this where you killed
Max Stanton, hmm?
What are you doing?
If you stick that
in me, I'll kill you.
No, brother Roy.
You'll kill for me.
Brother Cyrus
told me he killed you.
Guess he's not as strong
as you'd hoped.
Where'd you get the Mirakiru?
Who gave you the formula?!
It was a gift. A gift I would use
to save this city from itself.
Another failure.
Get up, Oliver.
Tommy?
You're not going
to die down here.
Tommy, I'm sorry.
I let you die.
You didn't
let me die, Ollie.
You fought
to save me.
Because that's
what you do.
What you have
always done.
You fight to survive.
I know I called you
a murderer,
but you are not.
You are a hero.
You beat the island.
You beat my father.
So fight, Oliver.
Get up
and fight back.
Kill him.
Hey. I am not leaving
anyone else to die!
You're strong, kid.
Come on! Come on!
Come on, Roy!
Fight. Come on, fight!
Roy?!
Hey, Roy!
Where have you been?
I've been looking all over for you!
I was...
I was running down
another lead.
It didn't pan out.
I thought you were
chasing after the Vigilante again.
I got so scared. I thought
something happened to you.
Hey, hey, don't worry.
I'm alive.
I want to serve
the people of Starling,
not the men and women
who think they own it.
Together, we can help
rebuild our city
into a place where there are
no elites and no oppressed.
Where we are all
brothers and sisters.
So your campaign begins.
The city
needs a leader.
And putting
the copycat hoods
up to assassinating
the mayor was just the first step.
The Vigilante...
He destroyed
the centrifuge
and the serum
along with it.
I will arrange for you to receive
another sample of my blood,
and then you can begin
to mass produce the serum again.
When I ask you not
to confront the Vigilante,
you will listen.
Remember, your mask
can be worn by another.
You know who he is
under that hood, don't you?
I know exactly who he is.
He's my friend.
That's why you don't
want him dead.
Death would be
a release from this life,
and his sentence is yet
to be carried out.
I am going to tear everything
he cares about away from him.
Destroy those who choose
to follow him.
Corrupt those he loves.
Once he has lost everyone
and everything he values...
I will drive an arrow
through his eye.
Shado...
Shado!
Ahhh!
No!
Why?
I...
Ivo just shot her.
He didn't say why.
Whoever did this to her...
is going to suffer.
Still have a ghost problem?
No.
I got the message.
But we...
We have other problems.
Wouldn't be us
if we didn't.
Roy was injected
with the serum.
Oh, my God, is he ok?
He's alive.
But we are going
to have to keep an eye on him.
And Cyrus Gold?
Died on Saturday,
buried on Sunday.
But he was working
with someone.
I saw him,
he wore a mask
with the image
of a...of a skull.
He's trying to mass produce
the serum to build an army.
For what?
You're a soldier.
What's the primary
purpose of an army?
War.
Where's Barry?
He went back to Central City.
Oh.
Wanted to get home in time to see
them turn on the particle accelerator.
I should take this.
Hi.
Hey
Did you make it?
I made it back
to Central City in time,
but I missed the cut off
in line at S.T.A.R. Labs.
I was late, as usual.
But in spirit
of not being late again,
uh, if you ever decide that
Oliver Queen
isn't the guy for you;
if you decide that
you want to go
on a date with
someone else, um...
You should know that
that guy, he'll be on time.
Good to know.
Oh, hey, and I left
something for Oliver.
I hope he likes it.
Bye, Barry.
Bye, Felicity.
I'm Linda Park and we're live
outside  S.T.A.R. Labs
despite the inclement weather,
which is only going to get worse.
The torrential downpour has
driven away almost all the protesters
though S.T.A.R. Labs
CEO Harrison Wells has assured us
that the storm tonight will in
no way affect the particle accelerator,
which is up
and running smoothly.
Wait, we are now
being told to evacuate the facility.
The storm may have
caused a malfunction
to the primary
cooling system.
Officials are now trying to shut down
the particle accelerator,
but so far have been unable
to regain control of the system.
Even the Arrow deserves
a Christmas present.
Here.
How do I look?
Like a hero.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man