My name
is Oliver Queen.
After five years
on a hellish island,
I have come home
with only one goal--
to save my city.
But to do so, I can't be
the killer I once was.
To honor my friend's memory,
I must be someone else.
I must be...something else.
Previously on "Arrow"...
It's a hozen.
In Buddhism,
it symbolizes reconnecting.
And now that Malcolm's
dead, there's only one archer left.
And I'm going to help
my boss catch him.
Let the kid go.
It's like you have a death wish.
And guess what?
It's going to come true.
Yeah, well, someone
has to do something.
Stand up for what's
right, like he did.
Faster!
Foot's on
the floor, man.
Call it in.
This is FEMA truck 52.
We're being pursued
by two armed bikers.
We're heading south on Third Street,
requesting immediate assistance.
Come on,
get us out of here.
Get us out of here!
Who the hell was that?
Just so you know,
the real bad guys
are getting away!
♪ Headed for the open door
♪ tell me what
you're waiting for ♪
♪ look across
the great divide ♪
♪ soon they're going to hear
the sound, sound, sound ♪
♪ when we come running
We're going to need
more sparring dummies.
I'll start
ordering them in bulk.
This mean you're ready
to launch crusade 2.0?
I'm ready, I just
don't know where to begin.
Last year, I had the list.
Getting justice was as simple
as crossing names out of a book.
This is Starling City.
You never have to look far
to find someone engaged
in illegal activity.
Yesterday Big Belly
Burger got robbed.
Was Carly there? She ok?
Yeah, she was, um,
it was her day off.
Good. Well, the three of us
should get dinner.
I haven't seen her
since I got back.
Why the sudden interest
in my love life?
If it's important to you,
it's important to me.
Hey! I didn't
see you come in.
I had a secret entrance
installed when I ran the club.
Kidding.
Hello?
Yes, yeah,
this is Thea Queen.
Of course
that's where he is.
Who is he, Roy?
I already told you,
I don't know.
So you just happen
to have one of his arrows.
I hear he likes
green ones.
Do you think this is funny?
Because I can charge you
with obstruction right now!
Look...
I used to feel
the same way as you.
He has this way of...
seducing you.
Making you feel like
he's some kind of guardian angel.
But he's not.
He causes chaos
and death.
And you trying
to emulate him
just makes
the situation worse.
Half the city fell into a hole.
I'd say the situation's
already worse.
Look, some of us
are just trying to make it better.
Who, like you
and the Hood?
Look, there--
There are others.
Others out there who are willing
to do what's right.
I've seen them.
I've seen her.
I'm not interested
in anyone else.
Just him.
What happened?
Are you hurt?
Fender bender.
He totaled his car
playing hood junior.
At least
it wasn't my car.
Don't say anything!
I already called you an attorney.
That won't be necessary,
we're not pressing charges.
So long as he gives up
looking for trouble.
Might as well
tell him to give up breathing.
I'll talk to him.
Ask him if he knows
anything about the Vigilante.
Roy has obviously forged
some sort of connection to him.
Maybe it goes both ways.
Doesn't sound like
the Vigilante to have a groupie.
That's just it--
we don't know anything
about the Vigilante.
Except for every time
that he shows up,
all hell breaks loose.
It has to stop, Ollie.
He has to be stopped.
Thea.
Can you ask Mr. Diggle
to bring the car around, please?
I'll always
think of you fondly.
Save the speeches.
Your ex-girlfriend
already laid one on me.
Still, no effect.
I used to be
a lot like you, Roy.
I doubt that.
I spend more time in the back
of cop cars than limos, so...
The world
doesn't work anymore.
It broke a long time ago,
but it was like you were
the only one who noticed.
That makes you angry.
And you're afraid
that that anger
is going to burn you up inside
if you have to live
in the world one second longer
knowing that you could
do something to fix it.
That anger's going
to put you in the hospital, kid.
Or worse.
Well, I'll take worse.
It's better to be dead than
in a hospital these days, right?
What do you mean?
Been to the Glades
Memorial, lately?
No, but I didn't read
that it was damaged by the quake.
It wasn't.
The medicine that FEMA's been
sending the hospital
is being hijacked.
So, if they don't
re-supply,
they'll be forced to close.
By who?
I don't know!
The doctors and nurses
are already bailing on the place.
And the cops? The cops rarely
venture that deep into the Glades,
so I guess
that leaves only me!
What's it take
to make you angry?
Others will come.
They won't be happy
we killed their men.
All the more reason
to figure out why they're here.
It's a map.
Of the island chain,
containing Lian Yu.
This is similar to the recon shots
that A.S.I.S. gave me
before I came here
to rescue your father.
Whatever they're looking for,
it must be here, on this island.
I've seen men in war
with that look in their eyes.
What look?
The one that says
he's split into someone else.
Someone
he doesn't even recognize.
If someone doesn't
talk to him, it'll tear him up.
Come on.
Let's get away
from this place.
They survived the quake
and ended up here.
From one hell
to the next.
Yeah, whoever's stealing from here,
they won't be for much longer.
This city is failing
on all accounts.
Who's that in the spotlight?
Sebastian Blood, the local alderman
that I told you about.
Not too shy about
sharing his opinions.
Which are?
Which are that the Glades
have been abandoned.
And no one gives a damn
about these people.
He hasn't met us yet.
We cannot stand by
while the doctors
on the other side
of those doors are working with
the bare minimum
of resources
because the police
department
already sees us
as a lost cause.
Meanwhile, thieves are seeking to
make a quick buck
off the misery
of the Glades.
Oliver Queen,
isn't it?
Alderman.
What brings you to Glades Memorial,
Mr. Queen?
I assume someone
of your means
can afford the best
medical treatment money can buy.
And I can assure you,
you're not going to find that here.
That's wrong, sir.
The people of the Glades have
suffered too much
not to have access to basic
medical services.
Well, that's very
compassionate of you to say.
Although I wonder
where your family's concern
for its fellow citizens was
when they ordered
the construction
of the earthquake machine
that killed 503 people.
Ladies and gentlemen,
ladies and gentlemen, please!
I will be doing
everything in my power
to atone for my family's
culpability in this tragedy.
Well, I'm sure the people of
the Glades that I represent
will sleep better
knowing that--
if they still had
a place to sleep.
If their homes
hadn't crumbled around them.
If their stores and their businesses
hadn't been condemned.
You did this to us!
Go back to your mansion,
rich boy!
Spare us your mercy
visits, Queen!
You've done enough
for this city already.
Excuse us.
Pardon us.
♪ Arrow 2x02 ♪
Identity
Original Air Date on October 16, 2013
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
I quit.
No, you don't.
Yes, I do.
Not my old job in
the I.T. Department,
but my new job
as your executive assistant,
which you think
I'm going to accept.
Your thinking could not be
more wrong in this matter.
I need a girl Wednesday.
It's...Friday,
and the answer is no!
These computers
have been upgraded.
Far more processing power
than your typical secretary.
Did you know
I went to M.I.T.?
Guess what
I majored in. Hint--
not the secretarial arts.
Felicity!
We all need to have
secret identities now.
If I'm going to be
Oliver Queen CEO,
then I can't very well
travel down 18 floors
every time you and I need to discuss
how we spend our nights.
And I love spending
the night with you.
3, 2, 1.
I worked very hard
to get where I am,
and it wasn't
so I could fetch you coffee!
Well, it could be worse...
My secret identity
is his black driver.
Right now...
I need you to figure out
how the hijackers
are getting a line
on the goods earmarked
for Glades Memorial.
If we know how
they're picking their targets...
We will know when
and where to stop them.
Fine.
Oh!
May I get you
a cup of coffee?
You're not actually offering to get me
a cup of coffee, are you?
Yeah, no.
That won't be
happening. Ever!
Well, if you can
bring yourself to do it,
can you please make reservations
for Dig, Carly and I
Saturday night at Table Salt?
Sure!
I'll get right on that.
Using the Internet,
which you also happen
to have access to.
Still haven't told him?
He has enough
on his plate.
Last year when Oliver Queen
returned to Starling City,
he was met with flowers
and well-wishes.
However, today down
at Glades Memorial,
he was met with a far less
cordial homecoming.
The question is no longer,
where have you been, Oliver Queen.
Now it's, but what
have you done for me lately?
Mr. Queen was not
available for comment.
You saved my life.
That's what I keep
telling myself.
That I killed that guy because
he was going to kill you.
But what if that's
not the reason?
I just feel like
this island is...
It's turning me into
something terrible.
No island, no place
can make you
something you're not.
So I've always
been a killer?
Everyone has a demon
inside of them.
The "dao de jing" recognizes
the yin and the yang.
Opposing forces
inside all of us.
The darkness.
And the light.
The killer...
and the hero.
Never thought I'd say this,
but I'm actually
getting more done
down in the basement
of an abandoned steel factory
than in the corner office of a high rise.
What do you have?
FEMA is shipping 100,000 units
of medical grade opiates
to Glades Memorial.
When?
Truck is scheduled to leave
the FEMA depot in 20 minutes.
Not if this motorcycle gang
has anything to say about it.
Bad luck for them.
I have something
to say about it.
No, no, no, please,
please, don't shoot.
Down!
Make your delivery!
Emerald archer.
I feared you had
perished in the quake,
denying me the opportunity
to pay you back in full
for your past interference
in my business.
Your business is going under--
permanently!
I don't think my friend
agrees with you.
Our new partnership
was easily cemented.
See, I was eager
to see you dead,
and he was eager
to kill you.
No kill shots?
I was promised a fight.
I hope you haven't
lost your nerve.
Find out.
Starling City police!
You're surrounded.
Put down your weapons
or we will open fire.
Cease fire, cease fire!
Find them.
Does it hurt?
Not as much as some things.
I love that we live in
a city where the police
are more interested
in catching you
than the drug-stealing
mobsters.
Our tax dollars at work.
The authorities have always
gone after the Vigilante.
This time was different.
Why, because this
time it's Laurel leading the charge?
Because they got in my way.
I can't make things better
as Oliver Queen,
and now I can't make things
better as the Vigilante.
So what if Laurel's involved?
Hey! Go easy on him.
It's all right, Felicity.
No, it's not.
You don't get to
jump down his throat
just because you happen to be
having a lousy week.
Ok, you're pissed
he invoked the almighty Laurel.
Well, you're not
the only one whose love life
is taking it on the chin!
Felicity...
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about,
you keep
bringing up Carly
but you're so involved
with yourself
that you don't even realize the
look he gets every time you do.
What is she talking about?
Me and Carly
pulling the pin.
It happened when
you were gone.
Truth is, it's been happening
for a while now.
Being the Vigilante's
wingman was a strain.
He needs to hear this.
This wasn't just about
what we were doing, Oliver.
This isn't
just about you, man.
I couldn't separate what's going
on with me and Carly, and...
What went on
with my brother.
Deadshot.
He's still out there.
My brother's killer.
Still breathing.
And I, uh,
guess I couldn't
hate him
and love her
at the same time.
See?
You are not
the only one
having trouble reconciling two
sides of himself.
Great crowd tonight.
Now that we're closed,
are you going to be
starting your second shift?
Suicide by Chinese
street thugs.
Do you really want
to talk about this again?
We never finished
talking about it.
I wanted Laurel
to arrest you.
You know,
you're not the first
girlfriend to say that to me.
She said I couldn't
change you,
so I'm not going
to try to.
What, so you're giving me
money and a rock?
The check is two weeks'
severance from the club.
Just because
I can't change you
doesn't mean I have to let you
be in my life
until you get
yourself killed.
And my brother gave me that when
he came back from the dead.
He said it was a hozen,
some Buddhist thing that
symbolizes reconnecting.
If you want
to reconnect with me,
keep the hozen
and tear up that check.
I don't do too well
with ultimatums.
And I don't do
all that great
with people I love
getting hurt.
And worse.
Your 4:00 is here.
Although I'm not
entirely sure
why you invited him
up to your office.
'Cause I need to fix
this situation,
and there are no
cameras or people
to throw things
at me in here.
Alderman.
Thank you for coming.
Mr. Queen.
This is some view.
How small the rest
of us must all look from up here.
Ms. Smoak.
Yes?
Would you get my guest
and I some coffee?
You know, I would, Mr. Queen,
but it seems that someone's
broken our coffeemaker.
Violently.
I was surprised
that you wanted to meet.
As surprised as I was
when you turned
a frenzied mob on me?
Oh, that shouldn't have
been too surprising.
My constituents have
a lot of anger towards your family.
They have a right to.
My mother was involved
in something...
Unspeakable.
But I'm my own man.
And I'm not your enemy.
You're not a friend.
To me, or the people
of the Glades.
I am hoping to prove otherwise.
Mr. Queen.
Not every problem
can be solved by money.
Real change
will never happen
until your elitist
friends realize
that it is morally
unacceptable
to allow thousands
of its fellow citizens
to live right down
the street but in a third world.
Then let's show them.
I'll host a benefit.
Invite some
of my "elitist friends,"
and then you and I can help them
see what needs to be done.
People seeing you...
Seeing you stand up,
the CEO of Queen
Consolidated,
taking responsibility and
being this cause's public face.
That would
make a difference.
Then let's make a difference.
Listen.
I am truly sorry for what happened
outside that hospital.
Sometimes my emotions
get the better of me.
I don't even know how
long it's been since I laughed.
Hey, kid.
Shado.
Yeah, just, um...
We were just
washing off.
Well, you better prepare
to get dirty again.
I think I figured out
where those men were headed.
It's a couple of clicks
northwest of here.
Well, let's go.
Be careful.
Don't fall too hard.
Why not?
To make sure there isn't part of
this island that doesn't totally suck?
To survive.
She's a distraction,
and in a place like this,
a distraction's going
to cloud your judgment.
And that is what's going
to get you killed.
Look at what this island has
already done to you, kid.
Hello, Laurel.
This seems like
old times.
I figured we should talk.
Fine.
Turn that thing off
and pull back your hood.
I'm not your enemy.
And I thought we understood
each other.
I understand that
you're a criminal.
And you think the law
doesn't apply to you-- it does.
But you didn't always
feel that way.
You used to think that I was helping
the people in this city.
And then I saw you.
I don't understand.
The night
of the earthquake.
I saw you at CNRI.
My friend was
inside the building
when it collapsed.
He went there
to rescue me.
And by the time I managed
to climb inside, he was gone.
But I saw you.
Running away
into the night.
You didn't save him.
You were too busy...
Fighting a meaningless duel
with Malcolm Merlyn.
And when people--
people you told me you would
protect needed your help...
You weren't there.
I don't think you wear
that hood because you're a hero.
I think you wear it
to hide that you're a coward,
and I promise you,
I will see you unmasked,
prosecuted
and sent to prison.
Don't ever speak
to me again.
You look like a woman
who's looking for someone.
Friend of mine.
He's throwing this benefit.
Ah. Oliver Queen.
Didn't realize
you were friends.
Very old friends.
So you can imagine how I feel
about you putting him in the crosshairs
of public opinion,
alderman.
For what it's worth,
I've apologized to Oliver
for my rhetorical excesses.
In fact, it is that détente
which brings us
all here tonight.
So where is Oliver?
That's exactly the question
I'm asking myself.
We're late.
The good news is,  at least you
get to make a dramatic entrance.
Oh, I'm just lucky
Oliver Queen
has a reputation for not
showing up on time.
You know, I've been
meaning to tell you
it really
weirds me out to no end
the way you refer to yourself
in the third person like that.
It's Felicity.
Tell me.
I've got
good news and bad news.
I hacked into FEMA's server,
yet another federal offense,
thank you very much,
and was able to find out
when the next shipment
of pharmaceuticals
is taking place.
When?
That's the bad news.
Five minutes ago.
I know this is the definition
of sucky timing,
but...which suit are you
planning on wearing tonight?
Doesn't seem Mr. Queen
is going to honor us
with his presence
this evening.
So where are you going?
To address his guests.
It's time they realize
what kind of a man their host is.
You're just going to crucify him
in the media again?
Crucifixion has such...
A bad reputation.
The Romans used it
to punish people
who acted against
the public good.
Alderman...
Ladies and gentlemen.
Thank you.
Thank you. But you should hold
your applause for Oliver Queen.
This evening's charity
was his brain child.
As such,
you could be forgiven
for wondering why
Mr. Queen isn't
with us tonight.
And the answer, I'm afraid,
is painfully apparent.
He doesn't care.
I told Mr. Queen
that this city's
problems cannot be
solved with his money;
that he needed
to stand up
and be counted
as someone who cares.
So where is he now?
Lieutenant!
We got a Hood sighting,
heading down Lemire Avenue.
Let's go!
I don't know where
Oliver Queen is.
All I know is that
he isn't here.
This city is dying.
And it needs
someone to stand up
and breathe
new hope into it.
And tonight, it is
painfully obvious
that that person
is not Oliver Queen.
Go!
I told you.
On time to die.
This doesn't make any sense.
This is supposed to be
live surveillance.
What the hell is this
building doing here?
It was destroyed
in the quake.
Who in the hell could be feeding
us year-old surveillance?
Healthcare has enough problems
without you punks.
You're not the only one
allowed to bring a friend!
I'm clear.
That makes one of us.
China!
Aaah!
Ahh.
Go ahead,
waste your arrows.
Aah!
That hurt,
but it won't stop me.
That will.
Dig?
Diggle!
You've changed.
You would have killed me
by now if you hadn't.
The police can take the shipment
the rest of the way.
They still won't see you as anything
more than the enemy.
You'll never be anything
but a criminal to them.
Which means
you'll never be a hero.
As long as
this city is safe,
it doesn't matter.
Those sirens
aren't for you.
After
a prolonged pursuit,
police have arrested
Chien Na Wei,
a high-ranking member
of the local Chinese Triad,
which was responsible
for the recent hijackings
of pharmaceuticals
bound for Glades Memorial.
Representatives praise
the efforts of the SCPD
in saving the hospital
from shutting down,
though some sources say the
Vigilante may have been involved.
In other news,
protests continue in...
I was just about to
make my move on her.
I didn't need one of your trick arrows
getting in the way.
Couldn't risk it.
Where would I be
without my black driver?
Diggle!
I'm sorry
about you and Carly.
Yeah, well,
couples break up.
Not everything that
happens in Starling City
is your responsibility.
I'm learning that.
What I meant was,
I'm sorry that
I wasn't there for you,
because I should
have been.
I got wrapped up
in my own suffering,
and I...forgot that
some other people
might be
suffering, too.
You know, we're getting
dangerously close to hug territory,
so I'm going to fall back.
You need a ride?
It turns that being CEO,
I actually have
some work to do.
I'll find my own way.
You always do.
Oliver Queen's
failure to show up to his own benefit
shouldn't surprise anyone.
He's no different than the rest of
the Starling City elite
who have failed to show up when
it comes to ending the suffering
of those left devastated
in the Glades.
Oliver Queen is not a friend
to the people of this city.
To those men, this location
could have been
on any one of 150
different islands.
But for somebody who knows
this island like he knows his own name...
So those men were
looking for this place.
Why?
- That would be the question.
- Slade.
Over here.
What happened to these people?
Whatever did happen to them
was over 60 years ago.
These soldiers belong
to the Japanese Imperial Army.
They've been here
since World War II.
We're missing
something here.
You don't just
come here for corpses.
I've been looking for you.
You need to stop.
You saved my life!
Made me realize it...
wasn't much of a life.
But I could do
what others couldn't,
or too afraid to do.
I could help you
save the city.
You're untrained.
I can fight.
You can take a beating.
There's a difference.
Then teach me!
Let me help you.
Ok.
You can help me.
But not by taking on
the Triad or the cops.
Then how?
To do what I do,
I need intel.
You can be my eyes
and ears in the Glades.
That's how you
can save the city.
How do I contact you?
Leave that
in the alley wall.
Then I'll know
to contact you.
Are you sure it's all right
that I keep this?
If I want to be with you,
do I keep that or give it back?
You were a little unclear.
You mean it?
No more fighting.
If it's a choice
between life with you
or life without you,
life with you will win
every single time.
I'm done trying
to be a hero.
I told you
to stay away from me.
I thought you might have
changed your mind
after I stopped the men
terrorizing our city.
This isn't your city.
It's your killing fields.
The copycats are still alive.
Tommy Merlyn isn't.
I lost a friend that day, too.
And I would gladly
have given my life for his.
Well, don't worry,
your life is over.
Your life as a free man.
I told you to stay away.
Somehow I knew
you wouldn't listen.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man