[GASPS]
Sara?
Murderer.
[PHONE BEEPING]
[SIGHS]
[SPEAKING IN RUSSIAN]
Alexi.
[IN RUSSIAN]
What can I do for you?
There's no gulags here in Starling City.
[IN ENGLISH]
Ha-ha-ha. Anatoli talks too much.
[LAUGHS THEN SPEAKS IN RUSSIAN]
I need you to find a man for me.
His name is Slade Wilson. He's rich,
Australian, and he's missing an eye.
I need to know where he sleeps.
First I need your assistance
with my business.
There is a man who owes me
a substantial amount of money.
-I am not here to trade.
-You know how our brotherhood works.
I do a favor for you and you do one for me.
Put it on my tab, Alexi.
I don't have time for these games.
Make time.
My services are of no use to you
unless yours are use to me.
Okay.
[ALL GRUNTING]
I know exactly how this brotherhood works,
and right now it works for me.
[IN RUSSIAN]
-I woke up and you were gone.
-Yeah.
I wasn't tired.
You should be.
When was the last time you actually slept?
Right before I found out that Slade Wilson
is still alive.
Do you wanna talk?
I mean, I know neither one of us are
very good about sharing our feelings, but...
...I mean, I get it.
Slade...
It's a lot. And, you know,
it's okay if you're scared. I am too.
I'm not scared.
Slade came back to Starling City
with an agenda.
First, he tries to mass-produce the Mirakuru.
Then he shows up at my mother's house.
So he wants a fight?
Fine, I'll give him a fight.
And this time when I kill him, I will make
damn sure that he stays dead.
I just need to find him.
[CHUCKLES]
-Coffee? Mm.
-Hot cocoa.
What, no marshmallows?
-I'm out.
-Mm.
What are you doing here, Dig?
-Keeping an eye on things.
-Okay...
...and by "things," you mean my neck.
The one you think Slade Wilson's
going to break in my sleep.
Yeah, something like that.
Look, I have extra security details on
Oliver's mother...
...Roy's keeping an eye on Thea,
Sara's staying close to Laurel.
So I get you...
...sitting outside my house like that
lacrosse player my freshman year of college.
You know, I had a life before
you and Oliver. You know?
Right.
-I just wanna make sure you're okay, Felicity.
-And I love you for it.
But if Slade wants to kill me, he can.
There's nothing you can do to stop him.
So go home.
Okay?
Hey.
Nice jammies.
[PHONE BUZZING]
What took you so long?
What is all this?
A little early for champagne, don't you think?
Not for me.
I just got back from a mission in Pyongyang.
Well, damn.
That was you?
I'm sorry.
-That's classified information.
-Ah.
But I missed my ex-husband, new boyfriend.
And A.R.G.U.S. has a standing reservation
at this hotel for very important assets.
-Mm
-Can you stay?
Oh, well, Oliver and I kind of have a...
...situation.
Everything all right?
Yeah. Yeah, it's... Yeah.
So you can stay.
Mm.
Hey.
-Is there a problem, Michaels?
-We need to rest. These women are tired.
We're all tired.
It's a long hike back to camp. Keep going.
Shall I go explain to the ladies
why they wanna get back before dark?
They're not allowed to talk to you.
-Because I'm an American?
-Because you're a man.
Five minutes.
Ugh. Girls in the military.
Can't keep up, don't join up, right?
[IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
Whoa, whoa. Hey, what's going on here?
What's going on?
You recognize that face?
You should.
He's on the U.S. military's
high-value target list.
Gholem Qadir.
Opium drug lord and arms dealer.
Wanted alive.
What were you saying about women
in the military?
Why didn't we do fun stuff like this
when we were married?
And take time from our busy schedule
of driving each other crazy?
[GIGGLING]
-Amanda.
-Don't look so worried, Agent Michaels.
We've all availed ourselves of the Ostrander
suite at some point in our careers.
Something's come up,
I'll need you to come with me.
-Duty calls.
-Yeah, guess so.
Actually, I meant both of you.
DIGGLE:
What are we looking at here?
-Hydroxy-Cyclosarin.
-It's a nerve agent.
WALLER: The apocalypse in the form
of a chemical weapon.
And it's about to hit the open market.
A.R.G.U.S. agents uncovered a
manufacturing plant in Kahndaq.
All samples were accounted for,
except for one.
Two weeks later, this footage was captured
in a remote village in Southern Qurac.
One milliliter has a kill radius of 10 miles.
It only took half that amount to produce
these results.
Our sources have traced the sample through
Europe, to an estate in Markovia.
So send in the Army.
We send in the Army, we risk an international
spectacle our government can't afford.
This has to be off-book.
If you need me to draw up
a smash-and-grab, done.
But John isn't a field agent.
He's not qualified.
Judging from how he and Oliver Queen
spend their free time...
...I'd say his credits transfer.
I don't want this thing out in
the open any more than you do...
...but I'm not sending my boss on
another of your business trips.
I have no intention of involving the Arrow.
-I need you.
-What for?
Gholem Qadir.
DIGGLE: We caught him.
-D.O.D. turned Qadir loose a few years ago.
And who thought that was a good idea?
It's a complicated world, Johnny.
The nerve agent's not the only WMD Qadir's
tried getting his scummy fingers on.
Last month, he tried to buy Malcolm
Merlyn's prototype earthquake machine.
Thank you for stopping that, by the way.
Fortunately, he doesn't know
about your involvement in that.
He remembers you as the man
who tried to save his life.
The nerve agent's under lock and key
at his estate in Markovia.
He's scheduled to host a fundraiser there.
The two of us haven't exactly kept in touch.
We've got that covered,
but our window is rapidly closing.
Okay.
I infiltrate the fundraiser,
come out with the package.
-Sounds simple enough.
-Nothing in this business is simple.
You know that, Mr. Diggle.
Follow me.
I don't need you to get the nerve agent out.
I need you to get your team in.
My team?
They're designated "Task Force X."
LAWTON:
Give me a break.
This ain't no task force.
Let's call it like it is.
Welcome to the Suicide Squad.
It's not only prisoners who grow coarse
and hardened from corporal punishment...
...but those as well who perpetrate the act
or who are present to witness it.
-Oh, please stop giving him books.
DIGGLE: So this is your unit, huh, Waller?
What, O.J. and Charles Manson
weren't available?
This is a dangerous operation.
And these men have useful skills.
-Should the mission be compromised...
DIGGLE: You'll just write them off.
The Suicide Squad.
Yeah, like he would ever make the sacrifice.
I can't believe you're
onboard with this.
-Those men are murderers.
-What's the number of...
...bodies between Oliver and Sara?
What they do...
What I do is completely different.
Not really, John. Don't you see that?
I see you letting the man
who killed my brother roam free.
It's not freedom. It's work.
-It's wrong.
WOMAN: Do you cuties need some counseling?
I'm a trained therapist.
[PEOPLE CHATTERING]
"Do you have previous experience in retail?"
Does shopping count?
Sara?
I've seen that look before.
On my face in the mirror,
when Ollie goes into distant mode.
Hang in there.
-He'll open up to you when he's ready.
-Yeah.
You'd think so.
I started by tracing the donation Mr. Wilson
made to Moira's campaign.
The money was routed through
offshore accounts, none of which...
...link back to a local address. So I looked
into credit card transactions...
...and car rental agreements.
He's gotta get around somehow,
just not by rental car.
Slade's former ASIS.
He knows how to be a ghost.
[COMPUTER BEEPING]
Robbery in progress.
5th and Giffen.
Still in the crime-fighting business, right?
Harbinger has eyes on the target.
Light the torches.
Deadshot is a go.
Shrapnel is a go.
Tiger is a go.
This is Mockingbird.
Harbinger, you have a green light.
Freelancer, you're a go.
-Deadshot?
-Got Freelancer in my sights.
What's stopping you from shooting me
right now?
Honor.
Can I trouble you for a cigarette, my friend?
Don't smoke.
And I'm not your friend.
You know who I am?
What it is I do?
You deal in drugs, weapons, and children.
You play both sides of the conflict.
You make money while your country burns.
I do not have to be the only one.
Let me go, I make you rich.
Trying to bribe my men, Qadir?
If we wanted to make a buck,
this is the last place we'd be.
[GUNFIRE]
DIGGLE: Get down.
WOMAN: Aah!
GAYNOR:
Heads up!
Oof. I'm sorry, I wasn't looking where I was...
Gholem Qadir.
I do not know what is less likely...
...that John Diggle would be clumsy,
or that I would find him here, of all places.
You like art, my friend?
-I know a good investment when I see one.
-Out of the military?
-And in a more lucrative line of work.
-What kind of work?
The kind you don't get to ask about.
It was good seeing you, Gholem.
-Everything all right here, Mr. Diggle?
-Yes. He's with me.
So the soldier now has his own security.
In my line of work, when I do a good job
I tend to make enemies.
A good man turns bad.
Bad man turns good.
-You changed my life, you know.
-Trust that was never my intention.
The intelligence I provided your government,
it saved many lives.
Now, as a free man, I give back when I can.
Of course.
[GUNSHOT]
-Get down.
WOMAN: Aah!
It's all clear.
Déjà vu, my friend.
-Mr. Qadir...
-I am fine.
I do not believe I was the target.
Like I said, when I do my job right
I tend to make enemies.
We should go.
Good job, Deadshot. You're a go for exfil.
Already in motion.
Except, uh, I'm not the only one.
Heh, Shrapnel just bolted.
Find him.
Picking him up headed east.
WALLER [OVER RADIO]: Shrapnel.
Stand down and return to the rally point.
I won't be conscripted into your
immoral army.
WALLER:
Stand down. Final warning.
Not in a country
without an extradition treaty.
WALLER:
Very well.
[HIGH-PITCHED WAILING]
[GROANING]
[CRASH]
What the hell is going on?
Shrapnel just fouled out of the game.
[DOOR OPENS THEN SLAMS]
What the hell was that?
We're gonna want popcorn for this.
You said it yourself, John...
...they're murderers. Criminals.
-They need an incentive to follow orders.
-So you rigged their heads with explosives?
There's no danger if they play by
the rules. Scheffer didn't.
It's like I don't even know you anymore, Lyla.
Where are we at with Qadir?
Save a man's life once...
...get a silver star. Save it twice?
Rent a tux.
I'll await further instructions, sir.
[IN RUSSIAN]
So is my patience.
This is Starling City bank account number
for your Mr. Wilson.
To be clear...
...take this envelope and we are through.
I do not care who your friends are.
[IN RUSSIAN]
Relax, it's just me.
What's going on, Ollie?
Hey.
-Talk to me.
-Now is not the time.
Then when is the time?
The Bratva, Ollie?
You're losing your grip, okay?
-Slade's getting in your head.
-I need this to stop.
And for it to stop, I need you to find him.
And until then, how long do you think
you can keep this up for?
You're not eating. You're barely sleeping,
and when you do, you have nightmares.
They're about her, aren't they?
Hey, look at me.
You did what you had to do, okay?
Ivo was going to shoot Shado, or me,
or both of us.
-It was an impossible choice.
-I made it anyway.
And if you had chosen differently,
then it would be me haunting you at night.
It still could be, Sara.
That's why we have to stop.
What are you saying?
He's gonna use you to hurt me.
Or he's gonna hurt you.
Stay away from me.
LAWTON:
Seeing as you haven't brought it up...
...I'm guessing you haven't gotten far
with that H.I.V.E. lead I gave you.
-Just make this quick.
-Heh.
You're usually so chatty, John.
These problems with your girl,
they got you down, huh?
And what about your girl?
The one you have a shrine to in that
cell of yours?
Zoe.
Your daughter know what
you do for a living?
She is why I do what I do.
-Really?
-Yeah.
How many enemies can a little girl have?
I wouldn't know.
Everything I make beyond expenses
goes in a blind trust.
A girl needs her father.
No, not this father.
The best thing I can do for her life?
Not be in it.
Is it ready?
We went through all that trouble
to get Johnny here invited to this shindig.
Seems like a waste not to use that invitation.
You're using it. Once you have hands
on the nerve agent...
...pocket it, walk right on out.
Heh. Copy that.
[PEOPLE CHATTERING]
Thank you very much.
Your generosity is much appreciated.
That's not exactly Army camo.
Have you given any thought to what
would happen if Qadir recognizes you?
Mr. Diggle, who is this vision?
His new bodyguard.
Mm. You will have to refer me
to your security company.
I'm glad you could come tonight. It's the
least I could do after you saved my life.
Again.
I will see you inside, my friend.
Gholem.
It would seem I didn't have time
to get credentials for my associate.
Come. This way.
[DEVICE HUMMING]
Gosh, I'm so sorry.
I forgot those were in there.
Enjoy the benefit, Mr. Diggle.
-Deadshot and his gear are in position.
-Tiger's got the overwatch.
Harbinger to all. Fire in the hole.
Shooter at my 10.
-Prepare to bound.
GAYNOR: Got you covered.
-Bounding.
-Go, go, go!
All clear.
He's just a kid.
[PEOPLE CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY]
And don't you look lovely tonight?
QADIR:
I appreciate...
[DIGGLE SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
Oh, I think you owe your bodyguard
a dance.
I insist.
[SMOOTH JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING ON PIANO]
Deadshot en route to package.
The fate of the world resting in the hands
of Floyd Lawton.
It helps to focus on the mission.
Is that what you tell yourself?
I tell myself to see the world how it is,
not how I want to see it.
We both operate in the gray.
The only difference is, I'm willing to admit it.
-Not the only difference between us.
-True. I don't judge other people.
-I'm the man I've always been.
-And I'm who I've always been.
You're rigid, John.
You're blind to any viewpoint
that isn't yours.
These past few months have been amazing.
But we've done more playing than talking.
Because when we talk,
we tend to get divorced.
Don't worry. It's virgin.
Ugh, which is why it tastes terrible.
-Jerk.
-Heh.
So. It looks like things with you
and Sara are going well.
I'm not sure you're the best person
to talk to about all this.
Why? Is it because of the
cheating, shipwreck, drowning...
...not drowning,
you're back, she's back thing? Sorry.
It's brutal AA honesty talking.
I preferred it when
we were all lying to each other.
No, you just thought you did.
I know you better than almost anyone, Ollie.
I know that you think that you don't deserve
to be happy, but you're wrong.
You think that keeping her at arm's-length
you're protecting her, but you're not.
You're only protecting yourself.
It's more complicated than that.
It always is.
I got the address for that account number
you gave me.
-I'll call Roy and Sara.
-No.
I'm not giving Slade any more targets.
You can't go out there by yourself.
It's suicide.
This started with the two of us.
That's how it ends.
Deadshot's on target.
Heh, bingo.
[PANTING]
OLIVER:
I don't know what to do.
He's too far ahead.
He's spent years planning this.
He knows everything about me.
I can't. I...
I don't know how to stop him.
You start by letting people help you.
But he's gonna come after you.
You're alive...
...because Shado isn't.
When he does, do you think it'll make
a difference whether or not we're together?
Let him come.
I'm not the girl he knew on the island.
I'm not that easy to kill.
Together.
I'm in.
I'll have the nerve agent in my pocket
in 30 seconds.
Harbinger...
...we've got what I would describe
as a little bit of a situation here.
-Explain.
-I've got eyes on the nerve agent...
...and I'm not gonna be able to move it,
much less pocket it.
Standby, Deadshot.
I need to talk to Waller.
WALLER: Go for Mockingbird.
-We have a situation.
The package is bigger than our
pre-op briefing indicated.
Standby.
Deadshot's on target.
I need to see what he does.
Activate the camera in his eyepiece.
Multi-spectrum from Lawton's rig
coming in now.
It's a match.
Tiger, move for extraction.
Deadshot, remain in position.
Harbinger and Freelancer,
evac and head to rally point.
Deadshot isn't topside with the package.
I only needed eyes on.
Fall back to the rally point.
Wait, you knew that the nerve agent
was too large to be extracted?
Fall back to the rally point.
The Nine is inbound and hot.
Mockingbird out.
-What the hell are Nines?
-MQ-9's.
Predators. Waller's called in a drone strike.
Everyone here is dead inside of 10 minutes.
The Nines carry the Hellfire missile.
Just one can level this building.
Your boss doesn't care
who's here when it does.
Lyla, we have to get these people
out of here.
Maybe there's a house alarm we can trigger.
John, we have to move now.
I have a better idea.
Excuse me.
If I could have your attention please.
In honor of our host.
Gholem Qadir excels at
everything he puts his mind to.
Be it business, philanthropy...
...or terrorism.
I guess you could say that Gholem
is somewhat of a Renaissance man.
He dabbles in a little bit of everything.
Arms trading, did I mention sex trafficking?
[GUESTS MUTTERING]
Or the deadly nerve agent that he's holding
just 30 feet beneath this very dance floor?
[ALL CHATTERING]
-These are lies. This man is a mercenary.
-Unh!
DIGGLE:
Lawton?
He's not answering.
I have to go help him.
Can't believe I just said that.
You. You were in Afghanistan.
Six years ago. You and that Judas were
deceiving me from the start.
-Good timing.
-I got tired of waiting for my invitation.
[CLICKING TONGUE]
Disobeying orders, John.
Behind you.
That's two you owe me, junior.
We have to go.
Waller told me to stay here.
-There's an incoming drone strike.
-How contemporary. Get your team clear.
You're on my team. It is time for you to go.
Yeah, that's right. It is time.
And this is my way to go.
Suicide Squad, remember?
I'm expendable, John.
Even got the damn bomb in my head
to prove it.
This way, at least I get to go out doing
something honorable.
-You don't get to die that easy, Lawton.
-Really?
Why don't you give me even just one
good reason why not, huh?
Zoe.
[MUTTERS]
-What about the nerve gas?
-Believe me...
...Waller's already got that covered.
Go. Go. Go.
The drone shifted course.
-It's following us.
-Ha-ha-ha.
-Do you find that funny?
-Waller, what a woman.
How do you think she knew where to
send the drone, huh?
And I mean, the precise coordinates.
-The implants.
-Bomb and GPS.
Pretty clever, right?
The drone ain't targeting Gholem's house.
It's targeting me.
Hang on, do I get a say in this?
-Turn around.
-What are you doing?
-Look, I think I'd rather get blown up.
-Hold still.
This is gonna hurt.
The Markovian government is threatening
retaliation...
...following an unprovoked drone attack
over a no-fly zone.
Just the attention we wanted to avoid.
Well done.
-I'm not the one that sent that drone.
-It was cloaked.
An explosion atop a chemical weapons
cache is easy to explain.
Instead, there were witnesses and we had to
send in a SEAL team to clean out the estate.
Think twice before
dragging me in to do your dirty work.
Somehow I don't think it will be an issue.
Good day, Mr. Diggle.
Kind of uncanny.
How Diggle knew exactly where
Lawton's implant was.
Still, it exposed an obvious design flaw.
We'll be putting the implants
in their spinal vertebrae now.
Have Lawton and the others
prepped for surgery.
Waller said in a few years
you might even get a pardon.
Don't worry, John.
We both know
I'm not gonna be around that long.
DIGGLE:
You still employed?
People with my security clearance
aren't that easy to get rid of.
Right.
What about us, Johnny?
Last night, the man who killed my brother
showed more character...
...than the woman charged
with protecting the world.
[SIGHS]
Good and bad is not so clear to me.
One thing I do know for sure...
...black and white...
...is that I can never lose you again.
Finally.
Something we agree on.
GAYNOR:
Well, there goes another...
...terrorist-turned-ally.
By the way, I put you in for a commendation
for saving Qadir's ass.
You owe me a beer.
Congratulations.
Yeah, well. "Kill a kid, get a medal," right?
When someone's shooting
a Kalashnikov at you...
...he's not a kid.
I see things differently.
It's a complicated world, Johnny.
Is it okay if I call you Johnny?
I don't think I caught
your first name, Michaels.
Lyla.
It's really good to meet you, Lyla.
In international news,
a United Nations inspections team...
...was called to a chemical weapons
manufacturing facility...
...hidden beneath the Markovian estate
of humanitarian Gholem Qadir.
Closer to home, mayoral candidate
Moira Queen stumped for...
...an initiative to revive inner-city
afterschool swim programs.
I remember how much my children
enjoyed swimming.
I couldn't get them out of the pool. Ha-ha-ha!
We need...
-I thought you hated swimming.
-I detest swimming.
So does Thea.
My mother sometimes, ahem, enjoys
a casual relationship with the truth.
Anyway.
Thank you for being there for me.
You mean, for not letting you
push me away?
I'm going to stop doing that.
Yeah. Good.
You'd be wasting your time, anyway.
LAUREL:
It looks like you took my advice.
Thank you.
Helping me with Sara, I know that that...
...can't be easy.
Helping two people I care about?
There's nothing easier.
I came by to take Sara to dinner.
Would you care to join?
I'd love to, but I need to go see an old friend.
Okay.
WALLER:
Hello, Oliver.
Hello, Amanda.
-Still mad at me?
-Lucky for you...
-...you've been pushed down that list.
-Really?
Who do you wanna kill more than me?
Slade Wilson is alive.
You killed him. It's not possible.
Everything is possible
where Slade is concerned.
And I need your help to find him.
-I might have something.
-What?
There's a new player we've been tracking.
Mercenary.
He's left a trail of bodies from Macao
to Istanbul to Lisbon.
A trail that leads right here to Starling.
We've been calling him Deathstroke.