(BEEPING)
(PANTING)
Computer time's up, blondie.
Don't think so.
The judge granted me
a minimum of 30 minutes per week.
I have 90 more seconds.
The judge ain't here. I am.
Let's see what you're so hot for
without an Internet connection.
BRIE: Bees.
I like bees.
(ALL GRUNTING)
Thea, your back foot's sliding out.
No, it's not!
(GRUNTING)
Just because you can't see me,
doesn't mean I'm not there.
You gotta sense my presence,
even when I'm not in your eye-line.
What advice would you
give to me? Humor me.
Getting tired,
you're dropping your shoulder
and you're opening yourself up.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
So you took your morning run from
six miles, to what? Maybe two?
(GRUNTS) Yeah, well, taking care of
a toddler is a marathon in itself.
Right, but when you
sacrifice your endurance,
you're losing steam too early
in our sessions. Let's go again.
I'll pass.
I keep on running out of excuses
for all my new bruises.
And they're from you, not bad guys.
The streets have gone quiet since
we took Darhk off the board.
His organization hasn't been.
HIVE is still out there.
Yeah. And when they rear their head,
we'll take care of them,
but we have to celebrate our victories.
If we don't, we forget
what we're fighting for.
-(SIGHS)
-What's wrong?
Alex has a new job interview.
With Ruvé Darhk.
What?
She's looking for a new chief of staff
for the April 6th election.
Oh, still don't know see
why you just can't
put yourself back in the race, Oliver.
You know, voters, they hate flip-flopping
and that would be a pretty big one.
I can't let him work for the wife
of the prince of darkness.
And what if he got a better offer?
Are you gonna run for mayor?
Palmer Tech.
They're hiring
a new head of public relations.
Oh.
I just heard that from someone.
Laurel, she's not Voldemort.
And I'm fine.
That's a good idea.
You should tell Alex to talk to Felicity.
Mmm-hmm.
-What?
-Nothing. It's just...
What, it's shocking that you know
who Voldemort is.
Well, I mean,
I'm not immune to pop culture.
I read a few of the Harry Potter books.
Really? I was gonna bet Thea
that you just saw the movies.
There were movies?
BARON: Mr. Queen. Where are my men?
I don't know, Reiter.
They're your men.
I wasn't gonna wait around
for them to kill me.
And what of Ms. Venediktov?
She's still here.
Don't move.
Where's my idol?
It's not your concern anymore.
It's nearby. I can feel it.
The powers it bestowed
are on the wane, but...
Enough!
As I was saying, the magics
are losing their potency,
but I still have enough to make
short work of the two of you.
A quarter of a million dollars per unit.
It's hard to believe something so small
could cost so much money...
When Digital Equipment Corporation
released the first VAX, it cost $700,000.
(SNEEZING)
Honestly, I think of this as a bargain.
Except we're not starting
a computer revolution here.
We're trying to repair spinal injuries.
The new estimate of spinal injuries
per year are at 12,000 people.
Unless everyone's a billionaire,
walking again is a luxury item.
Sounds like something
Mr. Dennis would say.
He already has.
He's called a board meeting
to discuss how many zeroes
he can add to
the end of that price point.
(SNEEZES) Anything I can do to help you?
No, you can't do anything
with that cold. Go home,
get some rest.
Get some chicken noodle soup.
You sound like my mother.
Yeah, I'm sure if she was here, she'd tell
you to listen to my favorite girl.
Hi, honey.
Fine, but only because my cold medication
is starting to make me see double.
-Aw...
-Help. Help me, help...
Did you hear that?
He thinks we look like twins.
I don't think that's what he said.
(CHUCKLES) I think he did.
What can I help you with, Mom?
Well, my beautiful baby girl.
I am here to rescue you.
-Oh.
-After the...
(SIGHS)
B-R-E-A-C-K-U-P,
you could use some
regular socialization so...
How about leisurely lunch?
Oh, my God. I don't know what's worse.
The fact that you just spelled out
breakup or that you misspelled it.
-Huh?
-Yeah.
-No.
-No, Mom. I'm fine.
I have a lot of work to do.
No. Just a quick one. Sweetie...
Sorry. Is this a bad time?
You people are like Tribbles today.
What's up? Everything okay with...
-Oliver?
-I was gonna say your night job.
You know, that thing that you do at night.
Yeah, no, that... That's fine.
Ollie is... Is fine too.
It's actually about Alex.
Um, he's no longer working
on the campaign so I was...
-(PHONE RINGING)
-Oh, my God, it's Mr. Dennis.
I have a board meeting.
You know what? He's a jerk. He can wait.
What did you wanna ask me about Alex?
(CHUCKLES) You know,
usually someone buys me dinner
before we start breaking out the cuffs.
(LAUGHS)
I thought you just lost your magic,
but your charm seems to be waning as well.
How the hell did you get in here?
(CHUCKLES) I used to be Ra's Al Ghul.
Yes. This, I know. What I'm less clear of?
Is why my resources haven't been deployed
to get me out of here.
Well, that's what I'm here to explain.
Although my time in here might be
limitless, Malcolm, my patience isn't.
That's cute.
As I was saying, I've been
in touch with your resources
and they don't seem to have any
particular love left for you, Damien.
Something to do with hocus and pocus
and killing fellow members
when you get miffed.
HIVE is moving forward with Genesis
but not with you.
They like you here, out of trouble.
But they do wish you
the best of luck with your trial.
(GRUNTS)
(CHUCKLES) Don't be embarrassed.
Performance issues are common
for men of your age.
(GRUNTS)
Whoa, you really do have eyes
in the back of your head.
I thought you had work to do.
I realized it could wait.
You've been pushing us pretty hard
and I know why.
Oliver, it's okay to miss Felicity.
I... I appreciate what you're doing but
I don't think that you're the...
Person to help you through it?
Why?
-Because of what we used to have?
-Yeah.
But maybe, it just gave me
a little insight.
Well, I mean, in fairness, I did
wreck what we had too, so...
In your defense, you were
missing and presumed dead for five years,
but that's not what I mean.
I know how passionately you love
and how much it hurts
once that love goes away.
You know, between...
Merlyn, Slade Wilson and Ra's al Ghul,
I thought that I'd be a little...
Tougher than this by now.
That's a different type of pain.
And this takes longer to heal.
But I'm here for you.
Thank you.
You're not late, Phil.
We're still waiting on Ms. Smoak.
-(GRUNTING)
-Are you all right?
Phil? Phil? Phil!
I'm calling 911.
-(YELLING)
-I can't get a signal!
You'll have to excuse my tiny friends.
Their bee-havior can be
appalling sometimes.
But it's a necessary evil.
You see, I needed your full attention.
What the hell do you want?
Straight to the point.
I like that.
Your CEO has miraculously
recovered from paralysis,
thanks to an implantable
bio-stimulant microchip.
Hand one over and I'll "bee" on my way.
There's only one prototype...
The one inside Felicity Smoak.
So, what's a girl gotta to do
to get on her calendar?
I can talk to Alex if you want,
but I can't promise a job
he'll be excited about.
Probably best to keep him away
from a super-villain's wife
THEA: (CHUCKLES) Yep,
you're right about that.
BRIE: Hello out there.
What the hell?
I am looking for Felicity Smoak.
Because it would be swell if we could
chat about a certain implantable bio-chip.
I'm sure your board would
bee-ally appreciate it.
Brie Larvan.
-You know this wackadoodle?
-I had a run-in with her last year.
If this Brie Larvan is coming for you,
we need to get you out of here
No, no, no.
No, I don't think she knew who I was.
She's after something else.
She said something about an implant.
A bio-stimulant microchip.
There's only one working prototype.
-Where is it?
-In the base of my spine.
Which brings me back to, we need
to get you the hell out of here
But we have to get everyone out of here.
I can't even get a signal
FELICITY: She's jammed all communications.
Oh, my God...
TV REPORTER: Eyewitnesses report the bees
have been swarming
the Palmer Tech headquarters
-for the past 20 minutes...
-(COUGHING)
Now all communications in and out
of the building have been cut off.
Have you seen this?
I was just there.
I'd still be there if Felicity hadn't...
Oh my God, Felicity.
(PHONE BEEPING)
(ENGAGED TONE)
But you have a 104 fever.
Where do you think you're going?
To get help.
I'm pretty sure the police
already know about this.
I'm not talking about the police.
FEMALE REPORTER: We are hearing that SCPD
has sent in an ESU squad.
(SIGHS) Felicity's in there.
Thea, too. I tried calling but no answer.
She must have already been inside
by the time the swarm hit.
-(SIGHS)
-(CELL PHONE VIBRATING)
John's coming in.
This is HIVE, right? There's no way that
this bee attack is a coincidence.
I don't think it's HIVE and I don't think
those are bees.
No. Bees don't give off hundreds
of different kinds of radio frequencies.
Robot bees. Terrific.
Last year, Felicity helped Barry Allen
take down the bees' inventor, Brie Larvan.
So it's payback.
Well, Larvan picked a hell of
a day for it. Donna is in there too.
-What?
-She stopped by Felicity's office to
you know, cheer her up a little.
Suit up.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
The department just tried sending
in an ESU squad,
they couldn't get through that swarm.
Now if their Kevlar couldn't hold,
what makes you think that yours will?
We have to try.
I am running out of patience,
Felicity Smoak.
You have 10 minutes before
I start voting board members out.
FYI, my drones pack a lot more "Ow!"
than your typical sting.
Tick, tock. Tick, tock.
Okay, we need to get out of here.
But, Thea, the bees are out there...
Yeah, and sooner or later,
they're gonna be in here.
Okay, you know... (SIGHS)
From now on, I'm going with flats.
I mean, these assaults are weekly.
It's ridiculous.
It's just so not conducive
to high fashion.
Okay, definitely sooner than later...
-What? We're trapped?
-Uh, I don't know.
-Not exactly.
-Okay.
Although I definitely don't have
the right shoes for that.
Oh, no, no, no.
-(BEEPING)
-Hello?
(COUGHING)
Anybody here?
(IMITATING GREEN ARROW)
Yes, we are here, Curtis.
And we just can't wait to hear how
you used the cell phone
that we gave you to help us
rescue Dr. Palmer to
track us back to our...
Secret lair.
Okay, so we don't need to
take out the bees.
We just need to take out Larvan.
Yeah, well, it doesn't make much sense
if we can't get inside.
Holy frak...
You're the...
And wait, you're...
Wait, wait, wait, you-you're...
Uh, just so you guys know,
if, if I pass out,
it's because I'm sick,
not because you know...
So can anybody just walk in here?
-(BUZZER SOUNDS)
-(GATE OPENS)
So you're the infamous Damien Darhk.
Oh, I get it.
You're big fans, aren't ya?
You want me to pose for a selfie?
Back in Star City, you were a big deal.
In here, the only big deal is him.
(MUBLES) Oh, gentlemen.
I think we're getting off
on the wrong foot.
There must be some sort of way
that we can have...
(STUTTERS) Wow.
(SCOFFS) No, I'm sorry, I just gotta know,
did you sew that in yourself or do you
have like some kind of lip sewing guy?
(ALL GRUNTING)
-(BUZZER SOUNDS)
-GUARD: Stop right there!
Break it up!
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
THEA: How did you deal with her
in the first place?
(GRUNTS) The old-fashioned way. Hacking.
(GRUNTS) I can't do that without
a working computer.
Okay. Well, at least all we have to do is
wait for Ollie and
the rest of them to get here.
Just when I thought I was out...
I thought I left this all behind.
(BEES BUZZING)
-Did you hear that?
-Bee.
Make that plural, bees,
in the air vents. Go!
(DONNA GASPS)
(BOTH GASPING)
(INHALES)
Curtis?
Oh, this is so weird. (CHUCKLES)
(STUTTERING) I literally just had a dream
where you were the Green Arrow.
Wait. This is happening.
-(GASPS) You're the Green Arrow?
-Yeah.
I could have sworn it was
Neal Adams in data processing.
(GASPS) And this is the Arrow cave.
Oh, my God.
Actually, we call it the bunk...
It's the bunker, but yeah.
You're Laurel Lance, the ADA.
(STUTTERS) I've seen you on TV before.
(GASPS) And you're Captain Lance.
And you're...
I'm sorry, I know I've met before
but I can't really place
your name right now...
Curtis, that's John Diggle.
I need you to focus for a second, please?
Oh, my God. This place is unbelievable.
I mean, you guys must be
drawing some crazy electricity.
How do you keep it off the grid? (GASPS)
This is STAR Labs 5000 Exostation.
What are the specs on this?
Curtis! Get it together.
Okay, now I'm starting to see
the whole Green Arrow thing.
And I'm actually starting
to feel better too.
That's because we gave you
an IV to rehydrate you.
It should keep you going for a few hours.
Okay, forget the how for a second.
What are you doing here?
I saw the beehive on the news.
Felicity's in there.
Yeah, we were just about to mount
a rescue mission.
Do you guys even know what that is?
That is an army of robotic bees.
Yeah, that's my life now.
Brie Larvan. Apparently, she hacked
the prison computer network
and got herself an early release. Clever.
Feel free to use that by the way.
I mean, you can't put me in front of
this beautiful machine
and expect me not to
take it for a test drive.
Looks like Felicity keeps files on
various criminals. Who's The Dodger?
Looks like we have ourselves a taller,
more dude-like version of Felicity.
And I can help. Now, look, these bees,
they're tiny computers, okay?
With Felicity trapped inside, you guys are
gonna need someone to hack them,
but I'll have to "bee" careful.
(LAUGHS)
It's too soon for, for bee puns, right?
Let's assume that it is.
-Yeah.
-LAUREL: Curtis,
can you immobilize enough bees
to give us a way in?
There's only one way to find out.
(SIGHS) Do it.
You want me on the team? I mean...
You want me on the team?
Let's go.
CURTIS: Whoo! (LAUGHS)
You see now,
the value of my prize, Mr. Queen?
What have you done to yourself?
There are primordial energies
that flow through all things.
I now command them.
You're insane.
Madness is a matter
of perspective, Mr. Queen.
Your morality blinds you from
understanding what I have achieved.
OLIVER: No, I understand.
You're killing people to gain power.
And what will you do about it?
Now, tell me where
you have hidden my idol,
and I promise to kill you both quickly.
We'll pass.
(GRUNTING)
-(BEES BUZZING)
-(FELICITY WHIMPERS)
Thank God.
Okay. (CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
How many are there?
Just try to think happy thoughts.
Okay. Now it's time to hack some bees.
Okay, so that's what that button does.
(GRUNTS)
Felicity...
(BEE BUZZING)
(DONNA WHIMPERS)
(WHIMPERS)
CURTIS: Felicity!
Curtis?
How do you know that bee's name?
I did it! I hacked the... (SNEEZES)
Bees! (CHUCKLES)
How did you... What are you doing there?
I know, right? I am still pinching myself.
(CHUCKLES)
All the bees are gone.
You're welcome.
The Green Arrow is on his way
as well as Black Canary and Spartan.
How cool is this?
Uh, they'll meet you at
the west utility entrance.
Can you get there?
Did I mention how cool this is?
Curtis, have you deactivated the bees?
Negative. Uh, I mean positive.
Sorry, I'm, I'm nervous.
The bees are down.
Uh-oh.
Now it's a negative. Negative!
CURTIS: The bees are back!
I... I got kicked out!
(GROWLING)
GREEN ARROW: Ahhh!
Come on, they're okay. Come on,
get back inside. Back inside.
(GROANING)
-(GREEN ARROW GRUNTS)
-LANCE: What the hell happened to him?
CURTIS: We couldn't see, I lost the feed.
He got stung.
Yeah, he's having some sort of reaction.
He didn't just get stung.
-The bee's inside you.
-Well, cut it out!
Do you guys have anesthesia around
here or something?
-Just do it!
-I can't find it, Oliver!
Okay, actually and
this is hard to believe...
We have a bigger problem.
The bee is replicating itself.
Inside Oliver.
What did that thing do to the Green Arrow?
Stung him. Badly.
He'll be okay. And he'll be back.
So will the others.
How do you know?
Hon, they just got their butts kicked,
by that, that, that bee man.
This is why we leave
the nicknames to Cisco.
-What?
-Inside joke.
-(CELL PHONE BUZZING)
-(SIGHS)
Oh.
BRIE: I thought we were friends, Smoak.
That you were gonna come through.
Ten minutes ago,
you had ten minutes to go.
You're out of time, glasses.
(GASPS)
BRIE: Bee-cause we got interrupted,
I'm gonna give you
an additional five minutes
before I start taking
your board members off the board.
-(FELICITY SIGHS)
-(DONNA WHIMPERS)
Oh, and,
your fiancé looks awfully sweet.
Sorry.
Ex-fiancé.
DONNA: Oh.
Okay, you cannot turn yourself in.
No, she'll kill everyone anyway.
(SCOFFS) To think she's in your office...
You're gonna have to sanitize.
Yes. She is in my office.
Which is A, yes, gross but B, means
she's not with the board members.
You know, since she
brought up Oliver, honey, have you
-spoken to him since everything...
-Mom. Mom, Mom, Mom!
-I'm thinking!
-I'm sorry. You know what, honey?
I'm curious. Okay, I...
I have an idea.
(GRUNTING)
It's not working!
You did it while we were at Palmer Tech.
The drone has evolved
and adapted since then.
And the damn things are like The Borg.
You know, the, the bad guys
in Star Trek which...
(GROANS) I wish Felicity was here.
Well, she's not, Curtis! You are!
You have to be able to do something, okay?
When these things hit critical mass...
I'm not John Hurt in Alien.
Sorry, when I get nervous I make
pop culture references.
Okay, you can't hack it.
Can you lure it out?
Like some kind of...
I can't believe I'm saying this,
but some kind of digital
honey or something?
Not exactly. But if these are really
modeled after bees then...
They'll operate on a singular frequency
to orientate themselves.
If we can disrupt it, then we
can disperse the colony.
But, only problem is that
we need to generate
a high enough frequency
to damage their network.
But unless you guys have a portable
sonic projector handy, then, uh...
What?
This technology is amazing.
It reads your own vocal emissions and then
reprocesses it via a digital output
into a multichannel.
Yeah, we get it. It's badass.
But how is this going
to help us save Oliver?
Just give him a full Mariah Carey
and it should disrupt whatever connection
the bees are operating on.
All right, man. You sure about this?
(GRUNTS) We don't have time to be sure.
Curtis, do it!
Three, two, one...
(SCREAMING)
(GRUNTS)
(BEEPING)
(PANTS)
That was awesome.
(SIGHS)
You son of a bitch.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
My victory is inevitable, Mr. Queen.
Just think, all of this power came
from the life essence of one man.
Imagine what I will become when dozens
of lives are sacrificed in my name.
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
You'll become a monster.
-No.
-(COUGHS)
A god. Let me show you.
(GRUNTS)
No, I need more. (PANTING)
-You get 'em?
-Yeah.
They were in Curtis' office.
Right where you said they'd be.
-Uh, no pun unintended.
-(DONNA GASPS)
This is like that thing from that, uh,
that Jodie Foster movie.
Yeah. Uh, Panic Room?
It's actually more like a lair.
Decommissioned.
But if we can get
the board members in there,
they can escape through a secret exit.
Secret exit?
Um, don't you think you should
have thought of that, like,
I don't know, 15 minutes ago?
Oh, I'm sorry,
I was busy trying not to die.
And you were talking, talking, talking.
Well, you don't open up to me, hon.
I have to force your feelings
out of you sometimes like...
-Like a pistachio.
-THEA: Okay, Smoaks.
We gotta go. Come on.
(BEES BUZZING)
-Felicity...
-Mom.
No, I meant... Felicity!
(SCREAMING)
-Okay, we're moving...
-(BREATHES HEAVILY)
I know. Hold on to something.
-What? Why?
-Why?
This elevator, it only stops at the
sub-level and we need to stop it at...
(ALL GASP)
-Conference room floor.
-(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
Oh... I think we missed our stop.
No, this is right. Like I said,
the elevator doesn't stop at this level.
What? Um, honey, I think
this is a concrete wall.
Yeah, and these are explosive devices.
Actually, they're autonomous
communication devices.
I'm just really hoping that
Curtis hasn't figured out
how to stop them from exploding.
-Oh...
-DONNA: Be careful.
Oh, my God. They're gonna blow.
-Okay.
-Oh, God!
(BOARD MEMBERS COUGHING)
Okay, who wants to go on
a secret elevator right now to the, um...
-Panic room.
-Yeah, the panic room.
-FELICITY: Come on.
-(THEA COUGHING)
Come on.
Trying to escape the hive?
Keep them safe.
Huh? What?
Beautiful creatures, my bees.
-They obey you?
-Neural implants.
You used to control them
the old-fashioned way.
How did you know that?
Lucky guess, I guess.
So why bees? Why not an obsession
with flying squirrels?
Squirrels aren't dying off
at a rate of 30% per year.
And nobody cares,
but bees are essential to life.
We're all connected.
The world is one giant honeycomb.
Kumbaya might have
a little more credibility
if you weren't threatening
people's lives.
What, you mean like this?
I am running out of patience,
and your friend is running out of time.
Now give me the damn...
(GRUNTS)
That was embarrassing.
I have a tumor on my L4 vertebrae.
The tricky little guy's wrapped
around my spinal cord.
The only way to cut it out
involves a surgery
that will leave me paralyzed
from the waist down.
All the bees in the world couldn't
get a cripple to walk.
And then I read about your miracle chip.
Of course... (CHUCKLES)
I couldn't afford it.
Maybe if you asked nicely...
I want the microchip specs or your friend
relives my favorite scene from My Girl.
Okay, honey, we all have a sad sob story,
but killing people doesn't fix anything.
The blueprints are on a remote hard drive
in Curtis Holt's lab.
You are a smart girl.
Elastic nanotubes, ultrasonic motors,
piezo ceramic elements...
I mean, this bee's got everything.
(CLEARS THROAT) That was inside me?
Well, that and thousands of its
microscopic larvae.
Don't worry. Should pass in a few days.
Can't wait.
Donna and the others made it out.
-Thea and Felicity?
-They're still inside.
Well, at least now we know
this stops the bees.
I wish it was that simple, but now
that we've played that card,
they've undoubtedly adapted to it.
But we just beat a group of robot bees
using a superhero doohickey,
if that's not high-five worthy,
I don't know what is.
Curtis. Now is not
the time for high fives.
Sorry. I, you know,
just got excited and...
You know, you gotta celebrate the wins
when they come.
What?
Thea and Felicity are still trapped
inside Palmer Tech
with who knows how many more bees.
-We're not winning.
-Oliver...
So, if you're gonna be down here,
if you're gonna be with us
then you need to understand the totality
of what it is you're signing up for.
If we do not do our jobs perfectly,
then people die!
And not just strangers but friends,
family and loved ones!
So think about that every time
you crack a joke
-or make light of what it is that we do!
-Hey!
Can I talk to you for a second?
Any puppies you wanna kick
while you're at it?
Bags of kittens that you wanna
throw down the river?
He needed to hear that.
Nobody needs to hear that, Oliver.
I know you're hurting, but you can't
take it out on Curtis.
I'm not taking it out on Curtis
I just need him to see.
-See what?
-That this is not a good life.
I walked away from it.
And I was happy.
For the first time in
eight years,
I was content.
-So why did you come back?
-I came back because of Felicity.
She convinced me that
we could do this job,
that we could save the city, and not...
Surrender to the darkness but...
I don't... I don't think that we can.
You're only saying that right now because
you're in 10 different kinds of pain.
But the harsh truth is that Felicity,
she broke up with you
because of your choices.
Because the lies that you told.
You, Oliver. Not the Green Arrow.
I know.
It just doesn't seem fair that I can save
a city, and not save my relationship.
Oliver, life's not fair.
(SIGHS)
Whether you're in Star City or Ivy Town.
But you're right.
You can save this city.
You do it every night.
You're a beacon of hope to people.
I just wish that you would try and use
some of that hope for yourself.
Oh, hi, fellas.
You know, I usually frown upon walk-ins
but how can I help you?
No guards are coming to save you
this time, Darhk. We made sure of it.
Good. Because then he'll only
has to kill two of you.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
I now you're probably asking yourself,
"What the hell just happened?"
It turns out your friend,
my new friend, Mr. Amar,
has a soft spot for his
only surviving relative.
A grandmother in Monument Point.
It is amazing what people will tell you
with a few phone calls and a kind voice.
Anyway, uh...
Are they dead? Are they dead?
No! I had this wonderful speech about how
I was gonna kill your grandmother
had you not killed them...
Never mind. On to other matters.
You many now call your organization
and have that other message delivered.
(LAUGHING)
I thought we were locked out.
Well, we're gonna have to see
if I haven't lost my touch.
And I have to see if my mom
and the board members made it to safety.
You really shouldn't have given
Brie what she wanted.
I'm sick of people being put
in vulnerable positions.
Yeah, well, now there's nothing
stopping her from bringing those
bee things back on us.
Well, at the very least it buys us,
the team... Your team, time.
Ollie's gonna be fine.
He always is.
Well, unfortunately,
in Oliver's case, "he always is"
isn't an accurate predictive metric.
I'm sorry. I'm just sick of worrying.
I'm sick of the violence...
Hey, so am I, okay? Of course I am.
But we put up with it, we push past it.
Because what we do is important, okay?
We have to be that beacon of hope.
Nobody else is.
You're the beacon of hope.
I quit the team because I couldn't
stand to work with Oliver, but...
But now that I'm out, I look at life from
a different perspective.
I mean, look around you.
Thea, we're in a Die Hard movie with bees.
Maybe I'm meant for great things, maybe
I'm not but whatever it is, it's not this.
I'm sorry. I'm not coming back.
Curtis...
You know, I'm beginning to see why
you and Felicity didn't work out.
Probably deserve that.
Look, I'm all for hugs and learning
but, like you said, there's still danger.
Yeah.
And you are a very scary man.
DIGGLE: Any luck with the bees?
Curtis is doing his best.
Thanks, Laurel.
Now that I've been able to actually
examine the bee,
I've deciphered their upgrade protocol.
The next time they adapt,
I can upload a virus
that will disperse into the entire hive.
Like what they did in
Independence Day, right?
What? I can't watch movies too?
So what's the plan?
I rigged an arrow with
a computer virus payload.
Shoot it near one of Bee Arthur's minions,
the virus will transmit to the rest
of the colony and we're done.
That's nice work.
(WHIMPERS) Uh...
Wait until it works before
you congratulate me.
(GASPS) I'm in. I mean, I'm out.
I mean, I have Internet.
-Mom and the board members, they're okay.
-What about us?
I'm working on overriding the bees,
the ones that are outside
guarding the building
BRIE: Don't bother.
These blueprints will be useful.
Thanks for those.
You have what you want.
So go build it yourself!
I think we're confused.
To get the schematics, I had to tip-toe
through Palmer Tech's computer network.
And I saw some
very familiar computer code.
You never forget the hacker
who sent you to prison.
Hi...
SPARTAN: We're clear.
BLACK CANARY: At least
there's no signs of the bees.
(BEES BUZZING)
(SCREAMING)
Go!
(GASPING)
(GUN FIRING)
Looks like your green friend
didn't forget about you.
Never will.
-Hey, are you hurt?
-I'm okay.
Hey! Behind you!
(FELICITY GASPS)
There you go. Team Arrow,
which I am now a member of, pinch me,
I need a few more minutes to hack this
latest firewall the bees adapted.
I thought you were a better shot.
(THEA GRUNTING)
(GROWLING)
(GRUNTING)
Come on. Come on, come on,
come on, come on.
Got you.
(BEE BUZZING)
(GASPING)
(GRUNTING)
(SCREAMING)
(YELPS)
(GASPING)
Ew!
(GRUNTS) Don't worry, I won't tell
anyone you screamed.
-Oh, right.
-(GRUNTS)
(GRUNTS)
-Thank you.
-(SIGHS)
You never, never have to thank me.
(GRUNTS)
If I can't walk, you can't live.
Who should I kill first? A or "bee?"
-(BEES BUZZING)
-CURTIS: Guess who's back in control?
It's me, Curtis. In case you guys
don't recognize my voice yet.
No. No, no. (GRUNTS)
(BRIE STRUGGLING)
(CHUCKLES) Lay down, bee-yotch.
(CHUCKLES)
Too on the nose?
The bee came alive and, well,
things got a little out of hand.
But don't worry, it's dead now.
You did good, Curtis. And I'm...
I'm sorry if I made you feel differently.
Thanks, GA. (CHUCKLES)
You mind if I call you GA?
All right, yeah, I'll just stick
to Oliver then. (CHUCKLES)
Or Mr. Queen. What about Larvan?
What's gonna happen to her?
She's at Starling General.
Overdosed on toxins from the bees
and is in some sort of a coma.
More importantly, she's no longer
holding a dozen innocent hostages.
That's both comforting and horrifying
at the same time.
Welcome to our world.
Hey...
-(SIGHS)
-Is everything all right?
Yeah, you know, I should probably
just head home.
You know, learning that
you are, you know, you
and the murderous bees,
and this coma news...
It's just a lot to digest.
Plus the IV you guys gave me
is starting to wear off.
Well, you are always welcome here, Curtis.
Just keep the property damage to
a minimum next time. (CHUCKLES)
Okay.
-What's the exit?
-Right there.
Oh, yeah. (CLEARS THROAT)
Hey. Nice apology.
Well, I'm just trying to
be a beacon of hope.
And like you said, save a little bit
of that hope for myself.
(SOFTLY) Taiana. Hey, hey.
All right. All right. Hey, Jesus.
Come on, come on.
Oh, thank God. Hey, Taiana, wake up. Hey.
Oliver...
It's okay. You're okay...
-No.
-It's all right.
No, Reiter...
He's gone.
He must be in the tunnels
searching for his idol.
We can't let him find it.
If he's in the tunnels,
searching for his idol,
that means he's not going to the prison.
This our chance to save your friends.
And what of Reiter's men?
They are still up there.
(PANTING)
That's why we're gonna
kill all of them first.
(DOOR OPENS)
I don't suppose it's too late
to reheat that soup?
Where have you been? You bolted
out of here like a crazy person.
Like some kind of a superhero
off to save the day.
I was chasing some silly fantasy
that I can help the police.
It was scary and thrilling and
dangerous and... Did I mention scary?
The... The point is, is that I saw enough
to know that this is where I belong.
At home, with you.
So no more disappearing acts?
I promise. (COUGHING)
(SIGHS) Let's get you some of that soup.
Terrific. (CHUCKLES)
(GRUNTS) Maybe I should burn
some incense in here or something.
Probably a very good idea.
Remind me to never wear
black and yellow ever again.
(CHUCKLES)
Wait, where'd your mom go?
Oh, Captain Lance drove her home.
Yeah, that is something I'll never
be able to wrap my brain around.
-(CHUCKLES) Kinda cute.
-(CHUCKLES)
Don't you miss this?
I mean, I... I know you said that you
wanted to get away from it all but...
How could you?
What do you mean?
This. The, the thrill of this. The rush.
I mean, we just took down
a bad "bee-yotch" tonight.
(CHUCKLES)
It doesn't get any better than this.
I was never in it for that.
Not ever.
I wanted to make a difference.
Be part of that
beacon of hope you speak of.
So come back.
Rejoin the team.
I think I figured out another way.
It's actually, that insane bee lady
who gave me the idea. Ironically.
(SIGHS)
To remake this company.
To use the technology that
helped me walk again
to make people's lives better.
To make Palmer Tech into a beacon of hope.
Our mutual friends in HIVE have abandoned
our other mutual friend Mr. Darhk.
But he reached out to me.
Told me about you.
He said you were his ace in the hole.
(CHUCKLES)
Is that what you'd like me to call you?
Or do you prefer Mr. Diggle?