MY NAME IS OLIVER QUEEN.
AFTER 5 YEARS IN HELL,
I RETURNED HOME
WITH ONLY ONE GOAL...
TO SAVE MY CITY.
TODAY, I FIGHT THAT WAR
ON TWO FRONTS.
BY DAY, I LEAD STAR CITY
AS ITS MAYOR,
BUT BY NIGHT,
I AM SOMEONE ELSE.
I AM SOMETHING ELSE.
I AM THE GREEN ARROW.
PREVIOUSLY ON "ARROW"...
FORMER POLICE
CAPTAIN QUENTIN LANCE,
WHO WILL BE SERVING BESIDE ME
AS DEPUTY MAYOR.
APPRECIATE THE VOTE
OF CONFIDENCE, MR. MAYOR.
ARE YOU NOT
FROM STAR CITY?
NO. HAVENROCK.
FELICITY, VOICE-OVER:
THERE'S SOMETHING THAT
I NEED YOU TO KNOW.
HAVENROCK WAS NOT
THE INTENDED TARGET.
SOMEONE REDIRECTED
THE MISSILE TO REDUCE
THE NUMBER
OF CASUALTIES.
THAT SOMEONE WAS ME.
EVER SINCE
I KILLED ANDY...
YOU THINK YOU NEED
TO BE PUNISHED.
STOP FIGHTING
FOR ME, LYLA.
LYLA: WE NEED TO
TALK ABOUT JOHN.
HE'S BACK
IN THE COUNTRY,
AND HE'S IN PRISON,
AND I NEED YOU TO
BREAK HIM OUT.
RENE: COME ON,
MR. OLYMPIA.
HUSTLE UP.
MR. OLYMPIA'S
A BODYBUILDING
COMPETITION.
I WAS...AM
AN OLYMPIC ATHLETE.
YEAH? THEY GIVE OUT
GOLD MEDALS FOR
EFFORT NOW?
CURTIS: VERY FUNNY,
AND IT WAS A BRONZE MEDAL.
WHY IS THAT SO HARD
TO REMEMBER?
OLIVER: QUIET. EVERY TIME
YOU'RE OUT IN THE FIELD,
YOU COULD DIE.
DON'T FORGET THAT,
DON'T LOSE FOCUS.
OVERWATCH, DO WE HAVE
THE TARGET?
HEADED TOWARD
THE EAST EXIT,
CLOSING FAST.
DO WE KNOW WHAT HE STOLE?
NOT YET,
BUT I HAVE A FEELING
WE'RE ABOUT TO
FIND OUT.
ONLY IF WE SNAG HIM
IN THE CORDON.
ARTEMIS, BE READY.
DOES THIS MEAN
I ACTUALLY GET
TO SHOOT SOMEONE?
I MEAN, NOT, YOU
KNOW, SHOOT SOMEONE
SHOOT SOMEONE.
I JUST MEANT THAT
MORE THAN...
OLIVER: WE KNOW
WHAT YOU MEANT.
YOU WAIT FOR HIM
TO REACH THE CORDON,
THEN ENGAGE.
-DO YOU COPY?
-COPY.
CURTIS: COPY.
RENE: COPY.
STILL A LOT
OF GROUND TO COVER.
RAGMAN SHOULD
BE HERE.
OLIVER: OVERWATCH, DO YOU
HAVE A 20 ON RAGMAN?
I TEXTED HIM,
LIKE, 10 TIMES
AND THEN 10 MORE,
BUT NADA.
MAYBE HE'S SICK.
I MEAN, THE FLU'S
BEEN GOING AROUND,
AND BY THE LOOKS
OF THOSE RAGS,
HE DOES NOT HIT
THE DRYCLEANER VERY OFTEN.
[DOOR OPENS]
HOLA, MUCHACHO.
WILD DOG, THAT IS
ARTEMIS' SHOT.
I GOT HIM.
[GUNSHOTS]
WHAT THE?
I GOT HIM.
[GUNSHOTS CONTINUE]
WHAT DID I SAY?
THAT WAS ARTEMIS' SHOT!
DUDE WAS
GETTING AWAY.
NO, HE WASN'T.
AND YOU MISSED.
YOU WERE IN THE NAVY.
YOU SHOULD KNOW BETTER.
I WAS DISHONORABLY
DISCHARGED ACTUALLY.
YOU THINK THAT
I DON'T KNOW THAT?
DELIVER THAT
AND THE EVIDENCE
TO THE ANTI-CRIME UNIT
AND THEN GO HOME.
WHAT ABOUT TONIGHT'S
TRAINING SESSION?
YOU'RE TAKING
A FEW DAYS OFF.
EVELYN: NICE GOING...AGAIN.
HOW ARE WE SUPPOSED TO
GET THIS BUY TO THE ACU,
CALL A UBER?
[DOOR SLAMS]
OLIVER.
THE OP'S OVER,
AND YOU'VE BEEN MIA
FOR DAYS.
IT'S NOT ACCEPTABLE.
GET IT TOGETHER
IMMEDIATELY,
OR YOU'RE OFF
THE TEAM.
THAT'S WHY I'M HERE,
TO TELL YOU IN PERSON.
I'M OFF THE TEAM.
FEELS PRETTY QUICK
TO THROW IN THE TOWEL.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE
JUST GETTING STARTED.
I WAS,
AND THEN FELICITY
TOLD ME THE TRUTH
ABOUT HER ROLE IN HAVENROCK.
YOU DIDN'T KNOW
SHE TOLD ME.
DID SHE ALSO TELL YOU
THAT SHE WAS FACED
WITH AN IMPOSSIBLE
CHOICE?
I COMPLETELY
REALIZE THAT.
I GET IT WASN'T
HER FAULT,
BUT THAT DOESN'T
CHANGE THE FACT
THAT EVERY TIME
I LOOK AT HER
I SEE THE FACES
OF MY FAMILY,
OF EVERYONE
I EVER LOVED.
FELICITY IS
A CONSTANT REMINDER
OF WHAT I LOST,
AND AS LONG AS THAT'S TRUE,
I'M SORRY.
I CAN'T BE HERE.
WHAT ABOUT
YOUR FATHER?
I THOUGHT HE WAS
THE REASON YOU WERE
DOING THIS.
I'LL HAVE TO FIND
ANOTHER WAY TO HONOR HIM.
I'M SORRY TO LOSE YOU.
I'M SORRY TO GO.
THANK YOU
FOR EVERYTHING.
FELICITY: DID MY COMMS
DECEIVE ME,
OR DID YOU ACTUALLY
LET THE RECRUITS TAKE
AN SCPD VICTORY LAP?
IT'S NEVER
A VICTORY LAP.
THEY'RE ROUGH
AROUND THE EDGES,
BUT THEY'RE MAKING
PROGRESS EXCEPT RORY,
WHO WAS WAITING
FOR ME UPSTAIRS
TO SAY THAT
HE QUIT.
HE SAID YOU SPOKE
WITH HIM ABOUT HAVENROCK.
HEY.
HOW YOU HOLDING UP?
SHE DOESN'T KNOW?
ABOUT JOHN BEING IN PRISON?
OLIVER TOLD ME.
I'M SO SORRY.
WHAT LYLA MEANS...
WE ARE GONNA
BREAK HIM OUT.
OF MILITARY PRISON?
-YEP.
-WAIT, AND THEN WHAT?
JOHN IS JUST A FUGITIVE
FOR THE REST OF HIS LIFE?
BETTER THAN
BEING PUNISHED
FOR SOMETHING
HE DIDN'T DO.
LYLA, I'VE BEEN
STUDYING THE SCHEMATICS
THAT YOU HOOKED ME
UP WITH.
THIS WOULD BE
A LOT EASIER
IF WE HAD JOHN'S
COOPERATION.
YOU DON'T HAVE
WHAT NOW?
APPARENTLY, PRISON IS
MORE APPEALING TO JOHN
THAN COMING HOME
TO HIS OWN WIFE AND CHILD.
OK. SO WAIT A MINUTE.
NOT ONLY DO YOU WANT TO
COMMIT MULTIPLE FELONIES
AND MAKE JOHN
A WANTED MAN
FOR THE REST OF HIS LIFE,
HE DOESN'T ACTUALLY
WANT YOU TO?
CAN I SPEAK WITH YOU
FOR A MINUTE?
YEAH.
IS SHE GOING TO BE
A PROBLEM?
NO, BUT...
I WAS COUNTING ON HER
BEING A HELP.
MAYBE I SHOULD PULL
A FEW OF MY AGENTS
IN ON THIS.
NO. IF THIS...IF THIS HAS
YOUR FINGERPRINTS ON IT,
THEN BOTH
OF JOHN JR.'S PARENTS
WILL BE FUGITIVES.
THERE IS SOMETHING
THAT MIGHT ACTUALLY
MAKE THIS
NOT IMPOSSIBLE.
I JUST READ
A BRIEFING MEMO
ON A NEW PIECE OF TECH,
AN ANTIMOLECULAR
COMPOUND.
I WAS KIND OF HOPING
FELICITY COULD HELP US
GET OUR HANDS ON IT.
LYLA, WHATEVER IT IS,
I'LL HANDLE IT.
ANATOLY: SECOND TEST OVER.
DO NOT MAKE ANY WORSE
BY PULLING OUT SUTURE.
ANATOLY, IF THIS IS
HOW THE BRATVA TREAT
THEIR NEW MEMBERS,
I'D HATE TO SEE
HOW THEY TREAT
THEIR ENEMIES.
PASS THIRD AND FINAL TEST,
FIND OUT.
WHAT'S THE TEST?
YOU KEEP ASKING
ABOUT KOVAR.
OUR SOURCES SAY
THIS MAN
WILL GET YOU
ONE STEP CLOSER.
YOU HAVE TO ACT
FAST, THOUGH.
HE WILL BE ARRAIGNED
IN MORNING.
ARRAIGNED?
-JAIL.
-YEAH,
BUT WHAT MAKES YOU
THINK HE'LL TALK TO ME.
YOU TRUST ME.
I TRUST YOU.
LOOK. IT'S A LITTLE
EARLY FOR A DRINK,
DON'T YOU THINK?
IT'S NOT FOR DRINKING.
ANATOLY, WHAT THE HELL
WAS THAT FOR?
[SPEAKING RUSSIAN]
I SHOULD PROBABLY
JUST START PRERECORDING
APOLOGIES
FOR BEING LATE.
DON'T WORRY.
THEA TOLD US.
I'M SORRY, MAN.
GOUT IS A BITCH.
YES, IT IS.
I'M ACTUALLY GONNA BE
TAKING SOME TIME OFF
TO HAVE IT
TAKEN CARE OF.
WELL, FORTUNATELY,
WE NOW HAVE
A DEPUTY MAYOR
TO HELP PICK UP
THE SLACK.
IT'LL BE GREAT
WORKING WITH YOU.
YOU'VE HAD AN IMPRESSIVE
CAREER, MR. LANCE?
YEAH. I MEAN, A LOT
OF PEOPLE OUT THERE
PROBABLY WOULDN'T,
UH, SHARE THAT
OPINION,
BUT THANK YOU.
PUBLIC SERVICE
ISN'T EASY.
SOMETIMES, YOU
GET A LITTLE DIRTY
CLEARING OUT THE FILTH.
SPEAKING OF WHICH,
I HEARD THERE WAS
AN ARREST LAST NIGHT
THAT MAY HELP
IN OUR CASE
AGAINST TOBIAS CHURCH.
SERGIO ESPINOSA,
LONG-TIME
LOS HALCONES MEMBER
TURNED CHURCH
STRONGMAN.
THE GREEN ARROW
AND HIS MERRY BAND
OF VIGILANTES
LEFT HIM GIFT-WRAPPED
FOR US AT ANTI-CRIME.
THE ONLY THING THAT
WAS MISSING WAS A BOW.
WELL, YOU DON'T SOUND
TO HAPPY ABOUT THAT.
VIGILANTES ARE
A SUPERFICIAL SOLUTION.
IF WE NEED THEIR
HELP TO GET OUR
STREETS CLEAN...
IT MEANS WE HAVEN'T
DONE OUR JOBS RIGHT.
DO YOU THINK THAT
YOU CAN GET ESPINOSA
TO FLIP ON CHURCH?
I'LL LEAN ON HIM HARD,
SEE IF HE BUCKLES.
MAKE SURE HE DOESN'T
GET ANY HELP
FROM CROOKED COPS.
NOT A CHANCE.
I'M GONNA WALK
EVERY PIECE OF EVIDENCE
IN THE CUSTODY CHAIN
THROUGH MYSELF.
GOOD. UH, IF IT'S
ALL RIGHT WITH YOU,
I'LL HAVE QUENTIN
ACCOMPANY YOU,
BE MY EYES AND EARS
WHILE I'M OUT OF TOWN.
SURE. GIVE US
A LITTLE BIT OF TIME
TO GET ACQUAINTED.
HEH.
GREAT.
I'M SORRY.
WHEN DID, UH,
BABYSITTING EVIDENCE
BECOME PART OF
THE JOB DESCRIPTION?
SINCE I TRUST YOU.
YOU DO?
I MEAN, ALL THINGS
CONSIDERED?
IF WE DIDN'T THINK
YOU WERE RIGHT
FOR THE JOB,
WE WOULDN'T HAVE
OFFERED IT TO YOU, RIGHT?
I HAVEN'T
HAD A DRINK
IN A WEEK, OK?
WHERE THE HELL
ARE YOU GOING
ANYWAY?
STRANGE TIME
FOR A VACATION.
YOU SHOULD PROBABLY
ASSUME THAT IT'S NOT
A VACATION.
SHOULD I EVEN ASK?
NO. I...I'M NOT
GONNA BE GONE LONG.
JUST PLEASE MAKE SURE
THAT NO ONE DESTROYS
THE CITY WHILE I'M AWAY.
SURE.
OK.
FELICITY:
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
REVIEWING THE SCPD
EVIDENCE LOG
ON WHAT WE KEPT
FROM GETTING STOLEN
FROM KORD INDUSTRIES
LAST NIGHT.
-6,800 PROCESSOR.
-SO?
EXACTLY. KORD
MANUFACTURES
BLEEDING-EDGE TECH,
MILITARY-GRADE
WEAPONS,
I MEAN, ALL KINDS OF
CITY-THREATENING ITEMS.
WHY WOULD CHURCH
SEND A GUY TO STEAL
A COMPUTER CHIP
THAT YOU COULD BUY FROM
ANY TECH VILLAGE STORE?
WELL, WHO CARES?
EVERYTHING'S ON
ITS WAY TO LOCKUP NOW.
BECAUSE KNOWING WHAT
CHURCH'S ENDGAME WAS
IS LIKE...IT'S LIKE
THIS THING THAT'S STILL
OUT THERE, LURKING.
YOU ALL RIGHT
OVER THERE?
BECAUSE I'VE BEEN DOING
A LOT OF TALKING,
AND YOU HAVEN'T,
WHICH IS VERY WEIRD.
HA!
YOU KNOW HOW YOU
TOLD ME TO TELL RORY
ABOUT HAVENROCK?
YEAH. OH! HE'S
NOT SICK WITH
THE FLU, IS HE?
NO. HE'S JUST SICK
OF WORKING WITH ME.
DID YOU TRY
TALKING TO HIM?
THERE'S NOT A LOT
I CAN SAY THAT WOULD
MAKE HIM FEEL OK
ABOUT HIS ENTIRE FAMILY
BEING KILLED.
[COMPUTER BEEPS]
INCOMING.
ANOTHER ROBBERY
IN PROGRESS AT...
PALMER TECH!
I GOT TO CALL
OLIVER.
OR MAYBE DON'T,
AND WE'LL JUST LET
THE GET ROBBED.
IT WILL SERVE
MR. DENNIS RIGHT
FOR FIRING US.
HE FIRED ME.
YOU QUIT.
BECAUSE HE FIRED YOU.
SAME THING.
[ALARM BLARING]
MAN ON RADIO:
SANCHEZ, YOU GOT
ANYTHING?
NADA.
[CELL PHONE RINGS]
WHAT'S UP?
HEY. THERE'S BEEN
A BREAK-IN AT PALMER TECH.
ARE YOU STILL
IN THE AREA?
UH...YEAH.
I CAN LOOK INTO THAT.
HOW WAS PALMER TECH?
BEFORE YOU ANSWER,
YOU SHOULD CONSIDER
THAT YOUR PHONE HAS GPS,
AND IF YOU WERE
THINKING ABOUT LYING,
I DO ADMIRE
YOUR CONSISTENCY.
I WASN'T THINKING
OF LYING TO YOU.
I WASN'T LOOPING
YOU IN AFTER YOU
MADE IT CLEAR
YOU DIDN'T APPROVE
OF THE DECISION.
JOHN IS THE ONE
WHO DOESN'T APPROVE
OF THE PLAN.
JOHN'S NOT THINKING
CLEARLY.
WELL, I BET ROY IS,
AND IF HE WERE HERE,
I THINK HE WOULD
TELL YOU THAT LIFE
ON THE RUN
IS NO LIFE AT ALL,
AND I SEEM TO REMEMBER
YOU NOT BEING ON BOARD
WITH THAT PLAN.
ROY WAS MAKING
A BAD CHOICE
JUST LIKE JOHN IS
MAKING A BAD CHOICE.
HE IS CURRENTLY LOCKED
UP IN A MILITARY PRISON
FOR A CRIME
HE DIDN'T COMMIT.
TO ATONE FOR A CRIME
THAT HE DID COMMIT,
AND WHAT DOES IT MATTER?
JOHN DOESN'T WANT
TO LEAVE.
IT IS NOT YOUR CHOICE.
WHY DO YOU ALWAYS
HAVE TO GO AND MAKE
DECISIONS FOR HIM?
HE ALREADY ABANDONED
THE TEAM.
I AM NOT GONNA LET HIM
ABANDON HIS FAMILY.
IS THAT WHAT
THIS IS ABOUT,
JOHN LEAVING THE TEAM?
THIS IS SIMPLE.
I AM GONNA STOP JOHN
FROM MAKING A DECISION
HE WILL COME TO REGRET.
YOU SHOULD CONSIDER
DOING THE EXACT SAME
THING WITH RORY.
YOU DO REALIZE THAT
ME HAVING A CHAT WITH RORY
IS COMPLETELY DIFFERENT
THAN YOU COMMITTING
HALF A DOZEN
FELONIES, RIGHT?
DID YOU EVER THINK
YOU'D BE DOING
THIS AGAIN,
HANDLING EVIDENCE?
NO. DIDN'T THINK I'D
BE DEPUTY MAYOR EITHER,
BUT HERE WE ARE.
I WAS SURPRISED
YOU TOOK THE JOB,
TO BE HONEST.
FROM WHAT I HEAR,
YOU AND QUEEN HAVE A, UH...
A COMPLICATED HISTORY.
GOT TO BE A LOT
OF HATCHETS TO BURY THERE.
YEAH. WELL, AT LEAST
I KNOW WHERE THEY'RE BURIED.
THAT'S SOMETHING YOU
CAN'T BUY OR STEAL.
PACKAGE IS HERE, BOSS.
D.A., DEPUTY MAYOR, TOO.
AH. BONUS.
GET READY TO MOVE.
[TIRES SQUEAL]
LET ME GUESS.
FELICITY FILLED YOU IN.
THAT YOU'RE GONNA BREAK
INTO A MILITARY PRISON?
YEAH, AND YOU GOT
THE NERVE TO CALL
ME WILD DOG?
I'M DONE
DEBATING THIS.
EVELYN: REALLY? BECAUSE
THIS IS THE FIRST
WE'VE HEARD OF IT.
I THOUGHT WE WERE
YOUR TEAM.
RUNNING OFF TO BUST
SOMEONE OUT OF PRISON
SOUNDS LIKE TEAM BUSINESS,
AND WHAT HAPPENS TO US
WHEN YOU GET CAUGHT?
YOU'VE MADE IT CLEAR
THAT WE CAN'T DO THIS
VIGILANTE THING WITHOUT YOU.
WHEN I GET CAUGHT?
I'M NOT GONNA
GET CAUGHT.
CURTIS: RIGHT BECAUSE
WE'RE NOT GONNA
LET YOU DO THIS.
I'M SORRY.
DID YOU SAY THAT
YOU'RE NOT GONNA
LET ME?
YES. I NEED TO SEE YOU
PHYSICALLY DEPOSIT
THE ITEM.
I'VE BEEN ON THIS JOB
15 YEARS.
I'VE NEVER LOST
A PIECE OF EVIDENCE.
NOW RELAX, SERGEANT.
NO ONE'S DOUBTING
YOUR PROFICIENCY
HERE, OK?
SEEMS LIKE.
[WHISTLING]
THIS IS IT.
YOU GONNA LET ME DO
MY JOB NOW?
HAVE AT IT.
[CASE HUMMING]
-WHAT THE HELL?
-WHOA, WHOA, WHOA!
GET OUT OF HERE!
[ALARM BLARING]
CHURCH: WHOO!
FIND THE WEAPONS, BOYS.
AHH.
SORRY, GENTS.
LOAD THEM UP!
AND BURN THIS PUPPY DOWN.
CHURCH: LET'S GO, LET'S GO!
OK.
LAST CHANCE.
GET OFF THE STREET.
I DIDN'T THINK HE'D
ACTUALLY HIT YOU GUYS.
RENE: YOU KNOW WHAT
REALLY SUCKS?
CURTIS: REALIZING
THAT IN ALL THOSE
TRAINING SESSIONS
WHERE HE WAS KICKING
OUR RESPECTIVE ASSES
THE WHOLE TIME HE WAS
TAKING IT EASY ON US.
EVELYN: YEAH. REMIND ME
TO NEVER, EVER
GET ON HIS BAD SIDE.
CURTIS: I THINK THAT
WOULD IMPLY THAT HE
HAS A GOOD SIDE,
AND, YOU KNOW, FELICITY,
COULD YOU PLEASE
EXPLAIN TO ME AGAIN
HOW YOU THOUGHT THIS
WAS ALL GONNA GO DOWN?
WELL, I THOUGHT IF HE
SAW YOU GUYS ALL UNITED
AGAINST HIS CRAZY PLAN
HE'D RECONSIDER.
RIGHT BECAUSE
OLIVER QUEEN IS KNOWN
FOR THINKING THINGS
THROUGH AND TAKING
INPUT FROM OTHERS.
RIGHT.
WOW.
THE EVER-EXPANDING
CLUB HOUSE.
AND WHO ARE YOU?
I'M THEA, OLIVER'S
CHIEF OF STAFF.
AND ALSO HIS SISTER.
DON'T TELL ME OLIVER
BEAT YOU UP, TOO,
HEH. OLLIE DID THIS?
OBJECT LESSON,
LONG STORY.
IT'S FINE. DON'T ASK.
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU?
TOBIAS CHURCH HAPPENED.
THAT EVIDENCE THAT
YOU GUYS RECOVERED
FROM KORD INDUSTRIES...
MODIFIED
TO GO BOOM.
HE WANTED IT TO BE PUT
INTO LOCKUP.
AND HE WANTED
TO RAID IT.
ONE-STOP SHOPPING
FOR WEAPONS.
INCLUDING THOSE RPGS THAT
HE TOOK FROM AMERTEK
IF THIS REPORT'S RIGHT.
WE GOT TO FIND OUT
WHAT HE'S PLANNING
TO DO WITH THOSE
WEAPONS...BECAUSE IT
AIN'T NOTHING GOOD.
THIS IS A REALLY BAD
TIME FOR OLIVER TO BE
OUT OF TOWN.
YEAH. I JUST TRIED HIM.
HE'S GONE DARK.
WHY DON'T YOU GUYS
HIT THE STREETS?
WE WANT TO FIGURE OUT
WHAT CHURCH IS UP TO
BEFORE IT'S TOO LATE.
-YOU SURE?
-MM-HMM.
I DON'T THINK OLIVER
WOULD WANT US OUT
THERE WITHOUT HIM.
RIGHT. WELL, OLIVER
FORFEITED HIS OPINION
WHEN HE LEFT.
OK, BUT THIS IS
AN ALL HANDS ON DECK
SITUATION,
RAG-COVERED HANDS
INCLUDED.
JUST SAYING.
WHERE'S PRIVATE JESSEMAN?
THIS IS USUALLY
HIS DELIVERY.
FLU'S BEEN TEARING
THROUGH THE BASE, SIR.
I DREW THE SHORT STRAW.
I DON'T SEE YOU
ON THE LIST.
YOUR C.O. SHOULD HAVE
SUBMITTED A CHANGE
OF PERSONNEL FORM.
YOU SURE HE DIDN'T?
IT'S AN HOUR'S DRIVE
BACK TO THE BASE.
CAN'T YOU REFRESH
YOUR WI-FI OR SOMETHING?
THERE YOU ARE.
AS YOU WERE, PRIVATE.
THANK YOU, SIR.
[BEEP]
I'M IN.
25 MINUTES
TILL EXTRACTION.
ROGER THAT.
FACILITIES CAMERAS
ARE ON A CLOSED NETWORK.
IF YOU CAN GIVE ME
ACCESS TO THE MAINFRAME,
I CAN OPEN IT UP.
-I'M ON MY WAY.
-OLIVER...
IF YOU DON'T MAKE IT TO
THE EXTRACTION POINT...
I'LL MAKE IT,
AND I WON'T BE ALONE.
[SPEAKING RUSSIAN]
AHEM. OHH. AHH.
HEY. YOU SPEAK
ENGLISH?
YES.
YOUR ACCENT...
YOU ARE AMERICAN.
YEAH, MAYBE
ONCE UPON A TIME,
BUT, UH, NOW I'M MORE
JUST ENJOYING
EVERYTHING THAT RUSSIA
HAS TO OFFER.
YES. I CAN SMELL THAT.
YOU JUDGE ME?
YOU'RE IN THIS
CELL, TOO.
YES. A MISTAKE
MY BOSS WILL CORRECT
VERY SOON.
YOU MEAN
KONSTANTIN KOVAR?
HOW DO YOU KNOW
THAT NAME?
OH, SAME WAY THAT
I KNOW YOUR NAME'S
PYOTR FRIEDKIN,
SAME WAY I KNOW THAT
YOU LAUNDER MONEY
FOR KOVAR,
SAME WAY THAT I KNOW
THAT'S WHAT YOU'RE
DOING HERE.
HOW CAN YOU KNOW THAT
UNLESS...
ARE YOU BRATVA?
[GAGS]
[COUGHING]
[SPEAKING RUSSIAN]
HE'S FINE.
MMM.
I AM BRATVA,
AND YOU ARE GONNA
TELL ME EVERYTHING
THAT I WANT TO KNOW.
YOUR TURN TO RUN
SYSTEM CHECK.
I'M GONNA HIT THE HEAD.
DON'T TOUCH MY BALL.
[BEEP]
DUDE, WHAT THE HELL?
TRANSPONDER'S IN PLACE.
ROGER THAT.
I'VE GOT EYES NOW.
I'LL WALK YOU
TO JOHNNY'S CELL.
HEY!
HEY. IS THIS...UH,
IS THIS A BAD TIME?
DO I WANT TO EVEN ASK
HOW YOU FOUND ME?
HEH. I FEEL LIKE
THAT'S A TRICK QUESTION.
SORRY ABOUT THE MESS.
WOW!
THESE ARE AMAZING.
YOU SPEND ENOUGH TIME
WITH OTHER PEOPLE'S CASTOFFS,
YOU FIND WAYS TO MAKE
SOMETHING USEFUL
OUT OF THEM.
MY FATHER ALWAYS
USED TO SAY THAT.
HE OWNED A PAWN SHOP.
ON SOUTHMOOR ROAD, RIGHT?
HOW'D YOU KNOW?
LAST WEEK, YOU TOLD
OLIVER THAT YOU HAD
JOINED THE TEAM
TO HONOR YOUR FATHER.
WHEN YOU QUIT...
I WANTED TO FIND OUT
MORE ABOUT WHAT YOU
WERE GIVING UP.
YOUR FATHER WAS
A GULF WAR VETERAN,
2ND BATTALION,
1ST MARINES,
BUT THAT'S NOT WHAT
MADE HIM A HERO, WAS IT?
NO.
HE WORE YOUR RAGS,
HIS FATHER BEFORE HIM,
WHOSE NAME WAS
ALSO RORY.
THAT'S A BIG LEGACY
TO LIVE UP TO.
MINE IS GOING TO BE
WHAT HAPPENED
TO HAVENROCK.
I'M GONNA HAVE TO
LIVE WITH THAT
EVERY DAY FOR THE REST
OF MY LIFE,
KNOWING THAT I CANNOT FIX IT
AND KNOWING THAT IT'S
NOT THE LAST MISTAKE
THAT I'M EVER GOING TO
HAVE TO MAKE.
I STILL DON'T KNOW
IF I CAN...
WORK SIDE BY SIDE
WITH SOMEONE WHO'S
A REMINDER
OF WHAT YOU LOST.
I UNDERSTAND.
JUST LIKE YOU'RE
A REMINDER
OF WHAT I DID,
AND I...I KNOW THEY'RE
NOT THE SAME THING.
WE BOTH WANT
THE SAME THING,
TO BE ABLE TO LIVE
WITH WHAT'S HAPPENED
SO THAT WE CAN MOVE FORWARD.
[CELL PHONE VIBRATING]
IT'S CURTIS.
I AM SO SORRY,
AND WE COULD REALLY
USE YOU.
I...I WISH I COULD,
FELICITY.
I JUST...
I CAN'T RIGHT NOW.
I'M SORRY.
IF YOU CHANGE YOUR MIND,
WELL, WE'RE HERE.
LYLA: CELL 1138,
RIGHT SIDE,
THIRD FROM THE LEFT.
HARBINGER. HE'S NOT HERE.
GIVE ME A MINUTE
WHILE I SCAN
THE FEEDS.
OH, NO.
WHAT?
THEY MOVED HIM
INTO GEN POP.
YOU GO IN THERE,
NEITHER OF YOU
ARE GETTING OUT.
TALK TO ME. WHEN'S HE
COMING BACK TO HIS CELL?
OUTSIDE OUR WINDOW.
IF THOSE MPs WAKE UP,
THE FIRST THING
THEY'RE GONNA DO
IS MOVE JOHN AND ALL
THE OTHER PRISONERS
TO A MORE SECURE LOCATION,
AND WE LOSE OUR SHOT.
ABORT. WE'RE BLOWN.
TELL ME WHERE I CAN
FIND KOVAR.
YOU THINK YOU SCARE
ME MORE THAN HIM?
NO, BUT HE'S NOT
LOCKED UP IN HERE
WITH YOU.
I AM.
YOU WOULDN'T KILL ME
IN FRONT OF ALL
OF THEM.
I'M NOT GONNA LAY
A FINGER ON YOU.
SAME CAN'T BE SAID
FORE ALISA.
OR MAYBE I'LL VISIT
YOUR WIFE MAYA
WHEN SHE'S PICKING UP
ALISA FROM BALLET.
SOMEBODY IS GONNA DIE.
IT CAN BE KOVAR,
IT CAN BE YOUR WIFE,
IT CAN BE YOUR CHILD,
BUT I NEED YOU
TO CHOOSE
AND DO IT QUICKLY.
KOVAR IS VERY
PARANOID, CAREFUL.
WE NEVER MEET
IN PERSON,
ONLY REMOTELY.
REMOTELY? HOW?
A DIGITAL DEAD DROP,
THE DARK WEB.
WHAT'S THE IP ADDRESS?
WHAT IS
THE IP ADDRESS?
108.166.7.161.
IF THIS INFORMATION
IS INCORRECT,
YOUR FAMILY WILL SUFFER.
HOW DOES AN AMERICAN
BECOME THIS...THIS...
BRATVA DEVIL?
I DON'T KNOW.
[BONES CRACK]
[SPEAKING RUSSIAN]
ABOUT TIME, BLONDIE.
CAN WE GO NOW?
FIRST OF ALL,
NOT MY NAME.
SECOND, WERE YOU ABLE
TO LOCATE CHURCH
ON YOUR RECON?
NO, BUT STREET CAMS
ACTUALLY PICKED HIM UP,
SO WE KNOW HE'S
ON THE MOVE.
WE JUST DON'T KNOW
WHERE HE'S MOVING TO.
WE CAN'T GO AFTER CHURCH
WITHOUT KNOWING
HIS ENDGAME FIRST.
SOUNDS LIKE AN EXCUSE
TO SIT AROUND
AND DO NOTHING.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
NOT NOTHING.
CURTIS: YOU'RE
CROSS-PLOTTING
CHURCH'S PRIOR LOCATIONS
INTO A PROJECTION ALGORITHM.
HMM.
YOU PROBABLY GOT BEAT UP
IN GRADE SCHOOL A LOT.
AND JUNIOR HIGH.
OK. BASED ON CHURCH'S
ROUTE, I'M CALCULATING
AN 86% LIKELIHOOD
HE'S GOING TO 18 MILL ROAD.
WHY DOES THAT SOUND
SO FAMILIAR?
BECAUSE WE WERE
JUST THERE
TO HAND OVER SERGIO.
THAT'S WHERE THE ACU'S BUNKERED.
CHURCH IS GONNA
TAKE THEM OUT.
MONTES, QUIT
SCREWING AROUND.
STATION CHIEF, THIS IS
GANS FROM CELL BLOCK "C."
WE HAVE A CODE YELLOW SITUATION.
INITIATE IMMEDIATE LOCKDOWN
AND HAVE ALL PRISONERS
RETURN TO THEIR CELLS.
I'M NOT ROLLING
ON CHURCH.
YOU THINK YOU SCARE ME
MORE THAN HIM?
HMM.
NO...
BUT HE'S NOT
HERE WITH YOU.
I AM.
HMM.
YOU'RE NOT GONNA
PUT A BEATING ON ME.
YOU'RE A D.A.
YEAH. HAVEN'T YOU HEARD?
ALL OF THE JUSTICE
IN THIS CITY COMES
FROM VIGILANTES.
WORD ON THE STREET IS
IS THAT CHURCH'S
PLANNING SOMETHING,
SOMETHING BIG.
YOU TELL ME WHAT IT IS,
AND HE'LL BE THE ONE
IN THOSE CUFFS
INSTEAD OF YOU.
HEH HEH HEH.
YOU'RE TALKING
ABOUT THE TRUST.
OH, YOU CAN'T
STOP IT, MAN.
CAN'T EVEN
COME CLOSE.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
[MACHINEGUNS FIRING]
CHURCH.
AT LEAST WE DEFINITELY
KNOW WHERE CHURCH IS NOW.
D'ANGELO'S RIGHT.
WE GOT TO PUT HIM DOWN.
EVELYN:
AGAINST THAT?
WITHOUT OLIVER?
NO. WE'RE SH...
SHORTHANDED
AS IT IS.
YOU SCARED?
NO, BUT I'M NOT
STUPID EITHER.
EVIE'S RIGHT.
I'M NOT SENDING YOU GUYS
OUT THERE JUST TO GET
SLAUGHTERED.
THANKS FOR THE VOTE
OF CONFIDENCE.
YOU SAW WHAT YOU'RE
UP AGAINST, OK?
THIS ISN'T SOME
DRILL WHERE YOU
TAKE DOWN
A PETTY THUG
OR DRUG DEALER.
THIS IS REAL, OK,
WITH REAL STAKES.
THE 3 OF YOU COULD
DIE OUT THERE.
RORY: THAT'S SOMETHING
WE GET TO DECIDE
FOR OURSELVES, ISN'T IT?
I MEAN, I DON'T KNOW
ABOUT EVERYONE ELSE,
BUT I DIDN'T JOIN
THIS TEAM TO STAY SAFE.
OK. WHY DON'T WE
TAKE A VOTE?
ALL THOSE IN FAVOR.
RENE: WE'RE ALL GONNA
SAY YES, BLONDIE.
GOD. THAT'S NOT
MY NAME.
GOOD. OK. GO.
DO NOT DIE.
MAN ON P.A.:
CODE YELLOW.
RETURN ALL PRISONERS
TO THEIR CELLS.
IMMEDIATE CODE YELLOW ENFORCED.
MOVE PRISONERS
TO THEIR CELLS.
IMMEDIATE CODE YELLOW ENFORCED.
MOVE PRISONERS
TO THEIR CELLS.
[ALARM BLARING]
HEY, JOHN.
WHAT'S NEW?
I'M NOT DOING THIS.
I TOLD LYLA.
YEAH. YOU CAN YELL
AT US LATER,
BUT RIGHT NOW,
WE'RE ON A BIT
OF A CLOCK.
ARE YOU EVEN HEARING
ME RIGHT NOW?
I DON'T WANT ANYTHING
TO DO WITH THIS.
THE MPs ARE GONNA
DO A COUNT IN
A FEW MINUTES.
MY GUESS IS THEY'RE
ONLY EXPECTING TO FIND
ONE PERSON IN HERE.
REALLY? SO THAT'S
YOUR PLAY, BLACKMAIL?
DO WHAT YOU SAY,
OR YOU GET CAUGHT
IN HERE, TOO?
YOU'RE MY BROTHER, JOHN.
WHAT HAPPENS TO YOU
HAPPENS TO ME.
OLIVER...
I KILLED MY BROTHER.
I WENT TO THE ARMY
TO CHANGE,
AND I HAVEN'T CHANGED.
I KNOW, ALL RIGHT,
AND I KNOW THAT YOU
THINK THIS IS YOUR
PENANCE FOR THAT.
OLIVER, IT'S NOT
JUST THAT.
I TRUSTED ANDY.
EVEN WHEN YOU TOLD
ME NOT TO, I TRUSTED HIM,
AND NOW LAUREL'S DEAD.
I NEED YOU,
THE TEAM NEEDS YOU,
THE CITY NEEDS YOU.
I'M NOT SAYING
YOU SHOULDN'T DO
YOUR PENANCE.
YOU PROBABLY SHOULD,
BUT DO IT
AS SPARTAN.
WHAT'S IN THE BOX?
IT'S AN ANTIMOLECULAR COMPOUND,
AND THEORETICALLY,
IT SHOULD EAT
THROUGH ANYTHING.
NOT GONNA ASK YOU
HOW YOU GOT YOUR
HANDS ON THIS.
HEY. YOU CAME
BACK FOR ME,
EVEN AGAINST MY WISHES.
I GUESS I HAVEN'T
CHANGED THAT
MUCH EITHER.
MAYBE THAT'S
WHAT I HAVE TO DO
MY PENANCE FOR.
THAT TOY OF YOURS
IS DEFINITELY
COMING IN HANDY.
PROJECT THAT LYLA'S
BEEN KEEPING AN EYE
ON FOR ARGUS.
SHOULD HAVE KNOWN
SHE'D BE HELPING OUT.
TELL JOHNNY HE CAN
THANK ME LATER.
YOU'VE GOT TO KEEP MOVING.
FOLLOW THE SUBLEVEL NORTH
200 METERS, THEN CLIMB UP.
[STATIC]
WHAT...WHAT IS IT?
COMM'S BEING JAMMED.
[ALARM BLARING]
ADRIAN: NO, NO, NO.
HEY. IS THERE
ANOTHER WAY OUT OF HERE?
MIND UNCUFFING ME
BEFORE THEY KILL YOU?
RORY: HEY.
ADRIAN: HEY. HEY.
IF THAT'S FOR
TAKING OUT THE WALL,
THE BLAST WILL
KILL US BEFORE
WE CAN GET OUT.
WE'RE IN TOO TIGHT.
-TRUST ME.
-YEAH, SAYS THE CREEPY-LOOKING...
WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU ANYWAYS?
I'M IN PLACE.
BLOW IT.
SORRY WE BLEW UP
YOUR BUILDING.
COME ON!
WE'RE GOING UP.
THEN WHAT?
[GUNSHOTS]
WHICH WAY,
OVERWATCH?
TAKE A RIGHT
AT THE END OF THAT HALLWAY.
IT SHOULD BE
A FIRE EXIT.
IF YOU GO THROUGH THERE,
YOU'RE HOME FREE EASY.
NOT SO EASY.
RAGS, COVER ME.
GO! GO, GO!
UNH!
GET HIM UP.
COME ON.
[GROANS]
I PROBABLY SHOULD
JUST SHOOT YOU,
BUT...
BUT YOU'VE EARNED
A LITTLE SUFFERING.
GET HIM TO SAFETY.
-BUT...
-GO!
IT'S OK.
HEY. DON'T KILL HIM.
HE MAY HAVE
HIS USES.
WE'VE GOT TO GO BACK
FOR WILD DOG.
COPY. OVERWATCH,
MR. TERRIFIC
IS HURT.
WE COULD USE
SOME HELP.
INBOUND. HOLD ON.
GET IN!
WHERE'S
THE WILD DOG KID?
STILL INSIDE,
FIGHTING CHURCH.
WE'VE GOT TO GO
BACK FOR HIM.
NO. UNLESS YOU ALL
WANT TO DIE,
WE'VE GOT TO GO NOW, NOW!
WE CAN'T JUST
LEAVE HIM.
YOU HAVE TO. GO.
COME ON!
-HERE.
-WHAT'S THIS?
JUST PUT IT ON.
LET'S GO.
DIG, YOUR HARNESS.
YOU TWO, FREEZE!
DOWN ON THE GROUND!
LACE YOUR FINGERS
BEHIND YOUR HEAD!
DO IT NOW,
OR WE WILL SHOOT!
JOHN, DON'T MOVE.
THIS PLACE SHOULD KEEP YOU
OFF THE GRID
FOR THE TIME BEING.
UNTIL WE FIND
A PERMANENT SOLUTION.
HEY. FIRST THINGS FIRST.
CAN'T BELIEVE YOU
BROKE ME OUT
OF PRISON.
FOR BETTER OR WORSE,
JOHNNY.
TOLD YOU I WANTED
TO STAY.
AND I FIGURED
IF YOU WANTED TO MAKE
YOUR OWN DECISIONS
THEN YOU WOULDN'T
HAVEN'T GOTTEN MARRIED.
OK. HOW MAD WAS
FELICITY THAT YOU
WENT ALONG WITH THIS?
HOW DO YOU KNOW SHE
THOUGHT IT WAS A BAD IDEA?
I KNOW FELICITY.
[CELL PHONE VIBRATING]
WHAT'S WRONG?
I HAVE TO GO.
HEY.
WHEN YOU SAID YOU
HAVEN'T CHANGED...
DON'T.
DOBROYE UTRO.
HOW WAS FIRST NIGHT
IN RUSSIAN PRISON?
FRIEDKIN GAVE UP
THE DEAD DROP,
AND NOW HE'S DEAD.
MISSION ACCOMPLISHED.
YOUR BEING
SARCASM, YES?
THAT MAN WASN'T
A THREAT, ANATOLY.
HE DIDN'T DESERVE
TO DIE.
IN BRATVA,
THERE IS NO DEATH
WITHOUT PURPOSE.
IF FRIEDKIN LIVING,
HE IS WARNING KOVAR.
IF HE IS WARNING KOVAR,
HIS INFORMATION
NOT SO GOOD.
VY PONIMAYETE?
MAYBE YOU COULD HAVE
EXPLAINED THAT TO ME
BEFORE YOU SENT ME
IN THERE.
I ALMOST DIDN'T
KILL HIM.
BUT YOU DID. WHY?
BECAUSE YOU
TOLD ME TO.
YOU TRUST US.
NOW WE TRUST YOU.
THIRD TEST OVER.
YOU GET IT?
YOU ARE BRATVA NOW, FAMILY.
LAST HANDFUL OF HONEST COPS
IN THIS CITY,
AND CHURCH NEARLY
TOOK THEM OUT
ALONG WITH ME.
WE'RE JUST GLAD
YOU'RE ALL RIGHT.
I'VE GOT TO BE
THINKING THIS IS
A PR NIGHTMARE,
SOMETHING LIKE THIS
GOING DOWN
AND THE MAYOR'S MIA.
LOOK. HE CALLED IN
THIS MORNING.
HIS HEALTH PROBLEMS
ARE ALMOST OVER.
THAT'S GOOD NEWS.
UM, WE'RE...WE'RE HEARING
THAT ONE OF THE, UH,
VIGILANTES
WHO WAS PART
OF THE RESCUE,
THAT HE DIDN'T
MAKE IT OUT.
UM, ANY WORD
ON HIM?
CSU HASN'T FOUND
A BODY, SO...
SO CHURCH HAS HIM.
I SPENT MOST
OF MY LIFE THINKING
THAT MEN IN MASKS
WERE ONLY CAPABLE
OF DOING
HORRIBLE THINGS.
I MAY HAVE TO
REEVALUATE THAT.
LET ME KNOW
WHEN QUEEN GETS IN.
WILL DO.
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
I MEAN, I BARELY
KNEW THE KID, THEA.
BUT THAT DOESN'T
MAKE IT STING
ANY LESS.
WELL, YEAH,
SURE IT DOES.
THE YEAR I'VE HAD,
THIS IS...THIS IS EASY.
YEAH. I MEAN, COLD
AS THAT SOUNDS.
LOOK. I KNOW WHY
YOU'RE ASKING, OK,
AND I'M...I'M FINE.
OK.
I MEAN, I'M...I'M...
I'M JUST SAYING
IF THINGS EVER GET
LESS EASY,
YOU KNOW I'M HERE
FOR YOU, RIGHT?
NOTED...
AND APPRECIATED.
OK.
WHAT IS THE POINT OF HAVING
KEYHOLE SATELLITE IMAGERY
IF YOU CAN'T USE IT
TO FIND ANYBODY?
I FEEL LIKE
I DON'T UNDERSTAND
HALF THE SENTENCES
YOU SAY.
WHAT I'M SAYING IS
IS THAT NO MATTER
HOW HARD I TRY
I CANNOT FIND RENE
ANYWHERE.
AND I WAS THE ONE
WHO TOLD YOU GUYS
TO LEAVE HIM BEHIND.
SOUNDS LIKE ANOTHER
IMPOSSIBLE DECISION.
DOES THAT MEAN I'M
SUPPOSED TO GET BETTER
AT MAKING THEM?
I'M SAYING
YOU WERE RIGHT.
IF WE'RE GONNA
DO THIS,
WE CAN'T LET GUILT
SWALLOW US UP.
I'LL KEEP YOU
FROM DOING IT
IF YOU PROMISE
THE SAME FOR ME.
DEAL.
CURTIS: OW!
OW! OW!
EVELYN:
SO "OW" THEN?
THINGS HAVE REALLY
FALLEN APART
WITHOUT OLIVER,
HAVEN'T THEY?
IT'S A GOOD THING
I'M BACK THEN.
WAS HE WAITING
FOR AN ENTRANCE LINE?
NOPE. HE'S JUST
THAT COOL.
I GOT YOUR TEXT.
HAVE WE FOUND RENE?
YOU GET JOHN?
YEAH. HE'S FINE.
HE'S HOLED UP
AT HIVE.
I COULDN'T WRITE
HIM OFF,
AND WE ARE NOT GONNA
WRITE OFF RENE.
WE'RE GONNA
FIND HIM,
BRING HIM BACK...
WHEREVER HE IS.
CHURCH:
AH. WAKEY, WAKEY.
YOW! YOW!
HEH HEH HEH.
HEY.
MAN, IT'S BEEN
A LONG TIME
SINCE I'VE BEEN TAGGED
LIKE THIS.
RESPECT.
OH, MY PLEASURE,
BUT I PROMISE YOU
IF YOU UNTIE ME
I'LL SHOW YOU
A HELL OF A LOT MORE
THAN RESPECT.
OOH, MAN,
YOU GOT SPIRIT,
AND I AM DULY IMPRESSED,
BUT I'M GONNA BREAK
THAT SPIRIT.
I'M GONNA BREAK
YOUR SOUL,
AND WHEN WE'RE FINISHED,
ASSUMING THAT YOU'RE
STILL ALIVE...
NOW I WOULDN'T BET
NO MONEY ON THAT, THOUGH...
THERE'S GONNA BE
VERY LITTLE OF YOU LEFT
FOR THE GREEN ARROW
TO WORK WITH.
LIGHT HIM UP.
[SCREAMING]