My name is Oliver Queen.
After 6 years of being a vigilante,
the only way to achieve my goal
and save my city was to confess
to being the Green Arrow.
Now my family and friends must
carry on my mission without me.
I am no longer a hero.
I am inmate 4587.
Previously on "Arrow"...
The bureau's going to stay in Star City
until Diaz is brought in,
but only if Oliver will turn himself in.
Diaz found Felicity. Your wife is dead.
You're okay.
I can't let what happened to
William and I happen again.
I have to fight back.
I know I want to keep
fighting for this city.
I know you've been in some
hot water here at A.R.G.U.S.,
burning so many of their
resources going after Diaz.
This place must be
very important for you.
It's not the place.
It's the person I'm
hoping to find there.
My father...
Is Oliver Queen.
William?
Vacation's over, 4587.
You're lucky you only
got two days in the hole
after what you pulled.
Apparently, there are
still people in here
who believe that you're a hero.
But we know better...
Don't we?
I asked you a question, inmate.
You don't know anything about me.
Sure I do.
I grew up with kids just like you...
Entitled, rich.
Thought the law didn't apply to them.
But look at you now... a criminal
just like every other bastard in here.
My wife and son were attacked.
I'll do anything to protect them.
Oh, you're back! Oh, man.
The way you beat the crap
out of that grim reaper guy
was awesome.
That face looked like hamburger meat.
Where is he?
He's gone.
The warden found out that he
attacked you in the shower,
got sent down to level two.
Which is worse than a death sentence.
He's my only lead on Diaz.
Don't worry. He doesn't know anything.
He just got a nice pay day.
Right. Why do you know that?
I asked around.
You should be keeping to yourself.
Asking questions in here
is going to get you killed.
Not when you're asking
for the Green Arrow.
Everyone saw what you did,
and they're all afraid of you.
'Cause we're friends,
now they're afraid of me.
All right. If that prisoner
wasn't behind the attack,
then who hired him?
That scary bald guy who attacked me.
Right. Brick.
So what's our plan?
Beat him up? Torture him for info?
Nope. We do it my way.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
A little more.
Do you want me to put
a straw in the bottle?
Ah, ah! Don't judge me.
A.R.G.U.S. is my
designated driver tonight.
Indeed they are, and every night
until we take Diaz off the board.
That psycho has been M.I.A. 5 months,
and then he goes after
Oliver and Felicity.
Why now?
Well, whatever he's up to,
now we know it's personal.
Which is exactly why I put Laurel
on protective detail.
She's got to be high on his hit list.
Not that I don't enjoy talking about
all the ways that Diaz can get to us.
Anybody have any idea
how we can get to him?
Well, I've been working on that.
What the heck is that thing?
I call it my Digi murder board.
I mean, I can probably work on the name,
but it analyzes all the
data we've collected on Diaz.
Plus, it searches for additional Intel.
And then it makes
predictive suggestions.
So it's like a brain that
only thinks about Diaz.
- Mm.
- Gross...
- Yeah.
- But also cool.
That's an electronic jammer.
What is Diaz doing with tech like that?
Well, it's the same tech he used to bust
my A.R.G.U.S. security
system when he attacked me.
Well, a model that sophisticated
is very hard to get.
Diaz has new friends.
Which is why I wrote algorithms to track
all his known associates,
like Cyrus Broderick
and the Longbow Hunters.
Well, this is all great work, Felicity.
Just remember you don't have
to do it all alone, okay?
We've all got your
back, whatever you need.
I know. Thank you. I... I appreciate it.
But what I need is for Diaz to go down.
There is somebody else
who might be able to help.
If you say, "The New Green Arrow,"
I'm gonna punch you in the face.
You did say, whatever she needed.
There is only one Green
Arrow, and he's in prison.
Okay, enough squabbling
and murder boarding.
Let's toast.
To friends reunited, to being back home,
and to bringing that son
of a bitch Diaz to justice.
- I'll drink to that.
- Hear! Hear!
- Yeah.
- Cheers.
Felicity and Oliver, they really...
They really just left you?
Pretty much.
And my ex-boyfriend wonders why
I have commitment issues.
I'm sorry. That's awful.
Yeah, he was a real jerk.
No. I was talking about
Oliver and Felicity.
Yeah, well, I survived.
So what about you?
What's your excuse for being here?
Where'd you get that?
Oh, um, Felicity gave it to me.
She said it was a
symbol of reconnection.
I thought it was B.S.,
but then, uh, 3 weeks
ago, it started to beep.
I opened it up...
And I found this.
They're GPS coordinates for this island.
Wait. Why would Felicity
send you to Lian Yu?
Cruel joke?
You know, the last time
I was on this island...
Was the day my mother died.
I still have nightmares about it.
But I came anyway.
Well, trust me, looking for answers is
only gonna cause you pain.
So what I would do is I would take that,
and I'd throw it right
there in the ocean
and never look back.
Hi there.
I'm looking for Global Solutions.
Fourth floor, ma'am. Everything
above that's restricted.
Tom, can I ask you a favor?
I have an interview with GS,
and I somehow ended
up here without a pen,
and I really need that job.
Of course.
Pardon me.
I am so sorry.
Excuse me, ma'am.
Who the hell are you?
So much for not making a mess.
I got bored.
Number 326.
Where the hell is she?
You or me?
Be my guest.
That never gets old.
We need to get out of
here. Did you get it?
Thanks a million, Tom.
No problem. How was the interview?
I think I nailed it.
Shortly after 0900 this morning,
a break-in was reported
at one of our off-site facilities.
Only one item was
stolen... Prototype B-24.
It's an ultra...
High-density renewable battery?
I didn't even know those existed yet.
One super battery has
enough juice to power a town.
We were reusing them to help refugees.
What kind of jerk gets
in the way of that?
Well, maybe you would know if
John let you in on his briefing.
Well, I do not have a high
enough security clearance.
Plus, I heard Deputy Director
Bell's gonna be in there,
and he scares me.
You know, I could just get
us the unredacted report.
Uh, no. I actually like my job, okay?
So whoever did this knows their tech.
They used an electronic
jammer to get past security.
Yes! The same tech that Diaz
used to breach my safe house
in hope Springs. That is
not a coincidence, Curtis.
Can you tell what type of
weapons they used in the heist?
High-tech shield, nano-powered
darts, sonic manipulator.
These are super impressive weapons.
Not just impressive. They're specific.
This was definitely...
The Longbow Hunters.
According to our
source, Anatoly Knyazev,
they were hired by our
old friend, Ricardo Diaz.
These assassins are extremely dangerous,
and we need to find
them and shut them down.
You have your assignments.
Deputy Director Bell,
I'm surprised to see
you made time for this briefing.
I wanted to check in,
given the reappearance of Ricardo Diaz.
I know you have a personal connection.
Well, I appreciate the concerns.
I assure you my priorities
are in the right place.
Diaz is a son of a bitch,
but A.R.G.U.S. isn't chartered
for criminal investigations.
That's why recovering
that tech is the objective.
Understood?
Yes, sir.
I know it's the Longbow Hunters.
You have to let me in on this operation.
A.R.G.U.S. is handling it.
Told you! Ahem.
The longbow hunters are a
direct connection to Diaz.
They are the best lead
we've had on him in months.
You know it, John. John,
I need to do something.
I know, and I'm sorry, but
A.R.G.U.S. has its protocols.
- John...
- We will keep you updated.
Felicity, just trust me.
Laurel...
We need to talk.
If this is about the Conway case,
I already told Anastas I need more time.
That is not why I'm
here, and you know it.
Aw. Did you miss me? That's so sweet.
Laurel, you ditched your
protective detail again.
Perhaps you should get your
facts straight, Captain.
Your officers had a medical emergency.
Food poisoning, I think it was.
Food poisoning does not
cause hearing loss or vertigo.
You know what does? A sonic wave.
Ooh, that sounds serious.
This isn't a joke, Laurel.
You know, I just heard from A.R.G.U.S.
the Longbow Hunters are in Star City.
Diaz won't be far behind.
Matter of fact, for all we know,
he could already be in town.
Now, I don't really
care if Diaz kills you,
but I do care if he kills the D.A.
Touching.
Diaz kidnapped you.
He killed Quentin, who everyone
believes is your father.
Such a joke.
Hey, I cared about him.
Then let my officers protect you.
It's what he would have wanted.
I can take care of myself.
Fine.
Isn't baby-sitting
a little bit below your pay grade?
Way below, but the SCPD
is going to keep you safe,
whether you want us to or not.
Okay, fine, whatever. Suit yourself.
You might as well make yourself useful
while you're here and
go get me a coffee.
Two sugars, no cream.
That's never happening.
Ricardo Diaz.
That seat's taken.
You're gonna tell me where to find him.
Hey, you sure you want to do that?
I still haven't gotten
a chance to thank you
for sending me to the hole.
I guess you don't know your place here.
You may have gotten your fight back,
but we're still at the
top of this food chain.
It's okay, boys.
I got this.
Diaz? Don't ring any bells.
You hired those prisoners
to attack me in the shower
for Diaz.
So why don't you tell
me how I can find him?
You know what your problem is, Queen?
You've forgotten where you are.
This is prison,
and you're playing by the wrong rules.
I'm not in any mood for games, Brick.
What I'm saying is
if you want to be a mate of mine,
you got to prove yourself
worthy of my friendship.
What do you want?
I want him gone.
Why?
That is no concern of yours.
You just take care of that guard,
and I'll tell you
anything you want to know.
Everybody wins.
Fine.
Queen.
If you say anything to anybody,
the deal is off.
Please tell me you are
not hacking A.R.G.U.S.
from inside A.R.G.U.S.
Of course I'm not hacking
A.R.G.U.S. from inside A.R.G.U.S.
I'm hacking Interpol
from inside A.R.G.U.S.
That's not much better,
and that will still get me fired.
Felicity, I really like this job.
Look, I know how badly
you want to get Diaz,
but we need to listen to John.
A.R.G.U.S. is more than
capable of doing the job
while we wait and eat some snacks.
I'm not waiting for A.R.G.U.S.
That's exactly what Oliver wanted
me to do, and Diaz found me anyway.
Okay, well, maybe we can
find the Longbow Hunters
without committing espionage?
Can I please... Just for one second.
Okay. Now, we know they
have a super battery.
Chances are they've tried
to test it. And doing that...
Would require an
incredible amount of energy,
which would, in turn,
create a power surge.
Which we can pinpoint and then
trace to a specific location.
Ohh! I miss this. I
miss working with you.
I miss hacking Star City's power grid.
- I mean, it just feels right.
- Bingo! A huge voltage spike
in a warehouse in Pennytown
about an hour ago.
- Great.
- You actually want to go there?
Of course you do. I really
should've thought this through.
Look, I'm not gonna engage
with the Longbow Hunters.
I'm just gonna grab one of
your T-spheres and use it
to track them back to Diaz. No big.
Very big. You know what?
I'm coming to back you up.
And who's gonna back you up?
I might know a guy.
Back in town a week,
and you're already
sneaking out of A.R.G.U.S.
behind Papa Diggs' back?
I'm so proud.
Thanks, man.
Don't encourage her, okay?
She's already moved on to espionage.
Thanks for coming out, Rene.
I know it's not the
best time to be Wild Dog,
what with the whole 25-to-life thing.
Wild Dog's not here.
You see a hockey mask?
Besides, this is exactly
what we should've been doing
in the first place instead of
waiting for Diaz to come to us.
The scan's complete.
The Longbow Hunters aren't home.
Damn. So we can't
follow them back to Diaz
if they're not here to be followed.
We can go inside.
Curtis, relax.
I just want to put a couple
trackers on a few things.
Five minutes, tops.
Are you familiar with the expression
"famous last words"?
Grab your balls, Curtis. We're going in.
They're not balls. They're T-spheres.
Feels weird doing this without
Oliver and without a headset.
I'm more worried about you holding in
so many snarky Overwatch comments.
Guys, look at this.
Anything worth putting a tracker on is
definitely behind that door.
Damn. I should've
included a lock pick module
in my last T-sphere update.
Never bring a T-sphere to a gun fight.
Jackpot. Let's plant the tracker.
You work on that. I'll work on this.
Oh, frak. I think I just
triggered a system self-destruct.
Guys, we got a bigger problem.
We're not alone.
Stay behind me.
I think I get the whole
"famous last words" thing now.
- Freeze!
- Don't shoot! Don't shoot! John!
John, it's us.
You three realize you've just
compromised an active investigation?
Yes. But in my defense, we
wouldn't have had to do any of this
if you had just included
me in the first place.
We wanted it as much as you did, Digg.
Rene, before you say another word,
realize that A.R.G.U.S. is quite
aware of your immunity agreement.
Just because you're not wearing a mask
doesn't mean you're
not breaking the law.
You wouldn't really turn him in, though.
But would you?
Felicity, A.R.G.U.S. has its rules.
What the hell were you thinking?
I was thinking about catching Diaz.
There are bigger things at stake here.
Like what, batteries?
It's not just a battery,
Rene. It's a weapon.
Say what, now?
A.R.G.U.S. developed an adapter...
An adapter that calibrates
the charge to power
a directed energy weapon.
- It's enough to flatten a whole city.
- God.
How were we supposed to know that?
You didn't need to know that, Curtis.
Please just pack up the
laptop. Restore the data.
We need to find out what the
Longbow Hunters are doing next.
That could take forever.
The security virus wiped the hard drive.
You have a better idea, Felicity?
Your little stunt just
blew our best possible lead.
This is prison.
There's tons of guys
in here that would be
happy to handle Yorke,
if you know what I mean.
Yorke's a hardass, but
he doesn't deserve to die.
Just...
I need to find his pressure point.
WWGAD?
What?
What would Green Arrow do?
Oh. I...
He'd have Overwatch gather information.
What's an overwatch?
We need a computer.
Once we get inside, we'll have two
minutes before the guards miss us.
You up for this?
Yeah. Hell, yeah. It's my
first Green Arrow mission.
What the hell?
No one moves! Everyone,
stay right where you are.
Control, we need
backup near the showers!
Does this thing even have the Internet?
We'll soon find out.
Even if it does, they don't
let felons surf the web.
My wife taught me a
thing or two. Sit tight.
And we got him.
Ok, so what are we looking for?
Anything that will give me leverage.
Peter Yorke was born in 1978.
He joins the army at 19, serves 8 years.
Commendations, injured in line of duty.
Started working at Slabside,
and he's been here ever since.
He's been here for 12 years.
No wonder he's such a jerk.
He's got no complaints.
He's got no disciplinary record.
He's a jerk, but he's a law-abiding jerk.
No one that's clean.
There's got to be something.
Look at that.
He's got a wife and a kid.
I bet a guy like that would do
just about anything to
keep his family safe.
All right! Back in line!
We have to go.
You're still here.
Stubbornness must be hereditary.
I'm a guy who spent over a
billion dollars trying to develop
affordable magnetic levitation.
I don't give up so easily.
Wow. You've done really
good for yourself,
considering everything that's happened.
You know, when I first met you,
you were with my Aunt Thea.
The two of you were leaving
somewhere together and...
You're not gonna get anywhere
with me by dredging up the past.
I came here to forget about all of that.
When Felicity gave me this,
she told me it was about reconnecting.
And it led me here to you.
That can't be a coincidence.
I know exactly where this is.
Come on.
Hey, where's the D.A.?
She said she needed some air.
Damn it.
I'm still a ways off
from repairing the laptop,
but I have compiled a list of known
directed energy weapons,
which could be powered
using a modified battery.
This list has too many potential targets
for this agency to reasonably protect.
We need whatever's on that laptop.
You blocked my computer?
What the hell, John?
That's my cue. Heh.
Felicity, we can no longer risk you
interfering with this mission.
This is not Team Arrow.
This is an A.R.G.U.S. operation.
Please. I'm asking for your patience.
I'm out of patience, John.
You have your life,
your home, your family,
but I lost everything,
and bringing down Diaz
is the only way for
me to get it all back.
Felicity, you can't get it back.
Your old life... Our
old life... is over.
And taking down Diaz
will not change that.
Oliver's gone,
and he is not coming
back for a very long time.
I need you to accept that.
I can't...
And I won't.
And I can't believe that you do.
The old John would've done anything
to bring down that monster,
and you're... you're here.
And you wouldn't even take
up the Green Arrow mantle...
The only thing that
Oliver asked you to do.
You've moved on with your life.
The last 6 years actually
meant something to me.
So I am going to stop
Diaz, whatever it takes,
even if I have to do it alone.
You know, just because
Yorke doesn't dirty,
doesn't mean we can't get him fired.
Blackmail's pretty much a prerequisite
for getting in this place.
I'm not about to ruin an
innocent man's life, okay?
Not the Green Arrow way. Noted.
I'm starting to think
you've lost interest in
my information, queen.
Yorke's clean.
There are other ways of
getting rid of somebody,
a more permanent way.
That's not how I do things.
That's not how you do things out there.
You asked me to take care of Yorke.
You didn't say how.
Well, let me make this clear.
You use that to get rid of Yorke,
or I will.
Cell check!
Cell check time.
You're up, 4587.
You know the drill.
Yorke, you need to listen to me.
No chitchat, inmate.
Someone in here wants you dead.
News flash: everyone
in here wants me dead.
Yorke, I don't care if
you quit or transfer,
but whatever you do,
you need to do it today.
Do you understand?
I have no idea what kind
of game you're playing,
but if you don't knock it off, I promise
you'll regret it.
I'm not playing a game.
I am trying to help you.
I don't need your help, inmate.
I just want to do the right thing.
The right thing?
Is that what you were doing,
running around in that costume?
You turned the law into a joke.
The Green Arrow's very existence
invited criminals into your city.
You think you're some kind of hero.
Have you ever stopped to think
maybe all you've done
is make things worse?
Hey. Can we talk?
Not unless it's about Diaz.
Felicity, I want you
to know I understand
why you're angry at me.
But I have not forgotten
Oliver or this team
or you.
But I need you to hear why I chose
not to become the Green Arrow.
Felicity, I watched as
Oliver, you, and William
lost everything important in life
because of that hood.
And I wanted to.
I wanted to put it on
because Oliver asked me to,
but I couldn't.
The truth is...
I saw what the hood did
to you and your family.
And I couldn't do it to mine.
Maybe that was selfish,
but I just couldn't make
that kind of sacrifice,
and I couldn't ask that of Lyla or J.J.
It's not selfish.
I'd like to think that I'm
honoring Oliver's mission
without putting that suit on.
I respect that you
want to keep fighting.
Oliver turned himself in
so the FBI would help us take down Diaz.
I may not agree with the decision,
but as long as Diaz is still out there,
Oliver's sacrifice will
have been for nothing.
Sorry to interrupt. John,
you have to see this.
I was finally able to pull the
data from that damaged hard drive.
Look what I found: Train schematics.
Let me guess.
One of these directed
energy weapons on your list
is being transported by train.
Yup. It's being shipped out of Star City
for testing tonight.
We can't let the Longbow Hunters
get their hands on that weapon.
John, wait. No one knows the
Longbow Hunters better that I do.
Felicity, if you're gonna help, you
got to do this the A.R.G.U.S. way. Deal?
Deal.
Hey.
What are you doing here?
You know, I should be
asking you the same question.
How did you find me?
Well, I am a cop, Laurel.
What is this place?
Diaz bought it right after
he joined the quadrant.
Planning on renovating,
he wanted to turn it
into his own castle.
And you think he's in there?
Well, I don't think he's
welcome at the Star City Plaza.
All right. Fine.
Call it in, then.
No, no. This is my fight.
Oh. Heh. Right.
This is what you've been
planning all along, isn't it?
This is why you've been
refusing protection.
Because you're going to kill him.
Let's hope so.
If Diaz is in this building,
the SCPD is going to be
the one to take him down,
and we're going to do it the right way.
I'm not interested in
doing things the right way.
That monster killed Quentin.
I want to see him in hell,
and I want to be the one
that sends him there myself.
You know, I knew you were faking
it this whole time, Laurel.
Becoming the D.A. and all your
B.S. talk about the rule of law.
You know, deep down,
you are still the same lying murderer
who killed the man I loved.
I'm not that person anymore.
But someone has to get
justice for Quentin,
and you know it.
So don't you dare try and stop me.
Alpha team's in position.
Sitrep?
The train is right on schedule.
60 seconds till the first
car reaches your position.
Copy that.
Overwatch, you ready for this?
Oh, I've been ready for 5 months.
Overwatch, I'm on the train.
Copy that.
I've logged into the train
control and management system.
I'm now inside the brain of the train.
Where's the weapon?
It's in the fourth car from the back.
- Any sign of our friends?
- Not yet.
You're coming up on the Bader tunnel.
We will have a snapshot from their
thermal imaging camera in about 30 seconds.
Hey. That way.
That'll be the engineer.
There. That'll be the Longbow
Hunters... Two of them, at least.
John, we got two bogies, both in
the baggage car in front of you.
Where's the other one?
Oh, my god. John, he's right above you.
Hold your fire!
Get to the weapon!
Hello there.
It's gas!
Get out of here! Go! Go! Go!
Oops. Guess it's locked.
Overwatch, I'm trapped!
Already on it. Hang on, John.
Diaz.
Diaz is there?
Felicity!
Sorry! On it. Got it.
You're almost there. The weapon
is two cars in front of you.
Go help the others!
I'll secure the weapon.
Are you ok?
Yeah, I think so.
How the hell did she do that?
I have no idea.
Diaz, freeze!
Hands up, slowly.
You miss me, John?
Yeah!
Hyah!
Uh!
I've got the battery.
Felicity, when I tell you,
I need you to uncouple that flatcar.
What? No.
We can't let Diaz escape.
We can't let him get ahold
of that weapon either!
Felicity, do it now!
I can't. He'll get away.
I thought I could do it, your way.
And then I saw Diaz.
There's no need to explain.
I just wanted to make sure you're okay.
I'm not.
I understand why you did what you did.
The world is a safer place
because Diaz doesn't have that weapon.
I was wrong before.
You may now be working
here at A.R.G.U.S.,
but you're still
honoring Oliver's mission.
I appreciate your saying that.
But I still can't rest until I know
that my family is safe...
Which means I need to work
with someone whose focus is
bringing down Diaz...
And that someone is not you.
I'm guessing that was your
last mission with A.R.G.U.S.
- Yeah.
- And probably with me, too.
I'm sorry, Curtis.
What are you gonna do?
Find help somewhere else.
I don't think you understand our deal.
It's a limited-time offer,
and it's just about to expire.
I understand.
I'm gonna take care of him.
Oliver told me what was
buried on this island.
When I got here,
I found the 4 graves
that he had mentioned,
but then...
Then I found this one
so, look, I can take care of
this on my own if you want.
Look, I would love to miss out
on staring into the face
of a desiccated corpse,
but I think it'll go quicker if I help.
I don't get it. It's my father's bow.
I can't even shoot an arrow.
Why would Felicity want me to have this?
I know why.
Wait. What the hell?
Grab your stuff. We're going back.
- Back? Back where?
- To Star City.
Laurel.
Isn't that supposed to be a doughnut?
So funny.
Can you give us a minute?
I just... uh, I wanted
to come by and thank you
for the backup.
Also, from now on, I will
be accepting protection
from the SCPD.
No more ditching, no more complaining.
Well, maybe a little complaining.
Well, uh, I appreciate that.
Anything else?
No. That's it.
Actually, that's not it.
I know that Quentin wasn't my father...
Not... not the father
that raised me anyway.
And... I guess I had just forgotten
what it felt like to have
someone who cared about me.
And losing him, it was the worst pain
that I've felt in a very long time.
And I can only imagine
how you must have felt
after Vinny's death.
Please don't.
Listen, I don't expect
you to forgive me...
But I have to tell you
that I am truly sorry
about killing Vinny.
And I hope one day,
you'll see that I am not that person.
Not anymore.
This Diaz guy seems
like a real nightmare,
but you sure this is a good idea?
My way's not working.
Do I have a choice?
Hey. Hey!
What's your problem?
I know you're not talking to me, inmate.
You've had it in for me since day one.
You need to shut your mouth
and get back.
Do your wife and son
know you're such a dick?
What did you just say?
It's Jenna and Noah, right?
You don't say their names.
Uh! Uh! Aah.
You... you stabbed me.
- What? I didn't stab you.
- Get away from him.
The video! That guard
stabbed me. He stabbed me!
I didn't... Dunbar, what are you doing?
I didn't touch him.
- Get him out of here.
- No! Wait. No! He's lying!
I didn't do anything!
Thank you for seeing
me on such short notice.
You made a deal with my husband.
And he's in prison because of it.
Now it's your turn to hold
up your side of the bargain.
We're gonna take down Ricardo Diaz...
Together.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --