My name is Oliver Queen.
After five years in hell,
I returned home with only one goal,
to save my city.
But my old approach wasn't enough.
I had to become someone else.
I had to become something else.
I had to become the Green Arrow.
Previously on Arrow...
You won't be able to stop him.
We need to trap him.
Dad?
"NOAH". We are the same, you and I.
You were wrong. lam nothing like you.
"JOHN". I had to put him down, Lyla.
He had reached for my gun.
- Alex. Where are we?
- Thea...
- No, I can't...
- Where are you going?
Rubicon. Designed to prevent any country,
even our own,
from firing a nuclear missile.
"LYLA". Darhk ripped it out.
Darhk would control
the world's nuclear stockpile.
Andy told me that "Genesis" was coming.
God wanted to give the world
a do-over so he destroyed it.
He destroyed it with a flood.
So, nuclear annihilation
is Darhk's flood,
what's he planning on building as his ark?
Russia, Markovia, Corto Maltese,
us, every NATO ally.
Rubicon has control
over all their nuclear systems.
You mean HIVE does.
I know it's a little late for this,
but whoever created an algorithm
that could override any country's
nuclear weapons really screwed up.
That would be Amanda Waller.
How much time do we have?
NW e“ f?
Oliver, I'm the director of ARGUS
and this goes way over my head.
This is executive-level
and this is Department of Defense.
Right. Right, right, right.
But how much time?
There's a startup sequence
before Darhk can actually launch a nuke.
We have just under 21 hours.
Yeah, you're gonna have to find a way
to interrupt that sequence.
Rubicon is a fail-safe
against nuclear Armageddon.
ARGUS designed it to be 100% un-hackable.
No, she can do it. She's the best.
Uh, actually, that would be my father.
As far as Rubicon's concerned.
It uses Fourier protocols.
Noah practically wrote the book on them.
The world is facing nuclear Armageddon.
My pride and my general dislike
for my father can take a backseat
for the next 20-plus hours.
Felicity, this isn't about pride.
Your father's a criminal.
He can't be trusted.
I'm not saying we should trust him,
I'm saying we need to.
Okay. He got out in Darhk'sjailbreak.
- How do we find him?
- I'm already running a search.
Can you try
and get in touch with Thea, too?
Please, we need her back here.
John, can I talk to you for a second?
- How you doing?
- Been better.
Well, I'm not going to pretend
to understand what you're going through...
Well, Oliver, you've been through this
with your mother,
which is why I can't quite understand
why you're putting the fate of the world
in the hands of another evil parent.
I'm not trusting Kuttler.
I trust Felicity,
and we should just let her do herjob.
Okay?
We have one of our own.
Yeah. Stopping Darhk.
His magic is powered by death.
So, if even one of those nukes hits...
He'll be unstoppable.
Okay, what's your plan?
Well, if he is planning
on harnessing all of this death,
he's gonna be at
something called a nexus chamber.
Basically, it's a collector of magic.
And here I thought earthquake machines
were as strange as it got.
Esrin Fortuna told me that
one of these chambers exists in Star City.
I'm betting it falls on a ley line.
What'd Vixen call them?
- "Wi-Fi for magic"?
- Yeah.
It's a big city, Oliver,
we've got 21 hours.
One step at a time.
We have to help them.
We're gonna help these people.
What are you looking for?
Well, Reiter and his men
found a way on the island.
There has to be a way off.
There's a plane.
East end of the island. It's far.
We'll make it.
- What's that?
- This may be a way to call for help.
Let's go.
Woof.
I know.
The predictability
was a terrible flaw in the design.
Predictability is your flaw, too.
Every time my life starts to suck,
you show up.
Leave us.
Is that hand a present
from your new best friend?
I'm not doing this for a prosthetic, Thea.
- I'm doing it to keep you safe.
- Keep me safe.
- Yes. Keep you safe.
- Yeah.
Like I said, predictable.
Only thing I don't get is,
how is brainwashing
some guy I really like
in your plan to keep me safe?
His conditioning wasn't my idea.
Ruvé Darhk wanted to assure
his compliance in the final phase.
Final phase of what?
Something called Genesis.
Darhk plans to burn the world
in a nuclear fire
while we are protected down here.
Then he and his followers
can rebuild.
Truth be told,
it's not dissimilar to the plan
I had for the Glades, once upon a time.
But on a much, much larger scale.
Let me guess.
You don't think that destroying
the entire world is completely insane.
The world is what's insane.
It is beyond saving.
It needs a do-over. A reset.
Look, once I realized
Darhk's plan was inevitable,
the math was simple...
Save yourself.
And my daughter.
Even if she doesn't want to be saved.
Look, I am way, way past the point
of telling you
that you are crazy.
I just want to see Alex,
just want to know he's okay.
And, look, I get it, I'm stuck here.
But I can be stuck here and compliant
or I can be a pain in your ass.
So take me to him.
Now.
Hey-
- Hey, hon.
- Hi.
What's up?
Um...
When I was at your place
this morning, I...
I found this.
What are you doing going through my stuff?
Snooping.
But this isn't any of your business,
Donna.
No, no, babe. it is my business, actually.
You getting suspended.
- It is, kind of.
- But, Donna...
Hey. What is this?
It's... It's...
It's an affidavit.
Pike said if I put my name to it,
then I can get my badge back.
It says you didn't know
that Laurel was the Black Canary.
I may not be in Mansa,
but I know how to read, sweetie.
I think it's "Mensa," actually.
You told me
that you knew what Laurel was doing.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, so?
This is a lie.
Yeah, but it's a complicated lie.
- Is it?
- Yeah.
Yeah.
'Cause, according to Pike,
lAB are willing to look the other way
about my working with Darhk,
'cause I was protecting Laurel.
Why would you have to protect her
if she was a superhero?
Yeah, exactly. Now you see?
I see that they're asking you to lie.
Sweetheart. Come on.
All I ever wanted was to be a cop.
Now, what's a small lie if it means
I can do some good for this city?
No.
No, that's just it.
There aren't any small lies, hon.
Take it from someone who had a child
with a man who was a liar.
I'm not Noah Kuttler.
I know, honey, and that's why I love you.
Okay?
I love you,
and that's why I have faith that
you're gonna do the right thing.
Gentlemen.
I've a little errand I need you to run.
A loose end
that needs tying up, not unlike...
Huh.
Do I detect some obstinacy, Mr. Brick?
I'm just used to giving the orders, Darhk.
Not taking them.
Not even as a little thank-you
for busting you out of Iron Heights?
Whatever happened to gratitude?
I'm here, ain't I?
And when the whole world is sitting
under a field of mushroom clouds,
you'll be glad that you are.
Now then, back to the errand.
Have either of you boys
heard of The Calculator?
There's no one here.
Found a deep-trunk fiber-optic hook-up
with polymorphic encryption.
Noah is there, trust me.
She's right. Look.
Whoever rigged that up
didn't want to be surprised.
I'm tracing the Bluetooth signal.
Head southwest.
Nope. He's not here.
- He has to be.
- He was.
Looks like he bolted,
and in a hurry.
Bolted from whom?
This was 20 minutes ago.
Looks like Kuttlerwasn't
the only one that left Iron Heights.
Those are Ghosts with him.
What does HIVE want with my father?
Okay-
Find the scrawny son of a bitch.
When you do, kill him.
Welcome to Tevat Noah,
your home in the new era.
Please proceed
to the registration building
to receive your residence assignments.
Sorry about that.
Wasn't easy finding my way down here.
You Ghosts are swell at keeping secrets,
but less swell at resisting torture.
So why don't you spare me the trouble
and tell me where I can find Damien Darhk?
You were right.
Kuttler's the only one
that can stop Rubicon.
That's why Darhk wanted him dead.
You all right?
Yeah. The word "conflicted" comes to mind.
Well, at least we know he got away.
With not much of a head start.
I hacked Kuttler's server
to see if there was anything in there
that could point us
to where he would run to,
and he cleared the cache
so I can't recover any files.
But there is a root directory
called Ravenspur.
- What's Ravenspur?
- Don't know.
Does sound familiar.
I just don't know why.
We're running out of time.
The whole world is, so yeah.
Meantime,
my ley line algorithm kicked back
a possible 20
on a magical clubhouse for Darhk.
We drove some of them off,
but Reiter's sending reinforcements.
- Reiter's dead.
- We heard him on the radio.
He's alive.
Map of the island in the pack.
- Get them to the plane.
- What about you?
I'm gonna find Reiter,
and I'm gonna end this.
Then I am staying, too.
Do you remember what you told me?
It takes a monster to kill a monster.
Now, get these people home.
Felicity just called.
She needs to see me about something.
Everything all right?
I don't know. It's Felicity, so...
You know, you never know.
Are you signing that thing?
Yeah, I was about to.
Hey, before you give me that dirty look,
you might want to read this thing.
- I already read it.
- Just read it, please.
Oh!
- It looks...
- Yeah, it's a little different now.
"Although I was against it at first,"
"I came to see
what Laurel was doing was vital"
"and important and good"
"as the Black Canary."
I gave it a little rewrite.
(Bab)',
lam so proud of you.
Laurel would be, too.
This is me signing my badge away.
No.
You don't know that.
All you can know for sure
is that you're doing the right thing.
Oh! Mr. Dennis.
Ms. Smoak.
You haven't returned my calls.
Yes. I am sorry. I've been busy.
So have I.
Running your company.
Do I need to remind you
of your responsibilities to Palmer Tech?
No, you don't.
But you're just gonna have to believe me
when I tell you that what is on my plate
right now is much more important.
- Hey!
- Hi. Um...
- Should I come back, or...
- No, no, no. Please stay.
- Ms. Smoak, the board...
- Can wait.
Whatever's so important,
I hope it's worth it.
Hi. I like your tie, it's very...
Good.
- Hi!
- Thank you for meeting me.
Of course, my baby girl.
My God.
Are you kidding? I'm always here for you,
as long as there's no bees around.
No bees.
Are you okay?
Does the word "Ravenspur"
mean anything to you?
If this has something to do
with your father, honey...
So it does? Thought I remembered
the two of you talking about it.
Notjust talk. It's a...
It's a cabin in Cypress Cove
we used to like to go to.
We'd, you know,
we'd nurse a bottle of wine,
- make love to Lionel Richie.
- Hmm.
- I was his penny lover.
You know, your father
could go all night...
Okay, that's enough. I don't...
You know what? Actually, I think
you were conceived in Ravenspur.
Please, make it stop. No, please.
Seriously, honey.
I want to be serious for a minute.
If this has anything
remotely to do with your father...
Don't worry. I have it handled.
I wouldn't be a Jewish mother
if I didn't worry.
Baby. What's that for?
With any luck,
you'll never have to find out.
There's nothing here.
What, did you think
he was gonna put up a sign?
I was thinking more along the lines
of Ghosts with automatic weapons.
Then we should've brought
our work clothes.
- Can I talk to you about something?
- Yeah.
I spoke to Lyla. She's worried about you.
Because you said that
you shot Andy in self-defense.
Oliver, I don't want to talk about this.
You've just never said anything
about self-defense to me, John.
Couldn't tell Lyla the truth
and have her look at me
the same way anymore.
Come on, you don't know that.
Oliver, you're the last person on earth
to lecture someone about lying
to the people they love.
I'm not lecturing.
I'm worried.
You're better than me at this,
and you're hurting worse
than I have ever seen you.
Don't compound that by lying to your wife.
The fact that I lied to Felicity
does not give me less credibility.
If anything, it should tell you
that I know what I'm talking about.
- Yeah?
- Noah's at a cabin in Cypress Cove.
We got him. We're on our way.
You're a hard man to find, Kuttler.
Come out now, we'll make it painless.
Make us work for it, we'll make it last.
I hate it when they run.
You make me chase you any more,
I'm going to put a bullet in you.
Isn't that the plan?
I'm willing to give you a sporting chance.
I heard about this game
when I was in prison, Mr. Brick.
You let me walk if I take you down.
Darhk said
you was a smart bloke.
So, what do you say?
It's the end of the world,
as I understand it.
Don't just stand there. Get in.
- I got him.
- Spartan, fall back!
Let's make this simple.
This isn't a reconciliation.
This isn't a reunion.
This is you helping me save the world.
And what makes you think I can?
Damien Darhk thinks you can.
That's why he sent last year's
greatest hits to take you down.
You're a smart man.
I'm assuming you know what Rubicon is.
And I'm assuming
it's under Mr. Darhk's control.
We have 12 hours to stop it.
That's it?
You seem surprised.
I was expecting a quid pro quo.
Felicity, I may be a terrible father...
_llMayll?
But I'm not a monster.
And terrible or not, I am your father.
As long as you live in it,
I have an interest in seeing
that this world doesn't end.
That said, I do need something.
Color me shocked.
I can't hack Rubicon with this setup.
Not in the time we have.
I'm going to need
the quantum subluminal processor
you developed at Palmer Tech.
How did you even know that we...
God help me
if you're using the end of days
to steal from my company again.
I'm an excellent multitasker,
but you can trust me this time.
- Ms. Smoak...
- Ah, Mr. Dennis. Wow.
You must be very desperate
for me to talk to the board
since you brought security to dragoon me.
These men are not here
to take you to the conference room.
They're here
to escort you out of the building.
Excuse me?
The board has grave concerns
about your plans
to basically give away
the bio-stimulant implant.
They wanted
to discuss the matter with you.
- And I will talk to them.
- It's too late for that.
They voted to terminate you,
effective immediately.
Wow.
Okay, well, I just need to grab something
and I will show myself out. Thank you.
Ah! I'm sorry,
but everything in this lab is proprietary.
We cannot allow you to leave
with company property.
Excuse me? You have to be kidding.
I'm very sorry.
I had hoped
that this would end differently.
All right, folks.
Please move in right on in here.
Have a great day.
Alex?
Hey, you.
You ran off like a crazy person.
Are you feeling better?
Do you know what's going on here?
Yeah, Ruvé told me.
- Isn't it fantastic?
- It is not fantastic.
It's the end of the world.
No, it's just the beginning of a new one.
I got into politics
to make a difference, right?
To make the world a better place,
and Ruvé has shown me
that the only way to do that
is to start over.
Just listen to me.
You are under the influence
of some type of drug right now,
and we need to get out of here.
You're just gonna have to trust me, okay?
Hey. He can trust you later.
Lonnie Machin is here.
He's killed five of Damien's men
that we know about.
Well, there's plenty of ways
I could respond to that,
but I'm going to go with, "Good."
He's hitting the CO2 scrubbers
hours before nuclear weapons
will render the atmosphere above us
unbreathable.
If the Ark's life-support fails,
we all suffocate.
Who's Lonnie Machin?
He's kind of an ex-boyfriend of Thea's.
Well, Damien told me
about your special connection to him.
I need you to help me put him
back in the box, or we're all dead.
You all right? Did you get it?
I got fired.
Before I could take the processor.
I can't even show my face in there.
- Maybe we should call in a bomb threat.
- What?
Just empty the place
or maybe plant an actual bomb.
Just a small one,
one that doesn't hurt anybody.
- But we have...
- All right. Maybe we should just go in.
It's too risky
to wear the gear in the daylight.
What about the elevator at the old lair?
Uh-uh. Mr. Dennis shut it down
after the Larvan attack.
So, John's right.
We'll go in and help you and your father
boost it from...
It's in Curtis' lab.
You want me
to help my father steal from me?
Well, it's not exactly yours anymore,
is it?
Nope. Guess not.
Door is unlocked.
Give me a count of three
and then come on in.
Copy that.
I love all this subterfuge.
Might our guardian angel
be the Green Arrow?
This was a line item on the budget list,
and it's still not fixed.
And they have the gall to fire me?
This is fun, working together.
Let's make this clear.
This is not
a father-daughter bonding exercise.
Felicity, we have personnel
walking the floor.
Just go on my signal.
Copy that.
Look, I know I've done
what appears to be some terrible things...
You tried to steal from me.
Are we not stealing from you now?
No. A, it's not my company anymore,
and, B, we're trying to save the world.
"JOHN". Hey, didn't I say go on my signal?
Okay, now.
I'm good at solving binary problems,
but matters of the heart...
Are not your forte.
And stealing a processor
to save the end of the world
is not the right time
for this conversation.
On some level, I've always told myself
I just didn't know
how to be a father or a husband...
And for a smart guy,
you don't seem to understand
the concept of "not the right time."
I don't know
why I tried to steal your company's tech.
Habit, I suppose.
Or something deeper.
Ah! The son of a bitch.
I've been fired for, like, 45 minutes,
and he's already locked me out.
You have an electromagnetic wave generator
and a battery tender?
To force a restart.
Yes.
There it is.
Open sesame.
That's it.
Guys, I've got incoming.
Northeast stairwell.
On it.
It's under a sub-lock.
It won't eject.
That never happens unless...
That happens.
We can't leave without the processor.
We can if we clone it.
Your sniffer device.
We can copy
the processor's operating code wirelessly.
More movement.
Felicity, you must have tripped something
because I have security
coming to the lab right now.
- We're running out of time.
- The device isn't finished.
- Come on.
- It's almost there.
Come on.
Felicity, you have to get out of there.
Security's inbound.
The R and D lab is secure.
I heard you needed a lift.
- You're the one who arrested me.
- He's not doing that now.
- You get it?
- No.
How bad is it?
Kuttler was able to clone
90% of the processor.
He may be able to extrapolate
the remaining 10%
to build us a workable processor.
I'm gathering parts for him to work with.
But we're still gonna need to upload
the override codes
to every nuke silo individually.
- Can you do that?
- Only from a server farm.
Mr. Queen.
My men are searching the woods
for my property.
But you chose not to die with them.
I killed a few of the stragglers.
My power has grown beyond your imagining.
Let me show you.
Valiant effort, Mr. Queen.
But still only mortal.
The primary scrubber's in here.
I'm betting Machin is, too.
Don't I get something to fight him with?
I don't think I can trust you
with a weapon for some reason.
You're just gonna have to make do
with Krav Maga, I'm afraid.
Welcome to Tevat Noah,
your home in the new era.
Ah, the irony.
All Darhk's parasites living underground,
breathing the waste product of sludge.
What happens if I turn this dial?
Well, if you're not gonna tell me,
I'm just gonna have to see for myself.
Step away from that.
Run along, little girl.
I'm a tad busy at the moment
trying to kill everyone here.
I'm not a little girl, Lonnie.
Remember me?
My name is Thea Queen.
I'm the one that gave you that face.
Mommy.
I didn't recognize you
without the red leather.
Whatever are you doing here?
Look, I get it, you're mad at Darhk
because he screwed you over,
and now you're trying to get payback.
I'm not going to stop you, okay?
If anything, I'm gonna help you.
But there are innocent people here,
people that have been brainwashed,
and they don't deserve to die.
Lonnie, don't do this.
I will help you take down Darhk, okay?
We can do this together.
You just need to get out of here.
The hell did you do that for? I had him.
No, you didn't. Explosive charges.
He was going to blow the scrubber
no matter what you said.
- Can you disarm it?
- We'll soon find out.
Clear.
I'm going to need the sub node
taken offline.
- Okay, I can do that.
- I'll cover him.
I'll take care of him.
Get to work.
Nice to meet you.
My daughter certainly has
some very impressive friends.
How long is this gonna take?
Ideally, less than it takes Mr. Darhk
to nuke the world.
I'm not the man
my daughter thinks, you know.
Don't tell me. Tell her.
I've tried.
I've tried explaining that
there are two sides to me,
the father and the hacker.
She sees only the criminal.
I mention this because you strike me
as someone with experience
leading a dual life.
Any insights you'd care to share?
Yeah. n doesn't work.
You leading a dual life
is why you lost her.
You sound like you're talking
from some personal experience.
What's that?
Felicity's taken the sub node offline
and we've developed a new problem.
- What?
- Tapeworm in the Rubicon code.
An anti-hack failsafe
courtesy of your friends in HIVE.
Well, can you override it?
I just did.
But not before the tapeworm transmitted
this terminal's location.
- I figure we have about 90 seconds.
- Until what?
Until HIVE rains
all manner of hell down on us.
What happened?
HIVE has our position.
We have maybe a minute before they arrive.
They're working on shutting me down,
but I know a few tricks.
This'll go twice as fast with two of us.
We'll hold them off as long as we can.
Establish a perimeter. Shoot to kill.
I don't need to tell you
what's riding on this.
POTUS and SecDef have taken us
to DEFCON 2.
- Just 2? They're optimistic.
- They don't want to cause a panic.
The President asked me
if the fate of the world is resting
in the hands of an IT girl, a criminal
and two guys in Halloween costumes.
They're not Halloween costumes.
Get the idol!
We got to go.
What about Reiter?
He can't do anything without the idol.
Come on!
If this is the end of the world,
I don't mind going out like this.
Oh, don't you ever stop?
Not when it comes to my daughter. No.
Alex?
Everything's fine.
We took out all the explosives.
Alex? Alex. Oh, God, are you...
Fine? Okay? Hunky-dory?
Believe me, there's nothing hunky-dory
about screwing up someone's plan
for vengeance a second time.
Which means I've got to wait
for Mr. Darhk to arrive.
Go with Plan B.
It's left me with some time to kill.
Soto speak.
- Okay, Alex, come on...
- Relax.
He's fine. Just taking a little nap.
What is it with you?
Why are you always
at the mercy of some guy?
You can make your own decisions, Thea.
You're not a pawn,
you're a queen.
Get it?
Yeah. Yeah, I get it.
Here they come.
That's a lot of firepower...
We don't need to beat them.
We just need to buy Felicity
and her father enough time.
Thea?
Alex, get out of here.
Get away from him.
I'm liberating you, Mommy.
You don't need another man
clouding your mind.
Alex, run!
No.
Alex.
I'm sorry.
Think I got an algorithm
down to 300 lines for the uplink.
Have you tried to break
the JSI encryption?
- That way you can directly bypass the PAL.
- Yeah, you're right.
Three minutes
till Rubicon launches the nukes.
Overwatch. Amar is headed inside.
We're running out of time.
Are you hit?
No, no, no.No.
- What's happening?
- We got every nuke.
Except one.
We lost one. It's in the air.
Headed straight for Monument Point.
The bullet went through,
but I need you to hold still.
I think we have more important concerns.
Such as preventing another launch.
I thought you two
stopped Rubicon.
Rubicon knows the missiles didn't launch,
it keeps trying to send launch codes.
Which we have to override manually,
one by one.
It's kinda like whack-a-mole.
Except we don't get a stuffed animal
if we win.
Is it true, there's one in the air?
Headed straight for Monument Point.
- Can you override?
- That is what I'm trying to do
while Noah keeps the missiles
in their silos.
We need to start evacuations.
There's not enough time
to get everyone out.
This is ARGUS director Lyla Michaels.
I'm reporting an end-time event.
Target is Monument Point.
Felicity.
I'm trying to hack
their navigation systems.
What's that?
Another hit
on the ley line algorithm I set up.
I cross-referenced it
with news reports and...
The mayor's office just evacuated
City Hall due to a gas leak.
Like you said, why would Darhk's wife run
for mayor of a city he wants to destroy?
To gain access to City Hall.
For this exact moment.
The nexus chamber
must be beneath that building.
If he's hiding where he should be hiding
to absorb the power of the nuke attack.
Let's go.
You need to divert that missile.
You are lucky I'm too busy to come up
with a witty response to that right now.
Stop. Stop!
Taiana. Are you okay? Are you hurt?
Something's...
- Got it. Mostly.
- What?
I sent the remaining launch algorithms
into an infinite loop.
Should buy the world 24 hours,
give or take.
What about the nuke
headed to Monument Point?
It's stubborn.
There's a reason why these things
were designed
to be impossible to move off course.
Which is why
I have to move Monument Point instead.
- GPS realignment.
- What do you mean?
As a prank,
I once relocated a GPS satellite.
Everyone on the Eastern Seaboard thought
they were 20 miles west
of their actual location.
Do that to the missile,
you avoid a direct hit.
That's it.
Direct hit on Havenrock.
Maximum yield.
How many casualties?
Tens of thousands.
Monument Point would have been
a couple million, Felicity.
Damn it, we've searched everywhere.
Hello, Oliver. Nice timing.
I think you're gonna need
much bigger arrows.
English - SDH