My name is Oliver Queen.
For 5 years,
I was stranded on an island
with only one goal--
survive.
Oliver Queen is alive.
Now I will fulfill
my father's dying wish--
to use the list
of names he left me
and bring down those
who are poisoning my city.
To do this, I must
become someone else.
I must become something else.
Previously on Arrow...
Who supplies you with Vertigo?
They call him the Count!
56 people died
to perfect this high.
I've never seen anyone od on
this much Vertigo and live.
The police never caught
your brother's shooter.
The bullets were laced
with curare, that's
Floyd Lawton's M.O.
- Lawton's alive.
- I'm sorry, John.
This Lawton guy
kick his dog or something?
He killed his brother.
How we doing?
We're in the black,
and the green.
I like how we've gone from throwing
money at clubs to catching it.
Oh, look at these.
What sort of business
has a lost and found
that's just filled
with women's underwear?
The best business ever?
Ohh, having this much fun
should be against the law.
Oh, if wishing made it so.
Sorry, am I
interrupting anything?
- Is Laurel ok?
- She's fine.
This visit is about
something else.
A girl just got mowed down
a couple blocks from here.
On Starling bridge.
Ring any bells with you two?
- No.
- Should she?
She was in your club tonight.
A lot of people were.
You think someone killed her?
Not someone.
Something.
Vertigo.
Yeah. You got a problem
with that in this club?
Not that I'm aware of.
We don't allow drugs
in here, Detective.
Control your clientele.
Before anyone else
wanders into traffic.
Is there any chance she could
have scored the drugs in here?
I doubt it. I try not
to hire too many drug dealers.
Get me a list
of employees, anyway.
I'll have Felicity cross reference
it for drug arrests.
That includes
the two of us, you know.
I thought the Vigilante
finished off the Count.
I did.
I just need to ask him
a few questions, Doc.
Well, you're welcome
to try, Detective,
but I'm not sure you'll get
very far with him.
What does that mean?
Is this a load about
doctor-patient privilege?
No, far from it. The unrefined
Vertigo overdose he suffered
caused damage to the caudal portion
of his anterior cingulate.
Well, you'll probably be
shocked to hear
that I didn't go
to medical school.
I've been working
with him for months now.
And all I've gotten
out of him is word salad
and the occasional
spit in the face.
- Best of luck to you.
- Thanks.
Here I was born,
and there I died.
It was only a moment for you.
You took no notice.
A woman died tonight...
from your poison.
Lots of women die,
lots of nights,
for lots of reasons.
Someone is selling Vertigo
again. Where is it coming from?
I remember you.
Man in hood.
You are never far
from my thoughts.
You have failed this city!
You could have just
said he was nuts.
You failed this city!
All right!
You're teaching me that one.
Only if you show me
where the knife was.
Who taught you how to fight?
My father wanted a son.
He got one.
The tension of that
bow's 150 pounds.
Snap it, you'll both be covered
by fiber shrapnel in your eyes.
She's right.
You're not strong enough, kid.
Go again?
It's pretty exciting
that both of you are
such bad asses,
but do you think that
maybe we should be
making a plan to stop Fyers?
And, I don't know...
Save your dad?
Does he always
whine this much?
Today's one of his good days.
Can he fight?
I've tried.
Never much success.
I'm sitting right here.
Well, I haven't tried yet.
- Uncle John.
- Hey, buddy.
Will you read
"Logan Bogan" to me?
Sweetheart, get into bed
and mommy will read
to you in a minute.
But I want Uncle John
to read to me!
Uncle John's had a long day.
He'll read to you next time.
Hey, I'm sorry.
I've been some place else today.
What's going on with you?
I'm just trying
to figure some stuff out.
If you need to talk
about anything,
you know I'm here for you.
It is Oliver Queen,
with an emergency.
Got to go.
Got here as quickly
as I could.
This about the glyph
in your father's notebook?
Felicity is still
working on that.
We have another problem.
Starling City
is once again at war
with the drug known on
the streets as Vertigo.
It used to be the city's
most lethal vice,
but the purple and green pill
was nowhere to be found
for the last 3 months.
Over the past few days, the city
has been flooded
with a new version of Vertigo.
More addictive, more unstable.
It killed a girl in the club.
Just like it
almost killed Thea.
Ok, what are you think?
We should pay the Count a visit?
He was my first visit.
Waste of time.
He's... sumasshedshiy.
Ahh.
Since he was the only one that
knew the forumla for Vertigo,
I don't...
I don't even know
where to begin.
Good, you're here.
Of course you're here.
Where else would you be?
You clearly love it down here.
You got to see this.
I'm here at the scene
where police say
a disturbed patient
escaped only hours ago.
Authorities issued
an immediate lockdown
at the Starling County
Institute for Mental Health
following the breakout.
Police are warning people
to avoid contact
with the drug dealer
known as the Count.
Not so crazy after all, huh?
1x19
Unfinished Business
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Resync for WEB-DL by lost0ne
I was administering his meds.
He was babbling.
His usual ranting,
then he's ice cold.
He overpowered me.
He forced me to take him out
through the maintenance exit.
I thought he was harmless.
Basically a vegetable, you said.
I know. Which means...
I've interviewed him
dozens of times
in the past few months.
To be deceived by
a patient so completely--
Don't worry.
We'll find him.
He's going to find prison
a lot harder to break out of.
Detective...
He's dangerous.
Don't underestimate him.
Did we get anything
from the security cameras?
Not according
to the orderly here.
Due to budget cuts, the
cameras were the first to go.
That is unbelievable.
There's another angle.
Veronica Sparks,
the dead girl from Verdant?
- Yeah?
- I checked her LUDs.
The last person
she texted before she died
was Tommy Merlyn.
He said he didn't know her.
Merlyn has two collars for
possession, one with intent.
Yeah, that was over
five years ago.
Maybe he's just better at
not getting himself arrested.
Well, Laurel says he's changed
ever since his father cut him off.
Yeah, a leopard
and his spots, you know?
Maybe pushing Vertigo
at his new club
is a way of maintaining
his old lifestyle.
Yeah, or maybe
going after Meryln's
a great way to get my daughter
to stop speaking
to me again, Hilt.
Look, Quentin,
you know I get that.
But here's the thing--
on a hunch,
I subpoenaed
the club's bank accounts.
There's ten large missing
from their operating expenses.
You think Merlyn spent
that money on Vertigo?
I think I can't explain how that
much money just gets misplaced.
Look, I'll take a run at it.
- Keep you out of it.
- No.
I should do it.
What you need?
All right.
The person of color has
successfully purchased your drugs.
For the record, I offered.
How will we know
when the tracker is active?
It already is.
I'm getting a good signal
off the monofilament strips
we placed in the bills.
Drug money's like a pigeon--
it always finds its way home.
We can follow the money
all the way back to the Count.
Keep tracking it.
Well, what are you going to do
with all the Vertigo you bought?
Plan on having
a party, Felicity?
My only experience with
drugs was an encounter
with a pot brownie
my freshman year--
by mistake.
Which could have been fun,
except I'm allergic to nuts.
All right, head shot.
Kills again,
this time a U.S. senator.
Where have you been
tracking him?
Not very far.
I ran his Floyd Lawton alias
through every conceivable
law enforcement database.
He's made a series of calls
to an Alberto Garcia.
- Huh.
- According to NSA,
Garcia's a reputed
underworld talent scout.
He books all
the Deadshot's hits.
It's not much to go on, but...
Yeah, but it's
something, Felicity, thanks.
Don't you think
Oliver should know?
No, this is personal.
Lawton is my problem
to deal with.
What brings you by?
Hey, would you like
some dinner?
Your daughter ordered
way too much Thai food.
No, thanks.
This is a business
visit, actually.
I got some follow up questions
on the Sparks' girl's death.
Sure. The girl was in the club
before she got run-over.
You said you didn't
know her, but, um,
but the last text
off her phone was to you.
Really? Because, uh...
Well, I'll be damned.
Huh. Well, I didn't reply.
I get a hundred texts
like this a night.
People wanting
to get into the club.
So that's what she meant by,
"Can you hook me up?"
What else would it be about?
$10,000 is missing from
your club's bank accounts.
What'd you spend the money on?
No idea. There must be some sort
of bookkeeping error--
Ok, let me put this
another way--
if you spent that money on Vertigo
so that you could "hook up"
- your clientele--
- Dad!
Then the best thing
for you right now
is to cop to it, ok?
Get out in front of this.
Don't say anything.
I am trying to--
To do your job?
Yeah, I know.
And this is me doing mine.
Laurel, I know I look like
the disapproving
father--again.
But I came down here
so another cop wouldn't.
You understand?
Tommy, I...
I'm not hungry anymore.
Hold up hand up.
Palm facing me.
Hit the water.
- What?
- Hit it.
Again.
Again. Harder.
If the point of this
is to make me feel like
an idiot, it's working.
"A journey of a thousand miles
begins with
a single step."
Confucius, great.
I'm starting to see
the family resemblance.
Laozi, actually. Again.
Now what?
Fill the bowl.
Start again.
What have you got?
The end of the money trail.
Sending the dealer's
location to you now.
Oh, hey! Hey, dude.
Hey yo.
Who's looking to party?
Oh, yeah.
Come on.
That's not enough, man.
You don't pay, you don't play.
It's all right.
Good for business.
My boss seems to like you, G.
That's right.
Hey, hey, come here.
How much for this?
Now that...
That'll buy you
a brick, my man.
Go, go, go!
Don't forget to breathe.
He won't.
I won't.
Congratulations.
You're officially the creepiest
person I've ever met.
I don't--I don't
feel so good.
Get away from me, creep.
Have we got a problem?
Are you ok?
All units,
all units, code 99.
417 in progress, Starling Aquarium.
All available units--
this just came over
the police frequency.
I hacked the aquarium
security system to get a better look.
Bystanders said
they saw him pop
some green and black pills...
There's a lunatic
high on Vertigo who's taking hostages,
and you're making--
making tea.
They're medicinal herbs
from the island.
They counter balance the effects
of certain drugs and poisons.
They should counteract
the effects of Vertigo.
And you aren't going to--
- What?
- You know...
My sister got high
on this garbage.
Could have killed someone.
She didn't deserve
an arrow in the heart.
This guy didn't fail the city.
The city failed him.
And so did I.
What's happening now
isn't your fault.
You didn't make him
take drugs.
No, but I did fail to put the Count
in a grave so deep
that he couldn't come back
and hurt anyone again.
You caught him.
They locked him up.
And now the city is on fire!
So clearly, it wasn't
the right decision.
Get in touch with Diggle.
With the security feed out,
I'm going need a second
set of eyes at the aquarium.
Glad I caught you stateside.
Just barely. I leave in
two days for Pyongyang.
Isn't that classified?
I figure an old army
buy can keep a secret.
I was glad to get your call.
Lyla, that's not why I called.
There's something else
you'd like me
to do for you, then.
Well, actually,
I think there's something
I can do for you.
I'm going to go out on a limb
and assume that Deadshot
is on Argus' most wanted list.
What do you know about him?
Well, his name, for starters.
Floyd Lawton.
We don't even have that.
Where'd you get it?
Same place I got this.
This is everything
you need to locate
who's giving Deadshot
his targets.
What's your interest in this?
Lawton came up in connection with
some things I'm working on.
I thought you were
the right person to pass it off to.
I remember you being
a better liar than that, Johnny.
Listen, Lyla, Lawton
is a very dangerous man.
And your people are the most
qualified to take him down.
It's that simple.
Nothing in our business
is simple.
Me to ask for my help again,
Mr. Lance?
Eric Messner?
Who?
He's a zoning commissioner
for Starling City.
A notoriously corrupt one,
at that.
Missing ten grand.
You paid it to him
to skip the inspection
of your nightclub.
Why'd you do that, Merlyn?
What didn't you want him to find?
We got nothing to hide here.
Great. Then let's just
take a little look around.
Absolutely.
When you come back
with a search warrant.
Are you sure this is how
you want to play this?
Apparently.
Doesn't my daughter
know how to pick 'em.
Stop laughing at me!
Shut up!
Stop! I don't want to hurt you.
I'm here to help you.
Hey, hey.
My mom does yoga.
Hey, remember when Slade
and I rescued you?
You rescued me?
Fine. When we all
rescued each other.
You said you knew
why Fyers wanted Yao Fei,
and how he was
forcing him to help.
Feel like sharing?
We're almost out
of slapping water.
My father was a Shangjiang
in the People's Liberation Army.
A general. I didn't hear
the details of Fyers plans,
but he wants my father
to be the face of it.
A scapegoat.
To take the blame
and conceal
their own involvement.
Why was Yao Fei
on the island in the first place?
Fyers says he murdered people.
No, he didn't.
The Chinese military
comitted the massacre.
Someone had to take the blame.
They chose him.
Sent him to this
island for life.
I spent years looking for him.
A few months ago, a man
came to my apartment.
Said he had information
about my father's whereabouts.
I had given up hope.
Let my guard down.
Didn't see the tazer until...
When I woke up, I was here.
I'm worried.
This island...
What he must have had
to do to survive.
That it changed him.
He saved my life.
He's still a good man, Shado.
Again.
So there I am sitting
at our favorite Sushi restaurant,
a bottle of saki,
and the only thing
that's missing is my boyfriend.
My God, I'm so sorry, baby.
I just have
a lot going on here.
Tommy, whatever's
going on with you,
I want you to know
I believe you.
I'm here for you.
Sorry.
Ollie.
What's wrong?
Bad night.
It's about to get worse.
Mr. Meryln,
as requested, a warrant to search
these premises.
I can't believe
you're doing this.
- Believe it.
- Detective,
I'm not an attorney,
but on what grounds
are you searching my club?
Your general manager bribed
a government official to keep him
from inspecting
the entirety of your building.
What?
Because he's selling
Vertigo out of the club.
Ollie, it's valid.
Thank you.
A sub level is not listed
on the inspection's
floor plans.
However, I pulled
the county records.
There's something down there.
I want to see
for myself what it is.
Oh, look at that.
Open the door.
You're making a mistake.
No. You are.
If you don't open that door.
I said, open the door.
Thank you.
The place is kind of a mess.
I've been using it to store
the bulk of our inventory.
What's in the boxes?
Why don't you have a look.
Well, if prohibition
were still in effect,
you might actually have a basis
of a criminal complaint.
Would you like to open
the rest of the crates?
So if you don't have
anything to hide...
Why didn't you want
the inspector down here?
Well, the ventilation
system in this place
hasn't been updated
since the sixties.
Maybe we shouldn't
even be open.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
I thought he was ok
with us being together.
He wasn't wrong.
I bribed a guy.
That's not why
he brought out his jackboots.
It's all gonna be fine.
I'll see you at home.
Good night.
Is there something
you want to say to me?
Thank you.
No, I meant the thing
that you were thinking
when Lance accused me
of dealing out of the club.
I don't understand
why you wouldn't
just tell me about the bribe.
I run the club, Oliver.
I don't tell you
a lot of things.
So let me ask you
a question, pal.
What have I done in the last
6 months since you've been home
that would lead you
to believe that I would sell drugs?
In the last 6 months?
Nothing.
Yeah.
Before I left,
you played hard.
You played with bad people
who were into bad stuff.
And so did you, Oliver.
But I changed
just like you did.
Now you put arrows in people
who do illegal things.
Last time I checked, bribing
a city inspector was not legal.
Do you actually think
that I could hurt you?
Truthfully, I have no idea what
the hell you would do.
You are a complete
mystery to me.
I've got no idea how you find it
so easy to kill people.
The next time you decide to think
the worst of me,
imagine what I now
think of you.
What's his problem?
What's yours?
Excuse me?
I asked Felicity
to get in touch with you.
There was a hostage
situation at the aquarium.
I'm sorry, I didn't get
that message till it was over.
Why?
Because I was busy
doing something else.
Lawton.
Oliver, you didn't
end up needing me.
You couldn't have known that.
In other words,
find your brother's killer
on your own time, right?
Vertigo's tearing
this city apart, Diggle.
So, yeah, maybe now's
not the best time
to indulge
a personal vendetta.
You're actually gonna stand
there and tell me
that you going after
the Count is not personal?
Oliver, listen, I cannot read
a book to my nephew
without knowing that Lawton
took his father from him.
I can't move on with Carly,
I can't move on with my life
knowing that he's
still out there.
I thought if anybody
got that it'd be you.
What happened here?
The ethernet cable
still works.
Would you plug in
your tablet, please?
Did you decide to remodel?
Long story.
Where's Dig?
The hostage-taking junkie.
He is the only lead
to the Count we've got left.
What type of information
are you looking for?
Anything that will give us
a line on the Count's location.
Has the M.E. performed the
autopsy report yet?
Yeah, just pulling it up now.
Check the toxicology to see
if there's something related
to the Vertigo he was on.
He didn't die of
a Vertigo overdose.
I saw it, Felicity.
According to the
coroner, cause of death
was severe anaphylaxis.
He died of an allergic reaction
to chlorpromazine.
That's an anti-psychotic.
Pull up the
Veronica Sparks autopsy.
Did she have chlorpromazine
in her system?
Yes.
How did you know?
The Count must have added it
as a new ingredient
in this latest iteration
of Vertigo.
But wouldn't the amount
he'd need
to manufacture enough
for circulation be huge?
Where would he get that much?
A mental institution.
What if we're looking
at this all wrong?
How so?
Everybody is looking
for him outside the asylum,
but what if he never left?
What if...
What if he faked his escape
the same way that he
faked being insane?
I should have killed you
when I had the chance.
Turn around.
I said turn around.
Yah!
Oliver Queen.
All those years
on that island.
So the Count didn't fake losing
his mind, did he?
This was you the whole time.
How'd you get him to give you
the formula for Vertigo? Huh?
Chemistry doesn't seem
like his best subject right now.
He couldn't tell me
if he wanted to.
I ordered a biopsy
on his kidneys.
The tissue was suffused
with the narcotic after his O.D.
When I got the results,
I realized I could
reverse engineer the chemical
compound of the drug,
produce a synthesized
version myself
using the facilities here.
And made a few improvements,
like adding chlorpromazine.
That's how you found us.
Cops came around,
started asking questions,
you faked the Count's
disappearance to draw
attention away from yourself.
It's clever.
I wasn't trying to be
a criminal mastermind.
I just needed the money.
Something I'm sure a billionaire
wouldn't understand.
Believe me,
I understand you perfectly.
Open his mouth.
What? No! No!
From what I've read
in the tabloids,
no one will be surprised
to hear Oliver Queen
died of a drug overdose.
Uhh!
Clear.
Freeze!
You don't look so good.
I doubt you could aim
a single arrow.
Looks like I'm
the last one standing.
Sitting. Spinning.
Something to do.
What was I going to do?
Memory not what it once was.
Nothing what it once was.
Is there a name
on the gravestone?
No.
It's new.
And clean.
And waiting.
We're finished here.
Hey. How we doing?
In the black.
Did the Hood get his man?
Well, we won't be having
any problems with Vertigo anymore.
Look, Tommy, I'm sorry.
I've caught up the bookkeeping
and all my notes
on the inventory are in there,
along with a list
of suppliers that we use.
Ok.
I don't see why
you're telling me that.
This club is important to me.
But for you it's just a front.
You want me to keep
your secret,
help you be this thing
you've become,
but you refuse to see me
for what I've become.
I've got just a bit
too much self-respect for that.
I quit.
Dinner.
You're still doing that?
Fyers better be careful
with his bowls of water.
When are we going to do
actual training?
There once was a young boy
whose father dropped him off
at a shaolin monastery
to study Kung Fu.
Good, a story.
After a year, the boy came
to visit his family.
When they asked what
he'd learned,
the boy hung his head
in shame.
All the monks had him do was
slap water in a barrel for a year.
We don't have a year.
So I hope your training
regimen is a bit faster.
The family didn't believe him,
so he showed them.
He raised his hand and hit
the table they were eating on.
It broke in half.
I'm gonna be able
to break a table?
Better.
Ok.
Draw the bow.
I'll be damned.
What's next?
We teach you to shoot.
Drinking alone?
Oh. Well, no,
not anymore.
Just soda?
Bartender forget the scotch?
I didn't really feel
the need for it.
So, um, the girl who died,
it turns out that she got
her Vertigo from a co-worker.
Guess I owe your
boyfriend an apology.
He has a name, you know.
Yeah, I just can't
seem to bring myself to use it.
Baby steps.
Did I screw things up
between us again?
No.
Look, I really wasn't
looking to jam up Merlyn, ok?
I knew by pursuing him
that I could throw a wrench in--
Then why did you do it?
There was evidence, Laurel,
and I had to follow it.
I had to.
Look, your mom was
right, you were right.
Like you said about me
and the Vigilante,
I can't let things go.
I close cases, it's what I do.
Everyone else be damned.
Well, maybe the fact that
there's no scotch in there means
you're ready to work on that.
People can change.
Hey.
You had my back.
You needed me.
Felicity told me
where you were headed.
You ok?
I'm the killer, remember?
I've killed before, Oliver.
It's just been a while.
If you're the killer,
why isn't the Count down, too?
I'm sure it must have been tempting
to take him off the board for good.
People change.
People like the Count?
No. I meant me.
Not so long ago I would have
put that guy down for good,
but looking at him today
all vacant...
There didn't seem to be
a point.
But not everybody
deserves mercy.
For example.
I thought he wasn't
a priority to you.
He's a priority to you.
You two have
unfinished business.
Where do we start?
I'd prefer we skip
the I-told-you-sos,
but the nightclub wasn't
really working out.
I guess I need something
more boring, stable.
9:00 to 5:00, go home kiss Laurel,
that sort of thing.
I guess what I'm saying is...
I want a job.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Resync for WEB-DL by lost0ne