PREVIOUSLY ON "ARROW"...
I HAVE A VILLAGE, TOO,
RUN BY A GOVERNMENT
STRONGMAN NAMED KOVAR.
YOU WILL GO TO RUSSIA
AND FIND MY PARENTS
AND TELL THEM WHAT
HAPPENED TO ME AND VLAD.
I AM SORRY.
[NECK SNAPS]
TELL ME WHO THIS
PROMETHEUS IS.
I GUESS YOU KNOW WHAT
I'VE BEEN UP TO, HUH?
REMEMBER, I'M ALWAYS
10 STEPS AHEAD OF YOU.
[ARROW SAILS]
WHAT'S GOING ON?
-CHASE IS GONE.
-AND SO IS OLIVER.
WE HAVE TO
ASSUME THAT CHASE HAS HIM.
JUST MAKE SURE HE SUFFERS.
THAT WAS ALWAYS THE PLAN.
ADRIAN: DID YOU HESITATE
AT ALL WHEN YOU KILLED HIM,
OR WAS HE JUST ANOTHER NAME
YOU CROSSED OFF YOUR LIST?
[NECK SNAPS]
ADRIAN:
IF YOU KILL ME,
YOU'LL ONLY REALLY
BE KILLING YOURSELF.
...4, 3, 2, 1.
[GASPS]
145 SECONDS.
THAT'S HOW LONG MY FATHER
STRUGGLED UNDER THE WATER
BEFORE HE DIED.
ACCORDING TO MY FATHER'S
AUTOPSY,
YOUR ARROW PIERCED HIS
AORTIC ARCH,
BUT IT DIDN'T KILL HIM. NO.
HE WAS STILL CONSCIOUS
ENOUGH TO FEEL
HIS LUNGS FILLING WITH
WATER FOR 145 SECONDS.
AND HERE YOU WERE
BRAGGING ABOUT A PLAN
MORE INTRICATE
THAN TORTURE.
DID YOU EVER THINK ABOUT WHY
I CHOSE THE NAME PROMETHEUS?
HE CHALLENGED
THE OMNIPOTENCE OF THE GODS.
YOU SEE, BECAUSE, LIKE YOU,
THEY PLAY JUDGE, JURY,
AND EXECUTIONER.
BUT PROMETHEUS TOOK AWAY
THEIR POWER.
IF THAT'S WHAT YOU'RE
GONNA DO TO ME,
YOU'LL NEED TO COME UP
WITH SOMETHING BETTER
THAN WHATEVER THIS IS.
I DID.
AND THE ONLY WAY FOR YOU
TO STOP IT IS TO CONFESS.
THAT I KILLED
YOUR FATHER?
NOTHING SO PEDESTRIAN.
I WANT YOU TO TELL ME
A SECRET, OLIVER.
I WANT YOU TO CONFESS
TO THE ONE THING
THAT YOU'VE BEEN AFRAID
TO ADMIT TO YOURSELF.
HOW MANY TIMES AM I
GONNA TELL YOU
THAT I DON'T KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT?
FINE. YOU'LL COME AROUND
EVENTUALLY.
NOW, WHERE WERE WE?
145, 144, 143,
BANDAGES AND WATER
WILL NOT HELP ME.
BEFORE YOU DIE,
TELL US WHAT YOU MEANT.
YOU SAID IF WE KILL YOU,
WE KILL OURSELVES. WHY?
[CHUCKLES]
YOU WILL FIND OUT
SOON ENOUGH.
YOU'RE GONNA TELL ME NOW...
OR I'M GONNA DIG THAT
BULLET OUT OF YOUR ARM.
GO TO HELL.
OLIVER! OLIVER!
[SCREAMING]
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
HE WILL NEVER TELL YOU
TRUTH IN THAT MUCH PAIN.
DOES THIS HAVE TO DO
WITH YOUR DEAL
WITH KOVAR, YES?
SAMOVOL'SHCHNIA.
IF YOU KNEW WHAT IT WAS
OR WHAT IS COMING,
YOU WILL BEG KOVAR
TO SPARE YOU.
AND YOU...
ARE NO ONE'S HERO.
EVERYTHING AND EVERYONE
THAT YOU LOVE
WILL WITHER
AND DIE
AT YOUR TOUCH.
DA.
GOOD RIDDANCE.
WHAT DO WE
DO ABOUT KOVAR?
WHAT DOES IT MATTER?
OUR PAKHAN IS DEAD.
WE MUST SWEAR IN A NEW ONE.
ANATOLY: THERE ARE
MEN LOYAL TO US
AND MEN LOYAL
TO GREGOR,
ALL WITHOUT
PAKHAN.
HOW DO WE CHOOSE A NEW ONE?
PAKHAN IS DETERMINED
BY SENIORITY.
OLIVER: WHY IS
HE DOING THAT?
IT'S FOR JOURNEY
TO AFTERLIFE.
IT MAKES GOOD GIFT
IN HEAVEN
BUT EVEN BETTER
BRIBE FOR SATAN.
DA.
YOU CAN GET IN THERE, TOO.
YOU'RE ONE OF US.
[GROANS]
VIKTOR. I THINK
HE CUT INTO TENDON.
OH, I DON'T THINK HE'S
VERY HAPPY YOU'RE PAKHAN.
YOU THINK? I KNOW.
I WISH THERE WAS LESS
PAINFUL TRANSFER OF POWER
IN BRATVA.
WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO
ABOUT KOVAR?
YOU ASKING FOR YOURSELF
OR YOU ASKING FOR BRATVA?
ANATOLY, GREGOR
MADE IT SOUND LIKE
ALL OF US WERE
GONNA BE KILLED.
SAMOVOL'SHCHNIA.
YEAH. "DO AS YOU WILL,"
BUT HE MADE IT SOUND
LIKE THERE WAS SOME...
SOME DEEPER MEANING?
YEAH. IT COMES FROM
RUSSIAN REVOLUTION, 1917.
WHY IS HE QUOTING
THE RUSSIAN REVOLUTION?
WELL, I CANNOT THINK
OF ANY GOOD REASON.
LET ME ASK KOVAR
WHEN I TALK TO HIM.
WHAT? YOU CAN'T MEET
WITH KOVAR.
KOVAR HAD DEAL WITH GREGOR.
GREGOR IS DEAD.
AS THE NEW PAKHAN, I...I HAVE
TO MEET WITH HIM.
HE WILL SUSPECT SOMETHING
IS UP.
I COULD TRY TO TALK
TO GALINA.
-TO WHO?
-I TOLD YOU ABOUT TAIANA.
OH, YES.
GALINA'S HER MOTHER.
AND SHE WORKS
FOR KOVAR.
MAYBE SHE HEARD
SOMETHING.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[SNIFFS]
YOUR BOSS? YOU...YOU WORK
FOR KONSTANTIN KOVAR.
HE SAID YOU WERE ENEMY.
NO, NO. NO.
-A...A BAD MAN.
-NO. NO, NO.
I'M FRIENDS WITH TAIANA.
MY PRECIOUS TAIANA?
W...WELL, WE'RE FRIENDS.
AND I...I...
-MM-HMM.
-I COULD USE YOUR HELP
WITH SOMETHING.
[SCREAMS]
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
HEY. I'M NO...
I'M NOT GONNA SHOOT.
LISTEN TO ME. WHEN
KOVAR HEARS ABOUT THIS,
YOU CANNOT SAY YOU SAW
ME, DO YOU UNDERSTAND?
IF YOU SAY YOU SAW ME,
HE'LL HURT YOU.
ALL RIGHT?
ALL RIGHT.
KOVAR: MY FATHER
ONCE TOLD ME
DO NOT HAVE
A HUNDRED RUBLES
BUT HAVE A HUNDRED
FRIENDS.
[MERLYN CHUCKLES]
FORTUNATELY, FOR US
WE HAVE BOTH FRIENDS
AND MONEY.
AS I ASSUME YOUR
PRESENCE HERE MEANS
THAT OUR, UH, AHEM,
ARRANGEMENT
HAS, UH,
BORNE FRUIT.
THE SHIPMENT WAS ROUTED
TO THIS LOCATION.
THE BIC CODES ARE INSIDE.
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS
RETRIEVE IT.
NOW, AS FOR MY COMPENSATION,
I THINK THAT...
UNIDAC INDUSTRIES.
YES, I WILL MAKE
SURE YOU GET
THE, UM, INFORMATION
YOU DESIRE.
NOW, IF YOU'LL
EXCUSE ME, I...I HAVE
SOME OTHER BUSINESS
TO ATTEND TO.
MY APOLOGIES.
MALCOLM MERLYN,
CEO, MERLYN GLOBAL GROUP.
ANATOLY KNYAZEV,
GANGSTER.
YOU UNDERCUT
YOU, UM...
YOUR NEW STATION,
MR. KNYAZEV.
[SIGHS]
PAKHAN OF THE
SOLNTSEVSKAYA BRATVA,
IT'S, UH,
IT'S NO SMALL FEAT.
NOR IS SAMOVOL'SHCHNIA.
ONE OF GREGOR'S LAST WORDS.
AND, UM...
WERE HIS, UH, OTHER
LAST WORDS
ABOUT WHO KILLED
HIM?
HE CALLED
THE MAN KAPIUSHON.
"HOOD."
DA. REPORTS OF MAN
WITH A BOW AND ARROW
ARE DISRUPTING BUSINESS,
BRATVA AND OTHERWISE.
[SIGHS]
THAT'S INTERESTING.
I HEARD SOME REPORTS
OF MY OWN OF...OF YOU HAVING
TROUBLE WITH GREGOR
BECAUSE OF HIS DEAL WITH ME.
I QUESTIONED IT, YES.
NOW THAT I AM PAKHAN,
I AM OBLIGATED TO LIVE
UP TO COMMITMENTS
THAT HE MADE, SUCH AS
SAMOVOL'SHCHNIA.
YOU STUDY HISTORY,
MR. KNYAZEV?
WHEN THE SOVIET UNION
WAS DISSOLVED,
MANY THOUGHT THAT, UH,
CAPITALIST OPPORTUNITIES
WILL GIVE RISE
TO A MORE STRONGER,
A MORE UNITED RUSSIAN
PEOPLE,
BUT MANY POWERFUL MEN
OF THE KGB, COMMUNIST PARTY,
THE KOMSOLMOL,
THEY DECIDED TO CASH IN
ON THEIR PRIVILEGES
AND, UH...
RUSSIA BECAME
NOT STRONGER BUT...
DISEASED.
AND SAMOVOL'SHCHNIA
WAS THE CURE ONCE.
IT COULD BE SO AGAIN.
OLIVER: ALL RIGHT.
W...WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
IT MEANS KOVAR IS PLANNING
SOMETHING VERY BIG
AND VERY TERRIBLE.
WHAT IS HE GONNA DO?
OLIVER, MAYBE TIME IS BEST
FOR YOU TO GO BACK
TO AMERICA.
ANATOLY, WE'RE BROTHERS.
WHAT'S HAPPENING TO YOU
IS HAPPENING TO ME.
KOVAR IS GOING TO OVERTHROW
RUSSIAN GOVERNMENT.
SAMOVOL'SHCHNIA IS COUP.
AND...AND, I MEAN,
HE JUST TOLD YOU THIS?
BEFORE I GOT THERE,
HE WAS MAKING DEAL
WITH AMERICAN BUSINESSMAN,
SOME SECRET SENSITIVE
SHIPMENT.
YOU THINK IT'S A WEAPON?
KOVAR HAS MANY MEN,
BUT NOT ENOUGH FOR A COUP.
BUT WITH WEAPON. LUCKILY,
I GOT A CHANCE TO SEE
THE FILE THEY'RE
WORKING ON.
OREKHOVO-ZUYEVO.
IT IS A...A SHIPYARD
IN MOSCOW.
THEN WE GO
TO THE SHIPYARD.
WE STOP KOVAR
FROM RETRIEVING IT.
SEEING YOU TAKE BULLET
OUT OF GREGOR,
I SAW HIM AGAIN...
THE FACE OF THE MONSTER.
THIS PLACE, IT'S NOT
GOOD FOR YOU, OLIVER.
GO HOME.
I DIDN'T SAVE YOU
FROM GREGOR
TO STAND BY WHILE YOU'RE
MURDERED BY KOVAR.
THIS ISN'T OVER FOR ME.
SO BE IT, BROTHER.
DO THEY LOOK FAMILIAR?
DO YOU EVEN REMEMBER
THEIR FACES?
THESE ARE YOUR VICTIMS.
THEY WERE PEOPLE WHO DID
TERRIBLE THINGS.
THEY HAD VICTIMS.
AND HUSBANDS AND WIVES,
DAUGHTERS, SONS.
CONFESS YOUR SECRET, OLIVER,
AND ALL THIS ENDS.
I'LL GIVE YOU A GIFT,
AND YOU CAN WALK OUT THAT
DOOR AND GO BACK HOME.
ADRIAN, YOU'RE SICK.
AND YOU'RE A HYPOCRITE.
THERE IS NOTHING THAT
I'VE DONE THAT COMPARES
WITH YOU.
YOU MURDERED
YOUR OWN WIFE.
CECIL ADAMS.
YOU KNEW HIM BY HIS
STREET NAME, THE COUNT.
[SIGHS]
YOU PUT 3 ARROWS IN HIM.
HE WAS GONNA KILL
A FRIEND OF MINE.
FELICITY SMOAK.
YEAH.
CONFESS OR YOU GET
THE SAME 3 ARROWS.
GO TO HELL.
I'VE ALREADY BEEN THERE,
OLIVER,
AND I'VE COME BACK
WITH A MESSAGE FOR YOU.
AGH! UNH!
ARE WE ALL CLEAR?
CLEAR.
SEE HOW EASY IT IS TO THINK
FIRST AND KILL PEOPLE LATER?
OLIVER: WHAT IS THAT?
SARIN GAS, ENOUGH
TO KILL THOUSANDS.
[GROANING]
WHAT'S NEXT?
YOU SAID SOMETHING WHEN I
BROUGHT YOU HERE,
ABOUT HOW YOUR FRIENDS
ARE YOUR STRENGTH NOW.
SHE DIDN'T EVEN KNOW
I WAS IN HER APARTMENT.
OH, I SWEAR TO GOD,
IF YOU HURT HER...
YOU'LL DO ABSOLUTELY
NOTHING
BECAUSE YOU'RE HERE.
YOU SEE, UNTIL YOU CONFESS
YOUR SECRET, OLIVER,
EVERYONE THAT YOU LOVE
IS AT PLAY,
EVEN YOUR SON.
OLIVER:
YOU'RE BLUFFING.
HE...HE'S IN HIDING.
I...I...
I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHERE HE IS.
'CAUSE YOU HAVEN'T
REALLY LOOKED.
BUT FOR ME, WE BOTH KNOW
IT'S JUST A MATTER OF TIME.
CONFESS.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT
YOU WANT ME TO SAY.
THEN I GUESS I SHOULD LEAVE
YOU HERE TO THINK ABOUT IT
AND WONDER WHO I MIGHT
KILL WHILE I'M GONE.
ADRIAN! ADRIAN, PLEASE.
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS
SAY THE WORDS.
I...
THAT'S WHAT I THOUGHT.
SEE YOU SOON.
[DOOR SHUTS]
[VEHICLE APPROACHING]
WE HAVE INCOMING.
[COUGHING]
[GUNFIRE]
THE TRUCK!
KOVAR HAS THE SARIN GAS.
THEN WE ARE ALL
GOING TO BE DEAD MEN.
HOW'S ANATOLY?
RECOVERING, WHICH IS MORE
THAN I CAN SAY FOR OUR MEN.
THE SARIN GAS
GET 'EM?
DA. WHERE WERE YOU?
I WAS KEEPING OVERWATCH,
LIKE ANATOLY ORDERED.
YOU HAVE SOMETHING
TO SAY TO ME, VIKTOR,
SO JUST SAY IT.
IT WAS YOUR IDEA TO GO
AGAINST GREGOR.
BECAUSE OF KOVAR WITH YOUR
VENDETTA AGAINST HIM.
NOW LOOK AT THE MESS
WE'RE IN.
WELL, DO YOU HAVE
A BETTER IDEA?
WE SHOULD BE HONORING
GREGOR'S PACT WITH KOVAR,
NOT THIS.
THE MOMENT THAT KOVAR
OVERTHROWS THE GOVERNMENT,
HE IS GONNA WIPE OUT
THE ENTIRE BRATVA.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
WE HAVE ONE OF
KOVAR'S MEN.
AND WE NEED TO KNOW
WHERE THE GAS IS
GONNA BE USED.
WHY WOULD HE TELL YOU
ANYTHING?
HE WON'T BE TALKING
TO ME.
PLEASE. I DON'T KNOW
ANYTHING.
THERE'S NO NEED
TO HURT ME.
[SHUDDERS]
QUIET.
[SCREAMING, GROANING]
A FRIEND OF MINE RECENTLY
SHOWED ME
THE SKINNING TECHNIQUE USED
BY HUNTERS IN MONGOLIA.
THEY REMOVE ALL THE SKIN...
AND THE THING WAS MUCH
LARGER THAN YOU...
IN LESS THAN 5 MINUTES,
WHICH MEANS YOU DON'T HAVE
VERY LONG TO TELL ME
WHAT YOUR BOSS IS PLANNING.
I DON'T KNOW
ANYTHING.
I WAS KIND OF HOPING
YOU'D SAY THAT.
[KNIFE SLASHES, MAN SCREAMING]
WHAT IS THIS
MONSTROSITY?
YOU SHOULD BE RESTING.
ANATOLY:
I WOKE UP WITH HEADACHE.
I...I CAME TO FIND YOU. I
WAS NOT EXPECTING THIS.
THIS...THIS IS
NOT HUMAN.
ANATOLY, I TOLD YOU
PUTTING ON THIS HOOD,
IT HELPS ME DIRECT
THE DARKNESS INSIDE OF ME.
IT WORKED, BY THE WAY.
I KNOW WHAT KOVAR'S
PLANNING.
BUT AT WHAT COST?
YOU'RE A FOOL TO
THINK A PIECE OF CLOTH
CAN SEPARATE
MAN FROM MONSTER.
DIVIDING YOURSELF
IN TWO
WILL ONLY MAKE
MONSTER STRONGER
UNTIL IT IS
STRONGER THAN YOU.
YOU KNEW WHAT
I WAS CAPABLE OF
BACK ON LIAN YU.
BUT THIS MAN I SEE NOW...
BARES MORE RESEMBLANCE
TO SLADE WILSON
OR ANTHONY IVO.
[HISSES]
TOUGH MAN.
CLEARLY WITHSTOOD A LOT
BEFORE BREAKING.
HE GAVE UP PRETTY
QUICKLY.
THE REST WAS ME
PRACTICING.
PRACTICING TO BECOME WHAT?
SOMETHING ELSE.
KOVAR IS INVITING KEY
MEMBERS OF THE GOVERNMENT...
POLITICIANS
AND MILITARY MOSTLY...
TO THE OPENING
OF HIS CASINO.
THEN KILL THEM
WITH SARIN GAS,
EVEN THE INNOCENTS?
IT'S NOT GOOD FOR
BUSINESS.
YES, BUT BEING
IN CHARGE OF WHOLE COUNTRY
IS GOOD FOR BUSINESS.
WE NEED TO GET
INTO THAT CASINO,
AND WE NEED TO STOP THE
ATTACK BEFORE IT HAPPENS.
THE PLACE WILL BE FORTRESS,
INCREASED SECURITY FOR
PRESIDENT AND GENERALS.
IMPOSSIBLE TO BREAK IN.
THEN WHAT DO YOU
SUGGEST WE DO?
WE SNEAK IN.
WITHOUT THE HELP OF
SOMEONE WORKING FOR KOVAR?
I KNOW SOMEONE.
WELL, IF YOU'RE THINKING
ABOUT HOUSE LADY,
LAST TIME IT DID
NOT GO SO WELL.
GIVE ME A SECOND CHANCE.
AND IF SECOND CHANCE
DOESN'T WORK?
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
OLIVER: MISS VENEDIKTOV...
EH, HE'S...HE'S FINE.
WELL, HE'S UNCONSCIOUS,
BUT HE...LOOK, I'M SORRY
THAT I SCARED YOU
THE OTHER NIGHT.
I JUST...I...I NEED
TO SPEAK WITH YOU. I...
WELL, IT'S LIKE I SAID,
I KNEW YOUR...
YOUR CHILDREN, TAIANA
AND VLAD.
[SPEAKING RUSSIAN]
DO YOU KNOW
WHAT HAPPENED TO THEM?
[STAMMERS]
I'M SORRY. THEY'RE...
THEY'RE DEAD.
BUT MR. KOVAR SAY HE'S
STILL LOOKING FOR THEM.
KOVAR IS LYING.
BEFORE SHE DIED, TAIANA,
WELL, SHE TOLD ME THAT
HE WAS A MONSTER.
AND SHE MADE ME
PROMISE...
SHE MADE ME SWEAR
THAT I WOULD BRING HIM
TO JUSTICE.
OHH. BUT EVEN WHAT YOU
SAY IS TRUE,
WHAT COULD I DO?
TAIANA TOLD ME THAT
THE SAME HAMMER
THAT SHATTERS GLASS
FORGES STEEL.
I SAY TO HER AS A CHILD
TO MAKE HER GROW UP STRONG.
WELL, SHE DID. EH...
AND SHE HELPED ME
GROW STRONG, TOO.
WOULD YOU PLEASE,
PLEASE HELP ME
KEEP MY PROMISE
TO HER?
THIS GETS ME INTO
MR. KOVAR'S BUILDINGS.
THANK YOU.
MAKE IT RIGHT FOR THEM.
UH...TELL ME...
WHO KILLED MY CHILDREN?
A MONSTER.
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR BUZZES OPEN]
[DOOR BUZZES SHUT]
WHAT DID YOU DO TO HER?
I MADE HER MORE...
COMPLIANT.
[GROANING]
[COUGHING]
GET UP. GIVE
YOURSELF A CHANCE.
UM...
I'M NOT GONNA FIGHT HER.
I DON'T WANT YOU
TO FIGHT HER.
I WANT
YOU TO KILL HER.
I'M GONNA LEAVE NOW.
WHEN I COME BACK, EITHER
SHE'S KILLED YOU
AND I LET HER GO
OR YOU KILL HER AND I
LET YOU GO.
NO. NEITHER ONE OF THOSE
THINGS IS GONNA HAPPEN.
IF YOU DON'T KILL HER,
YOU'RE GONNA WATCH ME
SNAP HER NECK.
ADRIAN! WHAT IS
THE POINT OF THIS?!
YOU SEEM TO BE HAVING
A LITTLE BIT OF TROUBLE
FIGURING OUT
WHAT YOUR SECRET IS.
I THOUGHT THIS MIGHT
REMIND YOU.
GOOD LUCK.
[DOOR BUZZES]
[DOOR BUZZES SHUT]
I'M SORRY, OLIVER.
I CAN'T TAKE ANOTHER
DAY HERE.
[SOBBING]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
HMM, I THINK IT'S, UH...
[EXPLOSION]
CANISTERS ARE
IN A STOREROOM,
SOUTHWEST CORNER,
SECOND FLOOR.
COPY THAT.
OK. IF YOU WOULD BE SO KIND
AND LET US IN NOW, PLEASE.
[DOOR UNLOCKS]
I'LL MEET YOU AT THE TARGET.
ANATOLY:DA.
I TOOK YOU INTO MY HOME.
I GAVE YOU FOOD AND SHELTER.
THIS IS HOW YOU REPAY ME?
ANATOLY:
NOW WHERE?
I STUDIED THE MAP. I KNOW
A SHORTCUT. HERE.
ARE YOU
SURE THIS IS THE WAY?
ALMOST THERE. SHOULD BE
AT THE TURN UP AHEAD.
[PISTOL COCKS]
YOU SOLD US OUT.
WE'RE IN A CASINO,
ANATOLY.
I LIKE TO THINK OF IT
AS PLAYING
THE HAND THAT I WAS DEALT.
VRAG NARODA.
EVELY...EVELYN...
HEY, LOOK AT ME.
LISTEN TO ME.
I NEED YOU TO...TO BRING
THE KNIFE OVER HERE.
I WANT YOU TO GET ME
OUT OF THESE THINGS.
AND WHEN HE COMES BACK...
[EXHALES]
WE WILL AMBUSH HIM.
NO, WE CAN'T BEAT HIM.
I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT
I WAS BUYING INTO
WHEN I SIDED WITH HIM,
BUT I...
IT'S OK. I FORGIVE YOU.
I, UH...
I JUST...I CAN...
TOGETHER,
WE CAN GET THROUGH THIS.
I'M DEAD. THAT'S ALL
HE KEPT TELLING ME...
I'M DEAD
BECAUSE I WAS A PART
OF YOUR LIFE.
UH, WOULD YOU BRING ME
THE KNIFE?
WOULD YOU BRING
ME THE KNIFE
AND I CAN SAVE US?
NO.
I'M SORRY. I'M SORRY.
OH, MY G...
COME ON!
ARE WE SERIOUS?
OLIVER, WHAT ARE YOU
TRYING TO PROVE, MAN?
EVELYN BETRAYED YOU.
YOU'VE KILLED PEOPLE
FOR LESS.
I'M NOT GONNA KILL HER.
I WON'T. JUST LET HER GO.
YOU JUST KEEP FORGETTING
WHAT I TOLD YOU
WOULD HAPPEN
IF YOU DIDN'T KILL HER.
ADRIAN, LISTEN TO ME,
PLEASE, OK?
YOU HAVE MADE YOUR POINT.
CONFESS, OLIVER.
TELL ME YOUR SECRET.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU
WANT FROM ME!
I WANT YOU TO TELL ME WHAT
YOU'VE BEEN TOO AFRAID
TO TELL YOUR SISTER,
FELICITY, DIGGLE.
TELL ME!
[EVELYN SOBBING]
I DON'T KNOW. I DON'T...
WRONG ANSWER.
[NECK SNAPS]
I'M GONNA KILL YOU.
FINALLY WE'RE
GETTING SOMEWHERE.
CONFESS.
ANATOLY: OLIVER,
WE'VE BEEN BETRAYED.
VIKTOR, HE...
[GRUNTS]
KOVAR: I AM SO VERY PROUD
OF THIS CASINO
AND WHAT IT MEANS FOR OUR
COUNTRY.
WELL, THAT'S WHY IT SADDENS
ME TO TELL YOU
THAT THERE WAS AN ATTEMPT
BY SOLNTSEVSKAYA BRATVA
TO CRASH THESE FESTIVITIES
AND ASSASSINATE EVERY ONE
OF THESE GOVERNMENT
OFFICIALS HERE TONIGHT.
BUT DON'T WORRY.
WE HAVE THEM ALL IN CUSTODY.
KOVAR: I AM TOLD THEY...
THEY PLANNED TO STAGE
A GAS ATTACK
IN THIS VERY ROOM...
KOVAR: BUT, UH,
SADLY FOR THEM,
EVEN THOUGH THEY WERE
SUCCESSFUL
IN LAUNCHING THE ATTACK...
IT BACKFIRED AND, UH,
KILLED EVERY SINGLE ONE OF THEM.
WELL, AT LEAST, UH, THAT'S
WHAT THE NEWSPAPERS
WILL REPORT IN THE MORNING.
[MURMURING]
GOOD EVENING.
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
ADRIAN: CONFESS.
YOU KILLED MY FATHER
BECAUSE HE WAS
A NAME ON A LIST.
BUT THAT'S NOT REALLY TRUE,
IS IT? NO.
[RIFLE COCKS]
IT'S TOO LATE,
KAPIUSHON.
THE GAS HAS ALREADY
DONE ITS WORK.
THE LIST WAS JUST AN EXCUSE.
THE HOOD, THE DISGUISE...
JUST AN EXCUSE.
THE IDEA THAT ALL THIS IS
SOME HEROIC CRUSADE IS
JUST AN EXCUSE.
EXCUSE FOR WHAT? HUH?
TELL ME!
YOU TELL ME, OLIVER.
YOU TELL ME.
KILL HIM.
OLIVER QUEEN.
WHO COULD HAVE IMAGINED?
I KNOW WHAT'S GOING ON
THROUGH YOUR MIND, OLIVER.
YOU'RE THINKING THAT YOU
CAN GET YOURSELF FREE
FROM THOSE CHAINS,
SLAM ME TO THE GROUND,
AND SNAP MY NECK JUST
LIKE I DID TO EVELYN.
[GRUNTS]
THERE IT IS.
THERE'S THE LOOK I'VE
BEEN WAITING TO SEE.
BUT IT'S NOT JUST ABOUT
STOPPING ME, IS IT? NO.
THERE'S SOMETHING ELSE
IN THERE.
CONFESS, OLIVER.
WHEN YOU SEE TAIANA
IN AFTERLIFE...HEH HEH...
GIVE HER A KISS FOR ME.
[PEOPLE SCREAMING, COUGHING]
-I'M GOING TO FINISH THIS.
-NO!
KOVAR: ARE YOU GOING
TO LET YOUR PAKHAN
FINISH THIS FOR YOU,
MR. QUEEN, EH?
YOU DON'T HAVE TO DO THIS,
OLIVER.
WE BOTH KNOW
THAT I DO.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO, OLIVER.
THE MAN WILL FACE JUSTICE,
I PROMISE.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
HE'LL FACE JUSTICE.
ADRIAN: YOU'VE TOLD
YOURSELF YOU KILL
BECAUSE YOU HAVE TO.
CONFESS, OLIVER.
YOU DON'T KILL BECAUSE
YOU HAVE TO. SO WHY?
WHY DO YOU DO IT?
BECAUSE I WANT TO.
WHAT?
I WANT TO.
I WANT TO!
AND I LIKED IT.
HOW'S IT FEEL KNOWING
THAT I SAW THE ONE THING
YOU COULDN'T ADMIT
TO YOURSELF?
I KNEW HE'D
BREAK...
JUST LIKE YOU
SAID HE WOULD.
ADRIAN: IT'S 'CAUSE
I KNOW HIM BETTER
THAN HE EVEN KNOWS HIMSELF.
GIVE US A MOMENT ALONE,
WOULD YOU?
[DOOR BUZZES OPEN]
ADRIAN: I TOLD YOU, OLIVER.
YOU INFECT EVERY LIFE
YOU TOUCH.
AND NOW DO YOU REALIZE WHY?
IT'S BECAUSE YOUR CRUSADE
WAS BASED ON A LIE.
YOU USED YOUR FATHER'S
MEMORY TO JUSTIFY
A KILLING SPREE.
THERE'S A PRICE TO BE
PAID FOR THAT, OLIVER.
YOUR MOTHER PAID IT.
YOUR FRIEND TOMMY
PAID IT, LAUREL.
DO YOU REALLY WANT TO
TELL ME THAT JOHN DIGGLE
AND FELICITY SMOAK'S
LIVES ARE BETTER
HAVING KNOWN YOU?
YOU...PROMISED
TO LET ME GO.
AND I'M A MAN OF MY WORD.
BUT FIRST I HAVE
A GIFT FOR YOU.
[ADRIAN SIGHS]
THIS TATTOO OF YOURS.
TO BE AN AMERICAN AND NAMED
A CAPTAIN IN THE BRATVA,
YOU MUST HAVE DONE
SOMETHING EXTRAORDINARY.
WHEN YOU LOOK AT IT,
IT MUST...IT MUST REMIND YOU
OF SUCH A VICTORY.
[CLICK]
NOW, WHEN YOU LOOK AT IT,
YOU'LL THINK ABOUT
OUR TIME HERE TOGETHER
AND THE SECRET THAT YOU
CONFESSED TO ME.
WHATEVER PAIN
I CAUSED YOU...
I'M SORRY.
I BELIEVE YOU, OLIVER.
I JUST DON'T CARE.
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
YOU KNOW, I'VE DECIDED.
YOU ARE MY FAVORITE
AMERICAN.
HOW MANY AMERICANS
DO YOU KNOW?
YOU AND JOKING ARE NOT
EXACTLY MADE FOR EACH OTHER,
BUT THAT LOOKS LIKE IT DOES.
ANATOLY, WHY MAKE ME
A CAPTAIN?
I'M NOT
STAYING IN RUSSIA.
BECAUSE NOW ANYWHERE YOU
GO IN THE WORLD,
ANY BRATVA YOU MEET
WILL KNOW
WHAT KIND OF MAN YOU ARE.
COME. I HAVE ANOTHER
GIFT FOR YOU.
HERE.
I RECOVERED IT
FROM THE CASINO.
THANK YOU.
YOU REMEMBER FIRST TIME
WE MET ON THE AMAZO?
I WAS PERFORMING SURGERY
ON MYSELF.
IT'S KIND OF DIFFICULT
TO FORGET.
YEAH. WHAT WAS IT I SAID
TO YOU THEN?
LIVING IS NOT
FOR THE WEAK.
I CANNOT BELIEVE SCARED BOY
IN CELL BESIDE ME
WOULD BE ONE TO KILL
KONSTANTIN KOVAR.
WELL, THAT WASN'T ME.
THAT WAS HIM.
THAT IS A LIE YOU TELL
YOURSELF,
AN EXCUSE THAT ALLOWS YOU
TO KILL.
YOU KILL BECAUSE YOU
LIKE IT.
THAT'S NOT TRUE,
ANATOLY. I HATE IT.
AND I THINK MAYBE
YOU'VE HAD
A BIT TOO MUCH
TO DRINK.
WELL, THAT IS ENTIRELY
POSSIBLE.
BUT IN THIS CASE,
I AM RIGHT.
THIS DEAL YOU
SOLD YOURSELF ON,
THAT THIS HOOD IS GOING
TO KEEP THIS MONSTER OF YOURS
AT BAY,
SOMEDAY IS GOING
TO FALL APART.
AND WHEN IT DOES, YOU'RE
NOT GOING TO LIKE
THE MAN YOU SEE UNDERNEATH.
WELL?
WILL TAKE WEEKS UNTIL
HE'S BACK ON HIS FEET,
BUT HE'LL LIVE.
HE GIVES YOU HIS THANKS.
JUST OUT OF MORBID
CURIOSITY,
WHO DID THIS TO HIM?
THAT'S HIS BUSINESS.
WELL, WHOEVER IT IS,
I'M GLAD I'M NOT HIM.
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
JOHN: HOW MUCH LONGER?
"HOW MUCH LONGER"?
WE LITERALLY HAD TO
REROUTE
THE ELECTRO-OPTICAL
DIGITAL IMAGING
FROM EVERY RECONNAISSANCE
SATELLITE I COULD
GAIN ACCESS TO.
CURTIS: THEN WE
HAD TO CAPTURE DATA
IN A 4-DIMENSIONAL
ARRAY, WHICH COULD
THEN BE PARSED
USING A REAL-TIME
ALGORITHM.
BASICALLY, SOLVING
COLD FUSION
WOULD HAVE BEEN
EASIER.
JOHN: OK. I'M SORRY.
I'VE JUST BEEN AT THIS SO LONG,
I DON'T KNOW WHICH WAY IS UP.
AND OLIVER'S BEEN GONE
FOR 6 DAYS AND...
AND WHAT?
OLIVER? OH, MY GOD.
JOHN: OLIVER?
CHASE HAD ME...
[GROANS]
AND HE LET ME GO.
GO SLOW, MAN.
IT'S OVER.
OLIVER, WE'RE GONNA GET
THIS SON OF A BITCH
FOR WHATEVER HE DID TO YOU.
JOHN, IT'S...
IT...IT...IT'S OVER
FOR ME.
I DON'T WANT TO DO
THIS ANYMORE.
I'M SHUTTING
EVERYTHING DOWN.
MAN: GREG, MOVE YOUR HEAD.