Previously on "Crisis
on Infinite Earths”...
There's a wave of
antimatter sweeping
across this universe,
destroying
everything in its path.
He fought to his last breath
knowing every moment
was another life saved.
Dig, we are working
on bringing him back
the same way that he
brought me back, remember?
You're talking about
a trip to Purgatory?
- “Yes.
- Fine. Count me in.
I need you to come back to us.
You're my brother.
Can't lose you, man.
Oliver Queen.
“Who are you? -Jim Corrigan,
but I'm also a Spectre.
It's your turn now.
Only you can light
the spark, Oliver.
Itis your destiny.
What's happening?
Iris!
Where are we?
This is the vanishing point.
It's a point outside
of time and space.
- Something's wrong.
- No. Hey, hey.
What did you do?
Well, I held The
Book of Destiny,
and I thought destiny
could use a little rewrite.
What do we do now?
Are we ready?
Just about.
You better suit up.
Ilove you.
I'love you.
Okay. This will be
temporal jump trial one.
All systems nominal.
+l look ridiculous.
Is this really the height of
fashion at the dawn of time?
The suit provides
a shield against...
the coronal radiation...
my body will be-- yes, yes, yes.
«I'm familiar with the jingle,
but you couldn't have
designed something
a tad less...bulky?
Remind me again,
why did I marry you?
You have a thing for
men of towering ambition.
Are you seeing this
quantum flux cascade?
I am just a time
traveler here, my love.
You are the Monitor.
Engaging quantum portal.
Field is stabilizing.
The portal is engaging.
Next stop... the dawn of time.
I'am in the temporal zone.
Oh, 1 wish you
could see this, Xneen.
The birthplace of all creation.
It is beautiful.
Mar, I'm getting readings
here I don't understand.
Your presence has
corrupted the zone somehow.
It's...it's releasing radiation
I've never seen before.
/ think-- 1 think this
might be anti-matter.
You have to get out of there.
Get out of there right now!
Xneen...Xneen, can you hear me?
Something went wrong.
1 do not think this
is the dawn of time.
No, itis.
It just isn't the dawn
of time of our universe.
What?
You breached the wall
between our universe
and its opposite.
An anti-universe?
Your body was suffused
with coronal radiation.
The suit couldn't contain it.
Mar? Mar, can you hear me?
I'm sorry, my love.
My towering ambition...
has doomed us all.
Dear Amanda,
so...you're dead
along with, well, everyone,
everyone who's ever
lived in any reality ever,
{electricity zapping]
and me, I'm supposed
to be a Paragon,
one of seven people
who are supposed to be
the multiverse's
last, best chance.
I don't see it.
The so-called
Paragon of Destiny,
she doesn't even believe
in tomorrow anymore.
The Paragon of
Courage spends every day
working herself to the bone,
training for a fight
that will never come.
The Paragon of
Honor just meditates
for hours on end.
The Paragon of Hope
has lost hers...
and me, I spend my
days trying to repurpose
the broken
technology of this place
to find us a way out.
Careful, careful.
Narcissist, sociopath,
evil genius--
there are a lot of ways
to describe Lex Luthor.
Agh! Idiot!
Why couldn't I be trapped
at the edge of eternity
with someone possessing
more than 200 IQ points?
But I find "douchebag"
to be the most descriptive.
As for Barry Allen,
aka the Flash,
aka the Paragon of
Love, he's just gone.
Missing.
What, you guys
building modern art now?
Hey, team. We're repurposing
leftover time masters tech.
Mr. Luthor and I
think we've retrofitted it
into a teleportation device.
To teleport us to where exactly?
Kate makes a good point.
There is no...there
out there anymore.
So we send somebody to test it.
- Hl go.
- No.
We've lost too many
good people already.
Thanks for volunteering, Lex.
Well, that's very cold.
Is it because I killed your
parallel reality cousin?
Start it up.
If this works...
We get out of here,
we defeat the Anti-Monitor,
and we find a way to get
all the people we lost back.
Perhaps it was too
much to hope for.
Is there some way
you can get it to work?
It was a longshot to begin with.
Watch out!
Barry! Ugh!
Where am 1? Where am 1?
The Vanishing Point.
You've been gone for months.
What are you--what
are you talking about?
1 just left two seconds ago.
To go where?
To the speed force. I didn't--
I couldn't--it was like--
it was like running into
a mountain at mach 10.
I couldn't--
there's no way out of here.
What did you see?
Everything.
I see everything now.
Then you're ready.
Why would you make
me relive all that?
Every fight, every
punch you've thrown,
every kick you've landed,
every arrow you've fired,
they have all led you here
to this moment,
to the ultimate fight.
Who am I fighting?
Not who.
What.
The Anti-Monitor.
The Monitor's adversary.
Not just adversary.
A being who stands against
all there ever was or will be,
the apocalypse itself
given life and form
and terrible purpose.
How do I beat him?
With help.
It's time to get your friends.
Barry, wait. You look
spent. You need to rest.
No. I'm fine. I
have to try again.
Hey, Barry, that's
a bad idea, okay?
The effort alone could kill you.
It's better than
just staying here.
We're not gonna
let you kill yourself.
Get out of my way!
- Barry!
- We're not letting you
go anywhere.
-So try and stop me!
-In the condition you're in, Barry,
-it's not gonna be
that hard. «Cut it out!
Whatever's going to happen is not
going to include us turning on each other.
M-maybe you're right.
Maybe the speed force
is our last, best hope.
ltis.
The speed force is
the key to saving you.
It's the key to saving everyone.
Oliver?
Yes and no.
It's complicated.
Nice outfit.
Very...Sith.
Oliver?
I am Oliver Queen,
but I'm also something more.
More what?
Some might call me a ghost,
a Spectre...
that's in tune with
the entire multiverse.
So there's still a
multiverse out there?
No. It's gone,
replaced with its antithesis.
An anti-matter universe.
Which we need to
prevent from happening.
Right now, the Anti-Monitor
is at the dawn of time,
fighting to make permanent
his destruction of worlds.
Then we go there,
and we end him.
He's extremely powerful.
The eight of us
might not be enough.
We need a backup plan.
You have our attention.
Several millennia ago
on a planet named Maltus,
Mar Novu attempted to travel
to the birth of the universe
but instead...opened a breach
to the anti-matter universe.
So the Monitor gave
us the Anti-Monitor.
Correct. So while some of us
fight at the dawn of time,
others must go to Maltus.
And prevent Novu from
freeing his doppelganger?
I'm in.
Travel to an alien world? So in.
Same.
Come on. You know
you don't want to risk
letting me out of your
sight for even a millisecond.
We can get to both
through the speed force,
but I can't get into the
speed force right now.
It's probably because
there's no multiverse left,
but you said you're in
tune with the multiverse.
Does that include
the speed force?
What you're asking me
is very dangerous, Barry.
But possible.
You could give me
the energy boost I need.
Please.
We have to do this.
Everyone's lives depend on it.
I've unlocked your
potential, Barry.
By touching my head?
Use this power with caution.
Do you trust me?
Are you Oliver Queen?
Yes.
Then I trust you with
every cell of my body.
Good. Now run, Barry.
Run.
Okay.
Thanks for the kind assist.
Why doesn't this alien
forest look more alien?
Let's focus. Mar Novu
could be anywhere,
and it's not like we can just
do an internet search for him.
Well, actually, maybe we can.
Look at that.
Any city that large has
to be a bureaucracy.
And?
Well, bureaucracies
require some form
of central data
bank to function.
We find that, we find Novu.
That's actually not
a bad idea. Lex--
Where's Lex?
Sorry I'm late,
but actually my train was late.
Well, the second one.
The first one { did miss,
but that was my
cab driver's fault.
I've got this great traffic
app, and he thought that...
Queen consolidated?
Not exactly.
You're in the
speed force, Barry.
What happened
to you? You're not...
spectrey anymore.
Oh. Well, I'm lost.
I'm out there somewhere
in the speed force, too.
Right. The
Anti-Monitor attacked.
We were separated,
and I am utilizing
various pieces of my essence
to keep me, Sara,
J'onn, and Kate together.
That's why I'm here. This is--
this is where we first met.
There are few things more
powerful in the universe
than memory and connection.
I am using our
memories of our friends
and closest allies
to keep all of us from
falling out of the speed force.
Wait. What happens
if they fall out?
We'll be consumed
by anti-matter.
I can buy you time, Barry,
but...you need to
get to each of us.
I mean, the speed
force is infinite.
I could never know
where to begin to look.
Remember, Barry,
memories and connections.
You need to consider
our greatest victories,
our most crushing defeats,
the moments when the
bonds between us were forged.
When the bonds were forged.
Now do this, Barry.
Because you have to.
What the--?
Um, hello?
What the hell is this?
I'm asking myself the
same question. literally.
No. This--this
can't be happening.
This--you--what
are you doing here?
Well, I'll tell you
that when you tell me
where...here...is.
Is this cosplay? Oh, do
you want a selfie, bro?
+'m sorry.
-No, no. We're not--no.
I'm also the Flash.
You're also the what?
-The Flash? ~The Flash?
~The Flash. -It's complicated.
+l like your outfit. It seems...comfy.
-l was thinking yours is pretty cool.
-Smooth.
-Seems safe and...
it's breathable.
I'm Barry Allen.
-No! What?
What does that
mean? How can this--
This should be impossible now.
Should be impossible now?
You don't know about the--
Oh, my God. Don't do this to me.
I don't know about the what?
- Are you okay? Oh, my God.
1 told Victor this was possible.
What does this mean?
What do you think you're doing?
What you should
have done the moment
Fleet Feet dropped us off here-
checked out the lay of the land,
looked for hidden dangers.
We are on an alien world.
Any number of chest busters or
predators could be lying in wait.
Don't you capes
ever watch a movie?
You know what? Whatever
it is you're planning,
I'm gonna figure it out, and...
I'm gonna stop you.
I doubt that.
In a contest of mind over
muscle, mind wins every time,
but here.
Let me make it easy for you.
Ask me what I'm up to.
Go ahead.
All right, What
are you up to, Lex?
Universal domination, of course.
Oh, I probably should
have mentioned
that I gave myself
a few upgrades
when I checked The Book
of Destiny out of the library.
What are you doing?
God, I am so tired of
answering that question.
Moving on.
Yeah. The Black Canary.
She tried to shut me up,
but it's not gonna work.
I didn't kill those people.
Yes, I know. Felicity told me.
An impersonator, right?
Hate when that happens.
Five years on a deserted island.
That kind of thing really
changes you, doesn't it?
Must have been
difficult if not impossible
to hold on to your
sanity all those years,
and here you are,
pretending you have
everything in control.
Felicity told you the truth,
and you should
trust her judgment.
How can I do that?
Her perception of
you is clearly clouded
by her emotional attachment.
She's not seeing you
for what you really are.
You have no idea what
this city is up against.
Actually, I think I do,
and I'm gonna stop him.
Who are you?
I want to limit your
involvement in this.
Why? Because I'm an alien?
I also happen to be
your biggest weapon.
You're an unknown quantity,
and this isn't personal.
Except that's
exactly how this feels.
When I--when I
started living this life,
Iwas going up against
human threats alone,
and I could handle that.
Then there were metahumans,
I just discovered that
there are multiple Earths,
and I was brainwashed
aboard an alien spacecraft.
I'm sure that was unnerving.
I don't get unnerved. When I
go up against something new,
I push back.
Right or wrong, it's who I am,
and it's what I do,
so I am asking you
for just a little bit of space
so that I can draw
a line somewhere,
so that I can claw back just
a small sense of normalcy.
I'm afraid we're
well past normal.
J'onn, what are you doing here?
That...is a very long story.
Supergirl?!
Supergirl, please wake up.
Hey. Ryan?
Yeah. I think Lex
pulled a Luthor on us.
On the bright side,
I've never been knocked
unconscious on an alien planet before.
It's pretty much the same as
being knocked unconscious on Earth.
No broken bones. You'll be fine.
Thanks. This definitely makes
me question again why I'm here.
I' haven't got special powers
or, you know, powers.
I'm pretty much the dictionary
definition of unspecial,
and I definitely don't feel
like I'm a Paragon of anything,
let alone Humanity.
Hey--wait.
Are you sure you
guys got the right guy?
You left your family
because someone
you never even met told
you you were needed.
I'd say that makes
you pretty special.
1 don't know about hope,
but you're definitely the
Paragon of Pep Talks.
Years of practice. We
need to catch up to Lex.
How do you know
where he's headed?
Well, before he knocked me out,
he said was looking for
universal domination, so...
Hardly sounds like a newsflash.
The universal part is
new, but if know him,
he's looking to mess
with Novu's experiment,
change history to his advantage.
He really is a selfish
asshat, isn't he?
You really have no idea.
What are you doing?
I'm guessing you haven't
flown on an alien planet either.
I've never flown. No,
but it's okay, Dr. Choi.
You don't have to be nervous.
It's just up, up, and away.
It's over, Deegan!
No. I decide when
the story ends!
Come on, Oliver. Where are you?
Agh!
I wasn't here for this.
Told you you'd catch me.
Thanks for the save.
With a magic arrow, no less.
It's a gift from the Monitor.
- Barry? Hey.
Did you go out shopping
for a new costume
while you were supposed
to be out saving the world?
What? Uh, no. No.
l-it's a crazy, long
story, and you wouldn't
believe me if I told you.
Can I talk to you for a minute?
Please. Excuse us.
Are you okay?
What I'm about to tell you
isn't gonna make any sense,
but...you're not really
h-here right now.
You're actually--
-In the speed force.
I remember. I...
I remember everything.
Okay. Well, in that case...
that arrow... from the Monitor,
1 always felt like
there was something
you weren't telling me.
I didn't want to burden
you with the choice I made.
The choice to do what?
You and Kara, Barry,
you were fated to die
trying to save the world.
Right before you died,
you said you'd given up
everything for me and Kara.
You made some
kind of devil's bargain
with the Monitor to
save us, didn't you?
No. It wasn't a
devil's bargain, Barry,
and I'd make it
again in a second.
It cost you your family, Oliver.
Cost you your life.
Dying's the easy part.
The dead are at peace,
but the real heroes are the ones
who have to keep going.
Go find the others.
Laurel.
Laurel, it's time. It's
time to put her to rest.
What am I supposed
to tell my parents?
My father, he--
he has a bad heart.
He won't live through this.
It should have been me.
She was the true hero.
A hero sets an
example, Laurel...
so follow hers.
Wear the mask.
Be the Canary.
That's how you
keep your sister alive.
Oh, boy.
Engaging quantum portal.
I wouldn't do that.
Xneen?
No.
No, obviously.
Hi. Lex Luthor.
I'm here to make you an
offer won't let you refuse.
How did you get in here?
Our security
protocols are-- A joke,
but the fact that I was able to
circumvent them with astonishing ease
is exactly why you
need to listen to me.
-Xneen?
-Is taking a little nappy time.
Not to worry.
So you are a scientist.
Tell me you're not intrigued
by what I have to say,
or do you get regular visits from
humans with future knowledge?
Speak.
The experiment you're conducting
will not only destroy you
but your planet and your wife.
Another ancient
zealot. lam so sick--
Don't know who they are.
I'm not even from this universe.
What I am from is the future,
so I know exactly how your little
time-jumping experiment will go wrong,
and I am willing to share
my future knowledge with you.
And in return?
Well, I don't cotton to aliens,
but you will soon
have certain abilities
that I will need in
order to deal with some,
shall we say, super problems
popping up in my world.
Ido not have any...abilities.
Stick with me, kid.
So what do you say? Team up?
The brave and the bald?
Who are you?
Hey. Um, this is awkward.
Long story short, you
guys aren't really you guys,
and none of this is
really actually happening.
What are you talk--hey! Hey!
Don't you touch her!
I'm so sorry.
It's a miracle.
Barry? Hey.
‘What's happening? t's
a long, very weird story.
I'll catch you up on the way.
-On the way to where?
You're not taking her anywhere.
I'm sorry. Like I said,
you guys aren't really here.
The speed force?
I can only assume.
We were moving through the
speed force when we were attacked.
Uh, by someone
called... The Anti-Monitor.
Doesn't even sound
like an actual name.
We're all trying to stop him.
We're working together.
The two of you... work together.
I know you don't
trust each other.
Right now, I know you
don't even like each other,
but all that changes.
In fact, we all come to
depend on each other.
We all come to trust each other.
Why are you telling us this now?
This seems to be
a pattern with you.
You don't trust people.
They don't trust you.
Then all of that changes,
and the bond between
you is stronger than iron.
I'm sorry. What's your point?
It's maybe something
I can learn from.
So basically, you
tore a little hole
in the space-time continuum,
opened a doorway into something
called the anti-matter universe.
Matter and anti-matter
cannot coexist.
Hence a lot of bad stuff
happening that we would
just as soon not have happen,
so I think what we need to do is
adjust the Ronstrom coefficient.
Lex, we need to talk.
Mar Novu, do not trust
this man with anything!
Give him a knife for his food,
and no matter how much
he thanks you for the dinner,
he'll stab you right
in the back with it.
Or the front. I'm not choosy.
Last time, you
caught me by surprise.
That's not gonna happen again.
Get Novu outta here.
Come with me, sir, please.
Xneen!
Okay. Listen to me.
Whatever you do, you
can't open that portal.
The hairless one warned me.
No. This isn't a
warning kind of situation.
This is a don't do it at
any...cost kind of situation.
It is my life's work.
Trillions of other
people's lives,
an infinite number,
will be lost if you
go through with it.
It's not worth it.
You just show up
here as if by magic
and demand belief.
The fact I'm here at all should
be enough to convince you.
You are a remarkable individual.
Funny. A new friend of
mine just told me I'm special.
1 didn't believe her until now.
I wonder, is it a double-cross
if I never trusted
you in the first place?
Why do you Kryptonians always
have to take things so personally?
You tried to kill my cousin,
you tried to kill me,
you betrayed Lena,
left her with nothing but a
ruined name and a broken heart.
All I did was
tell her the truth,
something you never
had the courage to do.
Don't take it personally.
Hey! If you would stop
trying to kill each other.
1 got through to Novu.
You just ruined a
perfectly good bad guy plan,
you know that, new guy?
{wind howling]
Where are we?
The anti-matter universe.
At the dawn of time.
We arrived, and he
was already here--
the Anti-Monitor.
That's impossible. 1 got
through to him. I know I did.
Some fates are inescapable.
You spoke to one man
across countless universes,
but within the tapestry
of the multiverse,
there will always
be one Mar Novu
who cannot turn from
his towering ambition,
and in that inevitability,
there is destiny.
Welcome to mine!
All of you,
listen to me.
This is why you were
selected. You're Paragons.
Yeah. I'm still a little unclear
on what all that means.
It means you're powerful enough
to hold the line,
to buy us the time we need.
To do what?
Rebirth the universe.
What, like, a do-over?
The dawn of time is the
only place it can happen.
I'l light the spark,
you fan the flame.
And how do we do that?
You'll know when it's time.
Why do you cosmic types
always have to be so obtuse?
If 1 knew, I'd tell you.
I don't.
All I have is trust.
Do you trust me?
With every cell in my body.
Let's do this.
Die, you creepy shadow things!
That's for Oliver!
Idiots! If anyone's gonna
take over the universe,
it's gonna be me!
ltis too late.
After 10,000 years,
I shall be victorious.
No, you won't be.
Such confidence.
You believe Corrigan
prepared you for this fight.
I believe my entire life
prepared me for this fight.
All life ends.
Only death is eternal.
Only I am eternal.
We'll see about that.
Is this typical for you
guys, saving the world?
Yes!
No!
My team and I
usually mess things up
for the better!
Focus! We're in the
fight of our lives here.
You have failed...
this universe!
We--we did it.
So this is what being
a hero feels like.
Interesting.
Where's Oliver?
There!
Oliver.
What is that?
"I'll light the spark"...
"While you fan the flame."
He said you would
know what to do.
I think dying kind of
messed with his head.
Well, think. You're
meant to be the genius.
A genius who's had the fortitude
to read The Book of
Destiny and retain his sanity.
I think the jury's
still out on that one.
The Book of Destiny.
I made myself the
Paragon of Truth.
What if truth can tell
us what we need to do?
Being what?
Use what's left of the book
to fan the flame.
How do we all use the book?
We focus.
A singular, laser-like focus.
On what?
Humanity,
truth,
love,
destiny,
honor,
courage...
and hope.
No!
Oh, my God!
Oliver! Barry, get us there.
Oliver.
I need both of you to
watch over my family.
Hey, Ollie. They're
gonna be fine, all right?
You're gonna be fine.
You did it.
You all did-- you all did it.
Did what? What did we do?
Just look.
Ollie, we saw, but what is it?
It's the new universe.
It's kind of small
for a universe.
Wait for it, Barry.
It's almost time, almost time.
There. You did it.
No, Ollie, you did it, okay,
and that's why you got
to come back with us,
s0 we need you to hang on, okay?
Sara, this is just what the
Monitor said would happen.
No. What?
There was an end...
and there's a beginning.
You remember what I told you?
Dying is the easy part.
I'm at peace.
The real heroes...
They're the ones who
have to keep going.
So keep...going...
don't ever stop.
This world, this new world...
it needs both of you,
Barry...
An end.
And a beginning.
Thank you, Oliver,
Greg, move your head!