The name
of the island they found me on
is Lian Yu.
It's mandarin for "purgatory."
I've been stranded here for
5 years.
I've dreamt of my rescue every
cold black night since then.
For 5 years, I have had
only one thought, one goal...
survive...
Survive and one day return home.
The island held many dangers.
To live, I had to make myself
more than what I was,
to forge myself into a weapon.
I am returning not the boy who
was shipwrecked
but the man who will bring
justice to those
who have poisoned my city.
My name is Oliver Queen.
Oliver Queen is alive.
The Starling City resident
was found by fishermen
in the North China sea
5 days ago,
5 years after he was missing
and presumed dead
following the accident at sea
which claimed
"The Queen's Gambit."
Queen was a regular
tabloid presence
and a fixture at
the Starling City club scene.
Shortly before
his disappearance,
he was acquitted of assault
charges stemming
from a highly publicized
drunken altercation
with paparazzi.
Queen is the son of Starling
City billionaire Robert Queen,
who was also on board but
now officially confirmed
as deceased.
20% of his body
is covered
in scar tissue.
Second-degree burns
on his back
and arms.
X-rays show at least
12 fractures
that never
properly healed.
Has he said anything
about what happened?
No. He's barely
said anything.
Moira, I'd like
you to prepare yourself.
The Oliver you lost
might not be
the one they found.
Oliver.
Mom.
Oh...
My beautiful boy.
I've got it.
Your room is exactly
as you left it.
I never had the heart
to change a thing.
Oliver.
It's damn good
to see you.
It's Walter...
Walter Steele.
You remember Walter,
your father's friend
from the company.
It's good to see
you, Raisa.
Welcome home, Mr. Oliver.
Mr. Merlyn phoned. He wants
to join you for dinner.
Wonderful.
Oliver?
Did you hear that?
Hey, sis.
I knew it.
I knew you were alive.
I missed you so much.
You were with me
the whole time.
Come on, Laurel. We're
lawyers, not miracle workers.
We can't win this.
If we can't win
a class-action suit
against a man who
swindled
hundreds of people out
of their homes
and life savings,
then we're not fit
to call ourselves
a legal aid office.
And if we
go bankrupt
in the process,
we won't be
a legal aid office.
Hunt has an army of
lawyers, and they're
ready to bury us.
You and I against an army.
I love those odds.
Why do you
hate me?
And in other news,
details
as to the castaway story
you've all heard about...
the son of a very
wealthy billionaire
will soon become
a legendary story.
Jessica now
has more details
and the complete
castaway story.
"The Queen's Gambit" was
last heard from more
than 5 years ago.
Mr. Queen
has reportedly confirmed
he was the only survivor
of the accident
that took the lives of
7 people, including
local resident Sarah Lance.
Survived by her sister,
Laurel...
After 5 years,
everything that was once
familiar is now unrecognizable.
The face I see in the mirror
is a stranger.
The storm's
a category 2.
The captain's
recommending
we head back.
All right.
Inform the crew.
Are we in trouble?
One of us is.
Ollie?
Where do you keep
the bottle opener
on this thing?
I'll be there in
a minute, Sarah.
You know, son,
that is not
going to finish well
for either of them
or for you.
What did I tell you?
Yachts suck.
Tommy Merlyn.
I missed you, buddy.
Ok. What else did
you miss?
Super bowl winners... Giants,
Steelers, Saints, Packers,
Giants again.
A black president,
that's new.
Oh, and "Lost," they
were all dead...
I think.
What was it like there?
Cold.
Tomorrow, you and me,
we're doing the city.
You've got a lot
to catch up on.
That sounds like
a great idea.
Good. Then I was hoping
to swing by the office.
Well, there's
plenty of time for all that.
Queen Consolidated isn't
going anywhere.
Oh, I am
so sorry, Mr. Oliver.
Dude, you speak Russian?
I didn't realize you took
Russian at college, Oliver.
I didn't realize
you wanted to sleep with my
mother, Walter.
I didn't say anything.
She didn't have to.
Oliver...
Walter and I are
married,
and I don't want you
to think
that either one of
us did anything
to disrespect
your father.
We both believed that
Robert, like you, was,
uh, well, gone.
It's fine.
May I be excused?
Hey, don't forget
about tomorrow, buddy.
1, 2, 3.
It's getting closer.
That's not
very scientific.
What would you know
about science,
Mr. Ivy League
dropout?
I happen to know a lot
about science.
I know about
fermentation.
I know biology.
Laurel's gonna kill me.
Oh, she's so gonna kill me.
Your sister
will never know.
Come here.
Ha ha!
Ok, that one was
really close.
Sarah, we're
gonna be fine.
Sarah?
Sarah!
Oliver!
Sarah! Sarah!
Gus?
No! No!
No! Dad, she's out there!
She's not there.
Sarah!
She's gone.
Oliver, wake up. Oliver?
Oliver!
I'm sorry. I'm so...
I'm so sorry.
Oh, it's ok, Oliver.
It's all right,
sweetheart.
You're home.
Where did you
get these?
Roxies. Thank you,
daddy's ACL tear.
Ollie.
No one's called me
that in a while, Speedy.
Worst nickname ever.
What, always chasing
after me as a kid?
I thought it fit
pretty well.
Maybe it still does.
See you at school, Speedy.
Sorry about her.
I have something
for you.
You did not come back
from a deserted island
with a souvenir.
It's a Hozen.
And in buddhism,
it symbolizes
reconnecting.
I kept it in hopes
that one day,
it would reconnect
me with you.
A rock!
That is sweet.
You know, I want
one of those
t-shirts that says
"My friend was
a castaway, and all I got
was this crappy shirt."
Don't let him get you
into too much trouble.
You just got back.
Take it slow.
Ahem.
The city awaits.
Have you noticed how hot
your sister's gotten?
Because I have not.
♪ it's been
a long night... ♪
Your funeral blew.
Did you get lucky?
Fish in a barrel.
They were so sad...
No.
And huggy.
And I am counting
on another target
rich environment
for your welcome
home bash.
At my what?
You came back from
the dead.
This calls for
a party.
You tell me
where and when.
I'll take care
of everything.
And this city's
gone to crap.
Your dad sold
his factory
just in time.
And why'd you want
to drive through
this neighborhood
anyway?
No reason.
So what'd you miss
the most,
steaks at the palm,
drinks at
the station,
meaningless sex?
Laurel.
Everyone is happy
you're alive.
You want to see the
one person who isn't?
Laurel, I just got this
from Hunt's lawyers.
They filed
a change of venue.
We are now in front
of Judge Grell.
Hunt funded Grell's
reelection campaign.
Mm-hmm.
He's got Grell in
his back pocket.
You know, it's fun
being your friend.
I get to say "I told
you so" a lot.
No. Adam Hunt is
not smarter than we are.
No, he's just richer
and willing to commit
multiple felonies.
We don't need to go
outside the law...
"to find justice."
Your dad's favorite
jingle.
Hello, Laurel.
You went to law school.
You said you would.
Yeah. Everyone's proud.
Adam Hunt's
a heavy hitter.
You sure you want to get
in the ring with him?
Five years and you want
to talk about Adam Hunt?
No. Not really.
Why are you here, Ollie?
To apologize.
It was my fault.
I wanted to ask you
not to blame her.
For what?
Falling under your spell.
How could I possibly blame
her for doing the same things
that I did?
I never meant to...
She was my sister.
I couldn't be angry
because she was dead.
I couldn't grieve because
I was so angry.
That's what happens when
your sister dies
while screwing
your boyfriend.
We buried an empty coffin...
Because her body was at
the bottom of the ocean
where you left her.
It should have been you.
I know that it's too
late to say this,
but I'm sorry.
Yeah, I'm sorry, too.
I'd hoped that you'd rot
in hell a whole lot longer
than 5 years.
How did you think that
was gonna go, Tommy?
About like that.
Ok, so we took care
of that. Good call.
Now we can make up
for lost time.
If you're not
too sick of fish,
I suggest we find
some leggy models
and eat Sushi all
day. What do you say?
What're they doing?
What the hell?
Hey!
Here, son. Drink.
What the hell
are you doing?!
That's all
we've got.
If anybody's making it
out of here,
it's gonna be him.
I'm so sorry. I thought
I'd have more time.
I'm not the man you
think I am.
I didn't build
our city.
I failed it.
And I wasn't
the only one.
Mr. Queen.
Mr. Queen!
Did your father
survive that accident?
I ask the questions.
You give me the answers.
Did he make it
to the island?
Did he tell you anything?
Yes, he did.
What did he tell you,
Mr. Queen?
He told me
I'm gonna kill you.
You're delusional.
You're zip-cuffed
to that chair.
Not anymore.
You killed that man.
You don't have
to do this.
Yes, I do.
Nobody can know my secret.
So that's your story.
A guy in a green hood
flew in and single-handedly
took out 3 armed kidnappers.
I mean, who is he?
Why would he do that?
I don't know. Find
him and you can ask.
Yeah. What about you?
You see the hood guy?
I saw...
Just movement.
Everything blurry.
I was kind of out of it.
Yeah.
It's funny, isn't it?
One day back,
and already somebody's
gunning for you.
Aren't you popular?
Were you able
to identify the men?
Scrubbed identities,
untraceable weapons.
These were pros.
Yeah. Well, they
probably figured you'd
pay a king's ransom
to get your boy back
or a Queen's ransom,
as it were.
After all, a parent
would do anything
to keep
their child safe.
I don't find your
tone appropriate, Detective.
If Oliver can think
of anything else,
he'll be in touch.
Thank you,
gentlemen,
for coming.
Your luck never seems
to run out, does it?
You are different.
Not like you to read
a book.
I missed you, Raisa.
No kitchen on
the island.
No. No friends either.
Hey.
Thank you.
Do I really seem different?
No. You're still
a good boy.
Oh, I think we both
know I wasn't.
But a good heart.
I hope so.
I want to be the person you
always told me I could be.
Oliver, I want to
introduce you to someone...
John Diggle.
He'll be accompanying
you from now on.
I don't need a babysitter.
Darling, Oliver's
a grown man.
And if he
doesn't feel he needs
armed protection...
Yeah, I understand,
but this is
something I need.
So...
What do I call you?
Diggle's good.
Dig if you want.
You're ex-military?
Yes, sir.
105th airborne
of of Kandahar,
retired.
Been in
the private sector
a little more than
4 years now.
I don't want there to be
any confusion, Mr. Queen.
My ability to keep
you from harm
will outweigh
your comfort.
Do we have
an agreement?
Sir?
Sir!
The abduction was unexpected.
It forced me
to move up my plans,
but what I told
the police was true.
The man in the green hood
was there in that warehouse,
and he's just beginning.
The suit alleges
that Hunt committed
multiple acts of fraud
and theft
against the city's
underprivileged.
Laurel Lance, an attorney
for the city necessary...
Adam Hunt...
his crimes go deeper
than fraud and theft,
but he's been able to
bully, bribe, or kill anyone
who's gotten into his way.
He hasn't met me yet.
You remind Grell I put
him on the bench,
I can take him off.
I will turn him into
a cautionary tale.
Yes, Mr. Hunt.
And this attorney
Laurel Lance...
you said she wasn't gonna
be a problem anymore.
I told you to fix
that situation.
Why are you
still here?
Unh!
Get in the car!
Hey. You missed.
Unh!
Aah!
Unh! Aah!
What? What?
Just... just tell me
what you want.
You're gonna transfer
$40 million
into Starling City
bank account 1141
by 10 P.M. tomorrow night.
Or what?
Or I'm gonna take it,
and you won't like how.
If I see you again,
you're dead!
He was wearing a hood,
a green hood,
and he had
a bow and arrow.
What, you don't
believe me?
That maniac put two
of my men in the hospital.
Well, thanks
for your statement.
We'll put out an APB
on... Robin Hood.
Hey, pal.
I'm not some grocer who got
taken for his register.
I go to the front
of the line.
Now he said he would be
back here by 10 P.M.
Make sure
you're here first.
You can coordinate with Mr. Drakon,
my new head of security.
All right. Well, uh,
thanks for your time.
It looks like Queen
was telling the truth.
Yeah. Well, there's a first
time for everything.
This hooded guy comes looking
for trouble, he'll find it.
Put on your
seat belt, sir.
Wouldn't want you
to miss your party.
♪ This beat's
for all my freaks ♪
♪ Time to lose my mind ♪
♪ 'cause I work damn hard ♪
♪ So I'll play damn hard ♪
♪ Lost in the night ♪
♪ 'cause I work damn hard ♪
♪ So I'll play damn hard ♪
♪ I, I, I, I work-ork-ork
damn har-har-har-hard ♪
♪ I, I, I, I ♪
Everybody, hey!
Man of the hour!
Whoo! And, ladies, please give
this man a proper homecoming.
♪ We are the champions ♪
Thank you very much,
everybody!
Ollie, Ollie,
Ollie, Ollie.
I missed Tequila!
What the hell's
going on out there?
It's across
the street.
Party for the guy that got
rescued off that island...
Oliver Queen.
Hey. Does he wipe
for you, too?
Now by my rough estimate, you
have not had sex in 1,839 days.
As your wingman,
I highly recommend
Carmen Golden.
Which one is she?
The one who looks like the
chick from "Twilight."
What's "Twilight"?
You're so better off
not knowing.
Back in a minute.
Ollie, hey!
This party is sick.
Who let you
in here?
I believe it was
somebody who said,
"Right this way,
Miss Queen."
Well, you shouldn't
be here.
I'm not 12 anymore.
No. You're 17.
Ollie, I love you,
but you can't come back
here and judge me,
especially for being
just like you.
I know that it couldn't have been
easy for you when I was away...
Away? No. You died.
My brother
and my father died.
I went
to your funerals.
I know.
No, you don't.
Mom had Walter,
and I had no one.
You guys all act
like it's cool,
let's forget about
the last 5 years.
Well, I can't.
For me, it's kind of
permanently in there,
so I'm sorry
if I turned out
some major
disappointment,
but this me is
the best I could do
with what I had
to work with.
Let's bounce.
You have
the fun dip?
Yeah. It's right...
No. I... I must have
dropped it.
Oh! Oh.
You're here.
Tommy. He made the
point that we have
too many years
between us
to leave things the
way we left them.
Is there someplace quieter
that we could go?
Yeah.
I'm sorry about saying that you
should have been the one who died.
That was wrong.
If I could trade places
with her, I would.
About Sarah.
There's something that
I've been afraid to ask,
but I need to know.
Ok.
When she died...
Did she suffer?
Sarah!
Aah!
No.
I think about her
every day.
Me, too.
I guess we still have
one thing in common then.
I can't believe
I'm gonna say this, but...
If you need someone
to talk to
about what happened
to you, I'm here.
Something wrong?
I asked somebody
to do something.
They didn't do it.
Laurel...
You always saw
the best in me.
Right now, that's
what you're doing,
looking at me,
and you're wondering
if that island
changed me somehow,
if it made me
a better person.
It didn't.
Stay away from me.
Otherwise...
I'm just gonna
hurt you again,
but this time,
it will be worse.
Got to roll.
I got 5 years of
debauchery to catch up on
You know what, Oliver?
You're wrong. That
island did change you.
At least now
you're honest.
Something I can
help you with, sir?
I just wanted a second
to myself.
I would believe you,
Mr. Queen,
if you weren't
so full of crap.
Party's this way.
It's locked.
You two cover
the elevator.
Hang back and be ready.
Stay in the corners
and stay alert.
It's past 10:00.
He's never getting
in here.
All's clear.
Yeah.
Unh!
You missed.
Really?
Hunh!
He's here!
All units, converge!
Aigh!
Go right, go right.
On me.
Lay down your weapons,
or we will open fire!
I repeat, lay down
your weapons.
Tell me
you saw that.
Ok. Let's go. Move.
♪ Girls, girls, girls ♪
♪ Hot babes ♪
Cut it.
Search the building
roof to basement.
Find him!
Starling City police!
The party's over, kids.
Oh, Mr. Merlyn. Imagine my
shock at finding you here.
Did you roofie anyone
special tonight, huh?
Detective!
It's a private party.
Yeah? Well, there was an incident
at Adam Hunt's building tonight.
You know anything
about that?
Who's Adam Hunt?
He's a millionaire bottom feeder, and I'm
kind of surprised you aren't friends.
I've been out of town
for... a while.
Yeah. Well, he just got attacked
by the guy with the hood,
the guy that saved
your ass the other day.
The hood guy.
You didn't find him?
I'm gonna offer
a reward.
Hey, everybody.
$2 million to anybody
that can find a nut bar
in a green hood.
Did you even try
to save her?
Ok. Let's go, partner.
Did you even try
to save my daughter?
Sarah wouldn't want this.
It's not.
Partner, let's go.
It's all right.
Let's go.
It's way too quiet
in here!
This is a party!
Some coincidence, I mean, you
asking to have your party here,
and Hunt getting robbed
right next door
and by the same guy who
rescued us at the warehouse.
If I were you,
Tommy,
I'd just be glad
you're alive.
What happened to you
on that island?
A lot.
What the hell
are you talking about?
$40 million doesn't
just up and vanish!
Untraceable?!
It is $40 million!
Find it!
How did he do it?
There's not enough
for all of us.
Save your strength.
You can survive
this, make it home,
make it better,
right my wrongs,
but you got to live
through this first.
You hear me, Ollie?
You hear me, son?
Just rest, dad.
No.
Dad?!
Survive.
No!
If hypothetically
$50,000 magically appeared
in your bank account,
it might be best
for you not to
speak about it...
To anyone... Ever.
God bless you, too.
I just got a very
grateful phone call
from one of our clients
against Adam Hunt.
Me, too. Heh.
It looks like Starling
City has a guardian angel.
By the way, your
cute friend's here.
You left the party
pretty quick last night,
even after I made sure the bar
was stocked with Pinot Noir.
It wasn't really
my scene.
I thought maybe you and Oliver
went mano-a-mano again.
I saw you two
head out.
There's nothing between
Oliver and I, not anymore.
Here I thought the only thing
between you and Oliver was us.
I wouldn't exactly characterize
us as an "us," Tommy.
Then what would
you call it?
A lapse.
That's quite
a few lapses...
your place,
my place,
my place again.
Oh, come on, Merlyn. We
both know that you're not
a one-girl type of guy.
Depends on the girl.
I have to go
back to work.
Dinah Laurel Lance always
trying to save the world.
Hey. If I don't try
and save it, who will?
♪ Let's get out of here ♪
♪ won't you come along? ♪
She says the island changed me.
She has no idea how much.
There are many more names
on the list,
those who rule my city
through intimidation and fear.
Every last one of them will
wish I had died on that island.
The police failed to identify the
men I hired to kidnap Oliver,
and they never will.
Should we arrange
another abduction?
No.
There are other ways of finding
out what my son knows.
Original Sync & Corrections by GeirDM for addic7ed
ReSync by www.SubtitleReSync.com