Last season on "arrow"...
This city still
needs saving.
Not by the hood.
It needs a hero.
If you survive a crucible,
you grow the stronger for it.
This is to remind you of that.
Welcome aboard.
Nyssa: Sara swore
her allegiance
To the league
of assassins.
You agreed to go back?
Laurel: She'll be ok.
Lance: Yeah,
I know she'll be ok,
But ok what is what
bothers me. [grunts]
Dad? Dad!
Slade's whole plan
was to take everything
from me. He did.
Slade took Laurel
because he wants
to kill the woman I love.
So?
So he took
the wrong woman.
I love you.
Do you understand?
[both grunting]
The five years that I was gone,
I wasn't always on the island.
My name is Amanda
Waller, Mr. Queen.
Welcome
to Hong Kong.
[Oliver grunting
and gasping]
Oliver: Got him.
Coming up 52nd street,
heading east.
Copy that. Or is it roger?
I never know the difference.
John, there's an illegal
shipment of RPGs
headed your way.
Roger. I'm on it.
Oh, so it is roger.
RPGs are secure.
I've got eyes on.
Roy!
We're coming to you.
[tires squealing]
[thunder]
Vincent steel grave...
You have failed this city.
[sirens in distance]
The arrow just
took down another
One of the city's
most wanted,
And there's
no denying that
the city's crime rate
Has plummeted
in the past
five months.
You're welcome.
But so has its unemployment
rate and its population.
We have experienced
two terrorist attacks
in as many years.
Starling city is dying,
and a prison full of criminals--
Take another
off the board.
We keep this up,
there will only be
two types of criminals
Left in starling city--
the ones we put away
And the ones that
are running scared.
What's that?
A fern.
It thrives
on the light.
I thought
since you were
living here now,
The place could do
with a little
sprucing.
I let you buy me a bed.
You were sleeping
on the floor.
[phone vibrates]
Another text
from Thea.
Where is she now?
Amalfi coast.
I keep telling her
to send photos.
I'm going to go
do a patrol,
clear my head.
Hey.
You did really
good tonight.
I'm going
to head out, too.
I have to pull
an early shift
at work today,
Which may or may not be
the most depressing
thing I've ever said.
But we're still on
for tomorrow night?
Absolutely.
I am going to turn you
Into corporate
master of the universe.
Those board members
are going to be begging
To sell queen consolidated
back to you and your backers.
I'm going
to roll out, too.
Lyla has me trying to build
the bassinet from hell.
That reminds me...
I figured since you and Lyla
are having a girl...
Man, you cannot
afford this.
I can't afford anything,
which is why I made it.
Arrowheads, one
of the few things
that I can make.
Well,
it's beautiful.
Thank you.
Congratulations, John.
And not just on the baby.
You and Lyla are happy.
Well, you know,
you should try it
some time.
Last girlfriend, she's in
the league of assassins.
My girlfriend before that,
she shot my girlfriend
before that.
I'm not...Not exactly
a catch at the moment.
Maybe Felicity will
change all that.
It's...It's not the right time.
Things are as good now
as ever will be, Oliver.
And you love her.
You even told her so.
I was trying to fool Slade.
Yes.
Except now the only
person you're
fooling is yourself.
Thanks again.
[horns honking]
[dialing]
[gunshot]
[crowd screaming]
[all screaming]
[both grunting]
[speaking Chinese]
I told you,
I don't speak
Chinese!
And I told you,
you try to escape again,
I beat you senseless.
[sirens in distance]
Steelgrave took
a plea for 15 to 20.
His lawyer folded
like a deck chair
After I hit him with
the evidence that
the arrow gathered.
Good work.
You catch 'em,
I cook 'em.
Did I say that
too loud?
No, you're fine.
Did you ever think
that we'd end up as
business partners?
Is that why you invited me
down here, Laurel?
To see mr. Steelgrave
sent off into his new life?
No.
I have a surprise
for you.
What's your dad doing here?
You'll see.
I'll be right back.
Mm-hmm.
Dad.
Hey.
Hi. How are you?
Uh, well, if they had
told me press conferences
came with a promotion,
I would tell them I prefer
getting shot at.
Good thing your doctors
Didn't give you
a choice, then.
You know, you could
try to hide the fact
That you're glad I can't
get out in the field anymore.
I can't hide
that I'm glad
that you're safe.
What's all this?
Your surprise.
[microphone feedback]
Lance: Uh, thank you
all--ahem, excuse me,
thank you for coming.
Five months ago,
this city was under siege.
And the scpd rallied
behind a man in a hood.
Well, I ended up
with a captain's rank,
And he didn't even
get a thank you.
But today, he does.
'cause today,
the starling city
police department
Is formally recognizing
the individual
Known as the arrow.
And I'm using
my new position
To disband
the anti-vigilante
task force
Charged
with capturing him.
Thank you.
Now make no mistake--
vigilantism will
never be tolerated.
But I refuse to hunt,
in the name of this city,
The hero who saved it.
Shut that crap off.
Less heat on the arrow
Means more heat on us.
And the atf now
has our shipment
of grenade launchers.
They got our
shipment already?
What are we paying
bribes to the cops for?
We have a more
pressing concern.
Lack of leadership.
I nominate myself.
Any objections?
Yeah, a few.
Oh, illuminate me.
Where do I start?
It's not just that
you talk funny.
You don't know
the first thing
about business.
You're just a low level
street dealer, a pill pusher.
Oh, those pills I push?
Are known as vertigo.
In the wake
of the count,
I tinkered some
with his formula,
Introduced
an additive produced
by certain mushrooms.
My vertigo
reveals the face
Of your greatest fear.
[growls]
As I was saying...
Lack of leadership.
I nominate myself.
Any objections?
Our course of action
is straight as an arrow.
Gentlemen...
We're going
to kill him.
Hey, hey!
How was work?
"it" is not work.
It is a soul crushing
exercise in misery
That offers health and dental.
Suffice it to say,
I am highly motivated
to help convince the board
to sell you back the company.
Unfortunately, you don't
really have the qualifications
to run queen consolidated,
But what you do have
is passion.
You care about the company
and the people that work there.
That's what you have
to get across to them.
You got to speak
from the heart.
Felicity...
Would you like
to go out to
dinner with me?
I'm being serious here, Oliver.
So am I.
I don't want to read...
Too much into this,
But are you asking me
out on a date?
Like an actual date?
Like a...Date-date?
Su--I mean,
the implication
being with dinner
That you...
Usually I'm the one
Talking in sentence fragments.
[chuckles]
Would you like to go
to dinner with me?
Yes.
Oliver: Go.
Kelvin nico just knocked
over a liquor store.
Nico's in steelgrave's crew.
Send his photo to Roy.
Get me Felicity.
You got it.
Felicity: I can't
talk right now.
I'm at work.
Could I ask you guys
just to wait one moment?
Someone's calling
for tech support.
Oh, you are going to get me
so incredibly fired.
Okay, I am hacked into
the city's database.
I am running
Facial recognition...Now.
Oliver: Do you like Italian?
What?
For tonight.
You like Italian, right?
Everyone likes Italian.
Oliver, you're in the middle
of a high speed chase.
I'm multitasking.
I got him.
He's in the sewer.
I'm picking up his cell phone
underneath. He's at the corner
Of grand and ames.
And yes, I love Italian.
Detective Lance--
captain Lance--
is also in pursuit.
You are welcome.
I have to go.
The arrow:
Detective...Thank you.
You had it handled.
For what you said today.
I wish I could do more.
You've already done
more than enough.
I've got to go.
Some place
I have to be.
You got a hot date
or something?
Amanda: So this morning
Makes how many
escape attempts
in the last five months?
Nine.
What we have here
is a failure to reach
an understanding.
[exhales]
go to hell.
So this is my reward
from saving you from drowning
In that freighter
off the coast of Lian Yu?
Yeah.
Why'd you do that?
That's need
to know.
Suffice it to say,
I have need of a man
of your capacity.
I don't care.
I don't care
about anything
except going home.
And you should know that.
You should know
that I will never stop
Trying to escape.
And you should know
that it's extremely
easy to kill someone
The world already
thinks is dead.
Kill me, then.
I don't care.
We're going
to have to try this
another way, then.
Hi. Thank you for waiting.
Ah, no problem.
I just want
to buy this.
This is a satellite frequency
communicator tx40.
Yeah,
I'm trying to breach
a torsecured firewall
And I need
something to help me
Piggyback off
a keyhole hexagon
satellite, so...
I did that once.
Hacked a public
wi-fi signal,
Piggybacked using
crowd-sourced
stealth processing.
Huh.
You're Felicity Smoak.
Formerly of queen
consolidated.
Do you mind if I
ask you something--
why are you here?
How do you know who I am?
I know a guy
who might be
interested
In hiring someone
with your expertise.
I'm not actually...Looking
for a new job right now.
God help me.
But I can help you buy this.
Unless I can't.
I mean, I shouldn't.
You shouldn't buy this.
Ok. Clearly
you don't understand
How this whole
sales thing works.
The next gen model,
the tx50, comes out
in a few months.
I got to touch
one last year.
Pure bliss.
And if you
want to breach
tor-level security,
You should really
deploy a remote
administration tool.
I have a good one.
Here's the url.
Thanks.
Happy hacking.
I certainly hope so.
False alarm.
Are you sure?
These contractions...
Just braxton-hicks. You're not
even four centimeters dilated.
I feel like an m1-a1.
It's a tank.
Think a big, big tank.
You did the right
thing coming in.
You don't want
your husband--
Boyfriend.
Ex-husband.
To be delivering
the baby on the side
of the freeway.
You can
get dressed now.
All right.
[exhales]
Are you ok?
Yeah, yeah, I'm not
the one that's nine
months pregnant.
You look a little scared.
Honey, please,
I've thrown down
with the taliban,
Malcolm merlyn,
and a host
Of mirakuru-powered
human weapons.
I'm terrified.
[both laugh]
Queen, party of two.
Hi.
Hi. [chuckles]
[chuckles]
What?
Nothing.
I'm just--
nervous?
Yeah.
Line forms behind me.
Scotch. Neat.
Just the water
for me, thanks.
Are you--are you sure?
The booze might sort of
help with the whole--
The alcohol is not
going to mix well with
the three benzos I took.
Am I being crazy?
I mean, what do we have
to be nervous about?
Well, we've already
exhausted every topic
That one would
normally talk about
on a first date
And a second date
and a third date,
And every date,
actually,
And I've already
seen you shirtless.
Multiple times.
Shirtless,
all the time.
Thank you.
There are still a few things
that you don't know about me.
Please. Name one.
The five years that
I was away...
I wasn't always on Lian Yu.
I thought so.
Where were you?
Hong Kong...For one.
And I have been thinking
a lot recently about...
My time there.
The choices
that I had to make.
Those years sound
like they were full
of a whole lot of suck.
I'm sorry.
I'm just a little
out of my element.
The entire time
that I was gone,
I could never...
Completely trust someone.
And when that
goes on for so long,
You stop...
Seeing people for people.
You see...
Threats.
Or targets.
And when I decided
to come home, I...
I just didn't know
how to turn that
part of me off.
Then I walked
into your office.
You were the first person
that I could see as a...
A person.
There was just
something about you.
Oh, yeah, I was
chewing on a pen.
It was red.
[beeping]
GPS shows him
in the restaurant.
The arrow's
definitely in there.
If we're going
to find him, we got
to get in close.
We're close enough.
Do you remember when I told you
that because of what we do,
I didn't think that
I could be with someone
that I...
That I could
really care about?
Yeah, I remember.
So maybe I was wrong.
[whistles]
Oliver, are you--
[grenade fires]
Ollie--
[explosion]
[patrons screaming and crying]
Is she ok?
She's just knocked out.
Saw it all over the news,
police and fire
are on the scene.
Yeah, I didn't think
it was the best idea
To stick around
and answer questions.
You don't think you
and an explosion
At the same place
is a coincidence?
Hey, check this out.
It's a GPS.
I found it
on your jacket.
It's wasted now.
You took out one
of steel graves' crew
earlier tonight.
It was a set up
So they could plant
that thing on me.
Oliver, I know
what you're thinking.
No, you don't.
Listen, I'm not other people.
I know exactly what's
going on in your head,
and you are wrong.
Diggle, somebody
put a tracer on me
and I don't notice?
The only explanation...
I lost my focus.
[dialing]
The arrow: Detective.
The person we took down earlier
Is working
with whoever's responsible
for tonight's explosion.
Another one
of steel grave's
crew, I'm guessing.
Well, I need to know
who's at the top of
that organization now.
And where I can find him.
I'm on it.
[gasps]
Hey, hey, hey,
you're safe.
You're safe. I'm here.
[footsteps]
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
I'm on your side!
Got this handled, detective.
These guys
blew up a building.
You think
I'm sitting this out?
Suspect's name
is Werner Zytle.
He's a real head case.
Keep your head
on a swivel, then.
[footsteps]
I'm Werner Zytle.
Ahh!
You can call me vertigo.
The Count's dead!
Some things never die.
You, for example.
It's frustrating.
Just means I have to try
a little bit harder.
[both grunting]
Ahh!
The count might
be dead, true...
But his glorious
narcotic lives on--
With a few enhancements
That will reveal to you
your greatest fear.
Like gazing
upon truth itself.
[both grunting]
[gunshot]
Get away from him
or get put down!
[groans]
No...No!
[beep]
[voice disguised]
Felicity, call an ambuLance!
Are you ok?
That was a pretty
strong psychotropic
Werner hit you with.
[clears throat] how's
detective Lance's condition?
Stable. He's at
starling general.
I hacked
the paramedic radio.
He had a coronary
artery spasm
Treatable with
medication.
He'll be fine.
How are you?
Believe it or not,
I have had worse
first dates.
Hit the streets.
Werner's agenda
can't stop with me.
I need to know
what he has planned.
On it.
I'll back
him up.
Roy's got it.
Go home to Lyla.
Oliver...
If this is about
what happened, man,
Risk is part
of the job.
Diggle. It's just
intel gathering.
Roy can handle it.
I know we need to talk.
About our dinner
or our dinner
getting blown up?
Both.
It's ok.
We'll talk about it
after we catch this guy.
But maybe we should
reschedule the board meeting.
It's in less
than an hour.
I've got this.
[speaking Japanese]
[groans]
When are people
going to realize that
I don't speak Chinese?
Japanese.
You speak English?
Better than
you speak Chinese.
Where am I?
Our home.
Mine and my
husband's.
Your husband?
Welcome to my home.
Dinner?
[sighs]
[monitor beeping]
I got to warn you,
the doctors told me
not to get yelled at.
Well, it's a good thing
you don't care about
Your doctor's
instructions, then,
Since you're still
going out in the field.
Do you know what an advanced
healthcare directive is?
It's what they ask for
when you're going
to die, dad.
The night Sara left,
The night
you collapsed,
The e.R.
Doctor asked me
if you had one.
[sighs]
I'm sorry, Laurel,
I really am.
I'm sorry, sweetheart.
Then why do you keep
pushing yourself
like this?
I don't know how.
I've been a cop since
before you and your sister
were born. It's all I know.
If I'm not a cop...
What am I?
You're my father.
And I need you.
And I just spoke
to ned foster.
He said the board is primed.
You just have to go
in there and wow them.
Which I am pretty sure
is a business term.
I'm afraid we have a situation.
Apparently there's another
bidder for the company.
Really? Who?
Ray palmer.
Nice to meet you.
Love your company.
Nice to see you again,
miss Smoak.
You two know
each other?
So sorry I am late.
Heh, traffic was terrible.
Which is why I took
my helicopter.
I parked on your roof.
I hope that's ok.
You guys validate, right?
Oh, frack.
Two years ago,
the people of starling city
Thought I was dead.
I came back.
And so can
queen consolidated.
With starling national
bank's new investment,
We can take qc
out of receivership
and into the future.
I mean,
this company's my family.
And as my mother
always said...
There is nothing
more important
to me than family.
Thank you.
[inhales,
exhales]
That was
a good speech.
Hard to top.
[exhales]
Thank you all
for coming out today.
I promise to be brief,
if not a little
entertaining.
Ahh. Oh, that's one
of my new smart watches.
I'm very proud of those.
You like it,
it works for you?
Yeah, good. Anyway.
Science. Numbers.
These numbers show
qc's performance
Under mr. Queen's
management.
I'm using that term
extremely, b-t-w.
Also b-t-w,
these numbers
Aren't sanitized
for wall street.
This is raw
information
From your company's
own servers.
How did he get into
our computers?
Something tells me
he deployed a remote
administration tool.
But the truth is,
This company's woes
are a symptom of
a much larger problem.
And that problem
is starling city.
Queen consolidated
can't hope to survive
If the city
it's located in is dying.
Guess what? It is.
Nobody wants
to live here anymore.
[chuckles] and after
two terrorist attacks,
Who can blame them?
This city
still needs saving.
And that is my vision
for this company.
To not only see it
rise from the ashes,
But to take this city with it
to that new horizon.
And that new day has a name.
[applause]
Oliver!
I'm sorry.
I really thought
it was going
to go our way.
So did I. But maybe
the company's better off
with dr. Palmer.
I couldn't make time
for qc last year,
And trying to get
the company back now,
it's selfish.
That's something
that the old me
would have done.
And if the past 12 hours
have reminded me of anything,
It's that two years ago,
I made the decision
to put Oliver queen aside
And be the arrow.
It's not a choice
I get to unmake.
Last night
at the restaurant,
you didn't feel that way.
Look what happened,
Felicity.
Oliver! The explosion
wasn't your fault.
When Werner hit me
with the vertigo dart,
He told me
that his formula,
It shows us
our worst fear.
And I saw myself.
You don't really think
you're afraid of
yourself, do you?
I think I'm scared
of what would happen
If I let myself
be Oliver queen.
What did we find out?
You know how we've got
the number of crime bosses
In starling city
down to three?
Well, this new guy, Werner,
he wants to make it zero.
Diggle: Take out
the competition.
Mikhail petrov,
luciano costa,
shintawa shimosawa.
What are their
locations?
I'm not getting anything
off of last known addresses.
Werner could be
moving these guys
right now.
I'm going as fast as I can!
It's not like these guys
Walk around with little GPS
attached to them.
Unless they do.
Petrov, costa, shimosawa,
They're all on parole
or out on bail.
Ankle monitors.
Can't be right.
They're all in
the same location.
Rockets arena.
The heavyweight
title fight's tonight.
That's like Christmas
for crime bosses.
There'll be like
20,000 people there.
He was willing
to blow up a restaurant
to take down one man.
He'll blow up a stadium
to take down three.
Yeah, but an RPG won't do it.
I need you looking
For a large explosive device.
Roy...Suit up.
Where do you
want me?
Here.
I can't have you
in the field anymore.
Really?
What changed?
You're going to be a father.
[chuckles] Oliver,
you've known for
The past five months
I was going to be
a father.
So I ask you again--
What changed?
I have.
My risks can't be your risks.
That...Diggle,
you have a life.
You have a new life, it's...
Life I can't have.
I get it.
You and Felicity
were in an explosion.
People died, either one
of you could have.
But you didn't.
You can't let that
shake you, man.
Detective Lance is laying
in hospital bed right now
Because I let him--
wait, wait, wait!
Lance is his own man who
makes his own decisions,
And so am I.
Not this one.
Oliver, I've given
the last two years
Of my life
to your crusade.
I don't know what
that's supposed
to earn me,
But it earns me
at least the right
to make my own choices.
No, it doesn't--
damn it, Oliver,
You would be dead
Ten times over
if it wasn't for me!
You're right.
But this is my crusade,
Which makes this my decision.
[crowd cheering]
[whistling]
Five minute timer.
Come on!
What are you
waiting for?
[grunting and groaning]
My partner.
[beep]
Go.
Felicity: I've isolated
a frequency spike
Consistent with
an incendiary device.
It's in the maintenance tunnel
underneath the stands.
I'll get the bomb.
Get the son
of a bitch.
Back for more?
It's as if you've
developed an addiction
To vertigo.
[distorted voices]
I've made my choice.
[both grunting]
Felicity,
we're running
out of time here.
Ok. From your description,
It sounds like
a collapsible
circuit design.
Roy: Felicity...
Cut the yellow wire.
There is no
yellow wire.
Ok, new plan.
Look above you,
there should be
insulated piping
Pumping the arena's ac system.
They're pumping freon.
You want to break one off,
aim it at the bomb.
You're going
to freeze the thing.
[both grunting]
Roy: It's not working!
[grunting]
Don't look so surprised.
I haven't been gone that long.
Lock me down,
it doesn't matter.
There will always
be a vertigo,
Always someone to
pick up the mantle.
You have given it
the power.
Don't you see?
You look well.
How's Nanda Parbat?
Hot.
It's good
to see you.
You've been missed.
I was on my way
to see Laurel,
Picked up
your radio chatter.
You should tell
Felicity mix up her
frequencies a bit.
That's a good tip.
And is this permanent,
you being back?
I hope so.
We'll see.
How are you doing?
I'm...Working
through a few things.
Word of advice?
We're not our masks.
And we need people in our
lives who don't wear one.
Hey.
What are you
doing here?
And the answer
better not be
stalking me.
Well, that depends
on whether you consider
Pinging your phone's GPS
stalking. Ok, guilty.
But you know how I know a guy
who would be interested
In hiring someone
with your expertise?
Yeah, turns out
I could really use it.
Seems somebody hacked
my cell phone and my laptop
And my desktop.
Gee, that's too bad.
All my data's been
replaced by audio files
of porcupine flatulence.
And so I was hoping
that whoever did it
Might be willing
to undo it
If I apologized
for misleading them
in any way.
That would probably work.
Oh, unless, of course,
you did all that
To steal that person's
friend's company,
In which case I would suggest
getting used to the sound
Of spiky rodents farting.
I didn't steal anything!
Ok, maybe a little,
but as it turns out,
I didn't even need the data.
I mean, you saw the speech.
It was a pretty good speech.
My friends
just had a baby,
So if you don't mind,
there's another slimy little
human that needs my attention.
Oh, and b-t-w,
Might want to check
your tablet while
you're at it.
[chuckles]
Hey.
Hi.
Oh, she is scrumptious!
Mazel tov, guys, seriously.
Diggle: Thank you.
I can come back.
No, Oliver, come in.
Oh, she's perfect.
Congratulations.
Thank you, Oliver.
For what?
For being right.
[inhales, exhales]
The second I looked at her...
Everything changed.
The whole universe...
Changed.
You were right.
How do I get
out of here?
You can't leave.
[scoffs] well,
why don't you
try to stop me?
You've already learned I can.
Repeatedly.
Amanda waller wants you
working for her,
And she will have her way.
Yeah, well,
too bad for her.
I'd rather die.
Which is why it's not
your life she's threatening.
I am to be responsible for you.
She's found the proper way
to motivate me.
Akio.
She's threatened my family.
She'll kill them
if I let you go.
My father had a proverb
he was once fond of.
A man cannot live
by two names.
And what does that mean?
In your case...
I believe it means
not having any choice.
Ahh. They look
really happy.
She's beautiful.
She is.
We need to talk.
I don't want
to talk.
Which for me,
I know, is a little
unprecedented.
But...[sighs]
As soon as we talk,
it's over.
I'm so sorry.
I thought that I could be me
And the arrow...
But I can't.
Not now.
Maybe not ever.
Then say never.
Stop...
Dangling maybes.
Say it's never
going to work out
between us.
Say you never
loved me, say you--
Felicity...
Don't ask me
to say that
I don't love you.
I told you as soon
as we talked...
It would be over.
[cell phone vibrates]
Hello?
It's barry.
Barry allen.
I woke up.
I could use some advice.
I'll be right there.
And here I thought
that you used up
All of your league
of assassin vacation days.
[laughs]
You look great.
How's dad doing?
The same.
Seeing you will help.
I don't want him
to know I'm in town,
Not just yet.
You don't want him
to know you're in town,
Or you don't want him
to know why?
Both.
This life, it...
It's complicated.
We didn't want you
to choose it.
Not for us.
I know.
I chose it for me.
[cell phone buzzes]
The arrow--
Oliver--
Busted someone who tried
to blow up rockets arena.
And my boss wants me
to head to the station
To backstop the interrogation.
Laurel Lance.
Always trying
to save the world.
Runs in the family.
Love you.
Man: Hello, Sara.
What are you
doing here?
Oh! No!
No! Sara!
Sara!
No, no!
[sobbing]
Please!