Yeah, Dad, college is great.
No. Me and my new roommate
totally hit it off.
We're like besties.
Okay. Yeah, Dad,
I gotta get back to Chem Lab.
Yes. It looks like I got
a long night ahead of me.
-[WHISPERS] Get off the...
-Okay. Love you, Dad. Bye.
[GIGGLES]
Ollie, you are trouble.
[IN NORMAL VOICE]
How is Detective Lance?
He's clueless, as usual.
Guess I was thirsty.
[THUNDER CRASHES]
Did you hear that?
One, two, three...
[THUNDER CRASHES]
It's getting closer.
That's not very scientific.
And what would you know about science,
Mr. Ivy-League-Dropout?
I happen to know a lot about science.
I know of fermentation.
I know biology.
Laurel's gonna kill me.
She's so gonna kill me.
Your sister will never know.
-Come here.
-Ha, ha.
[THUNDER CRASHES]
Okay, that one was really close.
Sara...
...we're gonna be fine.
[BOTH SCREAM THEN GRUNT]
Oliver...
-Oliver!
-Sara!
[SARA SCREAMS]
Help!
OLIVER:
Sara!
Oliver!
[GASPS]
[MAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY ON TV]
[DOOR OPENS]
OLIVER:
Can't sleep?
I don't do well with my eyes closed.
Thanks for letting me stay here.
I know you got a lot going on with your mom.
Thea's mostly staying at her boyfriend's...
...so don't worry about anyone
finding out you're back.
Thanks for understanding.
I don't understand.
Not a day goes by
that your family doesn't miss you.
Yeah? How do you know?
Because I missed you.
Probably they won't be as happy
to see me as you think.
How can you say that?
I know how hard it is to come home
when you've been gone for so long.
I'm guessing my father and Laurel
weren't too happy to see you.
No.
No, not at first.
I wasn't sure if you and she
ever got back together.
We tried.
It was too much.
Yeah, some things, you know,
just better left in the past.
I'm done waiting for Mr. Queen. Let's start.
[DOOR OPENS]
Sorry I'm late. There's an old friend in town.
I just explained to your mother and sister...
...that Ms. Lance will be sitting
for the prosecution.
This is a conflict of interest. Ms. Lance
practically grew up in the Queen house.
You overstate matters.
JEAN: We'll see when I move
to conflict Ms. Lance off this case.
Maybe there won't be a case much longer.
I come here not just with Ms. Lance
but also a plea offer.
Life, with a possibility of parole.
Heh. No. We are not pleading out.
Mrs. Queen is innocent.
She aided and abetted 503 homicides.
Under duress from a homicidal maniac
named Malcolm Merlyn.
She also withdrew from the criminal
conspiracy prior to its execution.
Five minutes prior.
With Malcolm Merlyn dead,
the jury will wanna blame someone.
Without the deal,
she'll face the death penalty.
Sounds a lot like blackmail.
Try reality. And here's some more.
We've subpoenaed over a decade's worth
of phone messages, records, letters, e-mails.
I'm willing to bet I find something
that crushes your duress defense to powder.
Mr. Donner...
...if you don't mind,
I'd like a few days to consider your offer.
Of course.
Excuse me.
I'll be right back.
Laurel?
I'll meet you at the car.
You're prosecuting my mother?
I didn't ask for this case. I was assigned.
-So say no.
-It's a new job, Oliver.
I don't have a lot of pull.
And what pull I do have,
I used to get that plea bargain for your mother.
This was your idea?
Life in prison?
The DA is serious
about the death penalty, Ollie.
We both know what it's like
to lose someone.
So think about it,
and save your mother's life.
Are you okay?
In case I wasn't clear last week...
...I'm done answering that question.
[CHIRPING]
Help!
Over here!
[GASPING]
[HORN BLARING]
OLIVER:
Sara?
Sara.
You okay?
-How'd everything go with your mother?
-I ran into your sister.
She's working on the case.
-You didn't tell her?
-No.
I know a little something
about keeping secrets.
And respecting them, even though I don't
totally understand why you're keeping yours.
Is this...?
Is it because of what happened
on the island?
No.
After.
There were things that I did...
...things that I had to do to survive.
Things that there's no forgiveness for.
Well, that's the thing about forgiveness.
You can't get it until you ask for it.
Merlyn?
[ALL GRUNTING]
Who are you?
Just a warrior, like you.
Why are you dressed
like Malcolm Merlyn?
Huh? Who sent you?
I remember the first time I saw this hood.
Shado was wearing it.
This is quite the setup that you got here.
Launching your one-man war for Starling.
I'm not one man.
These are my friends.
This is John Diggle and Felicity Smoak.
-Guys, this is Sara.
-Welcome home, Sara.
I was happy to hear
you're not dead anymore.
I mean, I didn't know you
before you didn't die the first time.
-I'm still glad you're alive.
-You're cute.
We just had an uninvited guest
in the mansion.
Trained.
Highly skilled.
And he was dressed like Merlyn.
Malcolm Merlyn is dead,
courtesy of an arrow jammed through his heart.
It wasn't him. It was a follower,
an underling bent on revenge.
Whoever it was, he knows who I am.
-Gee, I didn't get you a bag of dirt.
OLIVER: Copycat Merlyn tracked it in the house.
Analyze it. Hopefully, it will lead me to him.
-Then what?
-If he wants to follow Malcolm Merlyn so bad...
...he can follow him right into a grave.
Sara, we'll find this guy.
I don't want you to.
-What do you mean?
-He wasn't after you, Ollie.
He's after me.
Who is he?
He's called Al Ow-Al. The First.
He's a member of the League of Assassins.
DIGGLE: Wait, wait. League of Assassins?
I thought they were a myth.
What's the League of Assassins? Please,
don't say it's a league made up of assassins.
I heard about them in Afghanistan
from a tribal leader.
He claimed there was
an ancient sect of assassins...
...deadly warriors that killed
and vanished like ghosts.
Thought he was smoking
what he was selling.
I tried to tell you, Ollie,
but you wouldn't listen.
That's where you've been
the past four years.
That's where you learned to fight.
You're one of them.
After the freighter, a member of the league
rescued me, took me in...
...and brought me to Nanda Parbat.
They remade me into what I am.
And I swore them my allegiance.
Why are they kicking down doors
trying to find you now?
Because I left.
And there's only one way
that you leave the league.
Is that why you didn't
wanna see your family?
A year ago, I was in Guyana.
I was sent there for a man named Suarez.
He was a local diplomat.
And I slit his throat in his bed.
And his kids...
They found his body in the morning.
I'm a murderer, Ollie.
You think that my family
will be happy to see me?
[CELL PHONE CHIMES]
I have to go to Iron Heights.
Felicity, I need you to find this Al Ow-Al.
Thank you. Thank you.
What were you doing out there?
The boat that I was on,
we got caught in a storm, and...
-Come.
-Wait. Wait, wait.
Wait.
Robert Queen.
Robert Queen, it was his boat. And they're rich.
He'll pay you whatever you want. Please.
[SARA WHIMPERING]
Who are these people?
Please, no!
Please, don't. No, you've made a mistake.
Please let me out.
Wait, why won't you let me...?
No! Please come back!
Let me out!
THEA:
You cannot be serious.
-What's going on?
-She wants to take the deal.
-Mom, if this is about the death penalty...
-I've been explaining to your mother.
Even if we ever get to sentencing,
you were acting under duress.
I have everything I need
to keep them from sentencing you to death.
The death penalty doesn't scare me, Jean.
-Mom, then why aren't you fighting?
-I have my reasons.
-Name one.
-Because I'm tired of fighting.
I am not confident that I can win over a jury.
And I'm not altogether certain
that I deserve to.
-I think that was actually three.
-Thea...
But, no, seriously,
you're just ready to give up?
Just take your medicine
and spend the rest of your life in here?
We still need you.
I still need you.
I can't take this.
Growing up...
...I didn't think that
there were secrets kept between us.
Last year I learned different.
And I've gotten pretty good at knowing
when you're hiding something from me.
So, Mom...
...what are you hiding now?
Help your sister come to terms with my choice,
because it's made.
I'm sorry if I upset you before.
We all joined clubs we wish we hadn't.
Took me a year
to get out of that gym membership.
Heh.
-Thank you.
-For what?
Not making me feel like what I am.
Oliver's lucky to have you both as friends.
He hasn't always
had the best luck in that area.
-How'd it go with your mother?
-Not well.
-Have you found somebody for me to hit yet?
-Could be.
The dirt from your house had
trace amounts of aldicarb in there.
-What?
-It's a pesticide.
Starling City used to have
its own aldicarb plant...
...but it was shut down three years ago.
-What's it used for now?
FELICITY: Nothing. It's abandoned.
But my guess is it's the home base
to one League of Assassins assassin.
SARA:
He will kill you.
Like you, I am not that easy to get rid of.
-This is my fight.
-He made it mine when he came into my house.
And when he threatened somebody
that I care about.
Arrows.
Such an ineffective projectile.
I find it strange anyone still fears them.
GREEN ARROW: I'll show you why
if you don't leave Sara Lance alone.
That's your only warning.
And it would be effective...
...were you to pose a threat to me.
You barely defeated Malcolm Merlyn...
...at nearly the cost of your own life.
What hope would you have
against the man who trained him?
GREEN ARROW:
It helps that I didn't come alone.
The child of Ra's al Ghul awaits your return.
-I am not going back.
-That's not your choice.
I have orders to return you...
...alive or dead.
You're not going to kill me.
You overestimate your importance.
Regardless, you're coming back with us.
Us?
Like you, I did not come alone.
[ALL GRUNTING]
[GLASS SHATTERS]
If you will not return willingly...
...you will stay to bury your family.
You're not even flinching when he...
Pain and I came to a little understanding
a few years back.
Done.
The League of Assassins.
Why wouldn't she tell me
what happened to her all those years?
Probably the same reason why you didn't
tell us what happened to you on the island.
We need to protect the Lances.
I'll take Laurel.
-What can I do?
-Nothing. You're hurt. You need to stay here.
-What about my father?
-I'll go talk to Detective Lance.
Tell him he needs to get out of town.
Please don't tell him about me.
I can keep a secret. Just ask him.
You three are quite the team.
We have our moments.
[BARS CLANK]
BUTCHER:
Get up.
Wait, wait, no.
No, no, no.
-The more you struggle...
-Please, no!
-...the more it will hurt.
-No! Please! Please.
MAN:
Wait.
Let her go.
You don't give me orders.
I know. That would be the Captain.
But he works for me. Doesn't he?
[SARA GRUNTS]
SARA:
Help me, please.
Come on.
Laurel, listen, it's your father again.
I know you're still mad at me
after what I said last week...
...but it's not right, us not talking.
So please, just...
Just call me, okay?
Detective Lance, I knew you'd be
getting home around now.
-I knew because I pinged your cell phone.
-Ms. Smoak.
You have cockroaches,
and they mean business.
LANCE: When did you start making house calls?
-You're in danger.
LANCE: I'm not afraid of cockroaches.
-Yes, you're in real danger.
You need to get out of town
for a couple days.
I'm in danger
every time I put on this uniform.
You'll have to be more specific.
There's an organization called the
League of Assassins, and they're targeting you.
-That sounded less crazy in my head.
-I doubt it.
Malcolm Merlyn was a member.
That should give you an idea
about the type of people we're dealing with.
Okay, I'll bite.
What'd I do to piss him off?
That, um...
...is a very long story. You just...
You need to trust me.
You're not safe here in Starling City.
Ms. Smoak, nobody's safe,
especially not us cops.
We get shot at for a living.
And my shift, it just ended.
-Detective Lance.
-Good night.
-You need to listen to me.
-Good night, Ms. Smoak.
So this means you're not leaving town?
Evening.
It's not appropriate for us
to be discussing your mother's case.
I thought I'd swing by, see if I can give
you a ride home and maybe get a bite to eat.
It's been a long day.
I don't need a longer night of you...
...trying to talk me out
of your mother's plea agreement.
Laurel...
...I promise...
...this has nothing to do
with my mother's case.
You've had a rough couple of weeks.
You're really gonna tell me
you couldn't use a friend?
Come on.
-Hey.
DIGGLE: How'd it go?
Badly. He either didn't believe me
or didn't take me seriously.
In hindsight, I probably shouldn't have
led with "League of Assassins."
What do we do now?
What are you doing? I thought you didn't want
your father to know you're alive.
I don't, but it's better than him not being.
-Where do you think you're going?
DIGGLE: With you.
I'm not gonna let you go without backup.
Digg, you may be a Special Forces veteran...
...but I was trained by people that make
the Special Forces look like kindergarten.
So step aside or get put down.
It's your funeral, Sara.
Wouldn't be my first.
[SCOFFS]
[SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACH]
No, no, it can't be. It can't be Sara.
It's me. It's Sara.
Daddy, it's okay.
[SOBS]
Sara?
Sara.
[SOBS]
[SPEAKING IN MANDARIN]
[SPEAKS IN MANDARIN]
You speak Chinese now?
Picked up a couple of things
over the past few years.
Yes.
Why didn't you let us know you were alive?
Your mother and I, we...
We missed you. Your sister did too.
You know that, right?
I know you got divorced.
Yeah.
But it wasn't your fault.
-It was on me.
-Because of me.
-I'm sorry.
-None of that matters now. You're home.
You're home.
[NAPKIN HOLDER CLANGS]
Are you in trouble?
Huh?
No, Dad.
You are.
You sent Felicity Smoak to warn me
to leave town.
You know the Arrow.
You're the girl in the mask.
You've been kicking the crap
out of creeps in the Glades.
You've been home for weeks.
Tell me something.
If these assassins hadn't shown up,
would you have let us know you were alive?
No.
Felicity said that these guys
were part of a league or something.
-What do they want with you?
-To terminate their objective.
-Oh, this is crazy.
SARA: Dad...
-We have to go.
-No. You're not going anywhere.
Not till you tell me exactly
what you've gotten yourself into.
You are an amazing cop.
And you're strong and decent and honest.
But these men will cut you down
before you can lift a finger.
Now, please, come with me.
I'm afraid it's not much...
...but it's home.
[DOOR CLOSES THEN LOCK SQUEAKS]
Why did you lock the door?
No, no. No, no, it's not because...
It's just a habit.
My shipmates aren't exactly the nicest bunch.
Please come in. Have a seat.
[SARA CRYING]
My name is Ivo.
Dr. Anthony Ivo.
And you are?
Sara.
Nice to meet you, Sara.
Why do you keep those people
down there in those cells?
It's my work.
-I need them.
-What work?
I am going to save the human race, Sara.
Maybe you can help me.
I noticed you didn't have a drink.
No, I didn't.
So will you now admit that you
and my father overreacted last week...
...when you thought
I was becoming a drunk?
I am prepared to admit
that I care about you.
Is that why you insisted on walking me
to my door?
You know me.
I just wanted to make sure you were safe.
This is safe.
We shouldn't.
Then why did you come all the way up here?
-I'm sorry if I was sending the wrong message.
-No.
No. No, I got the message.
I get it loud and clear every day.
Run.
Run. Run away from Laurel.
Run as fast as you can.
-Laurel, come on.
-Sara...
She got on the Gambit with you.
My father, he... He climbed into a bottle.
My mother, she...
She climbed into her car and drove away.
And then Tommy...
What is so wrong with me
that everybody leaves?
I will never leave you.
Until you do.
I thought I locked that.
Stay here.
LAUREL:
Ollie?
Anything?
All good.
I have to go.
-Listen, I'm sorry about what I said...
-Don't be.
Just stay here.
Felicity, Al Ow-Al was at Laurel's place.
-What? Is she okay?
-She's fine. He moved on before we got there.
-But if Laurel's not his target...
-He's after Lance. I need a location now.
I can't believe I didn't think
to look for you up here.
It's a good vantage point.
You can see the whole city.
Like a bird on a wire.
Where I was,
they have you choose a new name.
I chose Ta-er al-Sahfer.
It's Arabic for "canary."
LANCE:
I bought you that canary when you were 10.
I was as far from home as you can get...
...but I never forgot where I came from.
They say the first thing you forget
about somebody is their voice.
You can remember their face
and the way they move...
...but you can't hold on
to the way they sound.
I never forgot your voice, Dad.
Sweetie.
But we're out of time.
[THUMP NEARBY]
OW-AL: So this is where
you wanted your father to die.
What the hell, Sara? Who are these guys?
OW-AL:
Associates of your daughter, Officer Lance.
She always did have the worst taste
in friends.
OW-AL:
Did you really think we could not find you?
No.
-I knew you would.
OW-AL: Now!
[ALL GRUNTING]
[GUNFIRE]
Be mindful of your surroundings.
[GLASS SHATTERS]
STICK: Guns are a coward's weapon.
What are you without your sidearm?
A guy with a spare.
You think because you are the beloved...
...you will be granted your freedom?
There's only one freedom.
Let me grant you yours.
-You don't have to do this. It's over!
-Not yet.
-Sara, baby, don't.
-Tell Ra's al Ghul that my family is off-limits.
His quarrel is with me.
I'm sorry you saw that.
I can't imagine what you must think of me.
I think you're a survivor.
I think you're one of the bravest people
I've ever known.
You're my daughter.
It's time for you to come back home.
SARA: I can't.
-Why not?
They are never gonna stop looking for me.
I'll protect you. We'll protect you.
Tell her it's safe to stay.
Dad, if they hurt you or Laurel or Mom,
then I really would die.
-But they need to know.
-They can't. They can't, Daddy.
-Why not?
-You know why.
I came back to make sure
that my family was safe, and you are.
But if they knew I was alive,
Laurel and Mom...
...they would never stop looking for me,
and that could get them both killed.
I can't let you go.
I'm fine. Dad, I have to...
I have to go.
LANCE:
I love you.
Keep them safe.
Detective.
She's right.
You have to keep her secret.
It's already the hardest thing
I've ever had to do.
How do you live like this?
I never mind getting a visit from my children,
but I know why you're here.
-Just one thing to say.
MOIRA: We've been through this.
-I am not going to change my mind.
-This is about me changing mine.
Because I thought that you didn't wanna
go to trial over a secret.
Then I caught up with an old friend
and watched as she struggled...
...to tell her family hers
because she was afraid...
...that they wouldn't love her
if they knew the truth.
Whatever you are worried about,
it will not make us love you any less.
-But you don't know.
-Who do you think you raised?
You've taught us to be strong.
That we could overcome
any obstacle that we faced.
To fight.
Do you really think
that we are gonna scare that easily?
OLIVER:
Whatever comes out...
-...you won't lose us.
-Ever.
Well...
I'll instruct Jean to reject Mr. Donner's offer.
Hey.
Dad.
I know I owe you a phone call.
I have a lot of work.
Can we do this another time?
I just had to see you.
Did something happen? Are you okay?
One day, honey,
when you have a daughter of your own...
...you'll understand that being a parent means
you never stop worrying about your children.
Dad, I'm sorry I didn't call you back.
I've had a really long week, and I'm tired.
Are you all right?
I don't know.
I wish that there was something.
A sign that it gets better.
It does, honey.
It gets better.
How do you know?
I wish I could tell you, sweetie.
I wish I could tell you.
Where's Sara?
She left.
-You cool with that?
-I didn't have much of a choice.
An old friend gave this to me.
He said I would know
when it was the right time to drink it.
-And now is the right time?
-I'm not sure.
But I need a drink.
[SPEAKS IN RUSSIAN]
Mm.
-So you were right.
-Yeah, I usually am, Oliver.
[CHUCKLES]
About what specifically?
No matter how hard I try, Diggle, my past...
...it doesn't wanna stay buried.
I don't wanna try so hard anymore.
The five years that I was gone...
...I wasn't always on the island.
[GROANS]
How are you...?
Prisoners do not speak.