Previously on Arrow...
What happened?
Gregor. His loyalty lies with Kovar.
But Gregor is Pakhan.
There is nothing we can do.
We can kill him.
These corrupt cops are taking down
big drug scores.
You said you're not a criminal
'cause you believe in justice.
Ask yourself, Warner.
Is that still the case?
Now, what are the odds of Oliver Queen
and the Green Arrow
being in Russia at the same time?
Very good...
if Oliver Queen is the Green Arrow.
Four years ago,
The Hood took down Justin Claybourne.
I have been working on a location
for Claybourne's mistress.
Prometheus' mother, we find her...
We find the name for this son of a bitch.
Thanks for coming along.
I know that being my body man
isn't your job anymore.
Sure it is.
Just a different suit, that's all.
Now, we're sure this is the address?
Yeah, Felicity is.
According to her, this is the house
that Justin Claybourne
bought for his mistress.
Think she'll play ball?
- That depends.
- On what?
Whether or not she knows
her son is Prometheus.
Amanda Westfield?
Yes?
Hi. My name is Oliver Queen...
I know who you are.
Mayor of Star City.
May I come in?
Very lovely home.
For the past several months,
there has been a serial murderer
that has been terrorizing Star City.
There is reason to believe
that this individual is your son.
I haven't seen my son
since Justin Claybourne's funeral.
But you know he's become something else,
someone else.
It's why you live here,
far away from Star City.
I moved away because
there was nothing left for me there.
Miss Westfield,
your son is an incredibly capable
and incredibly dangerous individual.
He has erased virtually all traces
of his identity from the Internet.
And I am...
Well, I am here simply
to ask you for his name.
And what happens when you find him?
He needs help. He...
I want him to get that help.
What you want...
Is to cage him up like an animal.
Like the animal who killed his father.
He put an arrow in his chest.
What kind of monster does that?
Whatever my son is doing,
he's doing it because he is hurt
and he is scared.
And I will not help you destroy his life.
Innocent people are dying,
and you might be our only chance
to save them.
Get out of my house.
I'm easily reachable
if you change your mind.
I won't.
Hey! Get back to your seat!
Can't a girl stretch her legs a little?
Sorry, I didn't catch your name.
And you're not going to.
Guards aren't allowed
to fraternize with prisoners.
So, take me out of these cuffs
and I won't be a prisoner anymore.
Sounds fun, but I'd lose my job.
How about your life instead?
This is your stop, ladies.
Come on, ladies. Go!
Next phase?
Star City. Time to return home.
How'd it go with Mama Prometheus?
- It didn't.
- She's probably protecting him.
Wow. My mom could
barely handle me being gay.
Says she hasn't seen him
in over four years,
but maybe they emailed.
What is that?
Just a little toy
that Curtis and I whipped up
in case the Prometheus apple
didn't fall too far from the tree.
It's a sniffer device.
It basically pulls electronic data
from any hard drives or devices nearby.
- Did it work?
- Oh, yeah.
A little too well.
I got a petabyte worth of data here.
It's gonna take me a while
to work through.
Which is fine
because something happened
while you and John were away.
- What?
- Check it out.
Those are some familiar faces.
- What happened?
- Jailbreak led by Liza Warner.
Didn't you put China White
in prison, like, forever ago?
Yeah, a couple times.
Why does she look so familiar?
Maybe she arrested you once.
She used to be a cop.
Warner was, too.
Lance convinced her
to turn over a new leaf,
which, I'm guessing that these ladies
convinced her to turn back over.
Well, according to the prisoners,
they took the Corrections Department bus
and they're headed towards Star City.
Let's get to work on finding them.
We have to go.
Yeah.
Hey, you ready for your big moment?
Oh. It's just a swearing-in ceremony.
You're gonna be a cop again, Dinah.
It's no small thing.
Yeah, I guess it's not.
The city council wanted me
to remind you they have a vote scheduled
right after the SCPD swearing-in ceremony.
Right, right, right.
They're gonna want to get
the show on the road, I totally get it.
Hi...
- I'm gonna need a minute or two, please.
- Mmm-hmm.
- Hi.
- Hey. Come here.
- How are you?
Mmm.
- What was that for?
- That was, "I'm sorry."
For cancelling dinner on me last night?
And the previous two times
that I also cancelled dinner, yes.
Mmm-hmm. Does this mean
I'll get to see you tonight?
Do you wanna have dinner
with the City Comptroller, too?
- Am I ever gonna see you again?
- Of course.
Okay.
Is everything okay?
Yeah, I think so.
Yeah. Yeah. Yes.
No, no, definitely not.
Uh...
Whatever is it, just, um, lay it on me.
What's up?
- Are you the Green Arrow?
- Yeah.
Really?
No!
No. I'm sorry, I thought that
you were doing a joking thing. I mean...
So I did a joking thing back. Are you not?
I was working on a different story,
and, well, some things came up
that relate to you and...
And then you just immediately jumped
to the most insane conclusion possible?
So that's a "no" for the record?
No. For the record.
Well, good.
'Cause I think our relationship
is complicated enough already
just with you being mayor.
Yeah, so do I.
Mr. Mayor, everyone's waiting.
- I have to go to this ceremony. Can I...
- Of course.
Can I show you out?
So, I figure that we go after Gregor
at the bathhouse
because he's gonna have the least number
of men guarding him and...
I mean, quite frankly, we can be sure
that he's not packing.
- Anyway, he has men here, here, and here...
- No. No, no, no, no.
No, what?
Bathhouse is Gregor's turf.
You cannot do it on your own.
- Okay.
- We need army.
Well then, who can we trust, Anatoly?
Because we're basically
talking about a coup.
Lying here
with my ass hanging out like baby.
Don't worry about my men.
They are loyal to me.
Soam I.
And, look, I'm gonna stay here
until we take out Gregor
and we protect the Bratva.
Ty skazal, stay? You going to leave?
Look, Anatoly, I realized I...
I have to get back to my life.
But then I saw what Gregor did to you
because of me, and...
You're a sin-eater, Oliver.
In some cultures, there's this guy
who lives on the edge of village.
And, when somebody dies,
they put body there
and cover with fruits and vegetables,
and he eats that.
He eats their sins?
Yes.
So they go on to the afterlife, yeah.
He takes their sins
as his own.
You are very much like...
What?
In the past ten minutes,
I've seen the same orderly pass by
five times with an empty stretcher.
Could be one of Gregor's men.
At any rate, they know that you are back.
Or they're just here
to finish the job on you. Either way...
It is time for me to kak ty skazhesh,
stretch my legs.
- Here, come on.
- Thank you.
I will always have the courage
to hold myself and others accountable
for our actions.
"I will always uphold the Constitution,
my community, and the agency I serve."
I will always uphold the Constitution,
my community,
and the agency which I serve.
Welcome to the SCPD, Officer Drake.
Is everything okay with Susan?
Yeah. What... Why?
Just, you know, your assistant
was clocking a little tension, some...
Thea, is my assistant your mole?
I like to think of him
more as like my informant.
Okay, what's going on?
Susan asked me if I was the Green Arrow.
Wait. What did you say to her?
I handled it.
I've been doing this
for a little while now.
Can I talk to you for a minute, please?
Quentin, if I delay this vote any more,
I'm gonna get impeached.
Listen to me,
Liza Warner escaped last night.
And China White, and Carrie Cutter.
We're on it.
As a matter of fact, we are on it
sooner than I thought.
- Felicity has their location.
- Great. Where am I going?
I have put all three
of these women away, Quentin.
This is nothing the team can't handle.
Mmm-hmm. Yeah, I know that.
But this is personal, Oliver.
Seems like we're a little late.
Looks like China White
had a falling out with the Triad.
This is more than just a "falling out".
This is a massacre.
Overwatch, all we've got here are bodies,
and a security camera.
On it.
That's Warner.
This isn't on you, Quentin.
I'm not so sure about that.
But either way, we gotta stop
whatever it is these women are up to
before more bodies drop.
Huh?
So, she said, "Where is the depository?"
I don't think she got her answer.
What "depository" is she talking about?
Well, I mean,
the word could also mean "storage."
So the three of them are looking
for something the Triad is storing?
But that could mean anything.
The Triad's got stashes all over the city.
Whatever these three are looking for,
they just killed an awful lot of people
trying to find it.
We want them to stop dropping bodies,
we gotta find it first.
It's all right.
Regretting your choice not to go home?
Not yet.
Come on, come on, come on.
That coup against Gregor?
That might be short-lived like us.
This just arrived, boss.
- What is it?
- No idea, but it said urgent, so...
Chapman, I want the entire ACU
in the conference room in five minutes.
Hey! Long time no see.
- What're you doing down here?
- Oh...
You know, just some damage control.
You have a minute?
Yeah, for you? Anything. What's up?
- Well, it's, um, Susan Williams.
- Hmm.
She's suspecting
that Oliver's the Green Arrow.
Why? I mean, other than the fact
that he is, but why?
I don't know. I mean, I...
He says that she confronted him about it,
and then, he claims he put it to bed,
but she's not just gonna drop this.
Agreed. What are we gonna do?
Hack into her computer,
and find out what's there and delete it?
Yeah, copy that.
Susan William's computer... I'm in.
- That was fast.
- Yeah, well, her password is "1-2-3-4".
And she has a file here
named "Oliver Queen info"
because she is super original.
- Oh, God. She has...
- Everything.
- She's been connecting the dots.
- This entire time.
We have to delete all of this.
Well, even if we do,
she got this from an outside source.
She's just gonna be able to get it again,
and again...
Okay, so what do we do?
Fashion make-over?
Kevlar weave in the jacket.
Figured if I was gonna be back
in the field,
I could have a little more protection.
There he is.
James Wong?
We wanna have a little chat
about your dead Triad friends.
I didn't have anything to do with that.
We know.
But what we wanna know
is what is the chucang?
What?
The "depository," the "storage,"
whatever it is.
Tobias Church...
Is dead.
Yeah, and he never got to spend
the $100,000,000 he got
from the AmerTek deal.
That's the "depository."
His cash stash.
- Where is it?
- I don't know.
Do we believe him?
See? If I'd done that,
I would've sprained my wrist.
So what is this place?
Los Halcones' money laundering facility.
It's likely Warner and her new friends
are after $100,000,000
that Tobias Church left behind.
And you think Church's old running buddies
might know where it is.
Wild Dog and Mr. Terrific
are staking out the Bertinellis.
Dinah and Spartan have eyes on the Bratva.
You know,
you gotta get that new girl a codename.
Well, when she's ready,
I was considering "Black Canary."
You all right with that?
Well, so long as she does Laurel proud.
So, you really think
Warner's gonna show up here?
Forget I asked.
We don't have time for that, Cutter.
Are you kidding me?
These things are expensive.
We find the money,
you won't have to worry about that.
Yeah, and when's that gonna happen?
Not one of these idiots knew a thing.
No, but they gave me the name
of someone who does.
Don't worry,
everything is going down as planned.
Think again!
You have failed this city.
You're under arrest!
Get on the floor
with your hands behind your head.
On the ground!
I'm good. Besides, I owe
this son of a bitch some payback.
Freeze! Get on the floor!
I listened to you once.
I'm not gonna make the same mistake twice.
Since when is doing the right thing
been a mistake, Liza?
Since you turned out to be a liar!
I was all in, Quentin.
You convinced me to turn myself in,
turn my life around.
And then one day, I'm in the TV room
and what do I see?
A news report about you
working for one of the worst terrorists
this city has ever seen!
He threatened my daughter, Liza.
And so you did what you had to.
Why shouldn't I do the same for myself?
Because what I did, and what you're doing
are not the same thing!
Sure they are.
We all do whatever it takes to survive.
And if that means breaking a few laws,
or betraying the people
who believe in you, so be it.
What are you doing?
You're letting them get away!
They're not our target.
You're under arrest for the murder
of Detective William Malone.
Listen to me, you're making a mistake.
Drop the bow,
or we will light your ass up.
Fine.
Son of a bitch!
What do you mean,
they were after you?
Somehow, they found out about Billy.
What?
I'm with her. What're you talking about?
Prometheus orchestrated things
so Oliver would kill Billy Malone.
- What?
- DA Chase
decided that we should cover it up, but...
But somehow the ACU knows
and thinks that you
took out one of their own.
We're gonna have to handle this,
but right now,
every second that we're down here
that crew is getting closer
to Church's money.
The more money they have,
the more guns they can buy
and more damage they can do.
Okay, let me talk with Pike,
I'll see if I can get him to stand down.
Look, Quentin, I appreciate that,
but I gotta handle it this time.
Why?
Because I'm the mayor.
A lot of firepower in this room.
What's going on?
We just have a couple questions
for you, Captain.
We heard the ACU attempted to apprehend
the Green Arrow last night, is that true?
One hundred percent.
He's a person of interest
in the murder of Detective Malone.
Based on what evidence?
This was delivered to me yesterday.
Open it. You'll see what I saw.
The ME report for Billy Malone's autopsy.
Cause of death was an arrow consistent
with the ones the Green Arrow uses.
This wasn't
in the original examiner's report?
That one said the cause of death
was undetermined.
I think we're looking at a cover-up.
There's a lot of whack-jobs running around
with bows and arrows these days.
Doesn't mean it was the Green Arrow.
Like I said, the edgework on the wounds
was consistent with his arrows.
Captain Pike, I have it on good authority
that the Green Arrow was not responsible.
On whose authority?
Right now, I'm not at liberty to say.
Well then, I'm not at liberty
to drop this.
Look, we're dealing
with a cop killer here.
If that's all, I've got a lot of work.
I'll keep you gentlemen posted
on the status of this investigation.
I wouldn't panic just yet.
We don't even know
if that report's legitimate.
I think it's safe to say that it is.
Question is, who sent it to Pike?
Adrian, I'm sorry.
Could we have the room, please?
It was Prometheus.
Isn't that a little paranoid?
I mean, I know that guy has given you
reason to be, but...
The envelope that Pike gave me
was postmarked from Opal City.
Yeah, so?
Prometheus' mother is from Opal City.
I'm not gonna even gonna ask
how you know that.
I went to see her.
This is Prometheus telling me
that he knows about that.
And he is pushing back,
he is keeping me in check
because he knows that I can't make a move
with the ACU breathing down my neck!
Well, you can't just give up.
I have to go.
Hey. Sorry, I got your text and I...
Huh. Okay. Look like you're having
as bad aday as I am.
Really? Did you get fired today, too?
What?
My producer called me out on the carpet.
Apparently, they received an anonymous tip
that I have been plagiarizing
my stories for the past two years.
And my laptop is filled
with incriminating evidence.
Your laptop?
It has all the fingerprints
of a hatchet job.
- Okay, Susan...
- And I have to wonder about the timing.
Because...
nothing like this has ever happened to me
before I asked
whether you were the Green Arrow.
Susan.
I swear to you,
I didn't have anything to do with this,
I don't know anything about this.
And you're going to stand here and tell me
that you're not the Green Arrow?
Because that tattoo on your chest
marks you as a Bratva Captain.
- Okay...
- I've got a photo
of you with the Bratva in Russia
at the same time that you were supposed
to be on a deserted island.
I've got another photo, same time,
of a man in a hood with a bow and arrow
operating in Russia.
But now, of course,
I can't go public with any of it
because I've been thoroughly discredited.
- So, well done.
- If you could just...
Unless the next words out of your mouth
aren't going to be a lie,
I'd really prefer
if you just said nothing at all.
Hey.
Hey, what's going on?
Did you hack Susan Williams' computer?
Okay, whoa, whoa.
Back up. You don't...
Did you hack Susan Williams' computer?
- Yes.
- What were you thinking?
I was thinking that you were one
news story away from being outed.
Thea asked me to put a few things
on Susan's computer and...
Wait. Wait, wait, wait. Thea asked you?
Yes. I don't know what she's planning
on doing, she said she had it handled.
Why, what did she do?
We'll have to make a run for it.
You ready?
Konechno.
Anatoly Knyazev.
- What are you doing?
- I surrender, and he lets you live.
He will kill you.
He's going to kill both of us.
We are trapped, Anatoly.
Only one of us is gonna make it
out of this alive.
I am avtoritet. There is no way you are
going to suffer for my sins, Oliver.
That's why I'm not giving you a choice.
Yeah.
Hey, stranger.
Haven't seen you around much today.
Yeah, you know,
just busy taking out the trash.
Yeah? Sanitation?
More like public relations. Uh...
I hear Green Arrow is public enemy
number one again.
Yeah, well, now Oliver thinks
that he can't make a move on Warner
and her crew. Yeah.
And what do you think?
I think that Warner's my mess to clean up.
And I'm assuming Oliver
said that's not the case?
What Oliver doesn't know
is that the reason her rehabilitation
was short-lived
was because she caught my confessing
to working with Damien Darhk on TV.
Oh, wow.
Yeah.
That is an unbelievable
load of crap, Quentin.
- What?
- Liza Warner is a criminal.
You didn't make her into one.
You've got to stop taking responsibility
for other people's sins.
You know, I really like
how wise you're getting lately.
That's just because I have
committed my own sin today.
What sin?
Don't worry about it.
Why don't you worry about
catching Liza Warner?
Not because you are responsible
but because she's a criminal.
Let's get moving, yo.
Hey, hey. What's this now?
- Looks like three hot chicks. Huh?
- Especially this one.
- Thanks for that.
- Anything for a friend.
We're looking for
Tobias Church's rainy day account.
The AmerTek money?
I tell you where it is, you let me go?
No. You're gonna show us where it is.
- What about the Green Arrow?
- The ACU is all over his ass.
We've got nothing to worry about.
Let's go!
You asked to see me?
Did you know that Susan got fired today?
I didn't know she was
gonna get fired, Oliver.
You should have come to me with this.
Listen, Ollie,
I just wanted to discredit her...
Thea, you should have come
to me with this!
And then what?
We would have the same conversation
we are having right now.
I would have told you that she was going
to out you as the Green Arrow...
- She wouldn't do that to me.
- And then you would say that.
Look, Ollie, the only reason
I didn't tell you
was because I was trying to keep
your hands clean.
- I know you care about her, so I...
- I do care about her.
I also care that
you destroyed her reputation.
She's gonna have a tough time
finding a decent job,
she's certainly not gonna find a job
in journalism. You just blew up her life!
Honestly, I didn't mean for it
to go this far.
Yes, you did.
You knew exactly what you were doing.
And that's the part
that I don't understand.
Who does that to a person?
You got a minute?
Yeah. We're done here.
What do you need?
Warner and her crew just hit
the Bertinellis. One dead,
two in critical condition,
and they kidnapped number four.
Yeah, that's a change in their MO,
they haven't been abducting people.
Yeah, the guy they took is Enzo Russo.
I'm thinking they took him 'cause
he knows where this depository is.
I'm thinking, you know, maybe,
Felicity can hack his cell,
we can track him that way.
No. We have to let
the police handle this one.
- What?
- The ACU will be all over me.
- Okay, then send the team.
- I'm not risking anyone getting arrested.
- What, you're just giving up now?
- Prometheus hasn't given me a choice.
Um...
Neither did Slade Wilson, or Damien Darhk,
but with those guys, you didn't just pick
up your football and go home.
- This is different.
- How?
Because what's happening now,
it's not something that Prometheus did.
It's something I did.
I mean, you're talking about Malone,
right? That was Prometheus.
I fired the arrows.
Listen.
Earlier, Thea was talking to me about
not taking on other people's sins.
What happened with Malone,
that's on Prometheus, not you.
Well, Quentin, that advice
would mean a little bit more
if it wasn't coming from Thea right now.
Well, I don't know what that means.
But I do know that if you're letting
Prometheus, ACU, or anyone else
keep you from stopping Warner
and her buddies,
then justice isn't being served.
I will have Felicity look
at Russo's phone.
That's what I wanted to hear.
I'll take another run at Pike.
No, I'll do it.
You sure?
I'm sure that I don't want Malone's death
to have been for nothing.
- Mr. Mayor.
- You have a minute for me?
Of course. What can I do for you?
It's about the Green Arrow.
- Sir, we've been over this.
- I know.
And I know that I told you
that the Green Arrow was not
responsible for Billy.
That's not entirely true.
You've got my attention.
Prometheus manipulated
the Green Arrow into
killing Detective Malone
by making it appear
that Malone was Prometheus.
Rightly fearing a city-wide panic,
District Attorney Chase
covered up the circumstances
of Malone's death.
And how do you know this?
- The Green Arrow told me.
- You're in contact with the vigilante?
I'm the mayor.
And, whether we like it or not,
the Green Arrow and his team
are auxiliary law enforcement.
Leaving whether I agree with that aside,
why should I believe whatever he says?
Because you know as well as I do
what he has done for this city.
What's the simpler answer?
That the Green Arrow all of a sudden,
out of nowhere, became a cop-killer?
Or that he was manipulated by a psychopath
who has had all of us, you included,
running in circles for months?
He still killed Billy.
Yes, he did.
And that's something that he is gonna have
to live with for the rest of his life.
All I'm asking is
that you don't let that stop him
from being the hero
this city needs him to be.
Ah...
I don't know, Mr. Mayor.
I'm gonna have to think on this.
Thank you for your time.
Yeah.
I got a GPS trace on Enzo Russo.
Well, at least, his cell phone.
Okay, text me the address.
Um, shouldn't we let the team handle
this considering you're the...
And there's really no delicate way
to put this. The SCPD's most wanted?
Text me the address.
All right, I traced Russo's cell to Oak
Hill Memorial. John's already en route.
Oak Hill Memorial. At least if we get shot
we don't have to go far.
That is really not
an encouraging perspective, Rene.
Hey, uh, just a quick note. Listen.
Um, now that you're a freshly-minted
officer of the SCPD we can't have you
going out into the field and having your
new co-workers recognize you, So...
This is gonna involve me
wearing a costume, isn't it?
Yeah, something like that, yeah.
You know, I'm not sure I'm ready
to fill her shoes quite yet.
Well, it's not shoes. It's a mask.
Unit 54 spotted the Green Arrow's Ducati
heading southbound on Riverside.
We believe he's en route to engage
Warner, Cutter, and Chien Na Wei.
We're tracking him
and we'll be there when he does.
Move out.
Thanks for keying me in on this.
Well, I trust you,
like I'm trusting that
certain people can handle the truth.
- Speaking of, how'd it go with Pike?
- We'll see.
Alpha team in position.
This ain't right, man.
Disturbing souls at rest.
This is how you get haunted.
I feel a presence.
Beta team in position.
On site.
How do you know it's this one?
It's got the least amount of dust.
Help me move it.
We have got the money, honey.
Take what you can carry.
We'll come back for the rest.
You did all this for money?
So what, you could go to the Caymans?
You think this is about taking a vacation?
We're taking over.
- We're taking back this city.
- Yeah, you and what army?
This one.
It's amazing the loyalty money can buy.
Take them down!
I'm gonna enjoy watching them
take you down.
Go, go!
Move on the targets!
- Thank you, Captain.
- Happy to help.
Didn't hurt that
the Mayor vouched for you.
I'm sorry about Billy Malone.
Know that it's something I'm gonna have
to deal with for the rest of my life.
That's funny, that's what the Mayor said.
Come to say goodbye?
Clear your conscience maybe?
My conscience is clear.
Hell, it is.
Look in the mirror sometime, Quentin.
You're no better than me.
I'm shot through with flaws, no question.
But at least I'm not using
other people's sins to justify my own.
Hey, hey. Are you okay?
Yeah, yeah, I'm fine. Just, she and I,
we got a little history. Hmm.
So, uh, Oliver tells me
that you're the new Black Canary.
Oh. Not yet.
I'm not ready
to take your daughter's place, sir.
Laurel didn't want someone
to take her place.
She wanted someone
to carry on in her place.
Hey. Nice job tonight.
Saw you on the news.
We need to talk
about what happened, Speedy.
Look, I'm sorry.
Have you...
Have you spoken to Susan?
No, she's not returning my calls.
I'm really sorry, Ollie.
- I know I screwed up and...
- But you didn't make a mistake.
You made a choice.
- And you reminded me of someone.
- Who?
Mom.
She would've done something like this.
Well, she would've done exactly this.
She was a wonderful mother.
But I think we both know that she
didn't always make the best choices.
Whatever's gonna happen with Susan is...
Is whatever's gonna happen.
Right now...
Right now, I'm really worried
about my baby sister.
How very selfless of you.
Did not expect it.
But don't worry, my word is good.
Anatoly will not be harmed.
Anatoly. Look at you.
Hiding like a rat in the sewer.
Did not expect this from Bratva Captain.
But then,
you are not going to be Bratva Captain
for much longer.
We have a problem.
Adrian, just once,
I'm gonna need you to walk into my office
and not say that.
I'm serious.
I just got a heads up on something,
and I think it's something you need
to get out in front of.
Mr. Mayor.
Something's happening.
I think you should turn on the TV.
Reports have recently surfaced
there has been a major cover-up
relating to the murder of
ACU Detective William Malone.
According to our sources,
the Mayor's Office ordered
the falsification of autopsy reports
to protect the identity
of Detective Malone's Killer.
If any of these allegations prove true,
it would constitute a gross overstep
of the Mayor's authority,
one that is likely to trigger impeachment
proceedings led by the Mayor's political...
Wow. You undersold this.
This isn't a problem.
This might be
the end of my administration.
English - SDH