My name is Oliver Queen.
After five years in hell,
I returned home with only one goal,
to save my city.
Today, I fight that war on two fronts.
By day, I lead Star City as its mayor.
But by night, I am someone else.
I am something else.
I am the Green Arrow.
Previously on Arrow...
Really sorry about this, Sergeant.
You're not here to secure the trigger.
You're stealing it.
You want to read your confession
before you sign it?
- You did this.
- No one will ever believe your story.
We call ourselves Helix.
We're calling the data cache "Pandora."
With it, you can spark revolutions.
So, you're not just
giving me the file for John?
I've got all we need to exonerate John.
- Well, how'd you do that?
- Long story.
Pleased to meet you.
I know exactly how this brotherhood works,
and right now, it works for me.
Shipwrecked on Lian Yu, fled to Hong Kong,
and now, you're mixed up with the Bratva.
The man who survived all this
is destined for so much more.
You need to give the monster an identity.
It's only when the monster
becomes someone else,
something else,
that you're free to be Oliver Queen.
I don't know if I'm ready.
I will help you become ready.
What are we doing here?
These are low-level drug dealers.
They're target practice.
Stop!
You're beginning to understand now.
Understand what?
That the man who embraces the dark
is never without sight.
Okay,
so is this the Orchid Bay facility
or the Downtown rebuild?
How long until the announcement?
Don't you have a chief of staff
who usually handles this stuff?
- Excuse us, please.
- Okay.
Thea is looking into a few
joint initiatives that I proposed
while in Hub City last week.
Oh, that's really too bad. I've come to
look forward to her many looks of death.
Thea likes you, she's just...
It's okay, Oliver.
She's not the Queen I'm seeing.
That's sort of an old-fashioned way
to say it, don't you think?
Well, I'm not really sure
how else to put it
given that we haven't progressed.
A funny way of saying
we haven't slept together.
Hi.
Hi, Quentin,
I wasn't expecting to see you today.
Well, you know,
that's the thing about rehab.
It's a long process, and then it ain't.
And by the looks of that assistant
out there, you need me back bad.
- How about I give you guys a moment?
- Yeah.
It's all right, Ms. Williams. I wasn't
planning on keeping my problems a secret.
In fact, I wanted to talk with you
about them. You know, on camera.
- I'll have my people set up an interview.
- Thank you.
I believe you are running late
for a press conference, Mr. Mayor.
- Oh, you live a complicated life.
- How are you?
You know, I'm better
than I've been in a long while, thanks.
That's fantastic to hear, but...
Look, maybe we shouldn't...
What, push my luck
by sitting down with your new girlfriend?
Well, no, just wait a little bit,
let Thea come back and prep you, and...
Oliver, if I were any more dry,
I'd be dust, okay?
I'm ready to move forward.
And this is how.
Now, didn't Ms. Williams say you were late
for a press conference?
Yep.
I like to thank District Attorney Chase
who stepped out of his lane
to represent my friend John Diggle
to make sure that justice was done.
Mr. Chase's efforts further exemplify
Star City takes care of their own.
Thank you, everybody, that'll be all.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
For getting me out.
Thank whoever leaked the NSA's case
against Walker. My job was easy.
Congratulations, Mr. Diggle.
I was wondering if the DA
might have a second to chat?
Save your energy, Ms. Williams,
I know you're doing a story
on the death of Detective Malone.
I have no comment for you.
And yet everyone I spoke to
said you're the man to speak to.
It's a little odd for a DA
to be so involved in a police matter.
The victim
was a member of the ACU.
That office is monitored by City Hall,
not by the SCPD.
- Oh, my God.
- Not what you wanted to hear?
Military police just took General Walker
into custody.
Walker and his men
just shot their way off of Fort Zerillo.
Thirty dead, and he and his men
are in the wind.
And the nuke trigger he stole
in Chechnya is still missing.
What can you tell us?
Lots. But first, welcome back.
- Hugs, kisses, warm feelings.
- Likewise.
I just got word from Lyla that A.R.G.U.S.
discovered a batch of encrypted emails
between Walker
and a group of Markovian separatists.
He's looking to sell the nuke.
We can't let that happen.
We have the US military and A.R.G.U.S.
hunting Walker.
They can't go where it's going.
The sale's in Russia.
This one's personal.
I gotta take that murderous son of a bitch
off the grid right now, whatever it takes.
City Hall gives me access
to a private plane.
- I'm coming, too.
- Felicity...
This is personal for me as well.
I promised I'd never let
another Havenrock happen again
as long as it was in my power,
and I believe that this qualifies.
Walker will have his whole unit with him,
maybe even some Markovians.
We need the whole team for this.
Agreed, but Quentin just got out of rehab,
and with Thea out of town I...
I need someone to keep an eye on him.
Who'd you have in mind?
Better be the report
on the Washington district water projects.
Not exactly, hoss.
- What are you... What?
- Why aren't you in your office?
Well, I came in here to work 'cause
everyone's been dropping by my office
asking how I am,
and I don't need the attention.
And by the way, I just got off the phone
with Oliver
who says he's on the way to Russia.
So what are you doing here?
Oliver said I'm supposed to help you prep
for your interview with Susan Williams,
and it was safer for me to be here
than over there
starting an "international incident."
Also, you need talk to your receptionist.
She didn't believe I was here for you,
I had to sneak past her just to get in.
I wonder how
she could've made that mistake.
Listen, why don't you just do us
both a favor, all right?
Just go home, polish your hockey mask
or something,
and I'll just tell Oliver you were here
the whole time. That's cool, right?
Sure. Except you're fresh out of rehab,
not a politician, about to face the media.
- So, what's it hurt to have a little help?
- Oh, just my waking sanity.
All right, well, pull up a chair.
Alrighty.
- Coffee?
- Sure.
Okay, this whole flying private thing
is something I could really get used to.
Being Mayor has its perks.
You're lucky that Star City's
"sister city" is in Russia.
As of 12 hours ago, at least.
You ready for this?
When I signed on, I didn't think
I'd be stopping a nuclear arms sale
in a foreign country.
Yeah, when I signed on,
I didn't think I'd be dealing with aliens.
- Aliens?
- Yeah.
John said you had friends in Russia.
One friend.
Reached out, didn't hear back...
- Oliver Queen!
- Anatoly!
You never should have come back to Russia.
- Anatoly?
- Alexi Leonov. You remember him, yes?
- He was one of your brothers.
- I can explain.
You asked favor of him.
He asked favor in return,
and you pulled gun on him instead?
You know why I can't be some Bratva thug.
You made promise. You swore oath.
And now one of your brothers is dead.
So why should I welcome you as brother?
Go home, Oliver.
There's nothing for you here.
Ugh. Feel like somebody died
of tuberculosis in here.
What's the Russian word for creepy?
Zhutko.
I was studying on the plane.
Where did you find this place?
Lyla.
This used to be an A.R.G.U.S. safe house,
but as you can tell
from Amero-Russian relations,
- it hasn't been used much lately.
- Yeah, no kidding.
Right.
And why aren't we working with A.R.G.U.S.?
I assume preventing black market
nuclear deals
would be pretty high on their to-do list.
John's right about Russia.
A.R.G.U.S. can't operate here
without causing a diplomatic crisis.
Oh, yes, speaking of diplomatic crises,
why did your friend punch you?
Three years ago, I used a Bratva contact
when I was trying to track Slade Wilson.
He asked me for something in exchange,
I refused. Slade Killed him.
How long do you think
until we're up and running?
I'm not sure. I'm pretty much
starting from scratch here,
and I have to hack the Russian server to
see if we can find any chatter on Walker,
and that might take no time,
or it might take, like, a lot of time.
What about your Bratva friend
with the good right hook?
You could try making nice.
It's not that simple.
Yeah, well, simple or not, Oliver,
we have to use every asset we've got.
I made a mistake with Leonov.
It was a challenging time.
But you still owe me for Gregor.
Lucky for you, I never liked Leonov. Sit.
John Diggle, it's good to see you.
Now you my favorite American.
Thanks.
So, what brings you to Russia?
We're looking for a US general
that has gone rogue.
We have reason to believe he's trying
to sell a nuke to Markovian terrorists.
What concern is that of yours?
Are you gonna help me
find this man or not?
After business with Leonov,
just me sitting with you
squares us with Gregor, yes?
Fine.
Then, we are even.
And back to how things work in Bratva.
I help you, you help me.
An arrangement you refused with Leonov,
if I'm not mistaken.
An arrangement I'm going to refuse again.
That part of my life is over.
Well, then I cannot help you.
But I can offer you some free advice.
Act quickly, Oliver.
The Markovians do not,
as you Americans say,
"Sit on their hands."
You did well.
You've proven to be a most adept student.
I know a few teachers
who would disagree with that assessment.
Hideo Yamane.
His name is in my father's notebook.
And for good reason.
Mr. Yamane's criminal enterprise
is responsible
for much of the designer drug trade
in Starling City.
I think you'll recognize
his chief product?
My sister was using this,
so I killed her dealer.
But I didn't consider the supply.
I left her, I left the city vulnerable.
This is why I found you, Oliver.
So you can correct your mistakes.
Now, Mr. Yamane is in town tonight
meeting with his Russian contacts.
He's a careful man,
he'll be heavily guarded.
- Am I ready?
- That's what we find out tonight.
Sorry. I don't really have much control
beyond "on" and "off."
Yeah, probably because you just produced
the sound of 1,000 Beyoncés?
I mean, polyphonics doesn't even begin
to explain what you're doing.
Can you guys please keep it down?
Okay, Walker has gone completely dark.
There is no way of pinpointing his IP
or his GPS from his phone,
which is probably just a burner anyway.
- That's good.
- How is that good?
Military men
tend to be creatures of habit.
If Walker's using a burner, odds are
it's the same model he used in the States.
And the only one
making calls to the Markovians.
Walker's flip phone of choice
is an old model.
The only network here
that supports it is DetraLink DST.
Can you hack it?
I mean, I could,
but it would take a lot of time.
I think I know someone
that could get us a shortcut.
You have contacts in Russia, too?
Well, kind of.
He might need a little bit of convincing.
Think you two could look like Bratva?
Sorry. I mean prosti.
- I can't see a thing in these.
- Tough guys don't say sorry, Curtis.
Right. No prosti.
Guys, focus.
Why isn't Dinah here with us?
Look, I'm secure enough in my manhood
to admit that she is way more intimidating
than either one of us.
Yes, and a total unknown quantity.
Look tough.
Maxim Ostrovsky. You speak English.
I suggest you start using it.
Who are you? What do you want?
To talk in private.
Don't make me ask you again.
Who are you?
Someone who needs access
to your system's credentials.
You work for DetraLink.
Not for long, I won't,
if I gave you my sign-in materials.
Funny, you didn't seem worried
about losing your job
when you ignored company policy to notify
the Kremlin about certain suspicious
and terrorist-like activity
on your network last year.
How do you know about that?
Better question is, who would I tell?
Because I am sure that the Kremlin
would love to hear about this.
You can't.
My family, they'll kill them.
Yes.
So I suggest it's in your best interest
to give me exactly what I want.
Time to go.
Prosti.
That guy was seriously shaken.
What'd you say?
What he needed to hear.
I've got what we need
to get a location on Walker.
Recon's in position.
I count 10 civilians in the church.
No sign of Walker or his men.
Backstop's also in position.
No activity here.
Are we sure
this is the spot, Overwatch?
Walker's phone just went active
from that address.
There.
John, there are civilians here.
I don't care, Oliver,
this may be our only shot.
We're moving on the target.
Everyone, stay sharp.
Proximity alarm!
Walker knew we were coming.
Diggle, get down!
- Are you guys hearing that?
- I'm guessing those aren't fireworks.
Recon, get those civilians clear.
Backstop...
I'm coming in.
I don't know
who you gentlemen are,
but I wanna thank you for
being so damn eager to find me.
- You guys all right?
- Yeah, we're good.
We lost Walker.
- Overwatch, do you have eyes on?
- Negative.
- All right, meet us out back.
- We've gotta find Walker.
We have his man.
He'll take us right to him. Come on.
What the hell is this?
There's no way you're A.R.G.U.S. or D.O.D.
Shut up.
Do whatever you want,
I'm not telling you anything.
There are thousands,
maybe millions, of lives at stake.
You don't want those deaths
on your conscience.
My conscience? You gotta be kidding.
What's that?
- This is your conscience.
- Stop!
Nothing stops.
Nothing stops until you tell me
when and where the buy is happening.
Now you have five minutes to decide
what you want your face to look like.
Oliver, you're just gonna leave him
in there?
Just give it time.
Oliver, we don't have time!
We have to get Walker now, right now!
Let me in there, and I'll give him
all the persuasion he needs.
He's gonna crack.
If you push him too hard right now,
he'll tell you whatever you wanna hear
to get the pain to stop.
We have to be smart, John, you know that.
As much as I enjoy my visits
to Mother Russia,
have you ever considered
relocating to Starling City?
What do you want? Money? Drugs?
I'll give you anything.
There's nothing you have that I want.
Why, why are you doing this?
Because you have failed Starling City.
All right, I got transcripts
of past interviews
Williams has done with alkies and addicts,
no offense.
Is you being here
really necessary?
Oliver wanted me to help you
prep for the interview.
So how about some practice questions?
All right, so you just got out of rehab.
What makes you think you're still fit
to serve as deputy mayor?
Well, that's a
very excellent question, Susan.
- Ms. Williams.
- "Ms. Williams..."
Well, I think
it's my dedication to this city.
- I have lived here my whole life...
- So have lots of people.
And I'm pretty sure not all of them
are recovering alcoholics.
I think it's been
my ability to persevere...
What are you persevering through?
Could you be more specific?
Well, I'm trying to. Would you let me
get a word in edgewise, please?
You think Susan Williams is gonna go
any easier?
Now, when did the drinking begin?
Was it before or after
the death of your daughter, Laurel?
What'd you just say?
Do you hold yourself
accountable for her death?
Or for working with Damien Darhk?
You shut your damn mouth
about my daughter!
Dude, chill! I'm just trying to help.
You're trying to help? Great.
I'm gonna leave here and when I get back,
you don't be here.
It's just me.
You know you have
a workstation inside, right?
Yeah, I wasn't having any luck
locating Walker,
so I decided I'd work on my frustration
in private.
What?
The guy back in the teahouse,
didn't look like someone
who owed you a favor.
He was terrified.
Felicity, what's really going on?
The NSA file that exonerated John.
It was part of a cache of information
given to me by a hacker group,
and that cache includes intel that I used
to pressure the DetraLink exec.
You mean you blackmailed him.
Well...
For this data cache to have exactly
what you needed for this particular guy,
it has to be huge.
I think the term is "beyond massive."
What?
One of the last things my dad said to me
when he gave me the rags,
was that they hold a power most
people could never even imagine.
And that I needed
to respect and guard that power,
not abuse it.
The people in this data cache,
they're not good people.
I'm starting to believe that my purpose
on this Earth is to stop people like them,
like Walker, no matter what the cost.
And sometimes
you gotta fight fire with fire.
I'm not worried about them,
I'm worried about you.
I thought you were
working on locating Walker.
Yeah.
Is everything okay?
This might be none of my business but
I think she crossed a line to find Walker.
- Rory.
- What? What line?
Stay here.
Where's the buy happening?
- Where's the buy happening?
- Hey, hey! John! That is enough!
That's enough!
I thought we were doing this my way.
Your way wasn't fast enough, Oliver.
I'm not letting Walker get away!
- Neither am I.
- What's happening?
- What happened?
- John got a little carried away.
Did he say anything?
No.
You get yourself cleaned up. I'll be back.
- Where you going?
- I'm going to handle this.
- What do you need me to do?
- That did not take long.
Anatoly, what do you want?
To our imperfect union. Vashe zdorovie.
Vashe zdorovie.
Thanks.
For coming as backup,
or for not telling anyone?
Both.
This isn't the first time
you've done something like this.
Is it?
- I don't mean as the Green Arrow...
- You mean as a thug, right?
No.
It's a part of my life that
I thought that I had moved past, but...
Here we are.
Right.
You know, the other guys said
when you get in one of your moods,
I should just let you be,
but, to be honest, brooding
really kinda gets on my nerves.
They told you about me.
They tell you about Prometheus?
Yeah, they did.
What... Why? Is this mood
because you got pulled back
into some Bratva drama?
No, it...
That I'm trying to move forward...
But I'm back here, I'm in Russia,
in the Bratva.
And it just proves to me
I can't seem to do that.
Prometheus got in your head.
What was it, some crap about
infecting the people closest to you?
Yeah, and tonight
I watched John torture a man.
And there is something
going on with Felicity. There's...
You affect the
people in your life, Oliver,
that's hardly a revelatory observation.
Yeah, in fact, I...
I think it's, uh... It's called living.
Prometheus has you so
fixated on what's wrong with you,
you've completely
stopped seeing what's right.
You know, John and Felicity,
they'll listen to you
because you have
more to offer than just this.
Your past is a part of you.
There is nothing you can do about that,
you can't change it.
Doesn't mean it has to be your anchor.
The other names in that book
are waiting for you, Oliver.
- They're waiting for you at home.
- I know.
Leaving the Bratva
is not going to be easy.
I swore an oath of allegiance.
Your father asked you to
take a different vow, did he not?
You told me he wanted you
to right his wrongs.
You cannot do that from here.
Can lcomein,
or is it still "no dogs allowed?"
You really got
a wise-ass mouth on you, don't you?
I'm not sure, but did you just say
my mouth looks like ass?
Look, I just came in here to tell you that
Susan Williams'
producer called to confirm that
10:00 a.m. tomorrow
still works for the interview.
When did you become my assistant?
When I answered the phone, I guess.
It was out of line
bringing up my daughter.
You gonna tell that to Susan Williams
at 10:00 a.m. tomorrow?
Look, man,
you expecting me to give you an apology,
- you don't know me that well.
- I don't know you at all.
But my sponsor says that
I'm the one that owes you the apology.
- It's cool, hoss.
- No, it's not cool.
My daughter, Laurel, is gone.
And I gotta figure out a way to live with
that which doesn't involve booze
or snapping at guys
that are just trying to help.
You know, 10:00 a.m.
will be here before you know it.
How about another dry run?
- Take a seat.
- Atta boy.
Quit calling me "hoss."
All right. You ready?
- Where are your questions?
- I got 'em right here.
Where were you?
Did you take Dinah somewhere?
Yes, but not like that.
Okay, what happens in Russia,
stays in Russia, remember?
- Where's Walker's man?
- Curtis and Rory are keeping eyes on him.
I think she means protecting him from me.
Oliver, I still think it's a mistake
not pushing the scumbag
for the location of the sale.
We don't have to,
we're gonna have it within the hour.
- What? How?
- Bratva.
Hey, Anatoly wasn't playing ball
unless you did the Bratva's dirty work...
Which is where you took Dinah.
Oliver, I thought you didn't
want anything to do with the Bratva.
I don't, but if it's a choice between
me crossing a line
and the two of you crossing one,
that is a very easy choice.
- What did you do?
- Doesn't matter.
Here's what does. I am who I am.
Now, I'm trying to work past that.
Maybe I do, maybe I don't, but I cannot,
I will not have the two of you
make the same mistakes.
Oliver, you're the one that taught us
that sometimes you have to
get in the muck to make things right.
Well, then Prometheus wins
because he'll be right.
I need the two of you to prove to him,
and quite frankly,
to prove to me that he's not.
I need the two of you
to be better than me.
Because you are.
That's why we work together.
Uh, there is a whole mess
of angry Russian dudes outside.
I have location for Walker,
and men to help in fight.
But we have to leave now.
Your strange friend's pronunciation
is horrible.
Yeah, I'll tutor him later.
Hey.
Pleasure doing business with you, Lev.
You sure you don't wanna
toast the transaction?
Ah, I'd love to,
but I got a plane to catch.
And there's someone I'm trying to avoid.
- American government?
- I wish it were just them.
Green Arrow, tango headed your way.
I love saying the word "tango."
So dol.
Okay, in the future,
you might not wanna do that
with a van carrying a nuclear bomb!
That was a neat trick.
Now what's your plan?
Stay down, you son of a bitch.
Who the hell are you?
You didn't expect to
see me here, did you, General?
And no one's gonna believe that I was.
But everyone's gonna know that you tried
to sell a nuclear bomb to terrorists.
You're assuming I actually meant to
sell a bomb to the Markovians, John.
Bomb's not here.
Walker's headed for the hangar.
Odds are that's where the nuke is.
Felicity!
Why the ruse?
Why sell a nuclear weapon once
when I can steal it back and
sell it to another rebel sucker?
Rory?
Curtis told me you needed some help.
He was probably worried
I'd do something stupid.
Those were his exact words, actually.
Okay, you need to get out of here.
I think he said those would be
your exact words.
The bomb is in countdown mode.
- What?
- It's wired with a failsafe.
We must have triggered it
when we entered the hangar.
- Can you disarm it?
- If I can't,
the yield of this thing
will spread over 50 miles.
Do it.
You know you want to.
Come on, John, you have to.
I got a lot of friends, John.
Lots of resources
with itchy trigger fingers.
And you, well, you got a wife and kid.
Terrific, Overwatch,
any luck locating the nuke?
Overwatch is off comms
and in the hangar.
I think she's trying to
disable the nuke herself.
- I'm on my way.
- No, no, no, no. No!
- What happened?
- Trapdoor code,
- I walked right into it.
- What does that mean?
Any attempt to disarm the nuke will
exponentially pace up the countdown clock.
Wait, what are you doing?
Hoping like hell I can
figure out how to fly a plane.
- What?
- I can't disarm the nuke,
but hopefully I can get it
to a less populated area.
Less populated? What, like Havenrock?
This isn't the time to revisit that.
No. No, no, this is exactly the time.
The rags survived Havenrock,
they can survive this, too.
I can use them to
contain the blast and the radiation!
- No, you don't know that!
- Well, I don't need to know, I have faith.
Okay, but it should be me. Not you.
I don't have time
to take these rags off, so...
Go! Just in case this, you know,
doesn't work.
Felicity, go!
Do it. Go on.
No, General. No, you're gonna stand trial.
I'm gonna see that justice is done.
What's happening?
- Rory!
- Oh, my God!
- Well, he always gets the credit.
- Are you okay?
This means I get a promotion, right?
To Rory and his
amazing nuke-stopping rags,
which hopefully doesn't
give us all radiation poisoning.
- Wimps.
- Yeah, can't you hold your vodka?
Now you my favorite American.
Did you hear from Lyla?
Walker's being escorted
under military guard as we speak.
Congratulations.
First, I wondered why
I didn't shoot him like I did Andy,
then I remembered
what you said to me and Felicity.
Well, I'm just glad that it took.
But, you know, Oliver, you were wrong.
Me and Felicity, we're no better than you.
You, me, Felicity,
we make each other better.
- I'll drink to that.
- You're my brother, Oliver.
Oliver. It's good,
good being friends again.
I forgot how strong this is over here.
I make sure I bring some
when I come to Star City.
Yeah.
Ah, I hear you're mayor now.
Big promotion.
Now you Pakhan,
now you tell everyone what to do.
That's not how things work in America,
Anatoly.
Yeah, that's the way things work
everywhere.
I was hoping maybe you could repay me.
- I thought we were even.
- I thought you return to Bratva.
That was temporary.
That is thing about oaths, Oliver.
They are never temporary,
they are for life.
I need to speak with Anatoly.
Where have you been?
Where is he?
Anatoly?
Oliver? Is that you?
Yeah.
What happened?
Gregor.
I questioned his deal with Kovar.
He did this to me.
You were right about him.
His loyalty lies with Kovar.
But Gregor is Pakhan.
There is nothing we can do.
That's not true.
We can kill him.
You are my brother, Oliver.
Oleg said that you
needed to tell me something.
That can wait.
You know,
if visiting Star City's "sister city"
is what it took to get you to bed,
I would've bought you
a ticket to Russia months ago.
A friend of mine told me that
my past doesn't have to be my anchor.
And I think my past is what was
stopping me from
moving things forward with you.
Looking at all this, I can understand why.
What exactly happened
to you on that island, anyway?
Things that I'm not ready to talk about.
Not even this crazy tattoo?
I mean, how do you even get
something like this on a deserted island...
Hey, hey.
You're not ready to talk about it.
- Mmm-hmm.
- Right. Okay.
Do you mean, like, not now or not ever?
Not now.
Maybe someday?
Yeah.
I can wait for someday.
Hey, what'd that bag ever do to you, huh?
- You got a minute?
- Sure.
How'd the interview go with
Oliver's girlfriend?
Cakewalk.
In fact, I asked her if she
went easy on me and she said she did.
'Cause of something you said to her.
I didn't say much.
I just told her a story about you and me.
- You and me?
- I figured you didn't remember.
When I was a kid,
you were a beat cop on my block.
You caught me tagging a building,
but instead of hauling me in,
you crouched down,
looked me in the eye and told me...
I could be more than just
some rip-run thug.
It really set me on a better path.
You did, I mean.
I had no idea, Rene.
Anyway, I just wanted the reporter to know
just what kinda guy
she was sitting down with.
Didn't you still get dishonorably
discharged from the military, though?
Nobody's perfect.
Hey.
Hey. What're you doing here?
Well, I'm just making sure
you're not radioactive.
- Are you going somewhere?
- Yeah, I'm sorry. I was...
I was gonna call.
Well, I was probably gonna
wimp out and text.
What's going on?
The blast did something to them.
They don't work anymore.
I don't have any control.
They don't offer any protection.
- Well, I'm sure it's just temporary.
- I'm not.
I have a bond with them, Felicity,
I can feel it.
And let's be honest,
without the rags, I'm a liability.
And one the team can't risk,
not with Prometheus out there.
Okay, well, that doesn't
mean you have to leave.
Don't worry. I'll be back.
You'll, uh...
You'll let the team know?
Yeah. I mean,
I'll probably just wimp out and text.
- Well?
- You were right.
All the guys in this photo are Bratva.
Means "brotherhood" in Russian.
I know.
Bratva get tattoos on their chests
when they make captain.
What about the other thing?
Nah, I couldn't find
anything else on Queen in Russia.
But I reviewed criminal activity
from the period he was there,
and I found something very interesting.
The Russians call him Luchnik,
the Archer.
Does he remind you of anyone you know?
The Green Arrow.
Now, what are the odds of Oliver Queen
and the Green Arrow
being in Russia at the same time?
Very good...
If Oliver Queen is the Green Arrow.
English - SDH