My name is Oliver Queen.
After five years
on a hellish island,
I have come home
with only one goal--
to save my city.
But to do so, I can't be
the killer I once was.
To honor my friend's memory,
I must be someone else.
I must be something else.
Previously on "Arrow"...
You're telling me you don't have
a substance abuse problem?
The D.A.'s office has a generous
severance package.
Wait, let me explain
to the D.A.--
I'm sorry, but you're done.
Time to choose, Oliver,
who lives and who dies.
You got what
you came for!
Time's up.
Freaking psychopath!
No!
I guess you made your choice.
Roy was injected with the serum.
We are going to have
to keep an eye on him.
Roy! Roy, I think
you're killing him!
You're stronger,
you heal faster,
but you're not in control.
I can teach you.
Let me help you.
When do we start?
Got your latest
customer.
Genius who held up
the convenience store
across the street
from a police precinct.
Not the smartest plan.
Come on through.
Bum knee.
I had it replaced
a few years ago.
Well, I guess we'll have
to do this old-fashioned-like.
Arms up.
Got your new bunk mate.
Play nice.
Ben Turner?
Tonight.
Midnight. Redwood Drive
and Larkspur Avenue.
What the hell
are you talking about?
Redwood and Larkspur.
The rooftop. Be there.
I don't know
if you've looked around,
but we don't exactly
have in and out privileges here.
My son is with his mother.
I won't get to see him, anyway.
This way, he's set.
I do this, he gets the money.
Do what?
What's going on
down there?
Crap.
What the hell
did you do to him?
I didn't do
anything.
♪ Arrow 2x12 ♪
Tremors
Original Air Date on January 29, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Again.
You know, I slapped water
out of a bowl yesterday.
And I slapped water
out of a bowl the day before.
You must be getting
pretty good at it.
Yeah, well, I can't wait to get
attacked by a dog dish.
This is how an archer
builds arm strength.
I'm not sure if you've
been paying attention,
but strength
isn't my problem.
No, controlling it is.
Again.
And that...
is how you put a guy
in the hospital last week.
How'd you know
about that?
It's none
of your business.
You made it my business
when you agreed
to let me help you.
I knew someone like you.
Someone injected
with the Mirakuru.
He was my friend.
But it warped his mind
to the point
where I didn't even
recognize him anymore.
Who was this guy?
How come I've never
heard of him?
Or that Mirakuru?
Is there anything
you can tell me about him?
Yeah.
I had to put an arrow
through his eye.
If I'm reading this right,
then Slade is back at the cave.
Well, why would he go back
to where the graves are?
We'll find out
when we find him.
And when we do...
You can't tell him.
Tell him what?
Don't talk to me like
I'm other people.
You've got that look
on your face.
The same one that you had
after the first time we kissed.
Pure guilt.
Because I am
guilty, Sara.
Ivo killed Shado
because of me.
But that's not true.
And even if it was,
nothing good comes
from telling Slade
that you think
you're responsible
for the death
of the woman he loved.
Love's the most
powerful emotion.
And that makes it
the most dangerous.
Great.
You still know how
to get to the cave?
Yeah.
It's this way.
Thea?
What are you doing home?
I thought you were
staying at Roy's.
Just needed
a little "me" time.
What's with
the fancy fancy?
Oh, I'm--
I'm going out to dinner.
With Walter.
Like a date?
Like a dinner.
Truly, I don't know
what the evening holds.
Are you all right?
Yeah. I'm fine.
Mostly. Uh...
It's Roy.
He had some trouble
last week, and...
I don't know
how to help him.
Do you want me to stay home?
I can call Walter
and we can reschedule.
Absolutely not.
If you and Walter
are going to patch things up...
No pressure.
But you're going.
It may be nothing.
Only one way
to find out.
No, please, Dad,
come right in.
Well, I guess you're going for
that lived-in look.
Can't afford a housekeeper
without a job.
Got enough beverage
money, I see.
I'm going to need to crack open
another bottle if we're going to fight.
I didn't come here
to fight.
Then why are you here?
Because I'm fine, really.
In fact, I have
a job interview.
At Joanna's new firm.
That's good. Good.
But the real reason
I came here is--
Is because you realized
that you didn't reach your weekly quota
of reminding me of how much
I'm ruining my life?
It's 'cause
I miss you, Laurel.
For a long time,
it was just you and me.
Whatever else was going on,
no matter how bad
either of us was doing,
we didn't disappear
on each other.
Because
you're my family.
And I miss my family.
So how about
we have dinner?
You and me, tonight.
I already ate.
Yeah.
How about
tomorrow night?
Sure.
Dinner tomorrow.
Thank you.
How's it
going with Roy?
Not well!
I don't know the kid
all too well,
but he seems to be
five kinds of angry.
You might be underestimating.
Roy was mad at the world
before he was injected
with Mirakuru.
You say you've seen this before?
Slade Wilson.
He was my friend.
Troubling use of
past tense there.
I thought I could
help him control it.
I was wrong.
But I know more now,
and I'm not going
to make the same
mistake with Roy.
What's that?
Iron Heights.
Due to their low security
post-quake, I thought it would be
a good idea to keep an eye on
their internal
communication for a while.
You hacked into
a prison system network?
Is that judgment
I'm hearing?
Pride.
Iron Heights just put out
a BOLO for Ben Turner,
aka Bronze tiger,
which, btw,
is a terrible nickname,
because tigers are not bronze.
Turner escaped?
Killed ten guards
on his way out.
You think that would
have made the news.
Iron Heights is better
at keeping secrets
than they are
at keeping prisoners.
Any idea where
he's headed?
No.
Get one.
Tell your men
to take a walk.
Leave us.
They can leave
their weapons, too.
Thank you for
the early release.
Thought about
taking off, but I'm...
Curious.
Who would break a stranger
out of prison?
Someone who wishes
to hire you for a job.
I need you to help mn
retrieve a certain item.
This is the item.
You know it, yes?
Yes, I do.
Do you know
what you're messing with here?
Won't be cheap.
This is not a problem.
You do know that thing could kill
hundreds of people?
No, Mr. Turner.
It will kill thousands.
Now you.
Go slowly.
Stop!
This is not about learning
to throw a punch.
This is about learning
to control
your strength.
First water slapping,
now this.
When are you going
to run out of ways
to make me look stupid?!
All I'm learning is new ways
to get pissed off.
And in case
you haven't noticed,
I'm already
pretty good at that.
There's nothing wrong
with anger, Roy.
Anger is energy.
But you need to learn
to channel it
in a positive way.
Like putting the hurt on guys
going after the city.
Let me try hitting something
that'll actually hit back.
Too soon.
Get me out there
with you.
One night.
All this, it would be
a lot easier to take.
Moira.
Ah. I didn't realize
we'd have company.
This is Mark Frances.
Mark's CFO at Kardak Holdings.
We've been putting
in some hours
with the party's
election steering committee.
Oh.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Those are words I'm not
accustomed to hearing these days.
Oh, well.
You were a lioness doing what
she had to do to protect her cubs.
You know, I'm not
the only person in Starling
who sees it that way.
That's a comfort.
It's the truth.
Please.
Thank you.
Well, it's unlike you to show
such an interest in politics, Walter.
It's part of my new position
at the Starling National Bank.
My Board of Directors
is very concerned
about the trajectory
of the city.
You mean Sebastian Blood.
Yeah.
We believe that his policies
will bankrupt Starling
within the next
eight months.
Not that the average
voter cares.
They're all caught up
in his charisma.
And he's not running
against a viable opponent.
Blood's trounced every potential
candidate we've focus-tested.
But we believe that he's vulnerable
on regulation.
Even if he is,
it hardly matters.
Banking regulations
are an SEC issue.
Starling City needs to use
the means at a city's disposal.
Walter
said you were smart.
But you didn't invite me to dinner
to hear my opinions.
You want to hear
my positions.
You want me to run
against Sebastian Blood.
I'm starving.
Where are we going?
It's little hole in
the wall right here.
Laurel, wait.
Don't touch me.
I can't believe you would
do something like this.
Well, you wouldn't
have come otherwise.
Well, you got that right.
Laurel, you need help.
Not from them.
There is not one
person in that room
who knows what I
have been through.
Yeah, you're right.
Some of them,
they've been through worse.
But for better or worse,
everyone in that room
needs to be there,
and you need to be there.
You think you're the only person,
who ever got fired, who ever
got their lives into a mess?
You think again, kiddo,
'cause you're not.
Now, look, we're here now.
So why don't you just
stay for a bit?
You don't have to share
or talk. You just listen.
I thought I made
myself clear.
I'm hungry.
And now I think
I'll eat alone.
Go ahead.
SCPD's network
just lit up with a fresh homicide,
multiple stab wounds.
Like claw marks.
The victim was an architect.
Turner ransacked his place;
Took blueprints of his designs.
One of the aforementioned
designs--Malcolm Merlyn's house.
I don't know much about architecture,
but this can't be good.
What would Turner want
with Merlyn's house?
Not sure yet. All of
Malcolm's holdings,
including the house,
are in receivership.
Who's that
you're talking to?
Oh, wait, let me guess, you can't
tell me that, either.
A guy that I put in prison
got out,
and I have an idea
where he's headed.
Do you have one
of your hoodies?
Do you seriously
have to ask?
Whatever happens,
whoever we run into,
do not engage.
And don't touch anything.
This is his kid,
right?
The guy that died?
Yes.
You know your way
around this place.
You been here
before?
What was that?
It came from underground.
Merlyn has a large garage.
Let's go.
What the hell is that?
Looks like a prototype.
Of what?
A machine that
killed 503 people.
Merlyn's own
earthquake device.
Ok, a simple
snatch and grab.
Don't know
why Mr. Armitage
thought
we needed you.
For that.
Step away
from the device.
You don't know
what it is you're dealing with.
Big machine, makes earthquakes?
Do you have any idea
what happens
if the wrong people
have it?
Yeah. I get paid.
Close it up.
That thing killed
eight of my friends.
Hey!
Uh-oh. You got angry face.
What happened?
Roy Harper.
You took him
out in the field--
He wasn't listening
to me, Diggle!
I'm trying  to reach him,
but he lost control.
Then he nearly
killed somebody,
which I obviously couldn't let happen,
and in the process--
Turner got away.
What was he there to steal?
Merlyn's art collection?
Something much
more dangerous.
It's a prototype
earthquake machine.
Oh, holy God.
Why would Turner
want to destroy the city?
He doesn't.
He's a mercenary
selling his services
to the highest bidder.
This watch belonged
to one of the guys
Turner was working with.
Fingerprints.
Turner's a loner, which mean
that guy works for his client.
Fingerprints equals name,
equals known associates.
I'm on it.
It was the look
in Roy's eyes.
It was Slade
all over again.
Oliver,
what happened with Slade?
Me.
Someone killed Shado.
Slade loved Shado,
and it was my fault.
I wanted to tell him,
because it would have been better
coming from me,
but I didn't.
And he found out another way.
If I had just
told him the truth,
I could have gotten
through to him.
And that's why it's so important
for you to get through to Roy.
I lived
a five year nightmare.
But if I learn
something
that could help me
reach Roy now...
It'll all be worth it.
He's not here.
Where else could he be?
We already checked the plane.
I don't know.
Do you remember
seeing these before?
I didn't really look around.
They look familiar.
This could be Lian Yu.
No, I mean
the calculations.
I've seen those before.
Maybe the first
time you were in the cave.
I don't think so.
Fyer's launcher.
What?
Oh, there were soldiers
on the island last year,
and they had a missile launcher.
I saw one of these
on the display.
They're firing calculations...
He's going to blow it up.
Blow what up?
The freighter.
Oh, thank God you're here,
I need your help--
I have to talk to you.
It's important.
Ok. You look stressed out,
is everything ok?
You have to leave town.
Grab your mother and your brother,
if you can, and leave.
It's just for a few days.
A reason
would be nice.
I need you to trust me, Thea.
I do. I just--
I can't up and leave
with my family without a reason.
No, you have to.
Roy, you're not
making any sense
right now.
Would you just tell
me what's going on?
Why aren't you listening to me?
I need you to listen to me!
Roy, you're
hurting me!
I didn't...I didn't...
I didn't mean to. I'm sorry.
I know!
Well. Your work
environment
has definitely
improved since CNRI.
This place is bigger
than my apartment!
Well, there is a limit to
the glamour, unfortunately.
I spend my days
in document production--
And answering interrogatories.
It doesn't feel like
practicing law so much as
pushing papers.
If I didn't know any better,
I'd think that you were trying
to talk me out of the job here.
I guess I do know better.
I'm sorry.
What's going on?
One of the partners
serves on
the bar association's
disciplinary committee,
and...Well, when
I sent your résume,
he did some checking.
That was a complete
misunderstanding.
I mean, sure, yeah,
I had some problems,
but I'm fine now.
The bar is going
to open disciplinary proceedings.
What for?
Conduct affecting
your fitness
to practice.
That's--
that's ridiculous.
I know.
But while
this is out there,
the firm
can't hire you.
Thanks.
Thanks for letting me know.
I have to go.
Laurel, Laurel.
You can fight this, ok?
I'll help you, and--
I need some time to...process.
I'll call you.
Can I fix you a drink?
Whatever
you're having.
It was good
to see you
the other night,
Moira.
It was lovely.
It's been a while
since I've had such a good laugh.
It was
no joke, Moira.
Mark was telling
the truth.
A significant number of people
in Starling City
feel that your actions
with Malcolm Merlyn
were justified to
protect your family.
43.6%, in fact.
You polled people about me?
Prudent course of
action when vetting
a potential
candidate, yes.
600,000 people in Starling City.
I'd think you could find
someone not responsible
for destroying it
with an earthquake machine.
Not with your
name recognition.
We need a game change
candidate, Moira.
And there's no one in Starling
with a higher profile than you.
Charles Manson
is rather well-known,
and no one is going to vote for him.
True.
Equally true, voters like
redemption stories.
Bill Clinton,
Elliot Spitzer,
Martha Stewart.
Oh, I don't believe
she ran for office.
But if she had,
she would have won.
Would have won what?
Ah, Thea.
Mmm, what's going on?
I'm just convincing
your mother to run for mayor.
Of what?
You see?
Sweetheart, are you all right?
You really need
to stop asking that.
Are you serious?
It's hard to believe, I know.
No. No, it's not.
Look, this is actually
the first election I can vote in,
and...as a newly
minted voter,
I don't think it
sounds that crazy.
From out of the mouths
of babes.
You're late.
I tried to get
my girlfriend to leave town.
But she won't.
You cannot bring her into this.
But how am I
supposed to lie to her
and protect her
at the same time?
How do you do it?
How do you keep secrets
from people in your life?
By remembering
it's the only way to keep them safe.
No, keeping them safe
is what keeps them safe.
Telling people
the truth.
But you, you won't
tell me anything.
Not about the Mirakuru,
and this other guy.
And you got me slapping
water and hitting dummies instead.
Roy, you're spiraling
and you need to calm down.
No. I need
to save Thea.
That thing is out
in the open because of you.
I think you've done enough.
Let go of me.
Roy...
I said let go of me!
Get control.
If not for me or yourself,
then do it for Thea.
What the hell
do you know about Thea?
Don't you talk about her!
Are you done?
No. I'm not done.
I'm going
to stop this thing.
And if you want
to stop me, try.
Try putting another arrow
in me. Go ahead.
'Cause I heal fast now.
But get in my way,
then I'll give you a good look at that
anger you're so worried
about me
losing control of.
You both scoffed
when I said we should invest
in an X-ray machine
for down here.
What do you want
to do about Roy?
Where are we
with the fingerprint?
I struck out
on domestic agencies,
but I'm checking Interpol,
PRC public security
and MVD databases now.
Oliver, I know
you've taken Roy on, and why,
but Roy, Slade,
a lot of guys I've served with...
Some people
are just broken, man.
And nobody can put them
back together.
I refuse
to believe that.
I'm not letting what
happened to Slade happen to Roy.
I'm not.
Yeah.
Are you near the club?
I'm pretty close. Why?
Laurel's here.
She doesn't look good.
Hey. Laurel's
upstairs.
Ohh! Excuse me.
Can I get something with olives?
I don't care what it is, as long as
there are a lot of olives.
How about coffee?
Coffee and olives?
Bad combination.
What are you doing?
This is where it's happening,
right? The big club?
Here you go,
Martini, triple olives.
Thanks.
Laurel, go home.
Thea Queen, telling me
enough is enough.
Now that is rich.
Fine.
Bar me from your bar.
That's today's theme,
right?
Disbarment.
Laurel, are you being disbarred?
Yeah, looks like
my law career's over.
But you know what?
Maybe Thea here can
hire me as a waitress.
Or, Ollie, I could
come be your secretary.
But that would mean you
would have to fire her.
Hi, Laurel. How are you?
Did you need
to borrow my car?
Did your limo
break down?
Oliver, can I talk to you
for a second?
Get her a cab, please.
Fingerprint was in
Interpol's database.
The guy worked
for Milo Armitage.
He's a black market
arms merchant.
He's trying
to sell the device.
I need you to search
for any indication
that Armitage
is in Starling.
I already did.
His ship filed a loadlog manifest
at the Starling City docks.
I'll get you
the slip number.
Hi, it's Oliver.
I just ran into Laurel,
and something's wrong.
She needs you.
Slade?
Oliver...
Slade!
Get back!
We know you're
targeting the boat.
I'm going to send
that son of a bitch
to the bottom of the ocean.
You're going to destroy our only
way off of the island!
As long as Ivo is dead,
it's worth it.
I can't let you do it.
Get back, or so help me,
I will put you down!
Mom? What
are you doing here?
I came by to get
your advice on something.
Step into my office.
Ahh.
This is about
the campaign, right?
It's really awesome
you're thinking of doing this.
You said something
that stayed with me.
The idea that there
could be voters out there
that wouldn't dismiss me
out of hand.
Well, you did run
a multi-billion dollar company.
Yes, and an undertaking
that destroyed the city.
People will
get over that.
What makes you so certain?
Because I did.
Can I make
a suggestion?
Instead of
punishing yourself
because you think
you destroyed the city,
how about you start
by saving it?
$10 million,
I believe was
the negotiated amount.
Congratulations, you're now
in a new tax bracket.
Just out of curiosity,
you pay me ten million,
and you get...
Three times that.
You already
have a buyer?
I recommend
that you stay clear
of Markovia for a few months.
I believe our business
is now concluded.
Not yet.
Looks like your partner
abandoned you.
He's not my partner.
He's someone I hired
to do a job.
And it turns out
it was money well spent.
Just too dumb
to stay down.
Don't do it!
You'll kill everyone here.
If I don't deliver this device
to my buyer in Markovia,
I'm dead anyway.
No!
Roy! I need you help!
Roy, stop!
Roy! Roy,
I need you to stop!
The earthquake device
is in there.
The steel is military grade;
It's built to withstand a bomb,
but not you.
Think about Thea.
Because she could die
without your help.
I know you love her...
Because I've seen it.
Save my sister.
Control.
Focus on Thea.
She needs you right now,
or she is dead.
Everyone is dead.
You're...
Yeah. Yeah.
Last year,
you saved my life.
And I don't mean
from the guy who kidnapped me.
I mean, you...
you saved me.
You gave me purpose.
We're just getting started.
So...The secret society
gets a new member.
Where is he now?
Home.
He's, uh...
Processing.
When I found out
who you really were,
I processed my way
through a pint of mint chip.
I stress eat.
Speaking of stress...
I'm not trying to Monday morning
quarterback here--it's Wednesday.
Didn't this all start
because you were worried
that Roy's marble collection
was on the short side?
She has a point,
Oliver.
Roy's a loose cannon. Now he
knows your secret.
You're right,
and I wasn't thinking
about the consequences.
I only knew that
I needed his strength.
His power.
On the island,
Sara told me that love
is the most powerful emotion.
Well, the Arrow
couldn't get Roy
to think about Thea.
But I could.
I said get back!
Think about Shado.
I am...
Thinking about her!
There's something
I have to tell you about Shado.
It's something
you deserve to know.
She loved you,
Slade.
Maybe not the way
that you wanted her to,
but she loved you.
And she wanted you
to make it home.
She wanted you
to see Joe again.
to hug your son.
I know you're angry.
And I know
you want revenge.
If you destroy
Ivo's freighter,
Shado will have
died for nothing.
What is happening to me?
I don't know.
I am not going
to let you go through it
on your own.
The man who killed Shado
is still out there.
And whether that freighter's
on the bottom of the ocean or not,
we're still suck
on this island.
Not for long.
Because we're going
to take the freighter.
I was glad
to receive your email.
Does it portend
what I'm hoping?
I'm going to run.
What changed your mind?
Thea.
Hmm.
She reminded me that
I still owe this city.
And I want to be remembered
as something more
than Malcolm Merlyn's pawn.
As you should.
But you know there was
another reason
for my reticence.
You're afraid
the people will learn
that Robert wasn't
her biological father.
I managed to get through a criminal
trial without the truth coming out,
but political campaigns
tend to be a bit more adept
at extracting skeletons
from closets.
But no one else knows.
Someone does.
My ob, Dr. Gill.
There were complications
when Thea was born,
and I had to tell him
that Robert wasn't her father.
If we're going
to move forward,
we need to make certain
that he won't be
a problem for us.
Hmm?
Mr. Turner.
Hmm.
I didn't know this place
allowed conjugal visits.
My name is Amanda Waller.
You say that like it's supposed
to mean something.
To the contrary.
My identity
is highly classified.
Then why are you
introducing yourself to me?
I have an offer for you.
A way to work off your sentence.
As it turns out,
I have need of someone
with your...
singular qualifications.
For what?
For a unit
I'm putting together.
What type of unit?
Actually...
It's more of a squad.
Is this the part where you kill me
'cause I know your secret?
Do you actually think
that I'd kill my sister's boyfriend?
Well, you did shoot me
in the leg.
Forgiven, by the way.
Thea.
She can never know.
I get the feeling
that if I did tell her,
that would be when you kill me.
Trust that instinct.
Ok. All right.
How many people know what--
who you are?
Too many.
But these are the only
two that matter.
John Diggle
and Felicity Smoak.
Does this group have a name?
Like team Arrow,
or something?
We don't call
ourselves that.
I do. Occasionally.
Stop.
Whatever.
Welcome aboard.
Sara...
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man