Where is Sara?
She came here for the League
two weeks ago.
We've not heard from her since.
There's something I have to tell you.
Sara's dead?
I'm so sorry.
It was an arrow, wasn't it?
How do you know that?
Where's her body?
-Nyssa.
-Where?
We buried her in her grave
from seven years ago.
She knows something.
I want you to follow her. But be careful.
I have to meet Thea.
Hi.
Sorry I'm late.
Late is your "on time," Ollie.
So much for my promise
that things would be different, right?
Relax. It's fine.
OLIVER:
Dinner is on me.
With what money?
Aren't you broke?
Um...
-Aren't you?
-Not so much, actually.
Uh, when I decided to come back,
I had no idea what I wanted to do...
...and realized I kind of missed the club.
And turns out, a lot of other people do too.
I have investors.
And, uh, they're gonna help me buy back
the foundry from Queen Consolidated.
I'm thrilled for you. That's fantastic.
You seem changed.
Stronger.
After last year, I...
-...don't see any other way I could've turned out.
OLIVER: And that's it?
You're not seeing someone or...?
I'm hoping Roy didn't put you up
to asking that.
No, I'm just trying to figure out
why you're so different.
How about just being
my big brother instead?
Okay.
[CHATTERING]
Target's on the move. He's headed north.
-He stopped.
MASEO [OVER COM]: What's he doing?
He's buying ice cream.
He doesn't look like a terrorist.
-The best ones never do.
-Why does Waller want me to take this guy out?
Too many questions.
Follow orders and eliminate the target.
Or is this one of your best friends too?
Oh, so I'm just a gun that she can point
at things she doesn't like?
That's exactly what you are.
-He's moving.
MASEO: Best not to waste time, then.
Nyssa.
[SPEAKING IN ARABIC]
You have my condolences.
And that of my father, Ra's al Ghul.
I don't want your condolences.
And I definitely don't want your father's.
She died with arrows in her chest.
You think that would've happened
if she hadn't met you?
You were the one
that showed her the darkness inside.
You and your father.
I know you grieve.
But so do I.
I didn't show Sara the darkness, Laurel.
It was already inside of her when we met.
When I found her, alone, starving
and terrified, I protected her.
I took Sara into my heart
and I loved her with all of my soul.
And that jacket...
...I gave it to Sara as a gift.
You are not fit to wear it.
ROY: She's moving.
-Where?
ROY:
She went to visit Sara's grave.
Now she's on the top floor
of some dump on Amsterdam.
Could be where she's crashing.
League's safe house or something.
Text me the address.
[SOBS]
Are you ready to talk?
We've nothing to discuss.
The trail for Sara's killer has gone cold.
And I could use your help.
Whereas I don't need yours.
Really?
We've gathered evidence,
we're working leads.
You're visiting cemeteries
and hiding in League safe houses.
I am not hiding.
And this is not my safe house.
It was Sara's while she was in Starling.
[CAMERA BEEPS]
These were her favorites.
Okay.
You said Sara was in Starling
for the League.
-That suggests her target is also her killer.
-Agreed.
Except it wasn't a target.
Sara came to Starling to confirm rumors.
Whispers,
that an enemy of the League was here.
-Who?
-Malcolm Merlyn.
He's alive.
Merlyn was a member
of the League of Assassins.
My father released him
from his obligation to us...
...with the understanding
he would abide by its code of conduct.
You guys are professional killers.
That is a pretty low bar.
Merlyn's undertaking
violated the League's principles.
When you killed him,
we considered the matter settled.
But we received word from a reliable source
that Merlyn faked his demise.
-What source?
-Oliver's mother.
Yeah, well, Oliver's mom
wasn't exactly known for her honesty.
No offense. I just can't believe that a guy
everyone thinks was dead suddenly isn't.
Neither did I.
Then we found these.
Sara took them two weeks ago.
Didn't the police find his body?
Merlyn had resources all over Starling.
I'm willing to bet one of them
was in the coroner's office.
Since learning Merlyn was alive,
the League has hunted him all over the globe.
Running down every rumor,
following every whisper.
And one of those whispers
put Merlyn back in Starling.
She tracked him here.
We're gonna retrace her steps.
-You said you found evidence on her person?
-Yes. Roy.
We found a blank piece of paper
in Sara's boot.
But why would she be carrying
a blank piece of paper?
Do you have a flame?
Unbelievable.
My father had a notebook
with hidden writing just like this.
A notebook he received from Merlyn,
I imagine.
This is ghost ink, one of the means
the League employs for concealing secrets.
It's Sara's handwriting.
Notes from her surveillance of Merlyn.
-There's not much to go on here.
OLIVER: There's a couple of things.
"Jansen," question mark.
"Dad help," question mark.
Sara reached out to Lance.
If Lance knew Merlyn was alive,
he would've told you.
Only if she told him.
-What matters is what he told her.
-And how do we find that out?
So, gentlemen, word of advice.
Next time you arrest a bookie, please
make sure the chief is not one of his clients.
That's what the chief told me to tell you.
As far as I'm concerned, keep doing your jobs.
First round tonight's on me.
Please get out of here.
-Buying rounds?
-Oh, buying love.
Fastest way to a cop's heart,
through his liver.
How are you feeling?
I'm fine. Do you have a minute?
-Yeah, yeah, yeah.
-I have to talk to you.
It's about Sara. She, um...
She called me.
She said that she was looking
into something.
Something called Jansen?
Um...
[CLEARS THROAT]
Uh, yeah, someone.
Ken Zhi Jansen.
I hooked her up with his last known address.
Sara was here.
She asked me not to say anything to you,
and I... I should have.
Maybe I should have. I'm sorry.
It's okay. She was...
-She's in a mysterious line of work.
-Oh, yeah.
-One I hope you're not getting mixed up with.
-No.
I'm just doing Sara a favor.
And her?
I'll be right back.
[PHONE RINGS]
[LANCE SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
What are you doing here?
Oliver told me of his plan to involve you
in the hunt for Sara's killer.
I have a handle on it.
Your father doesn't know, does he?
No, he doesn't.
-And he can't, he has a heart condition.
-He has the right to avenge his daughter.
-It's none of your business.
-Sara was everything I hold dear in this life.
-It is every bit my business.
-What would she say if she were here?
I almost didn't recognize you
without your Halloween costume.
Sara back in town too?
No, she is not.
But she told me to tell you
that she misses you very much.
The address I gave your sister for Jansen.
Now, she promised me there wouldn't be any,
you know, assassinating.
That still the case?
I assure you, Mr. Lance,
the only objective here is justice.
DIGGLE: This was the next lead
Sara was gonna follow?
Jansen's a Buddhist monk.
Nine years ago,
he was facing deportation to China.
Merlyn bankrolled his defense.
Jansen returns the favor
by giving Merlyn asylum in his garden.
Monastery. We should divide our forces,
take up flanking positions.
I agree. But not...
Never understood
what Sara saw in her in the first place.
Split up. But be careful.
Copy that.
DIGGLE [OVER COM]:
Oliver, we found Jansen.
Negative.
I have eyes on him.
Whoever is up there is not Jansen.
Jansen Sensei.
I am Nyssa, daughter of Ra's al Ghul,
heir to the Demon.
You will tell me where I can find Merlyn
or I will kill you where you sit.
Hello, Nyssa.
[GRUNTING]
NYSSA:
Where is he?
What's going on?
Did you find Sara's killer?
We have a suspect.
Malcolm Merlyn is alive.
Sara was here looking for him.
We think he found her first.
-And where is he now?
-We're working on that.
He got away from us earlier tonight.
But not before I hit him with an arrow
laced with particulate nanotechnology.
Felicity wrote a program
that tracks the nanites using GPS.
-A tracer arrow.
-Yeah.
You had a shot at Merlyn
and you didn't kill him?
-I tagged him.
-With a flesh wound.
OLIVER:
He's marked.
Nowhere in the world he can go
where I can't find him.
And when you do?
-I'm not a killer anymore, Laurel.
-Merlyn is.
He killed Tommy
and 502 other innocent people.
How many are gonna have to die
before you put him down?
-You think that's what your sister would want?
-Yes.
I do.
Let me speak with her.
-Merlyn may try to contact Thea.
-I'm on it.
The tracer arrow program.
You have Felicity monitoring remote
from Central City?
No, she told me an idiot could run it.
I will try very hard
not to take that personally.
I'll be on the streets.
-Talk me in when you have his location.
-Copy that.
[CHATTERING]
[GASPS]
[CLANGING]
It's done.
NYSSA:
Laurel.
I just found out Malcolm Merlyn
isn't only alive, but that he killed my sister.
I'm sure you can understand
why I don't wanna talk right now.
I understand.
I loved her too.
I'm sorry for your loss.
I promised Sara...
...and I promise you...
...we will find Malcolm Merlyn.
Apparently, you already did.
And Oliver should've killed him.
Yes.
If Oliver catches up with Merlyn,
he's going to let him live or let him go.
You can't let that happen.
You need to get Merlyn.
You have to do whatever it takes.
ROY:
Hey.
Grand re-opening
is not for another three weeks.
Looks like you still got
a lot more work to do.
Need some help?
Uh, thanks, but I don't really think
that's a good idea.
Just as friends and former co-workers.
[SIGHS]
Bonsai green, October mist, or avocado?
DIGGLE: Merlyn stopped. I got his position.
OLIVER: Go.
Air-conditioner factory, 18th and Milson.
You want me to share this with Nyssa?
OLIVER: No. She'll put an arrow in him
before I get any answers.
Agreed.
[SIGHS]
This place is empty.
He's not here, Diggle.
MALCOLM:
Hello, Oliver. You're absolutely right.
I'm not at the...
What is it, the air-conditioning factory?
It's a neat trick you have.
Sorry it didn't work out.
When I find you...
MALCOLM:
You absolutely will. We need to talk.
But I prefer a venue less conducive
to conflict.
Nelson Plaza at Coldwater and Fifth.
Bottom of the stairs.
It's a very public place.
You'll wanna leave your mask behind.
This should remain between the two of us.
So if I even see one of your associates,
I promise you, you will not see me.
[CHATTERING]
MALCOLM:
Hello, Oliver. How are you?
You've accomplished a lot with this city,
I see.
I'm not here to discuss Starling.
-You think I killed Sara Lance.
-How else would you know she's dead?
These streets were mine
long before you laid claim to them.
This is still my city.
I chose this place
because crowds equal invisibility.
Besides, I understand
you're not killing people these days.
I'm considering making an exception.
Ra's al Ghul has placed
a blood bounty on my head.
Why would I try to get it lifted by killing
the love of his daughter's life? It's illogical.
Sara comes back to Starling.
You come back to Starling.
Sara's murdered.
I came back for the simplest
and most noble of reasons: Thea.
Six months ago, during the siege...
...she was almost killed by one of...
One of Slade Wilson'sMirakurusoldiers.
-I protected her.
-You're lying.
Thea made it out before the attack.
Unfortunately, she didn't make it out.
But you wouldn't know that
because you were out being...
What are you calling yourself these days?
"The Arrow."
That was the night I realized
that Thea needs me.
Stay away from her.
Don't worry.
I've kept my distance.
Oh. But the world is a dangerous place.
And you're too distracted to protect her.
-You're a killer.
-Yes, I am.
But I swear, I swear to you on Thea's life...
...I am not Sara Lance's killer.
[CHATTERING]
From the look on your face,
you need something stronger than coffee.
-Are you okay?
-Yeah, are you?
Back in Corto Maltese, I promised you
there would be no more secrets...
...no more lies.
And I'm trying to honor that.
Okay.
I learned something last night
that's gonna be difficult for you to hear.
I think that it's what Mom was trying to tell us
the night she died, right before it.
The night of the siege,
you were at the train station.
Yeah, I...
It wasn't fun.
I got attacked
by one of those crazy masked things...
...and he tried to strangle me.
But he got shot by a cop, I think.
Did you see him?
No.
Why are you asking?
It wasn't a cop, Thea.
It was Malcolm Merlyn.
He's dead.
How do you know this?
One of Sara's friends saw him.
She's sure.
If he was gonna try to contact you,
he would've done it by now, okay?
Thank you for telling me.
[CELL PHONE BEEPS]
It's, uh, one of my investors. I...
Are you okay?
Yeah. I'm... I'm fine. I...
It's like you said,
if he was gonna contact me...
...he probably would've done it by now.
-Where's Oliver?
-Out, taking care of some family business.
As if there weren't more pressing matters
at hand.
He's not doing nothing.
He tracked down Merlyn last night.
Did he kill him?
OLIVER:
No.
-He swore to me he didn't kill Sara.
-And you know all of his words are lies.
I believe him.
Because he swore to me
on his daughter's life.
We had heard rumors
Merlyn fathered another child.
We couldn't confirm them.
[SIGHS]
-You know who it is.
-I do.
If you put me through the effort
of finding out on my own...
...I might have to exact a price
from whoever it is you're protecting.
It's Thea.
My sister is Merlyn's daughter.
[SCOFFS]
And that is the reason
he came back to Starling City.
Because she did.
He's protecting her.
And that is why you spared Merlyn, twice.
It had nothing to do with that.
He explained to me, in his own twisted way,
that he loves her.
And then he swore to me on her life.
And I swore an oath of my own
that I would see Sara's killer brought to justice.
OLIVER:
Nyssa.
-Nyssa!
-Oliver, wait.
OLIVER: We have to stop her.
-Do we?
Listen, I understand why you can't kill Merlyn,
all of the reasons.
[DOOR SLAMS]
-Maybe he killed Sara, maybe he didn't.
-He didn't.
Either way, the world is a better place
without Malcolm Merlyn in it.
You made a vow not to kill.
Nyssa didn't.
Where's your wife?
Tatsu? She needed to be someplace else.
She doesn't like me.
You're wrong.
She hates you.
She's not happy that I'm here.
Neither am I.
I killed a man today.
I don't even know the reason.
-Sometimes it's better that way.
-What, blindly following orders is better?
I'm not blind, Oliver.
I'm focused on what's most important.
You should do the same.
It's not our place or burden
to know why we carry out our missions.
I didn't realize having a conscience
was a burden.
[LAPTOP BEEPS]
What are you playing?
A reading game.
Oh, yeah? Do you mind if I try?
I wanna work on my Cantonese.
Dad said I shouldn't let you
use my computer.
Okay. Why don't we make a deal, then?
You don't have anything. You're a bum.
Well, this bum has something
that you don't have.
Height.
That stash of candy that your parents keep
in the cupboard above the fridge?
-I'll swipe you two pieces.
-Five.
-Three.
Fine, five. Give me the computer.
I need a meet with Waller.
-How did you...? Akio...
-It's not his fault.
I need a meet, make it happen.
-Waller's gonna want a reason.
-Ferris Air flight 637.
She'll know what I mean.
Thanks for your help.
You really didn't have to do that.
I like painting.
Actually, it helps me turn my brain off.
It feels kind of Zen.
Actually, I wish you were
still trying to get into my pants...
...because this "Zen, helpful Roy" thing
is really freaking me out.
[ROY GASPS]
Get away from him.
-I'm not here for him.
ROY: Thea.
Thea. Thea, are you here?
So Malcolm Merlyn is alive
and Thea's father.
Anything else you haven't told me?
-What'd you get at the precinct?
-Not much.
But I did get this off a traffic camera.
It was recorded 10 minutes ago.
After I struck out on anything related to Nyssa
or Thea, I just looked for strange.
Well, that definitely counts.
Sara, she never said much
about the League...
...but she said their communication system
was outdated.
-Smoke signal.
-Nyssa's sending Malcolm a message.
I'm willing to bet my wallet...
-...that means "we got your daughter."
-Video gives me her location.
-You mean "us," right?
-No, I need you to secure the perimeter.
-Can't risk Thea seeing you.
-Copy that.
She knows I know about the Arrow.
Not with a dose of League tranquilizer
in your system.
Oliver, this is my fault.
I told Nyssa to go after Merlyn.
-I told her to do whatever it takes.
-It's okay.
I know you're not a killer.
But he is.
Whatever else he means to you or Thea...
...know that.
I'm gonna get free of this
and when I do, I'm gonna kill you.
NYSSA:
I apologize for involving you in this.
My quarrel's with your father.
My father's been dead for years,
you crazy psycho bitch.
Not Robert Queen.
Your true father, al-Saher, the magician.
Known to the uninitiated
as Malcolm Merlyn.
Then you know what he's gonna do to you
when he gets here.
I know he'll die.
My father taught me ways to cut a man
to make his death last for days.
-Sounds like father of the year.
-My father may be the Demon...
...but yours is the devil.
[GRUNTING]
GREEN ARROW:
Run!
Apparently, we both handle grief differently.
[GRUNTING]
MALCOLM: There's a misunderstanding
the three of us need to clear up.
A conversation I'm eager to have
over your rotting corpse.
[GRUNTING]
NYSSA:
Do it, Oliver.
He killed Sara...
...Tommy.
He will corrupt your sister.
There is blood on my hands.
Almost too much to contemplate.
But none of it is Sara's.
Kill him!
I did not kill your beloved!
Your father doubted Sara's loyalties
the moment you brought her home.
[HISSES]
You know your father,
what he is capable of.
He will kill without hesitation.
Do you really need me to tell you...
...what he'd do to the degenerate
who'd steal his daughter's heart?
[GRUNTS THEN INHALES DEEPLY]
Nyssa doesn't believe me, Oliver.
If you don't believe me...
...listen to her.
Kill me.
You may not have killed Sara...
...but you're still a murderer.
What are you gonna do?
Arrest me?
I could have S.C.P.D. here
in three minutes.
And in half that time, I will escape
from whatever prison they put me in.
You know that, so does she.
We were trained by the League,
no prison can hold us!
Not even your one on Lian Yu.
Which leaves you with only one option.
To break your vows...
...and kill me.
Kill your sister's father.
-Is Thea okay?
-I spoke to her.
She's fine.
Doesn't know who took her or why.
I may have deserved that.
You deserve worse.
Um, what's going on?
OLIVER:
Merlyn didn't kill Sara.
Which means whoever did
is still out there.
NYSSA:
You're a fool...
...who insults the memory of a woman
he once loved.
I will honor Sara's memory by finding
and punishing the person who did this.
The real person.
Nyssa.
So long as Malcolm Merlyn is in my city,
the League will make no move on him.
He's under my protection.
You would incur the wrath
of the League of Assassins?
I would do what I have to
in order to buy the time necessary...
...to find out what really happened
with Sara.
You have made an enemy tonight.
One with a long memory.
LAUREL:
Oliver.
Are you sure?
If I wasn't sure,
I never would have let him go.
-I promise.
-What did I miss?
WALLER:
I hate Hong Kong.
And I hate trans-Pacific flights.
And do not even get me started on the topic
of being summoned by one of my operatives.
Ferris Air flight 637,
Paris to Hong Kong nonstop.
You prevented that flight
from being shot down over Lian Yu.
-Were you watching me?
-Via Keyhole Hexagon satellite.
How else was I supposed to know
you possess the capabilities I require?
That business with the freighter last year.
Impressive. Are we done?
Just getting started, actually.
Adam Castwidth.
The man you had me murder.
He was Edward Fyers' handler.
-And he worked for you.
-You're out of your depth, Mr. Queen.
I don't think that I am.
I think Mr. Castwidth had a USB drive
detailing everything.
I think he knew you told Fyers
to shoot the plane down.
-And I think that you wanted him silenced.
-And the world thinks you dead, Mr. Queen.
The convenient thing about dead men
is that no one tends to believe them.
What about dead men who make arrangements
to get the information on that USB drive...
...in the hands of every blogger
and journalist in this hemisphere?
If anything happens to Maseo's family...
...you're gonna spend a long time
testifying in front of the Senate subcommittee.
The world's a much more complicated place
than you realize.
Edward Fyers thought he was to shoot down
that plane to destabilize the Chinese economy.
In truth, I wanted to take out a single target.
So you blow up a plane
full of innocent people to take out one man?
No, to take out one woman.
Chien Na Wei.
Two years ago,
we had our only chance at her.
And you saved her life.
And now she's in Hong Kong.
I need to know why.
LAUREL: I thought you were going back
to your father.
I felt I owed you a goodbye.
I intend to make good on my promise
to Sara.
And to you.
It kills me that he's still out there.
Merlyn.
Someone.
It kills me.
It pains me as well.
I see you've been training.
And wearing her jacket.
If you're gonna stand there and tell me
I'm not strong enough...
...please don't.
Back at the cemetery, I would have.
But since, you've reminded me that
the strongest metal is forged in the hottest fire.
And what's that supposed to mean?
Don't forget to turn your hips.
It's where the power comes from.
[LINE RINGS]
SARA [ON VOICEMAIL]:
It's Sara, leave a message.
Sara, sweetie, it's, uh...
It's me. Look, I... I know you said
only call this number in an emergency.
And it's not, it's not, everything is fine.
But I just...
[SIGHS]
I just wanna hear your voice.
I know wherever you are,
you're looking after yourself...
...but, you know,
that doesn't mean I don't worry.
So, you know...
Don't... No need to call me back
or anything.
I just want you to remember...
...that I love you.
Are you okay?
It's not my first time being kidnapped.
It's not what I meant.
I never imagined you and scrubbing.
Unless a spa treatment was involved.
[CHUCKLES]
I spoke to Detective Lance.
He doesn't think that woman
is gonna bother you again.
Why did she come after me
in the first place?
Maybe she thought
the Queens still had money.
I wish.
But thank you for checking in on me.
I'm always gonna watch out for you.
Always.
Sorry, guys, I didn't mean to interrupt.
I was just leaving.
Take care of yourself.
-I thought you had guys for that.
-It's kind of Zen.
You got that same worried look on your face
my brother had.
Really, I'm fine.
Good.
I just wanted to make sure you were okay.
And I wanted to apologize.
I'm sorry I couldn't stop her.
You tried. Really.
Those were some nice moves back there.
[CHUCKLES]
Whatever you're doing with the Arrow
is clearly paying off.
Maybe I should apply for a job here
as one of your bouncers.
I think I got that covered.
But I could use an assistant manager.
For real?
I need somebody who knows the place
as well as I do.
Absolutely.
-Purely platonic.
-Understood.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Oh, it's my designer, Kurt.
I should probably take this.
-Hi.
MALCOLM [OVER PHONE]: Are you safe?
I am now.
-Is that woman gone?
-For now.
-And your brother?
-He's completely in the dark.
He doesn't know a thing.
But thank you, Dad.
For what?
For taking care of me.
I promised you, Thea...
...I will never let anyone hurt you.
The rumors were true.
Malcolm Merlyn is in Starling City.
MAN:
There is a sadness in your voice.
Ta-er al-Sahfer.
She has fallen.
MAN:
Sara Lance is dead?
Yes.
Struck through the heart with an arrow.
MAN:
At Merlyn's hand?
It appears.
I have vowed a blood oath to avenge her.
MAN:
Al-Saher will face the League's justice.
But for his crimes against our code.
-But Sara...?
MAN: Was never truly one of us.
What of Queen?
He has sworn to protect Merlyn at any cost.
If that is true...
...then Oliver Queen courts war with us.