My name is Oliver Queen.
For 5 years,
I was stranded on an island
with only one goal--
survive.
Oliver Queen is alive.
Now I will fulfill
my father's dying wish--
to use the list
of names he left me
and bring down those
who are poisoning my city.
To do this, I must
become someone else.
I must become something else.
Previously on
Arrow...
- Mom?
- What are you doing here?
I believe Sarah's still alive.
You don't actually
have any proof.
I have proof.
Doesn't it look just like Sarah?
I did manage
to find one thing.
Does that symbol mean
something to you, sir?
I want to get out.
Malcolm Merlyn.
I want you to kill him for me.
We have a traitor
in our midst.
He just made his last mistake.
Lawyers for John Nickels
spoke to the press today.
They say they're pleased
the D.A. declined to indict
their client on charges
stemming from the recent fire
in one of Nickel's buildings.
John Nickel
is one of the wealthiest
real estate developers
in Starling City.
He's also one of the dirtiest.
That building
that burnt down last night?
Wiring was not up to code.
Maybe he didn't know that.
I guess he also didn't know
about the seven people
who have frozen to death
in his other buildings
over the past three years.
Yeah, he's a real
man of the people.
Not for long.
The D.A. ignores this,
and the police can't do anything
because all these slums
are in the Glades.
So tonight, Felicity,
we cross Mr. Nickel's name
off the list.
You ok with that?
The scene outside
of the courtroom
where Nickel was
released this afternoon
was not surprisingly tense.
100 percent.
Hello?
Aahh!
He was just gone?
No! Not gone. Taken.
Looks like Nickel was on
somebody else's list, too.
After the fire last night,
it's not entirely surprising.
Felicity, I need you
to get me everything
that you can on Nickel.
Focus on his tenants,
and anyone who might have
filed a formal complaint
against him, or...
people that lost
something in the fire.
Well, it's going to be some
list. I mean, slum lords
aren't generally known
for their popularity.
- Plus...
- What?
Nothing, it's just--
you went over there to be
all, "grrr, stop being bad
or I'll arrow you,"
and now you want to rescue him.
I don't like the idea that
somebody dangerous is out there.
Somebody else.
Because typically...
They don't show
my level of restraint.
So you're going
to cross Nickel off anyway?
No.
I'm finding somebody else
who needs a talking to.
You're going out
there again, Oliver?
Why don't you go home and
be with your family, man?
That's when the work
is done, Diggle.
Ok, then I'll take
you out to dinner.
I'm not hungry.
I'm not asking.
Simple exchange.
You get us a way
off the island,
and we'll give you
the circuit board
so that your missile launcher
isn't just furniture.
You've grown up quite
a bit, Mr. Queen.
I'll give you that.
I can get you a boat.
But I need time.
You got an hour, Fyers,
and then you're never--
what?!
We understand it might take you
longer than an hour to get a boat.
What we mean is you need
to move with some dispatch.
Ah, Wilson, still
in command there, eh?
I thought your little pet
had staged a coup d'etat.
Just get us the damn boat.
1x18
Salvation
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Resync for WEB-DL by lost0ne
Mmm.
Now you want to stop?
Well, we don't all have butlers.
You know, some of us actually
have to answer our own doors.
Oh, the horror.
You look familiar.
Did I see you
on TV or something?
Probably.
I'm Thea Queen.
Yeah, right.
Did you get it?
Tomorrow night.
Joe wants us there at 11 p.m.
He said to be on time, Harper.
What's happening
tomorrow at 11:00?
You know, I'm actually
kind of focused on
what's happening right now.
- Oh, ok.
- Yeah.
No, no, Thea, don't!
Why do you have a gun?
Because I'm no good with knives.
Look, it's just a liquor store.
The guy's a creep.
Trust me, he deserves it.
Look, if it'll make you
feel any better...
I won't be armed.
But of course, the owner
won't know that, but...
I got you a job
at my brother's club.
You have choices.
You don't have to be a criminal!
I'm not talking about
phone bills.
I owe people.
People with much
bigger guns than this.
Look, here in the Glades,
this is pretty much
the only solution.
No, lots of people in the Glades
live honest lives.
Obviously not you.
- You're just a waste.
- No, Thea.
Thea!
I'm going to make sure
you get home ok.
Don't bother.
Yeah. Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
Hey, honey.
There you go.
Um, what's all this?
Well, you asked me to look into
your mother's leads on Sarah,
so I made some calls.
It looks like you did a lot
more than that.
Well, yeah, but you're the one who
said we should do this, Laurel,
so, you know, if there's even a
chance that your sister is--
- yeah, but--
- Thank you.
Hi, sweetheart,
I'm sorry about the mess.
Quentin, I just got off the phone
with the consulate in Phuket.
The secretary there's
going to run Sarah's photo
against their database,
see if there's a match.
That's good work.
What?
Well, I guess I just
thought deep down
that you were going
to help mom...
accept things.
Things you and I accepted.
Um...
Yeah, but...
You got to admit.
This girl, she looks
a lot like Sarah.
Sarah had that same cap.
The Starling City Rockets.
Your dad bought it
for her, remember?
Yeah, I remember.
Stranger things have happened.
Yeah. I can see that.
Hungrier than I thought.
Are you waiting for me to finish
before giving me the lecture?
Oliver, you've been
spending a lot of time
under that hood
the last couple weeks.
Keeps my ears warm.
And you made
this decision to, um,
avoid entanglements?
For their protection.
The people who get
close to me get hurt.
What's the problem?
Do you think
I'm losing my grip?
No, it's just the opposite,
really. You seem calm.
Scary calm.
I get that things didn't end well
with Helena, with McKenna...
With Laurel.
With Sarah.
- The list goes on.
- Yeah. But what do you do?
You hood up, you go home, you repeat.
It's not much of a life.
Well, the life that I'm leading
for myself right now
doesn't leave much room
for an actual life.
- And I don't need one.
- Wow.
That's a pretty bleak future
you plan on spending... with no one.
I'm used to isolation.
And that is exactly
what worries me.
You've been home
for 8 months, Oliver,
but I don't think
you left that island yet.
What the hell is going on?
Yeah?
Found Nickel. Click
the link I just sent you.
This came up on every screen
with an I.P. address
originating from the Glades.
If you make
the Glades your home,
you know who this man is.
John Nickel.
He owns your tenements.
Manages your slums.
Provides the leaking
roofs over your head.
The mold in your pipes
and asbestos in your walls.
Basically, he makes money
off our suffering.
But the police aren't
interested in helping us.
They may have let us down,
but I won't.
John, I want to give you
the chance to state your case.
Why shouldn't you be punished?
I knew there was
bad stuff in my buildings.
Track him, Felicity.
- I'm looking.
- Ok, yes, I made a little profit!
At least they had
a place to live.
Without me, people like that
would end up on the street.
"People like that."
That's all we are
to guys like this.
- Aaah!
- Don't.
I find you...
Guilty.
There are plenty more
people who need to answer
for their crimes against us.
So...
Who's next?
- Anything new?
- This guy's definitely
got more than
a subscription to "Wired."
His website's protected
by some very serious encryption.
Well, use that air magnet thing,
you said that it could trace--
Oliver! No offense.
Do I tell you how
to sharpen your arrows?
Spoke to my friend at the NSA.
The website code matches a cyber
crusader who's been on their radar.
He hacks into fringe sites
under the user name "The Savior."
NSA believes he's a former
resident of the Glades.
- Former?
- Yeah, well, a year ago,
he hacked himself
right off the radar.
He erased all traces
of his existence.
So what happened a year ago?
We're back.
I have with me assistant
district attorney
Gavin Carnahan.
Now, DAs are supposed
to go after bad guys.
But this one can't even be
bothered to bring them to trial.
Like the ones who killed
my wife in a bodega.
- Felicity...
- I'm on it.
They said there wasn't
enough evidence.
You think the evidence
would have turned up
if she'd been killed
in one of Starling City's
nicer neighborhoods?
Emma Falk. Grieving husband
is Joseph Falk.
What do we have on him?
Not much.
42, former city worker.
Department of transportation,
computer technician,
left his job when she was killed.
One year ago today.
No current phone,
no current address.
Gavin, you're a lawyer.
You're used to making a case.
So go ahead.
I'm going to give you
ten minutes to deliver
the closing argument of your life.
Come on.
I'm trying to get a lock
on his wireless signal.
10 minutes to convince
me not to blow you away.
What did Malcolm want
with you at the hospital?
A target for reprisal.
He wants justice, and he's not
going to stop until he gets it.
Besides, this is good.
I think your definition of good
requires an adjustment.
No, he came to me.
Which means he doesn't know
that we're responsible
for the attempt on his life.
Yet.
What are the chances
of Malcolm discovering
who paid the triad
to assassinate him?
I was very discreet.
I wired the money through
a shell corporation I own,
from an offshore account.
Offshore?
Good.
That's good.
I'm sending Amanda
to London for a few weeks,
just as a precaution.
Perhaps you should
do the same for your family.
There's nothing I wouldn't do
to protect my children, Frank.
Hey, can I talk to you
about something?
Almost woman to woman.
I'm really busy right now.
Ok.
Thea.
Sorry.
What's up?
I could use some advice.
I'm sort of dating this guy
who would definitely be
described as a bad boy.
And I figured,
as someone who's dated
like a gajillion of them...
I haven't dated a gajillion.
All right, guilty as charged.
You want my advice? Run.
As fast as you possibly can.
Yeah. See, that was my first
instinct, too, but--
Laurel?
The Chinese embassy's
on line two.
I'm transferring him over.
Chinese embassy?
It's just this case
that I'm working on.
But we are definitely continuing
this conversation later.
Thank you so much
for getting back to me.
I'm trying to track down
a woman in the photo
that I emailed you.
You did.
Really?
And you're sure that
she's in the states now?
Do you happen to have
an address on her?
- I got him!
- Shut it down.
Can't. He has a firewall
protecting his wireless signal.
But he's working off an IPX
located at 23rd and Mira.
- You want to hood up?
- The middle of the day!
Look! Listen.
Listen to me. Ok.
I have 53 cases
on my desk right now.
I don't always have time
to take on every case!
How's Carnahan?
Not making a very
persuasive argument.
I'm almost there.
See anything?
I'm only on the first floor.
Just six more to go.
There aren't resources.
I tried.
- Oh, my God! I'm sorry!
- Oliver, hurry.
Can't find him!
- He's not here, Felicity!
- What?!
I searched every office
on every floor!
He's not here.
Is this the right place?
- Are you sure?
- Yeah, I--
Oh, crap.
What?
How is this possible?!
This can't happen! He's--
- Talk to me!
- Wait.
He moved. Just north of you.
Ocean and Grand.
On my way!
I took on cases that were--that I
thought that I could...
- Win.
- Yes.
I'm sorry.
Gavin Carnahan,
I find you guilty
of crimes against the Glades.
Don't do this!
And I sentence you to death.
I'm at Ocean and Grand, Felicity.
That's just a vacant lot.
How is this possible?
This can't happen. He--
Find the right address, now!
He's...
Oliver, it's over,
Carnahan is dead.
Where's Diggle?
I asked him to leave me alone.
In my loud voice.
This wasn't your fault.
I was the one who was supposed
to find Carnahan,
and I was the one
who sent you that bogus location.
I've never seen anybody die.
Hey.
This is the thing
with what we do.
Sometimes we lose.
Maybe it is better being alone.
I'm not seeing anyone
currently, but...
If I were,
I don't know how I'd tell him
about today.
Gentlemen. Welcome.
So happy we were able
to reach an accord.
Oh, good.
Small talk.
Are we going
to get on with this?
As you wish.
Straight to business.
The circuit board.
Where is it?
Somewhere safe.
So get us to the boat and then
we'll tell you where it is.
And of course you'll be honest
about its location.
Well, I wouldn't be.
But this one's got
some strange hang up
about principles
and integrity.
I always imagined as much.
Which is why I'd like to
make a counter proposal.
Men!
No!
You will deliver back
to me the circuit board,
or I will kill
Yao Fei's daughter.
So I wouldn't leave.
I can't imagine
you want the death
of an innocent young
woman on your hands.
Not with your...
Principles.
Hey.
Hi.
I wanted to do
some research on my own
into the evidence
that you gathered on Sarah.
So I called my friend
from law school
who works at the Chinese
embassy, and...
The photo of the girl.
I found her.
I'm sorry. Can I--
can I borrow your phone?
I promised my fianée
that I'd call him before dinner.
My phone's dead.
Jen, these are my parents.
Hi. Nice to meet you.
Yeah, you, too.
I just told Jen
about this photograph
that popped up in this case
that I'm working on.
Is that you in the picture?
Yeah. I spent six months
on an island
off the coast of China.
That was taken
in a small fishing village
called Zhengjiu.
It's Mandarin for...
Salvation.
Are you all right, Mrs. Lance?
Yes, I--
it's just, uh,
you look like
someone I used to know.
Wow.
I was waiting for this.
Waiting for what?
The whole "You can change,
I can see the real you" speech.
Look around, Thea.
This is home sweet home for me.
You either starve
or you do things
that mean you're lucky
enough to make it to 21.
- I can't accept that.
- No.
You can't accept me.
- Roy Harper?
- Yeah?
Roy!
More on the story
out of the Glades.
The kidnapper seems
to have another victim
and is broadcasting the feed
to his website.
A warning to viewers,
this is live footage,
so we're not sure
what we're about to see.
Meet Roy Harper.
Arrests for larceny
and robbery,
aggravated assault.
And yet you're out
on the street.
Another gangbanger
in the Glades running free,
like the ones
who killed my wife.
I'm grew up in
the Glades, too.
And it didn't turn me
into a criminal.
I know that kid.
- How?
- Tommy!
Tommy?
Oh!
Oh, God, no.
I didn't know where else to go.
- You know him?
- Roy, he's my friend.
And we were in a fight and
some guy came out of nowhere
and just attacked us!
He doesn't deserve to die!
I promise you,
he's going to be ok.
You stay here with
Tommy, all right?
Hello?
Moira, it's Malcolm.
I've learned
a high ranking member
of the Triad
was just arrested.
Well, I should have
a word with him.
I already have.
He's agreed to find out
who hired his organization
to assassinate me in return
for a reduced prison sentence.
By tonight, we should know
the name, or names,
of the people
who tried to kill me.
Good.
What are you doing?
So it's not Sarah
in the photo.
But she's still
out there, Quentin.
And I'm going to find her.
Look, I understand now
that neither of you
have the stomach
to continue looking for her.
And that's fine.
I'm sorry I involved you both.
You know that I would cross
to hell and back
to bring her home,
but I can't!
'Cause she's gone, Di.
No.
You got to let go of this now.
No! I can't!
I won't!
How did you know
Sarah had her hat
with her when she
went on the boat?
You were so sure that the girl
in the photo was Sarah.
Not because she was American,
but because of her hat.
Her Starling City Rockets hat
that dad bought her.
Mom.
How did you know
she took her hat
with her on "the Queen's Gambit"
with Oliver?
I saw her.
What do you mean?
I came home early that day,
and I saw her.
Sarah.
I saw her put the hat in a bag.
She was packing.
You knew she was
going with him?
I told her not to--
I told her not to do this,
not to you, Laurel.
But she said she was in love
and she had to follow her heart,
even if nobody else
thought it was right.
Just like I told her...
Just like I told her I once did.
So...
I let her go.
I killed her.
I...
I killed my daughter.
I killed her.
I'm so sorry, Quentin.
I killed our baby.
Anything?
I've been going through
all the video we got,
trying to see if there's
anything that'll tell us
where this guy is.
I got nothing, except a sound.
Buried in the ambient noise.
Almost rhythmic.
Here, I've isolated it.
What is that?
Sounds like a car driving
over lane markers.
It's bigger than a car.
Bigger than a car.
What, a bus? Uh--
wait, I know this.
I know it.
Come on! Guys!
Felicity, show me a map.
Sights of the abductions
on where we've seen
the signal so far.
Right there, right there.
23rd and Mira.
Locksley and Adams.
Wells street down by CNRI.
Those are all subway stops!
Starling City
doesn't have a subway.
No, but they used to.
When I was a kid,
my dad used to take me down
to the Rockets game.
By subway. For 14 minutes,
I'd lean against the window,
feeling the rhythm
of the train moving.
That's how he did it.
He was at 23rd and Mira,
but he was underground.
He used to work for the
department of transportation,
so that's why he knows
all the old subway stops.
That's why I couldn't
trace the signal.
He was moving.
He was in a subway car.
Where is he now?
He's on the old
cross town line.
If he continues on this route,
he'll be at the Spring Street
stop in 15 minutes.
Let the girl go.
No deal?
Very well.
Kill her.
No!
That was unexpected.
Fire!
Ahh!
Come on!
Get her to safety! Now!
I'll only slow you down. Go!
Just go! You've got to go!
Go! Go!
Go!
- It's happening.
- I'll give you 10 minutes
to state your case, Roy.
So tell us.
Why do you get to live?
I shouldn't.
Just do it.
Kill me.
Just go on!
Kill me!
You really don't care
if you live or die?
No one's going to miss me.
I'm just a waste.
Then we agree on something.
This world would be
better off without you in it.
We seem to have lost the feed.
We will stay on this story
and keep you up to date
on any developments.
Let the kid go.
You kill this kid,
you'll never get
an opportunity to change!
You can give him
a second chance.
We're the only ones
who can save this city.
We can't stop now.
We're not the same!
You've killed people
for this city, so have I.
What's the difference
between you and me?
Emma never got
her second chance.
You have no idea
how lonely it is.
Joseph.
Joseph!
I understand being alone.
But it doesn't
give you the right
to kill people in cold blood.
He deserves it.
Just like the gangbangers
who gunned her down,
he's no different than them.
And now I get to gun him down.
Don't do it!
Got to get going
to the airport.
That red eye to Central City.
I should be home in a flash.
Mom.
Call me some time.
I'd really like that.
You would?
Of course I would.
You're my mother.
I love you so much.
I love you, too.
I thought you were
going to die.
That makes two of us.
I probably look like a mess.
I'm going to go
to the bathroom and freshen
way, way up.
Ok.
[ ♪ Stay ♪
by Rihanna playing ]
♪ All along, it was a fever ♪
♪ a cold sweat,
hot-headed believer ♪
Ollie?
Hi!
Hey.
I heard Thea's friend was ok.
Yeah. That worked out ok.
This Roy...
is more than just
a friend, isn't he?
Bad boys.
Hook you every time.
Oh, I think, uh,
Tommy actually went home
for the night.
Oh.
You all right?
You seem like you're something
other than all right.
My mom, she showed up
in town this week
and she's been...
What?
She had this crazy idea
that Sarah was still alive.
She was so sure of it
that she kind of had me
believing it, also.
But Sarah's gone.
Yeah.
I can't believe
she sucked me in like that.
- You miss her.
- I miss them both.
Thanks for listening.
Of course.
Laurel.
Want to have dinner, or...
coffee, I don't know.
Why?
I don't want to be
on an island anymore.
♪ The reason I hold on ♪
♪ ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
♪ 'Cause I need this hole gone ♪
- Good night.
♪ I want you to stay ♪
Slade?
Circuit board's gone.
Damn. Fyers played us.
While he was
screwing us around,
his men were combing
the woods for it.
Now his missile launcher
is fully operational.
And he was never going to
let us off the island, I get it!
Of course he wasn't
going to help you.
He couldn't chance you
warning the mainland
what he has planned.
- She speaks English.
- Yeah, well, guess what.
Neither one of us
have any idea what his plans are.
I do.
Thank you for coming, Frank.
Meeting like this
is dangerous, Moira.
- Particularly now.
- Yes, I know.
Malcolm knows.
- What?!
- I had no choice
but to turn over
what I've discovered.
The evidence
of the wire transfer;
the money that you paid
the Triad to assassinate him.
The money I--
Moira!
Oh!
Mr. Merlyn thanks you
for your loyalty.
You've done well.
Now Chen's family
will share his fate.
Chen betrayed us,
but his daughter didn't.
Tell Mr. Merlyn
I want her to live.
Amanda nearly lost her
life in the Glades,
now she's lost her father. I think
she's suffered enough.
We must send a message.
We have.
We...
- Very well.
- Thank you--
Thea's friend is upstairs.
I saw.
You probably saw that they were
very happy to see each other,
if you know what I mean.
Which you probably don't
want to talk about,
because she's
your baby sister.
You ok?
I'm getting there.
Thank you.
Psst.
By the way.
If you ever need to tell
someone about your day...
You can tell me.
What's that?
Felicity pulled it up.
It's an old map
of a decommissioned
subway line.
Runs underneath
the low rent district of the city.
I've seen that map before.
It was right in front
of our faces
the entire time.
My father, the other archer,
the undertaking,
whatever the plan is.
It's all connected
to the Glades.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Resync for WEB-DL by lost0ne