Previously on "Arrow"...
- I need your help, Roy.
- You really think
an energy weapon's gonna
stop this Monitor guy?
We got the plutonium
with an assist from Roy.
You're working with the Monitor.
Mar Novu is trying to save
worlds, not destroy them.
I didn't want to believe it.
The only way to win is
to accept the inevitable.
Where the hell are we?
We're on Lian Yu.
The name of the island they
found me on is Lian Yu.
It's Mandarin for purgatory.
Now I understand why.
The memories, the pain,
I've never escaped them.
They're always with me,
a reminder of what I had to endure
with only one thought, one goal...
Survive.
To save the multiverse, I
must become something else.
To do that, I have to return
to where my journey began...
Purgatory.
Synced & corrected by QueenMaddie
www.addic7ed.com
So this is the famous Lian Yu.
I did not want a return
ticket to this place.
The 3 of you were supposed to
be safe and sound in Star City.
How'd you get here?
A bunch of guys in tac gear came
and stormed the bunker.
A.R.G.U.S Agents.
Sounds just as fun as tranq darts.
I'm sorry about that.
I needed you here, and I didn't
have time to convince you.
What the hell's going on, Lyla?
Mar Novu needs us to build a weapon,
and it has to be done on this island.
I'm not doing anything for that guy.
John, we have to.
Since when do we take
orders from the enemy?
We were wrong about Novu, John.
He's not our enemy.
Since when?
He dropped me in an alternate reality
in order to teach me the lesson that
to fix the multiverse,
we need to work with him.
This is crazy.
I know it's hard to hear,
Johnny, but it's the truth.
John...
How do we build the weapon?
The materials we need are already here
in the crates outside.
Dr. Wong has been experimenting
with the dwarf star particles
since leaving Hong Kong.
He's designed schematics for the build.
Schematics? Why does that make me think
that this Dr. Wong guy won't
actually build this thing?
We're counting on you for that.
- Say again?
- The device is powered by plutonium.
Dinah, Roy, and Rene
are on their way here
with samples from Star City.
So my mission was part of this?
All of our missions are a part of this.
With all due respect,
what am I doing back on Lian Yu?
In the past few days,
the island has seen
a rash of energy spikes.
Is that your reason for it being green?
Because the last time that I was here,
Adrian chase blew it up.
Yes. Harnessing that energy is the key,
and we need to do it right away because
we have no idea how long
the energy spikes will last.
Okay, wait. So we...
build this magic weapon
for the space god
and we stop Crisis?
There is no stopping Crisis.
Well, then what's the weapon for?
I don't know,
but Novu said this is how we survive it,
and I believe him.
If we can't stop Crisis...
Sorry.
What is he talking about?
Oh, my God.
Would the group mind if I
had a moment with my kids?
Of course.
There's no easy way to say this.
Mar Novu has seen my fate.
I don't survive Crisis.
- What do you mean?
- I mean that he told me
what would happen to me
the day that he walked in
and asked for my help.
And when exactly were you
planning on telling us?
I've been fighting my fate
because of the two of you,
and I can't fight it, I can't change it.
So you're just giving up?
I am attempting to save the multiverse,
and I'm trying to keep
the two of you safe.
We're gonna build the weapon,
we're gonna finish this mission,
and that's the way that it has to be.
Well, then I guess we better get to it.
Lyla, what happened to no
more secrets between us?
I'm sorry I couldn't tell you.
So you thought tranqing
me and bringing me here
of all places was somehow
a better explanation.
Mar Novu made it clear that silence was
a requirement of the mission.
We couldn't risk interfering
with the journeys of the other players.
As in Oliver's journey
ending in a death sentence?
What did Novu ask you to do, Lyla?
He didn't give me details.
He just told me that
when the time comes,
I would know what to do.
You're just fine with that? Why?
Faith.
You remember that IED that took
out my unit in Afghanistan.
I remember that. Of course I do.
You were the only survivor.
Took you years to stop having
nightmares about that blast.
Mar Novu when he first came to me,
he told me he rescued me that day...
because I have a greater purpose.
- And you believed him?
- A grown man in costume
prophesizing the apocalypse?
I thought it was a joke,
but then he came to me again,
and he showed me...
us, our future...
just... wiped away,
gone as if it never existed.
So you made a deal with him?
We would work together to find heroes
strong enough to face this Crisis.
He told me it was the only way
I could protect our family.
Lyla, you may have accepted that this
was the only way to move forward,
but I have not.
I won't.
Guess I shouldn't be surprised
the Black Canary knows how to fly.
Flying's easy. Landing's the hard part.
Kidding.
There it is...
Purgatory.
Looks a little less bombed
out than I remember.
Wow. After everything I've
heard about this place,
I didn't imagine it to be so...
Terrifying?
Beautiful.
Makes sense you'd think so
since apparently you're moving here.
Maybe not.
This time around, you
are part of a team.
Island team, do you copy?
We are 5 miles south and
inbound for landing. Over.
We copy. Island team will meet you
at the airstrip to unload. Over.
No wind to speak of. Looks like we're in
for a relatively smooth landing.
Hang on.
Hang on. What the hell is that?
Something's wrong.
Hey. Is everything all right up there?
We're picking up...
Something's incoming.
Did she say, "incoming"?
Dinah, are you there? Can you read me?
Can you read me?
Oh, my God.
Brace for emergency landing.
Hold on!
They're not gonna make it.
We need to find the crash site.
I'm working as fast as I can.
I can't get in contact with
Roy, Rene, or Dinah.
Something keeps blocking my signal.
Not something, someone.
Whoever shot down that plane.
You should have told
us we weren't alone.
I thought we were.
I had A.R.G.U.S.
sweep the entire island.
Okay. I just got the coordinates,
but the plutonium landed
in a different spot.
There's a tracker in the case,
but it's nowhere near
Rene, Dinah, or Roy.
The people are the priority.
Well, obviously, but we
still need the plutonium
to build the weapon.
All right. John, let's split up.
I'll run point on the rescue.
Connor, you're with me.
I'm coming, too.
I called them here. This is on me.
Whatever the 3 of you
do, just be careful.
We don't know who these
people are or what they want.
Copy that.
And I guess that means,
what, the 3 of us,
we are on nuclear weapon duty?
I'm staying here.
Are you okay with that?
Someone needs to protect William.
Gee. Thanks.
It's fair.
Thank you.
William synched this map to
the plutonium's location.
It's gonna get us close to the case,
but the coordinates won't be exact,
so we're gonna have to sweep the area.
Well, the sooner we find it, the better
because I am not a fan of this island.
Yeah? Well, it has
that effect on people.
You know, I, uh... I never expected
to be on a mission with
you like this, you know.
I'm glad you're here.
No offense, but shouldn't
this Kodak moment
be with you and someone else?
- What?
- You and Mia.
Oh. Trying to give her a little space.
Sure you're not trying to
avoid a difficult conversation?
I'm pretty sure she doesn't
want to talk to me, Laurel.
Oliver, don't be an idiot, okay?
All that girl wants to do
is live up to her father.
Fine. All this father wants
is to complete this mission
so that my kids actually
have a world to live in.
We are almost there. Come on.
Oliver.
A piece of advice.
Don't leave this island
with more regrets
than you already have buried here.
Oh. Building this weapon with
2019 tech may actually kill me.
I miss the future.
What's this?
Those are very volatile
dwarf star particles
that could level an
entire city or island.
All right. What can I do to help, huh?
Well, do you know how to
calculate the volume of a sphere?
4/3 pi times radius cubed.
I was raised by Felicity, too, remember?
Right.
Well, do you know what the
Pauli exclusion principle
of quantum physics is?
Didn't pay that much attention.
Well, then that pretty much
takes you out of the running
of helping me in any meaningful way.
Damn. I'm gonna need a wire stripper.
These are the most complicated coding
and design sequences I have ever seen,
and I'm including 2040
when I say, "ever".
It's not like you to
hide out in the bunker
and miss out on all the action.
Still mad at Dad?
It's his life.
He can do whatever he
wants with it, right?
Always has.
You're being a bit
harsh, don't you think?
And you are being a bit
chill, don't you think?
I was right all along.
Yeah. He has always been a hero first
and a dad second.
We never should have trusted him.
- Mia.
- I'm getting your wire stripper.
I'm sorry our first
meeting had to be this.
I envisioned getting to know
my future son over a meal,
not en route to a plane crash.
This...
this feels about right for our family.
Most of our milestones got interrupted
by some sort of international
emergency or another.
Yeah. I guess your dad
and I weren't really there
for you and J.J.
You were there when it counted.
Besides, I was beyond
proud to be the son
of the two superspies that
co-founded Knightwatch.
You never mentioned that.
I think maybe I wasn't supposed to.
Time travel rules and all.
Have to assume that the
timelines are different now
unless you remember your
mother being in league
with a evil deity.
Mar Novu is not evil.
Our friends' plane got
shot out of the sky, Lyla.
How do you know that wasn't
part of his cosmic plan?
And don't say faith.
Because I'm fresh out.
Okay, okay.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
You guys okay?
I think so.
We have no idea where Roy is.
Okay. You are definitely not okay.
We cannot let this get infected.
You guys keep searching.
I'll take Rene back
- and get him fixed up.
- Okay. Go, go, go.
- We need to find Roy.
- Where? Where?
This way.
Laurel, I found it!
Laurel!
Let her go.
I'm afraid he can't do that.
Hello, Oliver.
Fyers.
- You're dead.
- What?
Seems I've been given
a new lease on life,
though this time I'll be
sure to finish the job.
Drop your weapon.
Drop... your weapon!
Friends of yours?
Edward Fyers and Billy Wintergreen.
They were on the island
when I first got here,
and they're both dead.
So now we're fighting ghosts?
How is that even possible?
- Get this to William.
- Where are you going?
I have to go after Fyers.
Or you come with me,
and we finish this weapon
and get the hell off
this nightmare island.
Fyers is my mess.
He's a mercenary that
I fought and I killed.
He clearly wants revenge,
and makes him my responsibility.
All right. I'll be back
as soon as I can.
_
Yao Fei?
- Are you real?
- As real as the men you hunt.
Why'd you try to shoot me?
Like the first time.
To keep you from danger.
No one can keep me from
danger. Okay? Not even you.
Because you are fated to die?
There are forces at play
that want you to not succeed.
Fyers and his men know about the weapon,
and they want to use it for themselves.
All right. Well, who
else has, um, returned?
Only those who were with
you from the beginning,
but you must not let the evil
that tempted you at the start
distract you at the end.
He's coming after more than my
mission, Yao Fei, you understand?
I'm not gonna let that happen.
Last time you tried to do
alone did not end well.
I'm not that person anymore.
I will hope.
- Roy!
Roy!
There!
I can't... I can't move!
Roy, we're gonna get you out of here.
His arm is pinned.
- Can you feel anything?
- No, no.
We got a problem. Fuel.
Okay. We got to get him out of here
before this whole thing blows.
Let's get this off of him, okay?
- Yeah.
- 1, 2, 3, lift!
How bad is it?
Tell me!
Your arm is crushed.
If you can't feel it, then
that means pretty badly.
If we can't move what is pinning you,
then we need to start thinking
about other contingencies.
What are we talking about here?
We don't have much time.
The best way to get Roy out
might be amputation.
Can you do that?
I have a med kit in my pack back there.
It'll have what I need.
If we can just move
this off of him, okay,
we have a chance at saving his arm.
I mean, the odds aren't very good.
We owe it to him to keep trying!
Just move this thing, all right?
Let's go!
- Dinah.
- I'm gonna check it out.
Yeah. All right. Look.
Let's try to find a lever
to help get this off of him, okay?
Roy, just hang tight.
We'll be right back.
Oh, good. You're not dead.
Or maybe I spoke too soon.
Rene is injured but okay.
Roy's in a bad spot.
Well, we're all gonna be there with him
if... if we don't keep moving.
Sounds like you found the
guys who shot down our plane.
Oliver's old island enemies.
They've been dead for the last 12 years.
Heh heh. Of course they have.
Where is Oliver?
He went after them,
made me the radioactive material mule.
Let's go.
1, 2, 3!
Damn it!
It's not moving.
It's got to be caught on something,
a root system or something.
All right. Then we dig him out.
- We dig him out.
- We have to hurry.
Guys, we're about to have company
- and not the good kind.
- We can hold them off!
The fuel's about to spark,
John. We don't have time.
We can trench it, Dinah!
- Dad, we are out of options!
- We are not out of options!
- I don't accept that!
- We don't have a choice!
We always have a choice, Connor.
Then I'll make it.
Do it. Just... cut me free.
No. No, Roy.
John, it's better my arm than our lives.
Get the kit. Get the kit.
Laurel and I will distract them.
Here. You apply the tourniquet.
I'll get ready.
Just hold on, okay? Just hold on.
Okay.
This will be over fast.
Am I gonna feel it?
Probably.
I'm with you, Roy. I'm with you, okay?
You ready?
Do it!
Hyah!
Fyers' camp is just ahead.
We should not be back here.
You don't have to help, Yao Fei.
I help for Shado.
I'm sorry I couldn't save her.
You know the bond now
between a father and a child.
I do. It's exactly why I
have to put Fyers down.
Should be right up here.
They're gone.
Okay. That doesn't make any sense.
He should be here.
Fyers knew you'd come here.
Well, now he's free and clear to
attack my friends and my family.
We need to get out of here.
How?
Use your bow?
It's pinned.
All right. Well...
We will have to cut our way out.
The net is made of braided steel.
- That blade won't cut.
- It'll cut.
I got you, I got you.
What the hell happened?
His arm got pinned
underneath the landing gear.
We had to amputate.
I'm sure you did what you needed to do.
- Roy?
- William.
Not sure it's really a good
time for a meet and greet.
Is Oliver back yet?
We thought he was with you.
No. He went after the
bad guys on his own.
- Why would you let him do that?
- Seriously?
We have to go after him.
No. No. William has
to finish the weapon.
I don't care about your weapon!
Oliver knows this island
better than anyone, Mia.
He'll be fine.
Plus it's smarter for
us to stick together.
No. We are not leaving him out there.
Mia!
Fine. I'll go on my own!
- This is a bad idea.
- Then don't come with me.
You heard Laurel. We
should stick together.
- It's smarter tactically.
- Are you really gonna lecture me
on tactics right now?
Well... no, but...
Dig is right.
I mean, Dad and this
island, they go way back,
and he knows every inch of this place.
You going out there
could make things worse.
I'll take my chances.
Get out of my way.
William.
Look. It is okay for you
to be afraid of losing him,
especially after the way
that you left things.
You don't know what
you're talking about.
This is exactly what
happened with Felicity.
You were angry with her, but
you still wanted to save her.
I'm not just gonna sit
here and do nothing, okay?
I will not leave him
alone out there. I...
I will not...
let him die.
I let myself believe for just...
Just a minute that I could
actually have my dad.
Look. When I was a kid, I spent
a lot of time pushing him away...
because I never thought
that I could lose him,
and then he disappeared.
Yeah. Now we might lose him again.
- How are you so calm about this?
- I'm not, but...
When I was little, Felicity
had me down in that bunker
watching Dad out in the field,
and I saw that he could cheat
death more than anyone,
but if this really is the end,
I don't want to waste the time that
I have left with him being angry.
Do you?
I was wrong. You haven't changed.
Still that impatient boy I found.
You realize that
insulting me is not gonna
make this go any faster, right?
Breathe.
Remember in everything, breathe.
I'm trying to...
...cut my way out of a net,
Yao Fei, not shoot an arrow.
We wouldn't be in this
net if you had breathed.
You know what Fyers
is capable of, right?
I need to get back to my family,
and I'm running out of time.
You could be with your family,
but you chose here instead.
I chose to protect them.
You avoid them because
you're fated to die.
I've been fighting that
fate for a long time.
I've accepted it.
That hasn't made things any easier.
What am I supposed to say to my kids?
What I could not to Shado.
You say good-bye.
I don't think that I can.
My kids have spent basically
their entire lives without me.
And they're about to have
to do it all over again.
You think you have failed.
The first thing that you taught me...
Shengcún, survive.
Well, I can't do that anymore.
Shengcún is more than body.
It is spirit, what lives on
like I did in Shado,
like she does in you.
That is survive.
How do I do that?
You live now,
with your children,
with the time you have left.
I need to get out of this net first.
Always have patience.
Like I said, patience.
Huh!
Just came by to check on
you. How you feeling?
I... I've been better.
I'm so sorry, Roy.
I should have found
another way to get you out.
This wasn't your fault.
Yeah. Well, that's where you're wrong.
I mean, you wouldn't
even be in this situation
if I hadn't come to
find you in Hub City.
Roy...
I can't protect the people I care about.
You know I worked with you and
Oliver for a really long time,
and if I've learned anything,
it's that this team
has each other's backs
no matter the cost.
Things just didn't
exactly go as planned.
That's an understatement.
No, but I would rather be here.
I would rather be here with you
and with the team than back in Hub City,
living a life all alone.
Heroes make sacrifices, John,
and for better or for worse,
this just had to be mine.
John... we got a problem.
Fyers and his men have
surrounded the camp.
We can expect an attack any minute.
How long before the weapon is ready?
I'm done building it. Once
the plutonium finishes
transferring the energy,
I can turn it on.
- How long will that take?
- I'm not sure.
Can we take this to a
safer part of the island
- and finish it there?
- No, no. It has to be here.
I've tapped into the center
of the island's energy.
- We can't move.
- And it has to be tonight.
We don't know when the next energy spike
will be, and we can't afford to wait.
We need to buy William more time.
Dad, you're okay.
Yeah. An old friend steered me back.
I'm sorry that I took off.
Should have been here
with the two of you.
You're here now.
How are we supposed to
beat an army of ghosts?
Power up the device.
The sphere's absorbing
the energy of the island,
and if that's what brought
these dead people back to
life in the first place...
Activating the device will destroy them.
We're talking about plutonium here.
That's nasty stuff. It can take out
this entire island, us included!
If this is our best chance
of surviving the Crisis,
then we need to take the risk.
Lyla's right. She's right.
This is it.
This is our best shot.
Suit up.
You are as foolish as ever, Queen.
Surrender!
I suppose that means you're
not here to surrender to me.
I'm the one who killed you, Fyers.
I'm very pleased to return the favor,
a task you've made much
easier by coming alone.
I'm not alone.
Now that the plutonium has
transferred the energy,
all I have to do is power it on,
and voilà!
It doesn't look on.
- Why isn't it working?
- I have no idea.
It doesn't matter how
many people you have.
The outcome is the same.
Kill them!
William, we're running out of time.
Okay. I think I have something.
There was a double
helix genetic sequence
in Dr. Wong's formula.
I thought it was an error,
but now I think the device
can only be powered on
using a specific DNA code.
Oliver.
Oliver, we need you back
here to activate the device.
Oliver, you got to go!
Yao Fei, if this works...
We will part again, but the
dead are never really gone.
I've got your 6.
They're not gonna be able to
hold them off much longer.
We need to hurry.
The sphere is touch-activated.
It'll turn on the moment
you pick it up, and...
I don't know what happens after that.
Okay.
Wow. That was anticlimactic.
- What the hell?
- What? What is it?
Dad's DNA doesn't match the
algorithm's specified sequence.
Does that mean we can't turn it on?
You can't...
But she can.
What are you talking about?
The DNA sequence isn't Dad's.
It's yours.
Is it me, or is this not going well?
We got to buy them some time.
God, I hate this island!
Might as well go out with a bang.
I thought this weapon was supposed
to help us survive Crisis.
That's what Novu told me.
Does this mean you're the weapon?
Johnny...
I understand why you have to do this.
Lyla, are you all right?
I have to go.
Hey, guys. I just, uh...
I just connected with A.R.G.U.S.,
and Lyla organized a rescue boat
before everything happened.
Should be here any minute, so...
So, we're all going home.
Did Mom... did she know what
was gonna happen to her?
No. No. She was just as
surprised as the rest of us.
Novu just loves surprises, doesn't he?
Whatever Mar Novu has planned for Lyla,
she can handle it.
How much time do we have,
before the Crisis?
Not long.
Should, um, probably finish packing,
before the boat arrives.
Agreed. No more island vacations.
Uh, hey, guys.
Listen. I just wanted to...
I wanted to thank both of you
for just being there
for me no matter what.
Why does this sound
like a good-bye speech?
Pass. Do not accept.
This ain't over till it's over, Oliver.
Come on.
Hey.
I don't really know what to say.
I'm really happy that you're
back with the team, and...
I'm really sorry.
I'll be okay.
Plus, Dig's gonna set me up with one
of those fancy A.R.G.U.S. doctors.
Uh, the boat's almost ready.
We good down here?
Yeah. We should go.
Oh. Uh, almost forgot.
This is what led me
here in the future...
to you and, uh, to the team.
Thought you might like it back.
I don't need it.
Plus, I think it should
stay in the family.
You know, when Felicity gave this to me,
she told me it was a
symbol of reconnection.
- She was right.
- She normally is.
No. You keep it.
William, what you were able to do,
you're a hero.
Well, I had a pretty good example.
It means a lot to me
that I've had a chance to...
to see the type of man you've become.
I hope you'll forgive me
for... lots of things eventually.
Dad, I already have.
I mean, I know for you
I only left a year ago.
For me, it's been 20 years,
and back then when I was a kid,
I didn't understand what it meant
to fight for something
bigger than yourself,
but now I do,
and I'm really proud of you, Dad.
Not as proud as I am of you.
- I'm gonna hug you now.
- You better.
Thinking about where Lyla went?
Can't think about anything else.
I know this is a
sacrifice she has to make
for the multiverse.
I feel like I'm always
asking you favors.
Anything you need, Oliver, always.
I need those kids back in 2040,
somehow, some way before
whatever's gonna happen happens.
Yeah. I was thinking
about the same thing.
I'll make sure they get home safe.
One more thing.
When this is over,
track down Felicity and...
Just tell her that I don't want...
Mia and William kept separated.
I think that they deserve
to grow up with each other.
I'll tell her.
Yeah.
You know, Oliver, I once
told you a long time ago
that a soldier never lets a
brother go into battle alone.
I think that's why it was so
hard for me to accept the idea
that you weren't gonna
make it out of this.
I felt like I'd be failing you.
You could never fail me, John.
I'm gonna stick by your side
for as long as I can,
but I know you have to do this alone.
Every mission has an end.
I wish this one didn't.
I couldn't have done any of this,
any of it without you.
You've always been my rock.
Don't mean the best
man you've ever known?
I also mean that.
Hey. Let's get out of here, man.
Don't want to keep the boat waiting.
I'll be right behind you.
One more thing I got to do.
Hey.
Um, William said I might find you here.
Figured you'd be the
first one on the boat.
You okay?
My whole life...
I heard nothing but stories about you,
you know, this legendary
Green Arrow and his team.
I should have been proud of you,
because you were a hero, and...
All I could see is that that is
the reason that you weren't with me,
and it's... it's kind of
hard to let that go.
I never meant to cause you any pain.
Your mom and me just
wanted to protect you.
I know.
I, uh... I understand that now.
For a very long time,
I have hated this place.
Just I'd think about all the
people that it took from me.
It would just... It would
just make me so angry.
But you're not now?
I'm still a little bit angry.
This island taught me to survive.
It turned me into someone else,
somebody better than
the person I was before.
So despite my feelings...
There are no stories about
the Green Arrow to tell...
if I don't make my way to Lian Yu,
and I'm also not
standing at this moment,
looking at my daughter.
Thank you for letting me
be a part of your story,
even if it was only for a little while.
Mia, something tells me you're
gonna create your own stories.
So what now?
We need to get back home,
and just be prepared
for whatever's coming next.
Okay.
Dad.
- Lyla?
- Not anymore.
I'm now a Harbinger of things to come.
- And that's...
- Yes.
The Crisis has begun.
For so many years,
I've traveled across worlds...
_
across the multiverse to do one thing...
Kill you.
And now here...
you saved my life.
Submit and begin your life anew.
Show me.
The knowledge is within you.
_