MY NAME IS OLIVER QUEEN.
AFTER 5 YEARS IN HELL,
I RETURNED HOME
WITH ONLY ONE GOAL...
TO SAVE MY CITY.
TODAY, I FIGHT THAT WAR
ON TWO FRONTS.
BY DAY, I LEAD STAR CITY
AS ITS MAYOR,
BUT BY NIGHT,
I AM SOMEONE ELSE.
I AM...SOMETHING ELSE.
I AM THE GREEN ARROW.
PREVIOUSLY ON "ARROW"...
REALLY SORRY
ABOUT THIS, SERGEANT.
YOU'RE NOT HERE
TO SECURE THE TRIGGER.
YOU'RE STEALING IT.
WANT TO READ
YOUR CONFESSION
BEFORE YOU SIGN IT?
YOU DID THIS!
NO ONE WILL EVER
BELIEVE YOUR STORY.
WE CALL OURSELVES HELIX.
WE'RE CALLING
THE DATA CACHE PANDORA.
WITH IT, YOU CAN SPARK
REVOLUTIONS.
SO YOU'RE NOT JUST
GIVING ME THE FILE
FOR JOHN.
GOT WHAT WE NEED TO
EXONERATE JOHN.
-HOW'D YOU DO THAT?
-LONG STORY.
PLEASED TO MEET YOU.
I KNOW EXACTLY HOW
THIS BROTHERHOOD WORKS,
AND RIGHT NOW,
IT WORKS FOR ME.
SHIPWRECKED ON LIAN YU,
FLED TO HONG KONG,
AND NOW YOU'RE MIXED UP
WITH THE BRATVA.
THE MAN WHO SURVIVED
ALL THIS
IS DESTINED
FOR SO MUCH MORE.
YOU NEED TO GIVE
THE MONSTER AN IDENTITY.
IT'S ONLY WHEN
THE MONSTER BECOMES
SOMEONE ELSE,
SOME...THING ELSE
THAT YOU'RE FREE TO
BE OLIVER QUEEN.
I DON'T KNOW
IF I'M READY.
I WILL HELP YOU
BECOME READY.
[MEN SPEAKING RUSSIAN]
WHAT ARE WE DOING HERE?
THESE ARE LOW-LEVEL
DRUG DEALERS.
THEY'RE TARGET PRACTICE.
[GRUNTING]
YOU'RE BEGINNING
TO UNDERSTAND NOW.
UNDERSTAND WHAT?
THAT THE MAN WHO
EMBRACES THE DARK
IS NEVER WITHOUT SIGHT.
AHEM. OK. SO IS THIS
THE ORCHARD BAY FACILITY
OR THE DOWNTOWN REBUILD?
HOW LONG UNTIL
THE...ANNOUNCEMENT?
DON'T YOU HAVE
A CHIEF OF STAFF WHO
USUALLY HANDLES
THIS STUFF?
EXCUSE US, PLEASE.
THEA IS LOOKING
INTO A FEW JOINT INITIATIVES
THAT I PROPOSED WHILE
IN HUB CITY LAST WEEK.
OH, THAT'S REALLY
TOO BAD.
I'VE COME
TO LOOK FORWARD
TO HER MANY LOOKS
OF DEATH.
THEA LIKES YOU.
SHE'S JUST...
IT'S OK, OLIVER.
SHE'S NOT THE QUEEN
I'M SEEING.
THAT'S SORT OF
AN OLD-FASHIONED WAY
TO SAY IT, DON'T YOU THINK?
WELL, I'M NOT REALLY
SURE HOW ELSE TO PUT IT
GIVEN THAT WE HAVEN'T
PROGRESSED.
THAT'S A FUNNY WAY
OF SAYING WE HAVEN'T
SLEPT TOGETHER.
QUENTIN: AHEM. HI.
HI, QUENTIN.
I WASN'T EXPECTING
TO SEE YOU TODAY.
WELL, YOU KNOW,
THAT'S THE THING
ABOUT REHAB.
IT'S A LONG PROCESS,
AND THEN IT AIN'T,
AND BY THE LOOKS
OF THAT ASSISTANT
OUT THERE,
YOU NEED ME BACK
BAD.
HOW ABOUT I GIVE
YOU GUYS A MOMENT?
IT'S ALL RIGHT,
MS. WILLIAMS.
I WASN'T PLANNING ON
KEEPING MY PROBLEMS
A SECRET.
IN FACT, I WANTED
TO TALK WITH YOU
ABOUT THEM,
YOU KNOW, ON CAMERA.
I'LL HAVE MY PEOPLE
SET UP AN INTERVIEW.
THANK YOU.
I BELIEVE YOU ARE
RUNNING LATE
FOR A PRESS CONFERENCE,
MR. MAYOR.
WHOA, YOU LIVE
A COMPLICATED LIFE.
-HOW ARE YOU?
-YOU KNOW, I'M BETTER
THAN I'VE BEEN
IN A LONG WHILE,
THANKS.
THAT'S FANTASTIC
TO HEAR,
BUT LOOK, MAYBE
WE SHOULDN'T...
WHAT, PUSHING MY LUCK
BY SITTING DOWN WITH
YOUR NEW GIRLFRIEND?
WELL, NO. JUST...JUST
WAIT A LITTLE BIT.
LET THEA COME BACK
AND PREP YOU AND...
OLIVER, IF I WERE
ANY MORE DRY,
I'D BE DUST, OK?
I'M READY TO
MOVE FORWARD,
AND THIS IS HOW.
NOW DIDN'T MS. WILLIAMS
SAY YOU'RE LATE
FOR A PRESS CONFERENCE?
YEAH.
OLIVER, VOICE-OVER: I'D LIKE TO
THANK DISTRICT ATTORNEY CHASE,
WHO STEPPED OUT OF HIS LANE TO
REPRESENT MY FRIEND JOHN DIGGLE
AND TO MAKE SURE THAT
JUSTICE WAS DONE.
MR. CHASE'S EFFORTS
FURTHER EXEMPLIFY
STAR CITY TAKES CARE
OF THEIR OWN.
THANK YOU, EVERYBODY.
THAT WILL BE ALL.
THANK YOU
FOR GETTING ME OUT.
THANK WHOEVER LEAKED
THE NSA's CASE
AGAINST WALKER.
MY JOB WAS EASY.
CONGRATULATIONS,
MR. DIGGLE.
I WAS WONDERING IF
THE D.A. MIGHT HAVE
A SECOND TO CHAT.
SAVE YOUR ENERGY,
MS. WILLIAMS.
I KNOW YOU'RE DOING
A STORY ON THE DEATH
OF DETECTIVE MALONE.
I HAVE NO COMMENT
FOR YOU.
AND YET EVERYONE
I SPOKE TO YOU SAID
YOU WERE THE MAN
TO SPEAK TO.
IT'S A LITTLE ODD
FOR A D.A. TO BE SO INVOLVED
IN A POLICE MATTER.
OLIVER: THE VICTIM WAS
A MEMBER OF THE ACU.
THAT OFFICE IS MONITORED
BY CITY HALL,
NOT BY THE SCPD.
-OH, MY GOD.
-NOT WHAT YOU WANTED TO HEAR?
THE MILITARY POLICE
JUST TOOK GENERAL WALKER
INTO CUSTODY.
WALKER AND HIS MEN JUST
SHOT THEIR WAY OFF
OF FORT ZERILLO.
30 DEAD,
AND HE AND HIS MEN
ARE IN THE WIND,
AND THE NUKE TRIGGER
HE STOLE IN CHECHNYA
IS STILL MISSING.
WHAT CAN YOU
TELL US?
FELICITY: LOTS, BUT FIRST,
WELCOME BACK.
-HUGS, KISSES, WARM FEELINGS.
-LIKEWISE.
I JUST GOT WORD
FROM LYLA THAT ARGUS
DISCOVERED A BATCH
OF ENCRYPTED E-MAILS
BETWEEN WALKER AND A GROUP
OF MARKOVIAN SEPARATISTS.
HE'S LOOKING TO
SELL THE NUKE.
WE CAN'T LET
THAT HAPPEN.
WE HAVE THE U.S. MILITARY
AND ARGUS HUNTING WALKER.
THEY CAN'T GO
WHERE IT'S GOING.
THE SALE'S
IN RUSSIA.
JOHN: THIS ONE'S PERSONAL.
I GOT TO TAKE THAT
MURDEROUS SON OF A BITCH
OFF THE GRID RIGHT NOW,
WHATEVER IT TAKES.
CITY HALL GIVES ME ACCESS
TO A PRIVATE PLANE.
-I'M COMING, TOO.
-FELICITY.
THIS IS PERSONAL
FOR ME, AS WELL.
I PROMISED I'D
NEVER LET ANOTHER
HAVENROCK HAPPEN
AGAIN AS LONG AS IT
WAS IN MY POWER,
AND I BELIEVE THAT
THIS QUALIFIES.
WALKER WILL HAVE HIS
WHOLE UNIT WITH HIM,
MAYBE EVEN SOME
MARKOVIANS.
WE NEED THE WHOLE TEAM
FOR THIS.
AGREED, BUT QUENTIN
JUST GOT OUT OF REHAB,
AND WITH THEA OUT
OF TOWN,
I...I NEED SOMEONE TO
KEEP AN EYE ON HIM.
WHO'D YOU HAVE
IN MIND?
[KNOCKS]
BETTER BE THE REPORT
ON THE WASHINGTON DISTRICT
WATER PROJECTS...
NOT EXACTLY, HOSS.
WHAT ARE YOU...WHAT?
WHY AREN'T YOU
IN YOUR OFFICE?
WELL, I CAME IN HERE
TO WORK
BECAUSE EVERYONE'S BEEN
DROPPING BY MY OFFICE,
ASKING HOW I AM,
AND I DON'T NEED
THE ATTENTION,
AND BY THE WAY,
I JUST GOT OFF THE PHONE
WITH OLIVER, WHO SAYS
HE'S ON THE WAY TO RUSSIA,
SO WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE?
OLIVER SAID I'M SUPPOSED
TO HELP YOU PREP
FOR YOUR INTERVIEW
WITH SUSAN WILLIAMS
AND IT WAS SAFER
FOR ME TO BE HERE
THAN OVER THERE STARTING
AN INTERNATIONAL
INCIDENT.
ALSO, YOU NEED TO TALK
TO YOUR RECEPTIONIST.
SHE DIDN'T BELIEVE
I WAS HERE FOR YOU.
I HAD TO SNEAK PAST HER
JUST TO GET IN.
WOW! I WONDER HOW SHE COULD
HAVE MADE THAT MISTAKE!
HEH HEH.
LISTEN. WHY DON'T YOU JUST DO
US BOTH A FAVOR, ALL RIGHT?
JUST GO HOME, POLISH YOUR
HOCKEY MASK OR SOMETHING,
AND I'LL JUST TELL
OLIVER YOU WERE HERE
THE WHOLE TIME.
THAT'S COOL, RIGHT? I'M...
SURE, EXCEPT YOU'RE
FRESH OUT OF REHAB,
NOT A POLITICIAN,
ABOUT TO FACE THE MEDIA,
SO WHAT'S IT HURT TO
HAVE A LITTLE HELP?
OH, JUST MY WAKING SANITY.
HA HA HA!
AHEM.
ALL RIGHT.
WELL, PULL UP A CHAIR.
ALL RIGHTIE.
-COFFEE?
-SURE.
OK. THIS WHOLE FLYING
PRIVATE THING
IS SOMETHING I COULD
REALLY GET USED TO.
BEING MAYOR HAS
ITS PERKS.
YOU'RE LUCKY THAT
STAR CITY'S SISTER CITY
IS IN RUSSIA.
AS OF 12 HOURS AGO
AT LEAST.
ARE YOU READY
FOR THIS?
WHEN I SIGNED ON,
I DIDN'T THINK
I'D BE STOPPING
A NUCLEAR ARMS DEAL
IN A FOREIGN
COUNTRY.
YEAH. WHEN I SIGNED ON,
I DIDN'T THINK
I'D BE DEALING
WITH ALIENS.
-ALIENS?
-YEAH.
CURTIS: JOHN SAID
YOU HAD FRIENDS
IN RUSSIA.
ONE FRIEND. REACHED OUT,
DIDN'T HEAR BACK.
-OLIVER QUEEN.
-ANATOLY.
UNH! OHH.
YOU NEVER SHOULD HAVE
COME BACK TO RUSSIA.
-ANATOLY?
-ALEXI LEONOV...
YOU REMEMBER HIM, YES?
HE WAS ONE
OF YOUR BROTHERS.
-I CAN EXPLAIN.
-YOU ASKED FAVOR OF HIM.
HE ASKED FAVOR IN RETURN,
AND YOU PULL GUN ON HIM INSTEAD?
YOU KNOW WHY I CAN'T
BE SOME BRATVA THUG.
YOU MADE PROMISE.
YOU SWORE OATH,
AND NOW ONE OF YOUR
BROTHERS IS DEAD,
SO WHY SHOULD I WELCOME
YOU AS BROTHER?
GO HOME, OLIVER.
THERE'S NOTHING
FOR YOU HERE.
FELICITY: OHH.
FEEL LIKE SOMEBODY
DIED OF TUBERCULOSIS
IN HERE.
RORY: WHAT'S THE RUSSIAN
WORD FOR CREEPY?
CURTIS: ZHUTKO.
I WAS STUDYING
ON THE PLANE.
WHERE DID YOU FIND
THIS PLACE?
JOHN: LYLA. THIS USED
TO BE AN ARGUS SAFE HOUSE,
AND AS YOU CAN TELL
FROM AMERO-RUSSIAN RELATIONS,
IT HASN'T BEEN USED
MUCH LATELY.
YEAH, NO KIDDING.
AND WHY AREN'T WE
WORKING WITH ARGUS?
I ASSUME PREVENTING
BLACK MARKET NUCLEAR DEALS
WOULD BE PRETTY HIGH
ON THEIR TO-DO LIST.
JOHN'S RIGHT
ABOUT RUSSIA.
ARGUS CAN'T OPERATE
HERE WITHOUT CAUSING
A DIPLOMATIC CRISIS.
FELICITY: OH, YEAH. SPEAKING
OF DIPLOMATIC CRISES,
WHY DID YOUR FRIEND
PUNCH YOU?
3 YEARS AGO, I USED
A BRATVA CONTACT
WHEN I WAS TRYING TO
TRACK SLADE WILSON.
HE ASKED ME
FOR SOMETHING
IN EXCHANGE.
I REFUSED.
SLADE KILLED HIM.
HOW LONG DO YOU
THINK UNTIL WE'RE
UP AND RUNNING?
I'M NOT SURE.
I'M PRETTY MUCH STARTING
FROM SCRATCH HERE,
AND I HAVE TO HACK
THE RUSSIAN SERVER TO SEE
IF WE CAN FIND
ANY CHATTER ON WALKER,
AND THAT MIGHT TAKE NO TIME,
OR IT MIGHT TAKE
A...A LOT OF TIME.
WHAT ABOUT YOUR
BRATVA FRIEND WITH
THE GOOD RIGHT HOOK?
YOU COULD TRY
MAKING NICE.
IT'S NOT THAT SIMPLE.
YEAH? WELL, SIMPLE
OR NOT, OLIVER,
WE HAVE TO USE
EVERY ASSET WE'VE GOT.
I MADE A MISTAKE
WITH LEONOV.
IT WAS A CHALLENGING TIME,
BUT YOU STILL OWE ME
FOR GREGOR.
LUCKY FOR YOU,
I NEVER LIKED LEONOV.
SIT. JOHN DIGGLE,
IT'S GOOD TO SEE YOU.
NOW YOU'RE
MY FAVORITE AMERICAN.
THANKS.
SO WHAT BRINGS YOU
TO RUSSIA?
WE'RE LOOKING FOR
A U.S. GENERAL THAT
HAS GONE ROGUE.
WE HAVE REASON TO
BELIEVE HE'S TRYING
TO SELL A NUKE
TO MARKOVIAN
TERRORISTS.
WHAT CONCERN IS THAT
OF YOURS?
ARE YOU GONNA HELP
ME FIND THIS MAN
OR NOT?
AFTER BUSINESS
WITH LEONOV,
JUST ME SITTING
WITH YOU SQUARES US
WITH GREGOR, YES?
-FINE.
-THEN WE ARE EVEN
AND BACK TO HOW THINGS
WORK IN BRATVA.
I HELP YOU,
YOU HELP ME.
AN ARRANGEMENT
YOU REFUSED WITH LEONOV
IF I'M NOT MISTAKEN.
AN ARRANGEMENT I'M
GOING TO REFUSE AGAIN.
THAT PART OF MY LIFE
IS OVER.
WELL, THEN I CANNOT
HELP YOU,
BUT I CAN OFFER YOU
SOME FREE ADVICE.
ACT QUICKLY, OLIVER.
THE MARKOVIANS DO NOT,
AS YOU AMERICANS SAY,
SIT ON THEIR HANDS.
YOU DID WELL.
YOU'VE PROVEN TO BE
A MOST ADEPT STUDENT.
I KNOW A FEW TEACHERS
WHO WOULD DISAGREE
WITH THAT ASSESSMENT.
HIDEO YAMANE...HIS NAME'S
IN MY FATHER'S NOTEBOOK.
FOR GOOD REASON.
MR. YAMANE'S
CRIMINAL ENTERPRISE
IS RESPONSIBLE FOR MUCH
OF THE DESIGNER DRUG TRADE
IN STARLING CITY.
I THINK YOU'LL RECOGNIZE
HIS CHIEF PRODUCT.
MY SISTER WAS
USING THIS,
SO I KILLED HER DEALER,
BUT I DIDN'T CONSIDER
THE SUPPLY.
I LEFT HER,
I LEFT THE CITY VULNERABLE.
THIS IS WHY I FOUND
YOU, OLIVER,
SO YOU CAN CORRECT
YOUR MISTAKES.
NOW MR. YIMANE IS
IN TOWN TONIGHT,
MEETING WITH HIS
RUSSIAN CONTACTS.
HE'S A CAREFUL MAN.
HE'LL BE HEAVILY
GUARDED.
AM I READY?
THAT'S WHAT WE
FIND OUT TONIGHT.
[CANARY CRY]
SORRY. I DON'T REALLY
HAVE MUCH CONTROL
BEYOND ON AND OFF.
YEAH, PROBABLY BECAUSE
YOU JUST PRODUCED THE SOUND
OF A THOUSAND BEYONCÉS.
I MEAN, POLYPHONICS
DOESN'T EVEN BEGIN
TO EXPLAIN
WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
FELICITY: CAN YOU GUYS
PLEASE...KEEP IT DOWN?
OK. WALKER HAS GONE
COMPLETELY DARK.
THERE IS NO WAY OF PINPOINTING
HIS IP OR HIS GPS
FROM HIS PHONE,
WHICH IS PROBABLY
JUST A BURNER ANYWAY.
THAT'S GOOD.
HOW IS THAT GOOD?
MILITARY MEN TEND
TO BE CREATURES
OF HABIT.
IF WALKER'S USING
A BURNER,
ODDS ARE IT'S
THE SAME MODEL HE
USED IN THE STATES.
AND THE ONLY ONE MAKING
CALLS TO THE MARKOVIANS.
WALKER'S FLIP PHONE
OF CHOICE IS AN OLD MODEL.
THE ONLY NETWORK HERE
THAT SUPPORTS IT IS
DETRALINK DST.
CURTIS: CAN YOU HACK IT?
I MEAN, I COULD,
BUT IT WOULD TAKE
A LOT OF TIME.
I THINK I KNOW SOMEONE THAT
COULD GET US A SHORT CUT.
YOU HAVE CONTACTS
IN RUSSIA, TOO?
KIND OF. UH, HE MIGHT
NEED A LITTLE BIT
OF CONVINCING.
THINK YOU TWO COULD
LOOK LIKE BRATVA?
[VIOLIN PLAYING RUSSIAN MUSIC]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
SORRY. I MEAN,
PROSTI.
I CAN'T SEE A THING
IN THESE.
TOUGH GUYS DON'T
SAY SORRY, CURTIS.
RIGHT. NO "PROSTI."
ERR.
FELICITY: GUYS, FOCUS.
WHY ISN'T DINAH HERE
WITH US?
LOOK. I'M SECURE ENOUGH
IN MY MANHOOD TO ADMIT
THAT SHE IS WAY MORE
INTIMIDATING THAN
EITHER ONE OF US.
YES, AND A TOTAL
UNKNOWN QUANTITY.
LOOK TOUGH.
MAXIM OSTROVSKY.
YOU SPEAK ENGLISH.
I SUGGEST YOU START
USING IT.
WHO ARE YOU?
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
TO TALK IN PRIVATE.
DON'T MAKE ME
ASK YOU AGAIN.
-WHO ARE YOU?
-SOMEONE WHO NEEDS ACCESS
TO YOUR SYSTEM'S
CREDENTIALS.
YOU WORK FOR DETRALINK.
NOT FOR LONG I WON'T
IF I GAVE YOU
MY SIGN-IN MATERIALS.
FUNNY. YOU DIDN'T SEEM
WORRIED ABOUT LOSING
YOUR JOB
WHEN YOU IGNORED
COMPANY POLICY TO
NOTIFY THE KREMLIN
ABOUT CERTAIN SUSPICIOUS
AND TERRORIST-LIKE
ACTIVITY
ON YOUR NETWORK
LAST YEAR.
HOW DO YOU KNOW
ABOUT THAT?
BETTER QUESTION IS
WHO WOULD I TELL...
BECAUSE I AM SURE
THAT THE KREMLIN
WOULD LOVE TO
HEAR ABOUT THIS.
YOU CAN'T.
MY FAMILY,
THEY'LL KILL THEM.
YES.
SO I SUGGEST IT'S
IN YOUR BEST INTEREST
TO GIVE ME EXACTLY
WHAT I WANT.
TIME TO GO.
PROSTI.
THAT GUY WAS
SERIOUSLY SHAKEN.
-WHAT'D YOU SAY?
-WHAT HE NEEDED TO HEAR.
I'VE GOT WHAT WE NEED TO
GET A LOCATION ON WALKER.
[ORGAN PLAYING]
[CONGREGANTS WHISPERING]
RECON'S IN POSITION.
I COUNT 10 CIVILIANS
IN THE CHURCH.
NO SIGN OF WALKER
OR HIS MEN.
BACKSTOP'S ALSO IN POSITION.
NO ACTIVITY HERE.
OLIVER: ARE WE SURE THIS
IS THE SPOT, OVERWATCH?
FELICITY: WALKER'S PHONE
JUST WENT ACTIVE
FROM THAT ADDRESS.
THERE.
JOHN, THERE ARE
CIVILIANS HERE.
I DON'T CARE, OLIVER.
THIS MAY BE OUR
ONLY SHOT.
WE'RE MOVING
ON THE TARGET.
EVERYONE, STAY SHARP.
[BUZZING]
JOHN: PROXIMITY ALARM!
WALKER KNEW
WE WERE COMING.
HEADS-UP! GET DOWN!
[MUFFLED GUNFIRE]
ARE YOU GUYS
HEARING THAT?
I'M GUESSING THOSE
AREN'T FIREWORKS.
RECON, GET THOSE
CIVILIANS CLEAR. BACKSTOP...
DINAH: COMING IN.
UNH!
WALKER: I DON'T KNOW WHO
YOU GENTLEMEN ARE,
BUT I WANT TO THANK YOU FOR
BEING SO DAMN EAGER TO FIND ME!
[CANARY CRY]
YOU GUYS ALL RIGHT?
OLIVER: YEAH. WE'RE GOOD.
JOHN:
WE LOST WALKER.
-OVERWATCH, DO YOU HAVE EYES ON?
-NEGATIVE.
ALL RIGHT.
MEET US OUT BACK.
WE GOT TO FIND
WALKER.
WE HAVE HIS MAN.
HE'LL TAKE US RIGHT TO HIM.
COME ON.
[MAN STRUGGLING]
WHAT THE HELL
IS THIS?
THERE'S NO WAY
YOU'RE ARGUS OR DoD.
SHUT UP!
DO WHATEVER
YOU WANT.
I'M NOT TELLING
YOU ANYTHING.
THERE ARE THOUSANDS,
MAYBE MILLIONS
OF LIVES AT STAKE.
[ZAP]
YOU DON'T WANT THOSE
DEATHS ON YOUR CONSCIENCE.
MY CONSCIENCE?
YOU GOT TO BE
KIDDING.
ERR! WHAT'S THAT?
THIS IS YOUR CONSCIENCE!
[GRUNTING]
-STOP!
-NOTHING STOPS.
NOTHING STOPS
UNTIL YOU TELL ME
WHEN AND WHERE
THE BUY IS HAPPENING.
NOW YOU HAVE 5 MINUTES
TO DECIDE
WHAT YOU WANT YOUR
FACE TO LOOK LIKE!
AGH! AAH!
OLIVER, YOU JUST GONNA
LEAVE HIM IN THERE?
-JUST GIVE IT TIME.
-OLIVER, WE DON'T HAVE TIME!
WE HAVE TO GET
WALKER NOW, RIGHT NOW!
LET ME IN THERE,
AND I'LL GIVE HIM ALL
THE PERSUASION HE NEEDS.
HE'S GONNA CRACK.
IF YOU PUSH HIM
TOO HARD RIGHT NOW,
HE'LL TELL YOU WHATEVER
YOU WANT TO HEAR
TO GET THE PAIN
TO STOP!
WE HAVE TO BE SMART,
JOHN.
YOU KNOW THAT.
AS MUCH AS I ENJOY MY
VISITS TO MOTHER RUSSIA,
HAVE YOU EVER
CONSIDERED RELOCATING
TO STARLING CITY?
[ARROWS WHOOSHING]
[GUNFIRE]
MAN: AAH!
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
MONEY? DRUGS?
I'LL GIVE YOU
ANYTHING.
THERE'S NOTHING YOU HAVE
THAT I WANT.
WHY? WHY ARE YOU
DOING THIS?
BECAUSE YOU HAVE FAILED
STARLING CITY.
ALL RIGHT.
I GOT TRANSCRIPTS
OF PAST INTERVIEWS
WILLIAMS HAS DONE
WITH ALKIES
AND ADDICTS...
NO OFFENSE.
AHEM. IS YOU BEING HERE
REALLY NECESSARY?
OLIVER WANTED ME
TO HELP YOU PREP
FOR THE INTERVIEW,
SO HOW ABOUT SOME
PRACTICE QUESTIONS?
ALL RIGHT. SO. YOU JUST
GOT OUT OF REHAB.
WHAT MAKES YOU THINK
YOU'RE STILL FIT TO
SERVE AS DEPUTY MAYOR?
WELL, UH, THAT'S
A VERY EXCELLENT
QUESTION, SUSAN.
-MS. WILLIAMS.
-MS. WILLIAMS. AHEM.
WELL, I THINK IT'S
MY DEDICATION TO THIS CITY.
I HAVE LIVED HERE
MY...MY WHOLE LIFE.
SO HAVE LOTS OF PEOPLE,
AND I'M PRETTY SURE
NOT ALL OF THEM ARE
RECOVERING ALCOHOLICS.
I THINK IT'S BEEN
MY ABILITY TO PERSEVERE.
WHAT ARE YOU
PERSEVERING THROUGH?
-COULD YOU BE MORE SPECIFIC?
-WELL, I'M TRYING TO.
WOULD YOU LET MET GET
A WORD IN EDGEWISE, PLEASE?
YOU THINK SUSAN WILLIAMS
IS GONNA GO ANY EASIER?
NOW WHEN DID
THE DRINKING BEGIN?
WAS IT BEFORE OR AFTER
THE DEATH OF YOUR
DAUGHTER LAUREL?
WHAT'D YOU JUST SAY?
DO YOU HOLD
YOURSELF ACCOUNTABLE
FOR HER DEATH
OR FOR WORKING
WITH DAMIEN DARHK?
SHUT YOUR DAMN MOUTH
ABOUT MY DAUGHTER!
DUDE, CHILL. I'M JUST
TRYING TO HELP.
YOU'RE TRYING
TO HELP?
GREAT. I'M GONNA
LEAVE HERE,
AND WHEN I GET BACK,
YOU DON'T BE HERE!
IT'S JUST ME.
YOU KNOW YOU HAVE
A WORKSTATION
INSIDE, RIGHT?
YEAH. I WASN'T HAVING
ANY LUCK LOCATING WALKER,
SO I DEICIDED I'D WORK
ON MY FRUSTRATION
IN PRIVATE.
-WHAT?
-THE GUY BACK IN THE TEA HOUSE
DIDN'T LOOK LIKE
SOMEONE WHO OWED
YOU A FAVOR.
HE WAS TERRIFIED.
FELICITY, WHAT'S
REALLY GOING ON?
THE NSA FILE THAT
EXONERATED JOHN,
IT WAS PART OF A CACHE
OF INFORMATION
GIVEN TO ME
BY A HACKER GROUP,
AND THAT CACHE INCLUDES
INTEL THAT I USED
TO PRESSURE
THE DETRALINK EXEC.
YOU MEAN,
YOU BLACKMAILED HIM.
-WELL...
-FOR THIS DATA CACHE
TO HAVE EXACTLY
WHAT YOU NEEDED
FOR THIS
PARTICULAR GUY,
IT HAS TO BE HUGE.
I THINK THE TERM IS
"BEYOND MASSIVE."
WHAT?
ONE OF THE LAST THINGS
MY DAD SAID TO ME
WHEN HE GAVE ME
THE RAGS
WAS THAT THEY HOLD
A POWER MOST PEOPLE
COULD NEVER EVEN IMAGINE
AND THAT I NEEDED
TO RESPECT
AND GUARD THAT POWER,
NOT ABUSE IT.
THE PEOPLE
IN THIS DATA CACHE,
THEY'RE NOT
GOOD PEOPLE.
I'M STARTING TO BELIEVE
THAT MY PURPOSE ON THIS EARTH
IS TO STOP PEOPLE
LIKE THEM, LIKE WALKER,
NO MATTER
WHAT THE COST.
SOMETIMES, YOU GOT TO
FIGHT FIRE WITH FIRE.
I'M NOT WORRIED
ABOUT THEM.
I'M WORRIED ABOUT YOU.
[VAN DOOR OPENS]
I THOUGHT YOU WERE WORKING
ON LOCATING WALKER.
YEAH.
IS EVERYTHING OK?
THIS MIGHT BE NONE
OF MY BUSINESS,
BUT I THINK SHE
CROSSED A LINE
TO FIND WALKER.
RORY.
WHAT LINE?
[WALKER'S MAN SCREAMING]
STAY HERE.
UNH!
WHERE'S THE BUY
HAPPENING?
-WHERE'S THE BUY HAPPENING?
-HEY, HEY!
JOHN, THAT
IS ENOUGH!
THAT'S ENOUGH!
I THOUGHT WE WERE
DOING THIS MY WAY.
YOUR WAY WASN'T
FAST ENOUGH, OLIVER!
I'M NOT LETTING WALKER
GET AWAY!
NEITHER AM I.
FELICITY: WHAT'S HAPPENING?
WHAT HAPPENED?
JOHN GOT A LITTLE
CARRIED AWAY.
DID HE SAY ANYTHING?
YOU GET YOURSELF
CLEANED UP.
-I'LL BE BACK.
-WHERE YOU GOING?
I'M GOING TO HANDLE THIS.
WHAT DO YOU NEED
ME TO DO?
THAT DID NOT
TAKE LONG.
ANATOLY,
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
TO OUR
IMPERFECT UNION.
VASHE ZDOROVIE.
-THANKS.
-FOR COMING AS BACKUP
OR FOR NOT
TELLING ANYONE?
BOTH.
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
UNH!
AGH!
[GUNFIRE, SHOUTING]
[MAN GROANING]
AGH!
[GROANING]
THIS ISN'T THE FIRST TIME
YOU'VE DONE SOMETHING
LIKE THIS...
IS IT?
I DON'T MEAN
AS THE GREEN ARROW.
YOU MEAN AS A THUG,
RIGHT?
NO. IT WAS...
IT WAS PART OF MY LIFE
THAT I THOUGHT THAT
I HAD MOVED PAST,
BUT...HERE WE ARE.
RIGHT.
YOU KNOW, THE OTHER GUYS
SAID WHEN YOU GET
IN ONE OF YOUR MOODS
I SHOULD JUST
LET YOU BE,
BUT, UM, TO BE HONEST,
BROODING
REALLY KIND OF
GETS ON MY NERVES.
THEY TOLD YOU ABOUT ME?
THEY TELL YOU
ABOUT PROMETHEUS?
YEAH, THEY DID.
W-W-WHY?
IS...IS THIS MOOD
BECAUSE YOU GOT PULLED BACK
INTO SOME
BRATVA DRAMA?
NO, IT...
DINAH, I'M TRYING
TO MOVE FORWARD,
BUT I'M BACK HERE,
I'M IN RUSSIA,
IN THE BRATVA,
AND IT JUST PROVES
TO ME I CAN'T SEEM
TO DO THAT.
PROMETHEUS GOT
IN YOUR HEAD.
WHAT WAS IT, SOME CRAP
ABOUT INFECTING
THE PEOPLE
CLOSEST TO YOU?
YEAH, AND TONIGHT,
I WATCHED JOHN
TORTURE A MAN,
AND THERE'S SOMETHING
GOING ON WITH FELICITY.
THERE'S...
YOU AFFECT THE PEOPLE
IN YOUR LIFE, OLIVER.
THAT'S HARDLY
A REVELATORY OBSERVATION.
IN...IN FACT,
I...I THINK IT'S, UH...
IT'S CALLED LIVING.
PROMETHEUS HAS YOU
SO FIXATED ON WHAT'S
WRONG WITH YOU
THAT YOU'VE COMPLETELY
STOPPED SEEING WHAT'S RIGHT.
YOU KNOW,
JOHN AND FELICITY,
THEY'LL LISTEN TO YOU
BECAUSE YOU HAVE
MORE TO OFFER
THAN JUST THIS.
YOUR PAST IS A PART
OF YOU.
THERE IS NOTHING
YOU CAN DO ABOUT THAT.
YOU CAN'T CHANGE IT.
IT DOESN'T MEAN IT
HAS TO BE YOUR ANCHOR.
TALIA: THE OTHER NAMES
IN THAT BOOK
ARE WAITING
FOR YOU, OLIVER.
THEY'RE WAITING FOR YOU
AT HOME.
I KNOW. LEAVING
THE BRATVA IS NOT
GOING TO BE EASY.
I SWORE AN OATH
OF ALLEGIANCE.
YOUR FATHER ASKED YOU
TO TAKE A DIFFERENT VOW,
DID HE NOT?
YOU TOLD ME HE WANTED
YOU TO RIGHT HIS WRONGS.
YOU CANNOT DO THAT
FROM HERE.
CAN I COME IN,
OR IS IT STILL
NO DOGS ALLOWED?
PFFT. YOU REALLY GOT
A WISEASS MOUTH
ON YOU, DON'T YOU?
I'M NOT SURE,
BUT DID YOU JUST SAY
MY MOUTH LOOKS LIKE ASS?
LOOK. I JUST CAME HERE
TO TELL YOU
THAT SUSAN WILLIAMS'
PRODUCER CALLED TO CONFIRM
THAT 10 A.M. TOMORROW STILL
WORKS FOR THE INTERVIEW.
WHEN DID YOU BECOME
MY ASSISTANT?
WHEN I ANSWERED
THE PHONE, I GUESS.
IT WAS OUT OF LINE
BRINGING UP MY DAUGHTER.
YOU GONNA TELL THAT
TO SUSAN WILLIAMS
AT 10 A.M. TOMORROW?
LOOK, MAN. YOU EXPECTING
ME TO GIVE YOU AN APOLOGY,
YOU DON'T KNOW ME
THAT WELL.
I DON'T KNOW
YOU AT ALL,
BUT MY SPONSOR SAYS
THAT I'M THE ONE THAT
OWES YOU THE APOLOGY.
IT'S COOL, HOSS.
NO, IT'S NOT COOL.
MY DAUGHTER LAUREL
IS GONE,
AND I GOT TO FIGURE OUT
A WAY TO LIVE WITH THAT
WHICH DOESN'T
INVOLVE BOOZE
OR SNAPPING AT GUYS
THAT ARE JUST
TRYING TO HELP.
YOU KNOW, 10 A.M.
WILL BE HERE
BEFORE YOU KNOW IT.
HOW ABOUT
ANOTHER DRY RUN?
TAKE A SEAT.
-ATTABOY.
-QUIT CALLING ME HOSS.
ALL RIGHT. READY?
WHERE ARE YOUR
QUESTIONS?
I GOT THEM RIGHT HERE.
WHERE WERE YOU?
DID YOU TAKE
DINAH SOMEWHERE?
-YEAH. NOT LIKE THAT.
-IT'S OK.
WHAT HAPPENS IN RUSSIA
STAYS IN RUSSIA,
REMEMBER?
WHERE'S WALKER'S MAN?
CURTIS AND RORY ARE
KEEPING EYES ON HIM.
I THINK SHE MEANS
PROTECTING HIM FROM ME.
OLIVER, I STILL THINK
IT'S A MISTAKE NOT PUSHING
THIS SCUM BAG FOR
THE LOCATION OF THE SALE.
WE DON'T HAVE TO.
WE'RE GONNA HAVE IT
WITHIN THE HOUR.
-WHAT? HOW?
-BRATVA.
ANATOLY WASN'T PLAYING BALL
UNLESS YOU DID
THE BRATVA'S DIRTY WORK...
WHICH IS WHERE YOU
TOOK DINAH.
OLIVER, I THOUGHT YOU
DIDN'T WANT ANYTHING TO
DO WITH THE BRATVA.
I DON'T,
BUT IF IT'S A CHOICE
BETWEEN ME
CROSSING THE LINE
AND THE TWO
OF YOU CROSSING ONE,
THAT IS
A VERY EASY CHOICE.
WHAT DID YOU DO?
IT DOESN'T MATTER.
HERE'S WHAT DOES.
I AM WHO I AM.
NOW I'M TRYING TO
WORK PAST THAT.
MAYBE I DO,
MAYBE I DON'T,
BUT I CANNOT...
I WILL NOT HAVE
THE TWO OF YOU
MAKE THE SAME MISTAKES.
OLIVER, YOU ARE
THE ONE THAT
TAUGHT US
THAT SOMETIMES
YOU HAVE TO GET
IN THE MUCK
TO MAKE THINGS
RIGHT.
WELL, THEN
PROMETHEUS WINS
BECAUSE HE'LL BE RIGHT.
I NEED THE TWO OF YOU
TO PROVE TO HIM
AND, QUITE FRANKLY,
TO PROVE TO ME
THAT HE'S NOT.
I NEED THE TWO OF YOU
TO BE BETTER THAN ME
BECAUSE YOU ARE.
THAT'S WHY WE WORK
TOGETHER.
UH, THERE IS A WHOLE MESS OF
ANGRY RUSSIAN DUDES OUTSIDE.
ANATOLY: I HAVE LOCATION
FOR WALKER
AND MEN TO HELP IN FIGHT,
BUT WE HAVE TO LEAVE NOW.
YOUR STRANGE FRIEND'S
PRONUNCIATION IS HORRIBLE.
YEAH. I'LL TUTOR
HIM LATER.
[MEN SHOUTING]
HEY.
PLEASURE DOING
BUSINESS WITH YOU, LEV.
YOU SURE YOU
DON'T WANT TO TOAST
THE TRANSACTION?
EH, I'D LOVE TO,
BUT I GOT A PLANE
TO CATCH,
AND THERE'S SOMEONE
I'M TRYING TO AVOID.
AMERICAN GOVERNMENT?
HEH HEH. I WISH IT
WERE JUST THAT.
OHH!
[TIRES SQUEAL]
GREEN ARROW, TANGO
HEADED YOUR WAY.
I LOVE SAYING
THE WORD "TANGO."
SO DO I.
[GUNFIRE]
[TIRES SQUEALING]
[CANARY CRY]
CURTIS: UH, OK.
IN THE FUTURE,
YOU MIGHT NOT WANT TO
DO THAT WITH A VAN
CARRYING A NUCLEAR BOMB.
THAT WAS NEAT TRICK.
NOW WHAT'S YOUR PLAN?
[TIRES SQUEAL]
[GUNS COCKING]
STAY DOWN,
YOU SON OF A BITCH!
WHO THE HELL
ARE YOU?
YOU DIDN'T EXPECT TO SEE
ME HERE, DID YOU, GENERAL,
AND NO ONE'S GONNA
BELIEVE THAT I WAS,
BUT EVERYONE'S GONNA KNOW
THAT YOU TRIED TO SELL
A NUCLEAR BOMB
TO TERRORISTS.
YOU'RE ASSUMING I
ACTUALLY MEANT TO SELL
THE BOMB TO
THE MARKOVIANS, JOHN.
BOMB'S NOT HERE.
WALKER WAS HEADED
FOR THE HANGAR.
ODDS ARE THAT'S
WHERE THE NUKE IS.
FELICITY!
WHY THE RUSE?
WHY SELL
A NUCLEAR WEAPON ONCE
WHEN I CAN STEAL IT
BACK AND SELL IT
TO ANOTHER REBEL SUCKER?
HA HA HA!
FELICITY: RORY!
CURTIS TOLD ME YOU
NEEDED SOME HELP.
HE WAS PROBABLY WORRIED
I'D DO SOMETHING STUPID.
THOSE WERE HIS EXACT
WORDS ACTUALLY.
OK. YOU NEED TO GET
OUT OF HERE.
AND HE SAID THOSE WOULD
BE YOUR EXACT WORDS.
-THE BOMB IS IN COUNTDOWN MODE.
-WHAT?!
IT'S WIRED WITH A FAILSAFE.
WE MUST HAVE TRIGGERED IT
WHEN WE ENTERED
THE HANGAR.
-CAN YOU DISARM IT?
-IF I CAN'T...
THE YIELD OF THIS THING
WILL SPREAD OVER 50 MILES.
DO IT.
YOU KNOW YOU
WANT TO.
COME ON, JOHN.
YOU HAVE TO.
I GOT A LOT
OF FRIENDS, JOHN,
WITH A LOT
OF RESOURCES
AND ITCHY
TRIGGER FINGERS,
AND YOU...
WELL, YOU GOT
A WIFE AND KID.
TERRIFIC, OVERWATCH,
ANY LUCK LOCATING THE NUKES?
CURTIS: OVERWATCH IS
OFF COMMS AND IN THE HANGAR.
I THINK SHE'S TRYING
TO DISABLE THE NUKE HERSELF.
I'M ON MY WAY.
-NO. NO.
-WHAT HAPPENED?
TRAPDOOR CODE.
I WALKED RIGHT INTO IT.
-WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
-ANY ATTEMPT TO DISARM THE NUKE
WILL EXPONENTIALLY PACE UP
THE COUNTDOWN CLOCK.
WELL, W-W-WHAT
ARE YOU DOING?
HOPING LIKE HELL
I CAN FIGURE OUT
HOW TO FLY A PLANE.
-WHAT?!
-I CAN'T DISARM THE NUKE,
BUT HOPEFULLY I CAN
GET IT TO A LESS
POPULATED AREA.
LESS POPULATED?
WHA...LIKE HAVENROCK?
RORY, THIS ISN'T
THE TIME TO
REVISIT THAT.
NO, NO, NO.
THIS IS EXACTLY THE TIME.
THE...THE RAGS SURVIVED
HAVENROCK.
THEY CAN SURVIVE THIS, TOO.
I CAN USE THEM
TO CONTAIN THE BLAST
AND THE RADIATION.
-NO. YOU DON'T KNOW THAT!
-WELL, I DON'T NEED TO KNOW.
I...HAVE...FAITH.
OK. WELL, IT SHOULD
BE ME, NOT YOU.
I DON'T HAVE TIME TO
TAKE THESE RAGS OFF,
SO GO JUST IN CASE
THIS, YOU KNOW,
DOESN'T WORK.
FELICITY, GO!
WALKER: DO IT.
GO ON.
NO, GENERAL.
[UNCOCKS GUN]
NO. YOU'RE GONNA
STAND TRIAL.
I'M GONNA SEE THAT
JUSTICE IS DONE.
OH, SHEMA YISRAEL.
ADONAI ELOHEINU,
ADONAI ECHAD...
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
-RORY!
-OH, MY GOD!
[GROANS]
HE ALWAYS GETS
THE CREDIT.
ARE YOU OK?
THIS MEANS I GET
A PROMOTION, RIGHT?
HEH.
[GROANS]
CURTIS: TO RORY
AND HIS AMAZING
NUKE-STOPPING RAGS,
WHICH HOPEFULLY DOESN'T
GIVE US ALL RADIATION POISONING.
-OHH!
-AGH.
[CURTIS AND FELICITY
COUGHING]
JOHN: WIMPS.
DINAH: YEAH. CAN'T YOU
HOLD YOUR VODKA?
NOW YOU'RE MY
FAVORITE AMERICAN.
DID YOU HEAR FROM LYLA?
WALKER'S BEING ESCORTED
UNDER MILITARY GUARD
AS WE SPEAK.
-CONGRATULATIONS.
-YOU KNOW, OLIVER,
WALKER THREATENED
JJ AND LYLA JUST
LIKE ANDY DID.
AT FIRST, I WONDERED
WHY I DIDN'T SHOOT HIM
LIKE I DID ANDY.
THEN I REMEMBERED
WHAT YOU SAID TO ME
AND FELICITY.
WELL, I'M JUST GLAD
THAT IT TOOK.
BUT, YOU KNOW, OLIVER,
YOU WERE WRONG.
ME AND FELICITY,
WE'RE NO BETTER THAN YOU.
YOU, ME, FELICITY,
WE MAKE EACH OTHER BETTER.
I'LL DRINK TO THAT.
YOU'RE MY BROTHER,
OLIVER.
OLIVER, HEH HEH.
IT'S GOOD...GOOD
BEING FRIENDS AGAIN.
I FORGOT HOW STRONG
THIS IS OVER HERE.
I MAKE SURE
AND BRING SOME
WHEN I COME
TO STAR CITY.
HEH.
AHH. I HEAR YOU'RE
MAYOR NOW.
BIG PROMOTION, HMM?
NOW YOU PAKHAN.
NOW YOU TELL EVERYONE
WHAT TO DO.
THAT'S NOT HOW THINGS
WORK IN AMERICA,
ANATOLY.
HMM. YEAH. THAT'S
THE WAY THINGS
WORK EVERYWHERE.
I WAS HOPING MAYBE
YOU COULD REPAY ME.
THOUGHT WE WERE EVEN.
I THOUGHT YOU RETURNED
TO BRATVA.
THAT WAS TEMPORARY.
THAT IS THE THING
ABOUT OATHS, OLIVER.
THEY ARE NEVER
TEMPORARY.
THEY ARE FOR LIFE.
I NEED TO SPEAK
WITH ANATOLY.
WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN?
I NEED TO SPEAK
WITH ANATOLY.
WHERE IS HE?
[HEART MONITOR BEEPING]
ANATOLY.
OLIVER...
IS THAT YOU?
YEAH.
WHAT HAPPENED?
GREGOR.
I QUESTIONED HIS DEAL
WITH KOVAR.
HE DID THIS TO ME.
YOU WERE RIGHT
ABOUT HIM.
HIS LOYALTY LIES
WITH KOVAR,
BUT GREGOR IS PAKHAN.
THERE IS NOTHING
WE CAN DO.
THAT'S NOT TRUE.
WE CAN KILL HIM.
YOU ARE MY BROTHER,
OLIVER.
OLEG SAID THAT YOU
NEEDED TO TELL ME
SOMETHING.
IT CAN WAIT.
YOU KNOW, IF VISITING
STAR CITY'S SISTER CITY
IS WHAT IT TOOK
TO GET YOU TO BED,
I WOULD HAVE BOUGHT YOU
A TICKET TO RUSSIA
MONTHS AGO.
HEH HEH HEH.
A FRIEND OF MINE
TOLD ME THAT MY...
MY PAST DOESN'T HAVE
TO BE MY ANCHOR,
AND I THINK MY PAST
IS WHAT WAS...
STOPPING ME
FROM MOVING THINGS
FORWARD WITH YOU.
LOOKING AT ALL THIS,
I CAN UNDERSTAND WHY.
WHAT EXACTLY HAPPENED TO YOU
ON THAT ISLAND ANYWAY?
THINGS THAT I'M NOT
READY TO TALK ABOUT.
NOT EVEN THIS
CRAZY TATTOO?
I MEAN, LIKE, HOW
DO YOU EVEN GET
SOMETHING LIKE THIS
ON A DESERTED ISLAND?
HEY, HEY.
NOT READY TO
TALK ABOUT IT.
RIGHT. OK.
SO YOU MEAN, LIKE,
NOT NOW
OR NOT EVER?
NOT NOW.
MAYBE SOMEDAY.
YEAH.
I CAN WAIT
FOR SOMEDAY.
[RENE GRUNTING]
HEY. WHAT'D THAT BAG
EVER DO TO YOU, HUH?
-YOU GOT A MINUTE?
-SURE.
HOW'D THE INTERVIEW GO
WITH, UH, OLIVER'S
GIRLFRIEND?
CAKEWALK. IN FACT,
I ASKED HER IF SHE
WENT EASY ON ME,
AND SHE SAID SHE DID
BECAUSE OF SOMETHING
YOU SAID TO HER.
I DIDN'T SAY MUCH.
I JUST TOLD HER A STORY
ABOUT YOU AND ME.
YOU AND ME?
I FIGURED YOU
DIDN'T REMEMBER.
WHEN I WAS A KID,
YOU WERE A BEAT COP
ON MY BLOCK.
YOU CAUGHT ME
TAGGING A BUILDING...
BUT INSTEAD
OF HAULING ME IN,
YOU CROUCHED DOWN,
LOOKED ME IN THE EYE,
AND TOLD ME...
I COULD BE MORE
THAN JUST SOME
RIP-AND-RUN THUG.
IT REALLY SET ME
ON A BETTER PATH.
YOU DID, I MEAN.
PBB. I HAD...I HAD
NO IDEA, RENE.
ANYWAY, I JUST WANTED
THE REPORTER TO KNOW
JUST WHAT KIND
OF GUY SHE WAS
SITTING DOWN WITH.
DIDN'T YOU STILL GET
DISHONORABLY DISCHARGED
FROM THE MILITARY,
THOUGH?
[SIGHS]
NOBODY'S PERFECT.
[GRUNTING]
HEY!
HEY.
UH, WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE?
OH, I WAS JUST
MAKING SURE YOU'RE
NOT RADIOACTIVE.
HEH HEH.
ARE YOU GOING
SOMEWHERE?
YEAH. I'M SORRY.
I WAS...I WAS GONNA CALL.
WELL, I WAS PROBABLY
GONNA WIMP OUT AND TEXT.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
THE BLAST DID SOMETHING
TO THEM.
THEY DON'T WORK ANYMORE.
I DON'T HAVE
ANY CONTROL,
THEY DON'T OFFER
ANY PROTECTION.
OH. I'M SURE IT'S
JUST TEMPORARY.
I'M NOT.
I HAVE A BOND
WITH THEM, FELICITY.
I CAN FEEL IT,
AND LET'S BE HONEST.
WITHOUT THE RAGS,
I'M A LIABILITY
AND ONE THE TEAM
CAN'T RISK,
NOT WITH PROMETHEUS
OUT THERE.
OK. WELL, THAT DOESN'T
MEAN YOU HAVE TO LEAVE.
DON'T WORRY.
I'LL BE BACK.
YOU'LL, UH...
YOU'LL LET
THE TEAM KNOW?
YEAH. I MEAN, I'LL
PROBABLY JUST WIMP OUT
AND TEXT.
[CELL PHONE CHIMES]
-WELL?
-YOU WERE RIGHT.
ALL THE GUYS
IN THIS PHOTO ARE BRATVA.
IT MEANS "BROTHERHOOD"
IN RUSSIAN.
I KNOW. BRATVA GET
TATTOOS ON THEIR CHEST
WHEN THEY MAKE CAPTAIN.
-WHAT ABOUT THE OTHER THING?
-NO. I COULDN'T FIND
ANYTHING ELSE ON QUEEN
IN RUSSIA,
BUT I REVIEWED
CRIMINAL ACTIVITY
FROM THE PERIOD
HE WAS THERE,
AND I FOUND SOMETHING
VERY INTERESTING.
THE RUSSIANS CALL
HIM LUCHNIK, THE ARCHER.
DOES HE REMIND YOU
OF ANYONE YOU KNOW?
THE GREEN ARROW.
WHAT ARE THE ODDS
OF OLIVER QUEEN
AND THE GREEN ARROW
BEING IN RUSSIA
AT THE SAME TIME?
VERY GOOD...
IF OLIVER QUEEN
IS THE GREEN ARROW.
MAN: GREG, MOVE YOUR HEAD.