Oliver:
My name is Oliver Queen.
After 5 years in Hell,
I returned home
with only one goal--
to save my city.
Today, I fight that war
on two fronts.
By day, I lead Star City
as its mayor,
but by night,
I am someone else.
I am...Something else.
I am the Green Arrow.
Previously on "Arrow"...
You have to promise me
that you will be
his father.
I promise.
William blames me
for Samantha's death.
Oliver: Now you don't
have to like me.
I'm your dad. I am
gonna be there for you
whether you want me
to be or not.
John: Curtis and Lance took Rene
to Dr. Schwartz for treatment.
Saw you take the shot
at that merc.
Never seen you miss.
Turn on channel 52
right now.
Bethany Snow: This photo
provides unequivocal proof
of the identity of the vigilante
known as the Green Arrow.
What are we gonna do?
I--I don't know.
Anything interesting
on the news last night?
Reporter: Can you comment on the photo
released last night?
Reporter two: How do you feel
about the accusation
of being
the Green Arrow?
Oliver:
Ladies and gentlemen.
Ladies and gentlemen,
please.
If you want to know
what I have to say,
it would probably help
if you could hear me.
Thank you.
Gonna tell you two things,
both of which you
probably already know.
First. This is important.
I am not the Green Arrow.
Reporter: If you're
not the Green Arrow, then who is?
Number two. Photos
can be doctored.
They could have put
Bruce Wayne's head on that body.
Has Bruce Wayne left Gotham to
hang out in Star City recently?
No. Now if I was running
around the city
during the day
and managing it as mayor
while running around at night
frightening criminals
as a vigilante,
that really would
make me a superhero,
but I'm not.
I'm just the mayor.
Thank you very much.
[Reporters clamoring]
You seem to be
taking this in your stride.
I've been here before
with you.
Ugh. Yeah, but I
didn't have a photograph
of you in flagrante
de-arrow.
Where did channel 52
get the photo?
Anonymous source.
Arrived in yesterday's mail,
no return address.
Let's get the envelope,
let's get it to forensics,
and let's figure out
who leaked it.
And why.
Can't let this
distract us.
Where are with rebuilding
the SCPD?
Well, I fast tracked
the insurance claim,
so we should have
20 million burning  a hole
in our account
by the end of the day.
- "Our" account?
- I figure we peel off
a few bucks and fly
off to Vegas.
Heh heh heh.
That's cute.
Think it might be
a little suspicious
if Oliver left town
right about now.
I need to be in town
for the Markovian
delegation.
So it's all right for me to go to Vegas
is what you're saying?
Oliver: Hello.
I don't think you
have an appointment.
No, but I really
don't need one.
Special Agent
Samanda Watson.
Quentin: Uh, can we help
you with something?
Not really. I'm here
as a courtesy
to inform you
of the investigation
I'll be conducting
in your city.
Investigation
into what?
You.
Ohh. You've got to
be kidding.
Yeah, because
the FBI is world renowned
for its sense
of humor.
You were on the news
last night, wearing
the outfit
of a known criminal.
Can you honestly
say you're surprised
there's
an investigation?
No, but I wasn't
expecting the FBI.
Well, quite frankly,
the local
law enforcement has
proven ineffective
where the Green Arrow
is concerned.
Uh, Agent...Watson?
Yes.
I was cleared
5 years ago.
Of being the Hood,
not the Green Arrow,
and you were cleared by the guy
who's now your deputy mayor.
Would you like me
to send you a copy
of the polygraph
that Mr. Queen passed?
For starters.
The local AG will be
issuing subpoenas
later on today.
It was nice meeting
you, gentlemen.
I'm sure we'll be
seeing a lot more of each other.
♪ Arrow 6x02 ♪
Tribute
Original Air Date on October 19, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
At least they caught
his good side.
Sorry. Not funny.
All right. John said
you guys have experience
putting this particular
genie back in the bottle.
Well, yeah. I mean,
John's put on the hood before,
but I don't see
how that's gonna work now,
not with
photographic evidence.
What about
the human target?
The human what now?
Best cosplayer ever.
He can literally
make himself look like
someone else?
John: Yeah. Chance is
out of the country right now,
only God knows where.
We have to think of a new way of
getting out of this.
And if we can't?
Because assuming Oliver
does not go to prison,
he's not gonna be
able to do anything
with a million eyes
on him.
Not to mention that
if he's outed,
rather if he stays outed,
it won't be much of a leap
to the rest of us.
One step at a time.
Ok. First step being
figuring out
where this picture
came from.
It came from nowhere.
What do you mean?
I mean this envelope
wasn't mailed,
delivered, or sent.
It came from inside
the channel 52 news offices.
How do we know that?
Bar code.
Channel 52 uses it
for internal traffic.
How many people
work there?
568.
[Sighs]
All right. I'm just
gonna say to say it.
What if this was
Chase, huh?
He could have put this
in motion months ago,
a little parting gift.
Seems like his style,
messing with you like this.
It is more than
possible.
How's your boy holding
up with all this?
Ok. I wanted to
keep him home from school,
but he insisted
on going.
Like his father, huh?
I wasn't much
of a student.
I mean, he's tough.
Curtis: Where's he
standing?
If we could figure
out when and where this was taken,
it would give us
something to go on.
I wrote an image
analysis algorithm,
but there's just not
very much for the computer to chew on.
Was the original photo
taken digitally,
or was it taken
he old-fashioned way?
Digital. Printed
on standard inkjet stock.
- Hmm.
- Ok. Maybe if we get the file,
there might be some
meta data on it,
and we can figure out
who took the photo.
That's a pretty epic
maybe.
Yeah. Well, like
you said,
if we don't figure
this out and fast,
we're screwed!
- I did say that, didn't I?
- Yeah, you did.
This could destroy
our whole lives.
It's hard to think
that before
my biggest worry was
getting a new job,
and now it's about whether or not
we'll end up in jail.
I thought you were sitting pretty
from your Palmer Tech severance.
Yeah, from, like,
a year ago.
What are you gonna do--
assuming that we're
all not in jail.
I mean, I'd definitely
rather go to Iron Heights
than work
at Tech Village again.
That place was horrendous.
What about you?
I mean, you've been
out of a job as long as I have.
Not really. I've been doing some
freelance coding
in my spare time.
What? What spare time?
Yeah. Tell me about it.
Barely any,
but I did not take
a dime from Paul in the divorce,
and a man's got to eat.
So you just had, like,
a secret job this whole time.
You didn't tell
anyone about it?
I thought we all, like,
had, like, secret jobs.
- No.
- Except for John maybe.
What does he do
for money?
That's something that's
been perplexing me.
He's--he's married
to the director of Argus.
Yeah. That's right.
She does make a lot of money. Heh.
Oliver: This building has
been vacant
since being claimed
by the city under eminent domain
4 years ago.
Reporter: Do you have
any comment
on the FBI investigating
you under murder charges?
We're not gonna talk
about that.
Quentin: Except to say
it's a load of crap.
Ahem. By offering
subsidized leasing
to Markovia's
Vortex Industries,
they're gonna be able to create
a high-tech factory here,
bringing at the very least
800 new jobs to Star City.
Reporter two: Can you
shed light
on the accusation
of being the Green Arrow?
You have said
you're not the Green Arrow.
Then who is.
Why are you being--
Guys, enough!
If we're not here
to discuss
the Markovian initiative,
then you can just get
back on the bus
because I will not--
for the last time--
be answering questions
on the Green Arrow.
Man: But I'd be
happy to.
Alec Tarkov.
I'm the vortex CEO,
and if your mayor is
truly a superhero,
which seems ludicrous--
Thank you.
We will double
our investment.
Safe city's a good place
to do business, no?
Well, I'm sorry to
disappoint you, Mr. Tarkov,
but not even my son
considers me much of a superhero.
[Gunfire]
Go for cover!
Get to the Van!
Agh!
Go, go, go, go, go!
Here we go!
Come on.
Hit it! Go!
[Tires squeal]
[Gunfire continues]
All right.
Hold on. Hold on!
[Tires squeal]
Is everyone ok?
Yeah.
Hello, Mr. Mayor.
Hope you're having
pleasant day.
You look like maybe
you want to throw punch at me.
Don't worry.
We are not here for you.
We have business
with our Markovian cousins.
Oliver: These are
legitimate businessmen.
I never said my business
was not legitimate
unless you know something
maybe a mayor should not know.
Teper.
We'll be in touch.
Dasvidanya.
You ok?
My best friend is
under a microscope
by everyone in this city
and the FBI,
so he couldn't stop the Bratva
from taking hostages,
so let's just assume
I'm not.
I wasn't talking
about what's going on with Oliver.
Dinah, I'm fine.
The only thing
that's really bothering me
is you being up
in my business.
[Door opens]
Hey. We came as soon
as we heard.
We need to know why
Anatoly took the Markovians,
and we need to find
him now.
Oliver, Felicity
and Curtis are on this...
- But you need to stay here.
- Look. I know I said before
Chase could be behind this,
but now I'm thinking--
It's Anatoly.
He leaked the photo
to tie my hands.
We're on this.
We'll take care of it.
- SQL or Java?
- What?
In your job
as a secret programmer,
are you coding
in SQL or Java?
Both, plus a little
Swift.
I can't believe you've had a secret job
this whole time
and you didn't even
tell me about it.
Is this relevant to locating the Bratva
and/or their hostages?
I am multitasking,
thank you very much,
and, yes, if you must
know, I am running
my image analysis
algorithm on the photo of Oliver.
[Computer chiming]
What? Get something?
No. Just my algorithm
crapping out again.
Don't despair. I think
I might have a line
on our friend Anatoly.
Now working
on the assumption
that he hasn't been
in town that long,
I wondered how he was
fixed for cash.
I bet his Bratva buddies
are good for it, no?
Well, he has to
pay them somehow.
Cash would set off
too many alarm bells,
plus he'd have to convert
it from rubles.
Credit cards are
way too easy to track,
but then there's...
Cryptocurrency's
virtually impossible to track.
For mere mortals,
but we're Mr. Terrific
and Overwatch.
Overwatch
and Mr. Terrific.
Oliver: No. I can assure you.
We are doing everything
in our power to get
the hostages back.
We haven't determined
a motive for the kidnapping,
but the police are working on it
around the clock, all right?
No. Of course,
of course, of course.
- Thank you, minister.
- Yes. That's right.
We'll be in touch.
Thank you.
The Markovian consulate
is losing their minds.
It's the same with the Vortex
home office.
They want to send private security to
get their people back.
I told them we've
got it handled, but--
Felt like
you were lying?
Where are we
with the SCPD?
Dinah's got people
rounding up every Russian thug
with a record, but, you know, they're
shorthanded down there.
Got a new problem.
[Coughs]
Snow: We received
an anonymous message
from the group
claiming responsibility
for today's abduction
of the contingent
of executives
from Markovia.
In what can only be
a small consolation,
the mayor and the reporters
at the delegation were not...
Lady's getting a lot
of anonymous messages these days.
As for what exactly
this group wants,
they said they will execute
the hostages in 12 hours
unless the city pays them
a ransom of $20 million.
Mayor Queen could not
be reached for comment.
- Rene.
- In related news, Mr.--
My comment is that
we don't negotiate with terrorists.
Yeah, but if we did,
we got $20 million
from the reconstruction
of the police department.
Quentin: It's funny.
That's the exact number
your buddy Anatoly
chose.
I don't care what number
he chose.
We're not paying him
20 cents.
[Cell phone vibrating]
Yeah?
This is he.
Is he ok?
No. Of course.
Of course.
I have to go.
Want to tell me
what happened?
No.
Did you see
who hit you?
Teacher was saying
it could have been a couple of kids.
Buddy, I can't help you
if you--
They know you're
the Green Arrow.
What?
They said you're
the Green Arrow.
They said you're not
here to help me.
Oh, man. Look.
William, I'm really
sorry that you have to--
They were really big,
eighth graders.
Eighth graders, huh?
You should go
for the nose.
What?
If something like
this happens again,
go for the nose.
Find the biggest one,
the biggest on in the group,
walk right up to him
without saying a thing,
and punch him in the nose
as hard as you possibly can.
He will have no idea
what is going on.
He won't be able to see,
and if he can't see, he can't fight,
and then all
of his buddies,
all the guys that
were being so brave,
they will back off.
Trust me on that one.
[Cell phone vibrating]
- But what if--
- Hang on.
Yeah?
Felicity: It's me
hang on a second.
[Beeping, static]
What was that?
Had to secure
the line.
Curtis and I found
Anatoly.
Russian restaurant owned
by a dummy corporation.
Thermal satellite reads 4 bodies in
an industrial cooler.
Is it the hostages?
That's what
we're thinking.
Text me the address.
I'll be there soon.
Stop the car,
please.
- What are you--
- I got to get out.
Listen. Ahem.
The driver and security,
they are gonna make
sure that you get right home to Raisa.
- But--
- I promise that we'll talk
about this
right when I get home,
but for now,
I got to go.
Just please trust me.
John: 3 access points
north, south, and east.
Lance said these guys
are packing some heavy artillery.
Where's G.A.?
Oliver: Right here!
We thought maybe
you couldn't get away.
It wasn't easy.
Terrific, keep eyes
on the perimeter.
Spartan, Canary,
occupy the guards.
I'll extract
the Markovians.
[Canary cry]
[Grunting]
[Men coughing]
There were 4 of you.
Alec Tarkov,
our CEO, they took him.
- Where?
- They did not tell us.
Spartan, Canary,
we are short one hostage.
We just did a sweep.
There is no one
else here.
- Overwatch.
- I don't know what happened.
Thermal read
4 warm bodies inside.
They must have
moved one.
Felicity: In the least
surprising news ever,
the Bratva-run restaurant
is lacking in security cams.
Dinah: Oh, you mean
Russian mobsters like their privacy?
Oliver: So what now?
So now I show you
security camera footage
from outside
the restaurant.
John: Where's Anatoly
going with Tarkov?
Well, from this feed,
it looks like he's headed northeast,
but then we lose him
right about there.
We could
cross-reference our list
of Bratva
crytpocurrency activities
with Bratva-owned
properties,
see what comes
from that direction.
John, Dinah,
be prepared to hit
whatever location
Felicity and Curtis come up with.
- Copy that.
- What about you?
Oliver: I have to meet
Quentin and Rene at the FBI.
The Agent that's doing
the investigation wants to interview me.
Felicity: You have
a lawyer for that, right,
or an army of lawyers?
That would probably be better.
That would work for you
if you had
an army of them.
I don't want to look like
I have anything to hide.
Where are we
with the photo?
Oh, I'm doing a recoding
of Felicity's
analysis algorithm.
Should have something
working
within an hour
to 30 days, give or take.
Ahem.
Much closer
to the hour mark, though.
Thank you.
Keep me updated.
[Clock ticking]
[Sighs]
Did you always know
you were gonna be FBI?
[Groans]
Because I have a little girl who I
think has that potential.
I mean, of course, a woman can do
anything a man can.
And why wouldn't they?
Exactly. I mean,
they can.
I'm a feminist
like that.
Hmm.
Look. It's been
over an hour,
and my patience is
beyond gone.
Actually,
you know what?
That's the mayor
himself.
He's got
a family emergency.
He's at home with the kid.
Look at that.
So it must just be
a coincidence
that during his
family emergency
the Green Arrow was
spotted rescuing
the Markovian executives
from the Russian mob?
Definitely
a coincidence.
Do I really look
that stupid?
You don't look
stupid at all.
Listen. Look.
We're really sorry
about keeping you
waiting, all right,
but I don't know
if you know this,
but the mayor is
actually recently a single dad.
Yes. After the boy's
mother died unexpectedly
in a car accident.
Well, most car
accidents are...
Unexpected.
And most leave behind
a car wreck and a body.
The only proof
to miss Clayton's death
was the accident report
and the autopsy,
both of which could have
been easily faked.
You're not exactly
a--a very trusting person,
are you,
special Agent Watson?
Trust isn't part
of my job description,
but let me make one thing
clear as glass to you both.
If you're protecting
Mr. Queen, I'll find out,
and I'll have you both
indicted for obstruction.
Now get out my office.
You wasted enough
of my time.
Let's go.
Hey, William.
That was a gift
from a very good friend of mine.
It's all fake!
Superheroes don't
save anyone.
Buddy, I know that
I ran out on you, and I'm sorry,
but people needed
help,
and I know that you
needed help, too,
so I am--I'm here.
Do you want to learn
a few more moves, or--
No, because I don't
want to learn how to fight.
I don't want you to
learn how to fight,
but you can't always
reason with bullies.
You just left me
by myself.
I know. I know,
and I'm sorry.
I didn't know if you
were gonna come back.
William, look at me.
I will always come back.
Just like my mom?
This is different.
Yeah. It's worse
because there's
a million psychos
always trying
to kill you.
I--I can handle them.
What if you can't?
Then I'll be alone.
I'll have nobody.
You won't understand.
I do understand.
I lost my mom,
and I lost my dad...
And I was a lot older
than you are now,
but I remember
exactly how it feels.
It's sad,
it's scary,
and it's lonely,
and I swear to God
I will never let
that happen to you.
It's not up to you.
[Cell phone vibrating]
I'm sorry.
It's work.
Which work?
[Vibrating continues]
Hello, Oliver.
Anatoly, why are
you doing this?
I need money,
and from what
I understand,
your city recently
came into possession of $20 million.
There are plenty
of cities in Russia.
Hmm. True.
Beautiful ones,
but, you see,
I have been exiled.
Apparently, Bratva
thinks I am too weak
due to my
friendship with you,
so now I show
everyone
I am not weak,
and you and I
no longer friends.
I know sometimes
you--you need persuasion
to do right thing,
so I--I help you.
This nice man has
paralysis of muscles.
Soon, will have lung collapse and not
be able to breathe.
This happens
in maybe 3 hours.
Now I have cure
for his problems.
Do you have cure
for mine?
[Beep]
All right. So you got
this off Oliver's phone?
- 5 minutes ago. Yeah.
- Any clues?
Wait. Look
at this face.
I was trying really
hard not to.
What is that?
Felicity: If we can
analyze the facial rash,
we might be able to
diagnose the poison.
And find the right cure.
On it.
Anatoly said Tarkov has
maybe 3 hours.
Curtis: Yeah.
That sounds bout right.
Got it!
Tetrodotoxin.
- That's a neurotoxin.
- Yeah.
"Inhibits the firing
of action potentials,
"preventing
the nervous system
"from carrying messages
and muscles from flexing
in response
to nervous stimulation."
I have no idea what you just said,
but that doesn't sound good.
- Is there a cure?
- Yeah. They should have
something down
at Starling General.
That's great. So all we have to do
is get it to him
before the poison
takes over his entire body.
- John.
- Starling General. I'm on it.
Dinah: John, I'm
coming with you.
Dr. Schwartz: Administer
this to the patient,
and it will neutralize
the TCCD poison.
I don't want to know
what this is for, do I?
How long will it take
to reverse the effects?
Starts working
immediately,
but I'd say 72 hours
until a full recovery.
Thank you, Doctor.
And, um, how are
you feeling?
I feel fine.
[Cell phone vibrates]
Excuse me.
I have a patient.
Keep taking
those pain meds.
Yes, ma'am.
It seems like you have
another chance to lie to me again.
I'm not lying.
I'm telling you this is
none of your business.
I am out in the field
with you at less than 100%.
This is damn well
my business,
and it's Oliver's.
What doesn't he know?
On Lian Yu, Felicity and I got caught
in one of the explosions.
I thought you guys
were fine.
Felicity was.
I caught some shrapnel.
And didn't tell
anybody?
Thea was comatose,
Samantha dead.
I was low-priority.
John, that was
5 months ago.
Dr. Schwartz said
I have nerve damage.
Degenerative.
That's why you haven't
been pulling your gun.
Dinah, I have
this handled.
Yeah? You should
tell that to Rene.
He ended up
in the hospital
because you couldn't even
get a single shot off.
It's just a tremor.
I can manage it.
I'm a soldier, Dinah.
Soldiers push through.
So, what, I'm just supposed to lie
to everybody now
just like you've
been doing?
You have to do
whatever you have to do,
but I'm asking you,
please...
Will you trust me
on this one?
We should get going.
I know Python.
The supervillain?
No, no, no.
The programming language.
Look. Maybe you could send
some of your freelance coding my way.
Look. I think that
would be a waste
of your prodigious
talents, Felicity.
You are a--
son of a bitch.
Not really a son, Curtis.
More of a--
No, no.
Talking about this.
I revised your photo analysis algorithm
and got back this.
What?
That's impossible.
Data analysis doesn't
lie, Felicity.
Question is
what do we do with it?
[Computer beeps]
What's that? Come on.
No more bombshells.
I can't handle anymore for the rest
of the night.
No. It's not
a bombshell, Curtis.
It might just be the key
to the Bratva's location.
[Ding]
- What are you doing here?
- Working obviously.
What are you
doing here?
Felicity and Curtis are
working on locating Tarkov.
He has maybe
an hour left.
So why aren't you home
with William?
Sorry if I hit a nerve.
When have you ever been
sorry about hitting a nerve?
That's a fair point.
Speaking of William.
Yeah?
We received a person
of interest list from Agent Watson.
She wants to
interrogate my son?
He's an alibi and probably not
a very good liar.
Absolutely not. She's not going
anywhere near him.
I don't think
that's up to you.
I'm gonna use everything
single thing in my power
to keep him as far away
from this as possible.
This--
this kid has been
through enough.
All right. Um, Lance
told me about what happened at school.
Kids are mean.
He's not worried
about bullies.
He's worried about me.
He thinks I'm gonna
make him an orphan.
- Damn.
-  told him--
I said, "that will
not happen.
I will always
come back."
I have never lied
to my kid before.
You know...I'm not
exactly father of the year,
but...white lies
are kind of like
an important
parental tool.
I remember telling
Zoe that she came from a cloud.
I really hope her
mom set her straight on that one.
So help me with this.
He do I reconcile
that he's right?
Because every time
that I'm in the field,
there's a chance
I don't come back
and that he's alone,
and now you're
telling me that he's
gonna have to lie
to an FBI Agent
so that he doesn't
lose his father to prison?
[Sighs]
[Cell phone chimes
and vibrates]
Ahem.
We have Anatoly's
location.
All right. You go
out the back entrance.
I'll lose them.
Rene, are you good to
get back in the field?
Hells, yeah.
All right.
John: Team's
in position.
You sure this is
the place?
Whoa! I am so insulted
right now!
Easy. It's just that
an abandoned shipyard
doesn't feel like
Anatoly's speed.
Yeah. Well, neither does
being a complete jerk.
People change.
The problem is this place
is massive,
so I can't pinpoint
the location
of the hostage
even with satellite.
Figure we'll
split up.
I distributed
the antidote
so whoever gets
to Tarkov first can inject him.
You ok?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Let's do this.
Curtis: If one of us spots Tarkov, we
should have a signal.
Rene: Yeah. I was gonna go with
something like, "I see him,"
or maybe even,
"Hey. Over there."
It's not terribly
original but effective.
What about if we spot
the Bratva?
How about heads-up?
Heads-up!
[Canary cry]
- You ok?
- Look out!
[Dinah groans]
[Choking]
[Gunfire]
[T-sphere whirs]
Unh!
Anatoly: I asked
for 20 million specifically
because I knew
you had it.
You trade this
man's life for new police station?
Not exactly.
I do not think
you understand how
this whole rescue
thing works.
No. I think I do.
[Tarkov breathing]
Some sort of antidote.
Very clever.
Now step away
from him, Anatoly.
He's not part
of this.
I made him part
[Gunshot]
And I never got
my money.
What the hell
has happened to you?
Not even Gregor
would have done that.
Yes, he would have.
You never saw because
you were too naive.
You still are.
We were friends.
Yes, but I see how
you treat your friends.
No, Anatoly, no.
This is on you.
You used to be
an honorable man!
I am an honorable man.
Did I have bomb planted
in your son's school?
Did I have him
kidnapped, tortured?
No, because even though
we stand apart,
I am still good man.
I wonder what would
happen to William
if you ran afoul
of someone who's not good.
Anatoly!
Don't you move.
Don't bluff.
We have been
here before.
We both know you
will not kill me.
Why did you leak
that picture of me?
As Kapiushon?
I did not.
I told you
I am honorable man.
[Door opens]
Thank you for
agreeing to meet.
I can always make time
for the subject of my investigation,
but I should advise
you have a lawyer present.
Why do I need a lawyer?
I haven't done anything wrong.
You know the kind
of person who says that?
- No.
- The kind that needs a lawyer.
Heh heh heh.
Agent Watson, if you
feel the need to investigate me,
I am more than happy
to open up my entire life to you
with the exception
of my son.
He's off limits.
You're aware that
telling a FBI Agent
how to conduct their investigation is
obstruction of justice?
If I really am the man
that you think I am,
how far do you think
such a man would go
to keep his son from
being scrutinized by the FBI?
[Knock on door]
Oh. Ms. Watson?
A little busy here.
There's something
on the news that you need to see.
Snow: Channel 52 just
received exclusive evidence
which conclusively establishes
that the photograph
of Mayor Queen
as the Green Arrow
was digitally doctored.
This is the second time
that Mayor Queen has faced
allegations of being
a vigilante,
and twice he has
been exonerated.
Lucky you.
Not really.
Like I said, I'm not
the man you think I am.
No, Mr. Queen.
I think you are,
and if you think this means
I'm dropping my investigation,
then you're the one
who's mistaken.
You should do whatever
it is you have to.
...the last 48 hours.
The evidence received
by channel 52
showing that Mr. Queen's
face had been placed
on the Green Arrow's body
was received earlier today
from an unknown source.
- Nailed it!
- You know, I don't want
to sound arrogant,
but we may very well be
the smartest human beings
on the planet.
Oh, well, it's not
arrogant if it is accurate.
Heh heh. True that.
And you still find the time to look
bummed out. Crazy.
I mean, our photo
analysis algorithm was right, right?
- Yes.
- The photo of Oliver
was doctored, so--
So what is
the problem?
So who would want to
frame Oliver for being the Green Arrow?
Wow! Way to kill
the mood.
- Sorry.
- No. Listen.
That is future us'
problem.
I'm not gonna, like,
let you take away
my buzz right now.
Ok. Present us is
only worried
about you quitting
your nobody-told-about job.
When are you gonna
let that go?
When you go
into business with me.
I'm sorry.
Go into what with you?
- Wait. What?
- Ok. Work with me on this.
We work so well
together.
Ok. The photographic
analysis algorithm is just one
of many in a long list
of amazing tech that
you and I have
collaborated on.
Think about all
the good we could do,
all the cool stuff
we could do,
all the cool things
we could make!
Please don't say no.
- Yes!
- Oh, thank God.
Good because I already
filed the paperwork.
Heh. Oh, man.
This is so cool.
We'll be like
Woz and Jobs,
like, back in '76.
Wait. Who's Woz,
and who's Jobs?
- Shotgun! Jobs!
Hey.
Can we talk
for a second?
There's nothing
to talk about.
We both know that's
not true, Dinah.
What do we both know?
I need you to say it.
You nearly got killed
last night
because you couldn't
rely on me.
Because you're
compromised.
I know.
Things just got worse
than I was willing to admit.
That's ok,
but what are you
gonna do about it?
Tell Oliver.
Go from there.
[Video game sound effects]
You're home early.
So I am.
Hoping to make that more
of a regular thing
if that's ok
with you.
Whatever.
I would like to
apologize.
For what?
For making you
a promise
I wasn't 100%
sure I could keep.
You were right,
and I was wrong.
[Game stops]
Raisa said you have
a hard time admitting when you're wrong.
You have no idea.
Buddy, I heard what
you said in the limo,
and I hear you,
but I also meant
what I said.
I--I am going to do
everything in my power
forever to make sure
that never end up alone in this world,
and I know that you
think that that's not up to me,
and that's a fair,
smart point,
which is why I think
I've found a way
so that maybe
it can be.
- How?
- I'm working on the details.
I want you to believe me
when I say that
I am trying to
make it happen, all right?
One more thing.
I promise
that I will do
my best every single day
to be the very best
father that I can be
and--and that I
know how to be.
That promise is 100%.
Ok.
You want to play
with me?
What is this?
Honestly, I don't know.
All you got to do
is just button mash
and see whoever
can win.
- All right.
- Want to try?
- Yeah.
- All right.
[Game starts]
[Footsteps]
- Thanks for meeting me.
- Yeah. Well, I wanted to talk
to you
about a few things, and--
What is it, Oliver?
I'd like you to do
something for me.
If it's suit up
as Green Arrow,
Felicity and I already
talked about it,
and we don't think it's enough
to take the heat off of you.
That's not
why I'm asking.
You're serious.
Every time that I'm out there
as the Green Arrow,
I'm a target
of the FBI,
of the Bratva,
of the threats that
are out there
and the threats that are
undoubtedly coming...
And on my own,
I can take it.
I'm not on my own
anymore.
I cannot be responsible
for my son losing
the only parent
that he has left.
Oliver.
Star City needs
the Green Arrow.
It just can't be
me anymore...
So I'd like it
to be you.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Greg!
Move your head.