My name is Oliver Queen.
After 6 months in hell,
I have been released from prison
and returned home with only one goal...
to save my city,
but things have changed.
Instead of operating outside the law,
I am now working alongside the police.
I am no longer Inmate 4587.
I am once more the Green Arrow.
Previously on "Arrow"...
Working with the SCPD...
that's what's best for this city.
The whole city will be watching you,
holding you to the highest standard.
Dad, please. Don't leave.
Dante took me under
his wing, and he trained me.
I kept holding out, thinking
one day you'd become
the father I deserved.
It's never gonna happen, is it?
Is there something else
you'd like to talk to me about?
No. Have a good trip.
When Emiko realizes that Dante
has been manipulating her,
it will drive a wedge between
her and the Ninth Circle.
Rot in hell.
The Ninth Circle got away
with a very dangerous
biological weapon...
the Cygnus X-1.
I have just received confirmation
of two fatalities here at the
Hudolin McGuire Metro Station.
SCPD have cordoned off the area,
but the community is very concerned.
Rumors are already flying as
to who might be responsible.
- Captain Drake.
- How's it look?
You need to see this for yourself.
Hey, keep those damn reporters back.
This is where we found them.
Oh, my god.
We'll have to wait for
the official M.E. report,
but it seems obvious...
blunt force trauma.
Looks like they got off a few rounds
before they went down.
Did they hit anything?
Nothing alive.
Where are the suspects?
We've got two dead guards
and one hell of a mess.
Your team was on-site.
I think you better start talking.
♪ Arrow 7x20 ♪
Confessions
Original Air Date on April 29, 2019
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
-  www.addic7ed.com -
This is... this whole
thing is ridiculous.
The real danger is still out there.
I don't think you get to decide
the real danger, Mr. Queen.
We went to the subway platform
to stop a terrorist attack,
which we did,
but the people that we were after
- are still on the loose.
- Well, luckily we have
half the department out there right now
following the same lead.
Do you think that these are
average street thugs, Dinah?
These are terrorists
that tried to release
a biological agent in Star City.
Thousands of people could have died.
Two people did die.
We found two emerald
arrows at the scene.
The new Green Arrow.
Why don't you tell me
about her involvement
at the subway tonight?
She was there.
She? How do you know that?
I think it's time we
tell people the truth.
The new Green Arrow is my half-sister.
Her name is Emiko Adachi.
She belongs to a terrorist organization
called the Ninth Circle.
The vigilantes have been tracking her
for a few weeks now.
Why didn't you inform the SCPD?
Because the Ninth Circle is
just a little bit
beyond the SCPD, Officer.
The SCPD-vigilante
partnership works best
when we operate as a covert unit.
Doesn't seem so in this case.
Well, I'm usually kept
aware of what's going on,
but I did not know about this.
Care to explain why?
Things started moving pretty quickly
after you told us about Dante.
Oh, thank God.
Please tell me the news
that you are bringing
is about Emiko and her
Ninth Circle buddies
because I have had no luck
with my typity-type
finding anything thing.
Oh, well, you're in luck now.
Dante, not so much.
A couple SCPD beat cops
found his body this morning.
Let me guess, and not
from natural causes.
Not unless you call 3 arrows
and a knife to the chest natural.
This was after you told Emiko
that Dante killed her mother.
- Can't be a coincidence.
- No. She went ahead and killed
the only father figure she had left.
Right. So that's a "no"
on the evil sister
redeeming herself then.
Ok, so we have to stop Emiko from using
this bio-weapon that
she stole from the D.I.A.
The terrifying bacteria
that eats through everything?
Yeah, let's keep that contained.
Ok, so the bad news is that
I haven't been able to
find the bio-weapon,
but the good news is
that the ninth circle
won't be able to either
unless they get a dissemination device,
A.K.A. a thermal fogger.
And, yes, I checked.
The only place to get one
is Aerodyne Initiatives.
Digg, let's get there and
- help them protect it.
- Ok.
I'll follow up with the detective,
see if I can get some more
clues off Dante's body.
- Ok.
- And I'll hang back with Felicity
and help her with the typey-type.
- That's ok.
- Moral support.
Ok.
Mr. Queen, Mr. Diggle,
it's a pleasure to finally meet
the famous Green Arrow and Spartan.
I always believed in
vigilantes in the city.
Well, love to hear it.
Wish we were meeting
under better circumstances.
We have reason to believe
that an asset of yours has been targeted
by an international terrorist threat.
Well, that's quite an accusation,
but I can assure you our
security's top of the line.
With all due respect,
this organization is far more powerful
than any private company
could possibly contend with.
And with all due respect to you,
we hired over a dozen of the
world's best hackers and thieves
to try to break into our facility.
None made it past the front entrance.
Uh, Mr. Toth,
we're simply offering to help you.
What possible reason could you have
for turning us down?
Well, I appreciate your concern,
but we've got this covered.
It seems odd that he turned you down.
We agreed,
so we had Felicity do a deep dive
into Toth's financial records.
Turns out he was getting
some very large deposits.
So he was on the take...
- From the Ninth Circle.
- Mm-hmm.
And why the hell didn't you tell me?
Because we couldn't confirm it
until later, Dinah.
Well, I want to believe you, Oliver,
but you've got to admit,
this looks really bad.
I mean, we got arrows
at the crime scene.
We've got a very
incriminating distress call
from one of the victims,
and you were there.
Not to mention the
missing security footage.
Ok. Dinah, you know me, all right?
You know that I didn't
kill those people.
You've killed before...
huh...
many times.
Five months ago, you were sitting
in a cell in Slabside.
You're not exactly innocent.
Enjoying yourself?
You having a good time?
You have had it out for me
since the moment that I
was deputized by the SCPD.
You know, those guards
were not just killed, Oliver.
They were savagely beaten to death.
Do you understand how bad
this looks for the department?
Yes, I do, but I didn't do it.
- Then who did?
- I don't know.
So it could have been
one of the members of your team.
My team...
Stopped a terrorist attack.
Except it wasn't just your team
who was there, was it?
There was somebody else there,
somebody besides Mr. Diggle
and Ms. Smoak and Mr. Ramirez.
Yes, there was.
We thought the Ninth Circle
was gonna wipe out Star City.
So I made a call.
You do understand
what accomplice to murder means, right?
You can't be serious.
Tonight's security footage
from Hudolin McGuire Subway
Station mysteriously disappeared.
You wouldn't happen to know
anything about that, would you?
Nope. Nothing, zilch, nada.
She's covering for her husband.
- Oh, come...
- That certainly is convenient.
And when exactly were
you planning on telling me
about Roy Harper's involvement?
Honestly?
After we saved Star City from
the Ninth Circle's attack.
We know how you guys feel
about "the unsanctioned."
Let's get real.
Emiko and the Ninth
Circle know our faces.
Roy was our ace in the hole.
So you risked your new
relationship with the SCPD
by teaming up with a criminal.
Former criminal.
Roy left the city 4 years ago,
and he's been on the straight
and narrow ever since.
Are you sure about that?
Yes, I'm sure about that.
Because we traced Harper's whereabouts
after he faked his death in prison
to get Oliver Queen off the hook,
and his trail went cold
in march of last year.
Oh. You mean when
Ricardo Diaz kidnapped Roy
to turn him against Oliver?
You might have forgotten
about that since you
weren't exactly on speaking terms
with Oliver and I at the time.
It still doesn't explain
where he went after
getting freed from Diaz.
I'm sure the kidnapping
was extremely traumatic.
He probably just went
to go get some R&R...
some Roy relaxation.
Not funny. I see that now.
Oh. So this is what legit looks like.
That's right. A badge and a bunker.
Never thought I'd see the day.
Good seeing you.
I'm glad you're finally
seeing it in person again.
- Ooh!
- Oh!
Oh, I missed you so much.
Sorry. I'm just a little
overly emotional these days.
I mean, not overly emotional,
not, like, heightened or anything.
Because why would that be?
My hormones are totally in check,
like they always have been.
Nerves of steel. You know me. I'm cool.
- Ok.
- The Arsenal. Nice to finally meet you.
You, too. Thanks for keeping watch.
The Glades can use as
many heroes as it can get.
Welcome back.
All right.
How's Thea?
She's good. Yeah, I think
she's finally found her passion.
You'd be really proud of her.
Last I spoke with her, she says
you were zeroing in on
the remaining Lazarus Pits.
Yeah, we found two already,
- which we destroyed.
- Mm-hmm.
We were checking the rest
when we got your call.
Speaking of which, why'd
you ask me to come here
instead of Thea?
Star City's new terrorist
is Oliver's new sister.
What?
Yeah.
Don't you think Thea
would want to know that?
- Yeah.
- Yes.
And I have every
intention of telling her.
I just... this woman's name is Emiko,
and we wanted to get her into
custody before we told her.
I feel like she's finally
free of her life in Star City,
and I... I don't want to hurt her again
with a wound inflicted on our family
by our father.
Roy had been traveling the world
doing some extremely normal sightseeing.
Apparently he was too busy
to even send a postcard.
Then why did you call him in?
Because of the thermal fogger.
The what?
The scary bio-weapon
that the bad guys needed
to spread the bacteria through
the subway's HVAC system.
The device found on the scene.
The device found at the scene, yes.
Look,
we thought it was weird
that the CEO of Aerodyne
wasn't going to let us protect
it from the Ninth Circle,
so we did some digging.
And found that Jason Toth
was dirty. Oliver told us.
We knew good old Jason would be
looking for members of the TGA,
and we needed someone with a
vigilante-like set of skills.
Voila. Roy Harper.
The facilities at Aerodyne are no joke,
and Roy is incredible at parkour.
I'm in.
Remember, Roy,
the floor is armed.
If you touch anything...
and I mean anything... it
is party time at Aerodyne,
- and not in a good way.
- Is there anything I can touch?
Walls and ceilings are fair game.
Anything that's not the floor.
So far, so good.
The control panel's
on the other side of the fan.
I got to get higher.
I see it.
You hit metal, it's over.
Shot has to be perfect.
Margin of error...
0.08, but who's counting?
Your target is the red button...
second from the left.
I don't have a shot...
But I will.
Just like that, piece of cake.
Oh, which actually
sounds so good right now.
Do you guys have any cake or cupcakes
or anything with, like, a cake-like...
Felicity, tell us what happened, please.
Roy squeezed his way through the blades,
and then after that, it was easy
to make his way into
the R&D vault. Boom.
Heads up. We're late to the party.
That was our only way in.
Not the only way.
Pleasure doing business
with you, Mr. Toth.
Oh, your new sister... not a fan.
Take care of him. Move! Move!
Who the hell are you?
Your new worst nightmare.
Hmm.
See youse lads.
Roy?
We lost the bio-weapon.
So let me get this straight.
If your plan had worked,
Roy would have successfully stolen
a very dangerous piece of tech.
In other words, committed a felony.
Well, technically,
Roy was there to stop the Ninth
Circle from doing what they did,
which was steal the device,
so technically,
Roy didn't do anything.
No harm, no foul. Could
I maybe get a pizza?
- Just a personal size is fine.
- No. I think you've abused
your food privileges enough for today.
- Ok.
- Tell me what happened.
We stopped the Ninth Circle
from terrorizing the city.
End-stop.
And the two fatalities.
That wasn't our fault.
Then tell me what you know.
We knew that the Ninth Circle
wanted to maximize the
bio-weapon's impact.
There were two possible
locations to do that...
the ventilation room and
the ventilation shaft.
Oliver went to one, John
and Rene went to the other.
Roy and I went to the switch room.
Oh, wow! This thing is a fossil,
and not in a fun ice age way.
Can you shut it down?
Well, once I shut down
the ventilation path,
we should be able to
minimize the damage.
Did you have any indication
those guards were still on-site?
No. I didn't see those
guards or any guards.
Sounds like we're not
alone. You got eyes?
All I got is two transit
guards in the corridor.
If they're Ninth Circle,
you can't let them in here.
Well, I can't just leave you here.
I'll be fine. I'll be fine. Go.
I stayed in that room until
Oliver gave me the go-ahead.
And what about Roy?
What do you mean?
Can you account for his whereabouts
between the time he left you
and the time those guards were killed?
Guys, the vents are shut down.
Please tell me that you have the device.
He was keeping me safe.
That wasn't the question.
Felicity, do you know where Roy was
when those guards were killed?
No, I don't.
Roy Harper, you are a
hard man to track down.
I've been traveling.
So we've heard. Whereabouts exactly?
The world.
Don't make this harder
than it needs to be.
You've got quite the
rap sheet, Mr. Harper.
B&E, Grand Theft Auto...
Aggravated assault.
So is that why you came
back to Star City, Roy,
to steal a device from Aerodyne?
I came back to help prevent
Emiko from stealing it.
She's the one you guys
should be going after.
We will.
But first, why don't
you tell us what happened
after you failed to stop her?
I went back to the bunker
to figure out a new plan.
According to Felicity,
all Emiko had to do was
fill that device with some
sort of killer bacteria
and Star City would've turned
into a real-life horror movie.
Cygnus X-1.
Yeah. So she ran some sort of algorithm
and came up with a few possible places.
And that eventually
led you to the subway.
Cut to the chase.
What happened when you got there?
Specifically, what happened
after you left Felicity?
I didn't want to leave
her, but she insisted.
We thought the Ninth Circle
might have showed up.
Turns out we were right.
Those guys in the hoods jumped me.
After I took out the
first one, they just...
Just kept coming.
I tried to fight back,
but there were just too many of them.
The last thing I remember is
I was taking a mace to the face
before everything went black.
And when I came to,
you all were on the scene,
and the guards, they were already dead.
So you have absolutely no idea
who may have killed them.
It's rather convenient, don't you think?
You being unconscious at the same time
two men are brutally murdered?
You think I did it?
Whose side are you on?
I am on the only side
that matters... the truth.
Now, why don't you stop wasting my time
and tell me what really happened?
I told you, Roy was
unconscious when I found him,
and that was before the
guards fired their sidearms.
So you don't think he killed them.
I just don't see how he could have.
You don't have to protect him, John.
Dinah, I'm not.
Right, right.
But that is what you do, isn't it?
You always put other people's
lives before your own.
At some point you might discover
not everybody's worth it.
Look, you don't know
Roy Harper the way I do.
He's had his troubles.
But deep inside, he's a very good man.
Well, you're very quick to defend Roy.
What about yourself?
Why? Are you asking me
if I killed those guards?
It certainly doesn't help
that you have blood on your sleeve.
Walk us through what
happened after you arrived.
Well, there were two
possible disbursement sites.
Oliver headed for the ventilation room.
And Rene and I headed
for the ventilation shaft.
And that's when we ran into trouble.
Access should be here,
ahead on the right.
Emiko.
- I've got her.
- Rene!
She's mine. Go secure the device.
So that's when you and Rene split up.
Rene was right. The
device was the priority.
I was headed for the ventilation shaft,
and that's when I found Roy unconscious.
And this was before the gunshots.
That's correct.
I ran toward the source
as fast as I could, but I was too late.
I checked their pulse,
but they were already dead.
That's how I got blood on my sleeve.
What about Mr. Ramirez?
Where was he during all of this?
John?
John, tell us what you saw.
When I got to the bodies...
That's when I found Rene.
Rene?
What happened to your hand, Rene?
I cut it.
Well, that's obvious.
Was it around the same
time you lost your glove?
What are you getting at, D.?
You know, I've seen plenty
of perps change their tune
the longer they sit in here.
The truth has a way of coming out.
This isn't my first time
being falsely accused of a crime...
Sir.
Two men are dead, Rene.
Now, we know Team Arrow was on-site
as well as Emiko, which
means our two main suspects
are either her or...
Me?
I didn't say that.
Well, that's what you were thinking,
'cause you've been
looking for any excuse
not to trust me this whole year.
That's because you have given me
every reason not to.
How many times have I
warned you about Emiko?
I told you she wasn't trustworthy.
You refused to listen.
Well, now she ends up
on the scene of an
attempted terrorist attack
and a double homicide,
and you were there, too.
And you what? You think I helped her?
I just want the truth, Rene.
Tell me what you were doing
before that mission tonight.
We managed to get the info
on the Ninth Circle's target
thanks to Felicity's algorithm.
She traced the chemical
signature of the bio-weapon
to the subway station.
And that's when you headed off.
Yeah. Straight away.
You good with all this?
I'll be better once we get
to the subway and stop her.
I know that it's going to be
tough going up against Emiko.
You guys got really close, Rene.
If you're gonna try and give me
a pep talk, save it. I'm good.
I don't want to give you a pep talk.
I want to make sure that if
you're going out on a mission,
you're doing it with a clear head.
When I first met Emiko,
avenging her mother's death
and helping the Glades were the
only things that mattered to her.
Right, except she was lying.
Then why did she kill Dante?
Why'd she do it?
I mean, she turned on a
member of the Ninth Circle
for her mother. That tells me
that family means more to her.
Fine. It doesn't
change the fact that she
could potentially kill
thousands... thousands of people.
I know, I know, but she's
still your sister, man.
Doesn't any part of you think
that maybe she's doing all of this
because of what your father did to her,
that if not for her upbringing,
she'd be fighting with
us instead of against us?
A big part of me thinks about that...
All the time.
At a certain point, Rene,
people need to take responsibility
for their actions.
Emiko made her choice. I've made mine.
You need to make yours.
There's something I'm not
liking about your story, Rene.
The part where we save the city?
The part you're not telling us.
Everything I told you
tonight is the truth.
Then why did we find your fingerprints
on the murder weapon.
What were you doing
with that pipe, Rene?
I didn't do anything.
That's getting harder
and harder to believe.
John and I split up.
He went after the bomb.
I went after Emiko.
And did you catch up to her?
No.
Emiko, it's not too late.
- Let me help you.
- I don't need your help.
I spared you once.
This time, I won't be so generous.
Why are you doing this?!
Because the Queens
took everything from me.
Now it's my turn to take
everything from them.
This isn't you.
You care about the Glades.
You're dressed as the new Green Arrow,
and you killed Dante.
And that proves what exactly?
That finding your mother's killer means
more to you than the Ninth Circle.
Why else would you risk
murdering their leader?
You really don't get it.
Dante wasn't their leader.
I am.
Your mother would hate
what you've become.
Agh!
I was still searching for Emiko
when I heard the gunshots.
Where were you exactly?
Some random corridor.
The gunshots were close.
I followed the sound, which
led me to the platform.
You know we have a witness
who pins you as the
first person on the scene.
Yeah. John. He showed up...
he showed up seconds after I did.
What are you not telling us, Rene?
Someone else got to the
platform before I did.
And who was it?
It was Oliver.
Bring back Mr. Queen.
You didn't tell us the truth.
What are you talking about?
Your friend Ramirez says he
found you near the bodies.
I have no more ways to tell you
I didn't kill those guards.
Let me tell you what I think.
I think you and your team were there
to stop the terrorist attack.
I even think you did.
But one of the bad guys got
away. You went after them.
And transit guards Rosenberg
and Kim got in your way.
I didn't kill those guards.
Ok, then who did, Oliver?
Because I really want to help you,
but I can't do that unless
you're honest with us.
So let's try this again.
Tell me what went on in that subway,
and I want the truth this time.
After we separated,
I went to the ventilation room.
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
Whoa, whoa. Careful, careful.
One wrong move, and we'll
all be in a load of trouble.
Aah!
You're a real pain in
the arse, you know that?
That's not the part we're interested in.
We appreciate you disarming the device,
but that's not why you're here.
The device is a weapon
that was gonna kill thousands of people,
and now it's in SCPD custody,
thanks to us.
What happened next?
I was still in the ventilation room
when I heard the gunshots.
The guards must have
gotten off a few shots.
Oh, no.
But when I got there...
The killer was standing over them.
They were gone.
Blood everywhere.
And you got a good look at who did it.
Yeah.
Then who was it?
Oliver, then who was it?
It was my sister.
Emiko killed those guards.
I can't believe we're letting him go.
Oliver Queen is protecting his sister.
It makes sense.
I don't know. Something
doesn't feel right.
We don't have enough evidence
to keep them here.
Their stories line up.
Mayor Pollard agrees.
So how's it look?
Pollard bought it.
Yeah, as far as the SCPD is concerned,
Emiko was the one who
killed those guards.
You all are very, very good liars.
So are you, D.
We know that this wasn't easy for you.
No, it wasn't.
If anybody finds out about what we did,
our partnership with the SCPD is over.
And the same goes for my job.
We just risked everything.
That's why we all had to agree.
This was the only way.
- I've got her.
- Rene.
She's mine. Secure the device.
I'll be fine. Go.
Aah!
Hey! What the hell's going on down here?
Vigilante attack in progress,
Hudolin McGuire Metro Station.
Roy!
Roy, stop it! Look at me!
Roy, stop!
Rene! Rene, don't touch that.
They're dead.
What the hell happened here?
What are we gonna do?
We have to protect him.
Two innocent people are dead,
and we're covering it up.
Dinah, if someone
on this team goes down,
this entire team goes down.
He's absolutely right.
And if pollard knew the truth,
we would be sitting in lockup
while the city rehashes
whether vigilantes are a threat or not.
Which would free Emiko up
for evil plan B.
But Roy is not a part of this team.
He's been gone for months
doing who knows what.
With due respect, you don't
know what he's been through.
Roy is and always will be
as much a part of this team
as the rest of us.
Except the rest of us don't go around
killing innocent people.
Dinah, as horrible as that was,
let's not lose sight that
we stopped an attack tonight.
And we framed Emiko for murder.
Emiko's a murderer,
a murderer who's the
leader of the Ninth Circle.
And as long as she is out there,
this city will remain under threat.
I hope we can all agree on that.
Yes.
My search algorithms are up and running.
It might actually be a good time
to go ask Roy what happened.
I'm pretty sure I already know.
That wasn't Mirakuru.
No.
How did it happen?
What do you mean?
How did you die?
How did you know?
You, Thea, and Nyssa
left here over a year ago
in search of Lazarus Pits,
and I have not seen bloodlust like that
since Thea was resurrected by one.
Damn it.
To help, I need to know what happened.
The Thanatos Guild had us surrounded.
I tried to get Thea to safety,
but I was hit with an arrow,
which... which is ironic.
I don't really remember a lot after,
except for... except
for seeing Nyssa and Thea
destroy the Pit.
The one they used to bring you back.
Yeah.
Nyssa had the Lotus Elixir.
She and Thea thought
that we could control
the bloodlust, and we did.
Until you didn't.
I keep trying to figure out why.
And all I can think of is that maybe
the Mirakuru changed something.
You know, I never
would've come back here
if I would've known
what was gonna happen.
- I never meant to hurt anyone.
- I know...
But keeping this information from us,
it jeopardized all the things that
we have been working for this year.
I never asked you to cover for me.
I didn't want you to.
You never have to ask me.
Ever.
Guys?
Felicity has something.
I expanded my search
parameters, and presto.
Facial recognition puts Emiko
in an abandoned building
a few miles outside of Star City.
Any background on the building?
I mean, you name it, it's been it.
Hospital, shipping warehouse,
manufacturing plant.
I mean, it's had more owners
than a "fortune" 500 company.
Which means it could be
a cover for something.
Yeah, something being
the Ninth Circle's headquarters
here in Star City.
Emiko's there, which is
all that matters to us.
We're going after her as a team.
Are you sure?
We got your back.
Oh, hey, Dinah!
Thank you for wiping that
security camera footage.
I could not get there
before the cops did.
I thought that was you.
No.
Let's go wide.
Arsenal, on my 6.
Overwatch, any heat signatures?
No. Not even yours.
Thermal imaging can't penetrate
through those walls.
I have eyes on her.
Moving to intercept.
Oliver, confirm your location.
This is over.
Is it?
Right now, Sergeant Bingsley
is receiving an anonymous gift
delivered to his office:
The missing security footage
from the Metro Station.
You're the one who made it disappear?
You set us up.
What do you want?!
For you to suffer the way I suffered.
You and your team are
gonna die in there.
And I will be out there
destroying your legacy.
You'll die a villain
just like our father did,
and I will be the cause
of both of your deaths.
And justice will finally be served.
What did you say?
I had the chance
to warn our father about the "gambit."
It was rigged to explode,
and I knew about it.
I let our father die because
he didn't deserve to live.
And neither do you.
Bye, brother.
Oliver, do you read me?
Does anybody copy?
Oliver, come in.
John?
John, come in! Oliver?
Come in, please!
Come in!
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
-  www.addic7ed.com -