Previously on Arrow...
I'm gonna run for mayor.
Mr. Palmer's last recorded statement
could shed some light on how he died.
What's happening to me?
We're going to Nanda Parbat.
You need to feed this impulse.
Once you do, it will subside for a time.
I want you to bring my sister
back to life.
"MALCOLM". Even if Sara went into the Pit,
what came out of the Pit
would not be Sara.
"LAUREL". Your daughter is alive.
The most loving act you can commit
is to return Sara to her final rest.
You are not gonna kill your own daughter.
She's not my daughter!
Sara?
Damn it!
Hey, honey! Why don't you just
leave that right there?
Step off, bitch.
Oh, my God! Thank you.
S. C. P. D.! Stay where you are.
I cannot thank you enough for
coming on board, Alex.
Well, then it is a good thing
you're paying me also.
- Sorry for the wait.
- Ollie, this is Alex Davis,
the new political strategist
that Walter recommended.
Old enough to vote, Alex?
I owned a bar and I wasn't even
old enough to drink.
I'm old enough to do both.
Well, I'm glad that you're
joining the team,
but I don't entirely know why I need
a political strategist.
Well, I guess the question then is,
do you want to take office
with 10% of the vote or 90?
After you win, you still need
to be able to govern.
Well, what has you concerned?
My lack of experience?
No. We can spin that.
No, I'm talking about the kind of
closet skeletons
that could cripple you on your first day
in office. Your personal Chappaquiddick.
Wait, like that game from Harry Potter?
Um, Chappaquiddick was a scandal
involving a can't-lose candidate
whose campaign fell apart
when he was caught having an affair
after his vehicle went underwater
and the girl he was with drowned.
Does that sound at all familiar?
Referencing the Queen's Gambit
and Sara Lance.
Yeah. Got it.
You're about to do your first
on-air sit-down, right?
Yeah.
Bethany Snow. Ten will get you 20
she brings up Sara and her sister.
Alex. All due respect,
I don't think that people care about my
friendship with Laurel Lance
and an eight-year-old scandal
when this city is disintegrating
and there are masked,
armed men helping it.
Not to mention there's a woman
in Pennytown
that's just running around killing people.
You're right. I'm sorry.
For a moment, I forgot how the electorate
always cares about the issues
and has zero appetite for scandal.
You want this city united?
You can't do it as the rich-kid playboy
from the tabloids.
And like it or not, Laurel Lance
is a constant reminder of that.
So from this day forward,
when anyone brings up Ms. Lance,
you distance yourself from her.
Hey! Just in time. I was looking for you.
Why?
I wanna talk to you about
something you forgot.
What's that?
That how you wanna play this?
Fine by me, pal. Let's go.
I don't appreciate the intrusion,
gentlemen.
There's communications gear in here.
We've got ourselves a mole.
And you believe it's Mr. Queen?
Look.
We've been on this island eight months
without a single problem.
He shows up.
Suddenly, two guys find landmines,
and a bunch of drugs go missing.
Yeah. Conklin, you got me. I didn't wash
up on shore here after a boating accident.
I parachuted in on a secret spy mission.
- You wanna die a liar, that's fine by me.
- That's enough.
Enough! There are more pressing
matters at hand.
Perhaps if you were focused more on
external threats rather than witch hunts,
you would've caught this man spying on us
in the fields.
I wasn't spying, mate.
Any of you squabblers got a cigarette?
She mumbled something.
It sounded, I don't know, Middle Eastern.
All right, um, we're gonna have you
sit down with a sketch artist, okay?
Take care of that.
- Dad. What happened?
- Hey.
You tell me. These two bodies
dropped by a woman.
Probably the same woman
that's been linked to the murders
of three other skels in the past few days.
A blonde woman.
Dad, I...
I didn't know what to make of it
till tonight.
This woman says her suspect speaks
some kind of Middle Eastern language,
just like Sara.
Is she still at your place?
I've been looking for her.
Why didn't you tell me, huh?
Did you tell Queen?
No. Because he would just see this
the same way as you.
Yeah, and how is that, huh? How is that?
That Sara is just a thing that
needs to be stopped.
This is my daughter.
Then why did I find you with
a gun pointed at her head?
I'm not proud of that, Laurel,
but people are dying.
And if I'd pulled that trigger,
maybe they wouldn't be.
I'm gonna go find Sara, and hopefully I do
before you or Oliver.
Curtis, I need you to do something for me.
Felicity, look at me.
Gym clothes, gym bag.
Do either of those suggest anything
to you?
Physical fitness. But then I remembered
you're a tech guy.
I'm also a bronze medal decathlete.
Bronze medal, huh?
Beijing, 2008.
Beijing. As in the Olympics?
Mr. Palmer's recording. Did you play it?
Yes, there's something off about it.
You sure it's not the fact that
it's a dying declaration from your ex?
I mean, that is some serious
Nicholas-Sparks-level stuff.
Don't judge. Man can write emotion.
No, not that. I mean, yes, there's that,
but there's still some artifacts playing
that shouldn't be there.
What about your workout?
Didn't seem to concern you 20 seconds ago.
I'm sorry, Felicity,
this is my fault. I got...
You hear that?
Like there's more to the recording.
Something overlapping with it.
I was hoping you could clean it up for me.
I mean, after your workout.
It can wait.
I'm glad you changed your mind
about hearing Mr. Palmer's final words.
Thank you, Curtis.
Oh, thank you for coming.
Well, I think we both know I didn't
have too much choice.
No, certainly not since you literally
doubled the number of daughters
I have to hold over you.
Or did you take my advice
and return Sara to the grave?
You didn't take my advice. Pity.
What do you want?
A new beginning for the world,
a nice glass of merlot.
Not necessarily in that order.
And for you to do me a favor.
There's a federal server farm
30 miles outside of the city.
I want you to gain access and plug this
little baby into one of the computers.
How much this thing gonna do?
It's of no concern of yours.
But don't worry, it's not like it's gonna
destroy the city or anything.
Whatever that spa weekend did to
clear your head,
it also improved your technique.
You're effortless.
Yeah, well, you know how I love
my hot stone massages.
By the way, that political strategist
was a good call.
But his advice was a little harsh.
I mean, distancing yourself from Laurel?
I wasn't expecting that,
but he made a few good points.
What? Like kicking your friends
to the curb?
Well, my friendship with Laurel
is complicated.
We have been in each other's lives for,
like, forever.
I mean, you have been in love with
Laurel and Sara.
And Laurel, she... She took me in at CNRI
when I was completely lost.
Even Captain Lance, okay? He has been
there for us since Mom died.
Okay. But your point?
My point is that pretending that you
don't know who your friends are,
it just doesn't feel very united.
This is your overlord,
Felicity Smoak.
We have a PA system?
Yet another decision
I might live to regret.
Hi! What's going on?
Code 47 at a nightclub on Ninth.
A blonde woman going cray-cray.
And since I'm down here,
it's probably the blonde woman
we've been looking for.
The woman who's killing people
in Pennytown.
- Suit up.
- Yeah.
Help!
Run!
You have got to stop this!
Sara?
Your sister's alive, she's out there
and she's hurting people.
How is she alive?
The Lazarus Pit?
Did you two spend your spa weekend
in Nanda Parbat?
It was the only place we could
get a reservation.
The bloodlust is worse with Sara,
isn't it?
Because you brought her back from death.
Yeah, and that's not the only problem.
Sara's not herself. She's changed.
Why didn't you come to me with this?
Come to you for what?
Your expertise with magical resurrection
or that judgmental look on your face?
For help finding her, Laurel, before she
gets hurt or she hurts anyone else.
And if I have a judgmental look on my face
right now,
it's because you played with forces that
you do not understand
and now people are dying because of it.
- Who's he?
- John Constantine.
Says so right on the business card
your boss took from me.
He had this on his person as well.
Do you recognize these landmarks?
Yeah.
Good. Whatever it is Mr. Constantine
is looking for,
I want you to find it and
bring it back to me.
Oh, come on!
I'm telling you, you can't trust him.
Then you can follow him.
What are you doing? You actually praying?
No. No, these aren't prayers, mate.
Ah, ah, ah!
Unless you wanna redecorate your lovely
hut with his brains,
I suggest you drop your weapon.
On the floor.
You won't escape this island.
I don't intend on leaving just yet.
Come on, you.
- You really know the place on that map?
- Yes.
- You do? Good.
You're gonna show me. Now drive.
We need to talk.
About Sara?
Laurel told you?
Not exactly.
You gotta admire her consistency.
Keeps her death secret from me,
her resurrection secret from you.
- Are you okay?
- Am I okay?
I think there are certain situations in
life where the word "okay" does not apply.
Well, we're working on finding Sara.
Good. 'Cause we got other problems.
FELICITYI It's a RAT,
a Remote Access Trojan.
Basically, a computer virus.
A polymorphic code designed to target
and erase certain pieces of data.
It's buried under three levels of
encryption. By the time I've cracked it...
Darhk could be wondering why
I haven't run his errand for him.
I'm not sending you to break into
a federal facility without backup.
I don't want Laurel knowing
about me and Darhk.
It wasn't suggesting Laurel.
Oliver tell you that Darhk works for
an organization? HIVE?
Yeah.
HIVE had my brother killed.
I'm sorry.
And now, Detective, you're telling me
that you were working with them.
For them.
It's a long story.
I've got time.
This city's been hurting.
This is nothing new.
Darhk comes to me.
He offers to help fix it.
He's got powerful friends. He's got money.
And this is months before the Ghosts,
all right?
I didn't see him as anything other than
a concerned citizen.
Okay. And then?
Well, then he's doing all this good stuff,
and then he asks me where the fire chief
is going on his vacation.
So, I give him the address of his
summer cabin.
Next day, the cabin blows up.
- You confront Darhk about this?
- Course I did.
And that's when he shows me pictures
of Laurel.
At work. At home. AA meetings.
So this thing with your brother,
is it gonna be a problem
for us working together?
No, Detective.
Because you being next to Darhk
is gonna help us take down HIVE.
Any luck
connecting Sara's victims?
Just that she's only killed muggers
and street thugs.
I still can't believe that it's Sara
we're talking about.
That she's alive. I mean, I know how
it's possible, but how is it possible?
The world is a much more
complicated place than most people
are comfortable believing.
I received an old message from Ray,
from the moment right before he died.
I almost didn't listen to it because,
you know, I didn't wanna feel
that grief again.
The threat of zombie apocalypse aside,
isn't it kind of nice not having to deal
with the pain of saying goodbye?
Only if it were that simple.
Not a day goes by
that I don't miss my parents
or Tommy.
Then I think about what I would
give just to spend
another minute with them.
But what's happening with Sara isn't
healing anyone's pain. It's just...
It's making it worse.
She almost killed those two girls.
I mean, why would she even go after them?
Her marble collection's a little
incomplete. Just guessing.
Or they have something in common.
Well, the waitress was Stephanie Dingess,
and the girl at the club was
Lindsey Poison.
- Oh, my God! Both these girls...
- They look like Thea.
Passing on the judgment for tonight.
Sara.
I just can't believe that Sara
would do something like this.
She's not Sara.
No, it...
That's not it.
Hey. Hey. How ya feelin'?
Sara, she...
No, I know. It's okay. You're safe.
She tried to kill me.
She's not in her right mind.
You've no idea.
This is the Pit.
She's going through the same thing I am.
Thea, I thought that you were better.
When I went to Nanda Parbat, I
killed two guys.
Malcolm served them up
on a platter for me and
helped keep my bloodlust at bay.
Oh, my God! Thank God you're all right.
Laurel, come with me.
Is Thea okay?
No.
Not only is Thea hospitalized,
but she has Merlyn influencing her
to kill people.
What are you talking about?
Just another thing that happened on
your secret trip to Nanda Parbat.
Hey, I didn't tell you that I took
my sister to Nanda Parbat
because I knew that you wouldn't approve.
Why didn't you tell me you took Thea?
- What does that have to do with anything?
- It's the hypocrisy that I can't stand.
What? It's okay for you to do whatever
you have to for your sister,
but it's not okay for me to do
the same to mine.
Sara was dead. Thea wasn't.
Then why didn't you tell me about Thea
seven months ago?
Because you don't see me as an equal.
Come on. Laurel, of course,
I see you as an equal.
No, you don't. You never have.
- You never told me you were the Arrow.
- Keep your voice down.
You never supported me becoming
the Black Canary.
And you never would've told me that
there's a way to save my sister.
My sister, she's out of her mind
right now
because of something that I did,
a decision that I made.
Did you everjust stop and think
for one second
about what I might be going through?
I'm sorry about what happened to Thea.
I really am. I love your family,
I always have.
I just wish that sometimes you would
give a damn about mine.
Get out.
You sure this is the place?
It's the place.
What's going on? Who are you?
How much do you know about what your boss
is really doing on this island, eh?
Making drugs.
If only. Your friend Reiter,
he's the dangerous sort.
What's that supposed to mean?
It means there are things on this island
that bad people shouldn't have access to.
Says the guy with a gun pointed
at my head.
I'm not a bad guy.
A little hardscrabble sure, but, uh,
I'm on the side of the angels, mate,
at least when they're not busy trying to
screw me over.
You're right. This is the spot.
What? You never seen magic before?
Go on then, Alice.
Down the rabbit hole you go.
Nice job getting us in.
You learn how to do that
before or after working with Queen?
I'll save that for another story.
Yeah, I bet.
- Is this the access point?
- Yeah. Yeah, it looks like it.
All right.
Keep an eye out for rent-a-cops.
This wouldn't do my career prospects
too much good.
It working?
Yeah, I think so. Looks like the virus
is erasing files on people.
Which people? And why?
Both really good questions.
Hey-
What are you doing here?
Waiting for you to wake up.
Thea, I owe you an apology.
No, no. There's no need for you
to apologize for anything.
Yes, I do. I brought Sara back without any
idea of how to control her.
And I'm the one who killed her
in the first place.
That's why she's after me, you know.
This bloodlust she's consumed by.
It's the same pain I feel
when I think about Ra's.
I don't understand.
Because the person that I'm driven
to kill,
the one who killed me, is already dead.
Thea, what're you talking about?
She kills me, she'll be okay.
If the only way to save Sara is to
kill you, then that's no cure at all.
- How much longer?
- Two minutes.
- Wait. Wait. What was that?
- What is it?
- I just saw my brother's name.
- What's that all about?
What'd you do?
Nothing. I just have to get
back to whatever it is this thing erased.
No, we don't have time.
Security's gonna be on their way now.
I'm not leaving.
Drop it! Drop it now!
Hey, hey, it's all right. Captain Lance,
Star City Police Department.
I just tracked this hacker here.
All right. Now, look.
Go get some back up, all right?
Call this in. Come on, go!
Go!
It's a good story. Just wish you would've
told me before you gave me a concussion.
Come on.
Then it wouldn't have looked real.
I didn't know you were still here.
Hey. Yeah, I just came to make sure
Thea was okay.
I didn't have a chance to before, so...
She sleeping?
TFYing to.
Look.
I know why you're here.
Okay, I get it.
I want you to know that it's okay.
And I want you to do it.
About what I said before...
You said some things that you meant.
Thea?
You sure you wanna be here?
I hated hospitals before tonight.
Just another excuse to stay away.
At the hospital, I looked Sara
in the eyes. She wasn't there.
What does that mean?
The Pit is not supposed to be used
on the dead.
It brought Sara's body back,
but all this is happening...
Because it didn't restore her soul.
We still need to find her. Okay.
Sara died long before you moved in
with Laurel,
and she knew exactly which hospital room
to look for you in.
What? You think Sara can sense
Thea somehow?
And here I was just about wrapping my mind
around metahumans.
Wait, we've both been in the Pit.
Maybe that gives us some type
of connection, a connection we can use.
Thea, you just got out of the hospital.
I don't wanna use you as bait.
Well, I guess it's a good thing
you're not in charge anymore.
We'll have her back, Oliver. All of us.
I don't understand. How did you...
Well, that's the great thing about magic.
It can't be explained.
There are places in this world as old
as the world.
Places of nexus draw bad people to them.
This island is such a place.
It's no accident that you're here.
Let me guess. "Do not enter."
More like, "Only for the pure of heart."
That's not you, mate.
There you are, my pretty girl.
How do you know it's a girl?
I can do that trick, too.
Clever boy.
I'd usually be more artful,
but I'm on something of a clock.
No!
I'm not a bad guy, either.
- Mission accomplished.
- Well done.
Are you sticking around
for a cupcake or something?
This thing you had me do. I saw some of
the names you had erased.
All military.
And here I had you pegged for a Luddite.
Fast learner.
One of those names,
Sergeant Andrew Diggle.
What is he to you?
He died six years ago. Why are you erasing
the record of a dead man?
You know what? I'm gonna tell you.
And only because you completed your task
with such efficiency.
We hired an assassin to murder
Sergeant Diggle.
Why?
Afghanistan's an interesting place,
replete with opportunities
for an enterprising enlisted man
to engage in.
What are you talking about?
Drugs, weapons, murder.
Your Sergeant Diggle was an eager beaver.
Unfortunately for him, our organization
weaved itself into that part of the world,
and as you know, we don't play well
with others.
So you had him killed.
What is this guy? Your best buddy?
I don't see you associating yourself
with crime lords.
Present company excepted.
Now, are we done?
Set.
I have to say, it feels really weird
being back here right now.
Don't worry.
E veryone's in position.
It's nothing, okay? I don't think this
is gonna actually work.
Oh, God, I take that back.
Get her out of here!
Dad was right. There's nothing left
inside of you, Sara.
Tranq arrow.
No. No, you said it yourself.
She has no soul.
Laurel.
Let's get it back.
What?
- Oliver.
- John.
It's been a dog's age, mate.
More than. Do you remember that favor
you owe me?
I hardly expect you to let me forget that.
How quickly can you get to Star City?
I need your help.
So you're gonna perform some kind of
exorcism on my sister?
No, an exorcism is a removal of
demonic possession.
What your sister needs is a restitutionem,
the restoration of her soul to her body.
And you've done this before?
Once. Maybe a year ago.
But don't worry,
it's just like riding a bike.
I'm sure we have a lot of work to do to
prepare. I assume you brought a list?
Apologies, I didn't have time to translate
that from its original Aramaic.
You know, if I knew you were surrounded
by so many pretty girls, Oliver,
I would have stopped by sooner.
Where did Oliver find this guy? The Luxor?
I'm just glad that the latest person
from Oliver's past
is not another gorgeous woman.
I'm not even going to ask.
You got my message. I'm so happy you came.
I'm her father, too.
I hate to be the one to say this,
but what if something goes wrong?
Oh, don't worry. If things go wrong,
then we'll all be too dead to care.
Well then, now we just need a...
I think I got everything in here that
you wanted,
although I am not entirely sure what you
need a dead peacock feather for.
Ah.
Oh, nice one.
That's been bugging me for hours.
Now, I've only got enough juice to send
myself and two of you
to the other realm and back, so...
I think it should be me. Um...
I'm the reason why
she's like this right now.
No offense, love, but from what I hear,
you're not exactly bringing out
the best in Sara right now, are you?
Laurel. Do you trust me?
Trust me when I tell you this will work.
Oh, there's, uh, one more thing.
Whatever's locked her soul away is not
gonna give it over without a fight.
So be ready.
All right then. On with the show.
Mmm.
Oliver!
Well, I've had worse hangovers.
So what are we supposed to do now?
Help!
Laurel, no!
- This is new.
- Well, new is why you brought me along.
- Help!
- No, no, no.No.
Well, I'm not gonna just stand here.
We need a tour guide.
Ah.
This way. Unless you want to be trapped
here for all eternity.
This is what
locked away Sara's soul.
- How the human mind perceives it, anyway.
- Help!
Get to the Pit. You need to work together
to get her out.
I'll take care of our new friend.
You want some, do you?
You know, any time today would be good.
Come on, Sara.
Laurel. You're all right.
You all right?
I don't know what happened. You okay?
What happened? What is she? Did we...
Sara.
Sara. Sara.
You're okay.
Thank you, John. I owe you one.
I believe I owed you one, mate.
How's about we just call it even, eh?
How about anytime, anywhere you need me,
and I'll be there?
I'll take that.
You know, the hair on the back of my neck
has been standing up
since the moment I got into town.
That is probably our current problem,
Damien Darhk.
Oh, you've heard of him.
You watch yourself around that one, mate.
He'll make what you saw in the other
realm look like a bloody gnat.
Any helpful advice?
Yeah, leave town while you still can.
Well, he's a very specific kind of yummy.
Oh! I'm gonna pretend I didn't hear you
just say that.
Are we okay? I mean, I just keep
waiting for you to blow up at me.
Because you lied to me about Nanda Parbat?
Yeah.
Thea, I don't have the right to be mad at
anyone for keeping secrets.
But I'm sorry that I made you feel as
though you had to. Come here.
So, mate, I owe you one.
What the hell is all this?
This is the Orb of Horus.
It's actually a grimoire,
an ancient spellbook. You asked.
And, uh, what are you gonna do with it?
Same as I do with all the other
mystical objects I find.
Keep them in a safe place, away from
the Baron Reiters of this world.
Remember what I told you about
this island, mate.
This Reiter bloke is not only here
for the narcotics.
But then again, it's not your problem,
is it?
Come back with me.
I've got a boat on the southern shore.
You saw those people at camp.
I can't leave them behind.
Well, aren't you the hero.
I also can't come back empty-handed.
Conklin suspects me enough as it is.
Fair enough.
Here.
Goons like Reiter, they're only interested
in the sparkly bits, anyway.
The real power is in the spell.
Here. Here. I'll show you.
Lift up your shirt, mate.
What?
What the hell did you just do?
I gave you some insurance against Reiter.
And when the time comes,
you'll know how to use it.
Now, I believe that concludes
our business.
Uh...
I need you to punch me in the face.
Right. My escape attempt
left a bruise, right?
All right. I must warn you,
I've got a hell of a right hook.
I'm... I'm fine. Thanks very much.
All right, so just stay on message.
Unity, united community.
- United. Got it.
- All right.
Hey! Laurel.
Maybe we need to work on your
understanding
of the phrase "distance yourself."
Only if you insist on continuing to use it
when it relates to my friends.
Okay.
It's your campaign.
You pay me whether you win or lose.
I am gonna go keep him from quitting,
but I'm very proud of you right now.
How's Sara?
Resting.
It turns out that getting your soul back
is exhausting.
Yeah.
Ollie, I don't know how I'm ever
gonna be able to thank you.
Just like that.
Well, thank you.
And thank you for inviting me
here tonight.
After what I said to you in the hospital,
I thought that I'd be the last person
you'd wanna see.
Well, you were right. I haven't always
been the best friend for you.
But I'd be grateful for the opportunity
to try and start to be.
How can I say no to the man that helped me
save my sister's soul?
Yeah.
I've made mistakes,
mistakes that have
hurt people close to me.
But I'm not hereto run from the past
because the past has contributed
to making...
I thought you'd be out celebrating
with Sara.
Yeah. There's enough time for that.
- Please.
- I figured I owed you something.
I asked Darhk about your brother.
He, uh, gave me something.
You don't have to read this.
You can remember your brother
how you knew him.
Are you sure about this?
Yeah. It's legit.
I'm very sorry.
Thank you, Detective.
Gut punch doesn't deserve a thank you.
I wanted to know why
HIVE had my brother killed,
and now I do, so...
Felicity! Welcome back!
Welcome, welcome, welcome.
How many of these have you drank?
It's "drunk," actually, and many.
But worth it.
You cleared up the rest of Ray's message?
I think so. The playback was rendering
when you came in. So, propitious timing.
You're not even allowed to say "energy
drink" while on company time ever again.
That's okay. I think I might be having
a cardiac incident, anyway.
So, check out the message.
I was just about to call you.
Wait, where's my phone.
Wait, did I call you already?
- Curtis!
- Wait.
I'm sorry, Felicity,
this is my fault.
I got myself into this mess screwing
around with my exosuit and nanotechnology.
But recriminations probably aren't the
best use of this limited bandwidth.
What I need you to know is
I'm alive and I'm in trouble.
English - SDH