My name is Oliver Queen.
After five years in hell,
I returned home with only one goal,
to save my city.
Today, I fight that war on two fronts.
By day, I lead Star City as its mayor.
But by night, I'm someone else.
I am something else.
I am the Green Arrow.
Previously on Arrow...
Before he was taken,
Cayden was working on a biometric tracker
that could recognize a heartbeat,
anywhere in the world.
Anywhere Adrian Chase is.
You're gonna help me free Cayden
from where A.R.G.U.S. is holding him.
We can think of another way to find him.
This is our only chance.
Don't do this.
Helix is about to extract Cayden James.
You're holding someone
with no lawyer, no trial.
The woman I love could never do this.
Lyla, this job has changed you.
You didn't back my play.
All of the times that I supported you,
you couldn't do the same for me.
What's that?
- Tracker's honing in on Chase's location.
- Where is he?
He's here.
Felicity?
No, Felicity. Hey.
Chase. He's here.
Don't move.
That's not gonna be a problem.
All right. If Chase is here,
he's not on this level.
It felt like an explosion,
but there was minimal damage.
It was an EMP.
A burst of electromagnetic radiation.
Everything in the bunker
with an electric circuit has been fried.
How do you know?
Because the spinal implant
that helps me walk isn't working.
I can't feel my legs.
You know, under different circumstances
these chemlights might seem festive.
No sign of Chase.
Looks like the EMP was his play.
Elevator and security doors offline.
- You check the emergency exit door?
- I did. It's welded shut.
If Chase wasn't so evil,
I might actually be impressed.
The air vents are gonna be down, too...
The air vents will last
a little while longer, but...
Yeah, we have to get a message out.
Other than standing at the door
and yelling really loudly,
I don't really know what our options are.
We're trapped.
Do you ever feel like we're trapped?
- What do you mean?
- Like, we're trapped
in this vicious cycle.
I mean, you put an arrow
in one crime lord,
- and another just, like...
- pops up...
Well, a lot of people are trying to fill
the vacuum left by Damien Darhk.
Yeah. This week's winner is Werner Zytle.
- Do you have a location on him?
- Not yet,
but Curtis is working on fixing a 20.
Sounds like you don't even need me.
Have you seen Curtis try to throw a punch?
I mean, we don't need you,
we need 10 of you.
Nice try...
If we had more boots on the ground
or masks on faces, or whatever,
we might actually have a real possibility
at catching one of these guys
that is auditioning to be
the new Damien Darhk.
I don't have the bandwidth
or, more importantly,
the temperament to train a new team.
Besides you're trying
to fix something that's working.
We are a good team.
Yeah, we are and we always have been.
Yeah.
Oh, my God. That's a nasty cut.
Oh. Well, it's not gonna scar
but I was thinking maybe...
Getting some Kevlar sleeves?
You know me too well.
- Hey, guys.
- Hey.
Hi, Curtis.
Palmer Tech has been working on
an advanced thermal imaging prototype,
which I borrowed, tweaked,
and developed to find...
Boom.
- Bad guy on a yacht.
- Dang.
Thank you for the assist.
See? Help is good.
I will contact you when I'm on-site.
Call me back, will you?
Better yet, just show up.
Things are going
all kinds of hell around here.
Still no luck?
No.
It's like Oliver's
dropped off the face of the Earth. Again.
How's it going over here?
Well, every defense attorney in town
just found out that the DA
is a serial killer, so not good.
You think the court's gonna
overturn Chase's convictions?
If I didn't, I wouldn't have convened
this war room.
It'd be sure nice to have
a mayor heading it up, though.
- You heard from Felicity?
- Radio silence.
- But I got Curtis.
- And?
He's gonna check and see
if Oliver's at the bunker.
Get on it.
You find Oliver yet?
Hey, Rene. You do realize
that you called me,
literally 15 minutes ago, right?
Blame it on Lance.
Guy gets freaky when he's worried.
Yeah, well. Lucky for you, I can run fast.
- Weird.
- What's weird?
No power. Whole place.
What are the chances that
Oliver forgot to pay his electric bill?
Infinitesimal, considering I rigged
the place so that it'd be off the grid...
And a bomb just went off.
Not funny.
I'm not kidding.
I heard some kind of explosion.
How many is that?
Eleven. Hasn't made a dent yet.
What's that thing made of anyway?
Keltium. It's a proprietary alloy
developed by the US Government
to repel nuclear blasts.
So, you're saying even if we had
a nuke down here, it wouldn't work?
Seems like Cisco did such a good job
of turning this place
into an impenetrable fortress,
he turned it
into an impenetrable deathtrap.
Chase doesn't want to kill me, remember?
Yeah, he just locked you down here
for the fun of it.
He locked us down here
because he is up to something up there...
And I can't do anything about it.
Well, the good news is
there's not much left for him to do.
I mean, he's already gone after
Curtis, Lance, Evelyn, even Susan,
and Thea's away and Lyla and J.J.
have A.R.G.U.S. protection.
I mean, who's left?
William.
William's in a different town, with
a different name and a different address.
I'd be surprised
if Chase even knows about William.
When he was holding me captive...
He showed me a picture of him.
What?
- Does he...
- Doesn't know where he is.
Yet.
We have to get out of here.
Cisco's original blueprints
are in that cabinet.
If you're just gonna stand there,
you might as well say something.
I thought you were sleeping.
I couldn't sleep.
I know you're upset.
I know you think that I violated
some kind of trust between us, but...
Lyla...
When you said that
you wouldn't become like Amanda Waller,
I was worried about you.
I'm fine.
You're the one who seems to have a problem
with the way
that I've been running A.R.G.U.S.
Which is particularly interesting to me
since neither one of us has a job
that fits
the conventional definition of morality.
What's that supposed to mean?
You're upset because A.R.G.U.S.
is locking people up without due process
when you and Oliver and your team
of masked recruits
has been playing judge and jury
for years now.
Lyla, I can't believe you actually
compared Team Arrow
to this clandestine
government super-agency.
Well, I just did!
Hello?
Diggle family? Anybody home?
I definitely heard Lyla yell.
Knock... Knock again.
Didn't know we were having a party.
I'm sensing a lot of marital tension...
- What do you guys want?
- So sorry to interrupt.
There's a problem at the bunker.
I can get us out of here
by climbing up the elevator shaft.
If you can think about
going up the elevator,
Chase has already
thought of a way to stop you.
So you're saying it's booby-trapped.
I'd bet my copious Palmer Tech
severance pay on it.
I'm saying I can handle it.
Or we figure out a new plan.
Like, getting a signal out to the team.
You just said that everything
with an electrical circuit down here
has been fried.
Only because I haven't figured out
how to get power yet.
So, figure out how to get power,
and I will go up the elevator shaft.
Seriously? Are you still
not listening to me?
Did the EMP give you short-term amnesia
about what we were arguing about
down here in the first place?
This feels like the best choice right now.
Besides the one I just gave you.
I told you so. I told you so.
I told you so.
How many times do you think that is?
I was not keeping count.
Eleven, I think. But not nearly enough.
You ready?
Because your operating theater is now lit.
And of all the things that we need to do
to get ourselves out
of this hermetically sealed bunker,
stitching up a wound from a fall that
I totally predicted isn't one of them.
I think that counts as 12.
I... Okay, I'm ready.
- That hurt?
- Yes. Yes, it did.
I won't say, "Good."
But let the record show I was tempted.
Do you remember what we were discussing
before we got EMP-blasted?
Mmm-hmm.
The fact that I back your play,
even when I don't agree,
but you don't have
the same consideration for me.
You didn't listen to me
when I wanted to join Helix...
With good reason.
I could say the same thing about you
a million times over, but I support you.
Because I trust you.
Felicity, I trust you.
Really?
There's a hole in your back
that says otherwise.
Fair enough.
Is that the painkillers talking?
If you have a plan
that will get us out of here, fantastic.
Let's finish this up and let's try it.
Okay.
What's an EDM?
Something you might hear at a nightclub.
This was an EMP.
Actually, fun fact, the previous lair
used to be underneath the nightclub.
- Curtis...
- Right. Sorry.
And you said Felicity's down there, too.
According to the last position
logged by her tracking nanites.
What do we need to get them out?
Rappelling gear, acetylene torches,
wideband active field probes,
tungsten carbide drill bits.
I can cobble together
most of those things but...
Text me a list of whatever you need,
A.R.G.U.S. is at your disposal.
- Great.
- If that's okay with you.
I hate to ask this, but how much air
do they have left down there?
Well, if they don't exert themselves,
five, maybe six hours.
Okay. Well, we're here. Now what?
The mainframe
has a built in cellular chip,
but our rewire didn't generate
enough kilowatts to jumpstart it.
Right. Because everything
with an electronic circuit is fried.
Everything with an electronic circuit...
My old bike?
She's a beaut.
Good old-fashioned combustion engine.
So we can generate electricity
without an electronic starter.
- Oh, yeah.
- That is smart.
SCPD is happy
to have Zytle off the streets.
Or, more appropriately, off the docks.
- Great. So, mission accomplished.
- Yeah.
- What's next for my favorite power couple?
- Power couple?
Yeah.
I thought that you and Oliver...
You guys aren't hooking up again?
Oh, no. No. God, no.
Why would you even think that?
Well, because every time I come by
you guys are in the middle of
exchanging longing looks for each other.
No, we're not.
- Oh, Felicity.
- We look nothing like that. I don't know...
"I wish I didn't
break up with him. Aww..."
What? What?
- "You know, we were so happy together..."
- Were?
- Yeah.
- Past tense. Yes.
Look, I know that he hurt you by
not telling you about his son, but...
Look, it's not just about William.
It's about what William represents.
Oliver having sex with another woman.
No, but thank you for that visual.
William is symptomatic of a larger problem
between Oliver and I.
That being?
Oliver doesn't trust me.
Right, your man who has put his life
in your hands a couple thousand times.
Trusting me as Overwatch is one thing,
but we're talking about his son,
Curtis, his child.
Oliver doesn't trust me enough
to share important information
and crucial information with me.
What's the point
of being in a relationship at all?
I'm not gonna say that
Oliver Queen plays great with others.
But?
But he can still
change that about himself.
You know what he can't change?
What?
That way he looks at you.
You both owe it
to each other to see, Felicity.
- Tonight.
- Tonight? No. Why tonight?
- Well...
- Don't say...
Curtis.
Next time...
Pick up your own Chinese food.
Um, you know, I just thought
we'd all be hungry
- from the crime-fighting.
- Yeah.
Oh!
Oh, man! I...
You know, I just remembered.
I have a date night with Paul, my husband.
I have a date with my husband,
so I have to go to that.
You guys enjoy that though.
You enjoy that.
Also, there is
wine in the garage, so... Bye.
What?
I'll get the wine.
Okay, gentlemen. Eyes are up.
Gotta say, this team is never boring.
Didn't think I'd be doing this
when I woke up this morning.
Oliver and Felicity might suffocate.
How can you be so glib?
You've met me, right?
And how come your toy balls
can't float down here and do this for us?
For the thousandth time, Rene,
they're called T-Spheres.
But if you want,
call them by their proper name.
You named them?
Kodo and Podo.
You know Dar's thieving little ferrets
on The Beastmaster.
Let's just say, uh...
A young Marc Singer was quite helpful
in me discovering my homosexuality.
And my heterosexuality.
You're on an open channel, by the way.
Open line...
Well, look, I can't get my T-Spheres
because they are in the bunker
and, therefore, fried. So, whatever.
I swear those two are going to make
the cutest couple one day.
John?
- John?
- Yeah.
Anything in particular you're looking for
with that 1,000-yard stare?
It's that obvious, huh?
Rene wasn't the only one who could
clock tension between you and the missus,
if that's what you mean.
Right.
Let me guess.
You confronted Lyla
about the A.R.G.U.S. black site
and it didn't go too good.
Something like that.
You wanna talk about it?
Not really.
Okay.
Well, if you did...
I'd tell you about Vinnie and me.
Vinnie?
My undercover partner.
On and off the job.
Working UC, we had to keep
certain things from each other.
And we didn't do it because we wanted to.
We did it because we had to.
Okay.
It took some horse-trading
but I got everything Curtis asked for.
- Great.
- What's the status here?
He and Rene are getting a lay of the land.
Kodo and Podo. Any updates?
No good ones.
The EMP fried the hydraulics system.
We have to cut through the magnetic seal
in order to reach the manual override.
- We'll need the acetylene torch.
- And the wideband active field probe.
Without my T-Spheres,
there's no telling
what's on the other side of this thing
after the EMP blast.
- Is it working?
- Give it a second.
Thanks again, for trying things my way.
A first time for everything.
Regarding Helix...
You know why I didn't back your play
and you know, or you should, that it had
nothing to do with a lack of trust.
If you're going to start saying,
yet again, that it's because
you don't want me to be like you,
you can hold your breath.
Particularly since
we are running out of oxygen.
Cayden James is a criminal.
Cayden James is a hacker.
As in, so much less worse than the Bratva.
I made the exact same trade-off
you did to get Chase.
I picked the lesser of two evils.
The fact that I didn't want you to do that
- doesn't make me a hypocrite.
- What does it make you, then?
It makes me someone
who doesn't want you to be like me.
Yeah.
Bam! That's what I'm talking about.
- You okay?
- Yeah, depending on what that sound is.
That's not good.
One of the pipes is damaged.
I just hope it's not the highly toxic
and flammable gas pipe...
So much for doing things my way.
Careful. Don't breathe.
Well, breathe but don't inhale.
- Done.
- You okay?
Yeah, I'm fine. I'm a little...
A little light-headed.
Hold on.
How much more duct tape do we have?
That's the last of it.
Um, we have the epoxy spray
that Cisco gave us to fix our suits.
If it's upstairs,
then that's definitely flooded by now.
How much time do we have?
Twenty minutes. Max. Before we asphyxiate.
Good times, right?
Oliver, we've already gone over that.
It's just full of dead ends,
which is an unfortunate
but accurate choice of words.
- Wait a second.
- Yeah, we can wait.
We only have 20 minutes, but we can wait.
There's a steam tunnel underneath
this part of the bunker.
Do we have anything to pry this open?
I don't know. It doesn't look pry-able.
Felicity, this is it.
Okay. This could be the fumes talking
but I think I have a slightly insane idea.
How insane is "slightly insane"?
Well, that depends on how you feel
about setting off an explosive arrow
in a room full of flammable gas?
Careful, Rene.
That seal is pure titanium.
It has a melting point of between 1,600
and 1,700 degrees Celsius.
Just let me do my thing, hoss.
That's weird.
No, no, no, Rene, stop!
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow! Ow!
I'm gonna need you
to stop making that noise.
I'm sorry my agonizing pain
is bothering you.
I mean, thank you very much
for helping me with this.
These are
just second degree burns, Curtis.
You should be just fine
in a couple of weeks.
Do we know what caused the explosion?
High levels of methane. Am I the only one
that thinks this is Prometheus?
No. But we need to find a way of saving
our friends without blowing them up.
- What about acid?
- No.
- No, I don't think that would...
- Wait, wait, wait.
You said the hatch was titanium, right?
Yeah.
Hydrochloric acid
will turn it into Swiss cheese.
I used to work undercover
with a gang of safe crackers.
That's good. Let's get cooking.
Careful!
If the powder is one gram under,
the grating won't blow.
What if it's one gram over?
Well, it'll increase the breaching radius,
igniting the gas,
filling this entire place with fire...
It'll kill us both,
is what you're gonna say, right?
Yeah.
No pressure. Careful.
Yup.
- Wait.
- What?
My math is probably right,
but what if it's wrong?
Are you still Felicity Smoak?
Yeah.
Your math is always right.
Right.
Okay, um, the arrow needs to go in
at exactly a 45-degree angle.
Okay.
By exactly, do you mean exactly?
Well, one centimeter off
and the blast will force the grate off,
igniting the gas and...
Please don't miss.
You didn't miss.
Looks like about a two-story drop.
Drop?
I'll get the climbing gear.
Remind me again, why I thought
this was gonna be a fun idea?
I don't know.
Hop down. Hop down. Hop down. Excuse me.
Ow...
Right. Okay, so...
- This is just a chin-up.
- Okay.
Everybody knows a chin-up.
- Well...
- All right?
It's a chin-up with a flourish at the end.
Yeah.
I can't do a chin-up.
- Come here.
- Okay. Um...
I don't flourish well.
- I believe in you. Ready?
- Oh. Whoa.
Oh, my God. Hey! I'm chinning and upping.
- Okay. Kind of.
- Whoo!
- Ow.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
- All right.
- Okay. Mmm-hmm.
- You ready?
- One... Two, three.
- Yeah.
- Go!
- No, no, no.
- Help. Help. It's too high.
- Yep. All right. I got you.
- Good. Higher than it was before.
- I got you.
Um...
Yeah. I kind of did it.
- I think.
- Sure.
There was the chin-up part,
I think we could work on.
You did a half of one.
Half. I'll take the half.
It's exhilarating.
I don't think that's really my...
In fairness,
you've had a little bit to drink.
Yeah...
I've had a lot to drink.
You should just... Thank you.
What happened? Did the acid work?
Yeah. It's just, it's gonna take
10 seasons of The Bachelor
before it melts those hinges down.
What? I don't judge your DVR.
Okay, how much time do they have left?
Ten minutes, give or take.
Yeah. Somebody better order up a miracle.
I don't know if this counts
but it could help.
Where the hell did you get this?
A.R.G.U.S. likes to keep tabs
on interesting tech.
You copied my T-Sphere?
No, we improved them.
No. You're both wrong.
Lyla, if you stole this,
what other surprises
can I be expecting from you?
It's okay. Just hang on. Hang on tight.
- Not that tight. Not that tight.
- Sorry.
That's okay.
- Almost there.
- Okay.
I got you. I got you.
- All right.
- Right here.
- Yeah, I know.
Thanks.
Are you okay?
- Hey. We made it. We made it.
- Yeah. I'm fine.
Yeah.
It's another dead end.
Okay, stop using that term.
We bought ourselves some time
away from the gas, at least.
Hey. Oliver?
Oliver?
Oliver? Oliver?
Oliver? Oliver? Oliver?
Hey, hey, hey. Hey, hey, hey.
You gotta stay awake, okay?
I think I'm losing a lot of blood.
Tell me something I don't know.
I'm so sorry.
Normally I would relish
an Oliver Queen apology,
but this sudden admission
is making me nervous.
You were right. I didn't have your back.
But it wasn't because I didn't want you
to end up like me, Felicity.
It was much more than that.
Okay. Lots of blood loss with
exposure to toxic gas makes you go crazy.
- Now we know that.
- I need you to hear this.
- I will. Later. Right...
- Might not have a later.
Do not talk like that.
I need you to know the truth.
About what?
I didn't have your back.
It was not because of you
or a lack of trust, it was because of me.
It was because of me.
I'm not the man you think I am.
I'm not the man you fell in love with.
I put the hood on
to right my father's wrongs.
But the basis of it, the foundation of it
and what you did and what Digg did
and what the team did in my name...
It was all based on a lie.
What are you talking about?
Chase, he showed me
when he held me hostage,
that I didn't do what I did to be a hero.
I did what I did...
Because there was a part of me,
a bigger part than I would like to admit.
I enjoyed it.
I enjoyed killing.
It's not about not trusting you.
I will always trust you.
I don't trust myself.
Oliver?
Oliver, don't... Oliver?
Oliver. Hey.
Hey! Oliver, come back!
Come back. Oliver!
Come back.
Just promise me you're not gonna
tell anyone that we had bunker sex.
And by anyone, I mean Curtis.
Because he'd never look at me the same.
Are you sure?
Because he had me pick up Chinese food
and then he suggested wine.
I'm pretty sure
that he was rooting for exactly this.
So...
Maybe he saw something that we didn't see.
I think Curtis watches
too many rom-come with Paul.
You okay?
Yeah. I'm fine.
It's just...
Talk to me. What's going on?
This was nice. You know?
It was really nice. It just...
It doesn't change things between us.
We still have our problems.
It's because we never talked
about our problems.
We never talked about William.
Even if there was no William,
there still wouldn't be an "us."
Because you don't trust me.
I was hoping that you'd change.
But you don't trust anyone.
And I don't know why.
You know, maybe if I knew why
things would be different.
I don't even think you know why.
I love you.
But that is why I can't settle
for anything less than your full trust.
I know I should be mad that
you stole my tech
but the modification designs
you guys put on here are ridiculous.
Hey. How about less geeking out
and more figuring out how to use
that thing to get to Felicity and Oliver?
They ran out of time 10 minutes ago.
What is this?
It's an audit
of every black op I've signed off on
as Director of A.R.G.U.S.
Why are you giving me this?
I don't want there to be
any more secrets between us, John.
But there is one thing
I need to know from you.
Name it.
No matter what Oliver Queen does,
no matter how morally compromising,
- you stand behind him no matter what.
- Lyla.
Why can't you do that for me?
Well, I guess I never really
thought of it like that.
Well, maybe you should start.
Because I'm not Oliver, Johnnie.
I'm your wife.
And even though I disagree with many
of your choices, I trusted those choices.
I trusted you.
I think I deserve the same consideration.
I figured it out!
Oh, sorry. Were you guys
in the middle of something?
It looks like you were
probably in the middle of something.
But I did figure it out.
So, let's chop, chop, chop.
It's okay, Curtis.
We're fine.
Let's go get Oliver
and Felicity out of there.
Oliver?
Oliver? Damn it. Wake up.
- Hey!
- Hey.
- Are you okay?
- Oh, my God. You're okay.
I think the wound re-clotted.
Careful. Hey.
Felicity, I don't...
I don't know
that I can get us out of here.
Well, it'll give us some time
to talk about something.
Like this crazy idea
that you enjoy killing.
It's why you disbanded the team, isn't it?
Yeah.
Oliver, you said that I don't know
the kind of man that you are.
I wouldn't have fallen in love with you,
or wanted to marry you
if I didn't know
exactly the kind of man that you are.
Chase tortured you for a week.
You're the toughest person I know
but anyone,
anyone would have admitted
to being a tap-dancing flamingo
after what he put you through.
Adrian Chase didn't make me a killer.
No. Five years in hell did that.
Five years dealing
with this city's worst did that.
You've spent a decade dealing with horrors
that most people don't even realize exist.
And the fact that,
that didn't turn you into a monster
proves exactly the kind of person
that you are.
I don't know what kind of person I am.
- Curtis?
- Not just Curtis.
Are you guys okay?
Oliver is a little hurt.
We could use your help.
About that. We got a new problem.
The bunker's generators
have a doomsday scenario fail-safe.
Assuming a catastrophic attack,
they're tamper-proof so no one
can stop them from turning back on.
Wait, why would you want to stop them?
The methane.
The power coming back on will spark it.
If we don't get the air-vents
back online first somehow...
You guys are sitting
underneath a four-story bomb.
How long do we have
before the generator kicks back on?
And blow you up?
Twelve minutes. But don't worry.
Too late.
We have a plan.
Careful.
We gotta be getting close.
Think we're there, D.
Talk to me, Curtis.
I'm trying to hack the city grid to
re-route power to the ventilation system.
Can you blow the gas
before the generators come back online?
Well, we'll know if we hear
an earth-shattering ka-boom
beneath our feet.
- Slow down. Slow down.
- We don't have time to slow down.
And we don't have time
for you to bleed to death, either.
It's a good point. It's good. It's...
Oliver! Oh, my God. Oliver?
Oliver? Oliver?
Hey, Curtis!
Oliver's down, we need your help!
Oliver.
Hang on. Coming to you.
This looks like
the Death Star interrogation droid.
I loaded it with 20 CC's of adrenaline.
You're gonna have to inject that into...
Whoa.
- I'm okay!
- You're nowhere close.
But we gave you enough adrenaline
to get us out of here.
Good.
Okay. All right.
Okay. Yeah.
Are you really gonna climb down there?
Somebody has to meet them halfway.
Nice jump, Digg.
John!
Are you okay?
I'm good.
We are running out of time.
I've almost got
the ventilation systems back up.
Oliver!
- Yeah!
- Hey!
Hey, you guys all right?
No, not really.
John!
You okay?
Stay there. We'll figure something out.
John, we don't have time.
Look, do you have enough cable
to meet us halfway?
- Yes.
- That's optimistic.
We only have 30 feet.
It's not helping. Throw him the line.
This is crazy.
You don't hear me arguing, do you?
All right. Hang on, tight.
I always appreciated you
doing the salmon ladder,
but never as much as in this moment.
It's all right. It's all right.
I've got about five feet of slack.
- I can make it.
- Oliver, if you don't...
I will.
You have to let me go.
You have to let me go! You have to go!
Curtis, cut the vents!
- Now he tells me?
- Do it!
Sorry, Felicity.
I know you hate it
when I don't listen to you.
Rene, pull us up.
Hey, Lyla.
Thanks for letting us come here.
See? A. R.G.U.S.
isn't always used for evil.
I know. You're right.
I should have trusted you. I do trust you.
We just work
in morally gray areas, Lyla, and I...
I let that cloud my perspective a bit.
Or a lot.
I'm sorry.
I promise, we will get through this.
Hey. Any word on Oliver?
Lyla's checking now.
Gotta say, it's good to see you up
and walking again.
Yeah. Thank Curtis.
He's the miracle worker.
It's just a temporary fix. I have to run
a more comprehensive diagnostics.
You guys are gonna have to explain to me
how all this works one day.
You really don't want him to do that.
Nerd-a-palooza.
Oliver just got out of surgery.
- He's going to be fine.
- Can we see him?
Actually, he asked to see you.
Ooh!
We were all thinking it.
Would it help if I didn't ask for lessons
on a particular piece of equipment?
I know you're probably a little upset
about what I said last night still...
I'm not mad.
- You were right.
- So were you.
You know, we never really did talk about
anything and...
I walked.
That was wrong.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
I'm not saying never about the talk.
I just...
Maybe not quite yet.
I'm not ready yet.
I'm not going anywhere.
Okay.
- Hey.
- You're walking.
- I am.
More importantly, you're living.
You really gave us a scare back there.
Well, I'd figured you'd be used to seeing
me close to death by now.
Never gonna get used to it. Ever.
But, speaking of being close to death,
I said a few things back there.
I really, really appreciate what you said.
Any of it stick?
Hopefully.
I'm sorry.
- For what?
- For being a hypocrite.
You were right.
I was starting to become like you.
And not in the heroic, you know,
honorable, muscular way.
It's just, after I lost Billy,
I was willing to do whatever to get Chase.
It drove me to work with Helix
and I was willing to break any rule,
do anything to get payback and,
you know, what I'm trying to say is
I think I got the tiniest taste
of what you've been through.
Tiniest, and I get it now.
I understand
why you lied to me about William.
Why you had to.
I get it.
And for the extent that I judged you
and I did judge you, I am sorry.
You know, you said you didn't know
what kind of person you are.
I think you should figure that out.
William.
My name is Matthew.
But it used to be William, right?
Before you and your mom left Central City?
You know my mom?
Actually, I knew your father.
And he knew mine.
English - SDH