PREVIOUSLY ON "ARROW"...
THERE WAS A FIRE
IN THE APARTMENT.
YOUR MOM WAS
IN THERE.
IT WASN'T THE FIRE
THAT KILLED HER.
YOUR MISSION IS
ABOUT REVENGE.
JOHN: DANTE'S A PERSON.
LYLA: HE IS THE FINANCIER
BEHIND DOZENS
OF TERRORIST ATTACKS.
DEPUTY DIRECTOR BELL.
WE'RE IN THE PROCESS
OF REINSTATING
THE GHOST INITIATIVE.
RESTORING THE PROGRAM
IS THE ONLY WAY WE
CAN GET DANTE
WITHOUT A.R.G.U.S.
OVERSIGHT.
WE WERE ABLE TO BACKTRACE
THE NUMBER DIAZ CALLED.
IT BELONGS TO DANTE'S
CONTACT VIRGIL.
BLACKSTAR'S OUR ONLY LEAD
ON FINDING THOSE BOMBS.
[DART WHOOSHES]
FELICITY'S STILL
ALIVE.
[GRUNTING]
YOU'RE NOT
GONNA SHOOT ME.
MY NAME IS MIA SMOAK.
I'M FELICITY'S DAUGHTER
AND YOUR SISTER.
[RAPID HEARTBEAT]
[BABY CRYING]
I'M COMING, I'M COMING!
[CRYING CONTINUES]
WHERE ARE YOU?
I CAN'T FIND YOU!
OH, OH, AAH!
I'LL ALWAYS FIND YOU...
BOTH OF YOU.
YOU STAY AWAY FROM ME.
YOU STAY AWAY
FROM ME AND MY FAMILY!
[GASPS]
YOU CAN'T PROTECT
YOUR BABY.
[GASPS]
WILLIAM, IT'S YOUR DAD AGAIN,
AND I DON'T KNOW IF YOU'RE
GETTING MY MESSAGES, BUDDY,
BECAUSE YOU'RE NOT
RETURNING MY CALLS.
I TRIED...I TRIED
CALLING THE HOUSE.
LOOK. I KNOW THAT I'M NOT
YOUR GRANDPARENTS' FAVORITE,
BUT FELICITY AND I,
WE JUST WANT TO KNOW
HOW YOU'RE SETTLING IN,
AND WE WOULD LOVE
TO HEAR YOUR VOICE
BECAUSE WE REALLY MISS Y...
VOICE: THE MAILBOX
IS NOW FULL. GOOD-BYE.
HE'S STILL NOT
ANSWERING YOUR CALLS.
NO.
ZOE FROZE ME OUT
WHEN I FIRST LOST CUSTODY.
DON'T WORRY.
HE'LL COME AROUND.
YOU JUST GOT TO
BE PATIENT.
PATIENCE IS NOT REALLY
MY THING, RENE,
BUT THANK YOU.
ANY WORD ON WHEN DINAH
IS COMING BACK?
WELL, SHE'S ALREADY
TRIED TO CHECK HERSELF
OUT THE HOSPITAL
A COUPLE OF TIMES.
PATIENCE IS ALSO NOT
REALLY HER THING.
-WORKING A NEW CASE?
-NOT EXACTLY.
IT'S FOR YOUR
SISTER. YEAH.
THAT'S STILL WEIRD
TO SAY OUT LOUD.
OK, RENE, LOOK.
OUR TEAM HAS BEEN DEPUTIZED
TO WORK WITH THE SCPD.
SHE HASN'T BEEN.
SHE SHOULDN'T BE OUT THERE
AS A VIGILANTE,
AND I WOULD ACTUALLY
REALLY APPRECIATE
IF YOU DIDN'T
ENCOURAGE HER.
DO YOU REALLY THINK
I COULD STOP HER?
STUBBORNNESS RUNS
IN THE FAMILY.
BESIDES,
THIS IS PERSONAL.
WHY?
THIS IS THE BULLET
THAT KILLED HER MOTHER.
HER MOTHER
WAS MURDERED?
-SHE DIDN'T TELL YOU?
-NO.
LOOK. I'M NOT TRYING TO GET IN
THE MIDDLE OF ANY FAMILY DRAMA.
TOO LATE.
HER MOTHER WAS MURDERED
OVER A YEAR AGO.
-OHH.
-EMIKO'S BEEN TRYING TO FIND
THE KILLER
EVER SINCE,
BUT ALL SHE'S FOUND
WERE DEAD ENDS.
THIS BULLET IS HER
ONLY LEGIT LEAD.
DOES SHE HAVE ANY REASON
TO BLAME MY FAMILY
FOR HER MOTHER'S DEATH?
Y'ALL DID BECOME
STARLING CITY ROYALTY
WHILE SHE AND HER MOM
WERE LEFT TO STRUGGLE
IN THE GLADES.
ALL I'M SAYING IS
THERE'S A DIFFERENCE
BETWEEN TRUST
AND TRUST FUND.
-SHE TRUSTS YOU?
-THAT'S BECAUSE I HAD TO PROVE
TO HER
THAT SHE COULD.
OK. I'LL PROVE IT, TOO.
JUST LIKE
MY FATHER TAUGHT ME.
HE SHOULD HAVE TAUGHT YOU
HOW TO AIM, BOY.
YOU'D BE LUCKY
TO BREAK SKIN.
DO YOU TWO
EVER STOP TALKING?
OOPS.
JOHN: THAT IS ENOUGH.
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO BE TRAINING,
NOT TRYING TO
KILL EACH OTHER.
CUPID: AWW. WHY YOU
GOT TO RUIN ALL THE FUN?
THE OP IN CAIRO
WAS A BUST.
DANTE'S EMISSARY
VIRGIL MANAGED
TO EVADE US.
VIRGIL WAS
OUR ONLY CONTACT TO DANTE.
ALL THAT EFFORT
TO TRICK DIAZ INTO
GIVING UP THE NUMBER,
AND WE'RE BACK
TO SQUARE ONE.
NOT COMPLETELY.
WE STILL HAVE
THE RECORDS FROM
VIRGIL'S PHONE.
THAT COULD LEAD
US TO DANTE.
MEANTIME, DANTE IS
WREAKING HAVOC,
FINANCING TERRORISTS
ALL OVER THE WORLD.
I WAS HOPING TO BE DONE
WITH THIS GROUP BY NOW.
I KNOW.
THE ONLY THING ANYONE
KNOWS ABOUT THIS OPERATION
IS THAT DIAZ IS A PART
OF THE GHOST INITIATIVE,
BUT THE LONGER THIS
TAKES, THE MORE LIKELY
A.R.G.U.S. BRASS IS TO
FIND OUT THE REAL REASON
FOR THE GHOST INITIATIVE
IS TO GO AFTER DANTE.
IT'S TIME TO TELL
OLIVER AND FELICITY.
OUR POSITION NOW IS
RISKIER THAN EVER.
THE LESS SECRETS WE HAVE,
THE BETTER.
MY SISTER?
NO. THAT'S NOT POSSIBLE.
I WISH IT WASN'T,
BUT HERE I AM.
NOW, GET THE DAMN GUN
OFF ME.
ZOE: HE WILL WHEN
YOU STOP LYING.
IT JUST DOESN'T
MAKE ANY SENSE.
WE ALL KNEW
OLIVER
AND FELICITY.
THEY NEVER HAD
A DAUGHTER.
GUESS YOU DIDN'T KNOW
THEM AS WELL AS YOU THINK.
IS THIS TRUE?
IS SHE THEIR KID?
HEY. WHOA. LET HIM GO.
HE DOESN'T KNOW WHO
MY PARENTS ARE.
I NEVER TOLD HIM.
SHE'S TELLING
THE TRUTH.
LOOK, MIA,
MIA, MY DAD TOLD ME
TO KEEP A WATCH ON YOU
AND KEEP YOU SAFE,
SO I KNOW WHO
YOUR FATHER IS.
YOUR DAD
KNEW, TOO?
MIA: WHO THE HELL
IS YOUR DAD?
JOHN DIGGLE IS
MY ADOPTIVE FATHER.
-A VIGILANTE.
-MIA...
SO YOU'VE BEEN
LYING TO ME
THIS ENTIRE TIME?
WELL, NOW THAT WE'RE
ALL ACQUAINTED,
WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU
DOING DOWN HERE?
SHE'S LOOKING
FOR FELICITY,
WHO'S APPARENTLY NOT DEAD.
HOW DO YOU KNOW?
BECAUSE SHE'S DONE
THIS BEFORE.
SHE'S JUST HIDING
SOMEWHERE, BEING
PARANOID LIKE ALWAYS.
MIA: FIGURED IT
MIGHT BE HERE THIS TIME.
DINAH: SO YOU'RE JUST
GOING ON A HUNCH, HUH?
NO. I AM GOING
ON AN ENTIRE LIFETIME
OF DEALING WITH HER.
DID YOU EVEN BOTHER
CHECKING INTO HER MURDER?
OF COURSE WE DID.
SHE DIED
IN AN EXPLOSION.
DID YOU ACTUALLY SEE A BODY?
WILLIAM: OK.
SO WHERE DO WE START?
YEAH. I'M NOT LOOKING
FOR ANY KIND OF
FAMILY REUNION HERE, BRO.
OH, I'M SORRY, SIS,
BUT I HAVE COME TOO FAR
TO GET SIDELINED NOW,
SO WE'RE HELPING EACH OTHER
WHETHER YOU WANT TO
OR NOT.
THE GHOST INITIATIVE SOUNDS
A LOT LIKE TASK FORCE X.
DIDN'T LYLA SHELVE
THAT YEARS AGO?
SHE DID,
BUT THERE'S NOW
A MORE IMMEDIATE,
MORE DANGEROUS TARGET
THAT THE BRASS
AT A.R.G.U.S.,
EVEN ABOVE LYLA,
IS PREVENTING US
FROM PURSUING.
WE'RE USING
THE GHOST INITIATIVE
TO GO AFTER
THIS TARGET
WITHOUT THEIR
OVERSIGHT.
WELL, I LOVE
A SPONTANEOUS OTA MOMENT
AS MUCH
AS THE NEXT PERSON,
BUT YOU DIDN'T REALLY
COME HERE TO TELL US
ABOUT RESURRECTING
AN OLD A.R.G.U.S.
DEFUNCT PROGRAM, DID YOU?
IT'S NOT
ABOUT THE PROGRAM.
IT'S ABOUT
WHO'S IN IT.
-RICARDO DIAZ.
-OHH.
YOU HAVE TO BE JOKING.
YOU'RE WORKING WITH THE MAN
WHO THREATENED
AND TRIED TO KILL
MY ENTIRE FAMILY?
I THINK IT'S IMPORTANT
THAT WE HEAR WHAT
JOHN HAS TO SAY.
WORKING WITH THIS MONSTER
IS A SMALL PRICE TO PAY
FOR BRINGING DOWN
A MUCH LARGER THREAT.
DIAZ WAS THE ONLY ONE
WE COULD USE TO GET
CLOSE TO THIS GUY,
AND I PROMISE YOU
HE IS A MILLION
TIMES WORSE.
SO DIAZ IS JUST WALKING
AROUND FREE RIGHT NOW
IN EXCHANGE FOR INTEL?
HE'S NOT FREE, FELICITY.
HE HAS A BOMB IN HIS HEAD.
IF HE MAKES ONE MISSTEP...
WE ARE TAKING
EVERY PRECAUTION.
WELL, I UNDERSTAND
WHY CURTIS LEFT.
HEY.
YOU CAN'T REALLY BE
OK WITH THIS.
NO, BUT I...I TRUST JOHN,
AND I BELIEVE
THAT HE WOULD ONLY TAKE
A STEP LIKE THIS
IF HE HAD
NO OTHER CHOICE.
THERE WAS
NO OTHER CHOICE,
AND I HATE THAT
IT CAME TO THIS,
BUT LYLA AND I
BELIEVE THAT USING
THE GHOST INITIATIVE IS
THE BEST WAY TO TAKE
DOWN THIS THREAT.
YOU REALIZE THAT THIS IS
THE SECOND TIME YOU HAVE
PRIORITIZED YOUR JOB
OVER KEEPING
YOUR FRIENDS SAFE?
WORKING WITH A.R.G.U.S.
DOES KEEP YOU SAFE
BECAUSE IT MAKES
THE WORLD SAFE.
YOU CAN KEEP TELLING
YOURSELF THAT.
LYLA: MEET VIRGIL,
AN INTERMEDIARY
FOR THE TERRORIST
FINANCIER KNOWN
AS DANTE.
-DIAZ SHOULD BE FAMILIAR.
-NICE GUY.
JOHN: YOUR JOB IS TO MEET
WITH VIRGIL,
CONVINCE HIM THAT HE SHOULD
BE IN BUSINESS WITH YOU.
YOU GET THROUGH VIRGIL,
YOU GET A MEETING
WITH DANTE.
SO OUR FIRST MISSION
IS A MEETING?
THAT IS WAY
BELOW OUR PAY GRADE.
WAIT. WE'RE GETTING PAID?
IF WE CAN EVEN
GET THE MEETING.
I TRIED ONCE.
VIRGIL WOULDN'T
TAKE MY CALL.
JOHN: HE WOULDN'T
TAKE YOURS,
BUT HE'LL TAKE HIS.
DIAZ IS THE REASON
WE'VE BEEN ABLE
TO TRACK VIRGIL.
SO WHAT DO YOU SAY, DIAZ?
YOU WANT TO MAKE THAT CALL
FOR REAL THIS TIME?
I THOUGHT YOU'D
NEVER ASK.
OK. OPERATION
BLOW THE HEAD
OFF THE DRAGON
IS OFFICIALLY
A GO.
I OVERRODE
A.R.G.U.S.'S
SECURITY PROTOCOLS
AND ACCESSED THE BOMB
IN DIAZ'S BRAIN,
WHICH MEANS AS SOON
AS DIG'S GHOST INITIATIVE
MISSION IS OVER, ONE CLICK.
[SNAPS FINGERS]
BOOM!
THAT'S GREAT.
-HIGH SCORE ON CANDY CRUSH?
-I'M WORKING.
I'M SORRY. I DIDN'T
REALIZE THAT BEING
A FAKE LAWYER
WAS MORE INTERESTING
THAT GETTING REVENGE
ON THE BASTARD
WHO KILLED QUENTIN.
FINE. I'M LISTENING.
HAPPY?
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO
IS GET WITHIN
100 FEET OF DIAZ,
WHICH SHOULD BE EASY
FOR THE D.A.,
AND THEN JUST CLICK
THIS BUTTON RIGHT HERE
AND ACTIVATE
THE REMOTE DETONATOR.
♪ DA DA DA ♪
WON'T THAT SEND ME
STRAIGHT TO THE TOP
OF MOST LIKELY TO HAVE
KILLED DIAZ LIST?
HEH. WHAT DO YOU CARE?
YOU'VE BEEN TRYING
TO KILL DIAZ FOR MONTHS.
I MEAN, THE ONLY
REASON HE'S STILL ALIVE
IS BECAUSE WE NEEDED HIM
TO GET OLIVER OUT OF PRISON.
TRUE...
BUT SOME THINGS
HAVE CHANGED.
I MEAN, I'M KIND OF
GOOD AT THIS D.A. THING,
SO I'M NOT REALLY SURE
I'M READY TO GIVE
IT UP YET.
WELL, I'M NOT READY TO
GIVE UP ON GETTING DIAZ.
DIAZ IS IN A.R.G.U.S.
CUSTODY.
HE'S NOT RUNNING
AROUND FREE.
TRUST ME. I WOULD BE
THRILLED TO SEE
HIS HEAD EXPLODE,
BUT IS IT REALLY WORTH
THE CONSEQUENCES?
YES, IT IS WORTH
EVERY CONSEQUENCE.
I HAVE TO PROTECT
MY FAMILY.
BY FAMILY YOU MEAN
YOU, OLIVER,
AND YOUR BABY?
WHAT, ARE YOU
PSYCHIC NOW?
WELL, THERE'S NO WINE
OR CHAMPAGNE
AND NO CAFFEINE
ON THIS MISSION,
AND THAT...THAT IS
A PREGNANT LADY
AMOUNT OF CHOCOLATES
YOU JUST CONSUMED.
I ATE THAT MUCH
CHOCOLATE BEFORE
I WAS PREGNANT.
-NO ONE ELSE KNOWS.
-NOT EVEN OLIVER?
I HAVEN'T FOUND
THE RIGHT TIME
TO TELL HIM.
I'VE BEEN TRYING
TO TELL HIM,
SO I WOULD REALLY,
REALLY APPRECIATE IT
IF YOU WOULDN'T TELL...
ANYONE.
I WON'T.
I PROMISE.
REALLY SNAP
YOUR WRIST NEXT TIME.
GIVES IT JUST A BIT
MORE POWER.
HOW THE HELL DID YOU
GET IN HERE?
I HAVE SOMETHING
FOR YOU.
-OF COURSE RENE TOLD YOU.
-DON'T GET MAD AT RENE.
I JUST...
I WANT TO HELP.
I HAD FELICITY ANALYZE
THE COMPOSITION
OF THE BULLET.
-IT'S MADE FROM A...
-A RARE PROMETHIUM ALLOY,
THE KIND USED BY
A HANDFUL OF BLACK MARKET
WEAPONS MANUFACTURERS?
I'VE DONE MY HOMEWORK.
DO YOU KNOW IT WAS SHOT
WITH A CUSTOMIZED RIFLE?
SPECS ARE
ON THE DRIVE.
THANKS.
I CAN HELP YOU CATCH
WHO MADE IT.
THIS IS MY MISSION.
OK. MAYBE WE CAN DISCUSS
YOUR MOTHER.
RENE HAS
A BIG MOUTH.
I'M GLAD HE TOLD ME, OK?
I KNOW WHAT IT'S LIKE
TO LOSE A PARENT.
I DON'T WANT
YOUR SYMPATHY.
I WANT JUSTICE.
EXCEPT YOU'RE NOT
AUTHORIZED TO GET IT.
I AM.
WHY SHOULD I
TRUST YOU?
I UNDERSTAND
THAT MY PARENTS WEREN'T
EXACTLY THE BEST PEOPLE,
BUT...IF THEY TAUGHT
ME ONE THING,
IT'S THE VALUE
OF FAMILY,
WHICH IS WHAT
YOU AND I ARE,
SO IF SOMEONE'S HURT YOU,
YOU BETTER BELIEVE
THEY'VE HURT ME, TOO.
[TYPING]
I DON'T KNOW HOW WE'RE
GONNA USED THIS OLD STUFF
TO FIND FELICITY.
IT'S LIKE
A TECH TIME CAPSULE.
HERE GOES NOTHING.
[GENERATORS WHIRRING]
ZOE: WHOA.
AND WE HAVE LIFTOFF.
MIA: I THOUGHT YOU
HAD ARCHER.
WHY DO YOU NEED ALL
THIS OLD JUNK?
BECAUSE AS ADVANCED
AS ARCHER IS,
IT WAS DESIGNED
FOR THE GLADES.
THIS SYSTEM WAS
BUILT FOR STAR CITY.
SO WHO AM I LOOKING
FOR AGAIN?
UH, SOME GUY.
PAUL LOISEAU.
SCPD HAS HIM LISTED
AS THE ONLY EYEWITNESS
TO FELICITY'S MURDER.
I'M GUESSING SHE PAID HIM
TO SAY SHE WAS THERE.
SAYS THIS GUY
COMMITTED SUICIDE
ABOUT A WEEK AGO.
WAIT. THAT WAS RIGHT WHEN
WE STARTED LOOKING INTO
FELICITY'S DISAPPEARANCE.
WHAT ABOUT THE CORONER?
ANOTHER SUICIDE.
ZOE: STAR CITY'S BAD
BUT NOT THAT BAD.
SOMEONE'S TAKING
THESE PEOPLE OUT,
BUT WHY?
SO FELICITY UNCOVERS
A BOMB PLOT,
BUT BEFORE SHE
CAN TELL ANYBODY,
THE PARTY RESPONSIBLE
FAKES HER DEATH.
NOW THEY'RE TYING UP
LOOSE ENDS.
ROY: SO WHY NOT JUST KILL HER?
DINAH: BECAUSE THEY NEEDED HER.
YOU WERE THE LAST ONE
TO TALK TO FELICITY.
WHAT DID SHE SAY?
JUST THE USUAL
BULL ABOUT HOW
THE CITY'S NOT SAFE
AND SHE WANTED ME
TO GET OUT OF TOWN.
IT MIGHT NOT
HAVE BEEN BULL
THIS TIME.
YOU GUYS ARE JUST
JUNKIES LOOKING
FOR YOUR HERO FIX.
MY MOM IS THE ONLY
PERSON I CARE ABOUT,
AND I'M GONNA GO LOOK
FOR HER MYSELF
WITHOUT ANY OF YOU.
-HOLD ON. MIA...
-GET THE HELL OFF!
THAT GOES
FOR ALL OF YOU.
[LOCK BEEPS AND LATCHES]
THIS IS MY KIND
OF PLACE.
THIS USED TO BE
A TRIAD HANGOUT.
JOHN: EVERYONE, FOCUS.
THE OBJECTIVE IS TO FIND VIRGIL
AND GET HIM TO AGREE
TO YOUR DEAL.
WHERE IS VIRGIL?
MAN: AH, SPEAK OF THE DEVIL,
AND HE SHALL APPEAR.
RICARDO DIAZ,
AND HERE I THOUGHT
THE ALMIGHTY DRAGON
WAS IN PRISON.
NO PRISON COULD HOLD ME.
YOU SHOULD KNOW THAT.
JOHN: NO BODYGUARDS.
THAT'S A GOOD SIGN.
NOW ALL YOU HAVE TO DO
IS CONVINCE HIM.
VIRGIL: YOU KNOW, MR. DIAZ,
I WAS, UH...
I WAS HAPPY
TO GET YOUR CALL.
MY EMPLOYER WOULD LIKE
TO KNOW WHEN HE CAN
COLLECT ON YOUR DEBT.
THE LONGBOW HUNTERS
WERE NOT CHEAP.
WE HAVE
A PROPOSITION,
AND I THINK IT
WILL COVER MORE
THAN WHAT I OWE.
THAT'S INTRIGUING.
TOO BAD IT WASN'T MADE
IN GOOD FAITH, THOUGH.
[WEAPONS ARE DRAWN]
KILL THEM,
EXCEPT FOR MR. DIAZ.
VIRGIL: DANTE WILL DEAL
WITH HIM PERSONALLY TONIGHT.
[GRUNTING]
DON'T LET VIRGIL LEAVE!
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
UNH!
[MEN YELL]
GREAT. NOW WE OWE
HER ONE.
VIRGIL: MOVE!
NOWHERE TO RUN, VIRGIL!
TREACHERY EARNS
THE WORST PUNISHMENT,
RICARDO.
DANTE WILL MAKE SURE
YOU GET WHAT
YOU DESERVE.
HA HA HA!
ARE THE HANDCUFFS
REALLY NECESSARY?
LYLA: UNTIL YOU TELL US
WHICH ONE OF YOU TIPPED
OFF VIRGIL.
CUPID: HEY.
WE WERE CAUGHT IN
THE SAME AMBUSH.
IN CASE YOU MISSED
THE SHOW OUT THERE,
WE ALMOST DIED.
KANE: WELL,
SOME OF US DID.
YOU GOT SOMETHING
YOU WANT TO SAY TO ME?
MAYBE "DANTE
WILL DEAL WITH
HIM PERSONALLY"
WAS ACTUALLY CODE
FOR "GET DIAZ OUT
BEFORE
THE BLOODBATH."
-THE PHONE CALL TO VIRGIL.
-MM-HMM.
DIAZ MUST HAVE WARNED
HIM SOMEHOW.
I'LL HAVE THE ANALYSTS
LOOK INTO ENCODED PHRASES.
DIAZ: LADY, YOU AIN'T
GONNA FIND ANYTHING
BECAUSE I WASN'T THE ONE
WHO WARNED THEM.
SURE YOU DIDN'T.
YOU DIDN'T REALLY
THINK THIS ONE THROUGH.
EVEN IF YOU AND VIRGIL
HAD RIDDEN OFF
INTO THE SUNSET,
MOMMY AND DADDY WOULDN'T
HAVE LET YOU GET VERY FAR.
HE DIDN'T THINK WE
WOULD REALLY DO IT.
YOU GUYS, YOU HAVE NO IDEA
WHO YOU'RE MESSING WITH.
LYLA: YOU'RE AFRAID.
YOU'D RATHER HAVE A BOMB
EXPLODE IN YOUR HEAD
THAN RISK DANTE
FINDING OUT THAT
YOU BETRAYED HIM.
ONCE DANTE FIGURES
ALL OF THIS OUT...
AND HE WILL...
YOU ALL ARE GONNA BE
WISHING FOR THE MERCY
OF A QUICK DEATH.
COMPUTER: LAUREL LANCE
ENTERING QUEEN RESIDENCE.
NO MORE SAD CHOCOLATES.
I GOT YOU
A ROASTED TURKEY SANDWICH.
IT'S NOT DELI MEAT.
I DOUBLE-CHECKED.
ALSO, I GOT YOU SOME
FRUIT AND VEGGIES.
ARE YOU ON ANY
PRENATAL VITAMINS?
ANY MAC AND CHEESE
IN THERE? NO?
CLEARLY, YOU'RE HAVING
SOME KIND OF WEIRD
PREGNANCY CRISIS,
AND KILLING
RICARDO DIAZ IS NOT
GOING TO SOLVE IT.
FOCUSING ON KILLING
THE MANIAC WHO WANTS
TO KILL ME AND MY FAMILY
MIGHT BE A LITTLE BIT
MORE HELPFUL THAN...
EATING THAT BANANA.
ONE, YOU NEED
THE POTASSIUM.
TWO, YES,
YOU'RE RIGHT.
YOUR HUSBAND'S JOB
IS TO BE THE ENEMY
OF MONSTERS,
AND THOSE MONSTERS
ARE GOING TO TARGET
YOU AND YOUR FAMILY
LIKE THEY ALWAYS HAVE.
THANK YOU. THAT IS
INCREDIBLY REASSURING.
YOU ARE MORE
THAN CAPABLE
OF PROTECTING YOURSELF
AND YOUR FAMILY.
I MEAN, YOU BUILT
THIS INSANE, CRAZY
SECURITY SYSTEM.
WHICH DIDN'T WORK THE LAST
TIME SOMEBODY TARGETED US.
-SO? YOU'LL FIX IT.
-YEAH. OK.
IN HALF A DAY, YOU HACKED
INTO RICARDO DIAZ'S BRAIN.
I DON'T KNOW
IF YOU'VE NOTICED,
BUT YOU'RE KIND OF
A BADASS.
WHAT IF IT'S
NOT ENOUGH?
LOOK.
THERE WILL ALWAYS
BE ANOTHER DIAZ.
-OH.
-YOU JUST HAVE TO HAVE FAITH
THAT YOU CAN HANDLE
THE NEXT ONE
AND THE ONE AFTER THAT
AND THE ONE AFTER THAT.
YOU KNOW, THIS
BABY'S REALLY LUCKY
TO HAVE YOU.
I KNOW IT'S SCARY,
BUT I PROMISE
YOU'VE GOT THIS,
AND IF YOU WANT TO
KILL RICARDO DIAZ,
I AM NOT GONNA
STAND IN YOUR WAY,
BUT DON'T DO IT
OUT OF FEAR
BECAUSE YOU HAVE
NOTHING TO BE
AFRAID OF.
WE JUST FINISHED
THE ANALYSIS
OF THE PHONE CALL
BETWEEN DIAZ
AND VIRGIL.
NO OBVIOUS CIPHERS
OR PATTERNS.
OK. WELL, IF DIAZ
WAS TELLING THE TRUTH,
THEN VIRGIL MUST HAVE
BEEN TIPPED OFF
BY SOMEONE ELSE.
PROBABLY THE SAME
SOMEONE WHO'S BEEN
BLOCKING US IN A.R.G.U.S.,
AND NOW THEY KNOW
WE'RE USING
THE GHOST INITIATIVE
TO GO AFTER DANTE.
WE NEED TO CATCH HIM
BEFORE THEY SHUT
US DOWN COMPLETELY.
ANY LUCK FIGURING OUT
HIS NEXT MOVE?
WELL, WE DID MANAGE
TO FIND THIS.
IT'S AN ITALIAN
FLORIN COIN
CIRCA 1300S.
WOULDN'T HAVE PEGGED
VIRGIL AS A COIN COLLECTOR.
HE WASN'T.
IT'S A FAKE.
TURNS OUT THERE'S
A MICROCHIP
HIDDEN INSIDE.
WELL, THAT SOUNDS
PROMISING.
UNFORTUNATELY, THE DATA'S
VERY HEAVILY ENCRYPTED.
I DON'T REALLY
TRUST GIVING IT TO
AN A.R.G.U.S. ANALYST,
BUT CURTIS DID LEAVE
US HIS DECRYPTION
ALGORITHM.
CONSIDERATE OF HIM.
IT'S GONNA TAKE
A WHILE.
WELL, HOPEFULLY,
NOT TOO LONG.
IF DANTE'S IN TOWN, IT MUST
BE FOR SOMETHING BIG.
UM, THE ALGORITHM
YOU WROTE TO FIND
THE WEAPON
IS LAGGING
A LITTLE BIT.
DO YOU...MIND
IF I TAKE A LOOK?
THE ALGORITHM'S FINE.
OK.
DO YOU HAVE TO
STAND RIGHT THERE?
RENE: HEY. SORRY I'M LATE.
I HAD TO HELP ZOE
WITH HER TEST.
GEOMETRY'S A BITCH.
-HOW WE LOOKING?
-FANTASTIC.
THE WEIGHT ON THESE
FEELS A LITTLE STRANGE.
DID YOU MAKE THESE
YOURSELF OR...
-NO.
-I'M JUST ASKING BECAUSE
WHEN I STARTED OUT,
I MADE MOST
OF MY OWN ARROWS,
AND I COULD SHOW YOU
A TRICK OR TWO
IF YOU WANT.
WHAT I WANT IS FOR YOU
TO NOT TOUCH MY THINGS.
[COMPUTER CHIMES]
RENE: AND THAT'S A HIT! OK.
ANDREW THORNTON.
SPECIALIZES
IN PROMETHIUM-BASED
CUSTOMIZED WEAPONRY.
THAT SOUNDS LIKE OUR GUY.
YEAH. NOW WE JUST
HAVE TO FIND HIM.
ACCORDING TO THAT
ONLINE CHATTER
RIGHT THERE,
HE'S DOING A DEAL
TONIGHT
AT AN INDUSTRIAL PLANT
IN PENNYTOWN.
-HMM.
-SO WHAT'S THE PLAN?
RENE'S GONNA ROLL WITH ME,
AND YOU NEED TO STAY HERE.
NO WAY. I'M NOT
STAYING BEHIND.
YOU DON'T HAVE
A BADGE, OK?
I'M SORRY,
BUT I PROMISE YOU
WE WILL TAKE CARE
OF THIS.
LET'S GO, RENE.
GENTLEMEN, WHO'S READY
TO DO SOME BUSINESS?
BEHOLD MY MASTERPIECE.
FULLY CUSTOMIZABLE
TO YOUR SPECIFICATIONS.
[ARROW WHOOSHES]
-UNH!
-UGH!
OLIVER:
I'LL HANDLE THORNTON!
COPY THAT.
UGH!
THORNTON'S MINE.
RENE: HEY! WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU DOING?
TAKING BACK MY MISSION!
THERE'S TWO OF YOU NOW?!
YOU'RE GONNA TELL ME
EVERYTHING YOU KNOW
ABOUT THE MURDER
OF KAZUMI ADACHI!
ANDREW THORNTON,
UP AGAINST THE WALL!
BY THE AUTHORITY
OF THE SCPD, I AM
PLACING YOU UNDER ARREST.
YOU HAVE THE RIGHT
TO REMAIN SILENT.
WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU DOING?
I'M TAKING HIM IN
FOR QUESTIONING.
NO. THIS IS MY MISSION.
I NEED TO QUESTION
HIM MY WAY!
YOU'D BE BREAKING THE LAW,
WHICH YOU'RE
ALREADY DOING!
THERE'S A RIGHT WAY
AND A WRONG WAY TO DO THIS.
THE ONLY THING
I'VE DONE WRONG
IS THINK THAT I COULD
EVER TRUST YOU.
[GROANS]
HEY. THORNTON'S READY
TO BE QUESTIONED.
THOUGHT YOU'D BE
HAPPIER ABOUT THAT.
YEAH. SORRY. I JUST...
WITH EMIKO.
I NEED TO MAKE HER
UNDERSTAND WE'RE
ON THE SAME SIDE.
I THINK THE PROBLEM
IS YOU THINKING
YOU CAN MAKE
HER DO ANYTHING.
YEAH. I'VE BEEN DOING
THIS A LONG TIME.
SHE'S NEW,
SHE'S UNSANCTIONED,
AND I'M TRYING TO
HELP HER.
BUT SHE DIDN'T ASK
FOR YOUR HELP.
IMAGINE HOW YOU
WOULD FEEL
IF, WHEN YOU FIRST
STARTED YOUR QUEST,
SOMEONE HAD
BASICALLY RIPPED
YOUR FATHER'S LIST
OUT OF YOUR HAND
AND TAKEN OVER
YOUR MISSION.
[SIGHS]
I SEE YOUR POINT.
EMIKO DOESN'T NEED
ANYBODY TELLING HER
WHAT TO DO
OR HOW TO DO IT,
AND SHE DEFINITELY
DOESN'T NEED
ANYONE'S PROTECTION.
YOU SEE THAT MOVE
SHE DID WITH THE BOW
AND SWITCHED HANDS?
YEAH. IT'S IMPRESSIVE.
RIDICULOUS.
JUST BE HER BROTHER
IF YOU WANT HER
TO BE IN YOUR LIFE
AND TO TRUST YOU.
JUST...
JUST BE HER BROTHER.
WILLIAM: HEY!
IT'S JUST ME...
YOUR BROTHER, APPARENTLY.
WHAT, YOU THINK
JUST BECAUSE
WE'RE RELATED
I'M NOT GONNA KICK
YOUR ASS OUT OF HERE?
THAT WAS THE HOPE, YEAH.
IF YOU'RE HERE TO
CONVINCE ME TO JOIN
YOUR LITTLE MERRY
BAND OF HEROES,
SAVE YOUR BREATH.
ACTUALLY, I WAS JUST
HOPING THAT WE COULD
COMMISERATE ABOUT HOW MUCH
OUR PARENTS SUCK.
I NEVER HAD ANYONE TO DO
THAT WITH BEFORE.
WHAT DO YOU HAVE
AGAINST OUR PARENTS?
SEEMS LIKE YOU
CAME OUT ALL RIGHT.
YOU'RE SUPER-RICH.
WELL, LET'S SEE.
OLIVER, BEING MY DAD,
GOT MY MOM KILLED.
THEN HE AND FELICITY
PROMISED TO STAY
IN MY LIFE
AFTER MY GRANDPARENTS
TOOK CUSTODY,
AND THEN I NEVER HEARD
FROM THEM AGAIN,
AND MY WHOLE JUSTIFICATION
FOR IT, YOU KNOW,
THAT IT'S HARD
FOR PUBLICLY RECOGNIZED
VIGILANTES TO RAISE CHILDREN,
SORT OF WENT OUT THE WINDOW
WHEN I FOUND OUT
THEY ACTUALLY HAD
ANOTHER KID,
WHICH MEANS THAT THEY
JUST DIDN'T WANT ME.
BEING THE KID THEY WANTED
WASN'T SO GREAT EITHER.
IF YOU HATE FELICITY
SO MUCH,
WHY ARE YOU WASTING
ALL THIS TIME TRYING TO
FIND OUT WHERE SHE IS?
-BECAUSE OF THIS.
-A ROCK?
FELICITY GAVE IT TO ME
WHEN I WAS A KID,
AND IT'S HOW SHE SENT OUT
HER DISTRESS SIGNAL...
NOW NEARLY
TWO DECADES LATER.
AND YOU HELD ONTO IT
ALL THIS TIME.
IT'S ACTUALLY
REALLY SAD.
THANKS.
YOU KNOW, PARENTS
AREN'T PERFECT.
THEY LOVE US
THE BEST WAY THEY CAN.
AHH. MAYBE I WAS JUST
TRYING TO DO THE SAME.
MY WHOLE LIFE,
MY MOM TOLD ME THAT
OUR DAD WAS A HERO,
BUT EVERYTHING
IN THIS CITY SAYS
THE OPPOSITE,
THAT ALL OF OUR PROBLEMS
TODAY ARE BECAUSE OF HIM
AND THE OTHER
VIGILANTES.
YOU KNEW HIM
BACK THEN.
WAS HE A HERO?
YEAH, HE REALLY WAS,
AND, YOU KNOW,
I'M STARTING TO THINK
THAT THIS ROCK WAS
SUPPOSED TO LEAD ME TO YOU.
FAMILY WAS ALWAYS
THE MOST IMPORTANT
THING TO MY...
OUR PARENTS.
DAMN IT, YOU ARE HERE
TO JUST TALK ME
INTO JOINING YOU.
WELL, DID IT WORK?
WE HAVE A LEAD
ON DANTE'S LOCATION.
-WHAT'S WRONG?
-I GOT A CALL FROM THE PENTAGON.
THEY WANT ME IN FRONT
OF THE JOINT CHIEFS
TOMORROW.
THEY'RE GOING TO ASK
FOR MY RESIGNATION.
LYLA, I'M SO SORRY.
I SHOULD HAVE NEVER
FORCED YOUR HAND WITH
THE GHOST INITIATIVE.
I BACKED THAT PLAY
WITH OPEN EYES, JOHNNY,
AND I STAND BY IT NOW.
STILL, I NEVER THOUGHT
IT WOULD MEAN YOU
LOSING YOUR JOB.
THEN WE BETTER
MAKE IT COUNT.
DANTE IS WITHIN OUR GRASP,
AND WE MAY NOT HAVE
ANOTHER CHANCE.
NOW TELL ME
ABOUT THAT LEAD.
WELL, CURTIS' ALGORITHM
ABSOLUTELY WORKED.
ACCORDING TO THE
MICROCHIP IN THE COIN,
VIRGIL WAS USING IT
AS SOME SORT
OF STORAGE DEVICE
FOR ALL KINDS
OF DATA,
INCLUDING A FORGED
DIPLOMATIC CREDENTIAL
FROM THE QURACI EMBASSY.
THERE'S A DELEGATION
THERE TONIGHT
WITH A VERY INTERESTING
GUEST OF HONOR...
PRINCESS NOOR HARJAVTI.
RUMOR HAS IT
PRINCESS NOOR IS PLANNING
A REVOLUTION.
SO SHE NEEDS DANTE'S
MONEY TO FUND
HER PALACE COUP,
WHICH MAY BE
THE REASON WHY
HE'S IN TOWN...
TO MAKE
THE DEAL.
WE NEED TO GET
INTO THE EMBASSY
AND STOP THAT DEAL FROM
HAPPENING AND NAB DANTE.
COPY THAT.
ONLY ONE PROBLEM.
WE HAVE NO IDEA
HOW DANTE LOOKS.
-WE KNOW SOMEBODY WHO DOES.
-DIAZ.
WHICH MEANS WE HAVE TO PUT
HIM BACK IN THE FIELD.
THAT'S NOT OUR
BIGGEST PROBLEM.
THE GHOST INITIATIVE
IS BLOWN,
AND WE CAN'T RELY
ON ANYONE AT A.R.G.U.S.,
AND WE CANNOT
GO IN THERE
WITHOUT BACKUP.
MAYBE WE DON'T HAVE TO.
OLIVER: JUST GOT
OFF THE PHONE WITH JOHN.
HE AND LYLA ARE
GEARING UP
FOR A GHOST INITIATIVE OP.
THEY ASKED ME TO BE
IN THE FIELD.
IN THE FIELD
WITH WHOM EXACTLY?
DIAZ?
I TOLD JOHN IT WAS
YOUR DECISION.
WHATEVER YOU DECIDE
AFTER THE MISSION,
I WILL BACK ANY MOVE
THAT YOU WANT TO
MAKE AGAINST DIAZ.
OH, YOU DON'T
MEAN THAT.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I KNOW WHY YOU'VE
BEEN ACTING SO STRANGE
LATELY, RIGHT?
-YOU DO?
-YEAH.
I WAS GONNA TELL YOU.
THERE'S JUST BEEN
SO MUCH GOING ON. I...
YOU'RE PLANNING
TO KILL DIAZ.
YEAH. UH, SO I'M
GUESSING THERE IS
A SPEECH COMING.
FELICITY, I THINK
THERE'S A BETTER WAY.
I...I THINK THAT,
BUT THAT'S MY CHOICE.
I HAVE NO RIGHT
WHATSOEVER
TO MAKE YOURS.
RIGHT AFTER I GOT
OUT OF SLABSIDE,
I...I DIDN'T REALIZE
OR TOTALLY UNDERSTAND
THE...THE PAIN THAT
YOU WERE DEALING WITH.
I JUST WANT YOU
TO GET CLOSURE
BECAUSE I WANT US
TO BE ABLE TO
MOVE FORWARD.
I HOPE YOU CHANGE
YOUR MIND,
BUT IF YOU DON'T,
I SWEAR I WILL NOT
STAND IN YOUR WAY.
-THANK YOU.
-I HAVE YOUR BACK
NO MATTER WHAT.
TELL JOHN YOU'RE
COMING ON THE MISSION.
AND SO AM I.
HARBINGER'S IN POSITION.
SITREP?
I COUNT 11, 12 GUARDS
IN THIS ROOM ALONE.
WE HAVE TO MOVE
ON DANTE AFTER THE MEET.
LYLA: AGREED. YOU COPY
THAT, DIAZ?
SURE THING, BOSS.
CAN'T WAIT FOR YOU
TO MEET DANTE.
LYLA: JOKE ALL YOU WANT.
JUST REMEMBER,
WE'RE ONLY KEEPING YOU ALIVE
SO YOU CAN I.D. DANTE.
AFTER THAT,
ALL BETS ARE OFF.
OVERWATCH,
WHAT'S YOUR STATUS?
THE FEED IS LIVE, BUT 5
OF THE CAMERAS ARE DOWN
IN THE SOUTHEAST CORRIDOR.
ONE GUESS AS TO WHY.
THAT'S WHERE WE'LL FIND
DANTE AND THE PRINCESS.
THEY DON'T WANT EYES
ON THE EXCHANGE.
HOLD ON. WHAT THE HELL
IS DIRECTOR BELL
DOING HERE?
SON OF A BITCH.
HE'S DANTE'S SOURCE.
LOOKS LIKE SOMEBODY
OWES ME AN APOLOGY.
THE PRINCESS IS HERE.
LYLA: EVERYONE HEAD
TO THE SOUTH CORRIDOR.
YOUR HIGHNESS.
PRINCESS NOOR,
AT LAST WE MEET.
LYLA:
THAT MUST BE HIM.
DIAZ, CAN YOU
CONFIRM? DIAZ?
HIS SIGNAL IS OFFLINE.
HIS LAST LOCATION WAS
THE AUXILIARY ROOM
TO YOUR RIGHT.
I'VE GOT IT.
STAY IN POSITION.
FORGIVE ME.
VIRGIL COULDN'T
MAKE IT.
I WASN'T EXPECTING
OTHER COMPANY.
BELL: NOT COMPANY.
MORE LIKE PROOF OF CONCEPT.
MR. BELL WORKS
FOR A.R.G.U.S.,
ONE OF THE MANY WE'VE
INSTALLED AT THE AGENCY
THAT NOW WORK FOR YOU.
MY GOD.
DIAZ MUST HAVE USED
A DEFIBRILLATOR TO
SHORT THE CHIP OUT.
THAT'S WHY WE LOST
HIS SIGNAL!
DANTE.
EXCUSE ME.
MR. DIAZ.
NO.
YOU OWE ME A DEBT.
THIS IS THE PAYMENT.
IT'S A SETUP.
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
PLEASE.
UNH!
FORGIVE ME, PRINCESS.
-YOU OK?
-YEAH.
DANTE'S HEADED
FOR THE SOUTH EXIT.
EVERYBODY MOVE IN.
WHAT ABOUT DIAZ?
DANTE'S THE OBJECTIVE. GO!
[ARROW IS PULLED
FROM QUIVER]
LEAVING SO SOON?
NAH.
DON'T MISS.
[EMPTY CHAMBER CLICKS]
FELICITY: HEY!
YOU DON'T GET TO
GO FREE.
HONEY, DIDN'T WE GO
THROUGH THIS ALREADY?
YOU DON'T HAVE
WHAT IT TAKES.
[CLICK]
I DO,
AND I'M NOT
SCARED OF YOU,
AND I AM STRONGER
THAN YOU ARE,
WHICH IS WHY
I'M NOT
GOING TO KILL YOU.
I THOUGHT DANTE
WAS THE OBJECTIVE.
HE IS THE OBJECTIVE,
JUST NOT THE PRIORITY.
NOT THIS TIME.
YOU MADE A BIG MISTAKE.
STAND DOWN!
THIS IS OVER.
FOR NOW.
HE'S GONE.
[PHONE RINGING]
JOHN: WELL, DIAZ WILL BE
TAKEN BACK TO SLABSIDE
FOR RENEGING ON HIS
SIDE OF THE DEAL.
THIS TIME,
HE'LL STAY HERE.
STILL NEED TO THINK
ABOUT DANTE.
HE'S NOT GONNA FORGET
WHAT HAPPENED TONIGHT.
FELICITY: I WON'T EITHER.
YOU COULD HAVE GONE AFTER
DANTE, BUT YOU CHOSE DIAZ.
LAST YEAR, I HAD
THE OPPORTUNITY
TO CATCH DIAZ,
AND I LET IT SLIP
THROUGH MY FINGERS.
I WASN'T GONNA MAKE
THE SAME MISTAKE TWICE.
WELL, WHAT ABOUT DANTE
BEING THE GREATER THREAT?
WHEN I KNEW THERE
WAS A CHOICE
BETWEEN CATCHING
DIAZ OR DANTE,
ALL I COULD THINK
ABOUT WAS
WHAT LETTING DIAZ
GO MEANT TO YOU
LAST TIME, FELICITY,
SO IN THAT MOMENT,
I DECIDED THAT
SOMETIMES THE BEST
CHOICE IS TO JUST
PROTECT YOUR FAMILY,
AND THAT'S EXACTLY
WHAT YOU TWO ARE.
[FOOTSTEPS]
I JUST GOT OFF THE PHONE
WITH THE PENTAGON.
WE'LL GIVE YOU
SOME PRIVACY.
OK.
AGENT BELL WILL BE GETTING
A HERO'S FUNERAL.
THE OFFICIAL STORY IS
HE WAS AT THE EMBASSY
ON A COVERT ASSIGNMENT
THAT WENT AWRY.
RIGHT. SO IT'S
A COVER-UP.
OK. WHAT ABOUT
THE GHOST INITIATIVE?
-IT'S BEING SUSPENDED.
-WELL, THAT'S SOME GOOD NEWS.
THAT'S ALL THE GOOD NEWS.
WE LOST DANTE,
AND I LOST MY LAST
CHANCE TO GET HIM.
YOU DIDN'T LOSE
YOUR LAST CHANCE.
I'LL BE THE ONE
TO RESIGN.
LOOK. WE WILL TELL
THEM THAT I TOOK OUT
THE GHOST INITIATIVE
WITHOUT YOUR CONSENT
AND WITHOUT YOUR
KNOWLEDGE.
NO. THIS IS
MY RESPONSIBILITY.
LYLA, LISTEN
TO ME.
WE HAVE NO IDEA
HOW FAR THIS
CONSPIRACY GOES.
IF YOU STEP DOWN
AS DIRECTOR,
WE MAY NEVER
FIND OUT THE TRUTH.
BEING TERMINATED
FOR AN OPSEC VIOLATION
WILL RUIN YOUR CAREER.
BUT YOU'LL STILL
HAVE YOURS.
LET ME TAKE
THIS FALL
FOR THE FAMILY.
OLIVER: HEY.
GLAD YOU CALLED.
THOUGHT YOU WERE
DONE WITH ME.
YEAH, I DID, TOO,
UNTIL I GOT THAT.
YEAH.
THANKS FOR HAVING RENE
BRING THAT OVER.
I'M SURE IT'S NOT
SCPD PROTOCOL
TO RELEASE
INTERROGATION RECORDS.
-UH-UH.
-YEAH.
LEAST I COULD DO,
THOUGH.
IT IS YOUR MISSION.
IT'S...BEEN
HARD FOR ME
NOT SEEING YOU AS HIM.
HIM BEING OUR FATHER?
I JUST ASSUMED
I SHOULDN'T TRUST YOU.
THAT'S WHY I'VE BEEN
KEEPING SO MUCH
DISTANCE BETWEEN US.
THEN YOU GIVE ME
A CHANCE,
AND I, OF COURSE,
IMMEDIATELY OVERSTEP.
PRETTY MUCH.
I'VE LOST A LOT
IN MY LIFE.
PEOPLE,
YOU KNOW, BUT...
WITH YOU,
I LOST TIME,
SO YOU GAVE ME A CHANCE,
AND I IMMEDIATELY SAW IT
AS AN OPPORTUNITY TO
GET SOME OF IT BACK,
BUT THERE WAS
NO EXCUSE FOR THE WAY
THAT I BEHAVED
WHEN I WAS COMING
ABOARD YOUR MISSION.
I'M SORRY.
I DIDN'T REALIZE
OLIVER QUEEN DID APOLOGIES.
WELL, I MEAN, I
DIDN'T, BUT I'VE...
GROWN A BIT
OVER THE YEARS.
SO? FILL ME IN.
WHAT DO YOU GUYS
HAVE SO FAR?
THE SAME BOMB PLANS
YOU HAVE,
PLUS A MAP OF TUNNELS
INTO THE GLADES.
CUBE IN A CUBE.
-YOU KNOW IT?
-FELICITY USED TO
FORCE THIS STUFF
ON ME.
LITTLE, UH,
MOTHER-DAUGHTER
BONDING TIME
BEFORE I WISED UP.
THERE'S ANOTHER SOLVE.
CUBE IN A...CUBE...
IN A CUBE.
NO WAY. HUH.
WHAT IS THAT?
I THINK IT'S
A MINI-CASSETTE.
MY GRANDPARENTS HAD
AN ANSWERING MACHINE
THAT USED THESE.
WHAT'S
AN ANSWERING MACHINE?
IT'S NOT IMPORTANT.
WHAT IS IMPORTANT
IS THE MESSAGE
THAT'S ON THIS TAPE.
CAN YOU HACK IT OR...
NO. YOU CAN'T
HACK THIS. HEH.
IT'S ENCRYPTION
THROUGH OBSOLESCENCE.
IT'S PRETTY GENIUS,
ACTUALLY.
YEAH, SO GENIUS,
YOU CAN'T LISTEN TO IT.
-WE'LL FIGURE IT OUT.
-I HOPE SO...
BECAUSE THIS COULD
BE THE KEY TO
FINDING OUR MOM.
COMPUTER: GREEN ARROW
ENTERING QUEEN RESIDENCE.
HEY! HOW'D IT GO?
-PRETTY GOOD.
-GOOD.
I FEEL LIKE WE'RE
GETTING TO A GOOD PLACE.
-MINT CHIP.
-HMM. YOU WANT SOME?
I'M GOOD.
JUST NEEDED A LITTLE
COMFORT FOOD
AFTER THE NIGHT
WE HAD.
A NIGHT THAT COULD HAVE
ENDED VERY DIFFERENTLY.
YOU WANT TO KNOW
WHY I DIDN'T
KILL DIAZ.
I WANTED TO.
I WAS READY TO.
THEN I REALIZED
KILLING DIAZ
WASN'T GOING TO
PROVE ANYTHING.
THE WHOLE REASON
I WANTED DIAZ DEAD
WAS TO PROTECT
OUR FAMILY,
AND...WHAT OUR FAMILY NEEDS
IS A FRESH START,
ONE IN THE LIGHT
JUST LIKE YOU'RE DOING.
I WANT OUR CHILDREN
TO KNOW
THAT THEY ARE
THE MOST IMPORTANT
THING TO US
AND THAT WE WOULD
DO ANYTHING...
ANYTHING FOR THEM.
AHEM. YOU SAID,
"CHILDREN."
I'M PREGNANT.
HA HA!
DANTE: IMPRESSIVE.
YOU SHOULDN'T BE HERE.
IS THAT ANY WAY
TO GREET AN OLD FRIEND?
I HEAR YOU AND OLIVER QUEEN
ARE GETTING ALONG
QUITE WELL.
-HE TRUSTS ME NOW.
-GOOD.
THE TIMING COULDN'T
BE BETTER.
IT'S TIME FOR YOU
TO COME HOME.
[PANTING]
WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE?
[METAL CREAKING]
UNH!
[LIGHTER FLICKS OPEN]
[LIGHTER STRIKES]
[SCREAMING]
[SCREAMING STOPS]
MAN: GREG, MOVE YOUR HEAD!