[PEOPLE CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY]
Mr. Queen's gonna be late.
He's extremely sorry. It couldn't be helped.
-Where is he?
-Um...
-Over there!
-Where, man?
Right there, man!
Just got a little held up.
You know, tying up some loose ends.
Agh!
I'm actually in direct contact
with him now. Let me check.
[GUNFIRE OVER COMM]
Where are you getting the guns?
Are you gonna kill me?
Get it over with already.
Dig.
Took down two more gangbangers. They were
armed with fully automatic M4A1 assault rifles.
DIGGLE: M4A1s are military-grade weapons.
Stolen, most likely.
Stolen from where?
DIGGLE:
Well, we can look into that after your party.
What party?
He's here.
Sorry I'm late.
This party is to attract investors
for your failing company.
Being late might do well for the club circuit...
...but it does not inspire confidence
on Wall Street.
-Is that blood on your face?
-Hm?
Don't worry. It's not his blood.
Of course, it's his blood. Why would
he have somebody else's blood on his face?
Who taught you to shave, mister?
What kept you? Was it our masked blond
that carries a giant staff to beat attackers?
This time it was guns.
-We were just talking about guns.
LAUREL: Hey...
-...Oliver.
-Hi.
-What's your interest in guns, Mr. Queen?
-Never touch them myself.
The Glades' gun epidemic
is out of control.
Which is why the DA's office
committed to ending gun violence.
I'm sure the police are doing what they can to
catch whoever's bringing weapons to the city.
Heh.
Did I say something funny?
They know who's been arming
the gangs, Oliver.
The Mayor.
I thought the hood copycats
killed the mayor.
Not the actual mayor.
A local gang lord calls himself the Mayor.
He thinks he's the man to save our city.
-But that position's already filled, isn't it?
-Heh.
Now, this Mayor has only one goal:
To create chaos, so he can rule the Glades
at the barrel of a gun.
[HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYING INDISTINCTLY
ON SPEAKERS]
[LAUGHING]
You are noticeably unarmed, son.
Sorry, Mr. Mayor. We ran into
the vigilante, you know.
-He ganked our weapons.
-Do you know who I was before the quake?
I was no one. I had no name.
None that mattered anyway.
I was just a...
Just another weak man waiting to get fired...
...or evicted or killed.
But then the ground shook.
And now I matter because I know
the guy with the biggest gun wins.
And that's why I will rule the Glades.
-There's no room at my table for punks like you.
-Come on, man.
Mr. Mayor, I wanna ask for leniency.
The kid's my cousin. I brought him in.
Oh, you did?
Now, let's hope you do your family
prouder than he did.
[SHUDDERS]
Hey.
Please don't ask me if I'm okay,
because I'm sick of everyone asking me that.
-I would never do that.
-Good.
You okay?
The Dollmaker was just your garden-variety
traumatic experience.
After the quake and Tommy...
-...I should be used to that by now.
OLIVER: I've had a few of those.
You never get used to them.
Excuse me, Oliver,
may I talk to you a second?
-It's urgent.
-Yeah.
You can have him back in a minute.
Excuse us.
I just realized something.
What if our masked friend
that keeps showing up everywhere...
-What about her?
-What if we've been going about this wrong?
We thought she was obsessed with you,
showing up at the DA's when you were there.
And in the chemical plant
the Dollmaker was holed up in.
But who else was at both those places?
What if our masked friend
isn't following you?
She's following Laurel.
Agh!
[PANTING]
[HIGH-PITCHED WAILING]
Does it get any louder?
[WAILING STOPS]
Why are you following Laurel Lance?
I could ask the same thing of you.
I guess some things never change.
You and her. Always and forever.
-Who are you?
-Once you know...
-...your life will never be the same.
-I can take it.
Not this time, Ollie.
Laurel's gonna kill me.
[SCREAMING]
Sara!
Sara?
I'll give you some time to let it sink in.
[DANCE MUSIC PLAYING ON SPEAKERS]
FELICITY:
Sara Lance.
Laurel's sister,
the detective's other daughter. The one...
...you took on the Gambit, even though
you were dating Laurel at the time...
I'm sorry, it's just...
Isn't she... Isn't she dead?
You told everyone that she died when
the Gambit went down, that she drowned.
You lied.
When the Gambitcapsized, uh...
...Sara was pulled under.
It was so dark and cold...
...and I thought she drowned.
About a year later, I saw her.
Where? On the island?
She drifted to the island too?
Not exactly.
Why didn't you tell the Lances
she didn't die on that boat?
Laurel and Mr. Lance blame you.
It was my fault.
What happened was my fault.
-Where has she been all these years?
-I don't know.
Diggle, I swear to God.
I was sure she was dead.
-Do you have any happy stories?
-To make sure I understand this correctly...
...after not drowning
when the Gambit went down...
...Sara didn't exactly make it
to the island with you...
...where you would see her die yet again.
Feel free to fill in the blanks.
-Not right now.
-You mean not ever.
Didn't her family have a right to know
she made it to the island?
These were five years!
Five years...
...where nothing good happened...
...and they were better off not knowing.
Do they deserve to know now?
I need to take care of some business
at the office.
-Where are we with the Mayor?
-I am in contact...
...with some of my military sources.
Trying to get a line on how he's getting
his illegal Army weaponry.
I'll keep you updated.
You know, Oliver, somebody once told me...
...that secrets have weight.
The more you keep,
the harder it is to keep moving.
You see how hard I work out.
You killed two of my crew.
How many others are with you
on the island?
What are your weapon capabilities?
Did you find the graves?
Two things will happen.
You will tell me everything I want to know.
Then I will kill you.
Or I will torture you until you tell me
everything I want to know.
And then I will kill you.
-Go to hell.
-Can't.
We're already there.
[SCREAMING]
Told you.
Patty Shack on 5th and Brewer.
Best burgers in town.
Well, Patty Shack's
in the Mayor's territory...
...so I'll take a subpar breakfast
over a bullet.
What's wrong?
Look, I know I'm skinny, but I can eat
two of these, and I will.
I just ran into an old boyfriend.
Just...
-...I'm worried he might tell my family I'm back.
-You have family in Starling?
Yeah.
My father, he's...
He's a policeman.
And my sister, she's a lawyer.
Well, they must be real proud
of their masked delinquent.
-Yeah, they think I'm dead.
-Oh, cool.
My folks think I'm dead too.
That or they wish I'd never been born.
One of those.
Why don't you want them to know
that you're still alive?
Because I'm not what they remember.
Good little Daddy's girl?
Far from it.
I was a lot like you.
Is that why you saved me
from those guys that night?
No woman should ever suffer
at the hands of men.
We've gotta stop meeting like this.
-What would your girlfriend think, Johnnie?
-Heh.
Lyla, I'm checking the box
marked "single" these days.
-Sorry to hear it. What happened?
-Mm.
Well, another man came between us.
Deadshot.
You're letting him ruin your life.
So I've been repeatedly told.
Anything on those stolen Army weapons?
A crate of M4A1s went missing
from Camp Kirby two months ago.
I know where they went.
Every crate was fitted with a GPS system
so they could be tracked.
I tried it but it's not receiving.
Must have been deactivated.
-Thank, Lyla.
-And your interest in this is what?
Lyla, you and I went to Afghanistan...
...to try to bring law and order to a country
overrun by warlords and weapons, right?
Should we do any less for our own cities?
Thanks again.
-Hey, Johnnie.
-Yeah?
These days
I check the box marked "single" too.
Mr. Blood.
-I see you've met Ms. Rochev. She's my...
-Superior.
-Partner.
-On paper.
Is that why you asked me to come down?
To mediate your title?
You and I got off
on the wrong foot repeatedly.
Seems to be your superpower.
I was inspired by what you said the other night
about gun violence in the Glades.
-I had an idea that might help.
-Really?
-Another party at your stately manor?
-No.
To sponsor a Cash for Guns event.
I give you the money and you get
your constituents to lay down their arms.
Everybody wins.
Especially you.
Trying to repair your family's tainted name
by ridding the Glades of guns.
You just get the money, Mr. Blood.
-I don't want my family's name involved.
-Mr. Queen...
...may I have a word with you?
Let me think it over.
-We are not sponsoring that event.
-I know.
-I am.
-With what money?
Your investment party cost QC 50 grand
and no one invested a dime.
I will not continue to authorize corporate
funds just so you can keep pretending...
...that you are the CEO.
Fine. I'll pay for it myself.
Heh, maybe you haven't noticed, but your
personal trust isn't what it used to be.
And this company isn't either.
As much as I would love
to make the city safer...
...my first obligation is
to Queen Consolidated.
And yours is too.
[DAUGHTER'S "YOUTH"
PLAYING ON SPEAKERS]
Shadows settle on the place
That you left
I was gonna order some takeout.
You want in?
-I appreciate the offer, Adam...
-I've eaten takeout every night this week.
I need a meal served on
an actual plate. So do you.
I get it.
It's easy to let the job become your life.
I keep having to remind myself to go to
the gym, see a movie, eat a good meal.
That sounds dangerously like having a life.
Ha, ha. What about you?
You can't be all about work.
-I'm the best me when I am working.
-And when you're not?
You don't want to meet her.
She's not good company.
I'd be willing to risk it.
Excuse me.
I just remembered.
-I have to go.
-I'm sorry. I didn't mean to...
No. It's okay. It's fine.
I just have to go.
-Good night.
[SIREN WAILING]
Crap.
-License and registration.
-Is there a problem, officer?
Have you had anything
to drink tonight, ma'am?
I'm Laurel Lance.
I'm an assistant district attorney.
I'm sorry, Ms. Lance, but I'm gonna have
to ask you to step out of the car, please.
I need some good news.
The bad news first.
Somehow, the Mayor did get his hands...
...on a crate of military-grade weapons
from Camp Kirby.
-The good news?
-If he kept the crate...
...we might find out where he's hiding.
This is the same tracking system the Army
installs on all of its weapons crates.
If they lose a crate, they send out
a signal that activates the beacon.
Mayor's clever. He deactivated his beacon.
Send a signal, nothing comes back.
You both need to work
on your definition of "good news."
Okay. How's this? Guess which company
designed the Army's tracking system.
I'll give you a hint.
Their CEO? Always late.
Nice.
I pulled up the plans
from the QC mainframe.
There's a design flaw.
The beacon is still susceptible to
a subform wave even if it's deactivated.
The Mayor turned it off, Oliver.
We can turn it back on.
I believe you ordered the crate of
stolen military weapons, Mr. Queen.
[HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYING INDISTINCTLY
ON SPEAKERS]
I thought you deactivated the tracker.
[ARROW WHISTLES]
Cover me.
Come on.
-Weapons are secure.
DIGGLE: And the Mayor?
Still in office.
Thanks for the heads up, Officer Daily.
Just FYI...
...she blew 0.6 past the legal limit.
Thanks.
He didn't need to call you.
No, but you're lucky he did.
You could have lost your job, your license.
-You could have killed somebody.
-I had a few too many glasses of wine.
-It was an accident.
-An accident? Well, I guess those happen.
Was I not supposed to notice that tone?
Between the two of us,
you get a lot from me, Laurel.
Maybe you got this too.
We can hardly compare my one mistake
to your drinking problem.
So long as it is only one mistake.
I don't know if you've noticed...
...but I've had a little bit
of a hard time lately.
I was kidnapped, nearly murdered
by a psychopath and my boyfriend died.
So, I don't know, maybe cut me some slack.
When I started having a hard time,
I wish people had not cut me slack.
Leave your car here. I'm driving you home.
-I'll take a cab.
-Laurel.
Laurel!
-Did you tell my family that I'm alive?
-No.
Sara...
...I saw you die.
Not the first time that's happened. Right?
I thought you were dead too.
What happened to Slade?
Where have you been?
-Everywhere.
-That's not an answer.
Well, it's the one you're getting.
About a year ago...
...I started hearing tales
of the Starling City Vigilante.
The man in the green hood.
I knew it was you.
I've never known you to be a fighter.
-Where'd you pick that up?
-I met some rough people.
-Thought I should get rougher too...
-Sara...
...why did you come back?
The earthquake.
Because you wanted to make sure
your family was safe.
But now you're still here,
watching over them.
Protecting them. So did you come here...
...to make sure I didn't tell them?
Or because you were hoping I had?
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
I'll get rid of them.
-Mr. Lance?
-Hi.
Something I can help you with?
I'm here about my daughter.
Laurel.
-Is she okay?
-Yeah. Well, no, she's not.
She got pulled over for a DUI last night.
I tried talking to her about it,
but she wasn't hearing me.
Ah, I saw her the other night. She...
...didn't seem like herself.
I know. She seems like me.
I don't know if you know...
...but when you and Sara disappeared...
...I hit the bottle pretty hard.
I know the two of you are friends.
She needs a friend.
Maybe talk to her.
Sure.
Anyhow.
-Mr. Lance.
-Yeah.
Um...
I'd be happy to talk to Laurel.
Thanks.
[YELLING]
Ugh.
Why...? Unh.
Wh...?
Why'd they do this? Unh.
They make all of us do this.
It's for to show prochnost.
It's Russian for "strength."
They did this to see if I'm strong?
They're doing this to see if you survive.
Living...
...is not for the weak.
[GRUNTING]
[YELLING]
-Oliver, hi.
-Hey.
-What are you doing here? Is everything okay?
-I don't know. Is everything okay?
Ugh. You've gotta be kidding me.
My dad went to you?
He spent the last six years cursing your name.
Now you're gossip buddies?
Laurel, he's worried about you.
Perfect.
A recovering alcoholic and former party boy
trying to tell me how to live my life.
-Don't you see the hypocrisy there?
-What I see...
...is somebody that both of us care for...
...having a rough go of it.
Do you know how many times
I've had to pull my dad out of a bar?
Or how many nights I've had to drive him home
while he's passed out in my backseat?
He's the one with the problem.
Not me.
Just because he can't cope with losing Sara
doesn't mean I can't handle my life.
Feel free to tell him that
during your next chitchat.
[DOOR OPENS]
Sewing is not your strong suit.
Now we can talk.
For two years...
...my crew and I have been looking
for a gravesite.
Did you find the graves?
Were the bodies...
...odd?
The bones...
...misshapen?
This is the right island.
Looks like we got a Colt 1911...
...Jennings .32 and a K-Frame revolver.
-We'll give you 250 for the lot.
-Keep it.
Do I even wanna know
where you got those guns?
They're from the old days. I told you.
Look, no more being a criminal.
No more being a hero.
I'm just Roy Harper,
busboy and boyfriend.
Yo, Abercrombie.
-Where's your manners?
-Sin.
This is Thea. Thea, this is Sin.
Thea Queen?
Look at you rolling with royalty.
-By the way, the salad fork's the small one.
-It was good to see you again.
She doesn't know you're the Vigilante's
delivery boy, does she?
-Nice to meet you, Your Highness.
-You too.
-So, how do you know her?
-From around.
SEBASTIAN:
You don't show up when you say you will...
...and when you promise not to,
here you are.
-Going well?
-Last check...
...we've taken in over 200 guns
in only three hours.
Try not to look so happy about it.
A lot on my mind, alderman.
My job is to help the people in this city
with their problems.
Two people that are very important to me...
...are having a tough time. Sisters, actually.
And neither one is making it
very easy for me to help them.
Sooner or later, we all go through a crucible.
I'm guessing yours was that island.
Most believe there are two types of people
who go into a crucible:
The ones who grow stronger
from the experience and survive it...
...and the ones who die.
But there's a third type:
The ones who learn to love the fire.
They choose to stay in their crucible...
...because it's easier to embrace the pain
when it's all you know anymore.
That's why I'm on the clock
to help this city...
-...before it becomes used to living like this.
-"Living is not for the weak."
-An old friend of mine once told me that.
-That's a wise friend.
Yeah.
Listen up, people.
This is your Mayor speaking.
Now, I don't recall this here event
being sanctioned.
What happens in the Glades
only happens if I allow it.
You're not the leader of this community!
You don't speak for these people!
And neither do you. Not anymore.
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
Hey. Are you okay? Are you hit?
No.
-Hey, Sin, you all right?
-All's good.
Go get help. Go!
The shooting was committed
by the gang leader known only as the Mayor...
...who, until now, has never
been seen in public.
We do want to warn our audience
that some of these images are graphic.
Coward finally decided to show his face.
Vanity is gonna cost him.
I borrowed the FBI's
facial recognition software.
Got a match. Xavier Reed.
-Did Mr. Reed serve in the military?
-No military history.
Family members?
Reed was in and out of foster care
his whole life. Wait, hold on.
In 1996, Reed spent three years
with a foster family...
...and their son, Ezra Barnes.
He served three tours in Iraq.
He's Stateside now.
-Twenty bucks says he was at Camp Kirby.
-Pay the man.
The Mayor's foster brother is assigned
to a weapons convoy...
...that carries SCAR 16s by truck.
The convoy's scheduled to come
through here tonight.
FN SCAR 16s are military assault weapons
with grenade launchers.
The Mayor gets a hold of these, Oliver,
it's game over.
He won't.
Bullet penetrated her anterior abdomen.
We were able to remove most of the fragments.
We'll know more in a few hours.
Hey. I'm gonna stick around
in case she wakes up.
Is it okay if I stick around with you?
You saved her life, Roy.
Guess you can't stop being a hero, can you?
[ARROW WHISTLES]
I wanna see how you do in a real fight.
Good. I was looking for a fight.
They're with me.
He wasn't.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
You're done being all you can be.
-Ahh.
-Ha-ha-ha.
You and I are gonna own this town.
Now, let's see what this bad boy can do.
[METALLIC RING]
[ALL GRUNTING]
Load up the weapons. Now!
-Behind you.
-Old school weapon. Respect!
But can your arrows do this?
[ALL GRUNTING]
Come on. Where are you?
[GRUNTING]
-You hurt a friend of mine.
-Let him go.
-You can't save a city with forgiveness.
-You don't have to forgive him.
But you do have to let him live.
Bitch. Knew you didn't have it in you.
Agh! Oof.
I really don't like that word.
SNOW [ON TV]:
Demonstrations opposing the construction...
...of the new S.T.A.R. Lab's
particle accelerator...
...have reached a fever pitch
with five more protestors being arrested.
In other news, the recent Cash for Guns
event held in the Glades...
...is credited for getting
over 800 weapons off the streets.
Still a mystery, the anonymous donor...
...whose generous donation
funded the event.
I guess it's true what they say.
-One man can change the world.
-I'll leave changing the world to you.
I'm only in the world because of you.
Thank you.
I was just acting on instinct.
It wasn't instinct. It was strength.
I see the signs, the graffiti.
"Blood for mayor."
Now that the Mayor is in jail,
maybe you should run.
There is more than one way to save a city.
-Mr. Harper.
-What's wrong? Is she okay?
Hi.
You saved my life.
Guess I have to keep your secret now, huh?
-You know you're dating a moron, right?
-Heh.
It's my first and last thought of every day.
Crap.
I like her.
You friend,
I took care of her medical expenses.
Thank you.
-Look, I don't want Thea to see...
-What's your plan, Sara?
Because right now you're just...
You're whipping across rooftops
and keeping watch over your family...
-...like some sort of ghost.
-We're both ghosts.
-We died on that island...
-No, we didn't.
We both lived.
And...
...I get that you have been in pain so long...
...that it probably just feels normal now.
You can let it go and come home.
I know that the earthquake brought you here,
but your family kept you here.
You have to tell them, Sara.
They need you.
You told them that I died on the Gambit.
-If they know the truth...
-They would never...
They would never talk to me again.
Not one of them.
It'd be worth it.
LANCE:
My daughter's in trouble.
She's, uh... She's been through some really
terrible things.
And...
...instead of facing up to them,
she's running away from them.
She's losing herself in her work...
...and maybe even worse.
She's my daughter. I just want her safe.
I want to protect her.
I guess, like we say in our meetings,
"More will be revealed."
[GROANING]
Your days of screaming are just beginning.
[GRUNTS]
How...?
What the hell is this?
This ain't the police station.
Hello, brother.
Are you ready to serve?
Why you wearing that mask?
This city is in chains and I'm going to free it.
But to do that I need an army.
An army of the strong.
What's in that thing?
A miracle.
Get that off me.
Get that crap away from me!
Are you ready to serve?
[GROANING]
[SCREAMS]
Bring me another.
Yes, Brother Blood.