OLIVER:
Previously on Arrow:
Maybe I'm finally ready to admit
that I still have feelings for you too.
No. Malcolm is planning
to level the Glades.
My father,
he told me that he failed the city.
But I never knew what he meant
until now.
Merlyn's plan is what I returned
from the island to stop.
Oh, no.
You can survive this.
Make it home. And make it better.
Right my wrongs.
- Dad.
- Survive.
[GUNSHOT]
[OLIVER PANTING]
I hope I didn't hurt you.
At least I can properly thank you now
for saving my life.
If I only knew...
...how you were spending
your nights.
My hope is that I can explain
everything to you...
...to help you understand.
You murdered my father.
You sentenced me to that island...
...to five years of hell.
I'm truly sorry
for what happened to you.
You know I have lost people.
Yeah, your wife.
Do you really think...
...that you're honoring
Tommy's mother...
...by destroying the Glades?
As surely as you believe...
...you're honoring your father
with this hood.
Not a day goes by
I don't miss your father.
You'll see him soon.
You can't beat me, Oliver.
Yes, you're younger
and you're faster.
Yet you always seem
to come up short against me.
Want to know why?
Because you don't know...
...in your heart,
what you're fighting for.
What you're willing to sacrifice,
and I do.
No one can stop
what's about to come.
Not even the vigilante.
Plane's holding steady at 33,000 feet.
The range for missile intercept.
Lock missile one on target.
Missile one locked
on the jet's heat trail.
FRYERS:
Prepare to launch on my mark.
DURAND:
Yes, sir.
[YELLING]
[DURAND GRUNTS]
Fire! Fire the missile now!
[GRUNTS]
[GROANS]
[NECK SNAPS]
[CRACKS]
[GUNSHOT]
I take back every joke about you
sticking a tracking device in your boot.
Felicity's
at Queen Consolidated.
She's going through data
she pulled off Merlyn's network.
- Did she find anything?
- Yeah.
The design schematics
of the earthquake generator.
So we can shut it down.
Assuming we find it in time.
[PHONE RINGS]
DIGGLE: Yeah, Felicity, I got him.
- Thank God.
- Is he okay?
DIGGLE: Mostly.
Okay. I'm on my way.
LANCE:
Miss Smoak.
Where are you off to
in such a hurry?
Please.
Take a seat.
You know, I think I'd rather stand.
- You're not exactly a hardened criminal.
- No, I'm not any kind of criminal.
- What do you call computer hacking?
- A hobby?
That I do not engage in.
Hey, I got a whole mess...
...of gobbledygook I don't understand
but it says otherwise.
I had my tech guy scrub through
your computer at Queen Consolidated.
You used it to hack into
Blackhawk Squad Security...
...research arrows shipped
to a company called Sagittarius...
...and to analyze a water sample
to tie back to a Vertigo drug lab.
These are all cases...
...involving...
...The Hood.
Tell me, Felicity.
What am I thinking?
[PHONE RINGS]
Saved by the bell.
Excuse me.
HOOD: Hello, detective.
- Funny you should call.
- I got your sidekick sitting in front of me.
HOOD: I don't have a sidekick.
When I need help, I call you.
Merlyn plans to level the Glades
with a manmade earthquake...
...using technology
from Unidac Industries.
What?
Ha, ha. Now you're trying
to have fun with me.
I don't know Merlyn's timetable. You need
to evacuate the Glades immediately.
Get as many people
to safety as you can.
Whatever you think of me,
detective, please...
...believe this.
Sounds like you have
bigger problems than me.
Don't leave town.
You know...
...I used to think the vigilante was
a criminal too but it seems to me...
...whoever he is, he's willing to sacrifice
to help the people of this city.
Kind of makes him a hero.
Doesn't it?
Look who it is.
- My best friend in life.
- Hey, buddy.
I took your advice, you know.
I went to Laurel's
to fight for her.
So imagine my surprise
seeing you there, kissing her.
- I'm sorry.
- No, you're not.
Something's happening
and it involves your father.
- Keep my father out of this.
- Our fathers.
They aren't the men
we thought they were.
They made a plan together...
...to destroy the Glades.
Do you have any idea
what you sound like right now?
Your father's gonna do it.
Because he thinks
it will avenge your mother's death.
Do not talk about my mother.
The difference...
...between us, Tommy...
...is that I didn't find out
the truth about my father...
...until it was too late.
But you've always known...
...deep down...
...you have always known
the man he is.
I wish you would have died
on that island.
Open.
[YELLING]
We need to reprogram
the missile.
I don't know how to reprogram.
- I do.
- Hey, Shado!
[GRUNTS]
Oliver, put the chip in.
Quick, I got a comm stat meeting in five.
I don't want to be late for my funeral.
I've got it under good authority
that Merlyn...
...plans to level the Glades
using an earthquake device...
...made by Unidac Industries.
- Who's your source in all this?
- The vigilante.
He called me.
Yeah, has done
the last few months.
He's been helpful
on some cases.
You asked for the task force
to catch him.
- You swore you'd bring him in.
- I know. I swore to uphold the law.
The law is steady and unchanging.
The law needed to be protected.
But what are laws, rules,
if they don't protect people?
I'm throwing away
my career by telling you this...
...I am willing to sacrifice catching this guy
if it means saving people's lives.
Please.
You're suspended.
Leave your gun and badge
with the duty sergeant.
- Lieutenant--
- Suspension or incarceration.
You choose.
No more lies, Mom.
The Undertaking.
We need to stop it.
Everything I have ever said
or done...
...has been to protect you
and your sister.
What about all those people
in the Glades?
I'm not their mother.
- I spoke to Malcolm.
- You what?
He could have killed you.
He killed your father.
No, he didn't.
After the Gambit went down,
dad and I both made it to the life raft.
And then we drifted, for days.
In the end, there wasn't enough
food and water for both of us.
So he shot himself in the head.
I don't want to hear this.
He sacrificed himself.
So that I could live.
Do you really think...
...that I could go on living...
...knowing that you sacrificed
thousands more in my name?
Mom. Please.
You have to help me
stop Malcolm.
We need to know where the device is.
[PHONE RINGING]
Malcolm.
How can I help you?
I see.
Yes, thank you for calling.
- What is it?
- Malcolm's accelerated his timetable.
The Undertaking is...
---haPDening tonight.
Where are you going?
Somebody in this family
needs to put an end to this.
Whatever the cost.
LAUREL:
Hi.
Hey-
LAUREL:
I woke up and you were gone.
I'm really sorry about that.
Oliver, I'm trying not to think
that our history's repeating.
- That you're scared again.
- No.
That's not it.
Then will you tell me
what's going on with you?
There are so many things...
...that I have wanted to tell you...
...for so long.
I never told you what happened to me
on the island.
You didn't have to.
I can see that it changed you.
That's the thing.
Laurel, it didn't.
Those five years didn't change me.
They just...
...they scraped away
all the things that I wasn't...
...and revealed the person
I always was, which is the person--
That's who you always saw.
I don't know how you saw it,
but you did.
Nobody in my life
is who I thought they were.
Except you.
Laurel, I need you
to do something for me.
- Stay out of the Glades tonight.
- Why?
You'll know soon.
One way or the other.
I have to go.
It's over.
Laurel and me, I mean.
She's with Oliver, again.
Always.
I'm sorry, son.
Yeah, and he said you wanted to nuke
the Glades or something.
It's funny, Scotch doesn't make it
any more believable.
Maybe after your jihad,
we can, uh, grab some steaks.
It's true, Tommy.
It's the reason
I closed your mother's clinic.
I didn't wanna see it leveled.
What?
I have something
I'd like you to listen to.
The night your mother died...
...she called me.
I awoke to a voice-mail from her.
- Dad.
- Her final gift to me.
REBECCA [ON RECORDING]:
Malcolm, I 'm in trouble.
I told, I told him
to take everything.
My 1110/79)”-
...my Ting-.
Turn it off.
REBECCA:
They shot me.
I screamed for help...
-...but no one would come. God.
- No one would come.
REBECCA:
Malcolm, I don't want to die alone.
She bled out into the pavement
while people passed and did nothing.
Your mother built her clinic in the Glades
because she wanted to save this city.
It can't be saved.
Because the people there
don't want it to be saved.
- So you kill them all--?
- Yes!
They deserve to die!
All of them!
The way she died!
The Undertaking
is happening tonight.
Felicity may have found something.
This symbol is the map
of the old subway tunnel system.
That's got us thinking the Undertaking
is connected to the Glades.
- What if it's more specific?
- What do you mean?
If I had a machine that could trigger
an earthquake...
...in an otherwise geologically stable area,
where would I position it?
- Underground.
- Yeah.
This is a U.S. geological survey...
...of the tectonic plates
running underneath Starling City.
This red line here is a known fault
that runs right below the Glades.
About a mile. Fault runs under
the old 10th Street subway.
Dollars to doughnuts, the seismic device
is somewhere along there.
I know where it is.
[PHONE VIBRATES]
Now is not a good time.
Yeah, understate much?
Mom has a whole bunch
of reporters here.
She's holding a press conference
or something.
What channel?
It looks like all of them.
Felicity, pull up the local news,
please.
My name is Moira Dearden Queen.
I am the acting CEO
of Queen Consolidated.
And God forgive me,
I have failed this city.
For the past five years,
under the threat for my life...
...and the lives of my family...
...I have been complicit...
...in an undertaking
with one horrible purpose.
To destroy the Glades
and everyone in it.
I realize now
that my family's safety...
...will mean nothing
if I let this dreadful act occur.
But you need to know...
...that the architect
of this nightmare...
...is Malcolm Merlyn.
[SCREAMS]
Yes, and I have proof
that he has killed dozens...
...in pursuit of this madness.
Adam Hunt, Frank Chen...
...and my husband...
...Robert.
Please.
If you reside in the Glades,
you need to get out now.
Your lives and the lives
of your children depend on it.
Please.
[REPORTERS YELLING INDISTINCTLY]
- I don't understand.
- I'm sorry. I love you.
- I love Roy.
- Roy?
He lives in the Glades.
- I can't leave him there.
- Sweetheart. Thea.
HILTON: You're under arrest
for conspiracy to murder.
Anything you say can and will be used
against you in a court of law.
You have the right to an attorney.
TOMMY:
Is it true?
Did you kill all those people?
I did What I had to do.
OFFICER:
Freeze!
Malcolm Merlyn,
you are under arrest.
Don't move.
Dad, no.
Please, Dad.
Stay back.
I don't want to hurt you.
You can't.
And you can't stop me.
FELICITY:
Oliver, I'm sorry.
Don't be.
She gave those people a chance.
I thought Merlyn broke your bow.
I have another.
I was going over
the device schematics.
The device can be set
for a timed detonation...
-...or remote activated by mobile transmitter.
- Something Merlyn could have on him.
If we can just get our hands
on this transmitter...
-...we don't need to track down the device.
-It's too big an if.
I need you in the subway.
- Find the device, disarm it.
- So you can take on Merlyn by yourself?
- I have to.
- Oh, he'll kill you, Oliver.
I know.
He's beaten me twice.
And I don't know how to stop him.
Okay. How about this time,
you bring along something...
...you didn't have
the last time you two fought.
- Me.
- I can't let you.
I can't let you do this
by yourself, man.
Oliver, you are not alone, not since
you brought me into this.
Us into this.
Besides, Army regulations.
A soldier never lets a brother
go into battle alone.
- I'm out of bows.
- I got my gun.
I guess it's up to me
to do the dismantling.
This whole area is ground zero.
I want you out of here.
If you're not leaving,
I'm not leaving.
Besides, if I don't deactivate
the device, who will?
[PHONE RINGS]
You were right.
I need one more thing from you.
- Yeah? What do I got left to give?
- I know where Merlyn is keeping the device.
It's in an abandoned subway station
near Pap Street.
LANCE: How do you know?
- That's where his wife was murdered.
[OVER PHONE] I need someone I can trust
to deactivate the device.
We have a mutual friend that I think
could talk you through it.
She says you care
about the people of this city...
...that it needs you.
Right now, detective...
...it needs you.
[YELLING]
REPORTER [ON TV]: Earlier today,
Moira Queen, CEO of Queen Consolidated...
...admitted to a conspiracy
to destroy the Glades.
Everyone within a five-mile radius
has been asked to evacuate.
MAN [OVER PA]:
Stay calm.
Do not rush and do not panic.
Proceed out of the Glades
in an orderly manner.
[GRUNTING]
Looks like we missed him.
Shade .
Sade.
[SLADE LAUGHING]
Oh, I should have figured.
You couldn't save the day...
-...without making a mess.
- Where's Shado?
- I thought she was with you.
FRYERS: Actually...
...she's with me.
Let her go. It's over, Fyers.
Let her go.
Amazing.
A two-year operation undone...
...because a young playboy
happened to wash up on the shore...
...and now here you are, a killer.
You wanted nothing more
than to leave this island...
...and now you can.
I can call in a rescue ship,
you can go home.
Tell me, Mr. Queen.
Are you prepared to sacrifice
your freedom for her?
Guess so.
[COUGHING NEARBY]
Tommy.
- Tommy.
- Oliver.
Where's your father?
I don't know.
You were right.
- You were right about him.
DIGGLE: Oliver.
Are you gonna kill him?
Get to safety.
Looks like a false wall.
Welcome, gentlemen.
I've been waiting for you.
I wanted to see you
watch your city die.
- Where's the transmitter?
- Somewhere I can easily get to it.
I doubt it. You'll be too dead.
[GROANS]
Stairs, Oliver. Go, go.
So tell me, are you ready to die?
FELICITY: You found it yet, detective?
- I'm not sure what I'm looking for.
You want me to describe it?
No, I got it.
FELICITY: You should see something that
looks like a circuit board. Pull it out.
Do you see a timer?
Seven minutes.
Okay. Well, the good news is...
...this is going to be
a paperweight in three.
MAN [OVER PA]:
Everyone leave the Glades. I repeat...
...leave the Glades now.
MAN 1: What do you got there, grandpa?
- Hey.
MAN 2: Please, please, it's all I have.
ROY: Hey.
Hey. Back off.
Learn how to count, jerkwad.
There's three of us.
Oh, is that right?
- Because I only count one.
- With a gun.
- Where did you learn how to do that?
- I have wicked aim.
I went to your house.
I figured I'd run for my life
with everyone else. Did you...?
- Did you come to rescue me?
- Yeah.
Come on.
[ARROW BEEPS]
Look for three wires,
you need a green one...
...a yellow and one blue.
- Cut the blue one.
- All right, I got it, I got it.
[WHIRRING]
Oh, my God.
LANCE: No, no, no.
- There must be an anti-tamper safeguard.
Hold on. Fm gonna figure out
how to override it.
Not enough time.
There's not enough time.
- Just hold on.
LANCE: Not enough time.
- Laurel.
- Dad.
Don't worry, I got your message
and I did not come into work today.
Save it, kiddo,
we both know you're there.
You got to get out of the Glades
right now. Okay, please.
- Dad?
LANCE: Right now, Laurel.
Right now, Laurel.
Daddy, you're scaring me.
Sorry, but I'm not...
I'm not gonna make it.
What?
- What?
LANCE: You have to promise me one thing.
You're not gonna die with me.
[OVER PHONE]
You have to go on with your life.
After your sister died, I pushed people away,
I became like a ghost.
Didn't think I had the right to live
if my baby couldn't.
Promise me you're not gonna make
the same mistakes as I did.
Promise me, Laurel.
[OVER PHONE]
Promise me.
I promise.
I love you, honey, now and forever.
I love you.
Dad.
Detective Lance? I need
you to listen to me very carefully.
You do know how dangerous it is
to text and drive, right?
- It can wait.
- It can't.
- I'm trying to find another route out of here.
- Let me. It's not worth the risk.
Roy.
Help me out.
Help me out. Help me out.
Roy, stop.
The device is about to go off
any second.
- I can't leave any of them behind.
- I know you have something to prove.
But you're not the vigilante.
Look, I can't do this
unless I know you're safe.
Then you better haul ass
out of here too.
Don't struggle. It's over.
There was never any doubt
in the outcome.
Don't worry. Your mother and sister
will be joining you in death.
ROBERT:
Survive.
[MALCOLM GRUNTS]
Thank you for teaching me
what I'm fighting for.
But my father taught me how.
Come on.
[POWERS DOWN]
FELICITY:
Oliver, Lance did it.
It's over.
If I've learned anything
as a successful businessman, it's...
[COUGHS]
"Redundancy.
[GROANS]
Felicity...
...there's another device.
There's two of them.
LANCE:
What the hell's happening?
Okay, that's enough.
I turned the damn thing off.
Merlyn had a second device.
Laurel. She's at CNRI.
Go. Go!
Laurel.
- Oliver?
- Are you okay?
Yeah.
[S053]
The damage seems to be contained
on the east side...
-...past Wells Street.
- Laurel.
- Are you gonna be okay?
- Go, Oliver. Go, go, go.
Help. Please.
Please! Help me!
Tommy.
What are you doing here?
I kind of figured
that you might come back to CNRI.
[TOMMY GRUNTING]
You came here for me?
I love you.
Get up. Go. Go.
I'm right behind you.
LANCE:
Laurel. Laurel.
- Dad. Dad.
- Oh, sweetie.
- No. No. Tommy!
- No. Laurel. Laurel.
- No, you can't. You can't.
- I love him!
Let go of me.
It's too late. It's too late, it's too late.
I'm sorry.
LAUREL:
Tommy!
Please, I want to help him.
- Get it off.
- Okay.
You're gonna be fine.
Another thing, unh,
we've got to disagree on.
- Tommy.
-ls--? ls Laurel safe?
Is Laurel safe?
I tried to get her out of here.
Yeah, yeah, you did.
You saved her.
All right, let me get you out of here.
You're gonna be fine.
Oliver, stop.
I'm sorry.
No. Don't apologize.
I was angry.
And I was jealous. I...
I am my father.
No. No, you're not.
Did--? Did you kill him?
No.
- Thank you.
- No, no.
Tommy.
It should have been me.
Open your eyes, Tommy.
Open your eyes.
[English - US - SDH]