Previously on
Arrow and The Flash...
Guys, this isn't a meteor.
We've been calling them
the Dominators.
We learned they were abducting humans
to gather intel about us.
If they decide to attack,
no military can stop them.
- You can't do this alone.
- I don't plan to.
Guys! Thanks for coming.
Barry, I thought
you were bringing an alien?
This is my friend,
Kara Danvers. Supergirl.
Call Lyla, tell her these Dominators
aren't here peacefully.
So, how was your run?
You know how it was,
I told you about it in the shower.
Here you go.
- How could I forget?
- Hmm.
Dinah Laurel Lance,
will you marry me?
I think I already answered that question.
Right.
Okay, time to get ready,
my sister will be here soon.
Any word from Felicity?
Only that Oliver, John, and Thea
have been abducted by aliens.
She actually made that sound normal.
I got every traffic cam from here
to Central City looking for them.
Yeah, like traffic cams are gonna
help against alien invaders.
You know what, it'll probably help more
than you trying to pretend
to be Oliver Queen.
Nothing to pretend about.
Gotta keep in shape,
so when these ETs show up,
I can kick their collective asses.
Yeah, you'll have better luck
on the salmon ladder.
My whole life, I've waited to see
a sign of intelligent life.
Now that I'm seeing it,
they're not intelligent at all,
they're just mean.
I can't believe it.
Try to start.
Guys, this is Cisco Ramon,
of S.T.A.R. Labs.
Curtis. Big fan.
- Rene Ramirez.
- Rory Regan.
Okay. Curtis, you're tall.
Rene, and Rory.
That's two Rorys I know now.
The other one, he's a douche though.
- You're not a douche, are you?
- No.
Okay. Good,
I just had to make sure, right?
Guys, we have to find Oliver and company,
and I'm not talking about the cherished
Disney animated film
starring Billy Joel, okay?
I'm talking, I gotta vibe, all right?
I need something to vibe off of,
something personal?
I got one of his old bows here somewhere.
That'll do.
Um, for those of us
who don't know you as well,
not me, 'cause I feel like
we're best friends,
and we've known each other
for a long time.
Uh, what are you going to do exactly?
Oh, right. Uh, I'm about to vibe.
It's this thing I do
where I touch something,
I can not only see the past,
I can see the future,
but most importantly,
I can see where people are.
So you're one of them, a meta-human.
Yeah.
Don't sound too excited about it.
Okay, so this is it.
Just, please don't break it.
Any more than it already is broken.
Okay, go.
I saw them.
They were in some kind
of stasis, like a ship.
It's a little Alien,
a little Star Trek, J.J. Abrams style,
and a whole lot of tech.
- You said tech!
- Yes, I said tech.
It's an alien spaceship, Felicity,
these guys aren't amateurs.
I think where she's going is,
if we had some,
we might be able download
some intel off it, like,
including everyone's location.
- Yes!
- Hold, please.
- Yes.
- That's what I meant.
- In fact.
- Thank you. Always got my back.
- Of course, yeah. Of course, I do.
What about this?
I took it off the Dominator ship
that crashed in Central City.
- What?
- We're gonna hack alien tech.
This is seriously the best day
of my entire life!
You didn't have to get me a gift, Speedy.
It's just a little
pre-rehearsal dinner gesture.
- Well, "little" is right.
- It's called a "Hozen."
It symbolizes reconnecting,
like you did with Laurel.
Thea, it's a rock.
It's a very thoughtful gesture
from your amazingly loving sister.
- Thank you.
- Yeah, that's better.
Wow. What's going on here?
Thea gave me a rock.
Let's go, champ,
we got a 6:00 appointment
at the tailors, gotta fight traffic.
Oh, Dad, you know
I'm not much of a fighter.
Tell that to the paparazzo you punched.
- Ten years ago!
- Still.
Might as well be a lifetime.
You're practically
a completely different person.
You both are.
Don't start crying again, Momma,
just save all the tears
for the actual wedding.
I think what your mother's trying to say,
is that both of us feel blessed
to have watched the two of you grow up.
Whoa! Sweet reflexes.
God.
How much luggage did you bring?
Thank you.
What do you think, you're moving in?
I wish.
- I miss you.
- I miss you, too.
This is beautiful.
Thanks.
Ollie got it for me.
- Is it a bird?
- It's a canary.
Sara?
I just really missed you.
A tux is a good look on you.
Never really felt like my thing.
Maybe you'd be more comfortable
in a suit and tie.
Dad, come on.
I get sworn in as Mayor
in less than two months.
I don't have time to find a
replacement CEO for Queen Consolidated.
What about, um...
Walter Steele?
The Board won't back him.
Besides, QC is a family company.
It should stay in the family.
Dad, I wanna make my own name.
I don't just wanna rely on yours.
Oliver, if you don't do it,
the Board's gonna push
to accept Ray Palmer's buyout offer.
- I...
- What?
I don't know.
- Excuse me.
- Excuse yourself.
Watches, wallets, phones.
What're you, deaf?
Trying to catch a bullet?
- Take it easy.
- I'll shoot your ass right here.
Hey!
- Get away from him.
- You want a piece of this?
Are you all right?
Yeah.
You could've been killed.
Why would you do a thing like that?
Wow. Mom is totally gonna freak out.
That's probably why
she doesn't need to know.
Yeah, she probably
wouldn't believe the part
about the guy in a hood, anyway, so.
Actually, your brother was the one
who came to my rescue first.
You're quite the hero, son.
Oh, my God.
I heard what happened.
Are you okay?
Yeah. Hey, hey.
I'm fine, I'm fine.
Oliver. Oliver, are you okay?
No, I'm fine, I'm...
Probably just need some air, I'm gonna...
I'll see you at the restaurant.
I'm so conflicted.
You know, on the one hand,
I get to hack
actual extraterrestrial technology.
But, on the other hand, ETs are real,
but unfortunately they're dickwads
who are gonna Kill us.
Don't worry, it's gonna work out.
You're not gonna tell me
God has a plan, are you?
- Well...
- Look,
I respect your religion and all,
I just find it a little hard to believe
that there's some divine plan
to the universe
which also includes space monsters.
What's that?
I like call it my 3PO processor.
"I am fluent in over six million
forms of communication."
And it speaks Dominator?
I didn't specifically program it for that,
but in my defense, I didn't know
the Dominators even existed.
Let's see if it works.
I feel like Elliot in E. T.
"It's working! It's working!"
- Your tech guy quotes movies?
- Yeah.
Real original.
- No, no, no.
- No, no.
What happened?
We made an idiot move,
that's what happened. Ow!
We tried to plug human tech
into a Dominator power source,
of course it overloaded.
We need a regulator, okay?
Something that can handle
the Dominator juice.
Van Horn Industries was working on
a prototype for NASA over a year ago.
Maybe they perfected it by now.
Yeah, they perfected it, all right.
So much so, somebody's already stolen it.
According to SCPD reports, it was
a doctor named Laura Washington?
A doctor? That doesn't make any sense.
It does if she's been artificially
augmenting herself with stolen technology,
because why would the universe
make anything easy?
It says here, implants give her
enhanced strength, stamina,
and electricity-based powers.
Well, it's nothing we can't handle.
That's everything we can't handle.
Come on, Felicity, I mean,
this might be our only chance
to find Oliver and everyone else.
That's why I'm calling in reinforcements.
- Oh, hey, Captain Lance.
- Hey. I was just on my way out.
Do you have a minute for me?
Yeah. Actually,
I should've called you earlier.
Detective Hilton told me
about what happened tonight. You okay?
Oh, yeah, my dad and I are fine.
Good, good.
Well, we got the guy in custody.
Because of the guy with the bow and arrow.
Yeah, yeah, we've been calling him
The Hood. Some kinda vigilante.
If I've got the time right,
your rehearsal dinner is practically now.
Freeze!
Oliver?
Do you have any leads
on who The Hood might be or...
This is the last thing
you should be thinking about
the night before your wedding.
Or is that what's going on here?
- What do you mean?
- You getting cold feet?
No, not at all, I promise.
Good, 'cause I would hate
to have to shoot you
for breaking my girl's heart, okay?
Paperwork would be hell.
In truth, I'm probably
a little bit more shaken up
by the whole mugging than maybe I thought.
Well, you know,
I got just the thing to fix that.
A few drinks at your rehearsal dinner.
I'm buyin', come on.
Yeah, actually, Captain Lance,
I'll meet you there.
- You sure?
- Yeah, I'll see you there.
Actually, uh, Oliver,
something I wanna say.
You know, um,
when you and Laurel were kids,
you know, teenagers,
I... Well, let's face it,
I didn't like you much.
Well.
Yeah, I thought you were a rich,
entitled punk.
I was.
But since then, Oliver,
you have grown into a hell of a man.
The kinda guy I'm proud
to have as my son-in-law.
Thank you, Captain Lance.
- See you at that dinner.
- I'll see you there.
All right.
He's not coming.
Don't worry, he'll be here.
You know Ollie's never been on time
for anything in his entire life.
You didn't see him earlier,
he had this look on his face,
like he was backing out.
No way. He loves you.
He looked like everything
that he knew was wrong.
I'm pretty sure that every guy has
that look the night before their wedding.
You know, there was a time
when I thought the two of you
would actually hook up.
You know I prefer girls.
Oh, hey.
Ah. Miss Lance. Hi, I'm Ray Palmer,
a business associate of Oliver's father.
I just wanted to say congratulations.
Thank you, it's really nice to meet you.
Uh, this is my sister, Sara.
Have we met before?
Ray!
No, I think I'd remember.
You just seem very familiar.
- Excuse us.
- Yeah.
Are you sure you prefer girls? He's hot.
Oh, wow.
What the hell?
Hi. We have an unauthorized entry!
What are you doing here?
How did you find this place?
- My name is Oliver Queen...
- I know who you are.
Everybody knows who you are.
- How did you find this place?
- Better question is why?
He's getting married tomorrow.
- Get out.
- Wait...
Get out!
Wait, wait!
No one can know my secret.
Your name is John.
- What did you say?
- Your name...
ils John Diggle.
My brother needed me.
No. No.
No! No, no, no.
Bad idea.
How do you know all this?
I think we've met before
and you were my bodyguard.
And you think I'm funny.
You're thinking of my brother, Andy.
He's in personal security.
You were in the military.
105th Airborne out of Kandahar.
Did a lot of things back then
I'm not proud of.
I came back here to...
atone, I guess.
Uh, John, stranger danger?
Might wanna ease up on the info dump.
Felicity Smoak?
Felicity...
This isn't right.
I don't think that any of...
of this is right.
I don't think that you're the Green Arrow.
And I don't think Andy's alive.
John, I think you killed him.
I hate being right all the time.
Listen to me. You're having
some kind of psychotic break.
Go back to your family, your fiancée,
and your fancy house,
and you're gonna forget about all of this!
Felicity is right,
you've got everything.
Everything, man.
Stop trying to throw it all away.
You should've taken him up on
his offer to carry you.
- It was awesome.
- Nobody's carrying me anywhere.
It's so cool Felicity reached out,
it's awesome to meet you.
Yeah, well, wait till you meet her.
Hey, everyone!
Oh, I've had enough of this.
Yo, you want some company?
Not really.
Right. Um, so, what exactly is it
you've "had enough of"?
Nothing. I just didn't know
there were flying meta-humans now.
No sign of Washington.
Yeah, Supergirl's not a meta,
she's an alien.
- Oh, well, I'm one of the good ones.
- There are no good ones.
Hey, what's your damage, man?
My "damage" is that people like you two
have the power of gods,
yet you think you can make
the world a better place
just by putting on a fancy costume.
No, we think we make the world
a better place because...
- Well, we do.
- Yeah.
Look around.
Moment he showed up,
metas start appearing everywhere.
Now you show up, and we get aliens.
Superpowers are evil, man,
and I don't want anything to do with them
or with either of you.
Thea, you have grown into
the most beautiful young woman.
It's just a bridesmaid's dress, Mom.
No one actually looks good in one.
Well, you do.
You look fulfilled.
Yeah, I don't know about that one, Mom,
but I do know I have never been happier.
Good.
- And I love you, Mom.
- Oh.
My baby girl.
Mmm!
Okay, we're gonna wrinkle the dress.
No, I really don't care.
Okay.
No! Mom!
Thea?
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Laurel, I...
Don't you know it's bad luck
to see the bride before the wedding?
Or skip out on the rehearsal dinner?
I know, I said I was sorry.
In a text.
Sara, can you give us
a few minutes, please?
You're lucky
I'm not a trained assassin or anything.
Oh, wow.
You, um, you look beautiful.
I called you over 20 times last night.
I can't explain last night, I just...
Today,
today I wanna marry you.
Well, that's good
because there are guests here...
No, not with guests,
not in a few hours, now!
Laurel, I need to get out of here.
- We can elope.
- Oliver...
I'm being serious, I don't know
what's going on with me right now,
I just know that I want to be with
you as quickly as humanly possible.
What is going on with you?
Last night, somebody reminded me
that I have everything,
and I don't wanna give it up.
I'm afraid that I'm gonna give it up.
Well, that's very sweet of you,
but we have over 200 guests coming
and your parents,
they've have spent a fortune
on this wedding.
I know, I'm just...
I'm sorry if this is confusing,
or if I'm scaring you,
but the only thing in the world
that makes sense to me right now
is that I love you.
And I'm gonna take that job
at Queen Consolidated,
and I swear to God,
I'm gonna work every single day
to be the man you fell in love with.
Sorry about the interruption,
the Russian lady downstairs told me
to come right up.
You got a minute to talk?
I'll be right back.
Now, what happened to,
"ll should just go back to my life"?
Well, look, have you been getting
out into the city lately?
Seeing maybe a particular building
that shouldn't be there?
- Smoak Technologies.
- Yeah.
Yeah, well, when I was with my dad,
I saw it, and it, felt...
- It felt wrong.
- Right.
Felicity Smoak says she never owned
a building or a company.
I don't know what's going on here.
But when you left,
I started having these...
Visions, right? Like, uh,
memory flashes, I'm getting them, too.
John, what is happening to us?
I have no idea. I've seen some weird
things in the 'Stan,
even stranger things as The Hood,
but this...
Look, when you left, I tried
to draw one of these
"memory flashes" as you call 'em.
I've never been much of an artist.
This is what I came up with.
- What the hell?
- I don't know.
I've been remembering things.
It's like they're dreams, but they're not.
John, I don't think
that any of this is real.
No, we're real. But whatever's playing
these head games with us,
- I don't think it's fully working.
- Are you sure?
'Cause the Queen's Gambit...
They've put me into a world where
I never got on my father's boat.
Oliver, I don't know if these
are memories, or feelings,
but I think you're a hero, and I don't
think it's because of any boat.
These head games aren't over.
They are gonna push back
against whatever we do.
Push back?
Like how?
Like that.
How did I do that?
All right, this is hard to explain.
Well, start trying.
We think...
We think we're in some sort
of shared hallucination.
That's crazy.
I mean, not as crazy as me knowing
kung fu, but it is definitely up there.
That wasn't kung fu, that was jeet kune do
and I think that you learned it
in a spot called Nanda Parbat.
Nothing you are saying is making sense,
none of this makes sense!
Okay, look. All right.
Sara, what is the last thing you remember?
- I don't know!
- I mean, before you came here, yesterday.
What is the last thing that you remember?
You remembered something. Come on.
Sara, come on, concentrate!
There was a fight.
There was five of us, and then...
- And then we were taken.
- Taken where?
I don't know.
All right, there were five of us.
Who were the other two?
Ray Palmer, and...
and, Thea.
I mean, if this some kind of dream,
or "shared hallucination,"
- then how do we wake up?
- By getting out of here.
The Smoak Technologies building,
maybe the reason why that place
seems so strange is because
that's the way we get out of here.
Wherever here is.
What do you want?
You stole something
from Van Horn Industries.
You mean this?
Yeah, hand it over.
Or what?
I'll take it from you.
I doubt that.
Do you wanna give up?
I'm just getting started.
Soam I.
That was awesome.
There's the regulator. She seems pretty
attached to it.
Maybe just remove it?
Okay, yeah.
Thanks for the save.
- Is that all you have to say?
- I don't do apologies, sweetheart.
But if super-powers are a thing,
it's good there are guys like you
to help the world.
You know, the green guy would've kicked
my ass if I talked to him like that.
- Oh, yeah. Yeah, we know.
- That he would.
Yep.
_
It's too bad Tommy couldn't
make it, though.
Well, they've got him working triple
shifts at the hospital these days.
Besides, Chicago isn't exactly next door.
Can't believe he's a doctor now.
Well, he says the same thing about you,
Ms. "Entrepreneur."
Yeah, I don't think running Verdant
makes me an entrepreneur.
No, but it makes you successful.
Your father should be very proud
of the woman you've grown into.
Ray, I need to talk to you.
Sara, right?
- Yeah.
- Hi. Um...
This is my fiancée, Felicity Smoak.
Hi, nice to meet you.
Oh, you're Laurel's sister, right?
Yeah. Can I steal him for a second?
Yeah, yeah. Yeah, okay.
Ray,
doesn't this all feel weird to you?
A little.
I need you to think.
She's not my fiancée.
My fiancée's name is Anna.
Or it was.
What's happening?
You're remembering.
Son, don't you think
you should be getting your tuxedo on?
- Um...
- Are you all right, Oliver?
I just need to speak with Thea.
I think I saw her talking to Malcolm
over by the ice sculpture.
- Yeah, okay.
- Son.
Think you need to calm down.
We both do.
You're acting terribly strange.
Your mother and I are concerned
if you keep up this unstable behavior,
that is not going to finish well.
That is not going to finish well.
I'm just saying.
Laurel, the company...
This is your life now.
No, itisn't.
Oliver.
I'm sorry.
Speedy.
She knows, Ollie.
She knows, and she doesn't wanna go.
Better question is, why would you want to?
Because none of this is real.
It's real enough, okay?
It's better than our real lives,
and in this life,
Laurel is alive, my parents are alive.
But those are not your parents.
They remember the only lullaby that would
actually work to put me to sleep.
They remember every day of my life, okay?
They even smell like them, Ollie.
They're not them, Thea.
I want them to be,
but they're not.
Where are John and Ray?
They're waiting outside.
Give us a few minutes?
We can't stay here, Speedy.
No matter how much we want to, we can't.
Why not?
What is waiting for us
wherever we are right now?
Nothing, nothing but
pain and suffering.
Thea, we have responsibilities,
we have people who count on us.
There's Flash,
and Supergirl and people
with actual powers now.
Whatever needs to be done,
they can handle it.
We...
We finally have a chance to be happy.
I mean, why can't you just,
for a second, accept that maybe
this is your reward
for all of the sacrifices you have made?
I didn't make those sacrifices
for a reward, Thea.
I did what I did
because I thought it was right.
And seeing all of this has just,
it has shown me
that there is still so much more to do,
So, please,
I'm begging you to come with me
because I cannot do it alone.
I can't lose them again.
I can't lose my family.
Okay.
Okay. All right. Just...
I want you to be well,
I want you to be happy.
I love you, Thea.
Where's Thea?
Thea's staying.
Have you explained to Ray
what we have to do?
Yeah, apparently we have
to get to an office tower
that my non-fiancée doesn't own,
which is a little strange.
All that, coming from the guy who's been
having memories that he's able to shrink.
Well, whatever we're doing,
we have to do it fast,
because whatever the Dominators
have done to us,
they would've built in safeguards
that are probably manifestations from
our memories designed to keep us here.
They're not real.
Well, they certainly look real,
but let's not get into that right now.
Speedy?
Yeah, I had a change of heart, okay?
Like I said,
I can't lose my family again.
Your father's still alive, Thea.
Your real father, at least.
Unfortunately, this is gonna be
a little less satisfying for me
than killing your sister.
Ollie!
Sara, Sara,
what's going on here?
Laurel, look, I can't explain but.
I have to go. We have to go.
What?
No, no, no, whatever it is, we can fix it.
Look, we can't.
Some things you just can't fix.
Ollie? Ollie.
Ollie, what's happening?
What...
I'm sorry.
The person you fell in love with,
it's not me.
And I never deserved that love,
and you always deserved better.
Please.
I love you.
I love you. Don't... Don't go.
Okay, John. What now?
Guys, I don't think that belongs there.
Okay, that's either the way out of here,
or we gotta click our heels together
three times and say,
- "There's no place like home."
- And if that doesn't work?
It has to work. He's running out of time.
Come on.
You're never without me,
my beautiful boy.
There's nothing else to say,
except I could not be more proud.
You've become someone else,
you've become something else.
You honor the dead by fighting,
and you are not done fighting!
I know I called you a murderer,
but you are not,
you are a hero.
You saved my life.
You gave me purpose.
This time, we had to save you.
I know who you are
in your bones, Oliver,
and that person doesn't give up.
This is your responsibility now.
Where are we?
You all right?
It may not be real, but it still hurts
like a son of a bitch.
Uh, guys?
There's something you really need to see.
Any luck with the regulator
we took off CyberWoman?
"CyberWoman"?
I think I'm starting to like you guys.
The regulator worked,
but my translator did not.
The only thing I got back
from the Dominator tech was soup.
What? What, no, no, no, no, this...
- No, this just looks random.
- It's not.
It's Gematria.
- Huh?
- Gematria is the numerology of...
Of the Torah. How did I not see that?
For the gentiles and those of us who
actually had social lives in high school,
what the hell are you talking about?
In Hebrew, each letter possesses
a numerical value.
Gematria is the calculation
of the numerical equivalence
of letters, words, or phrases.
You mean the Dominators' language
is based off the Old Testament?
Or shares commonalities, at least.
You wanted proof of a
"divine plan to the universe," right?
Guys, I'm getting references
to five Terran captives here.
Okay, the signal is coming from...
That's not possible.
"-3.127 latitude,
"-23.7987 longitude..."
That doesn't make any sense.
Geographical coordinates
don't have any negative numbers.
I mean, they do, only when...
Oh, my God, I think I know where they are.
Okay, so how do we find our way
out of an alien spacecraft?
This way. Even though
it's an alien technology,
certain principles of design
are universal.
Or not.
Ray was right,
certain principles of design
are universal.
You think you can fly one of these things?
I'm hoping that between
you, me, Ray, and Sara,
someone can fly one of these things.
Okay, now what?
Ray?
Um, now might be a good time
to find the owner's manual.
And Mom said I wouldn't amount
to anything if I didn't go to college.
Uh, really hope you hit autopilot 'cause
I don't see any controls on this thing.
Hold on, we got incoming.
How do you know?
Lucky guess?
We need to find a way to steer this thing,
or we're not gonna last very long.
Oliver, nice clothes.
Shop at an alien Gap?
- Not funny.
- Well, lucky for you guys,
the Waverider has a machine that
replicates old clothes and weapons.
- Hi, I'm Nate Heywood.
- Hi! Thea.
And this is exactly twice as many
spaceships as I ever thought I'd be on.
Well, actually, it's a time-ship.
How'd you find us?
I didn't. Your nerd army
back on Earth did.
I'm gonna take Digg to the Medbay,
have Gideon fix him up.
Whoever Gideon is.
- Get out!
- Thanks for the save.
No problem.
Except for all our other problems.
Like what, Ray?
After we woke up,
I got a look at the tech the Dominators
were using to keep us under.
They're using a neuromorphic interface
similar to how I manipulate the Atom suit.
And, wait... What does that mean?
I think,
the shared hallucination
was to keep our minds occupied
- while the Dominators...
- While the Dominators what?
Well, while they probed our subconscious.
I'm guessing, looking for intel.
Wait, maybe they didn't choose us
at random.
Maybe they chose us
because we couldn't fight back.
Because none of you are meta-humans.
Bigger question,
what intel were they after?
What is their plan?
Gesundheit!
It's what one of the Dominators
said to another.
Which sounds like the beginning
of a not so funny joke, but... Gideon?
Translating.
You ever think that our lives
would really get this weird?
The phrase loosely translates to,
"We are nearing completion of the weapon.”
What weapon?
I'm afraid I have no idea,
but I'm tracking the Dominator mothership
you escaped from.
And it appears to be on a direct course
for Earth.
English - SDH