Previously on "Arrow"...
H-how is this real?
- This is Novu?
- How do we stop a god?
I'm working on it.
Hello, bunker! So why'd
you call in the big guns?
Earth-2 was destroyed
by a wave of energy.
So it's probably powerful
enough to stop a god.
Yes, Curtis?
Whatever it is, it is
possible to replicate,
but there's a catch.
It is super illegal because
it requires plutonium.
Luckily, there's a
guy, a military general.
-Ok. Where is he? ‘Russia.
You can bring back my Earth?
The recovery of your universe
will require a single task.
You must betray Oliver Queen.
So that's the
secret? A tennis ball.
You know how you
use a honing steel
to keep the edge
on a chef's knife?
I don't really cook.
That makes sense.
All right.
This keeps you sharp.
Only a direct, precise
hit will pin the ball.
If you are off
just a little bit...
it deflects.
Ready?
Toss it.
Thought this was
supposed to be hard.
This is the warm-up.
Ready.
So specialty arrows,
and each one has
a specific purpose.
What does this one do?
Explosive arrow,
lighter payload,
meant to divert and disable.
Acidic arrow, meant
to breach covertly
or weaken structurally.
Bolo arrow-- to
secure and subdue.
These are just tools.
If you rely on them too
much, they become crutches.
Then why have them?
To get out of a fight
or to end one before it begins.
Not bad.
So what's next?
Hyah!
Nyssa taught you well.
Mom made sure of it.
How did you do that?
Variable acceleration.
All right? It's
all about timing.
You keep practicing,
you keep flowing,
it just becomes second nature.
All right. Again.
You don't want a break maybe?
She's a machine, Dad.
They don't need breaks.
And speaking of machines, I
have something to show you guys.
I created a facial
recognition algorithm
to find that general
that Curtis told us about,
which was a lot
harder than it sounds,
because no offense to Felicity,
but these computers are,
like, a million years old.
And Russia is a
very big country.
William, Right. Sorry.
His name is General Alexi Burov,
and he's in Moscow.
Curtis said that
the energy wave
that destroyed Earth-2
can be replicated, which
means we can weaponize it.
And right before
he went off the grid,
Burov was working on
plans for a weapon called
the pulse wave generator.
All right, We need those plans.
We also need plutonium.
It's the only thing that can
power Burov's machine.
Wait. Plutonium as
in a nuclear bomb?
“Mm-hmm, “Where
are we gonna get that?
Bialya. There's a
facility near the border
where all kinds of
radioactive material is stored.
I'm thinking a two-man fire
team can get the job done.
Okay. Want to take Connor?
-No, no.
Actually, he wanted
to check in on Sandra.
And he promised
to stay out of sight.
I have someone
else in mind to help.
Okay. I'd like the two of you
to accompany me
and Laurel to Russia.
Okay?
Yeah.
Okay. We'll wheels up at dawn.
Well, better go buy a parka.
Is it really that
cold in Russia?
Oh, oh! You are
so not ready for this.
Things seem to be going
pretty well with the kids.
Never thought I'd
get to know them.
Not like this.
Is that why you invited
them to go with you?
Well, I mean, I promised Mia
that I would keep training her.
And I think it's very valuable
for them to keep seeing
how we operate in the field.
And you're sure Russia's a
good place for a tutorial, Oliver?
That was a very
dark time for you.
It was a long time ago, though.
I'm a better man.
I'm a different man.
I think that I can
teach them good
without showing them the bad.
Hope so.
What the hell are
you doing here?
Our mutual friend sent me.
You're working with
the Monitor. Why?
-It's complicated. Really?
Because he destroyed
my entire Earth.
That seems pretty
straightforward to me.
He didn't.
Mar Novu is trying
to save worlds,
not destroy them.
All that stuff about grief,
you pretending like you
were trying to help me.
I should've known better.
I wasn't pretending.
It's a little hard to believe,
Lyla, after all the lying.
It doesn't matter
what you believe.
You're here just
the same as I am.
Now, do you want to get
your Earth back or not?
What does he want me to do?
Oliver's going to Russia
to retrieve plans
to build a weapon.
You need to get them first.
I thought Oliver
was your friend.
He is, but this is
bigger than him,
bigger than any of us.
Well, whatever the
Monitor offered you must be
really something for
you to be able to betray
everyone that you care about.
I am doing this for
them, to protect them.
Are you going to help me?
Yeah.
1 will.
Contact me when it's done.
And here I thought I was
supposed to be the bad guy.
Help you?
Yeah. I was looking for Jason.
Yo, Jason! You got a visitor.
How you doing, Jason?
How'd you find me?
Oliver's son--
William. He found you.
Oliver's son.
Isn't he, like, 13?
Heh! Yeah, well,
it's a long story.
I have a feeling you
didn't come all this way
just to catch me up to speed.
I didn't. I need your help, Roy.
Whatever you're about to
ask me to do, I can't. 'm sorry.
You haven't even heard
what I have to say, man.
‘Cause I don't need
to. You know what I did.
I'm not a hero anymore, John,
not with my condition.
So you're just gonna
walk out on me,
same way you did Thea?
No.
Thea told Oliver that you left,
man, without even saying good-bye.
It was for the best
for the both of us.
I needed a fresh start,
which is what I'm doing now.
Ok, it was...
it was good to see you, John.
Roy...
look, man,
I know earlier this year
was a struggle for you,
but this crisis is a
threat that's bigger
than anything we've ever faced.
I wouldn't be here, man,
if we did not need you.
If 1 decide to help you,
it'll be a one-time thing.
That's all I'm asking.
I hope you don't
mind, but, uh...
I brought you a
change of clothes.
So this is Russia.
Not what you were expecting?
I just thought there'd
be a lot less dirt.
Is very rude to insult
man's homeland.
Hello, Anatoly.
Oliver Queen...
my brother.
Oh, you think maybe
I punch you again?
Never even crossed my mind.
Welcome to Russia,
my favorite American.
Now, I have seen some
very crazy things in my life,
but adult children of Oliver
Queen sitting in my bar.
I hope you do not
think badly of me.
Last time we met,
you were little,
and I was on wrong
side of history.
I like this one already.
I was surprised to learn
that you were in Russia.
I thought the Maldives
would be permanent.
Oh, with Diaz dead,
50 reason to stay away.
You got bored.
I miss borscht.
So I reinvent myself.
Bar owner. Hm.
But I got inspired, too.
1 got really good
recipe for pifia colada.
You should try. It's delicious.
Who wouldn't want to
be reminded of the tropics
in these cold Russian winters?
Well, apparently, his customers.
Nice to see this
one's still charmer.
How's the search
going for General Burov?
Well, it's not very easy.
But I do have
friends I can call.
I know, but I--I don't
want them involved in this.
Why not?
If he has friends
that can help, it-
Because, Mia, with due respect,
the people that
Anatoly is describing...
aren't really friends.
Let's just keep this
one in the family, ok?
All right.
1 work to find Burov hard way.
You really think
an energy weapon's
gonna stop this Monitor guy?
Yeah well, that's the hope.
Why this place?
The military stores all
its excess plutonium here.
The problem is
it's impenetrable.
Which is why you
asked me to come.
You need a B and E
expert to get inside?
Yeah. Well, actually, it's
more of a smash and grab.
There's a shipment
coming in tonight.
We are gonna steal the plutonium
before it gets inside.
Go. Go. Go.
Why not bring Dinah or Rene?
They have their
hands full in Star City.
Must be weird, right?
Oliver meeting his future son.
Yeah. Well, he's
not the only one.
In the future, I adopt
Ben Turner's son, Connor.
He's an agent in Knightwatch,
future version of AR.G.US.
Well, it sounds like he
would've been a great candidate
for this mission.
You didn't need
me for this, John.
So what are we
really doing here?
You said you wanted to atone.
Well, you can't do
that by fixing cars.
You do that by
rejoining the team.
I know you think you
can't control your bloodlust.
That's only because you haven't
figured out a way that works.
Because there is no way.
So whatever you're about to say,
I don't want to hear it.
Look, we're already here,
so I'm gonna help you.
But once we're done,
I'm going to disappear
to a place where even
William can't find me.
I have classic bad
news/good news.
I find general Burov.
Is that the bad news? I'm
confused about the order.
Bad news is, is he is
man who likes betting
and blood, which means
only place to find him,
Krovavaya Banya.
"The Bloodbath."
Oh. Heh. Doesn't
that sound lovely?
It's not lovely.
It's a fight club.
Oh. That sounds
like where I met her.
He met you where?
Well, when I first left home,
I had to find a way
to make money.
So I fought, and I won,
Like father, like
daughter, eh, tovarisch?
You, me, and Laurel
will go to the
club to find Burov.
You two are gonna stay here.
Did you not hear
what I just said?
1 grew up in fight clubs.
You did not grow
up in fight clubs
that were run by the Bratva.
Then why did you
bring us on this mission
if you're not gonna let us help?
This is not a regular
mission. This is the Bratva.
They are terrible people,
and you guys are my kids.
Yes, but we're not children.
Well, you are when Ilook at you.
And I'm sorry, but this
is how it's gonna be.
Okay.
So this is what the
Russians do for fun.
I assume that we want to
have our chat with the general
without crossing the Bratva.
We want to move quickly
and keep our heads low.
There is General.
Damn it. So boring.
General Burov...
I am Anatoly
Knyazev, Danik's friend.
Danik has big mouth.
What do you want?
Your expertise...
with something sensitive.
Lucky for you,
this fight is boring.
Let us go talk.
I abandoned this pulse
wave generator project.
Too unpredictable, bad business.
So...
why should I give to you,
Kapiushon?
Maybe you should've kept
your secret identity secret?
So this means that
you won't be giving
us the plans willingly.
No need for unpleasantness.
1 am willing to make deal.
Good. What do you want?
A fighter,
someone to upset the favorite
so I cannot be bored.
Should be easy for
you, Kapiushon, no?
So I win, and then
you give us the plans.
Done deal.
Excellent. 1 will go make it so.
You saw that goliath, right?
He is twice your size.
So I give him half a chance.
You got a problem?
Nyet.
Oliver seems to think
you are hero now.
I'm not so sure.
I think you may be
like snow leopard
who cannot change spots.
You changed yours.
Worry less about me and more
about your friend over there.
I'll sweep the perimeter.
Wow.
Impressive, no?
Anatoly, let's
get the car ready.
Very good! I don't think you
have many fans here, though.
But I am man of my word.
Not so fast.
This one needs to
learn not to put nose
in other people's business.
Oleg, wha--what a pleasure,
Did you really think you
could conduct business
on Bratva territory
without me knowing?
Of course not. This simply
fighter collecting his winnings.
He's no mere fighter,
are you, Oliver Queen?
How does he know who you are?
Everyone in Russia
knows Kapiushon.
We have no fight
with you or the Bratva,
That is what we came for.
When we have it, we're gone.
The general only operates
here because we say he can.
And we did not say.
No!
Mia.
You okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
“Where are we? Um.
Yeah, probably
some Bratva hideout.
I told you to stay put, Mia.
What were you thinking?
That we needed
to finish the mission.
You understand that I
had it handled, correct?
Uh, apparently not, considering
we are tied up in
a creepy basement.
Why did he call you "Kapiushon"?
Kapiushon is a nickname
that the Bratva gave me.
It means "hood."
You were a member of the Bratva.
You should've told me.
1 didn't want you or
William involved in this.
- can handle myself.
-That is not what this is about.
Then what is it about?
Ugh. Damn it.
We tied your thumbs.
You went to a lot
of trouble to get this.
Even we couldn't crack
its security encryptions.
Must be worth a great deal.
Tell me what it is.
No.
I will only ask once more.
You have 5 seconds.
5... Don't tell him anything.
4.3...
2...
They're plans...
For a weapon that
Burov's building.
Was that so hard?
Now we can move
on to next phase.
Ok, what are the chances
that my father and sister
are in the clutches of the Russian
mob but aren't already dead?
Slim and getting slimmer every
second we do not find them.
Ok, their phones aren't online.
Why aren't their phones online?
Will have been destroyed
so as not to trace them.
Aren't the people in your family
constantly injecting each
other with tracking devices?
Normally, I would
say, "God, I hope not,"
but now I guess I can
see the advantages.
Have you ever hacked
a CCTV camera?
-No. Well, congratulations.
You're about to
learn the only upside
of a Russian surveillance state.
Okay.
The shipment
should be here soon.
What made you wait till
now to give me your big pitch?
I'm guessing Connor told you
something bad about me in the future.
Not just about you.
Tell me.
William finds you on Lian Yu
after being there for years,
apparently, in some
self-imposed exile.
I never get rid of my bloodlust?
You knew all that, and you still
thought you could come save me?
Because there's
more to your story.
You may have started
on Lian Yu, Roy,
but that's not where you ended.
Felicity sent William
to that island to find you
because she believed in you.
You go back to Star City,
man. You work with the kids.
You help them
save the city, Roy.
How is that possible?
Because you found the
way to control your bloodlust.
You found that it was
by being part of a team.
You kept your distance because
you believed that you were a danger
to everyone around
you, but the real danger
was believing that you can
deal with your past alone.
It's pretty ballsy
thinking you can give me
the answer 20 years earlier.
Yeah, well, hopefully, this time,
you don't have to wait that long.
Don't touch her.
Itold you everything
that I know!
We will see.
On the line.
No.
Mia, no.
Mi--Mi--Mia!
Ring the bell.
You have 60 seconds.
Begin.
Time is up.
I needed to make sure
you weren't lying
about the drive.
Got it. CCTV footage of
Mia and Dad being taken
into a warehouse on
the east side of town.
Thank you, illegal
Russian satellites.
Great. Well, let's go save day.
Are you ok?
I should've been able to do it.
Oh, I should have
enough slack now.
To do what?
Aah! Uh!
What the hell?
I can dislocate my thumbs.
It's a useful technique
if getting tied to a chair
is gonna become a habit.
You have got to teach
me how to do that.
So you not ring bell.
Still, very impressive
to, uh, not die.
You shouldn't have told
them what was on the drive.
They would've
killed you if I didn't.
Or we would've been
able to escape without you
~giving up the information. Mia.
Okay, can we please just
save the family squabble
until after we have the plans?
Oleg's bound to figure
out how much they're worth.
Well, he's smart businessman.
He will figure
out way to sell it.
We need to figure
out when and where
the sale is happening, and
then we go recover the drive.
Let me guess.
Me and William get
to stay at the bar, right?
You're going home, both of you.
No.
I have a feeling there's
less drama out here.
Yeah.
What do you mean, "no"?
I'm sorry, Dad, but
we just saved you
from being murdered
by a bunch of gangsters.
I'm on team Mia here.
Yeah, but Mia just got
kidnapped by the Bratva.
-So did you.
-I'm your father, all right?
It is my primary
job in the world
to protect you.
We don't need that.
In the future, we're the
ones that are saving the city.
Well, this isn't the future!
This is months after
I was heartbroken
right before I left...
that I couldn't get
you on the phone
at your grandparents'.
So I walked into your room
to look at you one last time,
and you looked back
at me from your crib.
And because you made
the choice to protect us,
I had to spend my
whole life alone.
I didn't have a chance
to get to know my brother,
to get to know you.
I'm sorry that it
worked out that way.
And both of you can decide
on your own how much--
how much you want to hate me
and how much blame
you want to assign.
But I made a promise to
your mother to keep you safe.
And there--there is no world,
there is no universe,
there's no past,
present, or future
where I break it.
Fine.
You ready?
As I'll ever be.
Let's go!
Must be some kind
of tamper alarm.
I'll get the payload.
-['ll keep watch.
Hey, hey! Hey.
Hey, Roy. Roy, look at me, man.
Look at me!
Roy, you're all right.
Y--you got it?
Ido. It's right here.
Let's get the hell out of here.
-Any word from your contact?
-Nyet.
Oh, these things take time.
I don't know about you, but
I could handle drink
without umbrella.
I'm good, thank you.
If by good, you mean--
how you say--moody,
yes, you are.
Is this because you
ruin family vacation?
I have to send them
home for their protection.
Do you not think
they can handle it?
They can handle it. I just--
I want to keep them
away from the Bratva.
You mean keep them
away from your Bratva past.
Dark time for me.
That is understandable.
You are ashamed.
You have truly done
some terrible things.
Thank you for the reminder.
But you also have
done some good things.
It's important that
the kids see both.
Right, but why would I
want to share some of the...
worst mistakes of my
entire life with my children?
That is the thing
about teaching.
It's not about what
you want to say.
It's about what
they need to hear.
Remember first
thing I taught you?
Living is not for the weak.
Your children are
not weak, Oliver.
They're also not children.
Whatever it is you have to say,
they can handle it.
If you do not, they will
never learn to be heroes.
Oof. It would suck
to be that door.
If you're here to give me
a pep talk or whatever,
just don't.
Don't flatter yourself,
I just couldn't stand the
smell of that stale bar anymore.
It smells like cabbage.
That's one more thing I
won't miss about this place.
So you're actually going home.
Why wouldn't I? Dad
doesn't want me here.
Oh, God. I can't
stand pity parties.
Easy for you to say.
And why is that?
You're the Black Canary.
All I've ever heard are stories
about how great you are.
In the future, you
even save me once
like it was nothing.
Are you sure that's actually
me you're talking about?
Okay, you can cut
the false modesty.
Some people are
cut out to be heroes,
others not so much.
Is this really all because you
didn't ring some stupid bell?
Well, I couldn't
save Zoe either.
Every time I try and
live up to my dad
or to prove that I can
do what it is you all do,
1-l fail.
Do you think your
father is any better?
If you're trying to
live up to us, don't.
We are just as flawed as anyone,
especially me.
All you can do is
live up to yourself.
What does that even mean?
Are you really the type of
person that just gives up?
Oh, good.
Do we have time for one
more fight before we leave?
I'm not looking for a fight.
Then stop trying
to send us home.
We're not leaving.
Good because I need your help.
Oleg is selling drive
during bloodbath tonight.
And how are we
supposed to get in?
They know our faces.
Right. We use that
to our advantage.
You and I are going in
the ring together as a team.
You would be helping us get in.
Sorry. I did not have
time to get it dry cleaned.
I'm really more of a behind
the screen kind of guy,
but wow. That is
a nice suit. Huh.
What exactly will
Anatoly and I be doing
while you two are playing
father/daughter fight club moment?
When Oleg realizes that
it's the two of us in the ring,
that'll cause a distraction.
You guys go and steal the drive.
What do you say?
Well, I'm in.
Fancy rich guy is the
role Iwas born to play.
You?
Why the hell not?
Suit up.
Now I see why they
call it the bloodbath.
You sure about this?
Just get us in, please.
Not from you, American.
Well, if it's not about money,
then how about stakes?
Has anyone survived
6 men before?
Nyet.
My guys will fight 6.
You fight next.
Do we really need to be
setting records tonight?
You like a challenge,
right? Just please don't die.
Anatoly, you guys set?
Da. But no sign of high rollers.
Now is good time to strike.
How much time do we have?
Five minutes give or take.
Well, this is gonna be fun,
I've seen what
you can do in there,
so just trust your
instincts, okay? I do.
Nyet..
That's our cue.
Pakhan will still be protected.
I'll deal with the muscle.
You just watch my back.
Tick-tock. You guys
have the plans yet?
Don't move or I'll shoot.
You said watch back.
I got it. Let's move.
I could actually
get used to this.
Congratulations. Now
you my favorite American.
Hey, don't get too excited. He
has a lot of favorite Americans.
Did you talk to John?
1 did. He got the plutonium
with an assist from Roy.
All we have to do is
whip up an energy wave
to destroy an all-knowing
space being. Easy.
Before that, I would
like to propose a toast
to Mia and William.
Couldn't have done
this without you.
Vashe zdorovie.
Actually, here we say prochnost.
Prochnost?
Prochnost. It means strength.
It means a lot more than that.
Um, would you mind
giving me a minute
with these two, please?
- Yes.
- Sure.
Ah. Leave the bottle.
I know that I haven't really
spoken to the two of you
about my time in Russia.
And that is because there
are some things that I did here
that I'm not very proud of.
As I'm coming to grips with the
fact that the two of you are grown up,
I'm realizing that
shielding you from the bad
isn't going to do our
relationships any good.
From this point forward,
whatever you want to know,
whatever you might want
to ask me is fair game, okay?
Like dislocating your thumbs?
‘Cause I can't
believe I missed that.
Maybe something
a little less painful.
What about that
island you were on?
It's Lian Yu.
It's Mandarin for "purgatory."
You think that'll be enough?
Yeah, well, this
should do the trick.
Roy, thanks for your help, man.
It was good having
you back, even if it was
just for one last mission.
I think I'm gonna stick
around for a while.
If you're gonna be
taking on a space god,
I figure you might need
all the help you can get.
I'm glad you changed your mind.
You know, when
I first met Oliver,
he gave me a purpose,
but he also gave me all of you.
It makes sense
that having a team is
what helps me in the
future, so why wait?
Besides, you know, 1
kind of miss this place.
Welcome back, Roy.
Don't forget to send me that
picture of my dad with that haircut.
Don't forget to ask
about Bratva tattoo.
We have matching.
Used to. Used to, actually.
Oh, ho. I'm gonna need to
hear that story immediately.
Thank you.
I always seem to
end up in your debt.
We are beyond keeping score.
We have been friends,
we have been enemies.
From now on, let
us just be brothers.
Not the Bratva kind.
No! Real family, like
the one you have now.
I can be the fun uncle.
Being father really suits you.
Good-bye, brother.
Thank you. Good-bye, Oliver.
All right. Let's go.
Oh, Laurel, uh...
there's something I want to say.
What? One last hilarious
Russian joke for the road?
Sorry to doubt you,
I guess leopards
really can change spots.
Or in your case, bird, feather.
I thought you said you
weren't sentimental.
Maybe I change, too, like you.
Did you bring the plans?
About that.
I have decided not to join you
and your cosmic fashion tragedy
that you're in cahoots with.
Then you won't
get your Earth back.
If saving it means going back
to the person that I used to be,
then what the hell is the point?
You really have changed.
Look, I'm new to this whole
doing the right thing game,
but you should really
tell your family the truth.
Not yet.
Then this is gonna
be a little awkward.
1 didn't want to believe it.
I'm sorry.
Lyla, what have you--
what have you done?
Greg, move your head.