PREVIOUSLY ON "ARROW"...
THIS LAPTOP CONTAINS
40 MILLION RUBLES
WORTH OF BANK TRANSFERS
FROM KOVAR
THAT GREGOR HASN'T
DISCLOSED.
THIS IS MOST
DISAPPOINTING.
I LIKED MANY OF YOU.
OLIVER:PROMETHEUS
SURPRISED ME
WITH A VERY SPECIFIC,
UNIQUE MOVE.
IT WAS TAUGHT TO ME
BY A WOMAN THAT I MET
IN RUSSIA.
YOU THINK YOU
AND PROMETHEUS HAD
THE SAME TEACHER?
YOU'RE ACCEPTING
THE INVITATION
TO JOIN HELIX.
FULL THROTTLE.
WHAT DO I DO
WITH YOUR SECRET?
I KEEP IT. I CARE
ABOUT THE CITY,
AND...AND YOU'RE WORKING
DOUBLE-TIME.
CAN YOU TALK SOME
SENSE INTO HIM, PLEASE?
MR. MAYOR, THEA,
MEET MY WIFE DORIS.
I THOUGHT
WE COULD TALK.
CAN WE SET UP
A MEETING TOMORROW?
I'M LATE FOR A DINNER.
IT'S IMPORTANT.
YOU COULD CALL IT
LIFE OR DEATH.
YOU SURE THIS
IS THE PLACE?
CURTIS:I DON'T SEE
ANY OTHER MONASTERIES
ON THIS MOUNTAIN.
FELICITY'S NOTE SAID
SOMETHING ABOUT A DEMON...
OH, WAIT, MAYBE
THAT SAYS, "LEMON."
ANYWAY, I...I TEXTED HER,
BUT SHE HAS NOT HIT ME BACK.
IT SAYS, "DEMON."
OLIVER, I'M LOSING YOU!
I'LL SEE YOU BACK
IN STAR CITY.
[TYPING]
[PEOPLE GRUNTING,
TRADING BLOWS]
WHERE IS SHE?
WHO ARE YOU?
I'M A FORMER
STUDENT.
FORMER, WHICH MEANS
YOU ARE NOT WELCOME HERE.
TALIA:HOLD!
LEAVE US.
I WOULD APOLOGIZE
FOR MY STUDENTS'
ENTHUSIASM,
BUT YOU SHOULD NOT
HAVE COME TO THIS PLACE.
WELL, TALIA, IT WAS
DIFFICULT TO FIND.
OUR BUSINESS TOGETHER
CONCLUDED 5 YEARS AGO.
NO. ONE OF YOUR
FORMER STUDENTS
IS TRYING TO KILL ME.
OH, HE DOESN'T WANT
TO KILL YOU, OLIVER.
HE MEANS TO DESTROY
YOU UTTERLY.
YOU KNEW?
IF YOU KNEW, THEN WHY
WOULD YOU TRAIN HIM?
WHY WOULDN'T YOU
WARN ME?
TWO YEARS AGO,
HE SOUGHT ME OUT.
HE'D ALREADY LEARNED
MUCH ABOUT YOU.
HE'S A MAN
OF REMARKABLE CAPACITY.
TALIA, ENOUGH!
IF YOU KNEW
WHAT HE WANTED,
THEN WHY WOULD YOU
TRAIN HIM?
YOU KILLED HIS FATHER,
AND I HELPED HIM
IN HIS PURSUIT
OF VENGEANCE
BECAUSE BY THEN
YOU'D KILLED MINE!
I NEVER TOLD YOU
MY FULL NAME, DID I?
NO, YOU DIDN'T.
IT'S TALIA AL GHUL.
[EXHALES]
RA'S AL GHUL WAS
YOUR FATHER.
YES.
MY FATHER AND I CAME
TO BE AT ODDS,
SO I FORGED
MY OWN PATH...
BUT HE WAS STILL
MY FATHER WHEN YOU PUT
A SWORD THROUGH
HIS CHEST.
SO THAT'S WHY YOU'RE
NOT GONNA HELP ME.
THAT'S WHY YOU WON'T
TELL WHO THIS...
PROMETHEUS IS.
OF COURSE I WILL,
OLIVER,
BECAUSE I WANT YOU
TO SUFFER.
HE CALLS HIMSELF...
ADRIAN CHASE.
EVERYTHING OK?
YES. PEACHY. HEH.
LET'S DO THIS.
-WHOA.
-YEAH. IT'S LIT, RIGHT?
ALL THESE PEOPLE,
THEY'RE JUST...
YOU SOUND SURPRISED.
YEAH. I MEAN, I GUESS
I JUST THOUGHT
THAT A SECRET HACKER
ORGANIZATION WOULD BE
A LITTLE BIT MORE, WELL,
I DON'T KNOW, INTIMATE. HEH.
WELL, HELIX IS
A WORLDWIDE OPERATION,
KIND OF LIKE THE U.N.
IF IT ACTUALLY
ACCOMPLISHED THINGS.
YOU HAVE 3D
NANOELECTRICS DESIGNED
TO INTERFACE
WITH A NEURAL NETWORK.
WE WERE WORKING
ON SOMETHING LIKE THIS
AT PALMER TECH, AND...
WHO DO YOU
THINK WE STOLE
THE PROTOTYPE FROM?
WHAT IS THAT?
REAL-TIME FEED FROM EVERY CELL
PHONE CAMERA IN THE WORLD
RUNNING THROUGH
A PATTERN RECOGNITION ALGO.
HOLY...
THAT'S...
SO MUCH BIGGER THAN
ANYTHING THE NSA IS
DOING. I KNOW.
THAT'S A LOT OF POWER
FOR SOMEONE TO HAVE
WHO'S NOT GOVERNMENT.
WELL, THE FACT THAT
WE'RE NOT GOVERNMENT'S
NOT THE POINT.
POWER TO THE PEOPLE,
RIGHT?
YEAH.
POWER TO THE PEOPLE. HEH.
WELCOME TO HELIX,
FELICITY.
WE'RE GONNA CHANGE
THE WORLD TOGETHER.
WOMAN:MR. QUEEN, I'VE BEEN
TRYING TO REACH YOU...
I NEED CAPTAIN PIKE
AND QUENTIN LANCE
IN MY OFFICE,
AND I NEED TO KNOW
WHERE D.A. CHASE IS
RIGHT NOW.
RIGHT NOW,
MR. CHASE IS IN
THE CONFERENCE ROOM.
TREATMENT FOR DRUG ADDICTS
OVER INCARCERATION.
MR. MAYOR, I DIDN'T
THINK YOU'D BE JOINING
US THIS MORNING.
I GUESS YOU KNOW
WHAT I'VE BEEN
UP TO, HUH?
-YEAH.
-I'VE BEEN WORKING
ON ADDRESSING OUR
SENTENCING POLICY
FOR DRUG OFFENSES.
CARE TO JOIN?
I'D LIKE TO SEE YOU
IN MY OFFICE, PLEASE.
ACTUALLY,
CAN IT WAIT?
THE COUNCILMEN
AND I ARE ON A CLOCK.
BESIDES, YOU'RE LOOKING
A LITTLE RAGGED.
YOU TIRED...
OR IS IT THAT YOU'VE
ACTUALLY BEEN ASLEEP
THIS WHOLE TIME?
ALL THE CAPTAINS
ARE DEAD.
DA. GREGOR WILL PROMOTE
NEW ONES LOYAL TO HIM,
AND THEY WILL
KILL US ALL.
GONNA TRY IT
THIS WAY NOW.
I GOT TO TELL YOU,
I DON'T KNOW HOW
THAT MASK IS
GONNA PLAY HERE,
ESPECIALLY SINCE
THE CITY'S NOT TOO FOND
OF YOUR ALTER EGO
THESE DAYS.
I'LL GIVE THEM
THE THROWING STAR KILLER,
SEE HOW THEY FEEL.
WAIT. THAT'S
YOUR BIG PLAN,
ARRESTING ME?
OH, MAN, THAT'S
A BIT OF A LETDOWN,
I HAVE TO SAY.
WELL, I'M NOT GONNA
KILL YOU,
IF ONLY BECAUSE THAT'S
WHAT YOU WANT ME TO DO.
BUT YOU'VE DONE
EVERYTHING I'VE
WANTED SO FAR.
DID YOU REALLY THINK
I'D LET ALL THIS END
IN A PARKING GARAGE?
WHAT DID YOU DO?
I GAVE YOUR GIRLFRIEND
AN EXCLUSIVE.
WAIT. ARE YOU STILL
DATING SUSAN WILLIAMS?
I GOT TO TELL YOU,
BUDDY.
IT'S BEEN A LITTLE
HARD TO KEEP TRACK.
WHAT DID YOU DO
TO HER?
SHE'S FINE. DON'T WORRY.
AS LONG AS I'M AROUND
TO MAKE SURE SHE GETS
SOME FOOD AND WATER.
STARVATION
AND DEHYDRATION...
TERRIBLE WAY TO GO.
BOTTOM LINE...I DIE,
SHE DIES.
I DON'T MAKE IT BACK
TO HER IN TIME,
SHE DIES.
NOW YOU COULD TRY
TORTURING ME
FOR HER LOCATION.
WE BOTH KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE CAPABLE OF
IN THAT DEPARTMENT,
BUT...
I THINK THAT WE BOTH KNOW
WHAT I'M CAPABLE OF,
SO, OLLIE, WHO DO YOU
THINK CAN LAST LONGER...
SUSAN OR ME?
OHH. I'M 10 STEPS AHEAD
OF YOU,
AND YOU HAVEN'T EVEN
FIGURED OUT WHAT GAME
WE'RE PLAYING YET.
QUENTIN:
THAT SON OF A BITCH.
YEAH, I'D SAY
THAT PRETTY MUCH
COVERS IT.
THIS IS A HELL OF A CITY
YOU GOT HERE.
DISTRICT ATTORNEY'S
A SERIAL KILLER.
HE'S WAY WORSE THAT THAT.
INFILTRATING
THE GOVERNMENT LIKE THAT
AT THE HIGHEST LEVEL
RIGHT NEXT TO OLIVER?
WE UNDERESTIMATED
THIS GUY.
I UNDERESTIMATED HIM.
I TRUSTED HIM.
WHERE IS FELICITY?
I'VE BEEN TEXTING
HER LIKE CRAZY,
BUT HER PHONE'S OFF.
YOU DON'T THINK THAT
PROMETHEUS HAS...
NO.
NO. HIS GAME IS SUSAN.
FOR NOW.
WE HAVE TO MAKE SURE
THEA'S SAFE.
LYLA AND J.J. ARE
SECURE AT ARGUS.
I GOT IN TOUCH WITH THEA.
SHE'S FINE...
B-BUT WE HAVE TO
FIND SUSAN.
WE CANNOT MAKE A MOVE
ON CHASE
UNTIL WE KNOW
SHE'S SAFE,
UNTIL WE HAVE HER HERE.
KEEP LOOKING FOR FELICITY.
YOU GPS HER PHONE
IF YOU HAVE TO.
WE SHOULD GO TO PIKE,
TELL HIM CHASE IS
THE THROWING STAR KILLER.
AND THEN HE ASKS
FOR EVIDENCE,
AND YOU SAY WHAT?
LOOK. QUENTIN'S RIGHT.
DINAH, WE KEEP THE SCPD
OUT OF THIS UNTIL WE
HAVE SOMETHING.
THIS GUY HAS US
IN CHECK.
YEAH, FOR NOW.
JOHN: SENT CURTIS
AND DINAH TO OPAL CITY.
-FOR CHASE'S MOTHER.
-HE HAS LEVERAGE,
WE NEED SOME
OF OUR OWN.
THAT'S NOT GONNA WORK.
THIS GUY ALWAYS SEEMS
TO BE 10 STEPS AHEAD.
WELL, OLIVER,
IT'S PRETTY EASY,
YOU CONFRONTING HIM
IN PUBLIC LIKE THAT.
WHAT THE HELL
WERE YOU THINKING?
I WASN'T THINKING.
WHERE YOU GOING NOW?
ACCORDING TO CITY RECORDS,
CHASE'S HOUSE
HAS A SUBBASEMENT.
CHASE DOES EVERYTHING
SIDEWAYS, MAN.
I DOUBT HE HAS SUSAN
SOMEPLACE OBVIOUS.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S
OBVIOUS ANYMORE.
OH, NO. I CAN'T LET YOU
GO OUT THERE ALONE.
-I'M GOING WITH YOU.
-I CAN HANDLE IT.
NEVER SAID YOU COULDN'T.
3 OF US CANNOT
DEFEAT GREGOR.
WE NEED MORE MEN.
NO. WE NEED A WAY
TO CONVINCE THEBRATVA
THAT GREGOR
SOLD THEM OUT.
WE HAD WAY.
WELL, WE DON'T HAVE
ANYONE THAT CAN PULL
DATA OFF A BULLET-RIDDEN
LAPTOP, SO...
WITHOUT PROOF,
GREGOR WILL SAY
WE ARE TRAITORS.
REST OFBRATVA
WILL BELIEVE HIM.
AND THEN THEY
WILL KILL US.
SO WE'VE GOT TO
KILL HIM FIRST
BEFORE HE TELLS
ANYONE.
OK. YOU'VE HAD
ENOUGH TO DRINK
ALREADY.
[SIGHS]
WHERE WOULD GREGOR
GO...
I MEAN, WHERE WOULD
HE GO RIGHT NOW?
HE'D GO TO GROUND.
BRATVA STRONGHOLD IS
HOCKEY RINK,
BUT IT'S HEAVILY PROTECTED.
HMM. WE WOULDN'T
EVEN GET THROUGH
THE DOOR.
I THINK I KNOW
SOMEONE WHO CAN.
I GUESS NORMA BATES GOT
THE HELL OUT OF DODGE.
CHASE ANTICIPATED
THIS PLAY.
I NEVER SAID THAT
HE WASN'T CLEVER.
SO AM I.
[WHIRRING]
UM...WHAT'S
YOUR TOY DOING?
IT'S DETECTING
RESONANCE FREQUENCIES
UPSTAIRS.
IT'S NOT A TOY.
IT'S A T-SPHERE.
WAIT. EVERY HORROR MOVIE
EVER HAS BASICALLY SAID
THAT YOU DO NOT GO
UPSTAIRS
AT A CREEPY SERIAL KILLER'S
MOTHER'S HOUSE.
[SUSAN SCREAMS]
HELP!
SUSAN:STOP!
[SOBBING]
UNH!
ADRIAN:EXCELLENT.
NOW GIVE US
ANOTHER SCREAM.
SO, WHAT, WE'RE
SUPPOSED TO JUST GO TO WORK
LIKE THINGS ARE NORMAL?
BECAUSE NEWSFLASH...
THEY AIN'T.
TELL ME SOMETHING
I DON'T ALREADY KNOW.
CHASE: HO HO! I DID
THINK OF ONE OR TWO
THINGS.
THIS IS NICE,
EVERYTHING BEING OUT
IN THE OPEN NOW,
ALL THE CARDS
ON THE TABLE,
AS IT WERE.
YOU GOT SOME NERVE
SHOWING UP HERE.
WHY WOULDN'T I?
I TAKE MY JOB
VERY SERIOUSLY.
SPEAKING OF, I
THOUGHT MY OFFICE
HAD REQUESTED
YOUR VERIFICATIONS
ON THE LATEST
COMSTAT REPORTS
FROM THE SCPD.
WHAT YOU
BEEN DOING?
I'M GONNA KILL YOU
IN WAYS THAT
WILL HURT.
THREATENING A CITY
OFFICIAL'S A FELONY,
MR. RAMIREZ.
YOU THINK YOU'RE
SO CLEVER.
THIS ISN'T OVER,
YOU SON OF A BITCH!
I AGREE. IN FACT,
I THINK WE'RE JUST
GETTING STARTED.
I WANT THOSE COMSTAT
VERIFICATIONS
ON MY DESK
BY TOMORROW MORNING,
DOG.
WE CAN'T JUST LET
THAT SON OF A BITCH
WALK AROUND HERE.
-WE GOT TO DO SOMETHING.
-WE ARE DOING SOMETHING.
YEAH. RENE AND I
HAVE GOT EYES ON CHASE.
HE'S AT CITY HALL.
YOU GOT A GREEN LIGHT
TO MOVE ON HIS HOUSE.
ROGER THAT.
OK, SPARTAN.
YOU CHECK THE UPSTAIRS
AND WORK YOUR WAY DOWN.
I'LL SWEEP THE BASEMENT.
WE CAN MEET IN THE MIDDLE.
ROGER THAT.
-PLEASE DON'T HURT ME.
-MRS. CHASE.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING
IN MY HOU...
MRS. CHASE, I'M NOT
GONNA HURT YOU.
GET AWAY FROM ME.
YOUR HUSBAND ISN'T
WHO YOU THINK HE IS.
GET OUT OF MY HOUSE.
MRS. CHASE, YOUR HUSBAND
IS THE THROWING STAR KILLER.
HE'S HOLDING
AN INNOCENT WOMAN HOSTAGE,
AND I NEED YOUR HELP
TO FIND HER.
-YOU'RE INSANE.
-DORIS, PLEASE.
YOU NEED TO UNDERSTAND
THE TRUTH.
YOU HAVE TO KNOW
ON SOME LEVEL
THAT YOUR HUSBAND
HAS BEEN KEEPING
SOMETHING FROM YOU.
AND POLICE AND THE MAYOR
SAY THAT YOU'RE
THE KILLER, YOU.
OFFICER: ON THE FLOOR.
ON THE FLOOR!
GET DOWN ON THE FLOOR!
ON THE FLOOR.
YOU ALL RIGHT,
MRS. CHASE?
I'M...I'M FINE.
WE GOT A CALL
FROM YOUR HUSBAND.
DON'T WORRY.
WE GOT THIS HANDLED.
GET HER OUT OF HERE.
TELL ME WHAT YOU
WANT ME TO DO.
I AM NOT GETTING
INTO A SHOOTOUT
WITH THE SCPD.
COPY THAT. I'M OUT.
SMART MOVE, DOUCHEBAG.
I WASN'T TALKING
TO YOU.
DROP THE BOW AND GET
ON THE GROUND!
[GROANS]
WHOLE THING'S ABOUT
30 SECONDS LONG.
I'VE BEEN OVER
EVERY FRAME,
AND THERE'S NOTHING
TO INDICATE A LOCATION.
AT LEAST IT'S
PROOF OF LIFE.
YEAH. SHE WAS ALIVE
WHEN THIS VIDEO WAS MADE,
BUT WE DON'T KNOW
HOW LONG A...SORRY.
IT'S FINE. HE'LL...
HE'LL KEEP HER ALIVE
TO KEEP ME IN CHECK.
I NEVER SHOULD HAVE
GOTTEN INVOLVED
WITH SUSAN.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT I WAS THINKING.
YOU WERE THINKING
YOU WERE LONELY, MAN.
EVERYONE NEEDS SOMEBODY.
YEAH? WELL, MAYBE
I GAVE UP THAT RIGHT
WHEN I PUT
ON THE HOOD.
FELICITY: HI! OH! HI!
I'M SORRY.
I KNOW I'M LATE.
I GOT CURTIS' MESSAGES.
I'M SORRY.
I'M HERE NOW. SORRY.
CAN YOU GIVE US
THE ROOM, PLEASE?
HEH. MUCH APPRECIATED.
YEAH. I USUALLY LIKE
MY TONGUE LASHINGS
TO BE DONE IN PRIVATE,
SO THANK YOU. HEH.
I'M...SORRY.
I'M NOT ANGRY.
YOU DON'T...YOU DON'T
WORK FOR ME.
YOU...
I'M WORRIED.
RIGHT. OF COURSE,
FOR ALL YOU KNOW,
PROMETHEUS COULD HAVE
KKHHK...OOH.
NOT...
I'M WORRIED
ABOUT YOU.
OH.
BECAUSE YOU'RE
INTO SOMETHING,
AND YOU DON'T WANT TO
TELL ANYONE ABOUT IT,
OR MAYBE YOU JUST DON'T
WANT TO TELL ME.
I THINK WE CAN BOTH
AGREE
THAT KEEPING SECRETS
DOESN'T END WELL,
SO...
YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
IT'S JUST THAT RIGHT NOW
IS NOT REALLY A GOOD TIME
WITH EVERYTHING
GOING ON.
YOU JUST HAVE TO
TRUST ME ON THIS ONE, OK?
-OK.
-BUT SPEAKING OF THE SOMETHING
THAT I'M INTO,
IT ACTUALLY HELPED ME GO
THROUGH THE PETABYTE
OF DATA WE TOOK OFF
OF CHASE'S MOTHER'S
COMPUTER.
-THIS
-WHO'S SIMON MORRISON?
-ADRIAN CHASE.
-WHAT?
SIMON MORRISON IS
HIS BIRTH NAME.
THAT'S HIS REAL IDENTITY.
BUT HIS MOTHER'S NAME
IS AMANDA WESTFIELD.
YES. WELL, SHE CHANGED
HER NAME WHEN SHE
WENT OFF THE GRID,
SO IT RUNS
IN THE FAMILY.
WELL, IF ADRIAN CHASE
IS AN ALIAS...
THEN THE PROOF THAT
HIS BACKGROUND IS FAKE
WOULD BE ENOUGH
FOR THE ACU TO
ARREST HIS ASS.
HOWEVER YOU DID IT,
GOOD WORK.
LET'S PUT THIS
ALL ON THE DRIVE.
-I'VE GOT TO GET TO CITY HALL.
-WAIT. OH.
NOW? I MEAN,
IT'S PAST 10:00.
YEAH. BEFORE
THE 11:00 NEWS,
I HAVE TO MAKE
A STATEMENT
ON THE GREEN ARROW
BREAKING INTO
THE D.A.'S HOUSE.
OBVIOUSLY, THIS IS
A HORRIFYING DEVELOPMENT.
UH, WE BELIEVE
THE GREEN ARROW WAS
RETALIATING
AGAINST THIS OFFICE
FOR SPEAKING OUT
AGAINST HIS RECENT CRIMES.
MR. MAYOR.
[CAMERA SHUTTERS CLICKING]
AHEM.
THIS OFFICE IS
IN COMPLETE AGREEMENT
WITH D.A. CHASE.
THIS SITUATION
HAS BECOME UNTENABLE...
AND I AM DETERMINED
TO BRING IT
TO A JUST
AND SUCCESSFUL END.
I WILL NOT LET ANYONE,
ANYONE...
TERRORIZE THIS CITY...
AND SO I AM DEMANDING
THAT THE GREEN ARROW
TURN HIMSELF IN.
HE HAS 24 HOURS
BEFORE I AM ORDERING
THE SCPD TO SHOOT ON SIGHT.
[REPORTERS CLAMORING]
THAT'S ALL.
[CLAMORING CONTINUES]
THANKS FOR SEEING ME.
I KNOW IT'S LATE.
UH, I THINK WE BOTH
KNOW OUR JOBS DON'T
RECOGNIZE LATE AND EARLY.
WHAT CAN I DO FOR YOU?
WHAT'S THIS?
THAT IS EVIDENCE
THAT ADRIAN CHASE IS
A FALSE IDENTITY.
HIS REAL NAME IS
SIMON MORRISON.
IN THE MIDST
OF AN INVESTIGATION,
YOU WILL LEARN
THAT HE IS
THE THROWING STAR KILLER.
OH. THAT'S ONE HELL
OF AN ACCUSATION.
THAT'S WHY I'M
GIVING YOU THAT.
AND THIS EVIDENCE COMES
FROM WHERE?
AN INVESTIGATION THAT
I'VE BEEN CONDUCTING
OFF THE BOOKS.
WITH WHAT PERSONNEL?
WORK THE LEAD,
CAPTAIN PIKE.
CONSIDER THAT AN ORDER
IF IT HELPS.
ONE LAST THING.
YOU DIDN'T GET
THAT FROM ME.
I SERVE AT THE PLEASURE
OF THE MAYOR.
THERE YOU ARE.
VIKTOR HAS CONFIRMED
GREGOR'S LOCATION,
BUT TELL ME, WHY
DID YOU WANT HIM GONE
AND WHY ARE YOU
PLAYING ROBIN HOOD?
I MET A WOMAN.
SHE TAUGHT ME HOW TO
GIVE MY DARKNESS
AN IDENTITY
SO THAT IT DOESN'T
CONSUME ME.
AND YOU BELIEVED HER?
[SPEAKS RUSSIAN]
OLIVER, WHATEVER YOU
THINK IS INSIDE YOU
IS INSIDE YOU.
YOU...YOU CANNOT NAME IT
LIKE THAT
AND KEEP IT APART
FROM YOU.
THIS WOMAN'S TAUGHT
ME DIFFERENTLY.
THIS WOMAN DOES NOT
KNOW WHAT SHE IS
TALKING ABOUT,
AND IF YOU'RE NOT
CAREFUL, OLIVER,
ONE DAY SHE WILL BE
THE SOURCE OF YOUR
GREATEST PAIN.
OH, MY GOD.
AND THIS IS...
WE'VE BEEN CALLING
HIM PROMETHEUS,
BUT YOU HELPED ME I.D.
HIM AS SIMON MORRISON.
I'VE BEEN STRIKING
OUT AT GETTING
A LOCATION OFF THIS,
BUT SOMEONE
WITH A CELL PHONE
AT SOME POINT
MUST HAVE ENTERED
THIS ROOM,
WHICH MEANS THERE
SHOULD BE PICTURES
OF IT ON YOUR DATABASE.
IF I CAN CROSS-REFERENCE
THE IMAGES
OF YOUR DATABASE
WITH THIS VIDEO,
I SHOULD BE ABLE TO HELP
THE POLICE FIND HER.
AND THAT'S, LIKE, REALLY
COOL AND NOBLE AND ALL.
I MEAN, SHE DEFINITELY
NEEDS YOUR HELP...
BUT?
BUT, FELICITY, WE GAVE
YOU PANDORA.
WE HELPED YOU SORT
THROUGH THAT DATA PULL,
AND NOW, WELL, PEOPLE
ARE STARTING TO ASK WHAT
YOU'RE DOING FOR US.
I MEAN, WE DIDN'T INVITE
YOU IN JUST SO YOU
COULD CHECK ITEMS
OFF YOUR TO-DO LIST.
SORRY. IT FEELS GROSS
SAYING...
NO. UH, NO.
YOU'RE RIGHT. OK.
SO QUID PRO QUO.
I HELP YOU, YOU HELP ME.
I WAS KIND OF HOPING
YOU'D SAY THAT.
WE'VE BEEN TRYING TO
BREAK THE ENCRYPTION
ON A CERTAIN
HOMELAND SECURITY DRONE.
-WHY?
-NEED TO KNOW, I'M AFRAID.
QUESTION IS
WHAT ARE YOU WILLING
TO QUO IN EXCHANGE
FOR YOUR QUID?
UH, CAN YOU CHECK
SOME FILES FOR ME?
ANY LEGAL RECORDS YOU
CAN FIND ON A SIMON MORRISON.
THANKS.
[GROANING]
HEY.
[COUGHS]
HEY. YOU OK, BUDDY?
NEED SOME MEDICAL
ATTENTION OR SOMETHING?
UNH!
-WHAT HAPPENED?
-SOME LOWLIFE ATTACKED HIM
OUTSIDE THE PRECINCT.
SCPD'S CANVASSING,
BUT THE SECURITY CAMERAS,
THEY DID NOT GET
A SHOT OF HIS FACE.
BUT...
HOW'S PIKE?
HE'S COMATOSE.
THIS WAS CHASE.
I DON'T KNOW, OLIVER.
MURDER BY LOWLIFE
IS NOT EXACTLY HIS STYLE.
EARLIER TONIGHT,
I GAVE PIKE A LEAD
CONNECTING CHASE
TO PROMETHEUS.
I THOUGHT WE DIDN'T
HAVE ANY LEADS.
FELICITY RESURFACED
WITH SOMETHING.
IS PIKE'S FAMILY
IN THERE?
NOPE, BUT SOMEBODY
ELSE IS.
LIFE'S JUST SO FRAGILE,
ISN'T IT?
DECADES OF HOPES
AND DREAMS,
AND IN ONE MOMENT,
ONE LITTLE MISTAKE,
AND IT ALL JUST
GOES AWAY.
I'M NOT GONNA LET YOU
HURT ANYONE ELSE.
REALLY? BECAUSE SO FAR,
YOU HAVEN'T BEEN ABLE
TO DO MUCH TO STOP ME.
SUSAN'S FINE BY THE WAY.
WELL, ALIVE
AT ANY RATE.
ME AND MY TEAM
ARE GONNA FIND HER,
AND WHEN WE DO,
THE SECOND THAT WE DO...
I'M GONNA PUT AN ARROW
RIGHT THROUGH YOUR HEART.
YOU DO REALIZE
HOW IMPOTENT YOU
SOUND, RIGHT?
YOU THINK THIS
IS A GAME?
I DON'T FEEL LIKE
PLAYING ANYMORE.
YOU DON'T HAVE
A CHOICE, OLIVER.
IF YOU KILL ME,
YOU KILL SUSAN,
AND SHE WILL BE
AS DEAD AS YOUR MOTHER,
AS TOMMY, AS SHADO,
AS LAUREL,
AS YOUR FRIEND PIKE
HERE PROBABLY...
ALL DEAD BECAUSE OF YOU.
SO GO AHEAD. KILL ME.
LET'S FIND OUT
HOW MUCH MORE LOSS
YOU CAN TAKE
BECAUSE I DON'T
THINK IT'S MUCH.
I THINK THAT
YOU'RE ONE LOSS AWAY
FROM BEING DESTROYED.
I GUESS WE'LL HAVE TO
FIND ANOTHER WAY TO
HANDLE THIS THEN.
YOU SEE, THAT'S
THE BEAUTIFUL THING
ABOUT ALL
OF THIS, OLIVER.
IF YOU KILL ME,
YOU'LL ONLY REALLY
BE KILLING YOURSELF.
[EXHALES]
[GUNFIRE]
[ARROW WHOOSHES]
[GRUNTING]
[DEEP VOICE]
THANKS FOR THE ASSIST.
WHAT IS THING YOU ARE
DOING WITH YOUR VOICE?
[DISTANT GUNFIRE]
[GUNFIRE]
OK.
[BOTH TYPING]
OK. OH, OH! I'M IN.
WHOO! WE'RE IN. YES.
WHOA! WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
DID WE JUST ACCIDENTALLY
HACK A DHS DRONE SYSTEM?
WELL, I WOULDN'T EXACTLY
SAY ACCIDENTALLY.
-TCH. AM I RIGHT?
-UH-UH, UH-UH.
FELICITY, PLEASE
EXPLAIN TO ME
WHY WE'RE HACKING
HOMELAND SECURITY DRONES
INSTEAD OF FINDING
SUSAN'S LOCATION
LIKE YOU TOLD ME
WE WOULD BE!
BECAUSE HACKING
THE DRONES IS WHAT'S
GONNA LEAD US TO SUSAN.
IT'S...IT'S...
SO COMPLICATED.
HOLY CRAP. YOU JUST
SENT THE RECEIVER
FALSE DATA,
AND NOW YOU ARE
SPOOFING THE GPS SYSTEM.
THERE'S NOTHING SLIGHT
ABOUT THIS.
THIS IS JUST
STRAIGHT-UP ILLEGAL.
SPILL 100% DEETS
RIGHT NOW.
-RIGHT NOW!
-OK, OK.
SO I'VE...I'VE KIND OF
MADE SOME...HEH...
NEW FRIENDS.
SURPRISE.
AND THEY HAVE ACCESS
TO UNACCESSIBLE AMOUNTS
OF DATA AND INTEL,
TONS OF IT.
THEY HELPED ME GET
JOHN OUT OF PRISON,
AND NOW THEY'RE WILLING
TO HELP US FIND SUSAN.
THAT'S ALL.
IF YOU REDIRECT A FEW
U.S. BORDER CONTROL DRONES.
HEY. DON'T LOOK
AT ME LIKE THAT.
OK. I'VE ALREADY GOTTEN
CHAPTER AND VERSE
FROM JOHN AND OLIVER.
PLEASE DON'T, PLEASE.
I CAN'T IMAGINE THEM
SIGNING OFF ON YOU
HACKING
HOMELAND SECURITY.
THEY DON'T KNOW,
DO THEY?
ALL THEY NEED TO KNOW
IS THAT I AM
A GROWN WOMAN MAKING
MY OWN GROWN-UP
DECISIONS.
HEY. GOT ANYTHING
FOR ME?
OLIVER.
WHAT IS IT, MAN?
IS IT SUSAN?
NOT YET,
BUT IT'S JUST
A MATTER OF TIME.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT
I CAN DO TO STOP IT.
WELL, OLIVER, THERE ARE
ALWAYS OPTIONS,
AND YOU'RE
NOT ALONE.
DO YOU THINK
THAT'S THE PROBLEM?
YOU'VE DONE
A WONDERFUL JOB
OF CONVINCING ME
THAT I'M CHANGING
FOR THE BETTER...
WITH THE RECRUITS
AND THE...
[SIGHS]
THE TRANSPARENCY,
MORE OPTIMISM,
MORE...MORE TRUST.
YOU THINK NONE
OF THIS WOULD HAVE HAPPENED
IF YOU HADN'T
TRUSTED CHASE, RIGHT?
TRUSTED ANYONE.
BECAUSE I...I CAN'T SEE
ANYTHING
PAST ME JUST CREATING
MORE TARGETS.
OLIVER.
WE'RE NOT
TARGETS, MAN.
WE'RE YOUR TEAMMATES.
WE'RE YOUR STRENGTH.
YOU GIVE ME STRENGTH
UNTIL CHASE TURNS IT
INTO A WEAKNESS.
LOOK WHAT HAPPENED
WITH SUSAN.
I LET MYSELF GET
CLOSE TO SUSAN,
AND IN SO DOING,
I GAVE CHASE A WAY
TO GET TO ME.
THAT COULD HAPPEN
WITH YOU,
WITH...
WITH FELICITY...
WITH MY SON.
ALL OF YOU MAKE ME
VULNERABLE, JOHN.
MAYBE.
MAYBE WE DO...
BUT CARING
ABOUT PEOPLE, OLIVER,
THAT MAKES YOU HUMAN.
[SIGHS]
BEING HUMAN'S A LUXURY
I MIGHT NOT GET TO HAVE.
[CELL PHONE VIBRATING]
YEAH.
OK. GOT IT.
TELL DINAH AND RENE.
FELICITY FOUND OUT
WHERE CHASE IS
KEEPING SUSAN.
-LET'S GO!
-JOHN.
THERE'S SOMETHING
I NEED YOU TO DO FOR ME.
IF I'M GONNA BEAT
THIS GUY,
IT'LL BE BY PLAYING
HIS GAME...
AND I KNOW SOMEONE WHO
MAKES HIM VULNERABLE.
RENE: THIS IS WHERE
PROMETHEUS IS HOLDING
YOUR LADY?
OR AT LEAST HE WAS WHEN
HE SHOT THAT VIDEO.
I'M READING A FEW DOZEN
HEAT SIGNATURES INSIDE.
CHASE BROUGHT BACKUP?
OR HE'S USING DECOYS.
IT'S DECOYS.
PROMETHEUS
WORKS ALONE.
PROBLEM IS SUSAN COULD
BE ANY ONE OF THOSE
HEAT SIGNATURES.
WE SHOULD SPLIT UP,
CANVASS FLOOR BY FLOOR.
AGREED.
OVERWATCH, ANY WORD
ON SPARTAN?
UH, PACKAGE IS EN ROUTE.
-ETA 5 MINUTES.
-PACKAGE?
OLIVER'S GOT SOMETHING
UP HIS GREEN SLEEVE.
THESE PUPPIES SHOULD
HELP DOUBLE OUR
SEARCH CAPABILITIES.
NEXT TIME, I GET TO
KICK THE DOOR IN.
YEAH. WHATEVER FLOATS
YOUR BOAT, LASSIE.
[BEEPING]
GET BACK!
WHAT WAS THAT?
SOME SORT OF EXPLOSION.
DINAH, RENE,
DO YOU COPY?
[COUGHING]
OW. YEAH. WE COPY.
BUT WE'RE TRAPPED
IN HERE.
-OH. SON OF A BITCH!
-YEAH.
WHAT IF THOSE
HEAT SIGNATURES ARE
INCENDIARY DEVICES?
I THINK WE CAN
PRETTY MUCH CONFIRM THAT.
WE GOT 5 MINUTES
FOR SEARCH AND RESCUE
BEFORE THIS WHOLE PLACE
COMES DOWN.
YOU GET DINAH
AND WILD DOG
OUT OF HERE.
-I WILL FIND SUSAN.
-ASSUMING SHE'S STILL HERE.
WHICH I'M TOTALLY
SURE SHE STILL IS.
[DING]
UNH! OLIVER!
HEY. ARE YOU OK?
-YEAH. A-ADRIAN CHASE IS...
-I KNOW!
DON'T WORRY.
I'M GONNA GET YOU
OUT OF HERE.
[ELEVATOR RUMBLING]
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
CHASE IS CONTROLLING
THE ELEVATOR.
SUSAN, WE NEED TO
GET YOU OUT OF HERE.
-THIS BUILDING IS GONNA EXPLODE.
-WHAT ABOUT...
CHASE WANTS ME.
YOU'RE NO LONGER
HIS TARGET.
I WAS GONNA SAY
WHAT ABOUT YOU?
I'M GONNA FINISH THIS.
GET TO SAFETY.
HELLO, OLIVER.
CAN YOU GUYS HEAR
ME IN THERE?
YEAH. JUST WAITING
ON THAT RESCUE.
GOOD. STEP BACK!
I'M GLAD TALIA TOLD YOU.
I PREFER IT THIS WAY,
FACE TO FACE.
THERE'S AN HONESTY
TO IT.
WELL, HONESTLY...
I'M GONNA KEEP BOTH
OF US HERE
UNTIL THIS BUILDING
COMES DOWN ON TOP OF US.
THEN YOU'D BE DEAD.
SO WOULD YOU.
REALLY? YOU REALLY
THINK I'D LET THAT
HAPPEN, OLIVER?
[BEEP]
REMEMBER, I'M ALWAYS
10 STEPS AHEAD OF YOU.
YOU KNOW, IF THAT
WERE TRUE,
YOU PROBABLY WOULD HAVE
SEEN THIS COMING.
ADRIAN?
YOU SHOULDN'T
BE HERE.
HOW ELSE WAS I SUPPOSED
TO FIND OUT THE TRUTH?
YOU KILLED
ALL THOSE PEOPLE.
IT'S NOT
THAT SIMPLE.
YOU KILLED THEM.
IT'S SIMPLE.
I KNOW, BABY.
THIS CAN'T BE YOU.
IT'S NOT YOU.
I'M SORRY.
I'M SO SORRY.
WHY DID YOU MAKE
HER COME HERE?
TO GET YOU TO STOP.
YOU HAVE TO STOP.
YOU HAVE TO...YOU HAVE
TO TURN YOURSELF IN.
I CAN'T DO THAT.
PLEASE. WHATEVER THIS IS,
WHATEVER YOU'RE DOING,
IT'S OVER.
YOU'D TELL
THE POLICE?
NO. YOU TELL THEM.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
I'M GONNA TAKE
CARE OF THIS.
[STAB]
JOHN!
[BOTH GRUNTING]
RAHHH!
FELICITY:I'VE GOT AN AMBULANCE
EN ROUTE TO YOUR POSITION.
OH, MY GOD.
OLIVER'S IN THERE
WITH CHASE.
GO HELP HIM NOW!
GO!
AGH!
RAH!
[ADRIAN PANTING]
I TOLD YOU, OLIVER.
I'M NOT GONNA KILL YOU,
AND YOU CAN'T KILL ME.
YES, ADRIAN.
YES, I CAN!
[METAL SCRAPES]
[ARROW WHOOSHES]
FELICITY:WHAT'S GOING ON?
GUYS, SOME SORT
OF SITREP.
CHASE IS GONE.
AND SO IS OLIVER.
WHERE'S OLIVER?
-GUYS!
-WE HAVE TO ASSUME
THAT CHASE HAS HIM.
WHAT ABOUT SUSAN
AND CHASE'S WIFE?
FELICITY: SUSAN'S
AT THE PRECINCT.
QUENTIN IS WITH HER,
UM, BUT DORIS PASSED AWAY
EN ROUTE TO STARLING GENERAL.
RENE: WE'VE GOT TO WORK
ON FINDING OLIVER.
FELICITY,
YOU FOUND SUSAN.
YOU CAN FIND HIM.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
FELICITY, PLEASE TELL ME
YOU'RE NOT GOING
TO SEE THEM AGAIN.
DINAH'S RIGHT.
THEY'RE THE ONES
THAT FOUND SUSAN.
AGH!
GREGOR!
UNH!
[PANTING]
OLIVER, IS THAT YOU?
NO.
IT'S THE MAN WHO'S
GONNA KILL YOU.
AGH!
YOU UP FOR MAKING
A STATEMENT?
YEAH, I'M UP FOR ANYTHING
THAT PUTS ADRIAN CHASE
IN THE ELECTRIC CHAIR.
ACTUALLY, WE ONLY GOT
LETHAL INJECTION
IN THIS STATE,
BUT I LIKE YOUR
THINKING.
HELLO, MS. WILLIAMS.
LONG TIME, NO SEE.
YOU GET AWAY FROM HER.
PLEASE DON'T
THREATEN ME.
I'M IN MOURNING.
HAVEN'T YOU HEARD?
THE GREEN ARROW
KILLED MY WIFE
EARLIER TONIGHT,
AND APPARENTLY,
THE MAYOR'S MISSING.
YOU WOULDN'T HAPPEN
TO KNOW WHERE HE IS,
QUENTIN?
HONESTLY, IT DOESN'T
LOOK GOOD,
OLIVER DISAPPEARING
UNDER THESE
CIRCUMSTANCES.
YOU GIVE ME
ONE GOOD REASON
WHY I SHOULDN'T HAVE
YOU ARRESTED RIGHT NOW.
BECAUSE YOU DON'T
WANT YOUR FRIEND
BACK IN PIECES.
RIGHT?
EVERYONE'S MEGAIMPRESSED
WITH THE DHS HACK
YOU DID FOR US.
THAT'S GREAT.
YOU'VE ALSO BEEN CHOSEN
AS THE FIRST WOMAN
TO GO TO MARS.
SORRY.
A FRIEND OF MINE
IS MISSING.
THE INFORMATION
WE GAVE YOU
DIDN'T HELP?
DIFFERENT FRIEND.
YOU HAVE A LOT
OF MISSING FRIENDS.
YEAH, AND THIS TIME,
I HAVE NO LEADS
WHATSOEVER.
YOU GUYS HAVE BETTER
RESOURCES THAN I DO,
AND I HAVE TO USE
EVERYTHING THAT I CAN
TO FIND HIM
AND DO WHATEVER YOU
NEED ME TO DO FOR YOU.
[CHAINS RATTLING]
[MEATAL DOOR OPENS]
[FOOTSTEPS]
TALIA: I DON'T BELIEVE
I TAUGHT YOU
HOW TO ESCAPE
FROM SHACKLES, OLIVER.
YOUR FATHER WAS
AN HONORABLE MAN.
YOU'VE ALLIED
WITH A PSYCHOPATH,
AND HE'D BE
ASHAMED OF YOU.
WELL, WHEN IT COMES
TO THE SHAME OF FATHERS,
I SHALL BOW TO YOUR
SUPERIOR EXPERTISE.
JUST MAKE SURE
HE SUFFERS.
THAT WAS ALWAYS
THE PLAN.
MY FRIENDS
WILL FIND ME.
THEY'RE MY STRENGTH.
THAT'S SWEET,
BUT I'M RUNNING OUT
OF WAYS TO TELL YOU,
OLIVER.
I'M NOT INTERESTED
IN KILLING YOU.
THEN WHAT THE HELL
IS THIS GAME THAT
WE'RE PLAYING?
WHEN I HAD SUSAN
AS MY GUEST,
I CONFESSED TO HER
THAT YOU'D HELPED ME
DISCOVER WHO I
REALLY AM.
THAT'S WHAT I'M GONNA
HELP YOU DO, OLIVER.
MAN: GREG, MOVE YOUR HEAD!