PREVIOUSLY ON "ARROW"...
FELICITY: 4 YEARS AGO,
THE HOOD TOOK DOWN
JUSTIN CLAYBOURNE.
YOU TOLD ME THAT
CLAYBOURNE DIDN'T
HAVE ANY KIDS.
THERE'S NO RECORD
OF THE KID'S NAME.
HE'D BE ABOUT 30 TODAY.
JUST OLD ENOUGH TO PUT
ON A HOOD AND A MASK.
OLD ENOUGH
TO WANT REVENGE
ON THE MAN WHO MURDERED
HIS FATHER.
OLIVER: EVELYN, WHY?
YOU'RE A FRAUD.
THIS CITY NEEDS TO BE
SAVED FROM YOU.
JOHN: HEY.
LYLA: JOHNNY, I NEED YOU
TO COME TO
THE SAFE HOUSE.
-SOMETHING'S WRONG WITH JJ.
-LYLA?
DID YOU FIND BILLY?
OLIVER: I DIDN'T KNOW
IT WAS BILLY.
I COULDN'T HAVE KNOWN.
HI, OLLIE.
I SAW YOU DIE.
I WAS SAVED.
I SAW THIS WHITE LIGHT,
AND...IT'S...
IT'S JUST LIKE
THEY SAY.
THIS ANGEL, SHE...
SHE REACHED OUT TO ME,
BUT SHE WASN'T
AN ANGEL.
SHE WAS MY SISTER.
WHAT?
SARA...SHE...SHE
HAD ME TELEPORTED
TO THE WAVE RIDER.
THEY HAVE
THIS TECHNOLOGY
THAT FIXED THE EMBOLISM.
I WAS THERE.
EVERYONE WAS THERE.
NOBODY SAW
A WHITE LIGHT,
AND YOU DIDN'T GO
ANYWHERE.
THAT'S BECAUSE SHE
HADN'T DONE IT YET.
OLLIE...
OLLIE I ASKED HER...
I ASKED HER TO BRING ME
TO YOUR PRESENT.
SHE GAVE ME THE SAME GIFT
THAT I GAVE HER.
SHE GAVE ME
A SECOND CHANCE.
IT'S A MIRACLE.
LAUREL?
HI, FELICITY.
OH, MY GOD!
OHH! OH, MY GOD!
IT'S A MIRACLE.
OLIVER SAID
THE EXACT SAME THING.
FELICITY: I THOUGHT
SARA AND THE LEGENDS
WERE AGAINST
CHANGING HISTORY.
SARA SAID THAT THEY
FIGURED OUT A WAY
TO BRING ME BACK
WITHOUT CAUSING
A, UH...
AN ABERRATION.
YES. THAT.
ARE YOU OK?
FINE.
YEAH. I JUST WISH
THE LEGENDS COULD
BRING BACK
EVERYBODY WE WANTED.
WHAT HAPPENED?
WHAT'D I MISS?
WE'LL TALK
ABOUT IT LATER.
THE IMPORTANT THING
IS THAT YOU'RE BACK
FROM THE PAST,
WHICH THEY BROUGHT
YOU BACK FROM
MONTHS LATER,
AND THEY JUST
DROPPED YOU HERE.
SO WEIRD.
TIME TRAVEL.
AM I RIGHT?
WOW! HEH.
DO YOU GUYS WANT
A COFFEE?
I, UM...GONNA GET
A DECA...DECAF
PROBABLY
BECAUSE OF...
IT'S NICE TO SEE SOME
THINGS HAVEN'T CHANGED.
OH. I HAVE TO
CALL MY DAD.
HE'S GONNA KILL ME
FOR COMING HERE FIRST.
LAUREL, AFTER YOU...
UH, Y-YOUR DAD LEFT
WITH DONNA
AND, UH, IT DIDN'T
GO WELL.
-HE'S DRINKING AGAIN.
-HE'S IN REHAB,
BUT HE'S...HE'S...HE'S
GETTING BETTER.
HE'S GETTING THE HELP
THAT HE NEEDS.
WOW. 9 MONTHS.
I GUESS I HAVE A LOT
OF CATCHING UP TO DO.
WHICH IS WHY I'M
GONNA TELL EVERYONE
TO COME TO THE PARTY.
-WHAT PARTY?
-THE PARTY THAT WE'RE GONNA
THROW FOR LAUREL
TOMORROW NIGHT.
THAT SOUNDS GREAT.
I MEAN, I...I WOULD
LOVE TO SEE EVERYONE...
THEA AND JOHN.
OH, MY...JOHN! OHH!
I CAME HERE
TO TELL YOU,
AND I TOTALLY
FORGOT.
WHAT'S GOING ON
WITH JOHN?
JOHN: I CAN'T BELIEVE
SHE'S BACK.
I WALKED
INTO THE BUNKER,
AND SH...AND SHE
WAS JUST THERE
LIKE NOTHING
HAD HAPPENED,
LIKE...
LIKE IT WAS SOME
KIND OF GIFT.
HOW MUCH DOES SHE KNOW
ABOUT WHAT'S HAPPENED?
WE'RE EASING HER IN.
THERE'S A LOT
TO PROCESS.
-THE RECRUITS.
-PROMETHEUS.
THE FACT THAT YOU
KILLED HIS DAD.
[SIGHS]
FELICITY AND LYLA
ARE WORKING ON
FINDING HIS MOTHER.
WHAT HAPPENED
WITH THE DUDE WHO
TRAINED THE TWO OF YOU?
WELL, SHE...
DOESN'T STAY IN ONE SPOT
FOR VERY LONG,
BUT, UH, I'M WORKING
ON FINDING HER.
IN THE MEANTIME,
WE NEED TO WORK
ON A WAY OF GETTING
YOU OUT OF HERE.
YEAH. WELL, WE DID THAT,
REMEMBER,
AND HERE I AM RIGHT BACK
ON THE INSIDE.
-WELL, JOHN...
-NO, MAN. NO MORE RUNNING.
IT'S TIME I FACED
THIS HEAD-ON,
FIGHT THESE
TRUMPED UP CHARGES.
THAT'S AN IMPROVEMENT
FROM LAST TIME.
ROGER THAT. I'M GONNA
SHOW WALKER
THAT HE PICKED
THE WRONG SOLDIER
TO SCREW WITH.
WE NEED TO HAVE
SOME KIND OF PLAN.
I'M GONNA NEED ONE
HELL OF A LAWYER.
I MIGHT KNOW A GUY.
UGH. AGH.
MY CAPTAINS WARNED ME
THAT YOU'D BE A RISK,
AN AMERICAN BRATVA.
[SPEAKS RUSSIAN]
BUT I THOUGHT THAT
YOU COULD BE USEFUL.
I DID WHAT YOU
ASKED ME TO DO.
I TRIED TO BLOW UP
KOVAR'S CASINO.
NO. ALL THAT YOU WERE
INTERESTED IN
WAS KILLING
KONSTANTINE KOVAR
BUT NOT FOR THE BRATVA.
FOR YOURSELF,
FOR A WOMAN.
KOVAR TOLD ME
EVERYTHING.
KOVAR...IS
A GOVERNMENT AGENT,
AND THE DEAL THAT
YOU MADE WITH HIM
BETRAYS THE BRATVA.
YOUR VENDETTA BETRAYS
THE BRATVA.
MY DEAL WITH KOVAR
BENEFITS OUR
BROTHERHOOD,
AND IN ANY CASE,
I AM PAKHAN.
MY DECISIONS
ARE THE LAW,
AND I WILL GET
OBEDIENCE FROM YOU,
EVEN IF I HAVE TO
BEAT IT INTO YOU.
IS THIS WHY YOU
JOIN BRATVA, HMM,
TO GET TO KOVAR,
BECAUSE YOU HAD SOME
PROMISE TO HER, HMM?
YOU DON'T HAVE TO DROP
EVERYTHING AND FLY HOME, THEA.
I'LL STILL BE HERE
WHEN THE CONFERENCE IS OVER,
AND THE WAY OLIVER
DESCRIBES IT,
YOU'RE THE ONE
THAT'S DOING ALL
THE HEAVY LIFTING
AT THE MAYOR'S OFFICE.
I GUESS SPONTANEOUS
RESURRECTION IS AS GOOD
AS ANY REASON
FOR A PARTY.
-BUT...
-BUT WE HAVEN'T EVEN BURIED
DETECTIVE MALONE
YET.
IT FEELS WEIRD
TO BE CELEBRATING?
IT DOESN'T FEEL
WEIRD TO YOU?
Y-YES, WEIRD, YEAH.
WEIRD OR...I GUESS.
AFTER THE PAST 4 YEARS,
IT'S JUST HARD FOR ME
TO ACCEPT GOOD NEWS.
RENE: HSS.
WEIRD, MAN.
SHE WAS DEAD.
NOW SHE'S NOT.
WELL, THAT'S
TIME TRAVEL FOR YOU.
WELL, I DON'T MEAN
LAUREL BEING BACK
IS WHAT'S WEIRD.
IT'S HOW YOU'RE ALL
REACTING TO IT
LIKE IT'S
HAPPENED BEFORE.
IT'S HAPPENED BEFORE?
THE LANCE SISTERS
HAVE A HABIT
OF COMING BACK TO LIFE.
WAIT, WHAT?
YO, CURTIS.
COME BACK INSIDE.
WE'RE GONNA MAKE A TOAST.
DOESN'T FEEL RIGHT
TO BE...
GATHERING AROUND
LIKE THIS.
DETECTIVE MALONE
IS DEAD,
EVELYN BETRAYED US,
AND PROMETHEUS
IS STILL OUT THERE.
WE SHOULD BE TRYING
TO FIND HIM,
MAKING HIM PAY
FOR EVERYTHING.
OLIVER: A LITTLE
OVER A YEAR AGO,
I...I STOOD RIGHT HERE,
AND I REMARKED THAT
I WISHED
IT WASN'T JUST
THE DARK TIMES
THAT BROUGHT US TOGETHER.
WITH ALL THE LOSS
THAT WE HAVE SUFFERED,
I THINK IT'S IMPORTANT
THAT WE EMBRACE
THE MIRACLES, TOO,
AND THAT WE REMEMBER
THEY ARE STILL POSSIBLE.
WELCOME HOME, LAUREL.
CHEERS.
HMM.
RORY: HEY.
FELICITY: WHAT?!
-SORRY.
-GOD.
I WASN'T EXPECTING
ANYONE HERE.
IT'S LATE.
I...I DON'T SLEEP MUCH
OR AT ALL.
SIDE EFFECT OF WEARING
HAUNTED RAGS, I GUESS,
SO I FIGURED
I'D TRAIN.
WHAT'S THAT?
IT'S NOTHING.
IT'S, UH...IT'S,
UH, MY Q-MAIL,
YOU KNOW, MY FACECHAT,
SNAPBOOK STUFF.
ALL THE KIDS ARE DOING
THESE NEW, CRAZY
SOCIAL MEDIA THINGS.
YOU KNOW, I JUST...
-YOU'RE RUNNING A DNA ANALYSIS.
-YEAH, I AM
ON LAUREL'S GLASS.
THAT, WHAT, YOU TOOK
FROM THE PARTY?
OH. IF BY PARTY,
YOU MEAN MY
BRILLIANT RUSE
TO COLLECT HER DNA,
THEN, YES, YOU
ARE CORRECT.
-WOW.
-YEAH.
YOU KNOW, THERE'S
LOOKING A GIFT HORSE
IN THE MOUTH,
AND THEN THERE'S...
BEING DRIVEN
BY PARANOID DELUSIONS,
DRAWING COMPARISONS
ON GENETIC BASE PAIRS?
YES, I'M AWARE,
THANK YOU.
-I...YEAH. YEAH.
-YEAH.
[COMPUTER BEEPING]
WELL?
DNA MATCHES.
OK. SO WE CAN RULE
OUT SHAPE SHIFTER.
-YEAH.
-OOH. WHAT ABOUT,
UH, EVIL TWIN?
-OH...NO.
-OK. I WAS JOKING.
NO. NO.
NO, NO, NO, NO.
-SHE ACTUALLY HAS AN EVIL TWIN.
-SERIOUSLY?
YEAH. SHE'S LOCKED UP
IN S.T.A.R. LABS.
I'LL EXPLAIN LATER.
RIGHT NOW, WE HAVE TO
CALL CISCO.
[SONIC SCREAM]
[EARS RINGING]
FINALLY. IT'S ABOUT TIME
SOMEONE FIGURED IT OUT.
YOU KNOW, I AM SO SICK
AND TIRED
OF PLAYING THIS WEAK,
VULNERABLE LAUREL.
SHE'S SUCH A PILL,
IT'S PATHETIC.
[SONIC SCREAM]
YOU KNOW, THE ONE PROBLEM
WITH MY ABILITY
IS THAT I CAN NEVER HEAR
MY POOR, LITTLE VICTIMS SCREAM.
[SONIC SCREAM]
OLIVER: LAUREL!
ARE YOU HURT?
I'M GONNA BE OK,
BUT...
IT'S NOT OUR LAUREL.
SO THAT LAUREL'S FROM
AN ALTERNATE REALITY?
TECHNICALLY, SHE'S
FROM A PARALLEL UNIVERSE.
WE'RE ON EARTH-1.
THE LOOK-ALIKE LAUREL'S
FROM ANOTHER EARTH, EARTH-2.
OVER THERE, WE ALL
HAVE DOPPELGANGER
VERSIONS OF OURSELVES
WHO COULD BE VERY SIMILAR
OR INCREDIBLY DIFFERENT
BASED ON AN INFINITE
AMOUNT OF VARIABLES.
I WOULD LOVE TO SEE
WHAT I'M LIKE ON EARTH-2.
OH, GOD.
WHAT IF I'M STRAIGHT?
RORY: OK. ONE THING
I DON'T GET...
WELL, YOU KNOW,
THERE'S A LIST
OF THINGS I DON'T GET,
BUT AT THE TOP IS
THIS FAKE LAUREL
SEEMED TO KNOW,
LIKE, EVERYTHING.
-HOW'S THAT POSSIBLE?
-PROMETHEUS.
CISCO JUST SENT
THIS OVER.
IT IS FROM 3 DAYS AGO,
BUT NOBODY KNEW
BECAUSE NO ALARMS
WERE TRIPPED.
IT'S LIKE HE'S
A DYBBUK.
YEAH. I DON'T KNOW
WHAT THAT IS.
ONE QUESTION.
JUST ONE?
CURTIS: PROMETHEUS BREAKS
INTO S.T.A.R. LABS,
GETS NOT LAUREL,
HENRY HIGGINSES HER
INTO COMING OFF
AS REAL LAUREL.
THAT'S A LOT OF HOOPS.
WHY NOT JUST KILL YOU?
OLIVER: HE TOLD ME
HE DOESN'T WANT TO.
HE'S PROVING TO ME
THAT I WILL DESTROY
MYSELF
AND EVERYONE
CLOSE TO ME.
WELL, HE'S GONNA BE
DISAPPOINTED
BUT WE ARE GONNA PUT
BLACK SIREN BACK IN HER CAGE.
BLACK SIREN?
EVERY META GETS A NICKNAME.
LET'S HIT
THE STREETS.
SHE IS NOT LEAVING
THE CITY UNTIL
THIS IS OVER.
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?
JOHN NEEDS MY HELP
AS MAYOR.
I WILL BE
ON MY CELL.
GREGOR: LET ME SEE
IF I UNDERSTAND.
YOU CARRY THIS GIRL
WITH YOU
THROUGH ALL OF YOUR
TRIALS AND TRIBULATIONS
ON SOME ISLAND.
-LIAN YU?
-YES.
AND YET WHEN YOU GET
OFF THIS ISLAND,
YOU DO NOT RETURN HOME.
NO. INSTEAD, YOU
COME TO A COUNTRY
WHERE YOU KNOW
JUST ONE PERSON,
YOU JOIN MY ORGANIZATION,
PASS ALL OF OUR TESTS
AND ALL OF THIS.
SO YOU CAN
AVENGE THE DEATH
OF A DIFFERENT WOMAN?
THE WOMAN IN THAT PHOTO'S
NAME IS LAUREL,
AND I DIDN'T RETURN HOME
BECAUSE AFTER...
EVERYTHING
I'VE BEEN THROUGH,
EVERYTHING I'VE DONE...
SHE WOULDN'T
RECOGNIZE ME.
NOW I SEE.
YOU THINK THAT
YOU'VE BEEN MADE
INTO A MONSTER.
BETTER A MONSTER
THAN A SELL-OUT.
HOW MUCH DID KOVAR
PAY YOU TO BETRAY
YOUR BROTHERS?
UNH!
YOUR FAILURE IS
UNACCEPTABLE.
YOU SHOULD HAVE
LET ME KILL THEM
INSTEAD OF SOME STUPID
ROLE-PLAYING IDEA.
IT IS NOT YOUR PLACE
TO QUESTION MY AGENDA.
YOUR FREEDOM, YOUR LIFE
IS CONTINGENT
ON FOLLOWING MY ORDERS.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND?
HEY. THANKS
FOR COMING IN.
NO PROBLEM.
I WANTED TO TALK
WITH YOU, AS WELL.
OK. UH, THE FILE
THAT I SENT YOU.
JOHN DIGGLE IS
MY FORMER BODYGUARD
AND CURRENT FRIEND.
AND FACING
A COURT-MARTIAL
FOR ESPIONAGE,
MURDER, ESCAPING
A FEDERAL PRISON,
AND ATTEMPTED THEFT
OF A WMD.
HE'S INNOCENT.
SO WHY DID HE ESCAPE
A FEDERAL PRISON?
BECAUSE HE'S INNOCENT.
THE MAN WHO FRAMED HIM
IS A 3-STAR GENERAL.
JOHN DID NOT THINK
THAT HE WOULD GET
A FAIR TRIAL
IN THE COURT SYSTEM,
WHICH IS WHERE
YOU COME IN.
OLIVER, I'M
A CITY PROSECUTOR,
NOT A MILITARY
DEFENSE ATTORNEY.
THAT'S WHY I THOUGHT
OF YOU.
JOHN NEEDS SOMEONE
OUTSIDE OF THE MILITARY
INFRASTRUCTURE.
THIS IS THE ONLY WAY
FOR JUSTICE TO GET DONE.
HE DOESN'T EVEN KNOW ME.
JOHN DIGGLE IS
A GOOD MAN.
HE'S BETTER THAN
THE BOTH OF US PUT TOGETHER.
GETTING
THE JUDGE ADVOCATES TO
EVEN TO AUTHORIZE ME
TO PRO HOC IN
WOULD BE A MIRACLE.
SOUNDS LIKE A YES?
EH, MORE LIKE
A "GOD HELP ME"
AND YOUR FRIEND.
HEY. I WILL OWE
YOU ONE.
THIS IS WORTH
MORE THAN ONE.
UM, ACTUALLY, UH, HEY.
UH, AS IF WE DON'T HAVE
ENOUGH ON OUR PLATE,
HAVE YOU HEARD
ABOUT THE CIRCUMSTANCES
SURROUNDING THE DEATH
OF DETECTIVE MALONE?
NO.
HE WAS WEARING
PROMETHEUS' OUTFIT
WHEN HE WAS KILLED.
HIS MOUTH WAS
TAPED SHUT,
A SWORD TAPED
INTO HIS HAND.
THERE WAS A WIRELESS
SPEAKER FOUND
ON THE SCENE.
UH...
WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
THAT IT LOOKS LIKE
MALONE WAS SET UP,
THE GREEN ARROW WAS
MANIPULATED
INTO KILLING HIM.
BY PROMETHEUS?
I MADE SURE THE COPS
WHO CAUGHT THE SCENE
WON'T SAY ANYTHING,
AND I'M HANDLING
THE CORONER.
I JUST WANTED TO
LET YOU KNOW.
YEAH, THAT YOU'RE
GONNA...
COVER THIS UP.
IF THE CITY FINDS OUT
THAT A MEMBER
OF THE ANTI-CRIME UNIT
WAS PROMETHEUS,
THERE'S GONNA BE PANIC.
IF THE GREEN ARROW
KILLED A MEMBER
OF THE ANTI-CRIME UNIT...
HOO...THERE'S GONNA
BE PANIC.
EITHER WAY...
GOT TO KEEP
THIS QUIET.
IT'S THE ONLY WAY
TO SEE JUSTICE DONE.
[CELL PHONE VIBRATING]
THIS IS MAYOR QUEEN.
OLIVER, IT'S ME...LAUREL.
DON'T YOU SAY
HER NAME.
I...I'M SORRY. WHAT I DID
WAS UNFORGIVABLE,
BUT...BUT HE MADE
ME DO IT...PROMETHEUS.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN
HE MADE YOU?
HE THREATENED TO
KILL ME.
YOU HAVE TO
HELP ME, PLEASE.
CAN YOU MEET?
WHERE?
THE BLACK CANARY
STATUE.
I'LL BE THERE SOON.
NOW WAIT...
FELICITY: ANY SIGN
OF BLACK SIREN?
OLIVER: NOT YET,
BUT EVERYONE'S GONNA
STAND DOWN AND DO NOT...
YEAH, WE GET IT.
FELICITY: YEAH?
WELL, I SAY TAKE HER DOWN.
OVERWATCH!
YOU HEARD THE BOSS.
THIS IS AN EYES-ONLY
OPERATION FOR YOU.
I HAVE EYES ON.
BOYS, I JUST PUT YOU
ON A SEPARATE CHANNEL.
UH, WHY?
SO IF BLACK SIREN
LOOKS LIKE SHE'S
ABOUT TO DOUBLE-CROSS...
AND TRUST ME, SHE WILL...
YOU HAVE IT ON MY AUTHORITY
TO LIGHT HER UP.
THANK YOU
FOR MEETING ME.
YOU DON'T BELIEVE ME.
PROMETHEUS THREATENED
TO KILL ME.
YOU'RE A VERY
CONVINCING LIAR.
I DESERVE THAT.
ACCORDING
TO S.T.A.R. LABS,
YOU'D HELP PROMETHEUS
EVEN IF HE WASN'T
THREATENING ANYONE.
THAT'S WHAT THEY THINK.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
I CAN HELP YOU
TRACK HIM.
TAKE HER OUT.
[SONIC SCREAM]
I TOLD YOU
NOT TO ENGAGE!
RORY: WE KNOW.
IT'S JUST...
SHE, UM, SPOOKED US.
YOU GUYS ARE
TERRIBLE LIARS.
I TOLD THEM TO
MOVE ON HER.
SINCE WHEN ARE THEY
TAKING ORDERS
FROM YOU?
I DON'T KNOW,
BUT I KIND OF LIKE IT.
SHE HAD SOMETHING
IN HER HAND.
SHE HAD HER PHONE
WELL, IT DIDN'T
LOOK LIKE HER PHONE,
AND I DON'T TRUST HER,
SO I TOLD THEM
TO MOVE.
I HAD THE SITUATION
UNDER CONTROL.
SHE TOLD ME
THAT PROMETHEUS
FORCED HER TO DO THIS.
NOW WHETHER OR NOT
THAT IS TRUE,
SHE WAS GOING TO GIVE US
VALUABLE INTEL ON HIM.
SHE'S PLAYING YOU,
OLIVER.
I UNDERSTAND THAT YOU'RE
SUSPICIOUS OF HER,
AND I KNOW THIS LAUREL
IS FROM ANOTHER EARTH,
THAT THIS IS NOT
OUR LAUREL,
BUT WE DON'T KNOW WHY.
WE DON'T.
I TOLD YOU. BLINDERS.
HEY. YOU GOOD?
WHY WOULDN'T I BE?
JUST GOT MY ASS KICKED
FOR THE BAZILLIONTH TIME.
SO BASICALLY,
I'M TRADING A CELL
IN CENTRAL CITY
FOR A CELL
IN STARLING CITY.
ACTUALLY, ON THIS EARTH,
WE CALL IT STAR CITY.
I'M SORRY
ABOUT THE CELL.
I TOLD YOU THAT
PROMETHEUS WAS
GOING TO KILL ME,
AND THAT IS WHY I DID
WHAT I DID.
YOUR HISTORY ON EARTH-2
WOULD SUGGEST YOU
HAD OTHER REASONS.
YOU DON'T TRUST ME?
CAN YOU BLAME ME?
NO, BECAUSE ON MY WORLD,
YOU'VE BEEN DEAD
FOR 10 YEARS NOW.
I MOVED TO CENTRAL CITY
FOR A FRESH START.
THAT'S WHERE
THIS HAPPENED,
AND FROM THEM,
IT WAS JUST ONE BAD
CHOICE AFTER ANOTHER,
AND I GUESS ONCE YOU
LET THE DARKNESS INSIDE
IT NEVER COMES OUT,
AND NOW I AM TRAPPED
IN A PARALLEL DIMENSION,
TELLING MY SOB STORY
TO THE DOPPELGANGER
OF THE MAN THAT...
THAT I LOVED.
SO STOP RUNNING.
FACE THE DARKNESS.
HOW DOES THAT WORK?
FIRST, YOU NEED TO
TELL ME EVERYTHING
THAT YOU KNOW
ABOUT PROMETHEUS,
EVERYTHING,
AND THEN WE KEEP
YOU SAFE.
AND YOU'RE WILLING
TO DO THAT WHY?
WHY? BECAUSE I LOOK
LIKE SOMEONE YOU
USED TO KNOW.
SOMEONE ONCE TOLD ME
THAT A CIRCUMSTANCE
COULD MAKE SOMETHING
POISON OR NECTAR.
WHAT THEY MEANT WAS
THAT WE GET TO CHOOSE
WHAT WE ARE,
WE GET TO CHOOSE
WHO WE ARE,
SO TELL ME...
WHO ARE YOU?
RENE: YO. HOLD UP.
I'LL WALK WITH YOU.
I'M HOPPING
THE "L" LINE.
-YOU TAKING THE SUBWAY?
-NO. I'M JUST GONNA WALK.
BY YOURSELF?
YOU...YOU DO HAVE
A TENDENCY TO GET
YOUR ASS KICKED.
DID YOU JUST COME
ALL THE WAY OUT HERE
JUST TO INSULT ME?
I'M JUST GOING HOME,
BUT THAT WAS MERELY
A PRODUCT...
I'LL SEE YOU
TOMORROW, RENE.
DAMN YOU SOFT.
I THOUGHT HAD
SOME WIT, MAN.
WHAT, THE BLACK SIREN
KICKED THAT OUT
OF YOU, TOO?
NOT NOW, MAN.
NOT NOW.
WHAT, DID I HURT...
HURT YOUR FEELINGS?
JUST LET ME BE, MAN.
WHAT'S YOUR
DAMAGE, HOSS?
I MEAN, EVER SINCE
THE PARTY, YOU BEEN OFF.
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO BE
THE HAPPY ONE, REMEMBER?
LIKE WHAT?!
LIKE THIS?!
WHAT THE HELL'S
GOTTEN INTO YOU?
I BEEN STABBED, SHOT AT,
PUT IN A COMA,
HAD MAGIC POWERS
USED ON ME,
SUPERPOWERS USED
AGAINST ME,
AND FOR WHAT?
WHAT DIFFERENCE
DOES IT MAKE?
ALL IT'S DONE IS COST
ME MY BLOOD,
MY SWEAT...
MY PAUL.
IT COST ME PAUL.
THAT'S YOUR
HUSBAND, RIGHT?
WAS.
HE LEFT ME.
BECAUSE OF YOU BEING
MR. TERRIFIC?
BECAUSE OF ME TRYING,
BUT I'M NEVER
GONNA MAKE IT
BECAUSE I DON'T HAVE
WHAT IT TAKES...
SO NOW I DON'T
HAVE ANYTHING.
[QUICK BREATHS]
HEY. KEEP YOUR
WRIST STRAIGHT
JUST SO YOU DON'T
JAM IT.
MMM.
I, UH...I SPOKE
TO LAUREL.
WHEN DID SHE BECOME
LAUREL?
SHE'S NOT LAUREL,
NOT LAUREL LAUREL.
SHE'S NOT OUR
LAUREL, OK?
OK. FELICITY, I'M...
I CAN'T PRETEND
TO UNDERSTAND
PARALLEL WORLDS,
BUT IF I'M GONNA
BELIEVE IN THEM...
AND...AND I KIND OF
HAVE TO NOW...
THEN I NEED TO BELIEVE
THAT DIFFERENCES
ARE CAUSED
BY CIRCUMSTANCES,
SO WHY CAN'T WE CHANGE
THIS LAUREL'S CIRCUMSTANCES?
YOU THINK THAT
YOU CAN SAVE HER?
AFTER SHE'S THROWN IN
WITH PROMETHEUS?
UNDER DURESS.
I...
HEH. I THINK
I CAN REACH HER.
WHEN DID YOU FIND
THE TIME TO GET
A PH.D. IN PSYCHOLOGY?
I'M A QUICK STUDY.
MY NAME'S ADRIAN CHASE,
STAR CITY DISTRICT ATTORNEY.
JOHN DIGGLE, CONVICT.
YOU HERE TO ADD
TO MY CHARGES?
NOT EXACTLY.
I'M REPRESENTING YOU.
YOUR FRIEND OLIVER'S
PERSUASIVE,
PLUS HE'S MY BOSS. HEH.
GENERAL WALKER,
THE GUY WHO WANTS YOU
OUT OF THE PICTURE,
YOU KNOW WHO
HIS BOSS IS?
THE PRESIDENT.
SO YOU CAN IMAGINE
HOW DIFFICULT
THIS IS
ABOUT TO BE.
MR. CHASE,
MP OFFICERS ARE HERE
TO REMAND
THE PRISONER INTO
THEIR CUSTODY.
WAIT. I THOUGHT I WAS
SUPPOSED TO STAY
HERE FOR NOW.
YOU'RE UNDER THEIR
JURISDICTION.
-THE TRIAL...
-THE TRIAL?
MAN, THERE WON'T BE
A TRIAL.
AS SOON AS I'M OUT
OF HERE,
WALKER WILL CONCOCT
SOME REASON TO PUT
A BULLET IN MY HEAD.
AHH. SERGEANT DIGGLE. HEH.
GOOD TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
HAVE SERGEANT DIGGLE
CLEARED OUT OF HERE
AND READY
FOR TRANSPORT ASAP.
GOT A LONG RIDE BACK
TO LANGHAM AHEAD OF US.
SO TELL ME...
WHAT HAPPENED
BETWEEN YOU
AND OLIVER?
DID HE FIND
SOMEONE ELSE,
OR WERE YOU NOT
TALL ENOUGH?
DO YOU HAVE
A SISTER?
BECAUSE I HEAR
HE LOVES SISTERS.
OLIVER SEEMS TO THINK
THAT BECAUSE YOU
LOOK LIKE LAUREL
THAT YOU COULD
BECOME HER.
AND WHAT DO YOU THINK?
I THINK...
YOU SHOULD GET USED
TO LIVING IN CAGES.
THERE'S A PART OF HIM
THAT BLAMES HIMSELF
FOR LAUREL'S DEATH.
IT'S WHO HE IS,
SO WHEN HE LOOKS
AT YOU...
HE DOESN'T JUST
SEE LAUREL.
HE SEES A SHOT
AT REDEMPTION.
WOW. IT MUST BE
REALLY FRUSTRATING
THAT HE DOESN'T
LISTEN TO YOU.
OH, I'M USED TO IT.
[ALARM BLARING]
[SONIC SCREAM]
HOW'D SHE ESCAPE?
THE POWER WENT OFF
AND THE DAMPENER
ALONG WITH IT.
RENE: AND GOLDILOCKS
HUFFED AND PUFFED
AND BLEW THE DOOR DOWN.
THAT'S NOT EXACTLY
HOW HER POWER WORKS.
WAS THERE SOMETHING
WRONG WITH CISCO'S SPECS?
BECAUSE DIDN'T WE JUST
REPLICATE THE PIPELINE
SECURITY SYSTEM?
WE DID.
I LET HER GO.
WHAT?
DAMN, BLONDIE!
I'M SORRY, BUT, EVERYONE,
JUST RELAX.
IT PUT TRACKING NANITES
IN HER WATER,
THE SAME ONCE WE USED
TO FIND MALCOLM MERLYN.
THAT MAKES
EVERYTHING BETTER!
ISN'T THAT EXACTLY HOW
YOU USED ANARKY
TO FIND DARHK LAST YEAR?
[SIGHS]
COULD WE HAVE
THE ROOM, PLEASE?
SERIOUSLY?
THIS IS GETTING GOOD.
RENE, RORY,
COME ON, GUYS.
YOU...
YOU COULD HAVE
BEEN HURT.
WHATEVER HAPPENED TO
"IF WE CHANGE
HER CIRCUMSTANCES"?
YOU RISKED YOUR LIFE TO
GET A LINE ON PROMETHEUS
BECAUSE OF BILLY.
WELL, NOW THAT YOU'RE
KILLING AGAIN,
I THOUGHT, "WHY NOT
PUT IT TO USE?"
NO. WE'RE GONNA GET
JUSTICE FOR BILLY.
BUT FIRST, WE NEED TO
TAKE CARE OF YOUR EX,
WHO'S NOT EVEN YOUR EX.
[COMPUTER BEEPS]
FELICITY ON RECORDING:
THERE'S A PART OF HIM
THAT BLAMES HIMSELF
FOR LAUREL'S DEATH.
IT'S WHO HE IS,
SO WHEN HE LOOKS
AT YOU,
HE SEES MORE THAN
JUST LAUREL.
HE SEES HIS SHOT
AT REDEMPTION.
IT'S LIKE I SAID.
YOU KNOW ME BETTER
THAN ALMOST ANYONE.
I FAILED LAUREL BEFORE.
I CAN'T...
I CAN'T FAIL HER AGAIN.
I DON'T HAVE TO REMIND
YOU THAT THIS ISN'T HER.
I KNOW.
OUR...OUR LAUREL'S GONE.
SHE'S THE LAST CHANCE
THAT I HAVE...OK?
BILLY IS MY
RESPONSIBILITY...
AND WE WILL GET JUSTICE
FOR HIM.
I'LL LET YOU KNOW
WHEN THE TRACKERS
METABOLIZE AND GO LIVE.
GREGOR: YOU'VE BEEN HERE
FOR JUST FEW MONTHS,
AND ALREADY YOU THINK
YOU KNOW EVERYTHING.
DID IT NOT OCCUR
TO YOU THAT I COULD
BE PLAYING KOVAR?
I...I DON'T
BELIEVE THAT.
OF COURSE YOU DON'T
BECAUSE YOU DON'T
UNDERSTAND
THAT CIRCUMSTANCES
ARE WHAT MAKES
A THING POISON
OR NECTAR.
YOU BELIEVE YOUR
FOOL'S ERRAND
TO KILL KOVAR
BECAUSE YOU THINK
THAT YOU ARE
RESPONSIBLE
FOR THIS DARKNESS
THAT'S INSIDE YOU.
LIKE BABY BLAMING
HIMSELF FOR BEING
LEFT OUT IN THE COLD
BY HIS MOTHER.
IF IT WEREN'T
FOR THAT ISLAND...
YOU WOULD BE
THAT HARMLESS
AMERICAN DOUCHEBAG
THAT YOU PRETENDED
TO BE IN KOVAR'S
CASINO.
[COUGHS]
SO I GUESS I'M...
JUST SUPPOSED TO
LISTEN TO YOU INSTEAD?
I CAN GIVE YOU FAMILY,
ONE THAT DOES NOT
SEE A MONSTER
BUT A BROTHER.
ALL I AM ASKING
IN RETURN
IS YOUR OBEDIENCE.
OR ELSE.
HMM.
OR ELSE...
[COCKS GUN]
YOU DON'T LEAVE
THIS ROOM ALIVE.
SO MOM AND DAD ARE
GOING 12 ROUNDS
UPSTAIRS.
THEY'RE JUST HAVING
A DISCUSSION.
LOOK. I...I KNOW THAT
I TOOK THE TEASING
TOO FAR EARLIER.
I CAN BE
AN ACQUIRED TASTE,
BUT...I'M SORRY TO HEAR
ABOUT PAUL
AND THAT I MADE YOU
FEEL WORSE ABOUT IT.
THANKS. THAT'S
REALLY BIG OF YOU.
SO WHAT ARE YOU
DOING DOWN HERE?
WELL, SINCE
THE BLACK SIREN'S CRY
WORKS ON A MORE POWERFUL
FREQUENCY THAN LAUREL'S,
THESE ARE USELESS.
SO I WAS TRYING TO SEE
IF THERE'S A WAY TO MAKE
THE DAMPENER PORTABLE
SO NEXT TIME
WE GO UP AGAINST HER...
YOU CAN TAKE
HER POWERS AWAY.
THAT'S AWESOME.
YEAH. WELL, IDEAS
ARE ONE THING.
EXECUTING THEM
IS ANOTHER.
-YOU DON'T GET IT, DO YOU?
-GET WHAT?
THAT MAYBE INSTEAD
OF BEATING YOURSELF UP
ABOUT WHAT YOU CAN'T DO,
TAKE A MOMENT
AND APPRECIATE
WHAT YOU CAN DO
BECAUSE IT'S
PRETTY BADASS.
GENERAL WALKER.
SORRY, GENERAL,
BUT I CANNOT LET YOU
TAKE JOHN DIGGLE
WITHOUT THE PROPER
PAPERWORK TURNED IN.
EXCUSE ME?
FORMS I-55 AND W-67
AND THE COMPLETED
TRANSFER ASSIGNMENT
SINGED BY
THE LANGHAM WARDEN.
NEVER SEEN A D.A. GET
INVOLVED
IN MILITARY MATTERS
AND ON THE DEFENSE SIDE.
I'M EXPANDING
MY PRACTICE.
ANYTHING ELSE?
IT'S NOT COMMON
FOR SOMEONE OF YOUR RANK
TO PERSONALLY SUPERVISE
A PRISONER TRANSFER.
I MAKE EXCEPTIONS
FOR TRAITORS AND TERRORISTS.
I'LL NEED A DISTRICT
JUDGE TO RATIFY
THE TRANSFER PAPERS.
THAT COULD TAKE
A FEW HOURS,
MAYBE EVEN A FEW DAYS.
DO YOU HAVE
THE ATTORNEY GENERAL
ON SPEED DIAL?
I DO, AND SHE
OWES ME A FAVOR.
I CAN HAVE YOU DISBARRED
IN 15 SECONDS.
NOW I EXPECT THE PRISONER
TO BE IN MY CUSTODY
IN 24 HOURS.
AM I CLEAR?
MM-HMM.
-TRACKER'S LIVE.
-WHERE IS SHE?
THE NANITES JUST
METABOLIZED.
I'M TRIANGULATING THEM
WITH THE KEYHOLE
SATELLITE FEED.
REMIND ME TO UPGRADE
OUR INTERNET TOMORROW.
GOT IT. 1400 BLOCK
BRAND BOULEVARD.
PULLING UP KEYHOLE NOW.
CURTIS: I THINK I HAVE
SOMETHING THAT WILL HELP,
A MOBILE VERSION
OF THE DAMPENER
FROM S.T.A.R. LABS.
THINK?
I MIGHT NEED
SOME MORE TIME WITH IT.
THE CIRCUITRY'S
PRETTY COMPLEX
I'M FEELING A LOT
OF PRESSURE,
AND I JUST WANT...
FELICITY CAN COME WITH
AND HELP YOU.
HOLD UP. NOT GETTING
A GOOD ENOUGH READING OFF
THE THERMAL IMAGING.
THERE'S NO WAY TO TELL
IF BLACK SIREN IS ACTUALLY
WITH PROMETHEUS,
AND THE WHOLE POINT
OF DOING THIS IS TO CATCH
THAT SON OF A...
BITCH.
WE NEED TO WAIT TILL
WE GET VISUAL CONFIRMATION
ON PROMETHEUS.
WE'RE NOT WAITING
FOR ANYTHING.
WE'RE GONNA BRING
HER IN RIGHT NOW.
GET ON BOARD
WITH THIS.
SUIT UP.
THIS IS PRIVATE PROPERTY.
MA'AM, WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE?
I'M JUST WAITING
FOR A FRIEND.
[SONIC SCREAM]
SHE'S HERE. CREATE
A PERIMETER. GO!
[SONIC SCREAM]
-DID YOU HEAR THAT?
-HEAR WHAT?
KIDDING. I THINK PEOPLE
IN FLORIDA HEARD THAT.
WE NEED TO HURRY.
SHE...SHE WAS CRAZY.
SHE COULD SCREAM.
RUN AWAY
AND CALL THE POLICE.
[GUNS COCK]
DON'T MOVE, TRINITY.
OH. I THOUGHT YOU'D
BE SOMEONE ELSE.
DISAPPOINTING.
[SONIC SCREAM]
-THIS SHOULD DO IT.
-ARE YOU SURE?
NO, BUT WE'RE
OUT OF TIME.
[SWORD DRAWN]
PROMETHEUS.
[SONIC SCREAM]
DIAZEPAM. THAT SHOULD
SLOW YOU DOWN.
[EARS RINGING]
DIAZEPAM...YOU COULD SAY
I HAVE A TOLERANCE,
BUT YOU SHOULDN'T BE
WORRYING ABOUT ME
RIGHT NOW.
AHH. FELICITY.
I AM SO SORRY,
BUT I THINK IT'S
ABOUT TIME THAT
I KILL YOU.
FELICITY OR ME!
LAUREL!
DON'T DO THIS.
THERE'S NO COMING BACK
FOR YOU.
IF YOU KILL FELICITY,
THEN YOU'RE KILLING
THAT PART OF YOURSELF
THAT EXISTED
BEFORE YOU LOST
YOUR FAMILY.
IF YOU END THIS NOW,
THEN WE CAN FIND
THAT PERSON AGAIN...
TOGETHER.
SHE WAS NEVER THERE.
[SONIC SCREAM]
[SCREAM BREAKING UP]
YOU REALLY NEED TO SHUT
YOUR DAMN MOUTH.
HEY, PUMPKIN.
OHH!
HEY.
KEPT MY WRIST STRAIGHT.
YOU TURN ME OVER,
I'LL BE DEAD
BEFORE YOU GET BACK
TO YOUR OFFICE.
I BELIEVE YOU.
YOU KNOW,
WHEN I WOKE UP,
I DIDN'T THINK THAT
I'D BE PISSING OFF
ONE OF THE MOST POWERFUL
MEN IN THE MILITARY.
[WHISPERING]
HIT ME.
WHAT?
[WHISPERING]
HIT ME.
UNH!
WHAT THE HELL IS
GOING ON HERE?
YOUR PRISONER
JUST DECKED ME.
UNSATISFIED WITH
YOUR LEGAL COUNSEL?
WHO KNOWS, BUT...
WE ARE IN STARLING COUNTY,
AND IN COUNTY CODE,
SECTION 47.15,
IT SPECIFICALLY STATES
THAT THE DISTRICT ATTORNEY,
ME, CAN SUPERSEDE
TRANSFERS TO OTHER
JURISDICTIONS
IF THE SUSPECT COMMITS
A SECONDARY CRIME
WITHIN MY JURISDICTION.
ATTACKING A CITY OFFICIAL'S
A VERY SERIOUS OFFENSE,
MR. DIGGLE.
I THINK I'M GONNA HAVE TO
PROSECUTE THIS ONE MYSELF.
IT COULD TAKE A WHILE.
FINE. I'LL BE BACK
WITH A WRIT SIGNED
BY THE PRESIDENT.
CAN'T WAIT. I'VE ALWAYS
WANTED HER AUTOGRAPH.
YOU KNOW HOW
PEOPLE HATE TO SAY,
"I TOLD YOU SO"?
I DON'T HATE IT.
I FRIGGIN' LOVE IT.
YOU REALLY WEREN'T
KIDDING ABOUT THAT
ACQUIRED TASTE THING.
IT'S LIKE SHOOTING FISH
IN A BARREL WITH YOU.
IT'S COOL.
I CAN TAKE IT.
YOU WERE RIGHT, RENE.
I NEED TO START
EMBRACING WHAT I CAN DO
FOR THE TEAM INSTEAD
OF WHAT I CAN'T.
THAT'S WHAT I'M
TALKING ABOUT.
MORE TINKERING
AND LESS FIGHTING.
WELL, I...I WOULDN'T
EXACTLY CALL IT
TINKERING.
-OH, ONE MORE THING.
-YEAH. WHAT'S UP?
YOU PUT YOUR HANDS
ON ME LIKE THAT
ONE MORE TIME,
AND I'LL KICK
YOUR ASS.
HA! HEH HEH HEH.
OH. GOOD TALK.
OHH!
OOH!
THIS IS WHY I
USUALLY LEAVE
THE PUNCHING
TO YOU GUYS.
IT WAS A MEMORABLE PUNCH.
OW. TYPING IS GOING
TO BE A...BIT
OF A CHALLENGE
THE NEXT COUPLE DAYS.
SERVES ME RIGHT.
BECAUSE I LET
BLACK SIREN GO,
ONE OF THOSE GUARDS
COULD HAVE GOTTEN
KILLED.
WE ALMOST GOT
PROMETHEUS.
YOUR PLAN WORKED.
HE WAS THERE.
NO. IF IT WORKED,
WE'D BE PUTTING CUFFS
ON HIM RIGHT NOW.
WE'LL GET THERE.
WE'LL GET HIM.
I'M SORRY
SHE WASN'T HER.
I KNOW.
I'M SORRY ABOUT BILLY.
HE WAS A GOOD MAN.
LIKE YOU.
SO I'M GUESSING THAT
LAUREL IS ON HER WAY
BACK TO CENTRAL CITY
THEN.
SECURE LOCKUP
AT ARGUS.
I'M KEEPING HER CLOSE
BECAUSE...
IF THERE'S ANYTHING
LEFT OF THE REAL
LAUREL IN THERE...
I'M GONNA FIND IT.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I COULD REALLY GET USED
TO THIS NEWFOUND
OPTIMISM OF YOURS.
I'M DONE ASKING.
FOLLOW ME OR DIE.
[GUNFIRE]
FIND OUT
WHAT'S HAPPENING.
[GUNFIRE]
HELLO, MR. QUEEN.
MY NAME IS TALIA.
I'VE BEEN LOOKING
FOR YOU.
FELICITY: JUST DOESN'T
FEEL RIGHT,
THEM JUST TAKING IT
AWAY LIKE THIS.
WE SHOULD BUILD
A NEW ONE.
I THINK WE CAN
DO BETTER.
YEAH. WHAT ARE YOU
THINKING?
I HAVEN'T KEPT MY
PROMISE TO LAUREL.
YOU'RE GONNA TRAIN
A NEW BLACK CANARY?
I THINK THAT SOMEWHERE
OUT THERE THERE IS
A WOMAN WORTHY
OF LAUREL'S LEGACY,
AND...NOW ALL WE GOT TO
DO IS FIND HER.
[HEAVY METAL PLAYING]
MAN: ♪ 10,000 WATTS
OF POWER... ♪
YOU BOYS WANT
ANOTHER ROUND?
NO. I WAS THINKING
OF ORDERING
SOMETHING THAT'S,
UH, NOT
ON THE MENU, HUH?
HEY. WHERE YOU
GOING, BABY?
WOMAN: SERIOUSLY,
COULD YOU TWO BE
ANY MORE
OF A CLICHE?
DON'T WORRY, SWEETHEART.
THERE'S PLENTY OF ME
TO GO AROUND.
I THOUGHT PEOPLE
LIKE YOU ONLY EXISTED
IN THE MOVIES.
YOU KNOW, TWO GUYS
TRYING TO OVERCOMPENSATE
FOR THEIR LACK OF MANHOOD
BY TAKING IT OUT
ON A DEFENSELESS WOMAN.
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA
DO ABOUT IT?
[SONIC SCREAM]
THAT.