[Oliver]Last season onArrow...
Are you offering to help me find my son?
I want us to find both of our sons.
I need your help.
[grunts]
-Oliver's gonna come for us.
-Yeah, I'm counting on it, sis.
Adrian, where is my son?
When we get to the airplane,
I'm not gonna get on it.
-What?
-I'm not leaving William behind.
Don't do that.
He's rigged the entire island
with explosives.
They're remotely linked
to some sort of dead man's switch,
if he dies, it detonates all the devices.
William, come here.
Are you okay? Are you all right?
He wants you to kill him
so it kills all of us.
No, Adrian!
[gunshot]
-[arrow whizzes]
-[man groans]
[gunshots]
[man groans]
[men groaning]
I'm on site. No sign of Faust.
[both grunting]
He's not at his last-known, either.
Well, his ordinance is.
If Faust is moving from bombs to missiles,
it makes you wonder
what else he's changed up.
Exactly. Stay sharp.
-[gunshot]
-[groans]
[gun cocking]
Boss says stay sharp, hoss.
[grunting]
[man] Faust, it's clear.
Apologies. Won't be but a minute.
If you have the opportunity,
please advise your mayor
that next time someone threatens to launch
a ballistic missile at his city,
he really should pay up.
Disappointing.
[groaning]
That's an MGM140. It's fire and forget.
You can't stop it.
You can't disarm it.
No.
But I have a very smart friend who can.
[beeping]
My T-Sphere spoofed
the missile's guidance system.
I'm drawing it back to the water.
You look troubled.
As if detonation stirred
unpleasant memories.
Chase sabotaged the plane,
we can't get off the island.
There's an A.R.G.U.S. supply ship
on the eastern shore.
That's on the other side of the island.
Slade knows where it is, go now!
Hey, Oliver says there's a boat
on the eastern shore.
You lot won't make it in time.
I'll take my own chances.
I always hated that guy.
-What are we gonna do now?
-What about the plane?
You said you couldn't get it fixed.
For shielding us from the blast,
it should work just fine.
It's not like there's a whole lot
of other options.
No, he's right. Okay,
it's better than nothing. Let's go.
[Samantha] No!
I have to find William.
[Felicity] Samantha?
Samantha?
Look, you go to the plane, okay?
I'll get her.
-[grunts]
-Careful. Let's go.
-You should be on the plane.
-I'm not taking refuge
from 100 bombs without you.
-It's more like 250.
-Go! Go! Go!
What's this?
Remarks for the police academy
graduation ceremony.
It seems my promotion came
with speech-writing duties.
-[John] You can write?
-You can read?
I can kick both y'all asses
is what I can do.
This is, uh, really good, Rene.
It's like I keep telling you, hoss,
got the soul of a poet.
I don't think I've ever
heard you say that.
Who the hell asked you, blondie?
You totally missed me redirecting
a ballistic missile, B-T-dubs.
Aw, man, I've already seen you
do that once.
All right, just as you ordered,
a triple stack with a side
of heart disease.
-Don't judge me.
-[Felicity] Yeah, that's for you.
-Surprise is for you.
-[John] Thank you.
-Here you go.
-Thank you.
You're welcome.
Sorry I was MIA.
I pretty much had to knock my mother
unconscious to get her on a flight
back to Vegas. She did not want to go.
That's fine. We had it handled.
[Rene] Yeah, even without Dinah
in the field.
Come a long way in a year.
Yeah. Also makes me grateful for all
the times that Oliver kicked our ass.
Almost.
I'm gonna go home.
We'll walk with you.
Wow. It's been over five months
and their subtlety hasn't gotten
better al all.
-[Rene] Heard that.
-No, it hasn't.
Um, there's some in there
for William, too.
Got some fries and mini cheeseburger
and then a burger without cheese
'cause I wasn't sure
if he was, like, lactose...
Do you think there's enough for three?
Oh, I already ate, and unless you're
asking 'cause you think now is
a good time... Do you need a buffer?
I don't need a buffer.
I could use some company.
I know we talked about it
and he's getting used to me,
and it might be a little weird...
I mean, confusing, right?
For him... For us... For me, for you.
Not tonight. Another night.
Promise?
Promise.
Okay.
[chuckles]
[sighs]
Hey, come here.
-Where's my mom?
-[Oliver] I know.
I'm gonna go find your mom,
but the island, what happened
is very dangerous,
and you are safe by the shore,
do you understand?
What happened?
The man who took you when
we saw the explosions?
Okay, he did this.
He said you're my father.
I'm gonna go find your mother.
I'm gonna find her
and make sure that she's safe.
I promise you, but you have
to stay here, okay?
Good.
That food is junk.
That's why kids like it, Raisa.
How'd he do today?
New school. It's hard.
It's been a few months.
You had trouble fitting in at his age.
What?
What are you talking about? I had Tommy.
I wouldn't call having a friend
who helps you get into trouble
"fitting in."
It's a fair point.
[video game playing]
Hey, kiddo.
Brought home some dinner.
Not hungry.
How's school?
-Fine.
-Yeah?
Making friends?
This weekend, let's go see a Rockets game.
You know, as mayor,
I get pretty good seats...
I'm tired. I'm gonna go to bed.
Okay.
Good night, William.
Good night, Oliver.
-Comfy?
-Could I get something to drink?
That'll be up to my lieutenant.
Thanks, Bob. I've got it from here.
Where'd you get the muscle?
Kettlebell swings.
-Oh.
-[both chuckle]
[groans]
The gunmen, jerkwad.
Aah!
You were rolling with some pretty
highly-trained mercenaries tonight.
According to your friend
in the green hoodie.
Highly-trained means highly expensive.
You were probably paying
as much to hire them
as you were extorting the city for.
So you're saying there's a problem
with my business plan.
Well, could I get something to drink?
I'd be more disposed to linguistics
if I weren't so parched.
What do you want?
Anything carbonated will do.
Don't look so dour.
Mr. Smug'll crack.
It's not the whack job, Lieutenant.
It's Quentin Lance.
As Deputy Mayor, he was supposed
to be here to review plans
for the academy graduation.
-So?
-So his appointment was an hour ago.
All right. It's okay. I know where he is.
So, get this guy a soda
or something, will you?
[Quentin clears throat]
Hey.
Thanks for coming.
You did the right thing texting me.
[scoffs] It's not like
I can call my sponsor, is it?
Why not?
If I tell him
why I wanna drink, what I did,
why I did it...
Yeah, he'd think you were on
something a lot stronger than booze.
It's like all I've got is this guilt,
and all I can do is just run,
run away from it.
And go where?
To the bottom of these glasses.
Well, you're not gonna do that.
Because you know and I know that
is not what Laurel would've wanted.
Which Laurel?
Perfect.
Open it up for me?
Hey, do you think you can
claim some kinda police brutality?
Not at all. No, I just needed
to get this loose.
[grunts]
[chuckles]
C4 implant.
Boom.
[chuckles]
[can crumples]
You're crazy.
I don't judge you.
[groans]
[woman] Well done, Alex.
Right on schedule.
[Faust] One does one's humble best.
[woman] Wire it up. Make it fast.
We're on a clock.
[policeman] SCPD!
Drop your weapon now! Drop it...
[policeman groans]
We're all set here.
Care to do the honors?
Let's go.
[electricity buzzing]
[indistinct chatter]
[Oliver] What's the casualty count?
Nine dead,
six in critical condition, four injured.
Good thing the academy's turning
out a new batch of replacements.
-Come on.
-Sorry.
[sighs] Look, we might want to consider
canceling graduation
or at least, closing it to the public.
This city doesn't bend to terrorism.
Look, the media's going crazy
wanting us to figure out how
we're gonna handle this stuff.
We have A.R.G.U.S. connections.
I'll have them handle security.
The question is,
who would do this, and why?
I think I've got an answer on that.
We've got video footage.
Has anyone seen this?
I managed to get to it
before anyone else could.
[John] Thought you said she'd died.
You said Black Siren died on Lian Yu.
She did.
She was dead,
buried under a ton of rubble,
when Quentin and I found her.
Okay. Well, unless our Laurel is
mysteriously back from the dead,
something I wouldn't put past
either of the Lance sisters,
Black Siren is not only not dead,
she is not on Lian Yu.
Right. And running with
our "old friend" Alex Faust.
Okay, clearly he was at SCPD
when the explosion went off.
Which means he either died or escaped.
He escaped.
The question is, why is he
working with Black Siren?
And where did they hire these mercenaries?
I'll get this image over to Lyla.
She can tell us where these guys are from
and when they started working together.
I promised Raisa
that I'd take William to school.
So, I'll check in when I'm done with that.
Hey, kiddo.
Sorry I'm late. Just I...
[door closes]
He did not sleep last night.
Was he having nightmares?
He seemed fine when I left.
I think he puts on a good act for you.
But when you left with the emergency,
he cried about the "bad man."
He says the bad man is why
his mother is dead.
Slade?
You all right, kid?
Yeah, I'm fine. Where's everyone?
I came back here looking for people.
What do you mean, you "came back"?
Two of your friends went to
the monastery to look for survivors.
Ra's al Ghul's daughter
went to the cages for that girl.
But your sister...
What about her?
Slade...
Where's Thea?
She's this way.
-Hey.
-Hi.
What do you need?
What do I need?
Lots of things, I mean, you know?
More out of Rene, for one, you know.
He's all right at the new job, but...
He's not Thea.
No, he's not Thea.
Actually, I wanted
to talk to you about, um, her.
About Thea?
No. No, the other, uh... Laurel.
Dinah wasn't being straight with you
when she told you she was dead
when we found her.
Well, it's complicated, isn't it?
-Mmm-hmm. Yeah.
-[sighs]
Well, listen, the point is that I was
supposed to be at SCPD last night,
and I think maybe she went there
looking for me.
Wait, why? Why would she be targeting you?
-[phone vibrating]
-[Quentin sighs]
[Quentin clears throat]
A.R.G.U.S. has a lead on Black Siren.
I have to go.
Okay. But, listen, I gotta come with you.
I know it's not my Laurel.
But I can't sit this out, either, so...
Okay.
Nice outfit.
Except for I would've gone with fishnets.
[screeching]
[both grunting]
[Oliver] Priority is Black Siren.
In custody and unharmed.
[groans]
Quentin!
[exclaims]
[yelling]
[grunts]
-[Felicity] How's Rene?
-Curtis and Lance
took Rene to Dr. Schwartz for treatment.
Collapsed lung, it doesn't look so good.
Black Siren and the mercenaries escaped,
but we pulled this off the van.
-GPS?
-Backtrace it,
-figure out where they came from.
-On it.
Dinah, Quentin thinks the attack
on SCPD was targeting him.
Any idea why?
No.
If Laurel was after Lance,
why blow up the precinct after
discovering he wasn't there?
Maybe Quentin was wrong.
Maybe our first instincts were right.
That she's targeting the police
for some reason?
We need to figure out what that
reason is and we need to find her.
[Felicity] Oh, funny you should say that.
GPS' last location was a warehouse,
surprise, surprise, outside of Pennytown.
If this Laurel
is half as smart as our Laurel,
she would not go back there.
Maybe she left something behind
for us to go on.
-John.
-We are on it.
The blast blew her over there...
[Oliver] Thea?
[sobbing]
[Dinah] Clear.
[John] Clear.
[Dinah] It's all packed up.
Doesn't look like they were planning
on coming back here.
[John] Question is,
where were they headed?
Stay sharp. Look around.
In my experience, bad guys aren't
very good at covering their tracks.
-[Dinah] You all right?
-Yeah. Why?
Since the bridge, you seem distracted.
Just worried about Rene, that's all.
I saw you take the shot at the merc.
Never seen you miss.
Nobody makes every shot.
What about you?
I don't know.
What about me?
I saw your reaction when Oliver asked
you why Evil Laurel targeted Lance.
And I said I didn't know.
And I didn't find your answer
that convincing.
Really?
[John chuckles]
What the hell is that?
It's a map of City Hall.
With ingress and egress marks
and line of sight.
For an attack.
Why the hell would they want
to attack city hall?
After the SCPD got bombed,
they had to move the academy
graduation to a different venue.
Oliver chose city hall.
That decision was kept
under wraps for security reasons.
How the hell did these guys find out?
I don't know, but we're running out
of time to stop them.
[Dinah] The bombs
really did their work here.
[Quentin] Yep.
Maybe I should just do this alone, huh?
What, in case you find
my fake daughter dead?
Or alive.
It's all right, I'll be fine.
[groans] What's that,
in case she's not dead?
In case Talia al Ghul isn't.
That's what John gave me this for.
Besides, swords aren't really
my thing. Come on.
[Dinah] You think they knew what
they were signing on for
when they threw in with Chase?
[Quentin] Seems to me they "threw in"
with Nyssa's sister.
Either way, I'm gonna go with "no."
Dinah!
Hi, Daddy.
Laurel.
This might be a late night, Raisa.
I remember when your "late nights"
were more like early mornings.
Thankfully, I've exchanged club openings
for police academy graduations now.
[William] Raisa?
Another nightmare.
I know how to get him back to sleep.
No, I'll get him.
Hey, buddy.
Where's Raisa?
I'm here.
It was just a dream.
The bad man was in my dream.
He's why my mom is gone.
Well, he can't hurt you anymore, William.
He's gone.
No, he's not.
The bad man's here.
Buddy, I'm confused. I'm...
Where do you think the bad man is?
Hey, everything okay?
Worried about William.
-You wanna talk about it?
-I would love to talk about it,
but we have more pressing business, okay?
-Right.
-Okay.
-Okay, well, I cracked the code.
-Mmm-hmm.
I mean, so to speak. You are welcome.
These are the targeted areas,
which means we can almost be
100% positive Evil Laurel and friends
will be attacking the police academy
graduation tonight.
The question is, why?
Nine dead officers wasn't enough for them?
No, it wasn't.
Because she didn't get who she was after.
-You mean you?
-Quentin.
Dinah, I appreciate you having my back.
But I appreciate the truth
a little bit more.
Wait, what exactly are we missing here?
You're missing why I told you guys
that Dinah and I found Laurel dead
back on Lian Yu.
Quentin, I don't think
you have to do this.
Yeah, I do.
I've been living with this guilt for
too long. I can't do it anymore.
Bad Laurel,
she wasn't dead when we found her
back on Lian Yu.
Bad news is that you won't be able
to scream anymore,
but the good news is that you'll be
too dead to care.
I told Quentin
to say she was dead when we found her.
Just spare him the pain
of telling you all the truth.
But the truth is, he saved my life.
The truth is I killed my daughter.
I killed my baby girl.
I just left her for dead.
That's the truth.
She was going to kill me.
As sure as I'm standing here right now,
she was going to kill me
and you saved my life.
-You're staying here tonight.
-I can't.
Quentin, if Laurel's targeting you...
Then she's not gonna stop.
And the only way we could stop her is
by dangling me right in front of her.
So, I 'm gonna be there tonight,
front and center, you understand?
All right.
You're at the graduation.
We need SCPD K-9 units
at every entry point.
Actually we can kill the K-9s.
What?
Uh, by kill,
I do not mean kill the actual dogs.
Curtis, what are those?
These are the latest
in high-tech sniffer devices...
Wait, those are bomb detectors?
They can spot as little as
an ounce of explosive material
within a 1,000-foot radius.
Yeah, the only catch is that
we have to be there to operate them.
Which means Curtis and I need
to be on the field,
which means no one will be down here
operating the comms.
I'll do it.
If someone has to take one
for the team, I can do it.
You sure?
Yeah. My gun'll get lost in all that
A.R.G.U.S. and SCPD firepower anyways.
I'll stay.
Okay.
Okay, let's get out there.
We have to get her out of here.
[Samantha] Oliver?
Samantha?
William...
He's fine. Are you okay?
Hey, hey, hey.
Yeah, he's fine. We have to get you
medical attention.
No, I just needed to make sure
that he was okay.
He wants to see his mom.
William needs a parent, promise me
that you will be his father.
I promise.
[sighs]
Curtis, you got anything?
Negative. And shouldn't you be
calling me Mr. Terrific?
I am in the field.
Yeah, but you're not in your suit.
So, no suit, no code name.
Them's the rules.
How about we try to focus instead?
Spartan, what do you see?
So far, so good.
Yeah, maybe they decided
to rethink their plan.
That'd be a smart move.
Haven't seen this many cops
in one place in my life.
Me, either. I'm a cop.
Yeah. Well, doesn't mean they're not
gonna try something.
Everyone stay sharp.
Thank you all for being here.
In light of the recent attacks
on the SCPD,
tonight's ceremony is
incredibly important.
And while we need
to mourn the loss of life,
I feel the need to mention that this city
is better off than it has been
in quite some time.
Crime is down,
our streets are peaceful,
people are not only moving here,
they are staying here.
Do you want to know why?
It's because you help them feel safe.
You have chosen a profession.
One of the most
dangerous professions in the world.
Where, as other people run from
danger, you run towards it,
time and time and time again.
And for that, we all owe you
a huge debt of gratitude.
So, thank you.
Thank you for protecting our families.
For protecting us.
And for our protecting our beautiful city.
-Thank you.
-[crowd applauding]
-Well done, Mr. Mayor.
-Of course.
You keep this up, they're gonna ask
you to run for governor.
Yeah? I'm just glad a bomb didn't
go off during the speech.
Anything from Black Siren and her crew?
You mean the psychopaths I unleashed
on the city? No, not yet.
You can not take that on, Quentin.
And this, speaking as one of the
world's leaders in feeling guilty.
Um, have you ever fired a gun
at your own daughter?
That is... [clears throat]
That's not what happened.
Black Siren is not Laurel.
She is Laurel.
You know it, and I know it,
and we both know that this
"parallel universe" crap is crap.
All right? Every time I see her,
I get that feeling, that instinct...
She's my child.
She's my baby girl, Oliver.
And I tried to kill her.
From what I understand,
you were protecting a friend.
You are not just a good man, Quentin,
you are a good father.
[exhales]
I know, because you are a better
father than I could ever hope to be.
You gotta give it some time.
You've only been at it, what, five months?
-It's not getting any easier.
-Well...
William blames me for Samantha's death.
Why?
Because he's a smart kid.
And he knows what happened,
happened because...
I was involved.
He shouldn't be with me,
he should be with Samantha's parents.
That's not what Samantha thought.
I don't know how to reach him.
Just be his father.
[door opens]
Hey, anything?
Nothing.
Curtis and I
scanned every inch of this place,
something seems really off.
Let's get in touch with Spartan.
See if he saw anything on the cams.
Spartan, you copy?
Yeah. Still here, still nothing.
Maybe A.R.G.U.S. scared 'em off.
Maybe they're targeting Lance another way.
-Maybe he isn't their target...
-[clattering]
[Felicity] [on radio] John?
John, do you copy?
John, are you okay?
Don't worry, Felicity. John's fine.
He's just gonna be catching up
with an old friend.
Shouldn't you be protecting
the graduation ceremony?
Oh, but what's wrong?
Did you loose your nerve
along with your aim?
I don't know...
You tell me.
[beeping, explosion]
You want me to kill him?
I'm not paying you to keep him alive.
Hey, psst.
Let's get to work.
[power shutting down]
-[gun fires]
-[man grunts]
[gunshots]
[grunts]
You're not gonna feel a thing.
I promise.
[groans]
You okay?
[grunts]
I'm pissed.
Just about finished.
Make sure you put one here too.
[distant arrow strikes]
Incoming.
[screeching]
God, you are such a bitch.
Yeah, takes one to know one, sweetheart.
[man] Go, go, go!
[grunting]
[grunts]
God news, the bomb sniffer works.
Bad news, it's working in the bunker.
[Curtis]Yeah, the whole place is wired.
If you can take the devices, I can
jam the detonation signal remotely.
Is John okay?
I don't know. But I might not be...
-[arrow whizzes]
-[man groans]
[Oliver] Spartan's fine.
I've got eyes on Black Siren.
[grunts]
To be continued...
[Quentin] Don't move.
I said, don't move.
Oh, this feels familiar.
Maybe this time you'll aim for the heart.
I'm sorry.
For shooting me
or for leaving me for dead?
You were trying to hurt my friend.
Oh, so, you choose your friend...
over your own daughter?
Don't make me do this, Laurel.
Please don't make me do this.
So, now, I'm Laurel?
Don't torture yourself.
Because if we were back on Lian Yu,
and the roles were reversed...
I would've pulled the trigger.
Hell of a mess.
Yeah. [clears throat] What's happening
with the graduation?
Went off without a problem.
Unless you count some food poisoning
from the city caterer.
Graduation was a distraction.
Laurel left that map
for me and Dinah to find.
So when did she pivot from targeting
them to targeting us?
Maybe she didn't. I mean...
Maybe the SCPD and the bunker
were her targets all along.
Yeah. Seems pretty random.
Particularly considering how much
trouble Laurel went through
to make sure we wouldn't be here.
Well, what if planting the explosives
wasn't her objective.
Planting the explosives
was to cover her objective.
Yeah.
What if she was trying to steal something?
Like what? She doesn't need weapons.
Mercenaries she's working with do.
We should inventory the armory.
We should inventory
everything that we have.
If she stole something,
we need to know what it is,
and we need to know fast.
Hey, you all right?
Uh, yeah, I'm fine. I'm just glad
that nobody was hurt, you know.
Yeah.
Listen, I'm sorry about lying to you
about what happened on Lian Yu.
Quentin... You don't have
to apologize to me.
I'm sorry that you had to go through that.
When're you gonna stop taking on
everybody else's sins, huh?
No time soon.
How you feeling?
Oh, like a million bucks.
Yeah?
All right, maybe more like
a couple of hundred, but...
I'm alive, right?
Dr. Schwartz would like you in here
for a few more days.
I feel good.
Besides, when have I ever
listened to anybody?
Not to get too personal,
but what would happen to Zoe
if something happened to you?
Not much.
She's got her
new family now, hoss. I mean...
She probably doesn't even think about me.
She's your daughter, Rene.
Of course she thinks about you.
That ship's sailed.
I blew that chance months ago.
Chase blew that chance for you.
One of many reasons why I think
you deserve another one.
I tried getting another hearing...
Yeah, you're not the mayor.
-You got me another hearing?
-Not just me,
the new DA had something to do with it.
Okay. All right.
[coughing]
Thank you, Oliver. I owe you one.
Pay me back by getting better.
Copy that.
Hey, kid.
Hello, Slade.
How is she doing?
She's the same.
What are you doing here?
I popped by to say that the intel
that you gave me on my son, Joe,
it panned out.
So, I'm heading to Calgary.
Well, that's great. I'm very, uh...
I'm happy for you and I hope that...
I hope you find what you're looking for.
You don't think I will?
[clears throat]
I think that finding your son
doesn't always go as planned.
Have things been that hard
with you and your son?
Be patient.
But be prepared.
For what?
Choosing between being the man
that people need you to be,
or the father
that your son needs you to be.
What do you mean by that?
You and I
walk between two worlds.
But we can only do that for so long.
Good luck,
Mr. Queen.
Good luck, Slade.
[exhales in pain]
-[Dinah] You okay?
-[sighs]
Yeah, I'm good.
Anything missing?
No. All's accounted for.
Including your gun?
Not that you seem to be using it
that much these days.
I, uh, checked it
after the fight down here.
You checked my gun?
You didn't even fire it.
And none of the guys
down here got hit, either.
[John] Yeah.
Dinah...
[Curtis] I found it.
By found it, I mean I found
what Laurel... Black Siren took,
which is more like not finding
anything at all. You get my point.
What? No, I'm not sure we do.
She took one of my T-Spheres.
A prototype version.
A prototype? Meaning it's not weaponized?
Well, then they can't use it against us.
Question is, what can they do?
[helicopter blades whirring]
Hey, buddy.
William, I know that the last few
months have been difficult for you.
And I know that you blame me
for a part of that.
[Oliver sighs]
I used to blame my dad for things...
Well, he wasn't perfect.
Neither am I.
But he loved me.
I know how much your mom loved you.
She really did.
But you need to know the last thing that
she asked of me was to take care of you.
Now, you don't have to like me
for me to take care of you,
because I'm your dad.
The way that works is,
I'm going to be there for you,
whether you want me to be or not.
I'm never, ever walking away from you.
There's a game on tomorrow
if you want to stay up late, watch it?
Football or baseball?
Baseball.
Okay.
[phone vibrating]
Hi, I was just gonna give you a call.
Turn on Channel 52 right now.
Okay.
...with the discovery
of a shocking photograph
that seems to finally solve the mystery
haunting Star City for the past two years.
Who is the Green Arrow?
This photo, which was obtained
exclusively by Channel 52,
provides unequivocal proof of
the identity of the vigilante
known as the Green Arrow.
-Oliver.
-This is the latest controversy
-to hit the Queen administration.
-What are we going to do?
What else has the mayor lied about?
I don't know.