My name is Oliver Queen.
For 7 years, I have fought
with only one goal...
To save my city,
but now a new threat has emerged,
a danger so severe it has forced me
to leave my family in order to face it,
and it won't be enough for
me to just be the Green Arrow.
To prevent the crisis that's coming,
I am going to have to
become someone else,
become... something else.
Previously on "Arrow"...
We see the wall coming
down as an opportunity.
For the criminals of Star City to
- Rob the Glades blind.
- To reunite the city.
Ever since we brought down
the wall, your brother...
The Deathstroke gang...
has really upped their game.
They've amassed more territory
and power than ever before.
Your brother hates you.
That makes things unpredictable.
Vasquez is one of the
Glades' wealthiest citizens.
Maybe the Deathstrokes
plan to extort him.
A crisis is coming, John.
- What are you doing here?
- Reminding you
what you are doing here,
which does not include
interfering in the events of this Earth.
- The city's under attack.
- By who?
A crisis is imminent.
Someone is coming,
someone far, far more
powerful than myself.
We have to get the hell out of here.
I missed you, buddy.
We found ourselves in each other.
You're never without me.
Beautiful boy.
What's happening?
Oliver!
Son.
I warned you not to interfere.
You didn't bring us here?
No. I discovered what
had transpired on Earth-2,
that you intervened
to save Laurel Lance.
I redirected you.
What... the hell happened back there?
A herald of what is to come,
an entire world erased from existence.
Where's my mother?
Where's... where's Tommy?
Where's... where's Rene, where's Dinah?
They are no more.
Did you hurt John and Laurel?
They are alive and nearby,
but now you know that if we fail to stop
the coming crisis,
what you witnessed will occur
on infinite Earths across
the expanse of time.
How did I fail? Your Dwarf
Star particles are right there.
You disobeyed my instructions
to avoid entanglements
on a parallel Earth.
You confronted Tommy Merlyn.
You altered the fate of Laurel Lance.
I watched her die once.
Okay. I wasn't prepared to do it again.
You are not a man accustomed
to following orders,
but the survival of
the multiverse requires
that you obey mine.
Where are we?
Your home Earth, where you
will complete your next task.
There's a man named Dr. Robert Wong.
Bring him to me.
- Why?
- Now, that is not your concern.
Do not fail me again.
Oliver, we have to
get out of here... now.
- Who are they?
- Local gang.
I think we busted up a deal.
Nice of you to show up.
Where the hell are we?
We're in Hong Kong.
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -
It's... it's not possible.
There's no way that my entire Earth
is just... is just gone.
You saw what happened
to the SCPD, right,
that energy wave,
people just disappearing?
That doesn't mean
it happened everywhere.
The Monitor told me that it did.
- The what?
- His real name is Mar Novu...
Oh. You call that a real name?
He's the one that has asked
me to be on this mission.
He is trying to prevent a crisis...
Oliver, just stop.
Hand me the breach device.
Give it to me. I'm going back.
Laurel, back where?
To my Earth
to look for any survivors.
- It's not working.
- Probably damaged
on our jump through the portal.
We don't have time to go all the way
to S.T.A.R. Labs.
I... I have to find somebody local.
I'm sorry, but we need
to focus on the mission.
First of all, there is no we here,
and the only mission that I care about
is saving what's left of my Earth.
Laurel. Laurel!
There's no one left to save.
The only thing that we can do right now
is prevent this from happening again
by doing what the Monitor tells us...
Screw the Monitor, Oliver,
and screw you, too.
None of this would have happened
if you hadn't shown up on
my Earth in the first place.
All of those people that you saw die,
they weren't real to you.
They were just copies of
the people that you love...
But that is my home,
and those people, those are real people
who are counting on me...
Adrian, my sister.
I just got my life back,
and I am not giving
it up without a fight.
Let her go, man.
She's wasting her time, John.
She's processing her grief,
and if we have a new mission
and the multiverse
depends on it, Oliver,
we have to get going right now.
Anyone want to fill me in
on what happened out there?
I almost got my throat slit.
Turns out Connor doesn't know
his brother as well as he thinks.
Hey. We're all still alive, aren't we?
Which means what exactly,
that your brother's not such a bad guy?
All I'm saying is JJ
could have killed you,
- and he didn't.
- Wow! That is some serious denial.
To answer your question, nothing good.
What about Alberto Vasquez?
He's safe, but he'd already
given JJ what he was after.
- Which was?
- Access codes
to the private vault in
Vasquez's penthouse.
Yeah. Well, we went to the vault,
but by the time we got there,
it had already been trashed and emptied.
This is all that was left.
Flash storage from the
vault's security mainframe.
Yeah. Don't get too excited.
- It's totally fried.
- Not to brag,
but totally fried is
kind of my wheelhouse.
If I can fix it, I'll be able to extract
the vault's security log.
Finding out what the Deathstrokes stole
could help us figure out
what they're planning next.
We already know what they're planning.
JJ wants to take over the city.
He needs the cash to do it.
Well, Vasquez did say the
vault was full of valuables...
Jewelry, cash.
So we figure out where JJ's
gonna sell, take him out.
I know exactly where you'd
go with that kind of product.
You're not the only one
around here with street smarts.
Okay. We'll find JJ,
take him out of play.
Stay here. Fix that
useless piece of junk,
and, you, next time I see your brother,
Don't get in my way.
Harbinger sends her regards.
Oh. This would have come
in handy 10 years ago.
Well, it helps to be
married to Lyla Michaels,
who is en route even as we speak.
John, I didn't even want
to get you involved in this.
I know, but if what you told me is true,
which is that we're
facing the destruction of...
Well, hell, man, pretty much everything,
then to me that's the very
definition of all hands on deck.
Check this out.
Now this machine is hooked
up to A.R.G.U.S.'s intranet,
so we can access all the
information it has on Dr. Wong.
You want to tell me what
that face is all about,
or are you gonna make me guess?
Laurel. She was right.
The Monitor warned me
not to get involved,
and, I don't know, if I'd just found
a way to get the Dwarf Star particles
without trying to stop
Tommy's undertaking, then...
Oliver, what were you supposed to do,
just sit back and let it happen?
I ignored the orders of a cosmic being,
and as a result, I
watched an entire world
just disappear, so...
I'm just trying not to make
the same mistake twice.
Well, if this cosmic being wanted
someone willing to watch the
mass murder of innocent people,
then... he picked the wrong hero.
Shouldn't blame yourself, man.
Well, what about my behavior
over the past 7 years
has given you the
impression that I would?
- Got him.
- Good.
Dr. Robert Wong, renowned biophysicist.
Won the Nobel Prize in the specialty
of complex proteins and antibodies.
First the Dwarf Star particles,
now a mysterious scientist.
Can't the Monitor just
snap his fingers and get both?
Well, he's not the biggest
fan of sharing information.
Ok. Looks like Dr. Wong might
not be that easy to find.
He's been missing a week.
This is the last-known photo.
Wan Chai university. He's a professor.
That's where we start.
Do this quietly, stay under the radar.
Too late.
Agh!
Tatsu?
You will be safe here.
So who were those men, Triad?
Shu gang, their rivals.
Why are you in Hong Kong?
I thought you were
with the Crescent order.
I was until I gave Nyssa the Lotus Cure
to save your sister,
and they called for my head.
So you decided to become a vigilante?
My son died in this city.
No more Akios will die here
as long as I'm here to protect them.
That explains what I'm doing here.
It's all you, man.
Right. We're looking for a
scientist named Dr. Robert Wong.
- Why?
- There's a crisis coming
that quite literally threatens
the entire universe.
A man... something like a man
has asked me to help him stop it.
- You mean Mar Novu?
- You've heard of him?
When I was with the Crescent order.
A being who transcends universes,
a crisis brewing.
He believes Dr. Wong
can help him stop it.
And you believe him?
I have to.
Then how can I help?
Tatsu, what we're
doing is very dangerous.
I... I can't ask you to be involved.
You're not asking. I'm offering.
Dr. Wong was seen last
leaving his classroom
at Wan Chai university.
That was a week ago.
We're trying to figure out
why he would have left town.
I don't think he has.
Those pins, they're only worn
by the security wing,
Hong Kong version of the secret police.
With a very healthy reputation for
silencing political
enemies of the state.
Yeah, but why would they
be going after Dr. Wong?
We need to find out.
Johnny told me you were
about to do something stupid.
He called you all the way
to Hong Kong to follow me?
- How nice.
- He thought you could use some help.
Clearly, he was right.
Clearly, he needs to
mind his own business.
He said you're
looking for an old friend.
Doesn't seem like the
kind who's too friendly.
His name is David Chin.
I met him a few years ago
through Cayden James.
He said he could help
me get back to Earth-2
so maybe he still can.
Do you have any idea what
you're about to walk into?
Nothing that I can't handle myself.
You'll need backup.
Hey. What are you doing here?
You can't be in here. What the?
What the hell?
I wouldn't.
Hello, David. It's been a while.
Black Siren?
David, I'm gonna need your help,
and if you don't help me,
then I am gonna hurt
you very, very badly.
What do you want?
Whoa? Is that an
Interdimensional Extrapolator?
If that's nerd talk for
breach device, then yes,
and I need you to fix it.
That's not really my area of expertise.
Okay, okay.
I'll do it.
Good. I'm so glad you reconsidered.
So this is, what, like a black market?
More or less.
If JJ wants to find a buyer,
this is where he'll be.
I'll check the back.
See, I still don't get it.
Your dad was bronze tiger,
and you turned out okay.
I mean, kind of.
Gee. Thanks.
John and Lyla were basically saints.
Yeah. Well, they spent all
their time worrying about me.
JJ got shortchanged.
Hey. You think JJ turned
out this way because of you?
No. JJ made his own choices.
I know you want to
believe that deep down
there's still some good in him.
There is. Listen.
JJ wasn't just my brother, okay?
He was my best friend.
That was a long time ago.
Come to have a drink
with me, little bro?
- This is over, JJ.
- I don't think so.
- Put down your weapons.
- You first.
Tsk.
Maybe there's a better
way that we can resolve this.
No, no, no. We can resolve this
by you coming with us.
You know, I wish that I could. I do,
I do, but I got business to attend to.
I would settle for a friendly
chat with my brother.
What you think?
I think that's never gonna happen.
Fine.
You want to talk, we'll talk.
That looked like that hurt.
Knowing you has changed my life.
I love you.
We're gonna be fine.
I spoke to contact
on Hong Kong police force.
As soon as I mentioned Dr.
Wong's name, he stopped talking.
- He seemed afraid.
- I think we know why.
It seems that Dr. Wong has been working
on a top secret project
for the Chinese government.
Exactly, which means the security wing
wasn't kidnapping him.
It was trying to help him.
- He must be in protective custody.
- Safe house in the Wan Chai district,
but they're planning on moving
him out of the city tonight.
Then we better get moving.
Don't hurt me.
Triad.
We can't let them
get away with Dr. Wong.
We won't. Go, go, go, go!
Out of the way! Out of the way!
Welcome back to Hong Kong.
Hyah! Hyah!
Agh! Ugh!
- Hyah!
- Unh!
Gah!
- It's gas.
- Got to get these people out of here.
We can't lose the doctor.
No sign of Dr. Wong.
Triad must have taken
him deep underground.
I thought China White
was in A.R.G.U.S. custody.
Yeah. Well, so did I, and as
far as I know, Lyla did, too.
Well, our situation just got
a whole lot more complicated.
You seemed ready to let
those people die back there.
I knew you had it handled,
and you knew that Dr.
Wong was the priority.
You sound like someone I used to know...
You 9 years ago,
single-minded about your mission.
Tatsu, with due respect, if you had seen
what I have seen, you would understand.
The Monitor is our best
chance at preventing it
from happening again.
I've seen that blind faith
in you before, as well,
with Amanda Waller.
That wasn't blind faith.
She threatened my family, Tatsu.
Right now, the stakes are
every family in existence.
Guys, I really hate to interrupt this,
but none of this matters
if we don't find
this missing scientist, right?
Why does the Triad want him?
His work does not seem harmful.
Yeah? Well, innocent men don't work
on secret government projects.
We need to know what this project is.
Then we'll know why
the Triad is after him.
I don't like this.
He's stalling.
Hey. Hey!
What's taking so long?
- It's done.
- Great.
So you won't mind if we test it out.
It isn't working.
Well, it should be.
Then where's the portal?
You want to go to Earth-37, Earth-14?
I want to go to Earth-2.
Earth-2...
is gone.
It registered at first, but now
I see that it's like a shadow.
There's no sign of life.
That doesn't make any sense.
You're lying. Fix it! Fix it!
I'm telling you I did.
I can fix tech. I can't bring back
a whole friggin' universe!
I'm so sorry, Laurel...
But they're gone.
Let's get out of here.
Laurel!
Now!
There's nothing in
any governmental databases
about the project Dr.
Wong was working on.
- So we're back to square one?
- No, not exactly.
An A.R.G.U.S. mole led
me to a paper trail,
some equipment that Dr. Wong purchased.
- He shipped it to this address.
- Well, it's his lab. It has to be.
- We need to get in there.
- That may not be so easy.
I know this place. It's a PLA Garrison.
Oh. Those Garrisons have a reputation
for being almost impenetrable.
Almost but not quite.
There are certain vulnerabilities.
Yeah. Well, even if we
could get in that place,
it's gonna be heavily fortified.
That's never stopped us before.
Ow.
I'm almost at the sublevel.
The elevator will take
you straight to the lab.
Most likely will be guarded.
Hyah!
Unh!
All right. I've definitely been made.
You only have a few minutes.
I'm starting the upload.
What? What is it?
I know what the Triad is after.
Dr. Wong has been trying to re-create
the Alpha/Omega virus.
He's not trying. He's already done it.
After what happened
last time, you'd think
the Chinese government would
have learned its lesson.
The Alpha/Omega is a powerful weapon.
Yeah, and the Triad
could already have it.
If they had it, they wouldn't
have any need for Dr. Wong.
It's just a matter of time
before they make him re-create it.
Which means, Oliver, that
we have a ticking clock
and absolutely no plan.
- We have this.
- You stole the virus?
This is what China White wants,
this is what I'm gonna give her.
Oliver, you more than anyone
else knows how dangerous this is.
Which is why I'm not actually
gonna give her the virus.
We're using this as
bait to draw her out.
My husband tried this
gambit once already,
and you're the one who
told him he made a mistake.
This is different.
Maseo had every intention
of actually giving the
virus to China White.
- I don't.
- It's too risky.
It's riskier to do nothing.
If anyone has a better idea,
I'm all ears.
I'll start making arrangements.
Here. It'll help with the swelling.
I don't have anyone here
who cares if I come home
with bruised knuckles.
I'm here. I care.
You barely even know me.
I know what it's like to lose people.
Do you know what it's like
to lose an entire universe?
No.
Then you don't know how I feel.
You didn't know them.
My sister, Adrian, they're my family,
they're... they're good people.
They don't deserve to be gone.
To think that I'm the one
who's done such awful things.
But you're trying to be better.
Everyone deserves a shot at redemption.
Well, then maybe this
is where I deserve to be.
When I was in Afghanistan,
my unit got sent out on patrol
on a day I drew base duty.
It was a routine op.
We'd done it a hundred times before.
Only this time, there
was an IED in the road.
None of them made it back.
I used to lie in bed at night
asking myself
"why them?
Why not me?"
And I made every deal I could think of
with any god I thought might listen.
And did it work?
Not exactly.
So you're right.
I don't know what you're going through,
but I do know something
about survivor's guilt.
Does it get any easier?
No.
All we can do is try and move forward.
How am I supposed to move forward
when everyone I've ever loved is gone?
By not giving up.
By doing the right thing.
We honor the dead by
fighting for the living.
This world needs you, too.
You're not talking me out of this.
- I know.
- Trust me, Tatsu.
I will not let China
White get the virus.
- And what if you fail?
- I'm not gonna fail.
9 years ago, you failed
to stop the virus,
and my son died.
And I regret it every day.
You must remember it
because of what happened after.
I tortured General Shrieve.
Your grief, your anger,
your guilt over the failure,
it stole your humanity.
This is different. I'm not angry.
I'm simply doing what has to be done.
How do you know that?
It is said that Mar Novu believes
order comes through chaos.
So he's bringing us order?
But first maybe chaos.
He's asking you to bring him a man
who re-created a deadly virus. Why?
How do you know he won't use it
for something worse than the Triad?
I don't know,
but I have to believe him.
I have no other choice.
Even if that is true,
he does not seem to care
who he hurts along the way.
Sometimes, the mission
is not worth the cost.
You know that,
so why are you still doing what he asks?
Because if I'm wrong...
If I'm wrong, then all
of this is for nothing.
Do you understand, Tatsu?
I left Felicity.
I left my children,
so if... if... if the... if
the Monitor can't fix this
and if he is not here to help,
then all of these things
that I've sacrificed
and all the things that
so many other people
have already sacrificed
will have been for nothing.
I need my family to live,
which means that I need this to work.
You're risking too much.
There's no other choice.
There's always another choice.
You seem stressed. Relax.
Look. You said you wanted to talk,
so talk.
Still can't believe that you
decided to become a vigilante.
You know you always have
a place here with us.
You do have the Mark.
You know why I got it.
That's right. You
and Dad's brilliant plan
to save me from the dark side.
I got it because I
wanted my brother back.
You remember when I was
in middle school, huh?
Remember when those guys tried
to get me to run their drugs?
Not really in the mood for
a trip down memory lane, Con.
When you found out, you were the one
that told me that I
was better than that.
Yeah. My favorite part of that story
is when you didn't listen
and I got grounded.
Dad held me responsible.
You want to hate me?
You want to hate Dad? Fine. Okay.
That... that's fair.
Don't throw your
life away because of it.
When I look at you, I still see
the kid who'd take on
somebody twice his size
just because he was messing with me.
Yeah. I'm not that kid anymore, Con.
Yes, you are,
and you can try... you can try
to snuff it out, to
cover it up with a mask,
but I know who you are,
and it's not too late.
And we can fix this... together.
You're late. I thought perhaps
you changed your mind.
Deal's a deal.
Thank you for meeting me.
Anything for a friend.
Now I have the virus.
- Where's Dr. Wong?
- He's nearby.
I was surprised when I got your call.
Well, I'm surprised that
you're not in an A.R.G.U.S. prison.
Well, apparently the
government doesn't like
when agents put bombs in people's necks.
You know what else they
don't like? Bad press.
So they bought your silence.
It's a shame your friend Mr. Diggle
had to lose his job over it.
I assume he's here, too.
Perimeter's clean.
Tatsu, any sign of Dr. Wong?
Not yet.
I don't think he's here.
Wait. Someone's coming.
Oliver, keep her talking.
You and I...
We have been enemies
since the very beginning,
but there's something coming.
It's bigger than us.
It is something that threatens
our entire Earth.
Let me see him.
Give me the case.
Tatsu, we have to move now.
I see him. I'm going in.
Wait. He's wearing some kind of vest.
It looks like explosives.
China White must have a detonator.
It's real.
_
That vest is not part of the agreement.
I had to be sure you weren't
gonna do anything stupid.
I'll deactivate it once
I'm safe in the car.
Until next time, Mr. Queen.
There's not gonna be a next time.
Now.
Hyah!
_
Damn it! I'm going after the virus!
Chien Na Wei.
Tatsu Yamashiro.
You really think this will
go better than the last time?
I have Dr. Wong.
Hi, honey.
Virus is secure.
I can't remove the
vest without triggering it.
We need that detonator.
Unh!
The detonator.
You better kill me now.
I have the detonator.
Tatsu?
Unh.
Looks like I'm not the only
one who needed backup.
Tatsu's resting in the infirmary.
She'll be in pain for a few
days, but she'll be fine.
She would have been dead
if you hadn't have come back
and fought with us.
I don't know if I'll ever
get over what happened
on Earth-2, but I'll help you
make sure it never happens again.
Well, at least we
accomplished our objective.
- How's Dr. Wong?
- He's fine.
In a secure location.
The virus is, too.
And so what... what, do we text
the Monitor or whatever,
letting him know
- we have his guy?
- Don't think he texts.
I don't want to hand
over Dr. Wong just yet.
I want answers, and if he is not
gonna give them to me,
I'm gonna find them somewhere else.
Oliver, what are you talking about?
Tatsu... she told me that I had to be
absolutely sure that I was
making the right choice.
She almost died, John.
A lot of people have died already
for the sake of this mission.
I owe it to all of them to find out
who the Monitor really is.
And, Oliver, what if we don't
like the answers to those questions?
What do we do then?
We find another way to stop it.
There's always another way.
Oliver, so what's the plan?
I need to apologize to
a friend of mine first.
So... what do you say?
How about you and me leave together?
It was a nice speech, but once again,
you have managed to make
everything about you.
This isn't about you or Dad.
Yeah. You both have this misguided idea
about duty and family, civic pride.
You fail to see the bigger picture.
I have vision.
What are you talking about?
Did you really not think that
I knew you'd show up here?
Yes. Worthless piece of junk, my ass.
What the hell did the
Deathstrokes want with this?
What did you do?
What did you do?!
Oh. Hey, hey. I knew that you thought
that I'd be after the
valuables in Vasquez's safe
and that Zoe would lead you here,
the one shady trading post
that she knows about, right?
You were never after the money.
Why cripple the system when
you can rip its heart out?
Oh, my god.
Once the unification movement is gone,
the power vacuum is ours to fill.
I think we're done here.
- Not even close.
- You are not gonna touch me.
Oh, yeah? And why is that?
Because if you do,
the men who are storming
your bunker right now
will kill your brother.
William?
William, do you copy?
Like I said, I think we're done here.
If you hurt my brother,
I swear I will kill you.
JJ... please.
You were wrong about me, brother.
It was never a mask.
Think the doctors would have
preferred you stay in the hospital.
I have survived worse.
Brought you something.
- Herbs.
- There's a rumor going around
they help with healing.
I have seen many battles.
For a moment, I believed
this was my last.
I saw Akio and Maseo,
but... this was not my time.
Tatsu, you almost died because of me.
I'm sorry.
Well, you were right when you said that
some missions aren't worth the cost,
so I'm gonna make sure that this one is.
So where will you go?
You heard a rumor about the
Monitor and a coming crisis?
I doubt the Crescent order
will have the answers you seek.
Thankfully, there are
organizations on this Earth
far, far older than the Crescent order.
I'm going to Nanda Parbat.
You should have told me what
was going to happen on Earth-2.
John was there. He
could have been killed.
The destruction of that Earth
was a necessary sacrifice.
And what about Laurel Lance?
Her friends, her family...
Countless more like them will perish
if we do not ensure that
Oliver Queen is prepared
for what is coming.
Were you successful?
Yes. I have Dr. Wong.
Then let us proceed.