Previously on "Arrow"...
H-how is this real?
- [Oliver] This is Novu?
- [John] How do we stop a god?
I'm working on it.
[Curtis] Hello, bunker!
So why'd you call in the big guns?
Earth-2 was destroyed
by a wave of energy.
So it's probably powerful
enough to stop a god.
- Yes, Curtis?
- Whatever it is, it is
possible to replicate,
but there's a catch.
It is super illegal
because it requires plutonium.
Luckily, there's a guy,
a military general.
- Ok. Where is he?
- Russia.
You can bring back
my Earth?
The recovery
of your universe
will require
a single task.
You must betray
Oliver Queen.
[arrow removed from quiver]
[Mia] So that's the secret?
A tennis ball.
You know how you use
a honing steel
to keep the edge
on a chef's knife?
I don't really cook.
That makes sense.
All right. [clears throat]
This keeps you sharp.
Only a direct, precise
hit will pin the ball.
If you are off just
a little bit...
it deflects.
Ready?
Toss it.
Thought this was
supposed to be hard.
This is the warm-up.
Ready.
So specialty arrows,
and each one has
a specific purpose.
What does this one do?
Explosive arrow,
lighter payload,
meant to divert and disable.
[arrow flies]
[explosion]
[Oliver] Acidic arrow,
meant to breach covertly
or weaken structurally.
Bolo arrow...
to secure and subdue.
These are just tools.
If you rely on them too
much, they become crutches.
Then why have them?
To get out of a fight
or to end one before
it begins.
[catapult arm is released]
Not bad.
So what's next?
Hyah!
Nyssa taught you well.
Mom made sure of it.
How did you do that?
Variable acceleration.
All right?
It's all about timing.
You keep practicing,
you keep flowing,
it just becomes
second nature.
All right. Again.
You don't want
a break maybe?
She's a machine, Dad.
They don't need breaks.
And speaking of machines,
I have something to show you guys.
I created
a facial recognition
algorithm
to find that general
that Curtis told us about,
which was a lot harder
than it sounds,
because no offense to
Felicity,
but these computers are,
like, a million years old.
And Russia is
a very big country.
- William.
- Right. Sorry.
His name is
General Alexi Burov,
and he's in Moscow.
Curtis said that
the energy wave
that destroyed Earth-2
can be replicated, which
means we can weaponize it.
And right before he went
off the grid,
Burov was working on plans
for a weapon called
the pulse wave generator.
All right.
We need those plans.
We also need plutonium.
It's the only thing that
can power Burov's machine.
Wait. Plutonium as in
a nuclear bomb?
- Mm-hmm.
- Where are we gonna get that?
[John] Bialya. There's
a facility near the border
where all kinds of
radioactive material is stored.
I'm thinking a two-man fire team
can get the job done.
- Okay. Want to take Connor?
- No, no.
Actually, he wanted to check in on Sandra.
And he promised to stay out of sight.
I have someone else in mind to help.
Okay. I'd like the two of you
to accompany me
and Laurel to Russia.
Okay?
Yeah.
Okay. We'll wheels up
at dawn.
Well, better go buy a parka.
Is it really that cold in Russia?
Oh, oh! You are so
not ready for this.
Things seem to be going
pretty well with the kids.
Never thought I'd
get to know them.
Not like this.
Is that why you invited
them to go with you?
Well, I mean, I promised Mia
that I would keep training her.
And I think it's very valuable
for them to keep seeing
how we operate in the field.
And you're sure Russia's
a good place for a tutorial, Oliver?
That was a very dark time for you.
It was a long time ago, though.
I'm a better man.
I'm a different man.
I think that I can teach them good
without showing them the bad.
[footsteps recede]
Hope so.
What the hell are you
doing here?
Our mutual friend
sent me.
You're working with
the Monitor. Why?
- It's complicated.
- Really?
Because he destroyed my entire Earth.
That seems pretty straightforward to me.
He didn't.
Mar Novu is trying
to save worlds,
not destroy them.
All that stuff
about grief,
you pretending like you
were trying to help me.
I should've known better.
I wasn't pretending.
It's a little hard to believe,
Lyla, after all the lying.
It doesn't matter
what you believe.
You're here just
the same as I am.
Now, do you want to get
your Earth back or not?
What does he want me to do?
Oliver's going to Russia
to retrieve plans
to build a weapon.
You need to get
them first.
I thought Oliver was
your friend.
He is, but this is
bigger than him,
bigger than any of us.
Well, whatever the Monitor
offered you must be
really something for you
to be able to betray
everyone that you
care about.
I am doing this for
them, to protect them.
Are you going
to help me?
[softly]
Yeah.
I will.
Contact me when
it's done.
And here I thought I was
supposed to be the bad guy.
Help you?
Yeah. I was looking
for Jason.
Yo, Jason!
You got a visitor.
How you doing, Jason?
[Roy] How'd you find me?
Oliver's son...
William. He found you.
Oliver's son.
Isn't he, like, 13?
Heh! Yeah, well,
it's a long story.
I have a feeling you
didn't come all this way
just to catch me
up to speed.
I didn't. I need
your help, Roy.
Whatever you're about
to ask me to do, I can't. I'm sorry.
You haven't even heard
what I have to say, man.
'Cause I don't need to.
You know what I did.
I'm not a hero
anymore, John,
not with my condition.
So you're just gonna
walk out on me,
same way you did Thea?
No.
Thea told Oliver that you left, man,
without even saying good-bye.
It was for the best
for the both of us.
I needed a fresh start,
which is what I'm doing now.
Ok, it was...
it was good to see
you, John.
Roy...
look, man,
I know earlier this year
was a struggle for you,
but this crisis is
a threat that's bigger
than anything we've
ever faced.
I wouldn't be here, man,
if we did not need you.
If I decide to help you,
it'll be a one-time thing.
That's all I'm asking.
I hope you don't mind,
but, uh...
[unzips bag]
I brought you
a change of clothes.
[bell ringing]
So this is
Russia.
[Oliver] Not what you
were expecting?
[William] I just thought
there'd be a lot less dirt.
Is very rude to insult
man's homeland.
Hello, Anatoly.
Oliver Queen...
my brother.
Oh, you think maybe
I punch you again?
Never even
crossed my mind.
Welcome to Russia,
my favorite American.
Now, I have seen some
very crazy things in my life,
but adult children of
Oliver Queen sitting in my bar.
I hope you do not
think badly of me.
Last time we met,
you were little,
and I was on wrong
side of history.
[speaking Russian]
I like this one already.
I was surprised to learn
that you were in Russia.
I thought the Maldives
would be permanent.
Oh, with Diaz dead,
so reason to stay away.
You got bored.
I miss borscht.
So I reinvent myself.
Bar owner. Hm.
But I got inspired, too.
I got really good
recipe for piña colada.
You should try.
It's delicious.
Who wouldn't want to be
reminded of the tropics
in these cold
Russian winters?
Well, apparently,
his customers.
Nice to see this one's
still charmer.
[Oliver] How's the search
going for General Burov?
Well, it's not
very easy.
But I do have
friends I can call.
I know, but I... I don't
want them involved in this.
[Mia] Why not?
If he has friends that
can help, it...
Because, Mia,
with due respect,
the people that Anatoly
is describing...
aren't really friends.
Let's just keep this one
in the family, ok?
[Anatoly] All right.
I work to find Burov
hard way.
You really think
an energy weapon's
gonna stop this
Monitor guy?
Yeah well, that's the hope.
Why this place?
The military stores all
its excess plutonium here.
The problem is it's
impenetrable.
Which is why you
asked me to come.
You need a B and E expert
to get inside?
Yeah. Well, actually, it's
more of a smash and grab.
There's a shipment
coming in tonight.
We are gonna steal
the plutonium
before it gets inside.
Go. Go. Go.
Why not bring
Dinah or Rene?
They have their hands full
in Star City.
Must be weird, right?
Oliver meeting
his future son.
[chuckles]
Yeah. Well, he's not
the only one.
In the future, I adopt
Ben Turner's son, Connor.
He's an agent in
Knightwatch,
future version of
A.R.G.U.S.
Well, it sounds like he would've
been a great candidate
for this mission.
[scoffs] You didn't need me
for this, John.
So what are we really
doing here?
You said you wanted
to atone.
Well, you can't do that
by fixing cars.
You do that by
rejoining the team.
I know you think you can't
control your bloodlust.
That's only because you haven't
figured out a way that works.
Because there is no way.
So whatever you're
about to say,
I don't want to hear it.
Look, we're already here,
so I'm gonna help you.
But once we're done,
I'm going to disappear
to a place where even
William can't find me.
I have classic
bad news/good news.
I find general Burov.
Is that the bad news?
I'm confused about the order.
Bad news is, is
he is man who likes betting
and blood, which means
only place to find him,
Krovavaya Banya.
"The Bloodbath."
[Laurel] Oh. Heh. Doesn't
that sound lovely?
It's not lovely.
It's a fight club.
[William] Oh. That sounds
like where I met her.
He met you where?
Well, when I
first left home,
I had to find a way
to make money.
So I fought, and I won.
Like father, like daughter,
eh, tovarisch?
You, me, and Laurel
will go to the club
to find Burov.
You two are gonna
stay here.
[Mia] Did you not hear
what I just said?
I grew up in fight clubs.
You did not grow up
in fight clubs
that were run
by the Bratva.
Then why did you bring
us on this mission
if you're not
gonna let us help?
This is not a regular mission.
This is the Bratva.
They are terrible people,
and you guys are my kids.
Yes, but we're not children.
Well, you are when
I look at you.
And I'm sorry, but this is
how it's gonna be.
[softly]
Okay.
[spectators shouting excitedly]
[Laurel] So this is what
the Russians do for fun.
I assume that we want to have
our chat with the general
without crossing
the Bratva.
[Oliver] We want to move quickly
and keep our heads low.
There is General.
Damn it. So boring.
General Burov...
I am Anatoly Knyazev,
Danik's friend.
Danik has
big mouth.
What do you want?
Your expertise...
with something sensitive.
Lucky for you,
this fight is boring.
Let us go talk.
[punches landing]
[kicks landing]
I abandoned this
pulse wave generator project.
Too unpredictable,
bad business.
So...
why should I give
to you,
Kapiushon?
Maybe you should've kept
your secret identity secret?
[Laurel] So this means that
you won't be giving
us the plans willingly.
No need for unpleasantness.
I am willing to make deal.
Good. What do you want?
A fighter,
someone to upset
the favorite
so I cannot
be bored.
Should be easy for you,
Kapiushon, no?
So I win, and then you
give us the plans.
Done deal.
[Burov] Excellent.
I will go make it so.
[claps]
You saw that goliath, right?
He is twice your size.
So I give him
half a chance.
[spectators booing]
[fight announcer
speaking Russian]
You got a problem?
Nyet.
Oliver seems to think
you are hero now.
I'm not so sure.
I think you may be
like snow leopard
who cannot change spots.
You changed yours.
Worry less about me and
more about your friend over there.
I'll sweep the perimeter.
[rings]
[spectators booing]
[laughing]
[heart beating]
Wow.
Impressive, no?
[Laurel] Anatoly, let's
get the car ready.
[booing continues]
[Burov chuckling]
Very good! I don't think you have
many fans here, though.
But I am man of my word.
[Man] Not so fast.
This one needs to learn
not to put nose
in other people's business.
Oleg, wha... what a pleasure.
Did you really think
you could conduct business
on Bratva territory
without me knowing?
Of course not. This simply fighter
collecting his winnings.
He's no mere fighter,
are you, Oliver Queen?
How does he know
who you are?
[Oleg] Everyone in Russia
knows Kapiushon.
[Oliver] We have no fight
with you or the Bratva.
That is what we came for.
When we have it, we're gone.
The general only operates
here because we say he can.
And we did not say.
[Oliver] No!
[gunshot]
Mia.
[groaning]
You okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
- Where are we?
- Um.
Yeah, probably some
Bratva hideout.
I told you to stay put, Mia.
What were you thinking?
That we needed
to finish the mission.
You understand that I had
it handled, correct?
Uh, apparently not,
considering
we are tied up in
a creepy basement.
Why did he call you
"Kapiushon"?
Kapiushon is a nickname
that the Bratva gave me.
It means "hood."
You were a member
of the Bratva.
You should've told me.
I didn't want you or
William involved in this.
- I can handle myself.
- That is not what this is about.
Then what is it about?
Ugh. Damn it.
[Oleg] We tied your thumbs.
[groans]
You went to a lot of
trouble to get this.
Even we couldn't crack
its security encryptions.
Must be worth
a great deal.
Tell me what it is.
No.
I will only ask once more.
You have 5 seconds.
- [Oleg] 5...
- Don't tell him anything.
4... 3...
2...
They're plans...
[Mia sighs]
For a weapon that
Burov's building.
Was that so hard?
Now we can move on
to next phase.
Ok, what are the chances
that my father and sister
are in the clutches of the
Russian mob but aren't already dead?
Slim and getting slimmer
every second we do not find them.
Ok, their phones aren't online.
Why aren't their phones online?
Will have been destroyed
so as not to trace them.
[Laurel] Aren't the people
in your family
constantly injecting each other
with tracking devices?
Normally, I would say,
"God, I hope not,"
but now I guess I can
see the advantages.
Have you ever hacked
a CCTV camera?
- No.
- Well, congratulations.
You're about to learn
the only upside
of a Russian
surveillance state.
Okay.
The shipment
should be here soon.
What made you wait
till now to give me your big pitch?
I'm guessing Connor told you
something bad about me in the future.
Not just about you.
Tell me.
William finds you
on Lian Yu
after being there for years,
apparently, in some
self-imposed exile.
I never get rid of
my bloodlust?
You knew all that, and you still
thought you could come save me?
Because there's more
to your story.
You may have started
on Lian Yu, Roy,
but that's not
where you ended.
Felicity sent William to
that island to find you
because she believed in you.
You go back to Star City,
man. You work with the kids.
You help them
save the city, Roy.
How is that possible?
Because you found the way
to control your bloodlust.
You found that it was
by being part of a team.
You kept your distance because
you believed that you were a danger
to everyone around you,
but the real danger
was believing that you can deal
with your past alone.
It's pretty ballsy
thinking you can give me
the answer 20 years earlier.
Yeah, well, hopefully, this time,
you don't have to wait that long.
Don't touch her.
I told you everything
that I know!
We will see.
[gun cocks]
On the line.
No.
Mia, no.
Mi... Mi... Mia!
Ring the bell.
You have 60 seconds.
Begin.
[Mia groaning]
[Mia breathing heavily]
[electricity crackling,
man groaning]
[thudding]
[buzzer sounds]
[Oleg] Time is up.
[empty gun clicks]
[exhales]
I needed to make sure
you weren't lying
about the drive.
Got it. CCTV footage of
Mia and Dad being taken
into a warehouse on
the east side of town.
Thank you, illegal
Russian satellites.
Great. Well,
let's go save day.
Are you ok?
I should've been
able to do it.
Oh, I should have
enough slack now.
To do what?
[crack]
Aah! Uh!
What the hell?
I can dislocate
my thumbs.
It's a useful technique
if getting tied to a chair
is gonna become
a habit.
You have got to teach me
how to do that.
[Canary cry]
So you not ring bell.
Still, very impressive
to, uh, not die.
You shouldn't have told
them what was on the drive.
They would've
killed you if I didn't.
Or we would've been able
to escape without you
- giving up the information.
- Mia.
[Laurel] Okay, can we please
just save the family squabble
until after we have
the plans?
Oleg's bound to figure out how
much they're worth.
Well, he's smart businessman.
He will figure out
way to sell it.
[Oliver] We need to
figure out when and where
the sale is happening,
and then we go recover the drive.
Let me guess.
Me and William get to
stay at the bar, right?
You're going home,
both of you.
No.
I have a feeling there's
less drama out here.
Yeah.
What do you mean, "no"?
I'm sorry, Dad, but we
just saved you
from being murdered by
a bunch of gangsters.
I'm on team Mia here.
Yeah, but Mia just got
kidnapped by the Bratva.
- So did you.
- I'm your father, all right?
It is my primary
job in the world
to protect you.
We don't need that.
In the future, we're the ones
that are saving the city.
Well, this isn't
the future!
This is months after
I was heartbroken
right before I left...
that I couldn't get you
on the phone
at your grandparents'.
So I walked into your room
to look at you one last time,
and you looked back
at me from your crib.
And because you made
the choice to protect us,
I had to spend
my whole life alone.
I didn't have a chance
to get to know my brother,
to get to know you.
I'm sorry that
it worked out that way.
And both of you can decide
on your own how much...
how much you want to hate me
and how much blame
you want to assign.
But I made a promise
to your mother to keep you safe.
And there... there is
no world,
there is no universe,
there's no past,
present, or future
where I break it.
Fine.
You ready?
As I'll ever be.
Let's go!
[alarm]
Must be some kind of
tamper alarm.
- I'll get the payload.
- I'll keep watch.
Hey, hey! Hey.
Hey, Roy.
Roy, look at me, man.
Look at me!
Roy, you're all right.
Y... you got it?
I do. It's right here.
Let's get
the hell out of here.
- Any word from your contact?
- Nyet.
Oh, these things
take time.
[sighs]
I don't know about you, but
I could handle drink
without umbrella.
I'm good, thank you.
If by good, you mean...
how you say... moody,
yes, you are.
Is this because you
ruin family vacation?
I have to send them home
for their protection.
Do you not think
they can handle it?
They can handle it.
I just...
I want to keep them
away from the Bratva.
You mean keep them away
from your Bratva past.
Dark time for me.
That is understandable.
You are ashamed.
You have truly done
some terrible things.
Thank you for
the reminder.
But you also have done
some good things.
It's important that
the kids see both.
Right, but why would I
want to share some of the...
worst mistakes of my entire life
with my children?
That is the thing
about teaching.
It's not about what
you want to say.
It's about what they
need to hear.
Remember first thing
I taught you?
Living is not for the weak.
Your children are not
weak, Oliver.
They're also not children.
Whatever it is
you have to say,
they can handle it.
If you do not,
they will never learn to be heroes.
Oof. It would suck
to be that door.
[scoffs]
If you're here to give me
a pep talk or whatever,
just don't.
Don't flatter yourself.
I just couldn't stand
the smell of that stale bar anymore.
It smells like cabbage.
That's one more thing I
won't miss about this place.
So you're actually
going home.
Why wouldn't I?
Dad doesn't want me here.
Oh, God. I can't stand
pity parties.
Easy for you to say.
And why is that?
You're the Black Canary.
All I've ever heard are stories
about how great you are.
In the future, you even
save me once
like it was nothing.
Are you sure that's actually
me you're talking about?
Okay, you can cut
the false modesty.
Some people are
cut out to be heroes,
others not so much.
Is this really all because
you didn't ring some stupid bell?
Well, I couldn't save
Zoe either.
Every time I try
and live up to my dad
or to prove that I can
do what it is you all do,
I... I fail.
Do you think your
father is any better?
If you're trying to
live up to us, don't.
We are just as flawed
as anyone,
especially me.
All you can do is
live up to yourself.
What does that even mean?
Are you really the
type of person that just gives up?
Oh, good.
Do we have time for
one more fight before we leave?
I'm not looking
for a fight.
Then stop trying to
send us home.
We're not leaving.
Good because I need
your help.
Oleg is selling drive
during bloodbath tonight.
And how are we
supposed to get in?
They know our faces.
Right. We use that
to our advantage.
You and I are going in
the ring together as a team.
You would be
helping us get in.
[Anatoly] Sorry. I did not have
time to get it dry cleaned.
I'm really more of
a behind the screen kind of guy,
but wow. That is
a nice suit. Huh.
[Laurel] What exactly will
Anatoly and I be doing
while you two are playing
father/daughter fight club moment?
When Oleg realizes that it's
the two of us in the ring,
that'll cause a distraction.
You guys go and steal
the drive.
What do you say?
Well, I'm in.
Fancy rich guy is the role
I was born to play.
You?
Why the hell not?
Suit up.
[crowd shouting,
fighters groaning]
[fight announcer
speaking Russian]
Now I see why they
call it the bloodbath.
You sure about this?
Just get us in,
please.
[conversation in Russian]
Not from you, American.
Well, if it's not
about money,
then how about stakes?
Has anyone survived
6 men before?
Nyet.
My guys will fight 6.
You fight next.
Do we really need to be
setting records tonight?
You like a challenge, right?
Just please don't die.
[comms beeping]
Anatoly, you guys set?
Da. But no sign of
high rollers.
Now is good time to strike.
How much time do we have?
Five minutes give or take.
Well, this is gonna be fun.
I've seen what you
can do in there,
so just trust your
instincts, okay? I do.
[fight announcer
speaking Russian]
[speaking Russian]
[cheering]
[rings]
[speaking Russian]
Nyet...
That's our cue.
Pakhan will still be
protected.
[Laurel]
I'll deal with the muscle.
You just watch my back.
[knife slices]
[blows landing]
Tick-tock. You guys
have the plans yet?
[pistol cocks]
Don't move
or I'll shoot.
[gunshot]
You said watch back.
I got it. Let's move.
[mouths "Wrap it up."]
[booing]
[booming]
I could actually
get used to this.
Congratulations. Now
you my favorite American.
[Oliver] Hey, don't get too excited.
He has a lot of favorite Americans.
[Laurel]
Did you talk to John?
I did. He got the plutonium
with an assist from Roy.
[William] All we have to do
is whip up an energy wave
to destroy an all-knowing
space being. Easy.
Before that, I would like
to propose a toast
to Mia and William.
Couldn't have done this
without you.
Vashe zdorovie.
Actually, here we say
prochnost.
Prochnost?
Prochnost.
It means strength.
It means a lot more
than that.
Um, would you mind
giving me a minute
with these two, please?
- [Anatoly] Yes.
- [Laurel] Sure.
Ah. Leave the bottle.
I know that I haven't really
spoken to the two of you
about my time in Russia.
And that is because there
are some things that I did here
that I'm not
very proud of.
As I'm coming to grips with the fact
that the two of you are grown up,
I'm realizing that
shielding you from the bad
isn't going to do
our relationships any good.
From this point forward,
whatever you want to know,
whatever you might want
to ask me is fair game, okay?
[William] Like dislocating
your thumbs?
'Cause I can't believe
I missed that.
Maybe something
a little less painful.
What about that island
you were on?
It's Lian Yu.
It's Mandarin
for "purgatory."
[Roy] You think
that'll be enough?
Yeah, well, this
should do the trick.
Roy, thanks for
your help, man.
It was good having you back,
even if it was
just for one last
mission.
I think I'm gonna
stick around for a while.
If you're gonna be
taking on a space god,
I figure you might need
all the help you can get.
I'm glad you changed
your mind.
You know, when I
first met Oliver,
he gave me a purpose,
but he also gave me
all of you.
It makes sense that
having a team is
what helps me in
the future, so why wait?
Besides, you know,
I kind of miss this place.
Welcome back, Roy.
[chuckles softly]
Don't forget to send me that picture
of my dad with that haircut.
Don't forget to ask
about Bratva tattoo.
We have matching.
[Oliver] Used to.
Used to, actually.
Oh, ho. I'm gonna need to
hear that story immediately.
Thank you.
I always seem to end up
in your debt.
We are beyond
keeping score.
We have been friends,
we have been enemies.
From now on, let us
just be brothers.
Not the Bratva kind.
No! Real family, like
the one you have now.
I can be the fun uncle.
Being father really
suits you.
Good-bye, brother.
Thank you.
Good-bye, Oliver.
All right. Let's go.
Oh, Laurel, uh...
there's something
I want to say.
What? One last hilarious
Russian joke for the road?
Sorry to doubt you.
I guess leopards really
can change spots.
Or in your case,
bird, feather.
I thought you said you
weren't sentimental.
Maybe I change, too,
like you.
Did you bring the plans?
About that.
I have decided not
to join you
and your cosmic
fashion tragedy
that you're
in cahoots with.
Then you won't get
your Earth back.
If saving it means going back
to the person that I used to be,
then what the hell
is the point?
You really have changed.
Look, I'm new to this whole
doing the right thing game,
but you should really tell
your family the truth.
Not yet.
Then this is gonna be
a little awkward.
I didn't want to
believe it.
I'm sorry.
[dart gun fires]
Lyla, what have you...
what have you done?
Greg, move your head.