ROY: Felicity, all I'm trying to do
is make things easier on you.
By having me completely reconfigure
our phone system?
Do you even know how difficult it is to ping
a clone off a hacked transband multiplex?
No, but only because
you weren't speaking English just now.
Sara.
I didn't know where else to take her.
Oh, my God.
-What happened?
-I couldn't...
I couldn't leave her.
FELICITY: We have to call...
We could take her to the hospital.
Ollie, it's not fair.
We just got her back. It's not fair.
No.
OLIVER: I'm so sorry.
LAUREL: No.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
We'll take our position here.
Who's your target?
I don't have a target.
-You do.
-What?
It might have escaped your notice,
but Waller doesn't have a sense of humor.
Oh, really?
Then why did she drag me off of Lian Yu...
...and bring me to Hong Kong
to become her hit man?
To become her operative.
She needs you or she wouldn't be threatening
my family to assure your compliance.
The target will be entering our line
any moment.
The target will walk 10 paces through
the roof garden, then arrive at his hotel suite.
-That's your window.
-I see it.
Now.
Tommy?
You know,
Sara used to have a stuffed animal.
It was this old worn-out shark
that she got from the Starling Aquarium.
Every time something awful
would happen to her, I would always find her...
...holding that stupid little shark
close to her chest.
And now that my sister's dead...
...again, the only thing
that I can think about...
...is finding that dumb stuffed animal
and putting it in her arms.
-I'm sorry.
-You have nothing to apologize for.
Hey, whoever did this, I'm gonna find them.
We're going to.
When I thought
that Sara died on the Gambit...
...the only thing I could do
was scream at the ocean.
I had so much anger and rage
I didn't know what to do with it. But I do now.
And I'm going to help you catch
whoever it is that did this.
You're already helping.
Laurel, you told us where to look.
-I'm just supposed to sit here and wait?
-No.
Now you take care of yourself
and your family.
Your father is gonna need you.
Telling him now, it would kill him.
If we wait until we catch whoever did this,
it'll be easier on him.
Okay.
Where are you going?
I don't know.
I don't know anything anymore.
But I know that a bar is the last place
I should be.
[DIALING]
[LINE RINGS]
Come on, pick up.
THEA [ON MACHINE]:
You've reached Thea. Leave a message.
Thea, it's Oliver. Uh...
I know you're still traveling,
but I just... I could really...
I'd really like to hear your voice.
So please call me back.
-What did we get off the cameras?
-The place is a drug haven.
They've all either been disabled
or paint-balled by local dealers.
-Where are you going?
-Where it happened.
Felicity told me.
You okay?
The killer stood there.
-Loose gravel on the rooftop.
-Oliver.
Sara was here.
Scuff marks back to the edge.
You don't have to do this right now.
-It's the only thing that I can do.
-I get it.
Military training, stay on task.
Your friend gets shot, you keep fighting.
But, Oliver...
-I'm fine.
-Well, I'm here for you just the same.
Sara was my friend too.
If you think you're going after the person...
...who did this solo,
you couldn't possibly be more wrong.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
-Yeah.
FELICITY:Detective Lance called.
He says it's important.
Think he knows about Sara?
[SIGHS]
-What is it, detective?
-You okay?
You look like someone
peed in your Corn Flakes.
That kind of day, huh?
-What's going on?
-Another archer in town.
Dropping bodies.
-Seen this guy's work before?
-I might have.
You know where S.C.P.D.'s finest
might find him?
-Who's the victim?
-John Burke.
Some corporate financier from Qurac.
Seems like he wandered into the wrong part
of town looking for local entertainment...
...ended up with an arrow in his chest.
Hey.
Watch your back, all right?
Whoever this guy is...
He's a killer.
Her hands are so small.
I never noticed before.
She was always so strong and brave.
[FELICITY SNIFFLES]
I always envisioned her
as this sort of Amazonian warrior.
[CHUCKLES]
Invincible.
Something I could never be.
I was so jealous.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Hi. I know, I was supposed
to come in to work today. I... The... I'm sorry.
There's been a death in the family.
Thank you.
DIGGLE: Do you have any idea
what other archer could have done this?
There aren't that many of us.
Maybe 10 that I know of and most of them
are in the League of Assassins.
-Oliver, you don't think...?
-No.
No.
They don't target their own.
-What'd you find out?
-He hit again.
An abandoned warehouse
on the corner of Third and Lemire. Ninth floor.
The victim was a foreman, Tim Kaufmann.
Security cameras can't get an angle.
-Then who's that?
-Just some low-level dealers.
They set up shop in warehouses.
Doesn't look like an archer.
-He might be a witness.
DIGGLE: Where do you want me?
Will Lyla give you access
to A.R.G.U.S.'s database?
Lyla will give us access to A.R.G.U.S.
I need a list of everyone on their radar.
Assassins who use a bow.
I'm on it.
What?
Thea hasn't called back yet.
-You didn't eliminate the target.
-That's not a target. That's my best friend.
Why am I pointing a gun at my best friend?
-Is this some sort of test?
-Yes.
-One you failed.
-Good. Flunk me.
You think it's a coincidence your friend
showed up in Hong Kong?
-He's here looking for you.
-What?
When you logged into your e-mail,
it set off an alert.
Dead men don't check their e-mail, Oliver.
-So this is my fault?
-Waller needs you.
She can't let you be compromised by a rich kid
flashing your picture all over Hong Kong.
Whether you're the one who pulls the trigger
or not, she wants Tommy Merlyn off the board.
That is a Cobalt encrypted workstation.
You better not be using it to tweet.
I was... I was, um, actually just...
Accessing an FBI database? What...?
Roy, why are you looking for Thea?
-I don't think she is where she says she is.
-Why would she lie?
Oliver needs to see this.
-No. This is my fault. He's gonna kill me.
-What if she's in trouble?
What if she's not?
What if she just needs space?
She's had five months
and thousands of miles of space.
Oliver needs to see this.
[SIGHS]
You need to show it to him.
[CELL PHONE CHIMING]
You have got to be kidding me.
-Wait. Where are you going?
-There's someone I need to kill.
[ELEVATOR BELL DINGS]
Did you do it to make a point?
Because I get it. Loud and clear.
You are rich. You are impulsive.
You are the creepiest stalker
that I have ever had to deal with.
Believe me, that is saying a lot.
What are you doing to our old offices?
Hi. I'll be right back.
Like it?
I'm trying to liven up the place a bit.
I'm hosting an event tonight.
A pledge drive of sorts.
Gotta make an impression, right?
-Now, what can I do for you?
-You can stop.
You can stop sending me flowers.
You can stop texting me and calling me
and e-mailing me, because I spam them.
Is spam a verb now?
Because I am never, ever,
ever going to work for you.
Actually, you already do.
Only because you bought the store
that I work at.
-No, I didn't.
-Yes, you did.
My boss just called
and told me that you did.
Well, he's wrong.
Kind of.
I bought the holding company
which owns all 20,000 Tech Village stores.
But I guess, either way,
yes, I am your boss now.
So you can either work for me here...
...in a big office with a big salary...
...or you can work for me there
in that awful uniform.
Or I can quit.
Which is what I just did.
[CHUCKLES]
You know, most girls would be flattered
that I spent $1.2 billion to hire them.
Even if I do have a plan
for rebranding the stores.
In case you hadn't noticed,
I am not most girls.
And I don't need this. Or you.
-Or any of this.
RAY: Felicity, I...
I piss people off on a daily basis.
It's part of business...
...and well, being the smartest guy
in any given room, I own that.
I have enough experience with people...
...to know when they're angry
at something else.
You, right now, are not angry at me.
What's your something else?
-Money won't fix this problem.
-Money won't solve most problems.
Not the ones that matter.
But talking helps.
I know we barely know each other.
I'm gonna leave now.
Listen, whatever happened, I'm sorry.
It helps to remember that it gets better.
[ELEVATOR BELL DINGS]
[CLATTERING NEARBY]
Someone was murdered here.
Tell me what you saw.
I saw nothing.
[MAN GROANING]
It was a black face mask. Like a...
Like a hockey mask. Please, man.
Diggle, are you at A.R.G.U.S.?
I've got something.
DIGGLE:
Yeah, I'm here.
I've got a list of archers 20 long, man.
-How many of them wear masks?
-Only one.
Simon Lacroix. Mercenary.
Goes by Komodo.
-Send Felicity everything.
-Yep.
Oliver, I'm opening up the file now.
LAUREL: Is that him?
FELICITY: Born in Sainte-Sophie, Quebec.
Raised by a single mom.
Terrible credit score.
And wanted for murder in seven countries.
-I need his location.
FELICITY:One minute.
Put him on speaker.
Indexing all active burner cell phones
within the city limits.
That's gotta be 10,000 phones.
Yes, but how many are making calls
to dear old mom in Sainte-Sophie, Quebec?
I got him. He's on the move.
ARROW:
I found Lacroix.
-I need to see what's happening.
-Okay. Pulling up street camera feed.
Oliver, what's happening?
Come on, Ollie.
-Get up.
FELICITY: Oliver?
Are you okay? Oliver?
[SIREN WAILING]
FELICITY:
Oliver, you okay?
He got away.
-I had him, Diggle.
-From the way you look, he almost had you.
-Where's Roy?
-He's out canvassing.
-Tell me about the driver.
-His name is Erlich Kelso.
-He just got out of Starling General.
-Where are we with Lacroix?
-Ditched his burner.
FELICITY: I'm searching for any calls to Quebec.
We used that to track him once.
He's not gonna let it happen again.
We stop searching for Lacroix
and start searching for his target.
-There must be a connection with his victims.
-Already on it.
Well, I mean, what if we just...?
We go to a local morgue...
...and we find a body
that looks like Tommy's?
At the Hong Kong morgue?
You've got a better chance of winning
the lottery and paying Waller off.
I'm not gonna assassinate my best friend.
Do you understand?
There has to be another way.
There is.
But it involves Amanda Waller
finding someone else to execute your friend.
No, not you, Dad.
Look, I'm already in Hong Kong.
No, I didn't tell you I was taking the jet,
because I knew you would freak out like this.
No, I don't know how long, okay?
It doesn't matter.
Listen, if Oliver is still alive,
if he is still here...
[CLEARS THROAT]
Look, why don't you just go back
to banging your Pilates instructor, okay?
I'll just be here searching for my best friend.
I'm sorry, miss. You can't go in there.
Laurel Lance.
I'm with the District Attorney's Office.
Erlich Kelso is a witness
of my ongoing investigation.
-Mr. Kelso is under protective custody.
-Not from me.
If you have a problem with that,
call your captain.
Tell him his daughter says hello.
-Who are you?
-I work in the DA's office.
I already told the police
I don't know anything.
I still have to ask you a few questions.
-Why isn't this working?
-It is.
It's running an NSA algorithm,
aggregating the victims' personal information...
...using every government database
known and unknown.
It's taking too long.
Sara's killer is out there,
which means every minute we waste...
I know. You don't need to tell me
as if I don't already know.
You're right.
And I apologize.
I just need your A game right now, Felicity.
I don't have it.
My friend, our friend, was shot with arrows
and fell off of a rooftop.
Her body is upstairs,
right above us, in a freezer...
...because we don't know what to do with it,
with her.
So I am so sorry, Oliver, if I have feelings,
but maybe if you did too, we...
I'm sorry. That was mean.
But this is Sara we're talking about.
Your Sara.
How can you stand there
being so cold and rational?
Because I don't have the luxury
of falling to pieces.
Everyone's looking to me to handle things...
...to make the right decisions.
Everyone is looking to me to lead.
If I grieve...
...nobody else gets to.
You're still a human being, Oliver.
You're allowed to have feelings.
I know sometimes that it's easier
to live under that hood.
I'm not.
Earlier today, I was looking at Sara.
I realized something.
One of these days, it's gonna be me.
And this...
This life that I've chosen...
...it only ends one way.
So that's it?
You're just gonna spend your life
hiding down here in this cave, waiting to die?
I'm sorry, I'm not gonna wait with you.
Because if there's one thing that today
has taught me, it is that life is precious.
And I want so much more to mine than this.
Let's start with the obvious.
Why would someone wanna kill you?
I have no idea. This whole thing,
it's insane.
Mr. Kelso, despite what you may have heard,
homicides at the hands of a stranger are rare.
Imagine how rare homicides
by bow and arrow are.
-Yeah, the guy was a sicko.
-And you're a liar.
-I'm the victim here.
-You're also a witness, my witness.
You better give me something useful,
or you'll face an obstruction charge.
I wanna talk to your boss,
because you can't treat people like this.
You wanna talk to my boss?
-Oh!
-How's your arm feeling?
What are you doing?
John Burke and Tim Kaufmann,
they were also shot dead with arrows.
-And they're too dead to tell me why.
-I can't.
-Aah!
-Burke and Kaufmann...
...what do the two of them
have to do with you?
We're all working on a deal,
but nobody was supposed to know about it.
[GROANS]
-What kind of deal?
-To build an oil pipeline...
...for AmerTek. It's...
THEA [ON MACHINE]:
You've reached Thea. Leave a message.
Hey, Thea, it's me again. And...
I don't know if you're getting these messages,
but I'd really like to talk to you, so please...
...just call me back.
Bye.
Lyla has multiple teams
trying to get an angle on Lacroix.
Where's Felicity?
Hmm?
She needed some air.
What do you need, Oliver?
I just need Thea to call me back.
That's not gonna happen.
Why? What do you mean?
It was during the siege.
We were gonna run away,
but I couldn't leave without helping you fight.
When I came back, she was gone.
I didn't say anything, because this is my fault.
She knew I was lying to her the entire time.
I'm sorry I didn't say anything about the letter.
I know that I should have.
Okay.
Felicity, I really need to talk to you, so please,
can you call me back as soon as you get this?
LANCE:
Laurel.
-Baby, are you all right? Are you hurt?
-I'm fine.
A guy just got skewered right in front of you,
I hope you're not fine.
What were you doing here
in the first place?
-The district attorney...
-Did not send you.
You lied to my officers,
and now you're gonna stand there...
...and you're gonna lie to me?
-I needed to talk to him. It was important.
LANCE: Look.
I know you wanna help, but you don't need
to take these kind of risks, do you understand?
Pretty sure your sister's got that covered
for both of you.
Yeah.
Go home. We got this.
Okay?
[CELL PHONE RINGS]
I've got something. Meet me at Verdant.
AmerTek Industries,
it's an oil company based in Starling City.
Okay, now that I've consolidated
all of Lacroix's victims' records...
...I can run an algorithm
and see who received money from AmerTek.
LAUREL: How long does that take?
FELICITY: Not long.
A million to Kelso, one more to Burke.
Two more to Kaufmann.
All from a subsidiary from AmerTek in Qurac,
the largest untapped oil field on the planet.
-AmerTek was trying to strike an oil deal.
-Someone paid Lacroix to stop it.
-None of this explains Sara.
-Sara told me she worked in Qurac.
And by worked,
I mean she killed people for the league.
-She might've brought her work home?
-Who authorized the payments?
Board member of AmerTek
called Tom Weston.
Lacroix's next target. What's his location?
You will not believe where he's headed.
-Where do you think you're going?
LAUREL: I'm coming with you.
-Absolutely not.
-The only reason you know where to find him...
You were reckless.
And Lacroix almost put an arrow in you.
Let me handle this.
Don't tell me to stay put and think I'll listen.
You know me better than that.
Sara was trained by some of the greatest killers
in history. Lacroix put her down.
-What is he gonna do to you?
-I don't care about anything except getting him.
-And I will.
-You couldn't before.
I won't let him escape again.
I promise.
[JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING
OVER SPEAKERS]
RAY: Hi.
-Mr. Palmer.
RAY:
Good evening. Hey.
Good to see you.
Thanks for coming. Thanks.
MAN:
Ladies and gentlemen, Mr. Ray Palmer.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you all for coming out tonight.
Given all that has befallen this city,
it's easy for us to lose hope.
To hide in our castles,
be thankful that our ledgers are in the black.
But we, the city's most affluent businessmen
and women, hold its future in our hands.
Tonight, I'm making a pledge.
I will give away half my net worth
to the benefit of our home.
And this will be my salary for the year.
So tonight, I invite you all to join me
in this investment.
Not just with your money.
But with your ingenuity
and most importantly, your time.
This city is my home, but it's yours too.
So help make Star City our future.
[BOTH GRUNTING]
So you're the Arrow.
-I thought you'd be taller.
-It's over.
Lower your bow and live.
We both know that's not gonna happen.
-Who hired you?
-Who is she?
-You don't wanna do this.
-Yes, I do.
Killing him won't bring her back.
I know it won't bring her back. She's dead.
I've stood where you are, where you're so
consumed with rage you can hardly breathe...
...and you think taking revenge
will make it better.
But, Laurel, it won't.
It only makes it worse.
-No, he murdered Sara.
-Who's Sara?
My sister, you son of a bitch.
Two nights ago
you put an arrow in her chest.
Two nights ago I was drunk in Bludhaven.
-You're lying.
LACROIX: I'm proud of my work.
-I wouldn't deny it.
-Even with a gun in your face?
-Laurel, you need to stop and listen to him.
LAUREL: No.
-No, he killed my sister.
-Laurel, Sara wouldn't...
Don't you dare tell me
that this isn't what Sara would've wanted!
Don't you tell me to think of her,
because I am thinking of her.
Laurel, if you pull that trig...
[GUN CLICKING]
You took the bullets out of the gun.
We have to go.
OLIVER:
Lacroix's alibi checks out.
Two murders in Bludhaven. Same M.O.
Same night Sara was killed.
I almost killed Lacroix.
The only thing that matters is you didn't.
Laurel, the trail's run cold.
I'm going to find whoever did this.
I will.
But I don't know when.
Your father deserves to know.
Hey. I got some info here
on the Lacroix fellow.
Yeah, some stuff's come through.
I don't know, yeah, it looks pretty good.
Lacroix. With an X, yeah. I don't know,
the guy's French or something. Why...?
Oh. Hold on, hold on, I gotta call you back.
Laurel, baby, what's wrong?
Hold on.
What is it?
Just tell me. Tell me. What is it?
It's about last night.
At the hospital...
...I lied to you.
You deserve to know the truth and...
[DEVICE BEEPING]
LANCE:
Sorry, sweetheart.
Damn thing goes off every hour
if I don't take my pills.
Laurel, what do you know? You were
in the middle of telling me something.
I just wanted to say that...
That I'm really sorry.
I know that I should've told you the truth.
I just...
I just couldn't.
Hey, I'm your dad. I forgive you.
I always forgive you.
It's all right.
She can rest now. She's home.
It's a Jewish custom.
I know she wasn't, but it feels right.
Laurel.
No, this isn't right.
This isn't...
She doesn't even get a fresh grave?
It's so perverse.
She deserves a proper burial.
-She's earned it.
-No, it's not fair.
No one will ever really know who she was.
Oliver, it's not fair. It's not fair.
Laurel, we'll know.
I know this doesn't count for much...
...but me and Lyla,
we're naming the baby Sara.
We will never forget.
Thank you.
How did I...?
What the hell is going on here?
Where am I?
Please, please don't hurt me.
Look, just let me go, please.
I promise, I won't tell anybody about this.
OLIVER [IN DEEP VOICE]: Would a fisherman
throw his prized catch back in the sea?
What are you talking about?
Look, whoever you are,
you really don't wanna do this.
Do you have any idea who I am?
Who my father is?
OLIVER:
You're Thomas Merlyn.
You've been looking for Oliver Queen.
How do you...? How do you know that?
OLIVER: A simple hack
of a missing billionaire's e-mail account.
I knew somebody would come looking for him,
but I thought it would be his mother, his sister.
But you, the son of the CEO of Merlyn Global,
jackpot.
My friend,
you are gonna make me a very rich man.
So Oliver didn't...?
He isn't...?
Oliver Queen is dead.
He's rotting at the bottom of the ocean.
And you will too...
-...if your father doesn't pay that ransom.
MAN: Hong Kong police.
-I'm in here! Please help! Help!
MAN: Hands up.
-Hong Kong police.
-Please, please, please.
Please, please, please.
Thank you.
-You're going home. You're safe.
-Thank you, thank you.
I'm gonna catch whoever killed her.
I know you are.
And until you do, I'm back on the team.
What about your family?
Sara is family, Oliver. Just like you, man.
So now what?
Now I gotta go get Thea.
It's long past time she came home.
John.
I don't wanna die down here.
So don't, Oliver.
[ELEVATOR BELL DINGS]
-Hey.
-Hi.
Changed your mind.
I just decided I want more out of life.
Well done.
Thanks, Dad.