My name is Oliver Queen.
After 5 years in hell...
I returned home with only one goal...
To save my city.
For 8 years, I've fought
alongside brave men and women
striving for justice,
but then a Crisis came,
and I had to become someone else.
I had to become something else.
I made the ultimate sacrifice,
which helped birth an
entirely new universe.
Now my friends and family will
have to go on without me,
and although I have become a spectre,
there is a part of me that will always be
the Green Arrow.
www.TUSUBTITULO.com
-DIFUNDE LA CULTURA-
Both my children will live.
Mom... what are you doing?
- Thea, I love you.
- No.
Close your eyes, baby.
No!
You possess true courage, Moira.
I'm truly sorry...
You did not pass that on to your son.
It's just such a strange thing to learn
that there's a whole other...
World, I guess...
Where I died.
The people that knew my son best tell me
that when Oliver sacrificed
himself during the Crisis...
OLIVER QUEEN DIES DURING WORLD WIDE CRISIS
that somehow he's the reason
that everything changed,
that the world we're living in right now is
a kind of gift from him.
I don't know. I'm just
trying to process it.
I... I think we're all still
trying to process it,
not only Oliver's death...
DINAH DRAKE
SCPD CAPTAIN
but what he leaves behind.
It's a hell of a legacy.
RENE RAMIREZ
"WILD DOG"
not just a city of heroes,
a world of heroes.
When I started this project,
it was intended to explore the history
and the pitfalls of
vigilantism in Star City.
MARCIA PEDOWITZ
DIRECTOR: EMERALD ARCHER
I never thought this documentary
would have to be retooled
to be a memorial.
Nothing really ever... happens
the way you expect it to happen...
JOHN DIGGLE
"SPARTAN"
and that was... certainly the case...
With Oliver and his mission.
He always said he would go it alone
and that the mission would never...
Be over.
I'm glad he was... wrong
about the first part...
Heartbroken he was wrong about the second.
Thank you.
That was very moving.
Yeah.
- Hey, hey.
- Hey, man.
You all right?
Everything good.
Why do I get the sense that
answer disappoints you?
I just can't believe it, you know?
Let's go.
When Oliver rebooted the universe,
he fixed things.
Ever since the Crisis,
crime in Star City disappeared overnight
literally.
Dig, he... he saved this city.
Yeah.
Come on. It's time.
Prochnost.
I didn't know you speak Russian.
No. That's what Oliver used to say
every time he drank this stuff.
- What exactly is this stuff?
- Vodka.
Yeah. It tastes like Turpentine.
With faint hints of nail polish remover.
So what's the plan?
I plan on getting as drunk
as humanly possible.
No. I mean after the funeral.
From what Dinah tells me,
there's not much need
for vigilantes anymore.
Lance's term ends in April.
He's endorsing me to replace him.
- As mayor?
- No. As a bald guy with an attitude.
Yeah, as mayor.
What about you, D?
Mayor.. for now at
least... Lance actually just
offered me a promotion to Chief of Police.
Guys, look. I know how this looks.
I just don't feel like this is over.
Yeah. You're not reading the
same CompStat reports I am.
We're a month out of this Crisis, Dinah,
and there's tons that we don't know,
but what I do know is this.
Though Oliver's gone, his mission
is far from over.
Finally. What the hell happened?
Jimmy Tarallo gave me a few problems.
And by a few, you mean a
dozen men armed with knives?
No. I mean 22 with machetes.
Queen, you shouldn't be doing this alone.
You're not ready to go
into the field, Diggle.
Yeah? Well, when I signed on,
I told you I was here to
keep the body count low.
That includes you.
Well, I'm fine.
And Tarallo?
A little less so.
What's this?
The next name on the list.
John Byrne? What's the
CEO of a beer company
have to do to deserve an
arrow between the eyes?
Well, the company's a front.
He's using his trucks to ferry
a very different type of commodity.
Drugs?
People.
Human trafficking? Where does this end?
How many names are on your list?
Too many to cross off. Listen, Diggle.
This doesn't end.
The mission is never over.
You can survive this,
make it home, right my wrongs,
but you got to live through this first.
Survive.
No!
- Hey.
- What the frak?
Sorry. I... I didn't mean to scare you.
I meant to time portal to your front door,
but I guess I... I overshot the mark a bit.
This is a... this is a nice room.
Time portal?
Yeah. I'm a time traveler, remember?
Right. Ok. And why did
you time travel here?
Because I'm here to take you
to your father's funeral.
You know, I actually
should have tried that sooner.
It's not that hard, actually.
That's because your arms are
the size of telephone poles.
You doing ok?
When am I never not ok?
I don't think any of us are really ok,
but it seems to be hitting
you particularly hard.
I'm fine, like always.
You ready?
- Yeah. Let's do this.
- Yeah.
So what did Oliver call this thing?
He called it the Mark of Four.
So how you doing?
I'm just... I'm nervous
about the funeral.
Yeah.
Yeah. You know, Thea's gonna be there.
Imagine both of Oliver's
sisters would be there.
I kind of left Thea abruptly.
You're worried about
an awkward reunion.
I'm worried about any kind of reunion.
Well, hey. Look at it this way.
After fighting the Mirakuru soldiers
and the Thanatos Guild,
seeing your ex-girlfriend should be cake.
That's why I'm scared.
I don't want her to be my ex-girlfriend.
So when's Felicity get to town?
I don't know if she's coming.
It's her husband's funeral, man.
Which is exactly why I
think she might miss it.
I don't know, Rene.
She has a nanny watching Mia right now.
Felicity hasn't even made it out of bed.
I have no idea how to help her.
At least bring me for backup.
How many times are we gonna
go over this, Diggle?
You know, I went through
Byrne's financials.
Every month, he gives over $1 million
to this outfit called Black Armada.
- You know who they are?
- Private security firm.
- Former Special Forces.
- That's right,
and you don't think it's
a good idea to bring
a former soldier of your own?
No.
You know what I think?
I don't think you really want me there.
Thanks for finally getting my point.
I don't think you want me
there because you're afraid
I will stop you from committing
cold-blooded murder.
You think that your role is
to keep the body count low.
There's a way you can stop him
tonight without killing him.
You could take him to prison,
you could see that justice is served.
The man traffics in human beings.
- Killing him is justice.
- But at what cost?
You say your mission will never end.
Well, trust me,
it will end a lot sooner
if you lose who you are.
Mia?
Don't worry. The Monitor didn't drop me off
because there's another Crisis coming.
That still doesn't explain
what you're doing here.
Laurel's sister showed up,
thought I might enjoy going
to my dad's funeral.
And what are you doing with all this stuff?
Trying my best to channel my mom.
Sorry. When Sara dropped me off,
she gave me this whole lecture
about not telling people
about the future, so...
A few weeks before Sara showed up...
Something happened.
William!
Right in front of me. I couldn't
do anything to stop it, and...
I am already failing at
being the Green Arrow.
What we do is not easy.
There are setbacks, there are tragedies,
but, God, Mia, your father,
he would be so, so proud
of how you're carrying all of that.
I can't even do the one thing that
he risked his entire life to do...
Protect my family.
What's this?
Well, your mother's Archer Protocol scans
news stations for certain key words.
William Clayton, the son
of the late hero Oliver Queen,
was abducted tonight in his
hometown of Central City.
The police have been unable to confirm
any suspects in the kidnapping.
- Hey.
Look. I'm sorry about the way that I left.
I just...
Ollie's just passed away,
and William's been kidnapped,
so... as far as apologies go,
your timing's a little not great.
If you still think Oliver's
mission's finished,
tell that to William when we get him back.
We will get him back, but, John, William
was kidnapped outside of Star City.
I'm sure that will make him
feel a whole lot better.
- I reached out to Felicity.
- Yeah. Me, too.
Radio silence.
I asked Sara to check on her.
I haven't seen this many
people down here in a while.
Hey.
It's almost like a party.
I tried running a
quad-grid search tasked
to a keyhole satellite array, but...
That array's dark-sided as it
undergoes a firmware upgrade,
but fortunately when William
moved to Central City,
his overbearing stepmom implanted
a subdermal tracking device
into his arm. Ethical... debatable.
Which went dark as soon as
he reentered Star City.
Well, that's convenient at least.
Just one second as I work up a
statistically correlated list
of possible locations he could be at.
That is a very long list.
Which is exactly why we called everyone.
Thank you all for coming,
some on very short notice.
Oliver made the ultimate sacrifice
for his friends and his family.
Now a part of his family needs our help.
This is our most important mission.
Suit up.
Ok. Well, he's not here.
What was the next place on Felicity's list?
Kord Industries.
All right. Well, let's go.
Hey. Can I talk to you for a second?
You already did back at the Bunker, ok?
I get it. You're sorry.
No. I never told you why I left.
And you don't need to.
I understand. You were going through a lot.
Dying, getting resurrected,
it gave me a whole new
perspective on... on everything,
including you.
You know, I got my whole life back,
and I realized that I wanted you in it...
Forever and... and always.
And what does that mean?
It means...
Will you marry me?
Get out.
Get out!
Nice. I would have some shots in the air.
My way's scarier.
So how are things?
It's been a while.
Yeah. Well, a while is what it took
for these rags to work again.
Since then, I've been fighting for justice.
To honor your father?
To honor Oliver.
We've had our differences over the years.
Yeah, I assumed.
Why?
Of everyone,
you're the most like him.
- Clear!
Damn it!
- What?
- He's not here.
Curtis said there's a bunch
of places he could still be.
- Well, we need to find him.
- We will.
We have to find him, Johnny.
We will, Lyla. Are you ok?
Oliver put our family back together.
What happens if... if we
can't do the same for his?
Lyla, look at me. We can,
and we will, I promise.
Let him go!
Who the hell are you?!
I said, who are you?!
You're wearing his hood. You should know.
No, please, please.
You stay back!
John Byrne...
You have failed this city.
Let him go!
I brought him up here to throw him off.
My whole life ended right here!
I don't care! Final warning.
He thought he was saving me.
8 years in Iron Heights never saved anyone.
So you kidnap his son,
the man who spared your life?
I should put this arrow in you right now!
Do it! After 8 years in prison,
I got nothing left to live for anyway!
Go ahead!
No. If Oliver Queen didn't kill you,
then neither will I,
but your ass is going back to prison.
This is the riser,
this is the arrow shelf,
and this is the fadeout.
That's really cool.
That's...
Mia.
Must be a lot to take in.
Yeah. That's the...
Understatement of the Millennium.
She became a hero.
Well, she had good parents.
Do you... you want to meet her?
I don't know.
She... she might be here,
but she's... she's also at home,
waiting for me,
and I get to see her grow up.
I'm not sure I want to rush that.
- Hey.
Something on the news you should see.
What?
William Clayton was safely recovered
from his kidnapper John Byrne.
Apparently the abduction was revenge
for Oliver Queen bringing
Byrne to justice 8 years ago.
We have exclusive footage of the rescue.
With Oliver Queen confirmed dead,
we can only speculate that he inspired
a new generation of heroes
to carry on his mission.
Like I said... proud.
Diggle?!
Don't use just your arms.
Power's coming from your hips.
Thanks for the tip.
Just get real good at that,
and maybe I'll eventually
take you out in the field.
Byrne didn't really have
a good night, did he?
He had a better night than you think.
He's being arraigned in the morning.
Plenty of people in this
book that deserve to die,
plain and simple,
but probably not everyone.
Let's consider Mr. John Byrne to be
proof of concept.
That people can be redeemed?
That one day I'll be able to trust you.
Your mom let me in.
Is it just me, or does the new Moira
seem to like me a lot
more than the old Moira?
Yeah. She never really liked you that much,
but in her defense, you were a criminal.
Well, I regret nothing.
If I never stole your purse,
then I never would have met you,
and even if you do say no to my proposal,
which I... I really hope you don't...
Loving you has changed my life, Thea.
If Ollie's death has taught me anything,
it's... that we don't have a
lot of time in this life.
As long as you promise
if you ever freak out
on me like that again,
you tell me instead of just leaving.
Yeah, yeah. I can make that promise.
Then yes.
Yes?
I will marry you, Roy Harper.
Hey. What are you doing here?
Looking for you.
Well, I was just looking for Dinah.
I think she's... ghosting me.
Do you have a second to talk?
Want to step into not my office?
So... what's up?
It's about Oliver.
Well, not exactly him, but...
Who his sacrifice brought back.
- Like me?
- And Tommy and Moira...
But not me
or the other me, yo...
Your Laurel.
Look. We don't exactly know the rules
of this whole resurrection thing.
Yes, we do.
You're all of the people who Oliver
would have wanted his
sacrifice to bring back,
and Laurel, she... she would have been
on that list, too, if it wasn't for me.
Oliver's death, it fixed everything else.
Why didn't it fix this, too?
Because, sweetheart, there
is nothing about you
that needed to be fixed.
It's all right.
Dig, what's going on?
The end of the line.
You were right. The mission's over.
Just took me a while to accept that.
I think accepting that meant accepting
that Oliver was really gone.
You know, Sara said that before Oliver died
that he became something else.
I'd like to think that somehow, someway,
he's still here.
I'd drink to that.
Just as long as it's no more
of that godawful vodka.
Ok. Cool. So... you're moving on.
So what's next for you?
Lyla accepted a promotion in Metropolis,
so we're all gonna move
there after the funeral.
So am I.
I'm not gonna take the promotion.
Just no point being police in a safe city,
and there are lots of cities
that still need saving.
Damn, and here I am getting to
be elected in a few months,
and you guys decide to move away.
Kind of hard not to take that personally.
Don't worry, Rene. You are
gonna be a great mayor
because you're a great man.
I learned from the best.
Oliver.
And the two of you.
Who's getting the lights?
I will.
I'm gonna miss this place.
We all will.
Thank you for coming.
For a long time...
I hated Oliver Queen.
I blamed him for the death
of my youngest daughter,
I blamed him for the violence in my city,
I interrogated him, I hunted him,
persecuted him.
I've never been more wrong in my life.
Oliver Queen wasn't just a hero.
He was a good man.
He was an honorable person.
The fact that he didn't start out that way
makes him, in my book,
even more honorable.
He stands as a reminder to all of us
that anyone can change.
So will this.
HE SAVED THIS CITY - OLIVER QUEEN
GREEN ARROW
I just don't understand.
If Ollie could fix everything,
then why couldn't he fix this?
I think that Oliver could
only change the things
that didn't change him,
and if not for your father and...
What he did for Oliver,
your brother would never have
become the man that he was.
I still can't believe Ollie's really gone.
I know, sweetheart.
I'm sorry to intrude,
but I wanted to meet you.
- I'm...
- My sister.
Oliver told me a lot about you.
I'm sorry that it took something like this
for us to finally meet.
Yes. Emiko, you are welcome here anytime.
Thank you.
So you're from another Earth, is that it?
I know it's a lot to take in.
Well, I just found out there's
a reality where I was dead,
so that's the curve I'm
grading on these days.
The Laurel of, well, this Earth...
She was my wife.
So it must be strange seeing me.
Yeah. Well, strange
enough to blow the curve...
But there's something nice about it, too.
My condolences on your husband's passing.
I had our marriage erased.
Feelings cannot be erased.
I had no feelings for him.
Our marriage was father's perverse joke,
meant to torment me.
Our father only ever meant for
you to have a normal life.
I have lived a life far more normal
than the one father designed for me.
Hey. Thank you for coming.
There's nowhere else I'd be.
Sara, this is my sister Talia.
- Hi.
- Hello.
Talia, this is Sara,
my beloved.
Hey, Dad.
Hi.
- I'm...
- I know.
This morning, you were teething,
and now you're... I mean, wow.
Dad had a very similar
reaction when he first saw me.
You met your father.
Yeah. He trained me.
He taught me to be a hero,
how to be like him.
I can tell you're a lot like him.
I can only hope.
Felicity.
Hey.
I'm so sorry.
- Thank you.
- He was a good man.
I was there at the end, and...
Every day, I'm tortured with the thought
that I could have done more,
should have done more.
No. You did everything
that you could, Barry.
How could you know that?
Well, because, you know, I know you.
I'm sorry.
Hey. Hey.
Hey.
Felicity.
I'm so sorry.
There is no body down there, no?
No.
We buried a casket full of mementos.
Does anybody want to say a few words?
I'm barely keeping it together as it is.
I think that Oliver would have been worried
that I'd say something
tactless anyway, so...
- I don't know what to say.
- Yeah.
Words seem... meaningless.
Hey.
Should be you.
The Oliver that I met 8 years ago
is not the one that we
say good-bye to today.
Oliver always told me that
in order to save his city,
he had to become someone else,
he had to become something else.
I always thought that meant
becoming the Green Arrow,
but... today, I realized
that meant becoming
a better man,
the best man he knew how to be,
and he took all of us
with him on that journey.
He changed everything.
Oliver brought heroes into the world,
he inspired heroes,
he inspired all of us here.
I was his brother,
and Oliver Queen was mine.
Of course, life will go on.
It always does,
but how, what twists and
turns it will take,
I can't say.
I don't know what the future holds...
Except to say to expect the unexpected.
VOTE RAMIREZ 2020
THE FUTURE IS NOW
Oliver may be gone,
but his mission endures.
That mission lives on,
Oliver lives on
in the people he inspired.
Some will take that mission
to the rest of the world...
Maybe even beyond that...
OLIVER QUEEN
MEMORIAL DRIVE
because if the past 8 years
has shown us anything...
It's that this universe is
far bigger than any of us
could have dared imagine...
Even if it is a little less bright
without him in it.
OLIVER QUEEN
1985-2019
BELOVED SON, BROTHER, HUSBAND, AND FATHER
HERO OF STAR CITY
THE GREEN ARROW
Where I'm taking you,
there is no return.
I have waited a very long time to see him.
I'm ready.
Hi.
Glad you could finally make it.
This is so nice.
Not to complain. I just thought
that the afterlife would look
a little less like your old office.
It's my mom's office.
I wanted to be where I first saw you.
Well, that would be in the I.T.
Department 7 floors down.
You sure?
You're cute.
It's too bad you're, you know, dead,
which is obviously a lot worse
for you than it is for me.
It's a long story.
Lucky for us...
We have all the time in the world
for me to tell it to you.
www.TUSUBTITULO.com
-DIFUNDE LA CULTURA-