Previously on "Arrow"...
These are
innocent people.
And you can save them...
By wiring $10 million into
that account every night.
$70 million.
D--don't.
I'm going to make sure
Vince didn't
die for nothing.
I'm going to kill every
last one of them...
Starting with Laurel.
Laurel!
There is
a piece of my daughter
in you somewhere.
And I'm gonna get it
out whatever it takes.
Thank you
for all you've done
to get justice for my boy.
The new police captain--
she's on my payroll.
Tell your boy
I said hello.
"Severed subclavian artery.
No defensive wounds."
How does this happen?
Sometime between
transfer and intake at Iron Heights,
an inmate caught
James unaware.
By the time the
guards intervened, it was too late.
Motive.
The inmate was
a head case off his meds.
For all we know, he thought he was
killing his mother.
Well, the random murder
of Cayden James, it--
it doesn't feel very random.
It was bad timing
and even worse luck, Mr. Mayor.
That's all.
All right.
But Cayden James was
my responsibility.
If a head has to roll for this,
make it mine.
That is not how I
run things here.
Just...
Keep doing
what you're doing.
One at
a time! One at a time!
Thank you.
I understand that you're angry.
I am...I am angry, too,
but we are not
gonna solve any problems
by yelling at one another.
Last I heard,
Cayden James is dead,
but you still don't have
the money he stole.
You mean the money
he was given.
We are still in the
process of recovering
the money that was
extorted from the city.
We just need
a little more time.
We're on the verge
of financial collapse.
Without an influx
of cash soon,
we all have to shut down--
schools, sanitation,
emergency services,
everything.
Fine. We will have
those funds back in 48 hours.
You have my word.
All of you have
my word.
Thank you.
Ok, um,
not that I don't love your
confidence and everything,
but, um, should we really be
making promises like that?
The accountant
is on his way back
from Corto Maltese with the
money that was deposited
into Cayden James' bank
account as we speak.
You could've
just told them that,
got those folks
off your back.
I'm not telling them
anything concrete
until that money is
back in the city's
bank accounts.
My bigger concern
right now is finding
Cayden's associates
before Dinah does,
because she is on
the warpath.
Yeah.
Any luck with that?
John is working
a few leads.
We should know more
in a few hours.
Don't worry. They're not
gonna let anything happen to Laurel.
Oh, right.
The accountant's here.
Send him in.
All right.
I'll take that as my cue.
I got to head
over to planning.
Ok. Ahem. Welcome.
What are you doing here?
Well, he's carrying
evidence.
I'm just, uh,
making sure
it doesn't get up
and walk away.
Good luck with that.
I wasn't planning on seeing you
today, Lieutenant.
Well, I wasn't
planning on it either,
but we've got a problem.
Cayden James'
Corto Maltese bank account
has been withdrawn.
What do you mean,
it's been withdrawn?
It's empty. All 70 million.
Somebody took
all the funds out
before we got access.
Do we have
any idea who?
No. But I do have 3 guesses.
I put in a request
for the withdrawal log,
but it's a long shot.
If we don't have
those funds in 48 hours,
this city's
government services
will shut down.
And I understand, but banks
in third world countries,
like Corto Maltese,
aren't exactly known
for their transparency.
I'm very sorry, Mr. Mayor.
Something smells good.
Well, that smell is
physics, mathematics,
and chemistry hard at work.
Felicity's teaching me
about thermodynamics?
That's right.
And we just
really wanted cookies.
Narc!
Don't you normally
have tutoring after school, bud?
We all got sent home.
Ms. Cho said it had to do
with the budget.
Is it true they might have
to close the schools?
I'm working very hard
to make sure that doesn't happen.
There's actually
something that I needed
to speak with Felicity
about.
I'll keep working on
the cookies.
Thank you.
Yeah. You definitely have
that "day from hell" look.
What's going on?
Ahem. The money that Cayden
extorted from the city,
someone emptied the account.
Yeah, that somebody's either
Anatoly, Diaz, or Laurel.
Or another player that we
haven't seen yet.
We requested the withdrawal
logs from the bank, but--
it's Corto Maltese.
It's taking too long.
You want me to help
expedite it.
I need it to look like
it's coming through official channels.
Yeah, I know. It's not my first rodeo
with Corto Maltese.
Give me about an hour.
Hey, you don't think
it's a coincidence?
Someone killing Cayden
right as the money
goes missing.
It could be the same
person that framed you
for Cayden's son's
murder.
Could be. The only thing that
I know for sure right now
is that if I don't get
that money in 48 hours,
this city is going
to have my head.
Any luck finding Anatoly?
Just Bratva dudes who
don't know anything.
What about you guys?
Diaz's trail has gone colder
than my love life.
Same with Laurel.
Well, if it's
any consolation,
the other guys are
striking out, too.
I ran into dig chasing
the same dead end.
I guess they're not
sharing their Intel with us,
not that we were
sharing any with them.
Well, we can't trust them
to keep us looped in.
And that's why I got put
on the Cayden James
bank situation.
Any clue we get can
lead us to the scum
who worked with him.
Scum, singular,
or scum, plural?
And, yes, that is me
bringing up
exactly what's going on
between you and Laurel.
Well, we're not braiding
each other's hair, Curtis.
I mean, but you are
out for revenge,
and I don't--
I don't feel
too good about that.
Got to go.
Looks like we got a lead
on the missing money.
You ok with this?
D. Hunting Laurel?
Let's just worry about
the money first.
Then we'll deal with Dinah.
You're not
gonna believe it.
The bank just sent over the
withdrawal log we requested,
plus security footage.
That is
unbelievable.
What are we seeing?
The account was accessed
by this woman.
She's listed in
the withdrawal log
as Siu Jerk Jai.
Took out the entire amount
in bearer bonds.
Some excellent
work, Jay.
Ok. We'll take it
from here. Thank you.
Thanks.
I'm guessing Felicity had
something to do with this.
Yes, she did.
Thank you for inserting
yourself into this, by the way.
Oh, yeah, sure. Well, you never
would've shared the information otherwise.
No, I wouldn't have
because I
don't trust you to
do the right thing.
And what is that?
Politely ask Laurel
to give back the money?
Not kill her.
Dinah, I understand
that you're hurting.
I get it.
I also understand that I don't have
the most credibility
when it comes to telling people not
to commit murder.
But the city is on the verge of
economic collapse,
and we just found
the key to fixing that.
Laurel is never giving
you that money.
You don't know that.
Yeah, I actually do,
because I know that when
you look at her,
you see the Laurel
that you lost.
And that's why
you'll never be able to do
what's necessary to get
that money back.
And you will?
Understand something--
I will never let you
cross that line.
If you're gonna
threaten me, Oliver,
you better be damn sure
you can deliver.
Easy, easy,
easy, easy.
You'll pop
your stitches.
How are you feeling?
Like I've been shot
in the gut.
Where am I?
You're someplace
nobody can find you.
♪ Arrow 6x14 ♪
Collision Course
Original Air Date on March 1, 2018
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Oh, I guess we know
now what happened
to $70 million.
Right. If we find her,
then we find it.
Quentin, I know that we
have been over this,
but just for accuracy,
you were the last person
that saw her.
Yeah, well, I d--
you know, I didn't see her, exactly.
- Right.
- I mean, l-l-like I told you,
Dinah got off a shot
before--
just as Laurel knocked
us both out with-- with her cry.
And, uh, yeah, when I--
when I came to, Laurel was gone.
So are we even sure
that Dinah hit her?
No. She didn't leave a definitive
blood trail at the scene.
We can go back over it with chemical analysis,
see if we missed anything.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We can do that.
Um, listen,
oh, actually, there--
there is something
I should--I should tell you.
Um, while Cayden James
was holding the city hostage,
Laurel started
following me, all right?
It was right after
James kidnapped me.
And, so, um, well, you know,
I caught up with her.
I, uh, tried to make
a connection.
Well, I mean,
after what we just saw her do
to Dinah's
boyfriend,
are we even sure
that that worked?
Actually,
it might've.
When we went through
her go-bag at the scene,
there was a photo in there
of you and, um, our Laurel.
I gave her
that picture. Heh.
Anyways, uh, my--
my point being, if she
hasn't skipped town yet,
maybe she'll come try
to find me,
make a connection.
You know, say good-bye
or something.
I mean, it's
a long shot, but--
I agree, but I also don't
think that we can afford to be picky. So...
I'll--I'll get home.
I'll make it easy for her
to, you know, get me alone.
If she shows up, just make sure
that you stall long enough
for John and I to get there.
Yeah. Sure. Fine.
But do you need me to,
you know,
go with you for backup?
Uh, no, no. You know,
like you said,
it's a long shot,
right? Heh!
So your time's probably
better spent here
at the office.
But--but thank you.
Ok. Well, call if you
need anything.
We've already been over
this spot a thousand times.
Yeah, which is exactly why
I brought my new toy.
Presenting Mr. Terrific's
supersonic spectrograph.
It uses Earth-2
Sonic frequencies emitted
from Black Siren
and combines them
with light imaging
to create a holographic
replication of her position
during that night's events.
- Is that...
- Laurel.
Is she crawling?
No. She was dragged.
Looks like she
wasn't putting up much of a fight.
Your bullet must've
tagged her, D.
Good.
Now we just
have to find her
before the others
do something stupid.
Stupid how?
Oliver is not
seeing clearly on this.
He's desperate to get
that money.
He will believe anything
Laurel says.
Shouldn't we also be
desperate for that money?
The city's hurting.
I know, but there
are more effective ways
to find out where she's
keeping that money.
Sounds like
you're talking about torture.
And it sounds like you
want to go soft on her.
Curtis, the only way
to get justice for Vince
and money for the city
is going to be messy.
Hey, guys,
look at this.
Tire tracks.
If they're from whoever
dragged her off,
could be something.
Let's make sure
they didn't leave
anything else behind.
I, uh, picked this up
at a noodle shop
my girls used to love.
I've never been
to any noodle shop.
Well, hot and sour's
the best thing for healing
no matter what earth
you're from. Ha ha!
And I think I might
have a picture here of the 3 of us.
Would you stop?
I've already told you, there is nothing
inside of me to change
or going to change.
Um, you know, you, uh,
you let me go
instead of killing me
like James wanted.
You hesitated killing
Vincent Sobel.
Before doing exactly that.
Yeah.
You've done some pretty
unspeakable things.
Have you ever stopped to
ask yourself why?
Huh?
Basically you grew up
without a father.
My guess, you've spent
your whole life looking for one.
Zoom, Adrian Chase,
Cayden James.
All those men are
gone now,
including Cayden James--
he was killed last night.
Well, it looks like
I have an opening
for a new domineering
father figure.
Feel free to send in
your application.
You don't need
anybody else
telling you what to
do with your life.
Interesting, coming from
someone who has me locked up
in a cabin in the middle
of nowhere.
You're welcome
to leave anytime.
But my--well,
my guess is that
it's been
a long time
since you had
a chance to decide
what you want your
life to be.
So I figured
I'd give you
a little
time and space
to do just that.
Now, I got my hopes,
for sure,
but you're the one
that has to want
to change.
It's weird.
I actually really like
hot and sour soup.
Maybe we have more things
in common than I thought.
You should tell me more
about your Laurel.
Well, the luminol's
certainly doing its work
on this blood trail.
Yeah.
So much blood,
we shouldn't need
the luminol to see it.
Someone cleaned
this place up.
Yeah, because Laurel lost
too much blood
to do it
herself.
What, so someone helped
her get away?
Nope. Someone took her.
I don't want to
believe it, but I can.
We need to find her before they do
something irreversible.
If they haven't already.
How has this print
gotten us nowhere?
We're not nowhere.
We've already ruled out
all the known vehicles
in the SCPD
criminal database.
Which just leaves us
with millions of
other unknown vehicles.
Otherwise known
as nowhere.
Rene is right.
This lead is exhausted.
What the hell?
Where is she?
We know you have
Black Siren.
If she dies, you've
destroyed the city.
Wait. Whoa, whoa, whoa.
We do not have Black Siren.
We'll figure that
out for ourselves.
Since when is
our word not enough?
Since you tried
to kill her.
If she dies, that money
is lost forever.
Lost forever,
like Vincent Sobel.
Where was the Green Arrow when
he needed saving?
Your team walked
into a trap.
If you came with us, Vincent
might still be alive.
Don't you dare
say his name.
Thermal imaging is only
showing our 6 heat signatures inside.
I mean, if Laurel's
here, she's...
Not warm.
Are you hacking us?
Don't hack us, Felicity?
I'm not hacking you.
I wouldn't hack--
yeah, I'm--technically,
I'm hacking you.
It wouldn't be
your first time.
No, it wouldn't.
She's tracked
all of you before
because we needed to know
if one of you
broke our trust.
One of you did.
You have already punished
Rene for that mistake.
You know, it's just too bad
he doesn't look like
Laurel Lance, Oliver,
because if he did, you would
probably forgive him
for murder.
Guys, we're not
actually about to fight
about this, are we,
like physically fight?
Keep your team in line,
Curtis, and we won't have to find out.
Hold on.
You guys barged into
another team's bunker.
Curtis, just listen
for once.
Hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey, guys, no. I--
I do think Oliver
wants to fight,
because that's how
you always solve your problems.
That doesn't make
you a hero.
It makes you a thug.
And it's a real shame
because he's
gonna feel so betrayed
when he figures it out.
You know who I'm talking
about, don't you, Hoss?
William.
Don't turn your back
on me.
- Hey!
- Don't move.
- So you're gonna shoot us, dig?
- Do it.
So this was your
plan all along, huh?
To get the chance
to look through our bunker.
And you wonder why
we can't trust you.
We don't have
to wonder anymore.
Laurel's not here. Let's go.
Just so you know,
we are gonna find her.
And when we do,
you'd better hope to God
you're not there, too.
You think you know somebody.
Then they do a triple worm/
blue cobalt IP hack
that you taught them right
into your soul.
Ohh. God. I can't
believe we
even ever worked
with them.
You say "with," but what
you really mean is "for."
They never treated us
like we were equals.
Perimeter alarms reset.
Uh, also, I borrowed a piece
of your tech, Curtis.
What did you do?
You didn't really think I
wanted Oliver to hit me.
Would you care
to share with the rest of the class?
I planted one of Curtis'
audio chips on Oliver.
So if they get the drop
on Laurel, so will we.
Ain't Karma a bitch?
I hate to state
the, oh,
so depressingly obvious,
but since Dinah and company
don't have Laurel,
we have nothing,
Nada, zilch, bupkis.
Not true. We have 3 former teammates
who hate us more now
than they did
before.
Can't worry about them.
Guys, we're out
of time here.
Should I reach out
to Lyla?
I appreciate that, John,
but the last thing
that we need right now is
yet another group
putting Black Siren in
their crosshairs.
Oh,
square, meet one.
She didn't vanish off
the face of the earth.
Are you sure? I mean,
because, technically,
she is
from another earth.
We're gonna find her
because we have to.
Quentin.
Thea, wh--wh--what
are you doing here?
You following me?
Yeah, well, I...
I knew
you were lying
about something.
I--I did not
think it was this.
Ok, she's sleeping.
Please.
Ok, well, why didn't
you tell me?
I thought we were
in on this together.
I didn't want to put you
in a position where you,
you know, you had to lie
to Oliver, ok?
But, listen, this is
the right thing, ok?
I think I am getting
through to her,
but you got to go before
she wakes up. Please.
Ok, fine, but did you
at least find where the money is?
Well, I'm building
up to that.
Look, I know how
important she and--
and this whole thing
is to you.
I get it.
But the city is dying
without that money.
We need to find it.
Right. Right, right.
And, you know, I'll ask her.
But she j--she just--
she can't feel like she's
being forced into something.
Ok, well, you're
running out of time.
I got to call Ollie
and get him in on this.
Ok, I'm sorry, but your
brother's not exactly known
for his light touch,
all right?
And you and I, we both know
that I am the only person
with any chance of
getting through to her.
Oh, that's so sweet
of you to think, Daddy,
but Thea's right.
You should probably
call your BFF.
Thea, I'll be back
to city hall
as soon as I can be.
Ollie, I am not
in the office.
Where are you?
With Quentin and Laurel.
What?
Are you ok?
Did she hurt you?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Don't worry.
She's too torn up
to scream.
Quentin has been taking
care of her in a cabin.
It's really cool.
He's been hiding her out here.
Excuse me. It's a little more
complicated than that, ok?
No, Quentin,
it's really not.
Ok,
let's cut the crap.
I hear your city's
on a clock.
Where's the money?
Don't worry.
I'll tell you everything
after you
help me get the hell
out of this country.
No deal.
Well, the offer's not
getting any better, Ollie.
And the only reason I'm even considering
handing over my nest egg
is because I need help
getting away
from that nasty little
songbird friend of yours.
Fine.
Speedy, text me
the address.
That was easier
than expected.
Oliver's willing
to burn Vince,
but he'll let that
murdering bitch go.
You were right, D.
Oliver just took Laurel at her word.
The city's not getting
its money back that way.
It's up to us.
Can you track
the bug?
You know I can.
Then let's suit up.
6 miles out. Head west.
Felicity, you might want to make sure
your seat belt is on.
Yeah, it's good. Why?
We got a tail.
We're marked.
- Ohh. Think it's the others?
- It has to be.
How did they find us?
- Oh, my--
- what?
This.
Rene wanted me to hit him.
It doesn't matter now.
They're in our dust.
But can you
keep them there?
You forgot what you
hired me for 6 years ago.
Whew! That was
exhilarating.
That was Alanis
Morissette-level ironic,
but it's ok.
Hello, Ollie.
Where's the money?
Haven't we gone through
this already?
No money until I am
safely out of this country.
You are in no position
to make demands.
I can think of 70 million
different reasons
why you're wrong about that.
Ok.
No, no. Oliver, Oliver,
please, please.
Listen, Dinah's just got
her scared, all right?
And for good--good reason.
Laurel needs our protection.
Which is why you
should let me go with you.
I'll make sure you get out
of the country safely,
and then we can start
your new life together.
Quentin,
that's insane.
Well, well, well. That
was quite the performance,
but now that I know that it was
only about the money, hard pass.
Actually, Thea
had it right earlier.
I was more focused on
getting through to you
than the money,
but I believe that if you'd
had someone in your world
to support you when
things got bad,
you wouldn't be
a criminal.
This is our chance to
find out if I'm right.
If, after a while,
you decide
that you don't want
me there, I'll leave.
I promise.
This time around,
everything's down to you.
Pack your sun block.
I've always wanted to
live somewhere tropical.
Quentin...
The minute that she is
out of the country,
you get added to the list
of people she's killed.
I'm betting
otherwise.
And you trust her enough
to risk yourself,
to risk the city?
Tell me now.
I do.
Then so do I.
That's it.
I am not sitting here on
the side of the road,
like trash, while they let
that murderer go free!
Guys, we're gonna
find them.
How? They tossed away our
bug like it was a--a bug.
I think I know a way.
But it's gonna
hurt John.
You say that like it's
a deal breaker.
That guy's the whole reason
I got shot, Hoss.
Curtis, this is not the time to be worrying
about John's feelings.
No, I mean really
hurt John physically.
Find them
whatever it takes.
Ok, well,
the union reps' deadline
is coming up soon.
3 1/2 hours to be
depressingly exact.
Don't worry. We'll be gone,
and the money will be back
in city coffers by then.
It had better be.
Your new cover
identities are almost done.
You have a one-way ticket
on a private plane
to your father-daughter
trip of a lifetime.
Just keep that vengeful bird
of yours from finding me.
Aah! Ugh!
John? It's his arm.
The implant,
it's been disabled.
Someone's hacking it
remotely to broadcast our location.
It's not "someone."
It's Curtis.
They know where we are.
Can you fix John?
I'm rebooting the chip now.
It's gonna be a while before
you have full functionality.
You're gonna be dealing
with your post-injury symptoms for a bit.
I'm aware.
How long do we have?
Based on the amount of
time that's passed since we last lost them
and now that they've
attacked John, not long.
I'm sorry, but with
the other team that angry,
that close, I can't protect
Laurel by myself.
You don't have to.
What, are you gonna fight
your old team?
This is insane.
Let's get ready
to move.
You're gonna turn right
in a mile, dirt road.
You got us back
on track, Mr. T.
I pity those fools now.
Do they know that we
know where they are?
Trust me. They know.
Here's the turn.
Listen,
Laurel is a meta.
Now, I know the people protecting
her were our friends.
But if you hold back,
if any of us hold back
our punches here,
we are the ones who
are gonna get hurt.
And Laurel and the city's money
will both be gone.
Understood?
Sonic dampener arrow.
I never thought Dinah
would be the one we'd use that against.
Having second thoughts?
Best-case
scenario, man--
Laurel avoids punishment
for what she's done
and we put a hurting
on the people
who used to be
our friends.
But we keep the city
from dying.
But at what cost?
If the people going
after her
didn't look like Curtis,
Dinah, and Rene,
would you even be asking
this question?
No. No.
But I can't help
but wonder,
would we be doing
this if the person they were after
didn't look like
Laurel?
Now, listen, man, I
would back any call you make, Oliver.
Always have,
always will.
We should acknowledge
the fact
that going after our former teammates
is maybe a line
we can never uncross.
I agree.
But they crossed it first.
Take the other car
to the main road and don't turn back.
We'll stop the other team
from following.
You'll have the city's money
in two hours, I promise.
Thank you
for fighting for me.
I'm not doing this
for you.
But when it's over,
I don't want
to hear your name
or see your face
ever again.
Why not
let me handle that?
You know, it's a shame
you can't scream.
It almost makes this
too easy.
Oh, sweetie, I don't have
to scream to kill you.
You are unbelievable.
I cannot believe
you did that.
You could've seriously
hurt John!
Just like you guys are gonna
really hurt the city
if you let her go!
Nothing's happened
that can't be undone.
We're not saying it's a perfect outcome
or even a good one,
but at least the city
gets its money.
That's not
justice, Hoss.
That's enough. We've
debated this already.
We know where you stand.
It's time to finish this.
Right now!
Dinah, not one more step.
Get to the car!
Rene.
You're wasting
arrows.
Am I?
Rene! Rene, stop!
Are you crazy?
Yeah, I must be! Yeah.
Run!
All right.
Go, go, go, go, go.
Hyah!
Go help Curtis.
It's all right.
We're getting there, Laurel.
Laurel, Laurel,
come on.
We got to go.
- We got to move.
- Quentin. Quentin.
You stay behind me.
Dinah, you can't do this.
Get out of my way.
You can't do this.
Please don't.
Uh! Aah. Dinah, don't--
Last chance, Rene.
Stay down!
No way.
- Hyah! Hyah! Hyah...
- Hey, is everyone ok?
- We'll live.
- Can you manage?
- Yeah.
We can cut them off.
Let's go.
- Hyah!
- Unh!
Is this what it
felt like
right before you
killed Vince?
I'm s--I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
We are way,
way past sorry.
Dinah?
If we lose her,
we lose the money.
But even if we had
the money...
You can't do this.
Oh, God. I have to,
Curtis.
You know I have to.
I have to get
justice for Vince.
Dinah, look around.
Look at what we're
doing to each other.
Does this look like justice?
It's nobody's fault
but theirs.
Then you sound
just like Oliver.
We formed this team so we
wouldn't be like that,
like him.
Dinah, I don't want
to start today.
I will not be put
back in that cage!
- Sorry.
- We can still catch her.
No. You can't.
No more advantages.
I don't need them.
He's still hurting.
Don't get soft now,
Curtis.
We're just get--
getting started.
Rene!
Quentin!
You ok?
What the hell's happening?
We need to get
to a hospital.
Now!
Any sign of Laurel?
That trail
has gone cold.
I don't think
that she'll be
able to get very far
with her injuries.
What about yours?
Nothing Felicity
can't fix.
Well, I still can't
believe Curtis did this.
I mean, messing with the chip in your arm
is totally crossing the line.
It's our company's
prototype.
Obviously, injuring
you is way more
a crossing of the line.
Way more.
It's not like we
didn't hurt them back.
Has anyone heard
about Rene?
I mean, he--he
didn't look so good.
He was shot 5 months ago.
The wound reopened.
Well, we should
go to the hospital.
We got to make sure
he's ok.
Well, unless anyone here
has $70 million,
there won't be
a hospital soon.
Listen, Laurel is
gonna call, all right?
She's gonna call.
No, she's not.
I know how much we
all wish she
was more like the
Laurel that we lost.
She's not.
We should get ready
to talk to the press.
Quentin's right.
We should go
and check on Rene.
Please tell him that
I'm sorry.
I screwed up, Thea.
No, Quentin. You...
You just believed
in your daughter, ok?
That's not screwing up.
And she is your daughter
in the only way that
really matters.
Yeah. What way's that?
In the eyes of her father.
Any update?
Yeah. My bloodstream
is about to reach
90% coffee
saturation.
Ohh. Ok.
You know, I said
that joke,
hoping that you
would laugh,
but maybe now is not the best time
to be saying jokes,
so I'll just...
Yeah.
No updates on Rene.
They've been working
on him for hours, huh?
Yeah.
But, you know,
Rene's the definition
of stubbornness.
No way is he gonna let
Oliver be the reason
he goes down.
Yeah.
Dinah, this whole
Laurel thing,
it's not over.
The second Rene is
in the clear,
we're gonna track
her down
and we are going to
arrest her.
We will get justice
for Vince.
Thank you for saying that.
If it wasn't for you,
I would've repaid Vincent's death
with more violence.
That isn't justice.
I'm--I'm grateful to you,
you know, just
for pulling me back. So...
The speech worked because
I have faith in you, Dinah.
I also had my T-spheres
programmed as a plan B.
City reps
are all waiting,
and they don't know
about the money or lack thereof.
You don't need to be here,
you know?
If you're facing the firing squad,
I'm standing by your side.
I don't know
what to tell them.
It's not your
fault, Ollie.
I'm the mayor, Speedy.
I made a vow to protect
Star City,
and I'm sorry,
but I didn't.
I couldn't.
And I swear that I will
make it up to them, but I--
just that, ok, Ollie?
You just tell them that.
Please, please.
I need to--ahem--I need
to inform everyone
that the money extorted
from us
by the cyber terrorist
Cayden James has not been recovered.
And to be honest with you,
I don't know that
it ever will be.
Now, I promised everyone
that I would find the funds
to keep the Metro area
running
without work stoppages,
but...
I'm so very sorry.
As mayor, I...
I have failed this city.
Now, I know that your faith
in me is likely shaken,
but my faith--my faith in
the citizens of Star City...
The mayor's luck
just keeps getting worse.
D.A. Armand.
You got a sec?
My case against Queen
is built on sand.
It's only a matter of time before
Jean Loring figures that out.
And why are you
telling me that?
I found something
that could bury Queen,
but I'll need
the full backstop--
all the SCPD's
resources.
I can see why Mr. Diaz
likes you.
The news isn't good.
Mr. Ramirez suffered
a traumatic hemothorax.
We were able to stop
the bleeding in his chest,
but the injury
also caused his lung to re-collapse.
Now, given the severity of
your friend's injuries,
I'm recommending he
be transferred to a facility
that can provide
the care he needs
outside of Star City.
Mr. Ramirez
is resting now.
You and your friends
will have to wait to see him.
What friends?
We thought Rene
would be here.
Well,
of course he's here.
You saw what Oliver
did to him.
Yeah. Yeah.
How's Rene doing?
You've lost the right
to ask that question.
You two need
to leave.
No. No, not until you
tell us if Rene's ok.
- This is not--
- Stop it.
Don't you guys get it?
We're not
just done fighting you.
We're done with
the 3 of you period.
No more cooperation, no
more communication forever.
Let's go.
Fine.
I don't know what
day it is.
I don't know
what day it is.
Are you ok?
I escaped. I--I was
kidnapped from here
two years ago, I think.
I--I don't know.
I...Ugh.
Lady, what's your name?
Laurel...
Laurel Lance.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man