I think you're letting personal feelings
towards the Arrow cloud your judgment.
Maybe I'm seeing things more clearly
than I have for the last few years.
Enough, both of you. I am tired of... Unh!
This is Captain Lance.
City Hall. Shots fired.
Suspect on the move.
I need ESU and an ambulance now.
-Are you okay?
-I'm fine.
[RAY COUGHING AND GASPING]
SNOW [ON TV]:
We have confirmation that Mayor Castle...
...was pronounced dead at the scene.
Palmer Technology CEO Ray Palmer
was taken to Starling General Hospital...
...where he is listed in critical condition.
I tried to call Felicity.
She's not answering.
SNOW: S.C.P.D. Captain Quentin Lance
was present for the attack...
...and had this to say on the incident:
I just requested a first-degree
murder warrant for the Arrow...
...and re-instated
the anti-vigilante task force...
...with shoot-to-kill orders if necessary.
REPORTER: Why would the Arrow suddenly
decide to assassinate the mayor?
I don't know.
But I should've trusted my first instinct...
...that this man is a killer and a criminal.
If I had, Mayor Castle might still be alive.
-No more questions.
-He could be right.
Don't think like that.
We have to deal with the problem at hand.
The murders are being orchestrated
by one of Ra's' lieutenants.
Maseo Yamashiro.
-You sound like you know him.
-I thought I did. Lifetime ago.
The man is a stranger now.
Oliver, the question is,
where do we find this stranger?
I know someone who can help with that.
[CHATTERING AND HORNS HONKING]
Who are those men?
I don't know.
AKIO:
Then why are we running away from them?
Shado?
What? How'd you know my sister?
Your, uh... Your sister?
-My twin. How do you know Shado?
-Oliver.
It's a long story. My friend and I
are in a little bit of trouble.
Uh, we're wondering if you could help us
get off the street.
-What's going on?
OLIVER: That's also a long story.
Can you help us?
LANCE:
Okay, listen up.
Suspect is armed and dangerous.
No warning shots.
Whatever happened to innocent
until proven guilty?
He was on that rooftop.
I saw him with my own eyes.
-He's being framed.
-By a copycat.
Wouldn't be happening
if he wasn't dressed up like Robin Hood.
That's not fair.
You don't understand what's happening.
I need you to trust me.
I used to.
-Who is he? Just tell me his name or I'll...
-What, Dad?
You'll charge me as an accessory?
I'll do what needs to be done.
This has to end.
And it has to end tonight.
[THEA CHUCKLES]
I am the biggest idiot in the world
for breaking up with you.
[ROY CHUCKLES]
Remember the last time we did this?
We were gonna run away together.
Why don't we?
Roy.
Things are complicated
with Oliver right now.
Ra's al Ghul complicated?
[SIGHS]
Oh, my God.
In the wake of the attacks, Captain Lance
has issued an arrest warrant...
...for the vigilante known as the Arrow...
...as the largest manhunt
in the city's history is underway.
Captain Lance confirmed that
arrest warrants have also been issued...
...for each of the Arrow's accomplices.
[RAY MOANS]
Ray?
Hey.
Hi. How are you?
Well, you're here, so I'm great.
Mr. Palmer, how are you feeling?
You have a not-so-good look on your face.
You see his face?
LOCKHART:
I've got some bad news.
During the surgery to remove the arrow,
you developed a thrombus.
-A blood clot?
-If left untreated...
...it could cause an ischemic stroke.
-Then maybe we should treat it.
-It's not that simple.
Your injuries have left you very weak.
A craniotomy could end up
doing more harm than good.
-And by harm you mean...?
-Brain damage at best.
At worst...
So you're saying basically
that if we have the surgery now, I could die.
And if we wait and the clot moves,
I could die.
What if I told you that I invented
a bunch of teeny-tiny robots...
...that were capable of entering
my bloodstream, traveling to the clot...
...and shrinking it?
All without damaging my brain
or any other organ in my body.
-I'd say you need a psych eval.
-Heh.
Okay.
But after, we go to my lab,
get the nanotech...
...inject it, and publish the results
in the New England Journal of Medicine.
Well, I'm sorry,
but that's simply not possible.
Uh, I invented the tech. It's possible.
Starling General has a very strict policy
against experimental procedures.
Wait, there is a procedure
that could save his life...
-...and you're saying you won't perform it?
-I'm saying I can't perform it.
The hospital won't permit the use
of an experimental or untested technology.
How do you know your invention
won't kill you?
-I don't. It's a risk.
LOCKHART: I'm very sorry.
But there's really nothing I can do.
We'll figure something out.
[SNIFFLES]
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Ray Palmer.
Even in a hospital bed, you're the most
handsome man I've ever seen.
Can you give us a minute?
Hi.
I heard what happened,
so I caught the first flight out of Vegas.
So tell me, what are the doctors saying?
Absolutely nothing good.
Okay, okay. Hey.
At least you finally have a boyfriend.
Mom.
How did you know I was still in Starling?
-Laurel.
-I need your help, Nyssa.
Maseo is also in Starling.
He's behind the murders
the Arrow's suspected of.
Sarab does my father's bidding
in an effort to force you to do the same...
-...and take your place as his heir.
-And do you feel betrayed by that?
Not so much
that I'd betray him by helping you.
People are dying, Nyssa.
What makes you think
that's any concern of mine?
Sara.
What would she want you to do?
I have Maseo's location.
A building called Magnuson Plaza.
Yeah, the company that owns that building
went belly-up a few months back.
NYSSA: The League has been
using it as a safe house...
...and staging ground for its attacks.
How'd you find this out?
I am Daughter of the Demon.
Your primary concern
should be the League.
You can place Maseo in the same cage
you put me in but my father has an army.
-One step at a time.
-Oliver.
We have to spread out
if we're gonna cover that.
-Dig, I want you on overwatch.
-Copy that.
What about her?
Don't confuse information...
...with the willingness
to take up arms against the League.
We appreciate what you've done.
We'll take it from here.
Let's do this.
We scoped out every floor. Nothing.
Same with the parking garage.
-Diggle.
-North side is clear.
You think Nyssa played us?
Hang on, I got movement.
Upper level, southwest corner.
[IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
[CLAPPING]
Clearly, I chose well
selecting you as my heir.
Killing me will only win you
the mantle you reject.
It will stop you.
I have legions who live
only to see my will done.
No, boy, you have but two choices.
You either ascend
to the calling of Ra's al Ghul...
...or you will spend the rest of your days
in a cage.
You're not gone take me prisoner.
No, I'm not.
OFFICER [OVER SPEAKER]:
This is the Starling City police.
Put your weapons down and your hands up.
You're all under arrest.
[SIRENS CHIRPING]
On the ground. Get on the ground!
Hold your fire. Hold your fire.
Lock down this entire area.
Three-block radius.
GREEN ARROW: Diggle?
-I got eyes on them. Blues everywhere.
LANCE [OVER RADIO]: Suspects
headed east on 8th. Keep them pinned.
DIGGLE: Warehouse door. West side.
Get there, you're in the clear.
Go, move.
Four more headed your way.
You gotta move, move, move.
[SIREN WAILS]
OFFICER [OVER SPEAKER]:
Put your hands in the air.
Go for the door. I'll draw their fire.
-We're not separating.
-They don't want you. They want me.
Now, go.
Cooper, Jones, box them in on 43rd.
Two masks in a warehouse,
west side of 43rd.
OFFICER:
Proceeding to warehouse.
He's headed toward the east exit.
This way. Take him.
[GRUNTS]
Laurel.
What are you gonna do?
Are you gonna shoot your own daughter?
No, but I'm thinking about arresting you.
A night in jail would bring you
to your senses.
Daddy, please. Please don't do this.
[LANCE GRUNTING]
-Leave her alone.
-Nyssa.
-Don't hurt him.
-Laurel, what are you doing?
We must go.
I'm sorry.
Did Arsenal and Canary get away?
Diggle.
Get back!
Get in.
OFFICER [OVER RADIO]:
I see a black, late model vehicle in the area.
Get to the tunnel off 8th, we're good.
If we clear those squad cars.
On it.
[TIRES SCREECHING
AND SIRENS WAILING]
[SIGHS]
Hey.
Thank God. I got so worried.
OLIVER:
It's okay. I'm okay.
Where's Roy?
He's still out there.
-It's like the whole city has lost their minds.
-It's not the whole city.
It's just one man.
-Yup.
-Hello, captain.
I got three men in the hospital
because of you.
I understand that you feel betrayed.
But you can't be so angry as to think...
...that I'm just running around
taking aim at innocent people.
I don't think anything.
I know this madness has to end.
You don't want any more people
getting hurt, you turn yourself in.
[SCOFFS]
Yeah, that's what I thought.
I'm sorry. He's in a lot of pain.
I thought that if we stopped Maseo,
we'd stop the killings.
But Nyssa was right.
This extends way beyond him.
THEA: Roy.
-I'm okay.
I got clear somewhere around Hudson.
I had to shoot a few officers.
But they're just flesh wounds.
I've underestimated Ra's.
And now we're all paying the price.
-I'm sorry.
-What are you talking about?
Ra's is after us because of Malcolm.
What don't I know?
You haven't told me your names. I'm Mei.
-I'm Akio. And this is...
-Tommy.
So, Tommy, who are you
and your little friend running from?
It's complicated.
But, Mei, the truth is that I don't know why
this person has sent men after us...
...but she did.
Is that your father?
His name is Yao Fei.
And how do you know my sister?
Oh, uh, medical school.
She never mentioned any American friends.
You are American, aren't you?
I dropped out. Of, uh, medical school,
not of America.
So when was the last time
you saw my sister?
It's been a while.
For me too.
Shado and my father disappeared
three years ago now.
Police think they were kidnapped,
but no ransom came.
I'm so sorry.
The police tell me they must be dead.
If they were, at least I'd have some closure.
But each time the phone rings,
someone knocks at the door...
...or when I meet someone
who knew them...
I can't imagine.
You must be tired.
Dirty. I need a shower.
My bedroom's through that door.
There are fresh towels.
OLIVER: Are you sure?
-Yeah.
I'll entertain your friend.
Thank you.
Listen, I'm a cop, not a psychologist.
But in my experience, killers don't
discriminate between guilty and innocent.
They kill because they view themselves
as being above the law.
And the Arrow is no different.
He is a criminal, and I promise you,
we will find him and hold him accountable.
-It's real easy to look the other way when...
-Oh.
DONNA: You okay?
-Mm-hm.
Thanks for getting this.
[DONNA SIGHS]
I ran into Dr. Lockhart in the cafeteria.
I thought maybe...
...I don't know, I could talk him
into giving Ray those nano-thingies.
-Nanotech.
-He wouldn't even look at me.
Have you seen this dress? Hello.
Man's an idiot.
I guess...
...you're just gonna have to inject
those tiny robot things into Ray yourself.
Great plan, except I'm not a doctor.
Even Ray said that they could kill him.
I'm not gonna be the one to risk his life.
His life is already at risk.
You're saying you don't wanna
be the one to take the chance.
-If your father were here...
-He would be arrested.
Probably.
But right before that,
he would tell you that sometimes...
...we gotta take a chance.
Particularly for the people we care about.
I don't give a damn about budgets.
This is a manhunt.
Now, approve the extra personnel
and the overtime, and you do it now.
[SIGHS]
[GRUNTING]
I apologize for the coarse treatment.
I didn't think I'd get you
to speak with me of your own accord.
[CHUCKLES]
-You're him.
-Ra's al Ghul.
It's an honor to meet you.
Sara spoke with such love about her father.
That's my daughter's name.
If she'd never met you,
she'd still be alive now.
If Sara had not met my daughter...
...she would've starved to death
on the shores of Lian Yu.
She was never on Lian Yu.
You suffer false perception.
One of many, I'm afraid.
[LANCE SIGHS]
Listen, what do you want?
To help the city as your daughter did.
-You hunt for the man they call the Arrow.
-Yeah.
Are you gonna help me find him?
You'll be able to find him easily...
...once I tell you his name.
And why would I believe
just any name that you throw at me?
Well, because with this revelation...
...everything will become clear.
And you will realize...
...that the man you've been looking for has
been right in front of you the entire time.
The same man who lied...
...telling you he wasn't with Sara
on Lian Yu.
Oliver Queen is the Arrow.
We need to talk.
Aren't you tired of these chats?
I know I am.
Then let's cut the crap. You don't think
the Arrow's behind the murders...
...you're just pissed off because he kept
Sara's death a secret from you.
That is not why. That is not why!
I mean, maybe at first. Yeah.
But then I realized,
he is the reason Sara got killed.
-Dad, that is ridiculous.
-No. You, Harper, Sara...
...the freak in Central City, Huntress.
I got a new guy flying around.
All these masks, they started with him.
And Sara died only because
she was part of it too.
You have no idea why Sara was killed.
She ended up in the League of Assassins...
...because she was marooned
on Lian Yu...
...because she got on that boat
with Queen.
So what?
Now Oliver's to blame?
Oliver, the Arrow. Either way, same guy.
On some level, I think I always knew.
When I thought he was doing good,
it didn't matter to me.
[CHUCKLES]
You know, when that boat went down
and we thought Sara was dead?
I blamed Queen.
It's funny how things
come full circle, right?
Well, I got things to do.
You calling him?
It's too late. I got officers headed
to his home, his sister's club, everywhere.
Uh, for what it's worth, I'm thinking
of starting a reality TV show, so...
...maybe I already have brain damage.
Don't joke, Mr. Palmer.
The next few hours are critical.
I'm going to want to keep you
under close observation.
-Ow!
-Mom?
No, no, no. It's nothing... Ow!
I think my back is spasming.
Oh, it hurts... Oh.
Oh, gosh, you're so strong.
Ow. Oh, my God. I think I...
I think I'm gonna faint.
-Maybe we should get you on a gurney.
-Yeah.
[WHIMPERING]
Oh, yeah. I'll just get on a gurney. Ow.
Ow. I'm sorry.
Is your mom gonna be okay?
Oh...
I think she'll make a miraculous
recovery in about five minutes.
-Just like you.
-Is that my nanotech?
Assuming the organizational system
in your lab is accurate.
Uh...
-Are you sure you want to do this?
-Aren't you?
Yeah. I mean, my alternatives
are brain damage or death...
...but if the hospital finds out,
you could go to jail.
I'll take my chances.
Okay. All right.
-How do we feel?
-Uh, normal...
...but I wasn't expecting any side...
[MACHINES BEEPING]
Ray? Ray? Ray?
Hey! Hey.
[GASPS]
Hi.
Okay, well...
...maybe there are some side effects.
THEA: I can't believe this is happening.
-Line forms behind me.
REPORTER [ON TV]: The citywide manhunt
for the Arrow continues this evening...
...as Captain Lance has made
capturing this dangerous vigilante...
...the S.C.P.D.'s top priority.
I'm sure those cops
that chased you are fine.
I shot them with arrows, Thea.
When it was happening,
there was a part of me that...
-That felt relieved.
-Relieved?
That I'd finally be going to jail.
That I'd get what I deserved.
Roy, listen to me.
The only thing that you deserve
is to be happy, okay?
You've got to find a way to forgive yourself.
What happened with that cop last year...
...it's not your fault.
Sorry that you had to go through this.
Roy, I gave you that mask...
...so you could help the police,
not run from them.
What's going to happen?
[BANGING ON DOOR
THEN DOOR BREAKS]
-Oh.
-Run.
OFFICER 1:
S.C.P.D.!
OFFICER 2: Freeze!
OFFICER 3: Put your hands in the air!
Thank you for the shower.
-You okay?
-I saw the tattoo on your back.
Why have you been lying to me?
-Oh. Mei...
-I need to know what happened to my family.
-I don't know.
-Another lie.
You knew my sister.
You were more than just friends.
Just believe me when I say the less
you know about me, the safer you'll be.
Fine, maybe you'll be more honest
with the police.
You're upset. Please don't call the police.
I already did. They'll be here any minute.
-Akio, we have to go.
-What's wrong?
Get down!
[GUNSHOTS]
Why are the police shooting?
Because they're not the police!
I am so proud of you. I'm so proud...
Your father would be proud of you.
He's not exactly a role model, but...
Oh, Ms. Smoak.
Just the person I wanted to see.
Do you know what these are?
They're Mr. Palmer's latest MRI.
-The clot in his brain is gone.
-Really?
LOCKHART:
Not moved, not smaller, gone.
He's going to make a full recovery.
You wouldn't happen to know anything...
...about this unprecedented
medical development, would you?
Huh?
You accusing my daughter of something?
I work a table at Caesar's...
...frequented by no less than three lawyers.
LANCE [ON TV]: Thank you, please.
Thank you all for coming.
We've had a breakthrough
in our investigation...
...of the vigilante known as the Arrow.
The District Attorney's office
has just issued an arrest warrant...
...for the person responsible
for these acts of violence.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
I had nowhere else to go.
It's okay.
Lyla took Sara to her mother's.
-Lance knows.
-The whole city knows, Oliver.
Mr. Queen should be considered
armed and highly dangerous.
But make no mistake, he will be found...
...and brought to justice.
SNOW [ON TV]:
A stunning development...
...as Oliver Queen has been outed
as the Arrow.
The accusation comes
as a particular surprise...
...considering that Queen was exonerated
of being the Arrow only two years ago.
News lady's right.
You put this genie back
in the bottle before.
Last time I had it all worked out.
Getting arrested was my plan.
This time it's Ra's al Ghul's.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Come in.
-How's Ray?
-So much better than you right now.
Please tell me you have a brilliant plan.
I don't even have a regular plan.
What about Dig going out as the Arrow?
Worked last time.
But this time Lance won't rest
until Oliver's in custody.
You have to leave.
You have to get out of town.
My father's posted men at every
bus station, train station and airport.
Also, he's frozen Thea's assets.
He's not giving you anything
you can use to run.
I can't believe this is happening.
-You think Ra's planned this the entire time?
-He's using this city as a weapon.
It's my city.
Where you going, Oliver?
Only place I can go.
[GUNFIRE]
-Akio, you okay?
-I'm okay.
-What's happening?
-Front door the only way in?
-Yes.
-Get low, take Akio to the bedroom.
Mei, they're coming to kill you too.
Go, go! Come on!
[GRUNTING]
[GUNSHOT]
Akio? Akio?
[SPEAKS IN JAPANESE]
We followed them.
They work for Amanda Waller.
[FLOORBOARDS CREAKING]
Who is she?
How are you feeling?
For a guy who just avoided death
and/or brain damage? Pretty good.
Good.
But are you okay?
It's, uh...
It's a long story. I'm just glad...
-...that you're all right.
-Thanks to you.
Oh, I think your nanotech
deserves some of the credit.
All I did was stick something in you.
You think there will ever come a time...
...when everything I say
isn't some weird double entendre?
I hope not.
It's one of your more charming traits.
That and the fact
that you had the courage to save my life...
...are just two
of the many reasons that I love you.
Wow.
That's a really nice thing to hear.
Especially after everything that's going on.
With the blood clot, and the nanotech,
and the nearly dying.
Speaking of,
you must be starving after all that drama.
I'm gonna go find a hospital nurse
and get you some of that hospital Jell-O.
[GASPS]
Oh, my God. What just happened?
-Nothing.
-Felicity. Uh-uh-uh.
You look the way you did
when you were 7...
...and stole your father's electronics
to make a super computer.
Oh, my God.
Did you and Ray just do it in this hospital?
-Did you just have hospital sex?
-No... Ugh.
-I've always wanted to have hospital sex.
-Way TMI. Gross.
What?
He told me he loved me.
You didn't say it back?
Oh.
What is wrong with me?
He's brilliant.
He knows the plot to every
Doctor Who episode, all 34 seasons.
He looks like a Disney prince. I mean, he's...
...practically the perfect man.
You don't love Ray...
...because you're in love with Oliver.
[CHUCKLES]
You don't even know Oliver.
You met him for, like, 10 seconds.
I knew it in five.
Honey, you lit up like Christmas
when he walked in the room.
FELICITY:
He's...
...terminally unavailable.
And that was before.
-You haven't been watching the news.
-No, I don't. It depresses me.
But here's what doesn't.
My daughter has two men...
...who are both amazing,
which just means...
...she has to make a choice.
I want pictures of Queen
distributed to every officer, okay?
No, a current one.
One with the scruff he's wearing.
[CHATTERING]
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Captain Lance...
...I'm here to turn myself in.
Cuff him.
[CHATTERING]
I got you 10 minutes with Oliver,
but let's make it five, all right?
It would not look good if these reporters
caught wind of you meeting with him.
Him and the three of you.
Makes sense.
[DOOR OPENS]
OLIVER:
You shouldn't be here.
Oliver, neither should you.
What were you thinking?
-Were you thinking?
-I was thinking clearly.
I asked Laurel to make a deal.
I turn myself in,
and all of you receive full immunity.
You know, Oliver,
you are out of your mind...
...if you think we're just gonna
let you take the fall for all of us.
I started all of this.
It's my fall to take.
And this is the best way to save lives,
including yours.
So stop worrying.
-I've been through worse than prison.
-This is insane.
How could we live with ourselves?
Roy, I'm just gonna need you to.
The only move that Ra's has left me
is telling the truth.
You have no idea...
...how powerful the truth can be.
Oliver, this is the wrong move.
John...
...you've followed me this far.
All of you have followed me this far...
...but I need you to follow me
just a little further...
...until it's over.
The bodies are taken care of.
-We should go.
-Just give us a minute.
I'm sorry about this.
They tried to kill us.
They weren't the cops.
They must've intercepted the call.
They're after you and the boy?
-You knew my sister. Is there any chance...
-Mei, it's...
This had nothing to do with Shado.
You have no idea
what it's like to live like this...
...looking for any kind of answer.
You were right that I knew your sister.
I loved her.
I knew your father too.
And your family...
...they saved my life more than once.
I don't understand.
The people that are after me...
They'll kill anyone
who knows too much about who I am.
-But Shado and my father...
-Mei.
They're gone.
I'm so sorry.
Thank you for telling me.
For three years now,
all I've wanted is to know the truth.
You have no idea
how powerful the truth can be.
MASEO:
We shouldn't stay here.
Thank you.
This isn't fair. This isn't right.
All Oliver has ever done
was protect people, help people.
We can't stay here.
This place isn't secure anymore.
And then what?
We just bug out and allow this to happen?
-Enjoy our new immunity?
-Roy, I don't know.
I have no idea.
If I did, you'd be listening to it right now.
If any one of us were in there and Oliver
was here, he'd think of something.
And it wouldn't matter
what the consequences were.
[SIRENS WAILING]
Lian Yu.
What about it?
This, uh, Ra's character...
He told me that Sara
made it to the island with you.
You didn't feel like
sharing that with me? Huh?
I mean, I'm only her father.
I was.
When did you decide
you knew what was best for my family?
I love your family.
You got the right to remain silent. Take it.
Just ask me what you want to know.
[SCOFFS]
What do I want to know?
Well, was it worth it?
All the pain and misery
you brought back from that island.
Merlyn, Slade Wilson.
Wouldn't it be better if you died there?
The reason I came back
was to try and save the people of this city.
I hate to break it to you,
but saving people isn't your specialty.
Tommy, Hilton, your mother...
...my daughter.
And now you're set on killing Laurel too.
I didn't want her to be involved in this.
I didn't want anyone to be involved in this.
But you involved me.
You spent a year
making me look like a fool.
making me your accomplice.
You have any idea what you've done, huh?
What you've done to all of us,
to the people you claim to care about?
You've made us criminals.
You've made us liars and victims.
You, Mr. Queen, are not a hero.
You're a villain.
But you know that, don't you?
[METAL CLANKING
THEN TIRES SCREECH]
-What the hell are your people doing?
-I told them to stand down.
I guess your word carries as much weight
with them as it does with me.
Get down on the ground!
You've got the wrong guy.
Oliver Queen isn't the Arrow.
I am.
OFFICER:
Behind your head!
[OFFICERS SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]