Previously on "Arrow"...
We did it. The bombs are deactivated.
The attack by the vigilantes has
provided us an opportunity.
- What is that?
- The tool that will allow us
to eliminate all vigilantes for good.
Gustavo Hernandez was found dead.
You think I did this.
I'm not exactly hearing a denial.
I have busted my ass,
but no matter what I do, you always
just see me as the Black Siren.
District Attorney Laurel Lance.
New photos show her with Ricardo Diaz.
Could the city's highest prosecutor
actually be a wanted criminal herself?
Looks like you've got a problem.
You lost?
I'm here to see Shadow Thief.
She's busy,
but you can stay here with us.
- Hyah!
- Unh!
I'll pass.
Where the hell is Shadow Thief?
Uh! Who are you?
I'm Black Siren.
- Synced by Chamallow & ChrisKe -
-- for www.addic7ed.com --
Still kicking ass, I see.
I heard you were back in town.
And I heard you traded in
your leather for a power suit.
Well, that suit didn't really fit.
Seems the entire city
has turned against you.
Just reminded me that there's
only one person I can trust...
myself.
It's too bad about Diaz.
What, that he didn't die sooner?
I couldn't agree more,
but at least he introduced
us before he did.
As much as I'm enjoying
this little reunion,
why don't you tell me why you're here?
I'm looking for a partner.
You got a job?
Multiple...
And I need someone with your
particular set of skills.
Ugh.
Who was that?
No one.
You still good with locks?
Hey, Laurel. It's me again.
I just had a craving for French fries,
milk shakes, and really cold fruit.
Are you in?
Look. I know this is
probably gonna get buried
between the many, many,
many, many messages
I have already left you, but
I'm just trying to make sure
you are OK, so if you
could call me back, please.
Still trying to get
in touch with Laurel?
Yeah. It's taking an alarming
"swingers" amount of time.
Not proud, and my go-to way to find her
would be Archer, but that is taking
an annoyingly long time
to get back online, so...
She doesn't want to be found, Felicity.
Her whole life has been
flipped upside down.
I know what that's like. Just...
Speaking of, are you
sure that you are OK
now that you know
that your sister's evil
and tried to kill you?
Too soon?
Need to focus on finding her
and the Ninth Circle and stopping
whatever they have planned.
Well, lucky for you, your
wife is incredibly resourceful.
So I made a cheat
sheet on your new lead.
Emiko's bullet led me to
Andrew Thornton's rifle,
which led me to 12
different shell companies,
which led me to the buyer.
And it's not weird that she
hasn't found the buyer herself
with the resources of the
Ninth Circle at her disposal?
OK. Well, not to toot my own horn,
but Emiko is more of the "Karate
Kid", Hilary Swank version,
and I am more of the "Mr.
Robot" version but prettier.
Have you considered that
Emiko probably made up
the whole "finding my
mother's killer" thing?
I know that she's lied about
basically everything else,
but I... I just have a sixth sense
that she's not lying about this one,
so if John and I can
find the killer first,
then we can leverage that
against Emiko and the Ninth Circle
and stop whatever they have planned.
Well, I have a sense that a road trip
with John is exactly
what the doctor ordered.
Bring Rene with you for backup.
Rene... ahem... has a
school thing with Zoe.
Speaking of which, will you just...
will you take it easy for me, please?
Oh, who? Me? Um, you know what?
I really wish I could, but I have
a really intense Netflix binge
that I have scheduled way back,
and I also am going to eat
everything in the fridge,
so it's gonna get pretty crazy in here.
- Precious cargo.
- I know.
Disarmed.
Is he still following us?
I don't see him.
I think we finally lost the son of a...
Oh! Uh!
Spoke too soon.
Over here. Hurry.
Zoe, Mia, come in.
What's your ETA?
Trying to shake a bogey.
What's the status on Nest Two?
Gone. Galaxy One has
raided all of our safe houses.
Alpha base is our last secure location.
All surviving Canaries need
to rendezvous here immediately.
Be careful.
We need to take this guy out.
Dinah gave us an order.
I don't work for Dinah.
We're clear. Let's go.
What the hell are you doing?
Finishing this.
You'll get us both killed.
Former District Attorney Laurel Lance
is facing allegations of murder
following the death of Halcone gang
member Gustavo Hernandez last week.
The SCPD has issued a
warrant for her arrest,
sparking a city-wide manhunt.
Anyone with information
on her whereabouts...
A manhunt? Don't you think
that's a little harsh?
- Laurel killed someone.
- Allegedly.
Her DNA and fingerprints
were found all over the scene.
Laurel is smart. You really think that
she'd leave evidence behind
if she really did kill the guy?
She had a pretty strong motive.
Hernandez's death was imperative
in her winning her case.
She hasn't killed anyone
since she's been the D.A.
Why would she start now?
You've seen how hard she's worked,
how much she's changed.
Except she obviously hasn't.
Look. I know she's your friend,
and for a while, I actually thought
the two of us were doing
good work together, too,
but the truth is Laurel is Black Siren.
She is a ruthless murderer,
and we are all fooling
ourselves thinking she is anything
like the real Laurel Lance.
We should be helping
her, not hunting her.
Laurel is a criminal,
and we are going to
bring her to justice,
something we should have
done a long time ago.
Pinky Santorini.
It's quite the operation
you've got here.
What are you talking about?
I own a dry-cleaning business.
Please. I haven't had
a problem in 22 years.
Well, it looks like
you have a problem now.
Thanks for playing.
Time for our payday.
Feels good to be back.
Hey. Are you OK? Your message made it
sound like the bunker was on fire.
Laurel didn't kill Gustavo Hernandez.
- Emiko did.
- What are you talking about?
This is his toxicology report.
There were traces of hydrogen cyanide
found in his blood, which is the
go-to poison of the Ninth Circle.
The SCPD had no reason
to trace it back to them.
Emiko framed Laurel because Laurel
told Oliver her secret. Boom.
Well, it still doesn't change anything.
Of course it does. Did
you hear what I just said?
Even if Laurel didn't kill Hernandez,
she's back to being Black Siren.
There was just a robbery
at Pinky's Dry cleaner.
- What'd they steal, bubbles?
- Pinky's is run by Walter Santorini.
He's a money launderer for the mob.
- They took over 100 grand.
- Whoa.
- Yeah.
- Maybe she needs the money
because she's planning
on leaving town again.
- She also now has a partner.
- Well, there has to be an explanation.
Santorini's actually part of a case
Laurel and I had been working
for the last few months,
a case which is now nonexistent
thanks to this last little stunt.
So she's using her D.A.
resources to identify targets.
That's clever.
Bad. Very bad.
OK. This is the
database of all the cases
currently being investigated by
the district attorney's office.
Please hold. Yeah. Looks like
Laurel's been accessing it
through a series of
rerouted IP addresses.
- Does that mean we can track her?
- I mean,
it means I could probably talk to her,
and then I can convince her
not to do this whole
Black Siren backslide
- or whatever this is.
- Well, even if you could,
damage is already done.
It was a good chat. I
really love our chats.
Felicity tell you how she tracked
the rifle to this apartment?
Just call her a genius
and leave it at that.
- Gonna check upstairs.
- Copy that.
- Oliver, I found some...
- Nothing!
You.
New outfit.
You think an arrow is gonna stop me?
I think a tranq arrow will.
- Do you know him?
- He's one of the Longbow Hunters.
What are they doing mixed up
in Emiko's mother's murder?
That's a good question.
Don't hang up, and I mean that.
Literally, you will not
be able to exit my window.
You really can't take a hint, can you?
Look. I know that Emiko
killed Gustavo Hernandez.
Ooh! Congratulations,
Detective Felicity.
It's only a matter of time
until Oliver stops her,
so whatever bad and evil
plan that you have brewing,
it's not too late for you to
not go over to the dark side.
Oliver's sister did me a favor
because I was really sick and tired
of pretending to be somebody I'm not.
- Plus, no one believed it anyway.
- I did.
Look. What happened to you wasn't fair.
You were accused of
murder, you lost your job,
Dinah didn't have your back.
I get it. You got a
bucket load of bad news,
but you are not Black
Siren, not anymore.
It's funny. I used to believe that, too.
Think of all the good
you've done, Laurel.
- Think about honoring Quentin.
- Quentin is dead.
Nobody cares about Quentin.
- He only wanted his daughter back.
- That is not true.
You've done a lot of good as the D.A.,
not to mention you were there
for me when I needed a friend.
I'm not willing to let you
just throw that all away
and forget about it.
Look. I'm really sorry if you thought
we had a real friendship,
but it was all just an act,
and don't you dare try and stop me.
Stopping those bombs prompted Galaxy One
to put their master plan in motion,
expanding Archer's
influence into Star City
and making sure they take
out any and all opposition.
Starting with the Canaries.
How many have we lost?
I'm waiting on a body count
from Roy, William, and Connor,
but they've already confirmed
10 dead and 5 missing.
It's not your fault.
But it's my responsibility.
Oh, thank goodness you two are safe.
Yeah. Um,
could have taken creepy
mask guy off the board
except someone got in my way.
Zoe made the right call.
We've lost enough
blood already as it is.
And until we know what
the hell is going on,
- we need to lay low.
- And do what, nothing?
What we do is mourn our dead.
Then we figure out a plan that
won't cost us any more lives.
You're right.
Galaxy One has us
out-manned and outgunned.
We need to find another
way to even the odds.
Galaxy One just decimated
the entire Canary network.
You want to even the odds,
you get out there and
you fight the hell back.
If you don't, we're all dead.
- Psst.
- Unh!
I really missed our girls' nights out.
- Me, too.
- Like taking candy.
From a filthy rich baby.
That's got to be $10
million worth of diamonds.
It's too bad it doesn't belong to you.
And what?
Are you gonna stop us?
Don't do this, Laurel.
Oh, I thought you'd be happy.
You were right about me all along.
Oh, and it's too bad that you
don't have your cry anymore.
But I still have mine.
Phew. What an entrance.
Oh, and feel free to
tell Laurel's new friend
that it's a bad idea to
leave vault schematics
just hanging around her lair.
What are you doing here?
Yeah. Same question.
Aren't you supposed to be on your
little spaceship or something?
I took a break to clean up your mess.
What is this, some kind of intervention.
I know you're not my sister,
but in another world or another life,
you could have been,
and my father believed in you.
Well, he was wrong,
but you're right about one thing.
You're not my sister.
Stay the hell away from me.
You didn't go back to the bunker.
- We always go back to the bunker.
- I had work to do.
I know I should have
told you about Sara.
It would have been nice.
And what was that device?
I modified O.G. Laurel's old collar.
- Same tech, new look.
- It was impressive.
Felicity, we are the only team
sanctioned to work with SCPD.
Please remember it doesn't mean
any vigilante gets a free pass.
In my defense, if anyone's
gonna get through to Laurel,
it's her sister... well,
not her real sister,
but the face of her sister...
you know what I mean.
You cannot seriously think
she's still capable of
redemption after what we just saw.
That is harsh, especially
coming from the person
who wrongly accused her of murder.
So you're saying what
Laurel's doing is my fault?
Our fault. Maybe if we had been
a better support system to her.
Laurel did not become Black Siren
because we were bad friends, Felicity.
That is a choice she made on her own.
It is not some inevitable
consequence of something we did.
Everything that has happened
since she has been fired
- is on her!
- I think you're being hard on her
because you feel guilty.
And I think you need
to drop the blinders.
This is Laurel's new gal pal...
Aviva Metula, former Mossad
agent turned master thief.
She now goes by the name Shadow Thief.
- Very on the nose.
- She used to work with Diaz,
which means she probably
used to work with Laurel.
It looks like Shadow
Thief has really leveled up
her bad guy game since her Diaz days.
There's no more petty heists.
It's only a matter of
time before she gets Laurel
mixed up in whatever
she came to town for.
- Then we better find them fast.
- OK.
Felicity must have figured out
I was using the D.A.
database to find our targets.
Which one was Felicity?
The chatty one.
Here.
You need this.
Don't worry. There are plenty of jobs.
Not if she knows how I'm finding them.
Maybe it's a good thing.
No offense, but your
jobs are small potatoes.
- What do you mean?
- Let's just say that since our Diaz days
I've met some new friends,
some very powerful friends
who pay very well for
my destructive services.
- So you're a terrorist for hire?
- Heh heh.
I prefer mercenary with perks,
and I could use someone like you.
I just want to make sure
that you're the same ruthless
Black Siren I once knew.
I wouldn't be here if I wasn't.
Good because if those women
continue to be a problem for us...
You don't have to worry.
They get in our way again,
I'll kill them myself.
Who hired you to kill Kazumi Adachi?
Kazumi who?
Wrong answer.
Doesn't matter to us.
How do you want this to go?
You guys can chop off
all 10 of my fingers,
and it won't matter.
I have no idea who hired me.
They never contacted me directly.
Then how'd they offer you the job?
They directed me to
a drop-off location.
Once I got there, found a coin.
Was it an Italian florin?
No idea. All I know is that it was old.
There was a microchip inside,
instructions to get
my weapon, the target.
Once the job was completed,
they wired my payment from a
bank account in Switzerland.
A florin, Swiss bank account.
John, this is Dante.
So what now? You guys kill me?
Let's go. We got what we came for.
Well,
I'm having déjà vu in
the best way possible.
Did Dinah read you the Riot Act?
Nothing I can't handle.
You've come a long
way from the I.T. girl
secretly crushing on Oliver Queen.
Apparently, it wasn't much of a secret.
Everybody knew. Zero poker face,
and I always wondered, you
know, were you flirting with me
- all those times you said I was cute?
- Why?
- Were you into it?
- Of course. It's you.
- Oh, I missed you.
- I missed you, too.
- Thank you for coming.
- Of course.
I just wish it had gone better.
Look. Laurel will come around.
All we have to do is get her away
from her new BFF long enough
to knock some sense into her.
I mean, that is if you
don't have to go back
for any timey-wimey shenanigans.
Well, every time I leave the ship,
it basically means the
inmates take over the asylum,
but it's fine.
Want to make sure that
my real sister's name
doesn't get dragged through the mud,
and, by the way, why
are you so concerned
with saving this Laurel?
I mean, she's more like
our Laurel than you realize.
She helped Oliver get out
of prison the legal way,
and she stopped me from
killing Ricardo Diaz.
Felicity Smoak is killing people now?
I really have missed a lot.
The point is, is that
I didn't kill anyone
because Laurel pulled
me back from the edge.
That's what I want to do for her now,
you know, send her out a lifeline.
Even if there was a way back
for Laurel, she has to want it.
You can't force redemption on people.
Oh, that I know.
Well, it's all theoretical
anyway since I have no idea
where Shadow Thief or
Laurel are operating out of.
Hold that thought.
Dinah just got a location
on Shadow Thief's secret hideout.
Turns out... of course, of course...
it's at a shady warehouse
in a shady part of town.
Is that where Laurel's been holing up?
- That's what Dinah thinks.
- _
Man, it is completely off the grid.
Dinah wants me to go with her
so she doesn't go in blind.
So we don't go in blind.
Um, no. Mmm. This is
more of a two-woman job.
Dinah wants to keep it above board.
No. Got it. Not invited.
- OK.
Call me.
Not to belabor the point or anything,
but it would have been
really nice to have
White Canary here with us...
the flight. Heh!
You know, since you're both
Canaries and everything.
- Can we talk about this later?
- Mm-hmm.
Who's here besides us?
There's only two heat
signatures in the entire building
besides us, and...
they're right behind this door.
It's got to be Shadow Thief and Laurel.
- You ready?
- Mm-hmm.
Where are they?
- They played us.
- Fake heat signatures?
That is devious and impressive.
Get down!
Are you OK?
Laurel tried to kill us.
It turns out we could have used some
White Canary backup after all.
- Well, you got it now.
- Sorry.
No worries.
Find anything at the lair?
No, not yet.
They were sloppy, though.
Probably too fixated on killing us.
The tech that Shadow Thief left behind
will probably give us some
insight on how she operates.
With any luck, that's
how we'll find her.
I'm so sorry.
I really thought Laurel had changed.
Well, that's all right. We're just lucky
she's rusty and messed up.
- Yeah.
- Or maybe it's not luck at all.
I mean, Black Siren's a
lethal, unforgiving killer.
It's rare she fails, even rarer
she doesn't do the job herself.
I'm gonna get some air. Let me
know if you guys find anything.
You know, maybe if I could
have helped more or...
Felicity, you have to
stop blaming yourself.
Laurel had every opportunity
to make the right decision,
and she didn't.
Laurel has not changed.
She is the same monster
who killed Vinnie.
What Laurel did is unforgivable,
but she's just on this path,
and she doesn't know
how to get off of it.
Do you know how many
times in my life
I could have gone
down the same path,
including killing Laurel
last year, and I didn't?
Yeah, you didn't because you had us.
I mean, when Oliver
brought you on the team,
you weren't exactly a Saint.
I was protecting women who
couldn't protect themselves.
Yes, but even in your darkest of times,
even when you were
hell-bent on killing Laurel,
we still had your back.
I mean, we gave you a second chance,
and look where you are now.
You're... you're captain of the SCPD,
you're a deputized vigilante.
I mean, you couldn't
possibly have imagined
that this is where you
would have ended up.
No, that's true, but I...
I'm grateful for Oliver
and for the whole team,
but I don't think it
matters with Laurel.
I don't think she ever even
wanted that kind of support.
Or maybe she wanted
it more than any of us
and didn't realize it until it was gone.
I appreciate you wanting payback
for what happened to the Canaries,
but not like this.
Mia, if you go out there on your own,
chances are you will
not make it back alive.
Galaxy One found all of
your safe houses, Dinah.
They'll find this one, too.
I'm not gonna sit
around and wait for them
to massacre the rest of us.
Believe me, there is nothing
I would love more than to see
those sons of bitches pay
for what they did to my girls.
- So why don't you?
- Because I know I can't do it alone,
- and neither can you.
- Then come with me.
Instead of hiding in the shadows,
let's take this fight to Galaxy One,
make them pay for blood with blood.
Sometimes, I don't know
who you sound more like...
your mother or your father.
Do you know why I started the Canaries,
what it represents?
This is more than just
some rebellion group.
It's a support system.
This is a way for women to know
we always have each other's backs
no matter what happens,
whenever we need it most,
something I failed to
do for a friend once,
but ever since that happened with her,
I made a promise to myself that I
would never make that mistake again.
That's why we wear these.
To honor that promise
and the bravery and the sacrifice
shared with these amazing women,
who somehow... no matter how many
times they get knocked down...
they always find the strength
to get back up and fight again...
And that is exactly what the
surviving Canaries are going to do
together but when the time is right.
It's too bad I'm not a Canary.
Dante has been pulling the
strings this entire time.
He orchestrates her mother's murder,
and he sends her down this path.
Sounds like you're softening
up on your sister again.
I just have a better understanding
of why she's done what she's done.
When Emiko realizes that Dante
has been manipulating her,
it will drive a wedge between
her and the Ninth Circle.
That's how we stop them.
_
Thought I might find you here.
It's pretty brave of you,
sneaking up on me from behind.
If you wanted to kill people,
you wouldn't have gave
them that warning time
before the bomb went off.
I really miss him.
It looks like you do, too.
Is this you trying to
convince me that I've changed,
that I'm more like your Laurel?
No. Nobody's as good as
the original Laurel Lance,
not even me.
Look. I don't know what
you've heard about me,
but basically, I had an affair
with my sister's boyfriend,
I allowed my entire family
to think that I was dead,
and then I became a
league-trained assassin.
Wow. That's impressive.
My point is even someone with a past
as checkered as mine can
still turn their life around,
- can be a hero.
- I was being a hero.
I was the D.A., I got
Oliver out of prison,
and I was the only one who figured out
that his little sister
was basically the devil,
and they still turned on me.
So, what, you think you deserve a medal
for trying to be good for 5 seconds?
Redemption isn't a
destination. It's a journey.
I wasted years running away
from all the bad things that I had done
because I didn't want to face
the pain that I had caused
because I didn't want to be that person,
and then I realized the only
way to stop being that person
was to come home and own up
to the things that I had done,
and, yeah, it was painful,
and it took a really long time,
but it was the only way
to become someone else,
someone better than who I was.
Well, that's great for you,
but even if I wanted to change,
it's a little bit too late
because this is who I am.
Heh. I was starting to
think you might not show.
I had some business to take care of.
So what's this weapon
that we're stealing?
Who cares? All that matters
is that we're getting paid.
You ready?
Absolutely.
Manpower seems thin.
I thought we'd run into some guards.
Why, do you think we're hitting it now?
I'm gonna check out the south wing.
- You.
- Don't look surprised.
Your friend's suit is
basically a giant tracker.
And we happen to know somebody
who's very good with a computer.
You brought your little friend with you.
How typical.
It's not too late, Laurel.
Don't do this.
Ohh. That song of yours
is getting a little old.
Laurel!
Ugh. God. You're here, too?
Do you know what Shadow Thief is
planning to do with that device?
Yes. Sell it for a lot of money
of which I get half.
Who do you think she's gonna sell it to,
the girl scouts?
That device is gonna
be used to kill people.
Well, that's not really
my concern now, is it?
- Move.
- No.
Seriously? Felicity, don't you think
you're just a little
bit out of your element?
That is correct. I know
that, but so are you.
Oh, for the love of God,
would you give it up already?
This is who I am! Do you not see that?
Who I see is someone that I believe in
and someone that I really care about.
Felicity, what are you doing?
Forget living up to Laurel's legacy,
and forget being who
Lance wanted you to be.
- What do you want?
- I want you to get out of my way.
I guess if you're OK with
that device killing people,
you may as well start with me.
- Me, too.
- And me.
I changed my mind. The deal's off.
I kind of expected. Good
thing I had a backup plan.
We have to get out of here.
Look. Is the payload device big enough
to clear out the building?
Yes, but the problem
is we're inside the building.
That's exactly why they
won't be expecting it.
How long do you need to arm it?
90 seconds. But how
are we gonna get out?
Birds fly, don't they?
Let's buy her some time.
Uh... go. Go.
Hyah! Hyah! Hyah...
Come on, come on, come
on, come on. Come on.
- Ohh!
- It's time to go.
Stay close.
Overwatch, now!
Can we never do that again?
- Is everybody OK?
- You came back for me.
We're only as strong as we are together,
something I didn't
realize till just now.
We are pretty bad-ass together.
Yeah. Like a birds of justice.
Something like that.
To ladies taking down ladies.
Heh. And to Laurel.
Thank you for the assist,
and I am very, very
sorry that I doubted you.
That means a lot.
- I just wish we got Shadow Thief.
- We'll get her next time.
So does this mean you're
not gonna arrest me?
I don't see why I would.
This new evidence proves
you didn't kill Hernandez,
and you went undercover to bring down
the Shadow Thief,
so I am as surprised as anyone.
Thank you.
Now that Laurel Lance,
upstanding citizen,
is back,
everything can go back to normal.
Actually, it can't.
Say what, now?
I am so tired of running.
It's time for me to go home now.
Home? As in Earth-2 home?
Yeah. Someone in similar shoes told me
if I wanted to be one of the good guys
that I needed to right my wrongs,
and the only way to do that is to go
back to where it all started.
Yeah.
Oh. Well, uh...
I'll cheers to that.
- Yeah.
- Ah-ah.
Heh. I think I deserve two of these.
I mean, come on. I worked
really hard, so there.
Cheers to me.
Oh, no. It's the SCPD.
OK. Apparently, criminals don't care
how badly I need a girls' night.
I have something for you.
From one Canary to another,
Sara wanted you to have this.
I can adjust it for you.
Probably get your cry
back if you want it.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
- Yes, you are welcome.
- Thank you.
No sweat.
Did it all the time when
my sister was pregnant.
Oh. Way to bury the lede.
That's how you knew I was pregnant.
Mm-hmm.
I have something for you.
It's Laurel's Black Canary costume.
Yeah. Yeah. I thought
you could use it here,
but, you know, maybe
Earth-2 needs a Black Canary.
You are still planning
on being good, right?
I'm planning to try, yeah.
Good.
I just really hope one day I'm
actually worthy of it.
Welcome home, Ms. Smoak.
Oh, you're home.
I missed you.
Did you get what you were looking for?
Yup. I'm exhausted.
Just want to sit on the couch
and order some food,
and... I don't know...
I'll have whatever you're craving, OK?
I already ate
after I said good-bye to Laurel.
So you found Laurel,
but you said good-bye to her already?
Well, yeah, after we stopped her
from going on a killing spree.
- Hmm?
- Dinah and Sara and I.
- Yeah. That Sara,
and we did it, super-easy, you know.
It was like "Charlie's Angels"
without the feathered
hair and casual sexism.
So that whole taking it easy thing?
Well, you know I'm not good at that.
Well, I'm here now, so
I'll take care of you.
Well, you could start with a foot rub.
Yeah.
Ahh.
We keep this up, people
are gonna start asking
why we keep hanging out in cemeteries.
I was never very good at good-byes.
Quentin always saw the good in me
when... when nobody else did.
I wish I could tell him
how much it meant to me.
He knew.
He was the first person to make
me feel like I was never alone.
You're not alone, not anymore.
So much for plan "A".
Unh.
Whoa.
But I've seen you before.
The old Green Arrow documentary.
- You're...
- A friend of your parents.
You're lucky we got here when we did.
Dinah sent you to watch my back.
It's what Canaries do.
Give this to Felicity.
You look so much like her,
and you may not be a Canary,
and you still have a long way to go
to prove that you're a hero.
Take it from someone who
knows how hard it can be,
and don't screw it up.
- Synced by Chamallow & ChrisKe -
-- for www.addic7ed.com --