Previously on
"Arrow"...
Diaz has people
everywhere.
He controls
Star City's government,
its infrastructure,
and its police force.
Diaz went after this
instead of going after Curtis.
What if these are all
of Diaz's books,
everyone he has
on his payroll?
We could liberate
the city.
Your digital sniffer,
can it read the drive?
If you get me close enough,
for sure.
Diaz's base of operations
is too secure.
We can't move on it
without losing people.
You want my help?
I'm gonna need you
to say the words.
I am the Green Arrow.
Sentries
are not responding.
You know, somebody want to
tell me why I got to do
everything
in this place mysel...
Why don't you watch
where you...
You got to be
a special kind of stupid
to be coming back
here alone.
I'm not alone.
- Move! - Move!
- Move!
- Clear!
Clear.
Where's Diaz?
Where is Diaz?
No sign of Diaz.
- What about Knyazev?
- Same.
Precinct reported
he's not there either.
This isn't over yet.
*ARROW*
Season 06  Episode 23
Episode Title: "Life Sentence"
Diaz clearly has
a third base of operations
we don't know about.
Yo, Hoss. Mask?
Mr. Queen and I have come
to an understanding.
Even if we didn't,
your identity is hardly
a well-kept secret,
Mr. Ramirez.
So you're done
trying to throw us in jail?
Everyone has immunity
from prosecution, Rene.
The FBI recognizes that
Diaz is the clear and present danger.
Better late
than never, I suppose.
That immunity
deal does include me, right,
because I'd really
like to not spend
the rest of my life
in prison if I can avoid it.
How did Diaz know
we were moving in on him tonight?
We've rounded up
the SCPD,
but Diaz still controls
dozens of city officials.
Diaz has a list
of all of them.
He keeps it
on his person.
Once we take, Diaz,
we won't need a list.
We need to interrogate
all the people we rounded up,
see if we can get one of them
to give up Diaz's location.
Oh. They won't
give it up.
They're more afraid of
them than they are of us.
They also know
without corroboration,
Diaz or this list
of his,
we'll have to kick
them in 48 hours.
Where's he going?
Probably to go talk
to his guy on the inside.
- Zdrahstvuyte.
- Anatoly.
Big night for you,
kapiushon.
How you turn FBI
from foe to friend, huh?
Same way you did me?
Where's Diaz?
Eh, he's been on the move
ever since he heard
FBI coming to town.
When he settles,
I want to know where.
Hmm. I'll try my best,
but... he's not
in very trusting mood
these days.
What?
Ok. Poka. Phew.
My sister.
What you Americans
call high maintenance. Heh.
You avoided the raid.
Yeah. I got hungry,
therefore lucky. Heh.
Got dinner.
When I got back here,
FBI all over place like
ants at picnic.
So what is your
next move?
You lost your army.
I made some new friends.
New friends?
The Longbow Hunters.
Thought those
were a myth.
They're very real.
We're going somewhere
to mount our counterattack.
Be there in an hour.
Yeah. I love
you, sweetie. Ok. Bye-bye.
- Lyla?
- Yeah.
Yeah. She, J.J., and William are
at the NORAD bunker,
but she would
much rather be here.
We have
enough backup.
A son needs
his parents.
And yours doesn't?
I'm gonna see
this through, Oliver.
Thought you might
say that,
so I think you
should dress the part.
I had a spare
made up.
There's no rule saying there can't
be more than one Green Arrow.
I should have done this
from the beginning.
Oliver, our disagreement
was never about the uniform.
I know that.
I'd like to apologize
for any part that I played in it.
I really thought
I wanted this mantle.
It means something.
You've made it
mean something.
When our city looks at it,
it gives them hope, Oliver,
and it would be diminished
if there was more than one.
For everything along
the way, thank you.
Hello!
Uh, excuse me.
Hello, everybody. Heh.
My name is Anatoly Knyazev,
and I'm here
to turn myself in.
Tch.
We... we also have, uh,
costume parties in Russia.
It's always great fun.
What do you have,
Anatoly?
Address for Diaz.
He said to meet him there
in one hour,
but he's not
going to be alone.
He's bringing
Longbow Hunters.
Long-what, now?
3 assassins that even
the League is afraid of.
Or they were because the last one
died out in the 1950s.
Or that's what
they wanted people to think.
We got the FBI
backing us.
Please tell me we're
not afraid of 3 guys.
Hell, no.
All right.
Let's get ready to move.
I'll go tell
Agent Watson.
Wow. It's funny.
Everything always comes down
to a signature
on a piece of paper.
Diaz's crimes are local,
which means the bureau
needs municipal authority
to operate in Star City.
Well, now you got it.
- Heh.
- What is it?
Got a location
on Diaz.
This'll be
over tonight.
Excuse me.
Hey, honey.
Hey, daddy.
So the relationship
between me and your daughter,
it took a turn.
I don't think she's, uh...
She's into me anymore.
- Listen to me.
- No!
You listen to me,
or Laurel dies
a second time!
What do you want?
For the mayor to kick
the FBI out of my city.
Do it tonight...
or Laurel's dead.
Go to hell.
What was that?
Nothing. You said you're ready
to move on Diaz tonight.
I'm ready to come down
on him like God's own righteous fury.
Do it.
I don't think your daddy
loves you anymore.
I think if you were
the real Laurel,
he'd already be here.
Go to hell.
That's a witty response.
I was expecting better.
Do you know what
the funny thing is?
You moved on me
because of him.
You got yourself
in this situation
because of him!
You could have
skipped town,
but you came
after me!
Was you afraid of
what I was gonna do
to your daddy
when you were gone?
Huh? Come on, baby.
Talk to me.
Talk to me!
We're on site.
The FBI has graciously
given me control
of their keyhole satellites,
which I got to say
are a lot easier to operate
when they aren't being hacked.
All right. Listen up.
Diaz may have lost
his police force,
but we believe he still
has his personal security
and Quadrant muscle
backing him up.
No warning shots.
Let's move out.
If this is where Diaz is planning
on making his last stand,
I would have expected
more guys with guns.
Not seeing
anything.
I'm getting a big thermal reading from
inside the northwest corner.
That's where we're
headed. Stand by.
Son of a bitch.
What is it?
Laser tripwires.
Tripwires to what?
Triacetone triperoxide.
It's the thermal source.
Diaz was never here.
It's a trap.
Hang tight. We're
almost at your position.
Negative. If you go in
there, if anybody moves,
the whole place
will go up.
If we can't move,
we can't get to the bombs.
How are we supposed
to disarm them?
I am working on that.
Everyone else, just get clear.
We can't leave Rene.
No. There might be
more explosives rigged.
Just please get away
from the building.
You heard her.
Let's go.
Talk to me,
Blondie.
I'm tracing a radio signal
to the explosives.
In case Diaz gets impatient,
wants to set off
bomb himself.
If I can piggyback
off the signal,
I might be able
to fool the triggers
into thinking that
you're not moving.
Might?
You can't see this,
but there's enough
explosives in here
to send us
into orbit.
Pressure is not
helping, Rene.
If the bombs can be
triggered remotely,
Diaz can kill us
anytime.
We're not making it out
of here, are we?
Hey, Peanut. It's daddy.
Nope. Everything's fine.
I'm safe.
I just wanted to hear
your voice...
And tell you
that I love you...
And I'm so proud of you.
You give my life meaning
every single day.
Yeah. You're
my everything, Peanut,
and I need you
to know that.
Daddy's got to go.
I love you.
I'll see you soon.
Ok. Bye.
Can we get in
through the roof?
Negative. Blowing
the roof will set off the TATP.
Stand by while I clone
the trigger frequency.
- Hello.
- So I'm curious.
How many did I get?
- You suhkin syn.
- You betray me,
and I'm
the son of a bitch?
The ones trapped
in there with those explosives,
they're gonna die
in a blink,
but you, Anatoly...
I'm gonna make it
last for days with you.
He triggered
the explosives,
but I'm bouncing the signal
off a bunch of satellites.
You have 7 seconds!
Move!
Come on!
You ok?
Thought I'd check in
on you.
I'm fine, Hoss.
Agent Watson told me
about your call with Zoe.
I thought I was gonna
die in that room.
I just wanted
to say good-bye.
Tell her how proud
you are of her?
There's not enough words
to say how much.
I feel the same way
about you, Rene.
When I first met you,
I... I didn't think
that you were much more
than a... thug
in a... heh...
In a ridiculous costume.
You're no prize
yourself, Hoss.
I judged you.
For far too long,
I judged you,
and...
that was a mistake.
I'm sorry.
I think that you're
a good man, Rene.
I think that you're the type of man
that this... this city deserves.
I know it seems like
I don't give a crap
about what anyone
thinks,
but this means a lot.
Good.
Guys!
We have another problem.
I told Diaz
to go to hell
because you were about
to move on him.
It was deception.
He learned I was
helping you,
and he
manipulated me.
Means we're right
back to square one,
not knowing
where Diaz is.
But now we
have a way to find out.
You tell Diaz you want to
see Laurel, proof of life.
We follow you to her,
her to Diaz.
You go in there guns blazing,
my daughter takes the first bullet.
From what Oliver tells me, she's not
actually your daughter,
and she's a criminal
that made her own bed.
This isn't
a hostage situation.
Our objective
hasn't changed.
- Oliver, please.
- We can keep her safe.
How? The first thing
he'll do when he sees you coming
- is kill her!
- I think this is
a risk we need to take.
Yeah? Would you be taking
that risk if this was our Laurel,
or is that the kind
of risk that got her killed
in the first damn place?
What the hell
do you want?
To give you
a second chance.
When you told me
to go to hell,
you know, I figured
that you figured
your buddies were
about to take me down.
Well, it didn't
work out that way,
so now we're back
to where we started...
You kicking the FBI out of here
in exchange for Laurel's life.
I'd need to see her first,
proof of life.
I'll send you
the address.
Listen. You better
come alone
because if something
happens that I don't like
something's gonna happen
to Laurel that you don't like.
Anyone ever tell you
it's rude to sneak up on people?
Diaz?
He's gonna kill her.
I won't let that
happen, Quentin.
What about Watson, huh?
Doesn't seem
so important to her.
Just let me worry
about Samanda Watson
and let me try to
keep Laurel safe.
I don't see
how you can, Oliver.
You can start
by trusting me, please.
I mean, I've earned it.
We've known each other
for a very long time,
Quentin.
Heh. A lifetime.
Yeah.
We've come a long way,
you and me.
It's been getting better
since the first time you arrested me.
You know, I've always
been curious...
How'd you beat
that lie detector anyway?
It-It just comes down to...
keeping a regular heart rate.
I got a pacemaker
that does that.
I didn't know you
had a pacemaker.
I got it after that Mirakuru business
a few years back.
The old ticker couldn't
take that pounding. Heh.
Yeah.
Truth be told, I don't know if
I could take it now.
Yes, it can, ok,
because you're tough.
Laurel is tough, too,
so trust me...
And this
will all work out.
You were supposed
to bring Laurel.
I give the orders.
He's clean.
And you're gonna give
an order as mayor
to get the FBI out of here,
and you're gonna do it
at a press conference.
Satellite track is clean.
Audio signal is 5 by 5.
Everyone get ready
to move!
Not going anywhere until we know
where he's keeping Laurel.
Not our objective.
You want me to
hold a press conference
before you even let me
see my daughter?
You have a problem
with that?
I'm not doing anything
until I see her alive.
What the hell is he doing?
The FBI is tracking
me by satellite.
They're gonna move on you
unless we move right now.
Now take me
to my daughter.
Son of a bitch!
Get him in the car.
All units,
move now! Go!
Can your satellite
track him?
- I've lost him.
- Your friend just
blew this whole operation
and our best chance
to get Diaz,
and his daughter's
still gonna die.
When this is over,
I'm bringing your friend Quentin up
on obstruction.
Our immunity arrangement
doesn't extend to him.
He was trying to
save Laurel.
Well, I'm trying to
save this city,
the city your friend's supposed
to be the mayor of.
I can't believe
he'd do something so reckless.
Or stupid. He knows Diaz
will kill him and Laurel.
What the hell
was he thinking?
He wasn't.
That's the problem.
Before Quentin went
to see Diaz,
he went out of his way to tell me that
he had a pacemaker.
Yeah, and he's never
told us that before.
So why would he
say something now?
- You can track a pacemaker.
- You know I can.
Quentin knew that Diaz's man
was gonna frisk him for a tracker
just like he knew that Diaz
wasn't going to actually bring
Laurel to the meet,
so Quentin had Diaz
bring him to her,
knowing that we
could track him.
How long will it take you
to find him?
Give me a high-speed
connection and a few minutes.
Agh!
You wanted to see her,
now you see her.
I'm a man of my word.
Great. Now let her go.
I just promised
proof of life.
We'll see how long
that lasts.
Hey. Felicity has
Quentin's location.
It's an abandoned
chemical plant
on the border
of Pennytown.
We're gonna move out
in 5 minutes.
- I'll be ready.
- The FBI's only objective is Diaz.
They're gonna do
their best to keep Quentin safe,
but they don't care if Black Siren is
collateral damage.
Your point?
My point, Dinah, is that it's up to us
to keep her safe.
I know that you have
put your vendetta aside
for the sake
of the mission.
And you want to make sure
I keep it that way.
I want to say
thank you.
It takes
a very big person
to not... seek vengeance
for someone they love.
If I haven't always
been sensitive to that,
I'm truly sorry.
I'm sorry I was
so hard on you.
You know, the truth is
I respect you more
than you could ever know.
You put together
a team of heroes.
That's no small thing.
- I'm gonna go get ready.
- All right.
- Hey.
- What is going on?
- What do you mean?
- I mean, you've been giving
the Oliver farewell tour
all around this place,
including giving John
the hood.
You know, everyone's
wondering what did you
have to give Watson
to get her to give us immunity,
and I'm just gonna go
out on a limb here
and guess that it was
giving up being the Green Arrow.
- Sort of.
- You can't be serious.
What happened to becoming
your best self?
I don't know if I
believe that anymore.
Oliver, this is
who you are.
You can't let Watson get
in the middle of that.
She's not.
It was my idea.
What do you mean,
it was your idea?
Ahem.
Uh, sorry to interrupt
what looks like
a pretty serious
marital moment,
but everyone's
ready to go.
To be continued. Ok?
Showtime!
You're gonna get
in front of the camera,
and you're gonna get
the FBI to leave Star City,
or your baby girl
grows a third eye.
He's not gonna
shoot me.
You willing to bet
your life?!
- Yes.
- Laurel.
Yes, I am!
You got 5 seconds!
5...
Don't let him
take this city.
4...
He's bluffing.
He's lying!
3...
2...
1!
No! Agh!
Gaah!
Daaaahhh!
- No! Dad? Daddy.
- Ohh!
Stay with me.
Stay with me, daddy.
- Ohh!
- Stay with me!
Look at me,
look at me.
- Ugh.
- Stay with me.
Errrgh!
Hey. Don't waste
your tears.
Where I shot him,
it'll take
a good chunk of time
for him to bleed out.
Gaaaah!
Laurel, you need
to get your dad
to get on the phone
and get the feds to go back
to their swamp.
I'll show him
some mercy.
Tss. Aah!
Huh? Like the end
of the movie
with the little dog.
What's it called?
I'm gonna kill you.
I'm not
doing anything. Ugh.
All right. We're
gonna do this another way.
Ohh!
Because I'm not
gonna count.
Your daughter's
brains
are gonna be splattered
on your face!
Don't you. Don't you!
It'll be all right.
FBI!
Quentin!
I got him!
Get Diaz!
It's ok. Stay...
Laurel.
Ohh! No.
We got to get him
to a hospital.
Come on.
I got you.
Errrrgh!
I need a chopper!
I don't have 5 minutes!
I agree!
You want to shoot me?
Do it!
Right here!
See, that's your problem.
It's always been
your problem!
Ugh!
He needs
a doctor immediately!
Yes, ma'am.
Agh!
Enough!
Hyah!
Ugh!
Aaagh!
Aah!
This is my city!
You want to stop me,
you're gonna have to
kill me!
He's right, Oliver.
The movie
with the dog,
it's called
"Old Yeller."
No!
What did you do?!
I had to!
I had to end it.
Yeah? You think that fall's
gonna kill him?
A girl can only hope.
I had him!
We scoured
every inch of this city
and trolled Starling bay.
He can't have
gotten far.
He was launched
off a rooftop.
He shouldn't have been able
to go anywhere at all.
Diaz doesn't go
down easy.
You seem pretty sanguine
about it.
It wasn't
a total loss.
Felicity reprogrammed this
with a digital sniffer.
I was able to get
close enough to Diaz
to clone the drive
that he wears around his neck.
I got government officials,
city employees.
We can give you everyone
on his payroll.
Huh. We can give you
your city back,
but the fact that Diaz
is in the wind,
it doesn't alter
our agreement.
I know.
- How is he?
- He's septic.
They're getting him
ready for surgery.
Rene's in there
with him right now.
What about Diaz?
You're gonna
be fine, Hoss.
These docs are gonna
fix you up.
Yeah. Do me a favor.
Anything, Hoss.
If this thing goes the wrong way
and I don't make it,
d-d-don't call me Hoss
at my funeral.
You're gonna make it.
Yeah.
How's he doing?
Kind of macabre,
actually.
I'll give you guys
a minute.
Mm-hmm.
- Hi.
- Ahem.
What's the latest
on Diaz?
Diaz... ahem...
He got away.
How?
Doesn't matter.
We'll get him.
We do have a list of
everyone that he's been controlling.
FBI is rounding them
up as we speak.
- So we can take our city back.
- Mm-hmm.
You did good, Oliver.
Thank you.
It's not over yet.
It is for you.
Am I wrong?
I've been dealing
with Samanda Watson for months.
There's no way she was gonna
help you without strings attached,
but those strings,
Oliver, that's a hell of a sacrifice.
I had to look at the way that I've
been doing things.
It's not working.
I lost my city,
I lost my team.
There's a penance
for that.
It just seems
a little drastic.
Coming from the guy
who just took a bullet for his daughter.
Quentin, I hope
I took the time to tell you, uh...
You're a really
good father.
So are you.
I had a good example.
Yeah. Your dad was
a good man.
I'm not talking
about my dad.
I'm sorry, but we have to
take him to the O.R. now.
Well, um, when you
get out,
everyone will be here
waiting for you.
Thanks, Oliver.
For everything.
Thank you for coming.
How is he?
In surgery.
The doctors, they're
optimistic, but...
But I thought you
should probably be here.
Thank you.
This is probably really strange
for you, right?
A little.
Are you, um...
Are you like my Laurel?
Hardly at all.
How long is this
gonna take?
How many times
are you gonna ask that?
As many times as it takes
to find out
how long it's
gonna take.
Mr. Queen.
- It's time.
- Time for what?
What is she talking about?
I'm sorry
that I haven't ex...
Explained this
to everyone.
Hasn't been any time.
There wasn't time
to explain what?
- You're arresting us?
- What the hell are you doing?
I thought you said
we had immunity!
You do... Thanks to him.
Oh, my God.
It was the only way.
No, it was not
the only way.
There are a million
other ways.
The judge threw
out his case.
You can't do this.
- I can. It's federal.
- Federal.
The bureau's going to
stay in Star City
until Diaz is
brought in,
but only if Oliver agreed
to turn himself in.
What the hell is
going on here?
Wait a minute.
Just wait.
Ahem.
How's Quentin?
Mayor Lance seized
during the procedure.
The surgeons worked
to revive him.
They did everything
they could,
but his brain was deprived
of oxygen for 7 minutes.
He's gone.
I'm very sorry.
Unfortunately, this
doesn't change our arrangement.
Mm-hmm.
I'm so sorry, Sara.
All of you, please take care
of each other.
Ollie.
Transport's delayed.
We'll be transferring
you in a half-hour.
Ok. I talked to John.
We have a plan.
We're gonna get
you out.
- No, you can't.
- Yes, we can.
We've done it before.
We got John out of...
We broke him out
of Langham Penitentiary.
Yes, we did.
They're transferring me
to a Supermax, Felicity,
and even if I wanted
to break out,
they would just
arrest everyone,
including you.
I think that William
deserves at least one parent.
During your trial,
you said you didn't want to go public
because you wanted a life
after the Green Arrow.
This is that life.
You could...
I wanted to stop Diaz,
and I wanted to save
you and William more.
Not everything
went our way.
Quentin and...
That protective custody
that we talked about
for the two of you
during my trial...
- No.
- Lyla's gonna handle everything.
Uh...
I promise just until
Diaz is off the board.
No. I refuse to believe that
this is the only option.
We won back the city.
We got it back.
Thought I had
lost it.
Oliver...
You didn't do that alone.
I know.
Diaz tried to kill
everybody close to me.
I had to find a way
to protect everybody.
This was the way.
Is William here?
Yeah, he's outside. He's...
He's scared.
He's confused.
He's wondering how the woman
that he's known for less than a year
is suddenly
his only parent.
Would you please
go get him.
Yeah.
Buddy, how you doing?
I don't understand...
What's happening.
I'm gonna explain
everything to you.
Mr. Queen,
why are you being arrested again?
I have voluntarily,
uh, handed myself over
to the FBI.
Can you comment
any further?
Yes, I can.
I am the Green Arrow.
I realize that
I've denied that claim
with the same conviction
with which I'm speaking now.
I have let good people
stand accused
of things that I've done.
Roy Harper
is not the Green Arrow.
Tommy Merlyn is most certainly
not the Green Arrow.
These are two names
on a long list of people
who have given so much
and sacrificed everything
in the name of my crusade.
Some of them gave
their lives
in the pursuit of one
simple objective...
To save our city.
Star City still needs saving.
Last night, we dealt our enemy
a critical blow,
but there is still work
to be done,
so I'm looking
to the people of this city,
I'm looking to
my allies, to my friends,
to my partners...
and I'm asking them to continue,
to keep fighting.
I'm asking them
to complete our mission...
To save our city.
I know you, Oliver Queen.
I know...
You're gonna die in here,
sucker! You're gonna...
back the hell off!
Sync corrections  by  srjanapala
♪♪