And action.
Trust me, true believer.
Not only
did I not think
I would be doing a cameo
in such a big movie,
I never dreamt
there'd be such a big movie.
In those days,
I was writing those books.
I was hoping they'd sell
so I wouldn't lose my job
and I could keep
paying the rent.
All of a sudden,
these characters
have become world-famous.
They're the subject
of blockbuster movies,
and I'm lucky enough
to get little cameos in them.
E, mark.
Okay.
And background action. Action.
They decided
any scene with Bob and me...
- Remember me?
- Sure don't.
...had to be
a sure crowd-pleaser.
You look great, Hef.
Cut.
Ladies and gentlemen,
that's a camera wrap
on the creator of Iron Man,
Mr. Stan Lee.
We are so lucky.
Robert Downey Jr.
playing this role.
I was born under a lucky
star, I gotta tell you.
And to be in a scene with
him, brief as it was,
and I'll talk to them
about that later,
it was a joy,
really a joy.
I just love doing cameos,
because first of all,
there's no real
responsibility.
We arrive at the place
where they're shooting.
The director says,
"Go to wardrobe, go to makeup."
When I'm all finished,
"Okay. Here's your line."
That's Captain America?
I thought he'd be taller.
I'd like to start
with the line
that might have been
put to you, sir,
which was,
"Did it work?"
I'm a very good study.
I can remember a whole line
after reading it
three or four times.
Did it work?
And action.
Superheroes?
In New York? Give me a break.
I mean, I say a line or two
if I'm lucky enough
to get a line.
Sometimes it's just pantomime.
- Larry King.
- Larry!
And there I am on the screen
and I'm a big ham,
so I love it.
Oh, man.
I am so fired.
I like them all. I mean, as I think
of them, each one is my favorite.
And shrink!
Well, the '60s were fun,
but now I'm paying for it.
And cut it.
And I love being
in the theater
and having somebody
next to me,
"Oh, look! That's Stan Lee!"
I get a big kick
out of that.
You know what?
I think I'll just take these,
bring them over here,
and hold on for safekeeping.
Are you Tony Stank?
Oh, man. Anyway,
before I was so rudely interrupted...
At that time,
I was a Federal Express man.
I'm trying to tie
the Marvel Universe together
by being the one common
denominator that they all have.
What's the matter
with you kids?
You've never seen
a spaceship before?
My cameos are always fun,
especially when I do
one with Thor.
I play a barber and I'm
about to cut his hair.
Touch something and then the
whole thing's gonna come to life.
- Okay. Good.
- Yeah.
No!
Yes!
Good.
Hey, you guys,
make love not war.
Each one stands out
more than the previous one.
This is one of the best cameos
I've done, let me tell you.
Look at the girl I'm with.
You know what I'm saying?
- She's crazy stupid fine, right?
- You go, "Yeah."
Yeah.
Crazy stupid fine.
It's so fun when you show up in the films.
It's really neat.
Well, it's great.
I love it.
I mean, people are so nice.
- Great to see you.
- Hey, brother. How you doing?
- All right.
- Great to see you.
Have a safe trip
down to Atlanta.
The fact that I'm working with
characters that I've created...
Not too shabby.
By the crimson
rings of Cyttorak,
it's Doctor Strange!
And the fact that they are
being directed so beautifully...
- "I'll need a ride home."
- Why don't you try that?
"I'll need a ride home."
...to work
with such professionals
and they all have
a love of the characters.
Chris Evans came over to me
like I'm his father.
He is so happy
to be doing what he's doing.
He's so happy to be
Captain America, you know?
See, nobody's going to recognize
you, 'cause they...
- They're expecting to see this little guy.
- They're expecting this big.
Hey, glad to see you, Chris.
Yeah. How are you?
Hey, congratulations
on the twins.
- Thanks, buddy.
- Hey, that's terrific.
- Yes. It's fun.
- So you say something first.
I say, uh, "It's aged for
a thousand years in barrels
"built from the wreck
of Grunhel's Fleet.
"It's not meant
for mortal men."
And then that's you.
What the hell
did you just say?
This is not meant
for mortal men.
Neither was
Omaha Beach, Blondie.
Stop trying to scare us.
Come on.
I don't think of them
as cameos.
All right.
I rather think of it as a
supporting role that I play.
Excelsior.
- And cut.
- Cut there.
And cut it.
Stan Lee. The whole
reason any of this exists.
My hero.
The greatest man alive.
Thank you for everything.
We should all be grateful.
I know we're all honored.
And Stan,
thank you so much for being here.
It is our absolute pleasure
and forgive us if there's lots of
handshakes and autographs now...
I sometimes wonder,
"Did this really all happen?"
- It's an honor to have you.
- Thank you.
Thanks a lot.
In the days
I was writing these things,
I never thought it would turn
into something like this.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
This is just unbelievable.
It's indescribable.
To work with creative people,
especially people who make
movies, is such a thrill.
It's overwhelming
when I think about it.
And I keep saying to myself,
"I can't believe this is me.
"I can't believe
I lucked out this way."
Let's give it up
for Stan Lee, guys.
Whoo-hoo! Yeah!
Five lousy words
they gave me to say.
Thank you, too.
You're a great director.
It's something
you never forget.
And thank you for all of this
and I hope that I didn't set
interviewing back a few decades.
Okay.
I'll see you later.
Thank you.
I appreciate that.
I remember every cameo I've
done since the first one.
And I think
I'm a very lucky guy.
The journey of the entire
Marvel Cinematic Universe
started with the journey
of Tony Stark.
- Much better than the big old...
- Oh, yeah.
- ...clunky, clunky monkey.
- And that sound is great.
I think it looks
a little large, too,
but I think we might be able
to get away with it all.
Going back to Favreau
and Robert Downey Jr.
And the founding moments
of Marvel Studios,
we said, "We want the hero to
be as interesting out of costume
"as they are in costume."
I had just been hired
to cast the first Iron Man.
Jon Favreau was on board
at that time
and I remember asking him
in a meeting with everyone,
"Tell me all the qualities
"that you think
are most important."
Fast, quick-witted
and funny and dynamic
and a bit troubled
and confident
and brilliant
and all of these things.
And we really kept
coming back to Downey.
Stan Lee said he
kind of created him on a dare.
Could you make a billionaire
weapons manufacturer,
philandering philanthropist,
you know,
who largely lives an ugly and
irresponsible immoral psychology?
To peace!
If you look at Downey
in his early work, you know,
it's amazing. I mean,
look at Chaplin.
You look at Less Than Zero.
I mean, they're tough
characters to watch.
Robert Downey Jr.
at that point in his career
wasn't necessarily
a family-friendly name.
Today it's ridiculous,
but at the time,
it was, "Whoa! Risky casting
Robert Downey Jr."
The truth was
we got to a point
that we realized
if we didn't cast him,
that would have been
the biggest risk.
Robert had a whole career
of great work behind him,
and he was at a point
in his life and his career
where he was ready
to break out
and do something really big
and exciting.
Jon was in love with the
idea of Downey playing the part,
and we all felt so sure about
him on a creative level.
Because he wasn't instantly
a slam dunk approval,
I suggested
we have screen tests.
I remember walking in with Robert
Downey Jr. the day of the tests.
He was laughing and in great
spirits and completely at ease,
and he got in front of the camera
and started saying the lines.
I assure you the day weapons are
no longer needed to keep the peace,
I'll happily transition to
manufacturing bricks and beams
for baby hospitals,
making hemp pants and the like,
but until that time,
can I get you a drink?
I don't want to call it
an out-of-body experience,
but it was one of those rushes
that I'm sure, like, somebody
would feel if they're about to play
a big sporting arena,
playing for the ring
or something like that.
It was just like, "Am I gonna
pass out or am I gonna nail this?"
On that day
that Robert screen tested,
it was clear that there was no
one else who can play that part.
It was magic. It was exactly the
feeling as a casting director,
with Kevin, with Jon,
with everyone
that we all wanted
to have that feeling, like,
"We have it. This is it.
This is Iron Man."
Iron Man 1 was incredibly special.
We sort of improved
the whole thing.
We laughed. We cried.
We got very,
very close on that movie.
We were the first
Marvel movie as a studio.
You know, there was
no real model for it yet.
Nobody expected
too much of it.
He's Iron Man.
We wanted to make
a good quality film,
a good story, something that
was smart enough, funny enough.
I still remember Tony
landing in the high desert
in the eastern Sierras
when he escapes the cave,
and I was buried up to my neck in
sand and the storm was coming in
and we only had a couple
minutes to get this take.
And it was like God's grace
just came in
and gave us the take
that was in the movie.
Not bad.
I loved the first movie
so much.
I was just so carried away
by the story.
It was funny. It was clever.
It was witty.
Let's face it, this is not the
worst thing you've caught me doing.
By casting Robert Downey Jr.,
they were intent on breaking
the tradition and mold
of these types of movies.
It was an
unexpected choice at the time.
And so it made
for this really dynamic,
really surprising performance.
Was that so hard?
He's so bright and so fast
and it takes you so long
to catch up with him and it's
perfect for that character.
Good luck keeping up.
I think most of us have been
pretty vocal about what he started,
and without him, none of us
would be in this position.
He really is the patriarch.
I think he really understood
the weight of the responsibility
with these movies.
Iron Man 1 changed the genre.
And I think the casting of Robert
Downey signaled to the world
that we are serious
about our characters
and we really respect
them in a way
that we're gonna hire
the best actors possible.
It really was
just this perfect storm.
I had hypnotized myself into
such a state of confidence
that I was certain...
everything
we were doing worked,
and, uh,
the rest is history.
I am Iron Man.
I'm not sure
we could have done
this notion of an interlinked
Marvel Cinematic Universe
without Captain America.
Whether it's bit by a spider
or exposed to gamma rays,
the notion of a super-powered
human started with Steve Rogers.
He is the backbone
of the universe.
As we were developing Captain
America: The First Avenger,
we brought in
these two writers
named Chris Markus
and Steve McFeely.
They were the sole writers on
the first Captain America film.
They went on
to become the sole writers
on Captain America:
The Winter Soldier,
sole writers on Civil War,
and now Infinity War
and Avengers: Endgame.
They deserve as much credit for
Captain America as anybody else.
When we were talking to them,
they had two movies out.
And so the idea that,
"No, this is going to build
"into a giant, ongoing
interconnected universe"
was like, "Uh-huh.
Yeah, sure, of course it will.
I have no doubt."
Chris and I sort of coincidentally
had been sort of blue-skying about,
"You know what someone should do.
A period superhero movie."
Right? When they were invented,
when they were created,
what would it be like to
use them in the proper time?
And then when we heard that Marvel
was going to do that, we were,
"Oh, my. We need to go
chase that down."
As for the writing,
we never worried
about the larger universe.
The mission is
always make the best
movie in front of you,
because this whole thing
is dependent on making
good movies one at a time.
We had the same goal in
the first Captain America.
We subtitled the Captain
America film "The First Avenger"
for a reason,
because putting a star
in red, white and blue
on that scrawny kid
who yearns to be
a part of the battle,
that is where it all started.
We knew that
the movie wouldn't work
if you didn't buy
Steve Rogers at the top.
I don't like bullies.
I don't care
where they're from.
Well, there are already so
many big men fighting this war.
Maybe what we need now
is the little guy, huh?
The spectacle and
the action sequences only work
if you're engaged
in the characters.
You know,
all the visual effects
and it doesn't matter
how big your budget is,
if you're not engaged in
Steve Rogers/Captain America,
I think you're
wasting your time, really.
We needed to fall in
love with skinny Steve Rogers
before he ever became
Captain America.
- And never forget that he's in there.
- Yeah.
The serum amplifies
everything that is inside,
so good becomes great,
bad becomes worse.
This is why
you were chosen.
Because a strong man who
has known power all his life
may lose respect
for that power.
But a weak man
knows the value of strength.
Steve Rogers,
more than any of the other superheroes,
really kind of loses
who he was
in the process of becoming Captain America.
The old him ceases to exist.
There's no life of Steve
Rogers that he goes back to.
In The Avengers,
he's the leader
because he's completely
dedicated to everything,
partially because he doesn't
have anything else to turn to.
His desire to keep it
ordered and to keep some meaning,
all that stuff
is still an issue for him.
He's always been
this very austere kind of guy,
but had this real loyalty
to institutions and to people.
We have orders.
We should follow them.
Following's not
really my style.
I think they slowly
strip that away from him.
You know, he loses his faith in
government in Winter Soldier.
He loses his faith in his friends
and his family in Civil War.
You know, I think when we
see him in Infinity War,
he's just turned his back
on a lot of things.
Earth just lost
her best defender,
so we're here to fight.
And if you want
to stand in our way,
we'll fight you, too.
With this movie,
they let him kind of return back to that
hopeful soldier, leader.
This is the fight
of our lives...
and we're gonna win.
Whatever it takes.
When we first
met the folks at Marvel,
we chased
the Captain America job
and certainly had no idea
that it would lead to the
next 10 years of our career.
And we've had Cap
most of the way.
It's been a lot of fun having
someone with that gravity.
It's a rare character.
You don't get to write
that character much anymore.
He's an aspirational figure.
It's a combination of where
we put him in the universe
and Cap rising
to the challenge.
You just don't know
when to give up, do you?
I can do this all day.
When our characters
are beginning to come to life,
it all starts with artwork.
Our visual development group,
led by Ryan Meinerding for
the better part of a decade,
has been
that very important step
between the comics
and the final product
that has brought
Captain America to life.
One of the great things
about the comics
is that Captain America
was always designed
to read really quickly.
And also, because they had
limited colors in the printing,
there's a simplification that
happened with a lot of them,
that they were just, you know,
this guy's red, white and blue.
There's a really fast,
iconic thing that happens
with the characters
as the source material.
Trying to bring that into a real
setting, like for a film,
whatever they simplified
for the design for the comics,
we're trying to fill out in a
way that makes it feel real.
If they only had line work
and four colors
and they're able to make something
that resonates with people
for 60, 70 years, how can we find
a way of putting it into our work?
In the case
with Captain America,
we're trying to find
reference materials
that bring him into sort
of the world of a soldier.
The first time
he puts on the costume
in Captain America:
First Avenger,
it's about him being that sort of
patriotic icon that's on the...
In the USO show.
So that was
where we were trying
to sort of take
those really classic
and iconic lines that were
designed back in the '40s
and turn it into something
that was always kind of meant
to be a little bit goofy,
sort of put him on stage and say,
"You're a symbol for America.
"Show us how much
of a symbol you are."
"Not all of us can storm
a beach or drive a tank,
"but there's still a way
all of us can fight."
One of the amazing things about
being able to work on a character
through multiple movies
is that you actually get
to tell the story of the
character through the costume.
Seeing Cap's change from Captain
America: The First Avenger
through Avengers and into Winter
Soldier, for example,
is a pretty big
visual change.
Being a person in the 1940s
and coming forward into 2012
and sort of living
in that period of time
and being a fish-out-of-water
and then sort of acclimating
very quickly and becoming
this very stealth-orientated,
extreme tactical ops person
is a crazy change.
And it worked
so well because...
Partially because the costume actually
reflects what he's going through.
What made Cap unique
in the Marvel Universe
and sort of in the nature
of his powers, he's sort of
basically a man,
only more so.
His fighting technique's
a very visceral,
surprising experience
of action.
From a visual standpoint,
you take the script
and you identify, like,
10 great moments
in the movie
and then you take
a brilliant artist, like Ryan,
and you say, "Here's what we're
looking for from this moment."
And then Ryan draws up
and colors and inks
a beautiful,
you know, frame
from the movie.
Before we get started,
does anyone want to get out?
They do
incorporate lighting.
They incorporate a strong visual
element, where will the camera be,
in a very, you know, sort of
dynamic and specific moment.
And that does
inspire the movie.
For Captain America,
almost every iconic sequence came
right out of Ryan's original drawings,
where he was just by himself with
his drawing pad at his computer.
I've been at Marvel
for about 12 years,
which is almost
the entire time
that Marvel Studios
has existed.
There's a sort of a craziness to the notion
that I've been able
to stay with the character
over the course of nine years.
Being that sort of medium
between the comics
and what is actually
on the screen
has been a joy that
I couldn't have imagined.
When we really distilled
the core qualities
that we wanted
out of Captain America,
I think there's
a moral fiber to him
that really isn't
something that you act,
that it's something
you need to possess.
And Chris Evans was someone
who seemed to inhabit all
of those qualities the most.
So everyone was in love
with the idea of Chris,
except Chris.
The only reason there
was hesitation to begin with
was because of the commitment.
It's a big movie
and, you know,
those are the movies
that if they succeed,
there's a change,
a lifestyle change.
And if it fails,
it's a whole other can of worms.
Even Chris's reluctance
to be a star...
spoke to how right
he was for the role
because Captain America was
not looking for the limelight.
He was humble. He was modest.
He needed to feel that
in his bones.
I love the character.
He's everything that I wish
I could be as a man, you know.
And the creative forces
behind the film are fantastic,
between Joe and Kevin Feige.
I mean, you know,
Marvel in general,
they know what they're doing,
so in the end, I was so excited.
Once he committed,
he committed 1,000%.
You know, he stands there,
tells the truth and then kicks ass.
I think there's a confidence
that he really brings
to the character
and an integrity
that people really respond to.
There's something so endearing,
so charismatic, so charming.
He has so much heart.
There was something very heroic.
There is something that
he brings to the character
beyond what we could
write on the page,
beyond what we could illustrate
in, you know, special effects
that is uniquely Chris.
It's no secret,
I love Chris Evans.
And I love Captain America.
Captain America was the single hardest
character to launch in this universe.
This kind of guy out of time,
and is it too retro?
Are people going to get it?
I cannot imagine
anybody but Chris
playing this role.
It's really... It's a very difficult
role to play because on one hand,
you have this character that has
this very strong moral compass
and you try to think,
"Where's the conflict in that?"
He allows himself
to be vulnerable,
but he allows himself
to not take it so seriously.
- Don't worry about it. It's just a...
- What's that do?
He makes you love
that character,
and it makes people
want to follow him.
It's been really great
watching him sort of pull this off.
What he does in these movies
may look effortless,
but it's effortless
because, you know,
it's a testament to what
he's done with the character.
It's tough to try
and present challenges
to someone who is so selfless.
The biggest worry is not only
trying to make the guy entertaining,
but also keep him
interesting enough
to have audiences
want him coming back.
Every time I see Evans,
he's like more
and more like Cap.
It's like we've invested him
with that.
And Chris is up for that
because that's what makes it
exciting and different.
There's this huge amount
of love for the character.
There's 20 Captain America
shirts wherever I go.
It's ceased to become
just about him
and how well he inhabited
the role and all that stuff.
It's become part of our
culture just as a symbol.
It's that thing that gives you kind
of, you know, teenage goosebumps.
I think we have a lot emotionally
invested in Cap as a character.
We have a lot emotionally
invested in Chris
as a friend
and a collaborator.
It's a proud moment
to be able to sit back
and look at
with perspective,
the journey that
that character's gone on.
You're looking at
yourself in this old makeup
and you're trying
to tap into Steve's journey,
but you can't help
but think about your own
and think about what this entire
experience has meant to you.
It's just been littered
with so many good memories.
They never want to work, these
kids, but I'll get them there.
It is
because of this journey,
of just such
an embarrassment of riches
and such good fortune
and just good luck.
And again,
it's just so unblemished
because there's so many
wonderful people around me.
This has been such an
incredible chapter in my life.
We'd love to take this character
in every different direction.
I think she certainly encounters her
fair share of the Marvel Universe.
It's nice to be able to play
a superheroine who has a past.
You know, she obviously has been
around for over, what, 40 years.
And I think
has a real foundation
for all different kinds
of spinoffs
or interactions
with other characters.
I think the possibilities
are really endless.
In Iron Man 2,
the part that appealed to me most
about her was her dedication
and just her intelligence.
I think you need smart people
in a movie like that.
There's too much
up for grabs.
There's too many things
that change.
And you need somebody who's going
to be a steward of their character.
"Cordon off all access
to the track
- "and clear the airspace for whoever needs."
- We got it?
- Here we go.
- Ding!
Scarlett was just a dream.
You know, she's so game.
And she had a really good time doing it.
I'm my own,
my own secret weapon.
Unlike some of us, uh,
older, uh, curmudgeons,
there's very little you can do
to get under her skin.
She's just
consummately professional.
I love
playing this character.
When we first met Natasha
in Iron Man 2
she was Natalie and, you know, you got
to see her, kind of, undercover work
and, you know,
it wasn't until the end of that film
her true identity was revealed
as an agent of S.H.I.E.L.D.
You are mind-blowingly duplicitous.
How do you do it?
You just tear things.
You're a triple imposter.
I've never seen
anything like you.
Is there anything
real about you?
- Do you even speak Latin?
- Fallaces sunt rerum species.
Which means? Wait, what?
What'd you just say?
It means you can either
drive yourself home
or I can
have you collected.
In Avengers, we see,
of course, her in her own environment.
Just like Budapest
all over again!
You and I remember Budapest
very differently.
We get to see a
little bit more of who she is,
a little bit of her history,
of her, kind of, shady past.
I got red in my ledger,
I'd like to wipe it out.
Can you wipe out
that much red?
Dreykov's daughter? Sao Paulo?
The hospital fire?
Your ledger is dripping.
It's gushing red.
You pretend to be separate,
to have your own code,
something that makes up
for the horrors,
but they are part of you.
And they will never go away.
With the second Cap,
the character starts to
question her own identity,
question her own choices.
I thought I knew
whose lies I was telling,
but I guess I can't
tell the difference anymore.
She's an isolated
character.
Cap doesn't know whether
he can trust her or not,
so she is not part
of the family, per se,
because she's never been taught to
rely on anyone other than herself.
And she has a view of the world
that is skeptical, and cynical,
and her and Cap grow over
the course of that movie
and he teaches her trust.
You know, it's kind of hard
to trust someone
when you don't know
who that someone really is.
Who do you want me to be?
How 'bout a friend?
Well, there's a chance
you might be
in the wrong business,
Rogers.
In Avengers 2,
she really, you know,
allowed herself to want things
and to envision a life for
herself outside of the things
that have kind of
fallen upon her.
I have no place
in the world.
Exactly.
And you realize
how strong she was
to have come out
the other side
and to be a part
of this very heroic team.
Her past is something
that's always been shrouded in mystery
and, you know, we continue
to open up the story,
give little, kind of, tidbits
and throw the bone out
once in a while
as to where she came from
and what her background is.
I had this dream,
the kind that seems normal
at the time,
but when you wake...
What did you dream?
That I was an Avenger.
That I was anything more than
the assassin they made me.
In Civil War,
she starts to realize
that the Avengers
are her family.
And she makes a choice to
try to preserve the family.
We've made
some very public mistakes.
We need to win
their trust back.
That's what makes
this character really heroic
is that she's, kind of,
dug her heels in and said,
"Look, you know, I could
kind of go down this road,
"which would be the more
desirable road personally,
"and disappear and live off the map."
But she chooses this,
kind of, greater calling.
Just because it's
the path of least resistance
doesn't mean
it's the wrong path.
Staying together is more important
than how we stay together.
Part of the reason
why the Avengers failed
in Infinity War
is because they were divided,
because of the fallout of Civil War.
Natasha's a very
strategic fighter
and she I think is really just
trying to give whatever she can
in order to save as
many people as possible.
He did exactly what
he said he was gonna do.
Thanos wiped out 50%
of all living creatures.
At the beginning of Endgame,
she wants to bring it all back
because she feels like it is the
strongest emotional connection
that she's ever had in her life.
She's struggling to deal
with the fact that they lost.
And she hasn't stopped.
Five years later,
she's still fighting
to figure out how to fix this
problem and she hasn't let go.
She has to do everything in her
power to undo what Thanos did.
She's presented with a choice:
she has to give her own life
to bring everyone else back
and she does it,
which is the most,
single most heroic moment
in the history
of the Marvel Universe.
It's okay.
I actually think
that in some weird,
and it is
a very emotional thing,
but some weird
twisted-up fateful way,
this character who, you know,
has searched her
whole life for a purpose,
actually finds her purpose.
And it's like this amazing,
super-emotional, beautiful thing.
You know what I've become.
Oh, I don't judge people
on their worst mistakes.
Maybe you should.
You didn't.
I feel very fortunate.
It's been an incredible gift as an actor
to be able to come back to a character
that's as complex as Natasha.
I think there's, kind of,
a lot to explore there
and that is so exciting.
Cars are coming
down the middle
as our heroes are running
this way and this way.
Love the Russos.
I remember them the first
couple days on Winter Soldier.
They really felt like the
new kids on the playground.
But everything they said they
were gonna do, they delivered on.
Their attitude kind of breeds
this sort of lightness on set.
Let's do one more.
They're the filmmakers
that took
the Captain America series
and elevated it
with the Winter Soldier.
"Gotta know, Cap.
This isn't personal."
And then you...
But then did it again
with Civil War.
That film is gigantic.
This is gonna be
a great shot.
We were midway through
production on Civil War,
and we saw the amazing job that
Anthony and Joe were doing,
handling all these
different characters,
telling this
very unique storyline.
It's going kind of this way right now
and then the window's gonna shatter.
Yeah. And then...
We knew where we wanted to head
with the next Avengers film,
and it was then that we
started talking to them
about coming from Civil War
onto Infinity War.
We had no time to settle between
Civil War and Infinity War.
As we were conceiving
and executing Civil War,
the end of that movie
was very much a setup
for what these movies
would be.
We always had
the sense of that.
Even not having a break,
I think we were able
to move forward
because there is such a
continuity in the narrative.
In Infinity War, the scope of the
film, I think, is unrivaled.
And really, the only way
the film could be made
was in the hands
of Anthony and Joe Russo.
That was an A-plus
version of the shot.
I was really blown away
by how culturally powerful
it was.
I've never seen a reaction
like that after a movie.
Infinity War takes people
on an epic quest
that does everything
from entertain
and delight you to
devastate you emotionally.
The success of that film
is certainly a testament
to the Russo brothers
as a directing team.
There's no doubt
it was not an easy task.
You look at Infinity War,
you're in the hands
of master filmmakers.
It is truly remarkable.
Slow it down just a hair and just
turn it into a little bit of a...
Yeah. Sure.
You know, like, "I'm getting...
I'm gonna get," you know.
Give it a little look and then go with it.
Okay? Here we go.
We talk a lot about the
culmination of Avengers: Endgame.
We wanted to do a great finale
that not only had the spectacle
worthy of Infinity War,
but with sequences and scenes
and character interactions
that could only be done
with Joe and Anthony.
They're the only directors that
could handle this many characters
and doing this
ambitious of a story
that needs to pay off every
film that we've ever made
in one climactic conclusion,
while at the same time,
introducing an entirely
new direction for the future.
When we were thinking
about these two Avengers films,
we came up with this idea,
let's shoot them together.
And it seemed like
a great idea at the time,
but it's impossible
to juggle one story.
And the idea of two stories
this complicated,
figuring out what they are,
how they intertwine.
The Russos are so adept at
handling complicated storylines.
You know, after the camera
whips to you...
- Yeah.
- Take in the group for a beat,
and then ask
where's Fury.
You have to understand
what makes
each character unique,
what special qualities
they bring to it,
how they can shine.
It's pretty amazing
watching these brothers, like,
create these amazing,
powerfully epic tales.
Go that way?
Well, that'll just be
the badass delivery.
You feel very, you know,
safe and taken care of
and at the same time,
you feel like you can contribute.
I'm clearly
charting the course.
And then you just come in
and start charting the course.
- Yeah.
- You're like...
Uh, we're going to...
Where to?
The magic trick is
that they're working with
so many actors that have,
you know, their own
relationship to the characters
that come from their own
sort of parts of the universe.
And to make that
all into something
that feels cohesive
is incredible.
- So, it's all in one piece.
- So it's gonna be like...
- It's focused at the end of it.
- Boom.
Go back to the stake.
They've done
the unthinkable, really.
I mean, it's not
just two movies back to back.
It's the two biggest movies
of all time,
and they've been at the helm
the whole time without fail.
They love these characters,
and they know
these characters inside out.
Anthony and Joe,
they've essentially been on a job
for six, seven years now.
And I love them.
And they love the Avengers.
Joe and I have
always loved to figure out,
"How do we take the character
and how do we take the audience
"and how do we take ourselves
on a surprising journey
"that is not
holding anything back?"
As you progress
through films like that,
your job as directors
gets bigger and bigger.
We really have
an amazing team around us
that allow us to focus
on the bigger picture,
so we're very happy
with this experience.
It's been really exciting
to get to work
with some of the actors
from different franchises
that I have just admired that,
I guess you could say,
are sort of an extended family.
And then of course,
there's new characters
that are also being
introduced to the family.
Where are you going?
To kill Thanos.
It's certainly
great to see that
the audiences are embracing and
even asking for, begging for
really strong
female superheroes.
It's wonderful to feel
like you've witnessed
and been a part
of that growth.
I'm always picking up
after you boys.
I think one of the dangers
of playing a kickass chick
is that you just mimic what
you've always seen kickass men do.
You want to show me
how to punch? Go ahead.
That's how you punch.
It's really important
for me to find
the voice and the rhythm
and the style
and the meaning of what
it means to be a powerful woman.
And that that be
its own distinct thing.
I so enjoy being
able to be a piece in the puzzle
that was a woman
who was the head of an army
and who was the right-hand
"man" of the leader.
And seeing how that resonated was
very humbling and very moving.
Women are demanding
equality in the workplace,
whether you're in a superhero
costume or an office job.
And I think Marvel
is doing a great job
of amplifying that
in the films
and representing
that properly.
And that's a beautiful thing.
Every morning, I think about
every way that I can help women
have representation
and be out there in the world.
And I think for me
it's important
for women to know
that it can be done.
Hi, I'm Peter Parker.
Hey, Peter Parker.
You got something for me?
Our goal with Endgame was to
provide a climactic conclusion
to the journey
that the MCU has been on
for these 11 years now.
And so we spent a lot of
time looking backwards
at the journey that the
overarching narrative has taken
and all the characters that
have been a part of that story.
And I remember it just
dawning on all of us one day,
just, like, the sheer number
of amazing female characters
that were now in the MCU,
which is so exciting
and impressive to all of us.
I mean, we really looked for an
opportunity to just celebrate that.
You could just see
this really beautiful thing,
which you kind of
get a taste of
with Avengers: Infinity War
as well,
which is very powerful
people meeting each other,
powerful people
all being in one room,
powerful people that all
have very specific skills
working together
to form a team.
We have a smaller moment
in the Wakanda field
in Infinity War,
where we have Okoye,
Natasha and Wanda
teaming up to fight Proxima.
And that moment in the trench
was pretty spectacular to see
when we were
shooting Infinity War,
and we wanted a little bit
more of that in Avengers 4.
I don't know how you're gonna
get it through all of that.
Don't worry.
She's got help.
It was really beautiful
to feel
this sort of Marvel
sisterhood, you know,
and we're all coming from so
many different films
that we all came together.
It was kind of like,
"I see what you do.
I know your powers. Okay.
"Show me what you've got,"
and then we just clicked.
And we were just, like,
cheering each other on.
Everyone just kind of
taking their turns
moving around,
trying to help each other out.
It was so fun.
- You share...
- Exactly.
- ...this connection, you know.
- So there's a connection
- without ever having met.
- Yeah.
It's a really cool thing
about the whole battle.
That day was insane.
We were all in it together
and it felt electric.
It was really, really cool.
Three, and action!
You know, I normally don't
watch playback on the monitor,
but I wanted to see that reveal
of all the women of Marvel,
and I thought
it was really powerful
and really exhilarating.
And I was thinking of all of
the young girls in the audience
who will probably feel
really inspired by that
in one way or another.
So, it was a really nice
thing to be a part of.
And it's exciting
'cause all of us are saying,
"I've never
experienced this before.
"I've never been in a film
with this many women
"and this many strong women
who stand equal to the men."
There is something
very powerful
and we're realizing it
more and more,
just how magical it is
to allow women to express
their full gamut of their power
and their abilities
as a unit.
- What's wrong with him?
- Oh, he's pissed.
He thinks he failed.
Thor has suffered
tremendous loss,
more so than
any other character.
Asgard has been destroyed,
and now he has to suffer
the loss to Thanos.
How does a person who's suffered
two devastating losses like that
move forward,
and how would he process that?
Boys!
Every aspect of him
was broken.
Some tragic things have
happened and he's decided,
"You know what?
I'm just gonna check out
"and eat pizza
and drink beer."
And that's what he's done,
you know.
You all right?
Yes. I'm fine. Why?
Why, don't I look all right?
You look like
melted ice cream.
So, what's up?
You just here for a hang?
He's a very depressed
sort of removed Thor,
becoming the opposite of what
we've known him to be in the past.
I know you think
I'm down here
wallowing in my own
self-pity...
feeling sorry for myself,
hoping to be rescued,
hoping to be saved,
but you're wrong, okay?
But the great thing
about Thor is, like,
there's something in his
spirit that stands in contrast
to where he's let himself go
physically and emotionally.
There's beer on the ship.
What kind?
Being able to do
this new version of Thor,
it's hugely liberating
and fun.
We had a big sort of fat suit,
which I think was
sort of 60 or 70 pounds.
This'll move.
Yep,
that's the shimmy.
It was the hottest
I've ever been.
How does that feel?
I mean, amazing.
It looks like
it's in the right place.
And we have,
obviously, the beard, the hair,
and I have these things
that go in the mouth
to kind of plump out
my cheeks a bit,
which sort of had a little
effect on the voice as well,
but probably in a good way.
It was a different Thor.
Hi, my name's Thor.
I'm 22 years old,
live on Asgard
and I like sugar.
We're shooting
a superhero film
and here's one of the most
recognizable superheroes,
but he's just turned
into a new character.
What Chris does
with that character
and how it just
kind of has this shift,
his excitement
was really palpable.
He'd been playing
the character for a while
and really wanted
to find something new.
He has such dexterity
as a talent.
He's incredibly funny.
He has just
really lovely energy.
Is he asleep?
No, no.
I'm pretty sure he's dead.
Thor's new look will seem
like it's being played for laughs.
But thanks to the performance
that Chris Hemsworth gives,
it becomes very touching.
Let me, just let me,
let me do this.
Let me do something right.
And we see
over the course of the film,
how he tries to regain
his sense of purpose
and regain
his sense of redemption.
It's not working.
At the end of the day,
even though he's carrying
a lot more weight,
he's still the Thor
that we love.
I'm still worthy.
The Avengers
pull him back in.
To have a sense of duty,
he finally comes around
and he's a full-on Avenger,
with carrying another 80 pounds, though.
Look at
the first couple steps.
I thought I was booking.
I thought
I was going so quick.
Maybe you want
to give a battle cry.
Oh, yeah.
Good one there.
It felt like I was playing a
completely different character.
There was a real opportunity to
just kind of swing for the fences
and it was so much fun.
What do you think
is coursing through my veins?
Cocoa Puffs? Nachos?
Embarrassment?
Lightning.
Asking a woman to dance
always seems so terrifying.
And the past few years just
didn't seem to matter that much.
- Figured I'd wait.
- For what?
Right partner.
The essential conflict
in Steve
is the desire to serve.
And that desire to serve would
supersede his personal identity.
He's got an amazing set
of morals and values.
He's an incredibly good man,
given the hand that life
has dealt him.
Doctors kinda know that if this
guy is given this great gift,
he won't
take advantage of it.
He understands
how to value what he has
'cause he didn't always
have it.
The common issue
among all the Marvel heroes
is that they have a very
vulnerable side to them.
And Steve Rogers is certainly
no exception to that.
He is probably
the most vulnerable
before he becomes
Captain America.
He, more that any
of the other superheroes,
really, kind of,
loses who he was
in the process
of becoming him.
'Cause he was a scrawny,
90-pound man,
who gets changed into
Captain America.
So the old him
ceases to exist.
There's no life of Steve
Rogers that he goes back to.
Almost,
I get the feeling,
he'd be more comfortable if he
could wear the outfit all the time
because then he has
a persona.
Then he knows who he is.
That's the first time
he was valued,
he had very few people
who valued him.
He wasn't quite
an orphan
but he was alone
fairly early on
and he had one friend.
It was Bucky Barnes,
and Bucky Barnes goes off to war.
And he was a scrappy kid
who got picked on all his life.
He is very relatable.
He is a superhero.
But all his power is basically
what the human body can do.
Once circumstances lead
him to being Captain America,
he finds, you know,
a purpose.
You told me you thought I
was meant for more than this.
Did you mean that?
Every word.
Peggy has a career.
And she has a lot of
self-respect.
And she's pretty sick
and tired
of lots of men kind of
not taking her
seriously in the Army,
and you know,
playing around with her.
I think Peggy relates to someone really
fighting for what they believe in
and really having to struggle
all the time to prove themselves.
And, she being the only
woman in this environment,
knows exactly what
that feels like.
It's not just the normal,
everyday love story.
There's something else.
In the same way
that we love Steve,
because he exhibits
some sort of determination
and selflessness,
that's the same thing
that attracts her to him.
Steve learned a lot
from Peggy Carter.
If you go back and look
at The First Avenger,
that is
the essential relationship
that I think turned him
into who he is today.
It turned him
into Captain America.
Her sense of integrity,
her call to action are all
qualities that have been engrained
in Steve
and are his best qualities.
And they come from
an example, from Peggy.
And so I think it was
critical that her character
embody
those essential qualities
because he wouldn't be
who he is without them.
I'm gonna need a rain check
on that dance.
A week, next Saturday
at the Stork Club.
You got it.
8:00 on the dot.
Don't you dare be late.
The great tragedy
of Steve Rogers' existence
was, now he found
he love of his life
and then,
had to sacrifice himself,
and 70 years of his life
to save the world.
I always found it
very endearing about Cap,
that for all that character
has sacrificed,
and he's sacrificed a lot.
But one thing he could
never let go of was Peggy.
And it just stayed with
him all those years.
It's been so long.
So long.
Well, I couldn't leave
my best girl.
Not when she owes
me a dance.
We want the audiences
to feel moved by it.
People have sent me poems that
they've written about Peggy and Cap,
and montages
that they've sent me
of Peggy and Cap's
greatest moments,
putting, like, soundtracks
over them,
like Aerosmith soundtracks
or something,
with longing looks
from Peggy and Cap.
And I'm realizing that the
story has affected them.
And that's great 'cause we feel
like that's what we wanted.
We wanted something
that had heart to it
that people,
essentially, cared about.
Even after he died, Steve
was still changing my life.
I really like what they let
my character experience
in these movies,
to be honest,
the struggle
and the sacrifice
and the culmination
of friendships
that have had peaks
and valleys.
And it's just a really
layered, colorful experience.
His arc over the course
of the movies
take him
from a place of service,
to where he started
to question authority
and ultimately
embrace his identity
and become
self-actualized.
And he has the opportunity
in Avengers: Endgame
to go back
and correct the loss
and be with Peggy,
the love of his life.
And he makes that choice.
So, did something go wrong
or did something go right?
Well, after I
put the stones back,
I thought...
Maybe I'll...
try some of that life
Tony was
telling me to get.
You're trying' to tap into Steve's
journey before you go to set
to understand what this moment
means to him.
But you can't help but think
about your own.
And think about what
this entire experience
has meant to you.
God, you can get choked up even
thinking about it right now.
You wanna tell me
about her?
No.
No, I don't think I will.
Are these our gojis?
- They're not.
- What's wrong with ours?
- Your alpaca ate them all.
- Oh.
- All of them.
- What a glowing endorsement.
First of all,
Gerald is our alpaca.
He's not my alpaca
if he's eating my gojis.
Okay. They're gonna be nice in
the salad right there, right?
No, don't, don't, don't!
Could you put it down?
- Get out of my kitchen.
- Okay.
Whoops.
- We're good here, right?
- Yeah, we're great.
Tell Madam Secretary
that lunch is in five.
I will collect
our alpha female posthaste.
And what happened
to the Tesseract after that?
It's at the bottom
of the ocean.
It fell out of the plane
after I had to crash it.
Yeah, I've been
meaning to ask,
why did you have
to crash the plane anyway?
There were bombs onboard.
Bombs onboard.
And you couldn't have jumped out of
the plane before you crashed it?
How long
did you fight these guys?
About, uh,
two or three hours.
Hours?
The Chitauri are the
suckiest army in the galaxy.
Why didn't you just
blow up the mother ship?
We didn't know
that was a thing.
You didn't know
that was a thing?
Everyone knows... Hey!
There we go.
All clear. Which way?
Oh.
You say something?
I said
I want to claw my eyes out.
But unfortunately,
it wouldn't do any good
'cause I already
saw the awfulness.
- Will you focus?
- I'm focused.
This pretty place is about
to get uglified real quick
by a bunch of frickin' elves.
Do you know that I saw
all these people die?
So this is a little bit
difficult for me, okay?
So why don't you
reach down deep inside
and try and find
a small ounce of humanity?
Just give me the thingy.
"Just give me the thingy.
Just give me the thingy."
I didn't even
want to come here.
Reliving all these
repressed memories.
- My God, get it together.
- Get it together.
You're embarrassing.
All right.
Which way?
I don't know.
You don't know?
You used to frickin' live here!
For 1,500 years.
Not forever.
That way, I think.
Yeah. Maybe.
We are dead.
We are so, so dead.
I get it. It's nutty,
it's crazy-making
'cause you start worrying
about a legacy, you know.
You want to leave them
the better world,
and then you realize you haven't
done all that much to give them one,
and it's...
What's your name, again?
- Potts.
Yeah.
You want to come work
for me, Potts?
I'm a little tied up
in futures right now.
Nobody pull a hamstring.
Warm your butt cheeks up.
Warm up your butt cheeks!
Cut there.
Copy that!
There you go, ya cub.
I broke it.
Fill.
Action!
No, no, not yet.
All right, here we go.
The thing about time travel...
It's more important
to look marvelous
than to feel marvelous.
I can't believe
I made a whole movie
with this thing on.
This is...
Yeah, does it
look cool or...
Yeah.
It looks cool. Right?
It doesn't feel cool, but if it looks
cool, that's what matters.
Do you have any idea
what's coursing
through my veins right now?
Funyuns?
Yes!
Orange soda?
We are getting the whole team,
aren't we? A duck!
There, good one.
You see what I have to deal with here?
Ten years of this...
♪ Her synaptic drive
was probably ♪
♪ damaged in battle ♪
♪ Her synaptic drive was
badly damaged in battle ♪
Are you sure
you want to 90210 this?
Fix Star-Lord's hair.
Whoo!
Turn her off!
I feel like I've given you
all you could ever want.
God, it seems
like a thousand years ago.
I fought my way
out of that cave,
became Iron Man,
realized I loved you.
I know I said
no more surprises,
but I was really hoping
to pull off one last one.
The really unique thing
about Endgame for Joe and I
was that this movie
was the ending.
Marvel and Kevin Feige
have certainly done something
singular in cinematic history.
We really want to bring that
same experience to the audience.
We want them to feel the
fullest range of emotion,
because we feel like that
creates the most complete ending.
Our goal was
to deliver an experience
that felt like
a very satisfying,
surprising,
yet fitting ending to this narrative
that they've been following
for these many years
and these characters that
they've loved for so long.
Avengers...
assemble.
It's about as massive a
production as you can mount.
You really have to have an
incredible team of collaborators
that you're working with,
so it's been a very
special experience for us.
There's an energy
here on set
that comes from everybody's
dedication and character
and belief in what we're doing,
that what we're doing is
important and matters to people.
Everybody recognizes,
I think, in the cast
what an amazing opportunity
these movies are,
and they know that it's going
to take everybody's best effort
to pull them off properly,
so the collaborative energy
that every one of these actors
brings to set every day
is really remarkable
and a big part of the magic
of these movies.
Ladies and gentlemen!
That's a wrap!
These are all people
that for literally the last seven years,
uninterrupted,
we have been collaborating with.
They've been
like family to us.
We're going to miss everyone.
This has been
such a rare opportunity.
It's the opportunity
of a career.
And I think
we look at it like that,
and I think
everybody involved does,
so this time that we've spent
at Marvel is irreplaceable.
Yeah.