Hey, this is Joss Whedon, um,
doing an unprecedented concept
of a director's commentary.
Um... I have a lot to say.
I have no idea what it's going to be,
or what order it's going to come in.
But if you like the sound of me babbling,
you're in for a treat.
Why on earth would I make
another Avengers movie?
They're really hard. It was...
It was ill-advised. I see that now.
(DISTANT EXPLOSION)
But I think the most important thing
about the movie is that it's mine.
That it's all me,
and that really because
I'm the director and the writer,
I really created it all myself.
I think that's important to bear in mind.
Especially because,
while I've been talking,
you've already seen
the work of two other directors,
not to mention
the insanely large village,
possibly a metropolitan area,
full of people who are working
in every frame
to fulfil whatever vision
it was I thought I had.
One thing about this movie
that you're gonna hear a lot
is how extraordinary the crew,
the post, the pre, uh,
the production people,
how they not just carried or fulfilled,
but inspired this movie,
which begins with
this rather iconic image.
Um...
A very deliberate decision on my part
was to start off with the hardest thing
in the movie from the first one,
what we refer to as the "tie-in shot."
Rather than getting
the Avengers back together,
I wanted to say right up front,
"No, they're in it.
"And here's the very climax
of the first film.
"Here's the very thing
you always showed up for,
"all of these guys in one enormous shot
"with a big slow-mo, kind of,
uh, comic book panel moment."
And my original concept had been that
the very first frame
would be the slow-motion part.
Kevin Feige very rightly argued
that without some context,
people just wouldn't know
what they were seeing, um,
and wouldn't appreciate it as much
as they would at the end of the shot.
Which, um, turned out to be very true.
When I talk about the other directors...
There was a short shot
of people running up the stairs
that my producer, Jeremy Latcham,
went ahead and got
with our "C" cameraman, Sam,
while we were in Dover Castle,
which is right here and played
as the interior of the fortress.
Um...
We were mostly stuck in big,
beautiful rooms filled with equipment,
and there are
so many lovely little spaces.
He said, "Shouldn't we go
and get soldiers running about,
"and show some
of the stairwells and the halls,
"and all the things that make this space
more than just big rooms?"
And we ended up
using a lot of that footage.
It was just grand.
And, of course, the other director
I'm referring to is John Mahaffie,
who is an actual director,
um, the second-unit director,
who shot so much great footage
for this movie.
I shot about 100 days, he shot over 50.
And some of them are elaborate.
That's another,
what I was referring to before.
Some of the more elaborate stuff
inevitably gets shot by second unit
because the characters in it are CG,
and requires camera setups
that take hours and hours.
And so on the one hand,
(IN BRITISH ACCENT)
I, being the most important director,
(IN NORMAL VOICE)
the director of the first unit,
I'm busy getting really
the heart of the piece,
and he's getting these secondary shots.
Except that the "secondary shots"
he was getting,
I just used air quotes,
you can't tell, but I did,
were very much
some of the most beautiful footage
that was shot in the film.
And I started to feel
like Reaction-Shot Joe.
I would just see these glorious things
he'd stitch together, and then I'd...
There'd be a close-up
of somebody reacting to it.
I was like, "That's me! I did that.
I'm also a part of the team."
Um...
Because the team
is how this gets done.
You're gonna find that's also part
of what we have to say in the movie.
But in the making of the movie,
it's very much the same thing.
Both of these guys,
Thomas Kretschmann
and Henry Goodman,
extraordinary thespians, who would
come in to do smaller roles.
I actually said, "If we made a movie
with only the day players..."
They worked more than that,
but just literally people
who were there for just a day.
"...we'd have the most star-studded
cast you could work with."
It's wonderful.
It's probably a terrible thing
about the industry
that you can get amazing actors
to play these smaller roles
in franchise films, but it works for me.
So I asked the question,
"Why would I do this, again?"
And the main answer was
because I wanted to make a new movie.
A different Avengers movie.
And while providing the things
that people expect
from the Avengers movie,
i.e. the tie-in shot that you saw before,
I also wanted to not just tell
a different story, but tell it differently.
And a lot of that can be seen
in the editing and framing
and general style, the lenses.
In the first film, I was very slavish to 3D.
I was playing it as though
anything not in the vernacular of3D
was going to be
confusing for the audience.
And in the couple of years in-between,
it became clear that,
that isn't really the case.
And, besides, 3D really spoke
to the way I was used to shooting.
I like wide lenses.
I like understanding
the space around me very clearly.
I didn't like a lot of heavy cutting.
I liked shots that would deliberately go
from one place to another,
very old-fashioned.
For the second film, I wanted to do
something unlike
anything I had really done.
It's a little bit like the film
I shot right before,
Much Ado About Nothing,
which was kind of...
We had a bunch of great actors
standing around,
speaking Shakespeare,
and, as often as possible,
three cameras,
occasionally four, at least two,
getting them.
And quick side note,
the mercenary who speaks right here...
SOLDIER: No, it wasn't.
WHEDON: That was a bit I added
very late in editing.
And that's actually Jeffrey Ford,
one of the editors,
who just, uh, did it on a mic in the room,
and we liked it so well, we kept it.
You're also gonna hear his name
and Lisa Lassek's name,
those editors who...
I don't wanna say saved my life,
but I just did.
They are so much a part of
everything that works in this movie.
I'm incredibly grateful.
Lot of moving parts,
partially because of the way, um, I, uh...
As I said,
I wanted to shoot this differently.
Where the first one was very deliberate,
this one was deliberately casual.
Yay.
WHEDON: That little "Yay," by the way,
for which both Robert and I
have been given credit,
was actually Jeremy Latcham,
again, saying,
"He needs to make a noise there,"
um, in post-production.
And I was like, "Oh, no, he doesn't.
"We could do it,
but no one's gonna hear it."
So, he gets all the credit for that.
And we have to talk about ILM, too,
and the extraordinary work they did
with the Hulk and with Ultron.
I mean, what they did
in the first movie was amazing,
but this is a completely different level.
This is a real performance.
And even with all the reference
that Mark gave them,
it's something that has
to be crafted pixel by pixel,
and then made human.
And I can never
stop looking at these guys.
Because, again,
with all of these cameras
and this very different way of shooting,
we ended up with something like that,
an over,
where you see just a blurry shoulder.
That blurry shoulder is about
as expensive as a face.
It's something we could never do
in the first movie.
But we talked about it specifically
as wanting to have the Hulk play
a character in the film, not an effect,
and to use the same casual vernacular
when we were shooting him
as we would with
any of the other, um, players.
And their thing, the idea that Natasha
has this power over the Hulk,
and obviously
this, uh, budding romance with Banner,
really came from that scene.
That's where it all started.
The idea of the lullaby
as how they deal with him
spiralled up into the idea that
Bruce Banner and Natasha Romanoff
are actually very similar.
And so the scene
always made perfect sense to me,
and we had Scarlett's side of it,
but we really didn't have the scene
until just a few weeks
before we delivered the film.
And even I was kind of stunned
by the physicality, the sensuality,
and the emotion of that encounter.
And it's one of those things
where you all say, "This will work,"
but then you get to feel it,
and it's like nobody
ever told you about it.
It's an extraordinary thing
to work on something for two years
and not understand it until you see it.
Or not understand
the power it will have.
(GROWLING)
It's fun to kill the Avengers.
I recommend it.
I particularly like the little twitch
from the Hulk. I wanted very much
the sort of dying bison,
kind of little spasmodic thing
with the spears sticking out of him.
And they gave me that.
They gave me this broken shield.
Look carefully at the way
the shield is broken,
because that's actually something
that I put in for just a few people.
You'll see that shape again
at the end of the movie
when Wanda tears...
With her magic, she tears
Ultron's vibranium chest apart.
And we very deliberately
had her do that,
had it come apart
in the exact same shape
as his vision of disaster.
Because we wanted to say,
"She's great,
and it's great that she's so powerful,
"but what if it wasn't great?"
In a way that one-and-a-half people
would recognise.
I think I said, "Five people
in the audience will cheer at this."
And Kevin Feige said,
"Yes, but I will be one of them."
It was a big decision whether to
go off on her smile or this grab.
Ultimately,
the grab very specifically said,
"We have a problem,
and the problem is Tony."
And, um, one of the things that also
sort of hit me late in the game
is that you can really look at this film
and just straight-up say,
"Tony Stark is the villain."
It's not just the beard.
He's a good man
who is corrupted by his own anxiety,
by this vision of a disaster,
and makes what is obviously
a really bad decision.
And I spent so much time in
the writing process and during filming
trying to protect Tony Stark.
Trying to make sure
that he was still a heroic figure.
And at one point I watched the movie,
and I went, "You can just go ahead
and lean into this,
"that he's now evolved into a villain."
Obviously, he's not just that.
He's redeemed,
and he is a hero in so many ways.
But it was very freeing to be able...
And I think it's not something
you get to do a lot
in something like this, narratively.
To just go ahead and say,
"Your guy just might not be okay."
And again, that's something that,
thematically, the entire movie is about.
It's been commented on,
and it's not by accident
that the word "monster" is used
by most of the team
about either themselves or each other.
STARK: Feels good, yeah?
WHEDON: I have
a "Jarvis is my co-pilot" sticker
on my laptop.
Because how could you not?
That's one of those things
that I thought of
and asked for while we were shooting.
"Can we just throw that in?"
And the prop guys just disappeared
and came back with the perfect one.
And, of course,
it comes right after he says,
"Jarvis, take the wheel,"
so clearly we're already leaning
into the Jesus thing.
And that's, um, again, not by accident.
We're not saying anything specific
about religion,
but we are playing on
Christian iconography a great deal,
partially because both Tony Stark
and Ultron have god complexes,
and partially because the Vision
himself does represent an ideal.
And when he picks up
the hammer, it's...
I don't want to say a miracle,
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
But it's playing on that idea of...
When we think
of that kind of religious figure,
we are thinking of
the best idea of ourselves.
Of what we wish we could be.
And this play is so much
about the best and worst.
This little bit's a bit of embellishment
that Robert and I came up with
on the day.
The two Enhanced?
WHEDON: It's always nice to be able
to have people
who know their character so well
that they can give you
what you've asked for,
but then make it feel lived in.
I love this shot.
It is very much of the idiom
of the first movie, in the sense of,
"Look at this big, expensive space.
Isn't it grand?"
And I love the two of them.
I did at one point realise
that I had sort of turned Maria Hill
into a girl Friday in this movie,
because there were too many heroes
for her to do that much.
But it makes it all the better, I think,
when she shows up in her old gear,
firing a gun like she should ought to.
This shot was very difficult.
Again, one of the last shots we got.
Kevin is very leery of shots
that feel artificial,
and when you are flying with someone
and you do a camera move
around them,
you're in great danger
of feeling artificial.
And so we worked hard in the colouring
and the way New York was
and in the textures,
to try and mitigate that and keep it real.
And then we went
right through that glass,
which is a beautifully crafted effect.
This shot is something slightly similar
to what I did in my first film, Serenity,
in that every member of the team is in it.
Not all of them speak,
but they are all visible at some point.
And we get, basically,
a tour of the place.
Obviously, because
they come in through the "A,"
it has only been referred to
as the "A-hole shot,"
but what it is for me
is a very important way
to explain the space of Avengers Tower
to the audience.
There is a bit of showing off.
There is a bit of,
"Look at all our grandeur."
But what I'm really doing is explaining
exactly where everything is
in relation to everything else,
because later on we will need to know.
Robots are down here,
and party's over here,
and Pietro is gonna be
standing on that glass later.
Charlie Wood designed the set,
and it's the biggest and one of
the most beautiful things
I've ever set foot on.
It is glorious.
Sometimes it's almost overwhelming.
And besides wanting to
show the scope of it,
to play into the epic nature of the thing,
it allowed me to come up with gags
like Pietro getting...
Like Hawkeye shooting out
the glass from under him.
And it allowed me to create action,
and also to just
(CHUCKLING)
have an enormous amount of fun.
Sometimes the least fun.
This particular space is so big
and that sort of holo area so empty
that it was sometimes
difficult to shoot in,
to figure out what to do with people.
But every frame is such candy
because the work these guys put into it,
building it and dressing it,
and the depth in frame
that you can get in these instances
is never not exciting.
I literally finished shooting on this set,
and on that day walked into a corner
I had never been in downstairs,
and was like, "Wait a minute,
"there's 100 cool ideas
I have for this area."
There are two kinds of filming
that are really delightful.
One is this, kid in a candy store.
The other is the opposite,
when you have
kind of an impossible space.
I like that very much
because you become more inventive
in those instances.
You have to think on your feet.
You have to let the space
dictate the frame to an extent,
and that makes it more real,
or just possibly more left of centre.
But in this instance,
I didn't mind the candy store.
And the "Science Brothers,"
as they are affectionately known.
Any time these guys get together,
it's fun.
They're very different
in their energy as actors.
By the way, give me curved glass
and reflections that go on forever,
and there is no way I'm not shooting it.
I want to apply this
to the Ultron program.
But Jarvis can't download
a data schematic this dense.
WHEDON: Which, by the way,
was another difference in this film
than anything else I'd shot.
I would stop and say, "Wait a minute,
we're gonna get another setup.
"We're gonna do something
"just because I think we can
and should and it looks cool."
Generally, because of my background,
I have shot exactly
what I needed and nothing else.
On this film, I shot everything I needed,
and then some things
I thought I might want.
Which during shooting
was very liberating and exciting,
and because we moved so quickly,
was not a problem for the schedule.
During editing, interesting side note,
(CHUCKLES) it turned out to be
the worst idea in the world,
and I'm definitely going back
to shooting only what I need
because that amount
of choice can sometimes,
like a giant set, be too much.
This is one of those cute little ideas.
We're on a memory-head track,
so that we can do four different setups
in the exact same configuration
and tell the story quickly.
It's one of those cute ideas
that takes half a day at least
to give you 20 seconds of footage.
So I tried to have
fewer cute ideas after that.
JARVIS: I'll continue
to run variations on the interface.
But you should probably
prepare for your guests.
I'll notify you
if there are any developments.
STARK: Thanks, buddy.
JARVIS: Enjoy yourself, sir.
STARK: I always do.
WHEDON: Oh, and now
we get to Mr. Spader.
ULTRON: What is this?
WHEDON: There's no way
I can say enough about
pretty much anybody in this cast.
But if you have to start somewhere, um,
James Spader and Paul Bettany
is not a bad place to start.
They are so extraordinary together,
so much the people they wanted to be.
And with James we were creating
somebody completely new,
and with Paul we ended up doing
the same thing with the Vision.
Because I originally wrote
the Vision as Jarvis,
and then went back in and realised,
"No, he's much more enigmatic
and interesting than that."
And what Paul gave me
was beyond my best fantasy
of the Vision I'd read as a kid.
Didn't have a fantasy
of the Ultron I'd read as a kid
because he was always
just kind of mad.
So my idea for who he would be
was a sort of grand madness,
a weirdness.
Um... And, uh...
ULTRON: Why do you call him "sir"?
WHEDON: That line,
"Why do you call him 'sir'?"
Has so much menace.
But is also, again,
one of the central themes of the movie.
So much of this movie is about
power and class and privilege.
I mean, we looked at this, we were like,
"It's literally Upstairs, Downstairs."
(CHUCKLES)
There's downstairs,
the Legion who come in
through the back door,
upstairs, the heroes.
And that scene, by the way,
was added in post.
I felt that we could very clearly explain
the problem that Ultron was having
and create a scene
that really made you feel for Jarvis.
Kevin and Jeremy, who really fought
for Jarvis' presence
to be increased throughout the movie.
I had always intended
to make him the Vision.
They kept insisting,
"We want more. We want a visual.
"We want everyone to mourn him.
We want him to be treated like a guy."
And I didn't really understand
the need for that the way they did.
And then putting it together,
it was clear,
"Oh, yeah, wait a minute, this guy,
he was there at the beginning.
"He was there in the first few minutes
of the first Iron Man."
And people have a bond with him
that is palpable and very human.
There are many versions of this scene,
some of them including the actresses.
One of the great things about
working with this many stars is
you never know who you're gonna get,
what schedule is gonna work out,
who's suddenly gonna
become available.
But when it became apparent
that neither was going to show up,
I thought it was important
to plant a flag on that and say,
"Well, that's something
that registers with our guys."
And the best way to do that
was to have them be dicks about it.
I fly it right up to the general's palace,
I drop it at his feet.
WHEDON: This was, again,
something that I thought of
on the day after we shot,
or while we were shooting the first half.
And it's one of those things
without which
the first half doesn't even work.
The payoff of him being all prideful
about his successful story
is one of the funniest things in the party.
LEE: Neither was
Omaha Beach, blondie.
Stop trying to scare us.
WHEDON: I liked the idea,
the texture of the idea
that Thor has something that could
actually get Captain America drunk,
because, as he explained
in the first movie...
I don't know who that actor was,
by the way.
He's really good, he's very familiar,
uh, the veteran.
But we were lucky to get him. I just...
The name isn't coming to me.
Um...
No, it was so much fun
to be able to do that.
And he used "Excelsior" here
as "I'm so wasted, '' (CHUCKLES)
Um, since I grew up with that phrase.
Fact is, he's not like
anybody I've ever known.
WHEDON: One of the other great things
about a movie like this
and the opportunities
they gave me with the actors,
the locations, the scenarios,
and the moods, and everything else,
was that you feel like
you're making 13 different movies.
And I'm very much...
Apart from actually having ADHD,
which I do,
I'm very much a fan of things
that change it up.
And this was one of the instances,
because they are both
so beautiful and charming,
where we all sort of went,
"When can we just make this movie?"
I actually said to them,
to Mark and Scarlett,
"You guys should do The Thin Man."
And they both asked me
what The Thin Man was,
which makes me feel
that, uh, the Earth is doomed.
But their energy there is so great,
and to be able to lean into it visually
and just go ahead and say,
"Let's pretend we're in the '40s,"
is a delight.
And leads to, um,
the after-party that's coming up,
which is a more well-known bit.
And it's interesting because this stuff,
particularly with them,
is very sort of studied. Again,
because I was going into
a slightly older visual template,
the camerawork is
somewhat less frenetic.
Then we got into
shooting this next scene,
and it was also very elegant,
and the camera moves, it went from
here to there, and it was bombing.
And nobody was enjoying it,
the actors didn't feel funny,
their lines didn't sound funny,
(CHUCKLES) it just didn't work.
And to the point
where they're all standing there,
and I've got all of them
for one of the few times...
More times in this movie
than the first one,
(CHUCKLING)
but I've got every major actor
I've ever admired
standing in front of me,
and I'm just drawing a blank.
And I finally turned
to Jamie Christopher,
our awesome AD, and said,
"Can you help me?
Can you make it stop?"
And he just turned around and said,
"Thank you, everybody,
that's a good day. See you all at 8:00."
And then I just kept working,
and eventually figured out,
"Oh, I'm shooting this in a very...
Like it's The Age of Innocence,
"and it's a party."
And the whole point of this movie is
you're at the party.
You're invited.
And I realised I had literally,
with Much Ado,
just shot an entire movie where people
sit around and drink and talk.
And the fact that I couldn't figure out
how to shoot the after-party scene,
in a movie whose code name when
we were shooting it was "After Party,"
very deliberately, was the source
of some embarrassment.
But we came back in, the cameras
got looser, the lines got looser,
the cast got happier,
and it just started to flow.
And they're all so good.
And that montage was
one of the first things I pitched.
You bet your ass.
WHEDON: It wasn't until, um,
much later that I casually,
thinking it would not be well-received,
pitched the payoff
that will come later with the Vision.
I said, "You know, you could do this."
And it was Kevin who instantly knew
how important it would be,
and it is in fact the biggest
cheer moment in the film.
ULTRON: No.
WHEDON: I like robot stories
'cause they're Frankenstein stories.
And as you can see,
I leaned pretty heavily into that.
This guy, I always think of
as resembling the very first
movie of Frankenstein,
which I've only ever seen a still from.
But it's this weird, screaming,
almost mummy-like guy
with tons of things,
of tattered cloth sort of
dripping off his arms.
And as much as puppet,
and as much as scary robot,
I wanted to evoke that,
the very first Frankenstein film.
Frankenstein, robots,
it all has to do with
the central human question of,
"Why am I here? What is this, please?"
(CHUCKLES)
Because we all have to ask that,
and we all have to feel the pain
of being brought into a world
(CHUCKLES) that was not made
to accommodate us.
And the Frankenstein story,
and most robot movies
where the robot is anything other than
a killing machine, deal with that pain.
And very baldly.
It's one of the things,
like superheroes...
By the way, that was Mark on the day,
that was not me.
(CHUCKLING) That was Mark's call.
He's a shameless physical comedian.
If you look at the DVD extras,
you'll see even more of that stuff.
God bless him.
But that idea of "Why am I here?"
The way it gets simplified in the
robot story is really fascinating to me.
Because we come back to it
because we can really ask
what it is to be human,
when we take away
every part of being human but one.
Or we take away
just one particular aspect.
And in this humanity,
our foibles and what we are as people,
as parents, as powerful,
as alliterative, we...
All of those questions
have to be asked in stories like this.
Come on! That's the one.
...is unsafe.
WHEDON: The Avengers have
so much power at the beginning of this,
and one of the things that I knew,
and I had this problem in the first one,
is nobody roots for the overdog.
And so it was very important to me
that they be brought down a peg,
but not just by circumstance,
but because they have...
In Tony's case, dramatically,
but in every case to an extent,
lost some aspect of the mission.
Lost some aspect of their humanity,
because that's the thing
about being a superhero,
it's the thing about having power.
When your decisions affect more than
the people around you, inevitably,
you are going to destroy something.
You're going to harm someone in
a way that removes you from humanity.
The more power you have, inevitably,
the less a part of
the human community you are.
And so Ultron himself says that,
although he doesn't always realise
how much it applies to him.
And once again, the Frankenstein.
And also the Pinocchio,
which was, by the way,
an idea I had for the Comic-Con teaser
that played so nicely,
it got used a whole bunch.
And then I ended up saying,
"Let's just go ahead and stick it
in the film because it is creepy."
She's picking glass
out of her feet there, by the way.
In the longer version
of the fight we had just seen,
Maria slid down and jumped in
after Rhodey in her bare feet.
And the jacket she's wearing,
by the way,
is Steve Rogers' bomber jacket,
which I have yet to hear
anybody comment on.
But I thought it was
an interesting little detail.
I wanted to, obviously,
make them more casual.
And we had to sort of
"de-mom" her makeup a little bit
when she arrived on set,
and kind of make sure she felt
as cool as everyone else.
I have more than enough words
to describe you, Stark.
Thor. The Legionnaire.
WHEDON: This was the scene,
as I mentioned,
where I, um, really struggled.
I struggled because with no central
sort of object to build around,
'cause it's an empty space where
we were gonna put a Jarvis later,
and with no intense
sort of source of light,
I really wasn't sure where to put people
and how to get them
where they needed to go emotionally.
Especially because Robert has
a really difficult job in this scene
of cracking up in the middle of
the worst thing he's ever done.
And to me, it was really important,
and Robert, too.
The moment I pitched it to him,
he latched on to it.
He's like, "I do that
whenever I'm busted. I can't help it.
"It's so bad. I get nervous, I giggle."
But I also think there's something...
I feel like Tony's...
There's a little bit of the Asperger's,
being on the spectrum with him,
where he's just, um... He's not quite...
He's just not good at people.
(CHUCKLES)
And for me, again,
that was something to lean into.
And ultimately, my whole
"Tony is the villain" thesis
nicely plays into it as well.
And again, "villain" doesn't
necessarily mean "mwah-ha evil,"
because here you see his pain
and the sort of epic nature
of his heroism.
Which is contrasted, as usual,
with the very simple nature of Steve's.
And Tony is a guy
who likes to do the math.
And Steve is a guy
who understands the situation he's in,
and is looking out
for the people around him.
In the DVD extras,
you'll also be able to see
a scene between the two of them
that comes before this.
Ultimately, it was an attempt
to show them in the community,
and how they were a bit rebellious,
but also very much community-minded.
It became apparent that the two of them
walking into a dark room,
looking for something,
and then talking to someone
who had clearly called them there,
gave us the information
that we needed,
and also kept them
a little more mysterious.
The scene was so mundane,
and they were so...
Just such normal bickering siblings,
that it didn't...
Didn't really add to their grandeur.
This is the first time we see Ultron.
And I look back, and I'm...
The fact of him sitting in that chair
is very, sort of, based on the great,
sort of, John Buscema kind of...
"The tortured king and
the weight of the throne" kind of thing.
But then he stands up,
and that's how he's revealed.
And I thought,
"That's less cinematic
than it could have been," after the fact.
ULTRON: Children...
WHEDON: This little bit
that he says here
is also really important in the theme.
Simply because
one of the first things I ever wrote
when sort of just freestyling
about Ultron in my head,
was that children all kill their parents,
because once you have them,
you no longer care
as much about yourself.
You accept your place
in the cycle of the world,
and you know that you'll die,
but there's something
more important to you than that.
And then, (CHUCKLING)
in parenthesis, I wrote,
'cause I was sending this
out as a memo,
"Don't worry, nothing like that
will ever appear in the film."
And then it actually did.
But I do think that a connection
that even I didn't make is
because so much of this
is about power...
Yet also, so much of it is about family,
and the responsibility we have
not just as leaders or as heroes,
but as parents.
There is no time when anybody
in the world understands
what the truly powerful can do
and go through, unless they're parents.
Until the moment they're parents.
And then, suddenly,
they have complete mastery
over somebody's mind.
Not forever. (CHUCKLES)
In the case of my kids,
not even for that long.
But there is the ability
to uplift or destroy.
It is a perfect connection
between what is going on in this movie,
politically and thematically,
and what is going on personally.
This shot here is
one of my favourite shots in the film,
just the way Ultron listens.
Again, ILM, they had James Spader's
performance to work off of.
They had face-capture on him,
so he wore cameras
on his face the whole time.
But they really took it and used it,
and managed to make a man who's
made out of metal not just sound,
but move like Spader
and give the performance.
When James took the gig, he said,
"I don't wanna do voiceover work.
"I wanna be able to
give a performance."
And, my God, he did.
And they did such an extraordinary job
of capturing it,
so much so that when he is
standing there doing nothing,
I cannot stop looking at him.
I developed a huge...
Not even a man-crush,
like a teenage girl-crush on Ultron.
Like, I want a picture of him
over my bed,
and I wanna write
about him in my diary,
and I wonder if he's thinking about me.
He's just gorgeous.
'Course, there's a lot of gorgeous
to go around.
This bit, there was a lot more of.
We played the mystery of
"What's up with Barton?" a lot.
Is he still possessed? Is he villainous?
Is he something terrible?
Ultimately, we just kept the fact
that he says, "I don't have a girlfriend,"
and then later says, "Girlfriend."
My issue with it was simply...
I mean, people felt,
"Can we get some time out of here?"
My issue was, I've just felt that
people would only think
that he was talking to Fury.
Since he had been a S.H.I.E.L.D.
agent, and we've never seen Fury,
and we know that S.H.I.E.L.D. is gone,
that they wouldn't think
that he was up to something dire.
They would just think,
"Oh, he's listening to his old boss."
And the dancing I would have
to have gone through
to make that clear
that he wasn't,
just didn't seem worth the effort.
So we kept just a little bit of it. I miss it.
I miss the idea of,
"What's his dark secret?
"What's his dark secret?"
'Cause I think it's important.
His dark secret is obviously
the crux of the film.
And, I mean, the fulcrum,
the thing upon which
the entire film revolves, um, changes.
But I still think it works
even without all the buildup.
I don't follow.
What comes out of Wakanda?
STARK: The strongest metal on Earth.
Where is this guy now?
WHEDON: This is another
one of those shots
that I don't get to take the credit for.
We had so many
extraordinary cameramen,
and our pilot was amazing.
And Matthew went out to Bangladesh,
where these shipyards exist.
We had originally
been going to Wakanda,
but since we weren't using anybody
from Black Panther, it became...
We kept going less
and less to Wakanda,
till I referred to it as "Wa-kinda."
We're just sort of on the outskirts.
And it became a tease, and not worth it.
But we wanted the vibranium dealer,
and the arms dealer, and all that.
So Klaue was the suggestion.
It was actually going through...
When we thought of it,
Jeremy went through
and looked at images of Klaue online,
and some fan had put up Andy Serkis.
"What if Andy Serkis played Klaue?"
And obviously,
we were already working with Andy.
He and his Imaginarium were guiding
both Mark and James
in their movement,
since he is the master of mo-cap.
But we realised that
we wanted him for something else.
And when he showed up
looking exactly like that on the day,
I thought it was mo-cap.
I could not believe
how different he had become.
And he's just the sweetest guy,
but also an extraordinary player.
He's not onscreen for that long,
but you do not forget him.
KLAUE: ...intimidating someone?
I'm afraid I'm not that afraid.
Everybody is afraid of something.
Cuttlefish.
WHEDON: Some of these things
in the film
are very autobiographical.
I saw a documentary on cuttlefish,
and I still cannot deal with it.
I don't think it's okay
that the Lord made cuttlefish,
and I wish that he hadn't.
They freak me out.
You should check them out.
They're unbelievable.
...and make me see a giant cuttlefish...
WHEDON: At some point, I will also
have to talk about the twins.
And I only deal...
WHEDON: And basically,
it'll just be another praise-fest.
A lot of people didn't want,
uh, necessarily,
to have the Scarlet Witch
and Quicksilver in the film.
They felt with Ultron and the Vision,
it was going to be overstuffed.
But it was very important for me
to have someone for Ultron to talk to,
and also someone else
whose powers would be different.
By the way, this lab here
was all created digitally after the fact.
Originally, it was just in the barrels.
One of the things I discovered in post
was that I had shot the least
science-fiction-y-looking
science-fiction movie ever,
which was fine.
It was what I had intended.
But when the vibranium
just looked like gold bars...
There was even a bit where they were
in a mining car, all stacked up,
being carted from one place to another,
and we were all like,
"Um, this is a little Indiana Jones.
"This is a little old-timey." You know?
We expected Walter Brennan
to show up.
So we replaced it after the fact,
and made it a little more
in the idiom of the science-fiction
movie this was supposed to be.
This contains
my favourite Spade moment.
His addition of the word "oh."
I'm... Oh!
I'm sure that's gonna be okay. I'm sorry.
It's just that I don't understand.
WHEDON: I can't say enough
about that moment.
I was sitting next to Paula,
the script supervisor,
Paula Casarin,
who's the best in the biz,
and I looked at her, I was like,
"Did he just say 'oh'?
"Do you think he'll do that again?
"Do you think he'll do it again?"
Because James learns everything
word-for-word.
That's his M.O., like it's a play.
And I was like, "You gotta do the 'oh. '
You gotta do the 'oh. "'
And then he did it when we rolled.
And I went up to him,
and the first thing he said was,
(MIMICKING SPADER)
"I added an 'oh. ' I hope that's okay.
"I can do it again without, if you like."
(IN NORMAL VOICE)
I'm like, "No, I love you."
I don't think I said that,
but you could see it in my eyes.
The idea that Ultron
is emotionally so capricious
is just something I hadn't
really seen in an AI movie,
particularly one where
the robots are going to decide
that all humanity must be killed.
For him to be the most human,
the most temperamental,
was very important.
And it's why Spader's the only guy.
Because he can do that
sort of classic Keith David,
(IN DEEP BARITONE)
"You want me to do voiceover
"because I make the subwoofer explode
"with the gravitas
of my basso profundo."
(IN NORMAL VOICE) But then he can
become completely goofy.
We shot it two ways with Andy,
whether or not the arm came off.
Kevin will tell you straight up,
he likes a good arm-coming-off.
It's like, "If I can cut off
somebody's hand, then I'm just fine."
His Empire Strikes Back obsession
might be even bigger than mine.
That was just one of those
sort of signature moments,
and one of the reasons
why I wanted Quicksilver in the film,
to be able to just see things differently
than we ever had before.
I didn't feel like...
With the exception of the one we do,
where we go into hyper slo-mo
at the beginning,
I don't feel comfortable
making a sort of hyperbolic,
surreal meal out of those moments,
unless I have a reason.
I'm kind of very pedantic
when it comes to filmmaking.
And so to have Scarlet Witch
and Quicksilver
justifying the strange way
I wanted to shoot these guys
and the new ways I wanted to
look at them was enormously useful.
Obviously, they're very important
as characters,
and I can't say enough
about the players.
But that was one of the main reasons
I brought them in.
Now, I just explained all this stuff about
how I don't like things to be all weird
for no reason whatsoever,
and I'm about to
make myself a big ol' liar.
ULTRON: This is going very well.
(RAPID BEEPING)
(SOLDIER GRUNTS)
WHEDON: The dreams.
The dreams were the other reason
why I wanted the kids in the movie,
because it was going to be
a chance to do something
that was very out of the Marvel idiom,
and something very surreal.
Surreal, but emotionally grounded.
That is to say that
there's a reason for everything we do,
but we played...
We referred to these as dreams.
And right here, for example,
they're actually all walking backwards.
People moved backwards,
or ran things backwards a few times.
Not so that you would notice,
just so that they would have
just enough awkwardness.
MADAME B: Only the breakable ones.
You're made of marble.
We'll celebrate
after the graduation ceremony.
WHEDON: Lisa Lassek cut these,
and we've worked together
for a long, long time.
She was able to create,
and Jeff added some notes as well,
but just moments that were
even more surreal than what I'd shot.
But everything is very deliberate
in its bizarreness.
Cap is the guy
who can't stop seeing war,
even at a party for the end of the war.
Who, when asked to imagine a life
of normalcy, comes up with nothing.
Which, by the way,
was Drew Goddard's idea.
I was asking him about Cap
and fretting over the dreams, and...
We call them dreams, by the way,
simply because
we can't call them visions,
because it was too confusing with
having a character called the Vision.
But this moment where he turns
around, yeah, Drew pitched it,
and it ended up
being the central moment.
I don't know
when I'm gonna get to the part
where I start talking
about Ben Davis, the DP,
because I'm not sure I can ever stop.
The work in this movie is the most
beautiful that's ever had my name on it.
By the way, those three guys in animal
masks standing in the arches there,
they represent something
I have never done before,
which is an absolute
balls-out Easter egg,
which I will discuss later on.
And not just a Marvel Easter egg,
an actual...
Having to do with my work.
The ceremony is necessary...
WHEDON: Yeah,
this whole cutting pattern here
was created by Lisa.
These dreams were
obviously much longer,
but we got what we needed from them,
which was to know what
sort of drove everyone,
and to reopen old wounds
and to make them
as vulnerable as possible, obviously.
She remembers that she was trained
and even abused
into being an assassin,
and that she has a history of killing
and a very dark career.
Cap is incapable of being a part of
the community
he's constantly talking about.
And Thor feels that his powers
will destroy everything,
that he is not on the right path,
that he's out of control.
I'm not exactly sure
what Banner's dreaming right now.
We looked at some point-of-view shots,
but nothing we created
really sort of did as much
as just showing
how bonkers the Hulk was being,
because, ultimately, it doesn't matter.
What I said to the animators
and to Mark was,
"He feels like the world
is attacking him."
It's like he's in the middle
of a wasp's nest all the time.
One of the most difficult things
about animating the Hulk is
trying to figure out
what he's pissed about now.
'Cause when he's there for a long time,
he has to keep this very specific energy.
That shot in particular,
the doggy cam or dinner tray,
where you sort of attach
the camera to someone,
I first saw it in Mean Streets,
when Harvey Keitel's super drunk.
And fought very hard to keep that,
and they had to create it
stitched from bits of
what we had from the day.
But it really does give you a good sense
that the Hulk's not in his right mind,
even for the Hulk.
And the question of
what's making him angry
became, um,
easier and harder to answer,
because, um, the answer is everything.
(CHUCKLES)
So we knew we had
all the energy we needed,
but you still have to figure out
where he's looking,
what he thinks the problem is.
Here, for example,
he's flailing,
but then when he turns around,
you can see he actually
does get shot in the face.
This shot,
which is among my favourites,
is also among the most difficult,
because the Hulkbuster armour is...
It's known from the comics,
it's actually from after my time,
because I'm super old. But even I knew
you absolutely have to have Hulkbuster
because nobody is
capable of fighting the Hulk
except Tony, and the idea that
Banner himself had, had a hand
in devising this
made perfect emotional sense,
and also made for
what would be an exciting sequence.
The reason that,
that shot that I mentioned
was difficult and
not just delightful is that
Iron Man is inside the torso of this thing,
and that's a very difficult thing
to convey, to convey the size.
I look back and wonder
if I should've had him
appear behind the Hulk.
I wanted to do the Western standoff,
but it's very difficult,
even with people around him,
to realise this guy's 15-feet tall.
He's not quite twice the size of the Hulk,
but he's up there, and when
they are all completely isolated
for most of the fight, it's very difficult
to really get the sense of that.
We're coming to something
that never fails to get a laugh,
which for a long time
was a real problem for me
because I didn't mean it as a joke.
I thought it would be cool
and obviously comic book-y,
but I didn't think of it
as a laugh moment.
And, by God, it is.
And I look at it now and I'm like,
"Well, it has a Warner Bros.
cartoon element to it."
But I love it when I actually don't get
the emotional gauge of what I'm doing,
because I feel like
if I'm getting more than I expected
from something,
or even something
completely unexpected,
it makes it more than
just efficient storytelling.
It makes it something that's alive.
There's the elevator gag.
Federico, one of the storyboard guys,
had worked that out,
and then we changed
the space we were in,
but we couldn't not have the
elevator gag because it felt so good.
Now the Hulk is
pretty much invulnerable,
so having him spit out a tooth
was a big deal,
and getting the emotional register
of that thing was a big deal, too,
because the instinct was, for everyone,
for him to be twitchy and monstrous
and all the things that
he had been in the scene, and
this was one of those things where,
"No, you need to take licence."
When he turns around,
he needs to be very quietly,
like the kind of
"calm before the storm" pissed.
I was like, "More Robert Mitchum,
more Robert Mitchum."
That's what I kept saying,
and people were like,
"We have no idea
what you mean by that."
But that kind of cool,
which may be a bit of a cheat?
Now this was quite a showpiece.
Delicate. (CHUCKLES)
I know, "delicate" is
a weird word to use right now.
Delicate for us, um, because even now,
many years later,
the last thing we wanna do is
egregiously evoke the spectre of 9/11.
And being, uh, callous about that
is unthinkable.
But, at the same time,
it was very important to me,
because it's part of
what this movie is about,
that there be a price,
that there be real damage, that we say,
"You don't just bust up a whole city,
and nobody suffers for it."
This, it informs the end of the movie,
and what the mission is,
and what the stakes are.
We originally shot it
that he changed back to Banner,
and was looking around and seeing
what he'd done, but I thought,
late in the game, that it would be
more effective if the Hulk himself
was able to register it,
and that it became stronger than
whatever spell
Tony had knocked out of him.
The only rule of science
I have in Avengers movies is,
"If somebody is mind-controlling you,
"then you get hit really hard,
"then it'll probably end."
That's actually all the science
that I know in the whole world.
HILL: ...stay in stealth mode
and stay away from here.
So, run and hide?
Until we can find Ultron,
I don't have a lot else to offer.
(SIGHS) Neither do we.
(SIGHS)
Hey, you wanna switch out?
No, I'm good.
WHEDON: This contains
the last vestige of the
"What the hell is Barton up to?"
A safe house.
WHEDON: He originally had a line,
"Where are you taking us?"
"A place I hoped I'd never take you."
But, on the day, all I could think was,
Tony would be like,
"Uh, I'm definitely driving.
I don't know what that means,
"but it sounds ominous."
And it either sounded ominous
or heroical.
So, him being all shifty and saying,
"Safe house," was just more efficient.
This house, these grounds,
we're on the Duke of Wellington's land
in England,
trying to make it,
like Springfield in The Simpsons,
every state in America,
so that they're just in America.
"We live in America, USA."
I have more to say
about the house and grounds,
but first, let's talk about
the secret weapon.
This is an agent of some kind.
Gentlemen, this is Laura.
WHEDON: And she was
a secret weapon
because we had to keep Linda
out of all of the promo stuff,
because the one secret
I was most anxious to protect
was that Hawkeye's dark secret
is that he has a family.
Chris there, by the way, just killing it.
He did four hilarious reactions,
which was great because,
in our heads,
when the Avengers walked in here,
it would be the strangest thing
in the world,
but with only two of them in costume,
two or three,
and the house being
so big and beautiful,
they didn't look that out of place.
And so for Evans to
keep doing very broad bits of,
"What's going on here?"
was just a lifesaver.
Traitor.
WHEDON: There are two of these girls,
and if you colour them pink,
they play John C. Reilly's daughter
in Guardians of the Galaxy,
(CHUCKLING) which is not
something I knew when I shot this.
But I'm sure
they can do an entire
four-issue limited series
as to how this girl's related
to somebody on another planet.
This next shot some of you
may recognise from The Searchers.
I realised I needed
that moment from Cap,
and it's very central to his whole theme
about not being able to be at home,
live a normal life.
I did mention it to Jeremy Latcham,
who then wrote a memo to everyone
because I said I need a little bit of
the interior of the house in this area.
And he's like, "Joss wants to
do a shot from The Searchers."
I was like, "Don't say it!"
But as long as I don't say
anything on the DVD commentary,
I think I should be fine, and
no one will know that I'm just a thief.
A thief!
You are so cute.
WHEDON: This is a scene that was
in danger of being trimmed
for the entire editing process,
and ended up with
maybe one line pulled out.
It's so crucial to see that...
What a normal life is,
and what a normal perspective is
on the Avengers and their life.
And, again, Linda is just so earthy
and so real, and you buy the two
of these guys together so much.
She not only represents home
and hearth and how he's cool,
she's so luminous that she's what
the Avengers can never have.
And also, her face showed up
in the picture on the left,
which was a fortuitous thing
that we then highlighted even further
because it looked so beautiful
in that wide shot, right there.
Things are changing for us.
WHEDON: She also just was dialled in
to the character from moment one,
and she and Jeremy met
a couple days before we shot,
and yet, the level of intimacy
is enormous.
His respect for her
and for what this life means
is so crucial.
This is actually in Seoul, Korea.
One of the great things
about doing this one
and shooting from London
meant we could go everywhere.
Where, in the first one,
we had to create places,
in this one we could really go to them,
and you find architecture like that,
which you would not find,
even perhaps in your own imagination.
So it's very exciting.
...is the next me.
WHEDON: Most of the stuff
in these labs
was rewritten many times after the fact,
and Claudia came in
to re-shoot a bunch of it
as it sort of got moved around.
There was so much exposition
that she and James had to give us,
yet keep it dynamic,
which they did a good job with.
That shot of the house and barn
is probably my last opportunity
to explain that those places don't exist.
They were built for the movie,
and we shot them for one day.
We shot one day outside there,
and then they were gone.
They built the interior of the house.
The barn was an actual barn
in England.
And the design
is not completely dissimilar
to the farm that I spent
a lot of my childhood on
in Upstate New York.
And it's a very comforting space.
If that were real,
I would want to live there.
But actually what really exists
on that field
usually is not a house,
but very angry cows.
Angry, angry, bitter cows.
I don't know what it is. They were just...
They weren't pleasant.
That I was an Avenger.
That I was anything more...
WHEDON: This scene,
you only get the first two-thirds
of the scene in the movie.
We cut out the end.
People thought it would be,
and I agree in part, I do,
that it would be better
to leave the question
of whether they were together
without answering it.
But if you watch the scene
in the DVD extras,
you see the whole scene,
and you see just more of why
I'm in love with these two people.
(CHUCKLES)
And I'm in love with their love,
and I'm in love with their pain.
And they were so good on this day.
And Mark and Scarlett only ever bring
goofy, happy energy to the set.
But then you start the cameras,
and they go to a place of pain
that is just so human
and so excruciating.
This scene caused my first-ever
completely un-ironic group hug
because I was so proud of them
and what they did.
I insisted we have an extra day
of shooting for this scene.
We didn't need it.
They just came out and nailed it.
This moment from her...
They sterilise you.
WHEDON: Um... That just kills me.
That throwaway, "It's no big deal.
"Then why are my eyes welling up?"
gesture is just beautiful.
I love the very haunting,
weird little plaintive melody
that Danny Elfman put over this.
Their romance was a point
of contention for some people.
Not for us, while we were making it.
In fact, it never occurred to us that
there would be any reaction against it.
They seemed so much
like they belonged,
if not together,
in the same sort of world that...
And the chemistry they had
from the first scene
they ever played together just felt right.
And people who thought
she was supposed to be with Clint...
Well, obviously, it's very important
that he's married, that he's normcore,
that his distance from the Avengers
is caused by the fact that he actually
has a connection to the world
and he knows they don't.
But, also, I think
it's much more interesting
for he and Natasha to be two people
who would lay down their lives
for each other,
but aren't interested
in sleeping with each other.
I think that's
a more interesting dynamic, a true one,
and better than just
the two of them hooking up.
Every time someone tries
to win a war before it starts,
innocent people die. Every time.
WHEDON: The log rip.
We built a lot of logs for him to rip.
It's a constant conversation
with Chris about Cap's power level.
With Captain America,
and particularly with the Hulk,
you get this thing of...
Okay, Sergio Leone.
Sorry. There, I said it.
You get this thing of, "One moment,
"I'm having a normal fist fight
with some guy,
"and the next moment,
I can jump two storeys."
So which is it?
I'm embarrassed to say
that "Hello, Deere" was Robert's.
That's one of those moments
where I just kick myself,
I'm like, "How did I miss that?"
Was she ever not working for you?
FURY: Artificial intelligence.
You never even hesitated.
It's been a really long day,
like Eugene O'Neill long,
so how's about
we skip to the part where you're useful.
WHEDON: There was
a certain level of uncertainty
about whether
the Eugene O'Neill line would play,
and, after the hammer moment,
it might be the biggest crowd-pleaser
with every audience we've played it for,
and I'm not sure why, honestly,
but I'm very pleased.
STARK: I saw it.
I didn't tell the team. How could I?
I saw them all dead, Nick. I felt it.
The whole world, too.
Because of me.
WHEDON: The idea of playing
Tony's confessional.
Because there was a long period
where it was like,
"Well, does he tell everyone
he had a vision?"
And we had lines in it for quite a while
that indicated he had said something,
or said something off-screen,
but you don't bring Nick Fury in
without a reason.
And although it was important to say
that they were flying on their own,
we knew we wanted to see Nick,
and to have him be the first person
that Tony can actually talk to,
and for that to become,
in a way, the sea change for Tony,
even though he's about to do
something even more absurd
than what he's already done,
is important for the whole group.
I like the look.
WHEDON: This is actual
Royal Holloway, University of London.
Again, any time
we could go to the place,
let it be the place that we said it was,
and that wasn't all the time,
but was as much as possible.
Obviously, that scene was
a little bit longer.
All of Stellan's stuff, there was more of.
Again, enjoy your DVD extras.
The "Thor and Stellan go to
a cave together" subplot
is one of the more complicated issues
in the movie.
People either think
there's too much of it or not enough,
but what we have
gets us where we need to go.
I contacted our friends
at the Nexus about that.
Nexus?
WHEDON: This scene, difficult,
not unlike the scene in the lab,
even though we had the table.
Just difficult to get the energy.
It's a very bucolic kind of setting.
It's very deliberately
the opposite of the Helicarrier.
I mean, he mentions the Helicarrier,
Fury does, on purpose,
because it's important for him,
A, because later on
he's gonna show up with it,
and if you had forgotten it exists,
you don't want that moment
of like, "What?"
But also because this portion
of the movie last time,
where everybody's sort of
searching their soul
and wondering what the heck to do
and conflicting,
came on the Helicarrier last time.
And it was a very kind of science-fiction,
kind of comic-book-y space,
and the whole point of
coming to the Bartons' farm
was to do the opposite of that.
To bring them, literally,
back down to Earth.
But having done that,
you then have to allow
for this moment of respite
from the giant action set pieces,
two more of which are coming up,
and, at the same time, keep some
kind of energy and momentum.
For some reason,
every time we did a shot on Mark,
when he got to the line,
"Has anybody seen Helen Cho?"
He called her Anita.
(CHUCKLING) I mean,
we came back the next day
and did more coverage,
and as soon as we were off him,
he was fine.
And as soon as we came back on him,
it was Anita.
I have no idea why. Nobody knows why.
But, oh, my God,
it made us laugh so hard.
Poor man. It's so random. "Anita Cho."
But when he did nail it, he did nail it.
You look at that shot where he says,
"Has anyone been in contact
with Helen Cho?"
The camera is moving here,
he's looking there.
It's very precise.
And that's an interesting thing
with Mark,
because I think he's probably
the best actor of his generation.
But that precision is not natural to him.
I have to sort of go,
"I need you to do this thing."
And because what makes him so great
is he's so honest in his stuff,
it doesn't come from,
"And we land here,"
which is a very sort of
comic book vernacular
and very much the way
I've always created that sort of,
"Everything is precise and musical
and it goes..."
And then it goes to the next thing.
He's not that,
because everything he says
sounds like it just came from him.
He doesn't play characters.
He just becomes them. He just exists.
So it was interesting to work that out.
We pulled out
some of the rail for this shot
because I was like,
"I'm going Gone with the Wind, guys."
I'm going full-out.
I'm going full Western,
full melodrama, all of that stuff.
And that scene between the two of them
was obviously part
of my ongoing campaign
to ensure the belief
that Hawkeye is a dead man.
Even to the point where he says that
that's his last project at the house.
Really meaning,
"This is my last mission."
I mean, he might as well say,
"Don't worry, honey.
"It's just one more job.
It's perfectly safe."
And then walk under a ladder.
He's like Dead Meat in Hot Shots!
And it's all a ruse.
How do you find it?
It's pretty simple. You bring a magnet.
WHEDON: This is not
actually in Oslo, okay.
That part is a total lie.
The idea, though,
that Tony is searching his world,
the world of science,
and Thor is searching
the world of magic.
Obviously, there was
a much longer scene with Thor,
but there was also
at one point a version
where we just intercut
the two enormously,
the cyber search and the dream search.
And in the end,
we went with the least amount of stuff
to explain what knowledge
Thor needs to come back with.
Chris is great, and very patient with me,
because he's trying hard
not to be irrelevant.
And it's tough with Thor
because he doesn't speak
the way people do,
he doesn't live the way people do.
He can't just sort of be the casual guy,
although Chris is hilarious
at throwaway jokes.
And I kept saying to Chris,
"I'm gonna figure this out.
"I'm gonna give you
something really exciting."
And whether or not I succeeded
is open to some debate. (CHUCKLES)
But, God knows,
everything I've thrown at him,
he's done so well that it makes you
want to protect the character,
because he's the only one who's...
Well, he ain't from around here.
You said we would destroy
the Avengers, make a better world.
It will be better.
WHEDON: That fist, curling up in frame
on the left there,
that's another example of something
that could never have been done before
with what we could do in the first film.
Um...
Just these casual frames.
They're a little static.
Some of Ultron's stuff
was devised later,
was sort of honed later.
And this we actually shot on the day.
And the space was a little small
and didn't afford a lot of opportunities,
but I realised that I was so
into the things they were saying
that I felt like I dropped the ball
a little bit, visually.
And that's the case with Ultron.
In some cases, because
we were building it after the fact,
and we had a plate of the background
that we were then
animating him in front of,
so actual camera movement was
more difficult to put in late in the game.
And sometimes I think
I just missed some opportunities.
I look at all the opportunities
I've missed.
I look at this movie as a series
of compromises and failures.
Just so you know,
I'm not actually gonna emphasise that,
and I'm talking to my shrink about it.
But the things about it that I love,
I love very much.
But I always think,
"I could've done better there."
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
- He's uploading himself into the body.
- Where?
WHEDON: And this is Claudia,
who is so impressive,
doing the hardest thing in the movie,
emotional exposition,
where we give her
a ton of dialogue to say,
then we add to it later,
and she's still emotional and cool.
ROMANOFF: No manifest.
That could be him.
There. It's a truck from the lab.
Right above you, Cap.
On the loop by the bridge.
WHEDON: Coming to Seoul was
a real opportunity for us.
Not a lot of people had shot there.
And we had to sit down with
one of their ministers of culture,
and explain what it was
we were trying to do,
and make sure that we were gonna
show Seoul in a good light.
And, in fact, why we liked the city was
because we knew we were
gonna have a chase
throughout the whole city and...
Not the whole city, it's one of
the most enormous cities in the world.
(CHUCKLING)
But through some lovely bits of it.
And we wanted a place that
was very modern and very exciting,
and not gritty in the same sense.
We wanted everyplace
to register as itself.
Johannesburg, Seoul.
And then we wanted
to fly under buildings,
when clearly he could have
flown over them,
just because they were there
and they were pretty.
You know what's in that cradle?
WHEDON: I've talked about ILM
and the extraordinary work they did,
which I can't say enough about.
But, as is the case with movies like this,
there's hundreds of houses
doing various effects and various bits.
This whole sequence,
the Ultron portion of it,
most of the major work in it
was done by Dneg.
And the houses are really good
about helping each other out.
Some of these shots were shared
by, like, four different houses.
Somebody's doing a background,
somebody's doing
a stunt face replacement,
somebody's doing a digital creature.
And with the Vision,
somebody at one house did body,
one did face, one did cape,
one did background. It was just...
But they're all very cooperative,
they're very inventive,
and everybody brings that extra quality.
A lot of these low-angle shots you see
of Cap going over camera,
her going through alleys,
were shot with
a little remote-controlled car,
which honestly is my favourite thing.
(CHUCKLES)
I like the remote-control car
way more than the motorcycle
(LAUGHS) because it's just so cool.
This moment here, um,
Bryan Andrews, storyboard artist,
who has done a lot of great stuff for us,
came in after the fact and looked at this.
And we had knocked all the cars over.
It was Bryan's idea
to add Captain America
to what we referred to
as the "car ballet."
And it took something that was pretty,
but pointlessly destructive,
and turned it into a moment of peril
for one of our guys,
and made it not just more exciting,
but worthy.
And that kind of feedback,
and having those new eyes
is so crucial and so exciting,
because it just keeps getting better.
The thing about a sequence like this
is it's always about the connection
between the players.
The more you can connect them,
the more we would add dialogue
between them.
It wasn't just stunt, stunt, stunt.
You felt their humanity.
There was an emotional thread
going through here
for Scarlett when we shot it,
that she had been rejected
by Banner very brutally.
If you see the entire sequence on DVD,
it's a rough thing,
and it made her have
this kind of self-destructive,
just brave kind of fatalism.
And then some of this stuff was shot
after that had been cut,
but most of it beforehand,
and so you end up with
someone who's playing something
that is no longer in the film.
And it's just a very delicate process
to make sure that you don't have
some inexplicable
emotional malaise from her.
But luckily she's the kind of person
who hides that sort of stuff,
and as a character, she plays
on the surface as very in control.
And so we were able to cut it together
without it seeming strange.
But it also means that
one of the emotional arcs
of this sequence disappeared,
and then you end up
relying on spectacle,
which is the last thing that you want,
even though the spectacle
is beautifully put together.
And you have the kids
going from villain to hero,
which is a major plot turn.
And you have Ultron
disappearing with Widow,
so you're servicing the story,
but emotionally there's not as much
going on as there would have been.
And that's complicated because
once you start a sequence this massive
without that particular emotional hook,
it's very easy for people
to get pummelled.
But by bringing the kids in,
by cutting it down,
and just by the beautiful job
Jeff did cutting it,
I think it sustains.
But I'm always gonna look at what's not.
Almost all of that was in Korea,
or shot with plates from Korea.
This is actually in England,
in Longcross,
a place we used for a few of the sets
and exteriors near Shepperton,
where we shot most of it,
that they dressed up very specifically
and brought the trains.
I think we brought them from Korea,
the two train cars that we had.
Dressed them in.
One of the things I love about
having all these characters
is the way their alliances
can shift and change,
and Captain America's
never expressed anything
but sympathy for these guys,
even while he was fighting them.
So for him to suddenly
say one mean thing,
and then, boom, they're allies.
It's exciting,
but it also feels emotionally logical,
and then it brings us back
to the idea that Tony is the villain.
One of the true villainous moments
he has is telling Hawkeye,
"Why don't you disappear?" and
I'm gonna make an evil eyebrow face,
because I'm about to do
something crazy.
And the idea that
he's gonna lean into the very thing
that is wrong with him
is interesting to me,
because the idea that
the worst thing about us is useful
gives this thing texture.
Look at the reflection of Jarvis
in Bruce's glasses.
That's something that...
That level of detail is...
Because, of course, Jarvis is not there,
that was added later.
And that level of care and detail
is in every frame of this movie.
Our VFX head, Chris Townsend,
was running 97 different houses.
And one of the things
I love about Marvel is that
good enough is never good enough.
And the level of texture
and detail and character
that they put into VFX doubles,
this sort of amorphous character.
It's so complicated figuring out,
"How do we make him
feel like a program that's talking?"
Give him personality, but not too much.
Make him not cartoony.
Make him feel integrated into a universe
that is, at its base, very grounded.
We're asking that question
about every effect, every day.
And the stuff they gave me
is so human on every level.
And ultimately these stories never work.
This scene was created in post.
There was some amusement
at the literal translation
of what had been post-viz.
On the left the... I don't want to
say phallic, uh, implement of...
But if you look carefully at it, oh, yeah.
And we sort of laughed about it,
but then I decided I wanted to keep it,
since, as he becomes more aggressive,
the idea that his iconography
becomes more male.
When he's just a program,
it's very Georgia O'Keeffe in the lab,
and then now
he's becoming pure aggression.
This is also one of my favourite
performances from James and ILM.
The love and poignancy
of his dream deferred,
and how insane it makes him.
We had another version of the scene
that was just too civilised,
something I do a lot,
where people are
just holding a cup of tea
instead of ripping their own faces
and guts apart.
And Scarlett, with no lines,
giving me beautiful stuff,
and the idea obviously
of somebody doing the infamous
and, in fact,
somewhat clichéd Nietzsche quote,
but then putting a genuine spin on it.
A very literal one.
It was very exciting and fun.
And designing his final armour
to be different,
it was super tough
to find something that worked.
It covers his face and some of
the greatness of his delivery a little bit,
and I think we all regretted
that a little bit.
But it also brings him
more towards the Ultron
that we know from the comics,
and gives us that distance
that we need to get into the final act.
- ROGERS: Shut it down!
- Nope, not gonna happen.
You don't know what you're doing.
And you do?
She's not in your head?
WHEDON: Once again, internal conflict
is the thing that makes
these things work.
And that's fairly badass of Banner.
WANDA: You don't know what's in there.
ROGERS: This isn't a game!
- No, no. Go on.
- (POWERING DOWN)
- You were saying?
- (GUNSHOT)
WHEDON: As I said, this moment came
from just walking the set and saying,
"Well, they are talking a lot,
and he's very fast.
"Why wouldn't he just... Oh, okay."
And then, of course, the call back,
which I threw in late in the game.
It was just very necessary,
because you would
not remember that phrase
from the beginning
of the movie to the end.
And at the end of the movie,
it becomes quite important.
Watch her particularly in this moment,
when she casts a spell through herself,
boom, to him.
All of that movement
was very specifically choreographed.
It's probably the first thing that
I worked on.
I worked with Jennifer White,
a dancer and a choreographer,
with Lizzie, and the three of us
spent a lot of time
with me translating
what are very literal moves
to create the language of her magic,
so that people would understand it
and not just think,
"Oh, she can do anything she wants."
It would be like throwing a magic punch.
And besides, it meant choreography,
and if you've seen the movie,
you know I like a lot of that.
That shot of Scarlet, which is one
of my favourites in the film as well,
because she's been desperate to keep
this from happening more than anyone,
because she's seen
the apocalyptic vision that it contained,
and yet, when she sees the Vision,
what's on her face is clearly
fear/I am falling in love with you.
(CHUCKLES) And as I grew up
reading the comics,
where they actually fall in love
and get married,
it's nice to throw to that a little bit
without overplaying it.
This was another moment that
came from just walking the set.
And originally, there was a big fight
between him and Thor
as he was still becoming
a conscious guy, and then
we pulled that out, but it all led to
the moment where he is at the window,
'cause I thought,
"First of all, look at this cool window
"and I need a reason
to shoot outside it."
But, more importantly,
the stages of his self-awareness
involve seeing the world,
the outside world,
outside of himself,
and then seeing himself in reflection.
And those feel like two separate stages
of any human understanding
of existence.
And he goes through that,
and is complete.
- Then why would you bring...
- Because Stark is right.
WHEDON: There's a lot of buys
in something like this.
And to have a purple guy show up
in the beginning of the third act,
uh, it's a big buy.
And so to be able to
have these little moments
that help explain the story of
his rather convenient consciousness,
it's both necessary
and an exciting piece of texture.
I can barely talk
about how cool Bettany is,
and what great work
they did on his face,
both in makeup, and then after the fact,
because all the rendering
of textures on his face
made it very easy to give him
what we refer to as digital Botox,
to take away the expressiveness
in his eyes,
and so the little wrinkles and things
that you wouldn't expect
to see on an android,
that you need for him
to be what Bettany brought,
is actually very difficult to render
and very beautifully accomplished.
This moment when he asks,
"What will you do?"
This was part of my recalibration
of the Vision
from Jarvis to the Vision,
where he basically lays it out,
"You can't really stop me."
(CHUCKLES)
I wrote him before as,
I would say, polite.
And here, he has his own thing,
his own agenda
that goes beyond humanity.
And later on has
what is, for me, the most
important moment in the movie,
based on his understanding
of life beyond us and our agenda.
I'm not what you are,
and not what you intended.
So, there may be no way
to make you trust me.
WHEDON: And then,
of course, there's this.
The great thing is,
we set it up for the whole movie
without anybody realising
we were setting something up.
Well done.
WHEDON: Chris improv'd that line
(CHUCKLES)
In the moment, which I love.
But it's also not just a trick,
it's an important piece of storytelling.
Not just because of who the Vision is
and what he's going to mean,
but because we need to trust him.
And there's no better way to say,
categorically, (CHUCKLES)
"we can," than that.
Now, you'll hear Tony talking about
"Someone's gonna die,"
over a picture of Hawkeye
looking at his wife once again,
leaning into the...
"He's definitely going out."
This speech,
which got tweaked somewhat,
there was a point at which
I almost didn't shoot it
because we shot a lot of footage,
and I thought,
"Well, we know what we're doing here."
But it became very, very crucial to me.
First of all, I thought Chris killed it,
and the footage looked wonderful.
But most importantly,
the idea that Ultron could be right,
that the Avengers could just be
a destructive bunch of thugs,
is important not only to articulate,
but for them to internalise,
so that you understand their idea
of the stakes of what's coming.
ROGERS: Keep the fight between us.
WHEDON: This, again, is a frame
you would never have seen
in the first movie.
This very tight close-up, long-lens thing
is a different vernacular,
but I never felt it was more effective
than it was there.
BANNER: Natasha!
Natasha!
WHEDON: Now, this is an
interesting piece of footage
because I wrote this scene...
We had a very different scene
with the Hulk and Ultron,
and it did not play.
It was good, but you just... It didn't fit.
And I kept saying,
"Well, we've got to do something else."
So I wrote this scene,
and the scene in between
the two of them that comes after,
and we did it in reshoots.
And what's interesting about it is
we never actually got them
on the same day.
And I'll explain more
when we see them again.
These pieces pounce... This is on
the outside of London. So is this.
A huge complex
where we built this church,
and where we built that bridge,
and basically turned it into
our biggest piece of real estate
in Eastern Europe.
Uh...
Have you been juicing?
Little vibranium cocktail?
WHEDON: And then where Hawkeye
and the Scarlet Witch are
is in northern Italy,
very close to
where the exterior of the fortress,
which is actually Fort Bard
in the Italian Alps, is.
So that we still had
that European flavour,
but we got some old world
and some more modern.
And really give it a realistic feel,
'cause unlike every other place we shot,
there is no Sokovia.
We didn't feel
we could take an actual city
and rip it out of the ground.
That seemed irresponsible,
even by our standards.
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
Go!
WHEDON: Another thing that's...
This kind of thing is insanely complex,
but made more so by the fact
that I was very determined
that we would have a passage of time.
That there would be
a pre-dawn sequence,
and then there would be dawn
when the sun was just rising,
and then there would be morning.
So that we would feel
the toll of this thing,
because I wanted it to
feel like it took a lot.
But inevitably you end up
reorganising certain things
and repurposing them,
so we had to go in
and kind of recolour certain things.
Make certain things
more pre-dawn purple,
and then brighten up some other things.
Occasionally the seams show,
but, in general,
they did a really good job
of keeping it all together.
And the main plot points were all
where they were supposed to be,
so most of the footage
we were able to use intact.
And, again, Ben Davis, our DP,
who is just a phenomenal master,
really leaned into the difficulty
of what it was he was going to
have to accomplish.
And there was so much to get,
and so much footage,
and so much epic stuff.
And then I started
putting restrictions of time
and when we could shoot,
and he just worked it all out.
Just one of those guys
who does not ever remark
upon the fact that his job is impossible,
and I'm grateful for it.
The voice in Tony's head
was originally a different actress,
but, again, the "girl Friday" thing
was something that
I liked very much, but...
And Friday was one of
his HUD personalities from the comics,
but when she came on as American,
the only way to establish who she was
as a sort of different person
was to have banter between them,
which literally meant establishing
an entirely new character
after the Vision.
So to give her the accent,
it sort of made
a little piece of shorthand.
ULTRON: When the dust settles,
the only thing living in this world
will be metal.
WHEDON: This is, again,
some of ILM's most beautiful work,
and flying around that place.
So he's playing the scene
with Dominique,
one of Scarlett's stand-ins.
She is playing the scene, because
they shot them on different days,
with Sean Maher, my old crony
from Firefly and Much Ado.
He seemed like he would be a good fit,
since we knew we couldn't get
them both at the same time.
And, oddly enough,
from that back angle,
his jaw looks exactly
like Mark Ruffalo's.
So, it's complicated.
It's a classic Marvel problem,
when you make these giant movies
that you can't actually get the actors
on the same day, occasionally,
for intimate scenes.
Frustrating, but you work around it,
and luckily Dominique and Mark
are both really strong actors
and gave their counterparts
a lot to work with.
This stuff is always deadly.
Creating some kind of sense of scale
that is realistic is so difficult.
And this work, which is pure digital,
is, to me, just really staggering.
But to keep the sense,
and, I think, in shooting and in editing...
Not editing, but in sort of the way
we were looking at post-vis
and kind of setting these things up,
I feel like I could've been clearer
about the feeling of that floating city.
Stark, you worry about
bringing the city back down safely.
WHEDON: This was
all added after the fact,
but it's one of my favourite bits,
and Evans was more than happy
to have that little speech.
And this was also added to give
a very useful sense of
the scale of the thing,
and the height of it.
That is Dominique, by the way.
She had a bigger role in the film.
You saw her at the beginning
of the film,
her and her little brother,
and they had a bigger role.
Once again, I wanted...
When she calls out for him to be saved,
I wanted them to be
more than just extras,
I wanted us to know
that Pietro knew them
and that it was important to save them.
But at the end of the day,
as I often find in these movies,
people really just
wanna see the Avengers.
WANDA: How could I let this happen?
BARTON: Hey, hey, you okay?
- This is all our fault.
- Hey, look at me.
It's your fault, it's everyone's fault.
Who cares?
WHEDON: Now, this scene,
obviously, is a favourite.
We have what I refer to,
and I'm not the first person
to use the phrase, as inoculation.
We're fighting an army of robots,
and I have a bow and arrow.
None of this makes sense.
(BARTON GRUNTING)
WHEDON: Where he says the thing
we're all thinking.
And it plays,
and it's also his little power talk,
his little pep.
It's emotional.
His whole relationship
with these characters...
I knew what I wanted to do with Pietro,
and I knew that he was gonna have
a relationship with them
that was incredibly contentious.
But part of it came simply from the fact
that all of their action together in Italy
was because it was the first thing
we were shooting,
and they were the only actors available.
And everybody else was off
having babies or doing publicity
or making another Marvel movie,
or one of the 19 movies they had
all made during this. I mean...
So they said,
"Well, we're gonna start in Italy,
"and you've got these three characters."
And so what was
a sort of matter of convenience
became a real arc.
I said, "Well, okay, then these guys
are really gonna have a relationship
"that progresses
and means something."
And for the guy
who likes Pietro the least,
who discounts him completely,
and who is sort of a father figure
to these kids,
for Pietro to prove himself
the truest hero of the bunch
by saving him
is, I think, much more interesting
and emotional
than if it just happened to happen.
This is definitely a point at which,
putting things together,
it turns into crowd-pleasing gags
that are gags.
This is a point in the movie where I...
When we were putting it all together,
I felt a little bit,
"We've lost the mission,
we're doing cool gags,
"but what we're not doing
is setting up moments
"so that when something
like this happens,
"it means everything it could."
The difficulty in taking
something like this
is not having these moments,
it's earning them.
It's setting them up,
and making sure
that when they happen,
they mean something.
This was another specific piece
of magic,
the idea that she's actually
pulling energy out of the ground.
For me, there was the idea,
a little bit, of,
"She's using Sokovia itself,
"again, which she sort of represents,
against them."
And here, he had a different line,
"I hate that kid.
I really don't like that kid."
And I said, "Well,
maybe try 'No one will know, '
"or something, and then just riff."
And then all of this is just Jeremy.
Which just killed us all on the day,
and is one of my favourite things
in the film.
And, again, plays very heavily
into what's to come.
Getting to create the look for these two,
the look for their magic,
was extremely exciting.
And whenever we got her red
up against his blue,
to me, it's very dazzling,
and putting, again,
that stuff to the movement,
it's some of the last stuff to come in,
and so you're always going,
"Well, I think it looks cool."
But then when it finally
does come together,
it's much more than that.
Obviously, that scene was
a little joke moment,
but it was also there to show
that he can't actually
always outrun a bullet.
Keep the atomic action doubling back.
FRIDAY: That could vaporise the city.
And everyone on it.
(PANTING)
WHEDON: In addition
to the passage of time,
we also wanted to, obviously,
go in and out of the clouds
to change the light up that way.
And anything I could do
to make Ben Davis' life harder,
he used to make my movie look better.
ROMANOFF: Cap,
these people are going nowhere.
- If Stark finds a way to blow this rock...
- Not till everyone's safe.
Everyone up here versus everyone
down there? There's no math there.
WHEDON: Again,
there's a little bit of missing context
when she talks about
she's ready to die up there.
Originally, that had been part of a run of
she was still feeling upset
about things going south with Banner,
but at this point
that's a different relationship.
But because it's such a soldier thing,
it still played.
And this, we're actually using
the Alan Silvestri cue
from the first time the carrier takes off
in the first movie.
We used some of Alan's stuff
throughout the movie
because it really connected us
to the other movie when we needed to,
but never more than here.
FURY: Nice, right?
WHEDON: It really does,
when we saw the finished effects,
which were so beautiful, I thought,
"Oh, yeah, this was
a science-fiction movie at one point."
And there, Fury's got his mojo back,
he's got his coat back,
Hill's back at her station.
All of this, the set you see,
is exactly what we had.
We didn't have even any reference
of the old set,
so we had to build a lot of it digitally,
or take it from tails of shots
from the first movie.
That shot of the rafts coming out
is also one of my favourites.
I think it's kind of the mission statement
of the movie.
This is not so bad.
WHEDON: And I love Aaron so much
in that moment.
Let's load them up.
WHEDON: To bring the carrier back...
So, for example, what's behind her?
It's just a shot we took people
out of from the first movie
(WHISPERING)
because we really couldn't
actually build the entire set again.
It's way too big.
Getting the two of these guys
flying together
and bantering together again is
just a really nice bit of personal texture,
and a way to sort of lead us
towards where we're going
with the end of the movie
in terms of the Avengers lineup.
The reason I had him
talking about War Machine
in the first place was that, again,
like Fury mentioning the Helicarrier,
for people who are not
familiar with that universe,
I needed people to know that he has
an Iron Man suit that he flies around in,
and is a superhero.
So that when he showed up,
people wouldn't not know
what that was.
Oh, God!
WHEDON: Aaron, there, is obviously
from Captain America 2.
I thought his little sequence in Cap 2
was one of my favourite parts
of the movie,
and so when Fury had collected
a bunch of people to run the carrier,
I thought it would be emotionally
effective if he was one of them.
...and as long as there is life
in my breast...
I am running out of things to say!
Are you ready?
WHEDON: If there's one thing
Hemsworth is absolutely great at,
it's undercutting Thor's pomposity.
He can sell the Asgardian thing,
but when he gets to do
something casual, he's such a delight.
This was obviously, again,
one of the most difficult
and sort of giant 3D-friendly shots
that I insisted, "We need this.
"We need the roller-coaster ride.
"We need to remember
that we're up in the air."
And then later on
in the process was like,
"But I also want him to be
doing some math during it."
Because the idea that he is
in the middle of a firefight,
and he's doing calculations,
being a scientist in his head,
that, for me, it's what makes him cool,
and it's what keeps the fighting from,
again, just being a punch-a-thon.
Romanoff.
You and Banner better not be
playing "hide the zucchini."
ROMANOFF: Relax, shellhead.
Not all of us can fly.
(PANTING)
- What's the drill?
- This is the drill.
If Ultron gets a hand
on the core, we lose.
WHEDON: So this is where the movie
kind of unabashedly
turns into Rio Bravo.
Little bit of Zulu, Dawn of the Dead.
It doesn't matter.
If you've read the comic books,
there are very famous panels
by George Pérez
of just a sea of Ultrons
attacking the Avengers,
and that, to me,
was what I wanted to evoke.
I also think that the work
of Bryan Hitch, who did the Ultimates,
which is really in many ways
the father of the MCU,
particularly the Avengers,
that style of very muscular action,
is going on here.
But most importantly,
what's going on here
is not a sort of laid out, literal fight.
The detail work in the backgrounds
of shields and arrows,
and the idea of all the teamwork
and all of the things that are going on.
What specifically is going on
is much less important to me in this
than the idea of this fight,
than the feeling of it.
Rather than set up specific stakes
beyond "We must protect this"
and "Here they all come,"
what I wanted to do was just show
the feeling of an Avenger.
It's the closest I feel like
I've ever come to panel art
and, to be specific, Thor there has
ripped out someone's spine and head
and is hitting other people
with his head,
which means that this movie is,
at least on one level, awesome.
I feel about the sequence that
there are more missed opportunities,
that I should have spent
months more fine-tuning it,
but I also feel that
it is as beautiful as anything
I've ever put on film.
I feel this combination of
despair and extraordinary elation
when I watch it, I just want...
Again, I want to
make sure I've earned it,
and I want to spend even more time
watching Thor hit people
with somebody's head.
The rhythm of it
was done very musically.
That big hero theme
is another piece by Danny Elfman,
and among the most important,
if not the most important, in the film.
And it came in
somewhat late in the process,
but then Jeff Ford re-tweaked
everything to fit its rhythm.
Its rhythms were very close
to what we had been using,
but then, uh, we had to play to it.
The musicality and the physicality
are what interest me there.
I wished I could've hurt more people,
I wished I could've taken
more of a toll on the characters.
The complexity of
not just how we shot it,
but when we had all the people,
and what came before and after what,
meant that you couldn't be
as specific as I would have
liked in that sense,
but it's still... That sequence is, for me,
the reason we show up.
And this sequence is, for me,
the reason I show up,
where two people are in an apocalypse,
talking about eating in the dining room.
That says more about their relationship
than anything else I could've done,
and it's something
that I always love about Marvel,
is that they're not afraid
of that conversation.
Even at this late and very
sort of momentous stage,
they're like,
"Yeah, you should totally have...
"They should talk about re-decorating.
"That makes perfect sense."
And I don't feel that
there are a lot of studios
who would've embraced that
in the same way.
Again, you can hear someone saying,
"You're safe now,"
as he gets on the boat.
I couldn't be more shameless
about trying to convince everyone
that Hawkeye's gonna die.
Oh, no. One more time, back in.
Yeah, no.
It's over.
This also came late.
I think it was Jeff Ford's idea
that we knew Thor was
gonna hit it from up top,
but the idea that Iron Man's
down below came late.
Iron Man's action usually
gets enhanced late in the film
because, like the Hulk and Ultron,
he's not there.
He doesn't exist,
that's a CGI character, and so
you think you know what you
want him to do, and then you find,
"Wait, there's a way
to up the stakes here."
This is another thing that I feel like
(CHUCKLING)
other studios wouldn't let you do,
is have him just singing
like that, to himself.
And then getting genuinely brutal.
I wanted this to be unlovely.
And when I said to Jeremy,
"Just look at it and know
that your death is imminent,
"and that you're okay with it."
The look on his face was, um, priceless.
And the cut to Wanda with the sound
of what's going on here
before anything happens,
is revealed, rather, is also great.
I almost didn't wanna cut
to that overhead shot of him
because he did that fall,
just face-planted, so beautifully
that I wanted people to see.
But then I couldn't resist the hyperbole
of being directly above him
when he landed on the ground.
Emotional hyperbole,
let's face it, that's my jam.
We shot that...
That's one of the first scenes we shot,
and then we re-shot it, where she...
They have their last exchange,
and then she senses he's dead,
and goes down on her knees,
and the first time we shot it, she wept.
And just an enormous amount of snot
came flying, just pouring down.
It was very realistic,
it was kind of awesome.
She was laughing about it afterwards,
she's like,
"I probably should have
warned you that would happen."
So we dialled that
back the second time.
But she still conveys such
extraordinary grief and gravitas,
and her bit with Ultron after
is one of my favourite things
I've ever put on film.
As much as this process was difficult,
that's something I end up
saying a lot in this movie.
Wanda.
If you stay here, you'll die.
WHEDON: He had different lead-ins
to her line, "I just did."
I liked the idea that what he said
was something to try and help her,
that he couldn't quite get past the fact
that they had a relationship,
that she meant something to him.
Now, see, there's the shield.
The severing of his chest
is in the exact shape of the shield.
It's hard to talk over that scene
because they're so good in it.
But I did, so I guess I must be awesome.
And then, of course,
the final problem.
And, of course, Iron Man's in
the thick of it, in his own literal,
when I say literal, sort of visual hell.
He's down below, in the inferno,
and Thor is up above,
and so much of this movie
is about that juxtaposition.
This part is
what I refer to as,
"Can you read my mind?"
It's a little shamelessly romantic,
but then that's not about theme,
that's just about the two of them.
It's about the mission,
which was to save everyone.
And obviously it's also a nod to
the romance they will later share
in the comic book universe.
I can't say what's gonna happen
in the Marvel Cinematic Universe.
But, emotionally,
it takes that big falling rock
and turns it into something more.
ROMANOFF: The job is finished.
Now I need you to turn
this bird around, okay?
We can't track you in stealth mode.
So help me out.
WHEDON: This is another, um,
really beautiful performance.
I shot Mark on
a mo-cap stage doing this.
But, again, ILM has to
bring their own integrity
to what his face is doing,
and what was great was
that we kept saying, "Less."
And then that shot,
Scarlett was doing her ADR,
and so for the first time
was seeing his side of that,
and she looked at it, that beautiful shot
from behind him, pulling away,
and she just went,
(MIMICKING CRYING)
"Oh, my God, that's so emotional.
"Fat man in a little car."
(IN NORMAL VOICE)
So that sequence is only ever known
as "Fat Man in a Little Car."
Of you?
WHEDON: And then this is the thing.
This scene is kind of the reason.
I refer to it as "Miller's Crossing."
The mob hit, The Godfather,
"Can you get me off for old times?"
The civilised kill
is always a beautiful scene,
but this is where I feel you get to know
the Vision in a way
that you hadn't before.
And you get to make
a summer tentpole movie
where you actually get to say
that humanity is doomed.
They're doomed.
Yes.
But a thing isn't beautiful
because it lasts.
It's a privilege to be among them.
WHEDON: That was just
a nice thing to think,
and then to have somebody say.
But the first time, because
they did these scenes together,
so often people don't, but they did
all of their scenes together, together,
and the first time James ever said,
"They're doomed," and he said, "Yes."
And he's established himself as the
most noble, worthy of the hammer.
And yet, he says "Yes" without pause.
Um...
That, for me, is...
What few hairs I have left,
it raised them right up to hear
the sympathy and certitude
with which he said that.
Just loved it.
This, obviously, (CHUCKLES)
the "Best Years of Our Lives" moment.
The "I'm standing in the kitchen,
and I know he's there."
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
Maria Hill and Cho, back in action.
And, of course, our boy Stellan.
The idea that everyone we know is
in on it, is a part of the new world,
and that everybody's
moving and shaking except her.
FURY: One of our tech boys
flagged this.
WHEDON: This whole sequence, we...
'Cause it was a place in London,
a convention centre, it's beautiful.
And the question of how to dress it,
we spent a long while on,
(CHUCKLES)
and then I suddenly was like,
"Wait a minute. Don't dress it.
"Don't put anything in it.
Don't put anybody in it.
"Just have a big,
beautiful space with these guys."
Because that's enough.
In fact, it expresses
her emotional state much better,
and it also gives it an epic quality that,
despite the hugeness
of the place in the wider shots,
you don't get in the same way.
Nothing lasts forever.
Trouble, Ms. Romanoff.
No matter who wins or loses,
trouble still comes around.
WHEDON: This next bit...
STARK: We're dealing
with something new.
The Vision is artificial intelligence.
WHEDON: We did this in re-shoots,
and I had said
we really need somebody
that expresses the gravitas
of what they've been through,
and Kevin said,
"Or they could make that joke about
the hammer that you almost put in."
I'm like, "Okay, yeah,
let's do that instead. '' (CHUCKLES)
And I think, ultimately,
my desire for people to
internalise what's happened
and pay for it is sometimes
not the best instinct
for these summer movies.
I'm at war (SIGHS)
With my own intentions
when I make these things
because I want to make a fantasy,
but I'm offended by
the irresponsibility of the fantastic.
And, uh, so the tone of the thing is
something I have to
play with very specifically.
And there is a moment
where I feel that I got it wrong.
And putting the score together
came late in the process,
later than it should've,
and there was one cue
that we had two versions of,
and it's Cap's revelation that he...
Or his telling Tony that he's at home
here in this place.
We had a cue that expressed
the kind of doubt and poignancy in that.
And I suggested,
"Well, what if we tried putting in
"a version of
the Captain America theme there?"
And everyone liked that better.
And, I mean, absolutely everyone.
But every time I watch it now, I go,
"No. Should've had the doubt,"
because I don't want him to be saying,
"Oh, no, it's great. I found my home."
I want him to be saying,
"I'm a guy who never will."
And, "I'm not satisfied.
"I'm not proud of this,
that this is what I am.
"It's just something I've come to accept,"
so that music cue will drive me crazy,
like many things, until the end of time,
possibly because I'm already crazy.
The whole point of this movie,
and part of the conflict I described,
was the idea of closing,
of changing, of something that ends.
And yet,
something that's just beginning.
And luckily, because
the Avengers are defined
by the idea that
they're always changing,
they literally changed their roster
in their second issue,
it was easy to have my cake and eat it.
To say, "We've lost something.
Camelot is over,"
but also to say,
"Exciting adventures yet to come."
Some people have complained that
Cap left that sentence unfinished.
I've never been more certain of
anything in my life, that he needed to.
It was in the script exactly as that.
The first time I ever told Evans
how the movie was gonna end,
he just lost it because you don't say it,
you don't finish the sentence.
You let the audience
finish the sentence.
And you also say, "There is more."
This whole sequence is my favourite
of these that I've seen.
The idea of...
The post-credits sequences
in Marvel are always really good.
This one, I thought,
is lovely because it...
The idea that they have been
immortalised in statue.
There's a statue at the beginning
you see before Grand Central,
which is the heroes of New York,
and its cops and first-responders,
and we had a whole sequence
about the unveiling of that,
and then it was taken out,
but we made sure we kept
the statue in the movie.
So, to put these guys in marble,
it elevates them,
but, to me, it also grounds them
in a way of saying, "Yeah,
these guys were veterans of a war
"that they fought to the last,
"and, in some cases,
gave the last full measure."
And that they should be remembered,
and that an era is over.
And as this is my goodbye
to the world of Marvel,
it seems like a nice one.
But there's still this guy.
This was exactly what I pitched,
again, before the movie.
Loki failed, Red Skull failed.
Ronan failed.
So, it's time.
Third movie, it's time,
which is somebody else's problem.
There is one more thing I have to say.
I'm not going to speak through
48 minutes of credits,
though you should watch them all
because every person listed in them
did extraordinary work,
and I'm enormously grateful.
And I apologise to all the people
I didn't mention because I should've.
But I did promise that I would say
something about an Easter egg.
I don't...
Usually, I try not to be self-indulgent.
I just had a feeling
there was a connection
between the evils of this world
and the evils of all worlds.
And there is that one shot
in Thor's dream
of three guys in an archway,
wearing three masks,
and the masks are very expressionistic,
so it might be hard
to see exactly what they are,
and we only held on them for a moment.
And they were originally
seen over a line of Thor's
that was taken out, where he says,
"It's been a long journey,
and dark forces followed me."
And the idea that
there is something bigger at stake,
which we hit in
his revelation of the jewels,
but "dark forces"
was when you cut to those guys.
Basically, though expressionistic,
they are based on three animals,
a wolf, a ram, and a hart.
And some of you might know
what that means to me.
Thank you for listening. We're done.