"Whosoever, be he worthy,
shall have the pow..."
Whatever, man, it's a trick.
It is much more than that, my friend.
- If I lift it, do I get to rule Asgard?
- Yes, of course.
I will be fair but firmly cruel.
Be right back.
- Are you even pulling?
- Are you on my team?
- Just represent, pull!
- Alright, let's go.
Come on, Cap.
Nothing.
Oh, no, no.
That's not a question I need answered.
The handle's imprinted.
"Whosoever carries Thor's fingerprints"
is, I think, the literal translation.
Yes, that's a
very interesting theory.
I have a simpler one:
You're all not worthy.
How could you be worthy?
You're all puppets tangled in...
strings.
Strings.
It's the end.
The end of the path I started us on.
Nothing lasts forever.
But now
I'm free.
There are
no strings on me.
translated by :
|| killer_sub ||