1
00:01:34,427 --> 00:01:35,828
You ready?

2
00:02:02,288 --> 00:02:05,057
<i>How am I doing?</i>
Sure you want to know?

3
00:02:05,059 --> 00:02:08,460
"Does your boyfriend
always get his way?"

4
00:02:08,462 --> 00:02:10,762
Yes.

5
00:02:10,764 --> 00:02:13,165
"Does he admit
when he's wrong?"

6
00:02:13,167 --> 00:02:15,734
Never.

7
00:02:15,736 --> 00:02:17,903
Does your boyfriend know how
to build a fire with no matches?

8
00:02:17,905 --> 00:02:20,405
Answer is D, who cares.

9
00:02:20,407 --> 00:02:22,774
A, yes. Very well.

10
00:02:22,776 --> 00:02:24,176
Sorry, that question's
not on here.

11
00:02:24,178 --> 00:02:26,111
<i>It should be in there.</i>
Sorry.

12
00:02:26,113 --> 00:02:27,846
So you're still zero.

13
00:02:48,769 --> 00:02:52,771
No-o-o!
Oh, yeah-h-h!

14
00:03:16,830 --> 00:03:18,564
Put your hands on the wheel.

15
00:04:12,085 --> 00:04:14,419
<i>Hello?</i>
Hey.

16
00:04:14,421 --> 00:04:17,289
<i>Just give me a second, will you?</i>
Yeah, sure.

17
00:04:17,291 --> 00:04:19,191
How you doin'?
Good, good, good.

18
00:04:19,193 --> 00:04:21,460
Uh, we're reserved
under Louis.

19
00:04:21,462 --> 00:04:23,195
What's the name?
Alex Louis.

20
00:04:25,732 --> 00:04:28,300
<i>Yeah, sign in here.
You're ready to go.</i>

21
00:04:28,302 --> 00:04:30,802
<i>Your canoe will be
right down there by the water.</i>

22
00:04:30,804 --> 00:04:32,604
<i>Bring it back Monday at five.</i>

23
00:04:32,606 --> 00:04:34,439
That's right,
back to work Tuesday.

24
00:04:34,441 --> 00:04:36,608
Need a map?
No, I'm good.

25
00:04:38,211 --> 00:04:39,444
You don't want a map?

26
00:04:39,446 --> 00:04:41,413
No. No.
I know this park well.

27
00:04:41,415 --> 00:04:43,282
It's kinda end of the season, right?

28
00:04:43,284 --> 00:04:45,083
I mean the weather
can change on you..

29
00:04:45,085 --> 00:04:46,585
... just turn on a dime.

30
00:04:46,587 --> 00:04:48,253
Less people.

31
00:04:48,255 --> 00:04:50,088
Amen to that.

32
00:04:50,090 --> 00:04:52,457
You mind me askin' you,
Mr. No Map..

33
00:04:52,459 --> 00:04:53,759
... where you're headed?

34
00:04:53,761 --> 00:04:56,228
Blackfoot Trail.
I can't wait to show her.

35
00:04:56,230 --> 00:04:58,664
It's her first time here.
It's gonna be awesome.

36
00:04:58,666 --> 00:05:01,066
I got some bad news for you,
I'm really sorry about this

37
00:05:01,068 --> 00:05:03,268
but Blackfoot Trail's
closed for the season.

38
00:05:03,270 --> 00:05:04,903
Why?
Had to.

39
00:05:04,905 --> 00:05:06,638
I mean, so many yahoos

40
00:05:06,640 --> 00:05:09,441
you know, trampin' around there,
disrespecting everything.

41
00:05:09,443 --> 00:05:11,109
This is a treasured site.

42
00:05:11,111 --> 00:05:12,778
I don't have to tell you
I guess.

43
00:05:12,780 --> 00:05:15,814
And Parks and Recreation
want to keep it that way.

44
00:05:15,816 --> 00:05:18,083
Look,
going to Blackfoot Trail

45
00:05:18,085 --> 00:05:20,152
is kinda the whole point
of this trip.

46
00:05:20,154 --> 00:05:21,987
It's 500 bucks

47
00:05:21,989 --> 00:05:24,089
if you're caught up there. Each.

48
00:05:24,091 --> 00:05:26,725
That'll be a 1000 bucks
expensive little camping trip.

49
00:05:28,861 --> 00:05:30,529
Alright.

50
00:05:30,531 --> 00:05:31,863
Jenn, you ready?

51
00:05:31,865 --> 00:05:33,999
Yeah.
Oh, hang on.

52
00:05:34,001 --> 00:05:36,335
Hey, rodeo,
here's your medical kit

53
00:05:36,337 --> 00:05:38,437
and there's a whistle in there,
try to bring that back

54
00:05:38,439 --> 00:05:40,639
and I'll try not to charge you.

55
00:05:40,641 --> 00:05:41,940
Thousand bucks?

56
00:05:42,675 --> 00:05:44,176
You're pretty good.

57
00:05:46,546 --> 00:05:48,814
Bye. You have a nice trip.

58
00:05:48,816 --> 00:05:49,948
<i>Thanks.</i>

59
00:06:09,202 --> 00:06:11,536
Really?
Last one.

60
00:06:11,538 --> 00:06:12,804
Come on, babe.

61
00:06:12,806 --> 00:06:14,339
This is really important.

62
00:06:14,341 --> 00:06:15,574
You know, we've been waiting
forever for this.

63
00:06:15,576 --> 00:06:18,176
I'm...
Just... just give me...

64
00:06:18,178 --> 00:06:21,079
They're all important.
Can't wait till we get back?

65
00:06:22,715 --> 00:06:24,850
Okay, I'm done. Okay?

66
00:06:24,852 --> 00:06:26,251
Alright.
I don't believe you, but..

67
00:06:26,253 --> 00:06:27,886
Well, putting it away,
so it's..

68
00:06:27,888 --> 00:06:29,654
Oh, hang on, hang on.
Let's take a picture.

69
00:06:29,656 --> 00:06:31,223
Just to mark the departure.

70
00:06:31,225 --> 00:06:33,091
Put it to good use, right?
Fine.

71
00:06:33,093 --> 00:06:34,092
Okay.

72
00:06:41,734 --> 00:06:43,168
Good.
Yeah.

73
00:06:43,170 --> 00:06:45,470
One of us looks good.
Alright.

74
00:07:23,876 --> 00:07:26,178
Hey.
Hey, have a good one.
Thanks a lot.

75
00:08:40,853 --> 00:08:42,354
Fuck!
You okay?

76
00:08:42,356 --> 00:08:45,857
Oh, fuck, fuck that!
Fuckin' hurt like a bitch.

77
00:08:45,859 --> 00:08:48,527
<i>You sure you're okay?</i>

78
00:08:48,529 --> 00:08:51,263
<i>Yeah. Yeah, yeah, I'll just walk it off.</i>

79
00:08:53,199 --> 00:08:55,200
This is for you.

80
00:08:56,736 --> 00:08:59,538
You look scared anyway.
Feel safe.

81
00:09:00,806 --> 00:09:02,607
I probably won't need it.

82
00:09:04,010 --> 00:09:06,111
Got it taken care of already.

83
00:09:10,149 --> 00:09:12,584
Look what I got.

84
00:09:12,586 --> 00:09:16,254
When did you get that?
I got it a few days ago. You're not gonna need it.

85
00:09:16,256 --> 00:09:19,157
Do you wanna have a good time
on this trip or do you want me to be freaking out?

86
00:09:19,159 --> 00:09:23,094
This is what makes me feel safe.
Okay. Okay.

87
00:09:23,096 --> 00:09:25,196
Well, if you can have it
it's useless in your bag.

88
00:09:25,198 --> 00:09:27,165
Give it to me. Thanks.

89
00:09:27,167 --> 00:09:29,834
Just gonna clip it
to your belt, alright?

90
00:09:29,836 --> 00:09:31,570
And you're not gonna need it.

91
00:09:33,205 --> 00:09:34,339
Bear spray.

92
00:09:36,742 --> 00:09:38,009
Wonder what other goodies
you have in there.

93
00:09:38,011 --> 00:09:39,411
Nothin'.
Let's see.

94
00:09:39,413 --> 00:09:42,147
I don't have anything in there.
Hey, there's nothing.

95
00:09:43,416 --> 00:09:45,517
Oh, come on.
What?

96
00:09:45,519 --> 00:09:48,019
Seriously?

97
00:09:48,021 --> 00:09:50,055
This is a road flare.
I know what it is.

98
00:09:50,057 --> 00:09:52,223
Yeah. This is for when your car
breaks down on the side of the highway.

99
00:09:52,225 --> 00:09:53,391
Mm-hmm.
You know this.

100
00:09:53,393 --> 00:09:55,860
I know you know this.

101
00:09:55,862 --> 00:09:58,096
Jenn, come on, if you wanted a flare,
I could've picked up a pen flare.

102
00:09:58,098 --> 00:10:00,031
They sell them
at any camping store.

103
00:10:03,102 --> 00:10:05,003
Here's your flare.
Thank you.

104
00:10:07,740 --> 00:10:09,808
You ready?
Think so.

105
00:10:09,810 --> 00:10:11,343
Okay.

106
00:10:13,946 --> 00:10:16,047
Oh, my God.

107
00:10:19,385 --> 00:10:21,353
You good?
Yes.

108
00:10:46,245 --> 00:10:49,614
Huh?
What, sorry, what?

109
00:10:49,616 --> 00:10:52,350
Jenn, you know
we'd be lucky to see

110
00:10:52,352 --> 00:10:53,918
anything bigger
than a chipmunk, right?

111
00:10:53,920 --> 00:10:54,886
Mm-hmm.

112
00:11:17,043 --> 00:11:18,410
Hi.
Hey.

113
00:11:42,802 --> 00:11:43,968
Pfft! No!

114
00:11:49,308 --> 00:11:52,077
Hey, look at that.
That's cute.

115
00:11:52,079 --> 00:11:54,045
We should take it.

116
00:11:54,047 --> 00:11:55,780
Here's a good spot.
Yeah.

117
00:11:59,152 --> 00:12:00,885
Counselor, back up, please.

118
00:12:18,938 --> 00:12:20,905
Tryin' to turn me on right now?

119
00:12:20,907 --> 00:12:22,407
Is it working?

120
00:12:22,409 --> 00:12:24,476
Oh, yeah. It's pretty hot.

121
00:12:25,778 --> 00:12:27,479
Speaking of..

122
00:12:31,550 --> 00:12:33,518
... do you remember the little
swimming hole we walked by?

123
00:12:33,520 --> 00:12:36,788
Nope, I don't. No.
Really?

124
00:12:38,791 --> 00:12:40,725
You said you would.
<i>I didn't say that.</i>

125
00:12:40,727 --> 00:12:41,793
Yes, you did.

126
00:12:41,795 --> 00:12:43,628
I said maybe.
No, no, no.

127
00:12:43,630 --> 00:12:46,231
You said yes.
Come on, babes.

128
00:12:46,233 --> 00:12:49,467
No. It's like when you say, "Do you
want to order Chinese food tonight?"

129
00:12:49,469 --> 00:12:52,904
And I go, "Maybe,"
and then we get Italian.

130
00:12:52,906 --> 00:12:54,105
It's like that.

131
00:12:54,107 --> 00:12:55,940
I'm gonna be
all lonely by myself.

132
00:12:55,942 --> 00:12:57,575
Well, no one's making you
do this.

133
00:12:57,577 --> 00:12:58,810
Stop it!

134
00:13:03,082 --> 00:13:05,350
Oh, my God, please.
What if there's..

135
00:13:08,120 --> 00:13:09,587
Don't leave me hangin', babe.

136
00:13:12,057 --> 00:13:13,491
Okay, okay. Fine.

137
00:13:28,675 --> 00:13:30,074
You ready?
No.

138
00:13:30,076 --> 00:13:32,110
Come on.

139
00:13:37,082 --> 00:13:40,819
5... 4... 3, 2, 1!

140
00:13:40,821 --> 00:13:41,886
Whoo!

141
00:13:43,422 --> 00:13:45,256
Aah! Whoo!

142
00:13:46,592 --> 00:13:48,693
Jenn, come on!
<i>No!</i>

143
00:13:48,695 --> 00:13:49,994
Whoo!
<i>It's freezing.</i>

144
00:13:49,996 --> 00:13:51,529
Whoo!

145
00:14:02,041 --> 00:14:04,342
I'm gonna get some more wood
before it gets too dark.

146
00:14:04,344 --> 00:14:05,543
Okay, I'll come help you.

147
00:14:05,545 --> 00:14:08,112
No, no, I'll be back
in a second.

148
00:14:08,114 --> 00:14:09,347
Okay. Yeah.

149
00:14:53,158 --> 00:14:54,559
Hello.
Oh.

150
00:15:15,414 --> 00:15:16,915
<i>How long have you been?</i>

151
00:15:16,917 --> 00:15:19,083
<i>Oh, at this time..</i>

152
00:15:20,886 --> 00:15:22,120
What?

153
00:15:46,111 --> 00:15:48,780
Hey. Uh, this is Alex.
Alex this is Brad.

154
00:15:48,782 --> 00:15:51,282
Brad, right?
Yeah. Hi, how are you?

155
00:15:51,284 --> 00:15:52,650
I'm good. Thanks.

156
00:15:54,453 --> 00:15:55,887
Were you just walkin' by or..

157
00:15:55,889 --> 00:15:57,288
Oh, yeah, I was comin' up
the trail

158
00:15:57,290 --> 00:15:58,623
and I ran into your friend here

159
00:15:58,625 --> 00:16:00,158
and she invited me over
for a chat.

160
00:16:00,160 --> 00:16:02,493
Yeah. Turns out that he also

161
00:16:02,495 --> 00:16:04,295
kind of grew up
in a park, uh, the woods.

162
00:16:04,297 --> 00:16:06,130
<i>And he's got a ton of fish</i>

163
00:16:06,132 --> 00:16:07,966
<i>so I thought maybe we could
all have dinner tonight.</i>

164
00:16:07,968 --> 00:16:09,634
Couldn't eat 'em all
if I wanted to.

165
00:16:09,636 --> 00:16:12,070
I mean, I could try, but..

166
00:16:12,072 --> 00:16:14,072
I just gotta
put a shirt on, alright?

167
00:16:14,074 --> 00:16:15,673
<i>Okay.</i>
Yeah.

168
00:16:16,909 --> 00:16:18,643
So you were sayin'..

169
00:16:25,751 --> 00:16:27,852
Jenn..
Yeah?

170
00:16:27,854 --> 00:16:34,425
Would you come
help me here for a sec?
Sure.

171
00:16:34,427 --> 00:16:35,994
What's up?
Come on in.

172
00:16:35,996 --> 00:16:37,362
Okay?

173
00:16:40,165 --> 00:16:41,833
What's goin' on?

174
00:16:41,835 --> 00:16:43,701
You comfortable with this?

175
00:16:43,703 --> 00:16:45,937
What? Him?

176
00:16:45,939 --> 00:16:48,039
Yeah, I don't know,
this guy could be..

177
00:16:48,041 --> 00:16:50,441
I was talkin' to him
for like 10 minutes. He's great.

178
00:16:50,443 --> 00:16:53,044
He's great. Hmm.
Well, he's a liar.

179
00:16:53,046 --> 00:16:54,712
Why is he a liar?
Woods?

180
00:16:54,714 --> 00:16:56,948
What the woods of Ireland?
Come on, come on.

181
00:16:56,950 --> 00:17:01,019
<i>What does that have to do
with anything?</i>

182
00:17:01,021 --> 00:17:02,286
Did you invite him
or he invited himself?

183
00:17:02,288 --> 00:17:03,921
I did.

184
00:17:07,027 --> 00:17:10,795
I can do that, I can do that.
It'd be really awkward, but I'll do it.

185
00:17:10,797 --> 00:17:14,032
You'd never be able
to do that. I know you.

186
00:17:14,034 --> 00:17:15,800
What do you need help with?

187
00:17:15,802 --> 00:17:17,068
I obviously don't need help.

188
00:17:17,070 --> 00:17:18,736
Oh, I guess it wasn't obvious
because..

189
00:17:18,738 --> 00:17:20,738
...you told me
to come in here.

190
00:17:23,175 --> 00:17:25,510
You know, I don't wanna
bother you all, so..

191
00:17:25,512 --> 00:17:28,379
Probably better if I just be on
my way and... have a nice trip.

192
00:17:28,381 --> 00:17:29,847
Oh, no, no, no. Stay.
No, no, no.

193
00:17:29,849 --> 00:17:31,582
No, no, no.
You're gonna stay..

194
00:17:31,584 --> 00:17:33,484
... and you're gonna have
some dinner with us.

195
00:17:33,486 --> 00:17:35,253
Yeah?
Of course.

196
00:17:35,255 --> 00:17:37,622
Yeah, it was just, it was just
a misunderstanding, that's all.

197
00:17:40,592 --> 00:17:43,528
Well, alright, then.
Let's do it.

198
00:17:43,530 --> 00:17:44,495
Oh-ho-ho-ho-ho!

199
00:17:54,673 --> 00:17:55,640
<i> Mm-mm.</i>

200
00:18:02,614 --> 00:18:04,348
You wanted fish.
Mm-hmm.

201
00:18:11,423 --> 00:18:13,791
I thought it was illegal
to fish these lakes.

202
00:18:15,727 --> 00:18:17,728
Grandfather law.

203
00:18:17,730 --> 00:18:21,566
So that's when, like an,
old law applies
to existing situations

204
00:18:21,568 --> 00:18:23,301
but then a new one applies
to all the future ones?

205
00:18:23,303 --> 00:18:25,236
I know what
a grandfather law is.

206
00:18:25,238 --> 00:18:27,972
Okay. Sorry.

207
00:18:27,974 --> 00:18:30,274
Lawyer.
Yeah, I got that.

208
00:18:33,745 --> 00:18:36,848
What about you, Alex?
What do you do?

209
00:18:38,750 --> 00:18:40,918
Well, um, right now I'm, uh..

210
00:18:40,920 --> 00:18:42,720
My buddy has
a landscaping business..

211
00:18:42,722 --> 00:18:45,890
... so I'm... I'm working with him.

212
00:18:45,892 --> 00:18:48,092
Are you Mexican?

213
00:18:48,094 --> 00:18:50,228
I didn't mean
anything by that.

214
00:18:50,230 --> 00:18:53,731
I just thought that's a job
that the Mexicans do here.

215
00:18:53,733 --> 00:18:55,600
Well, what he does
is pretty high end.

216
00:18:55,602 --> 00:18:59,003
And actually he's starting
a new company soon, so..

217
00:18:59,005 --> 00:19:01,472
...it's great.
He's really talented.

218
00:19:01,474 --> 00:19:03,207
Well done you, Alex.

219
00:19:09,114 --> 00:19:11,616
Trout looks good.
It does, right?

220
00:19:11,618 --> 00:19:14,619
Yeah, and lucky for me
if I cannot find any fish

221
00:19:14,621 --> 00:19:16,254
I got a license to kill a deer.

222
00:19:16,256 --> 00:19:18,089
Oh, cool.

223
00:19:18,091 --> 00:19:21,592
Fuck me tryin' to get
a license for that these days.

224
00:19:21,594 --> 00:19:23,828
You guys have anything we can
cook for sides with these?

225
00:19:23,830 --> 00:19:26,364
Yeah, you know, I could, um...

226
00:19:26,366 --> 00:19:28,266
Maybe fry the veggies or potatoes?

227
00:19:28,268 --> 00:19:30,134
Yeah, veggies sound good.
Okay.

228
00:19:30,136 --> 00:19:32,537
Well, I say the potatoes.

229
00:19:32,539 --> 00:19:34,839
Why don't we do both?

230
00:19:34,841 --> 00:19:37,175
You know, Alex..

231
00:19:37,177 --> 00:19:38,910
... let's eat the potatoes.

232
00:19:40,812 --> 00:19:42,213
I'll get 'em.

233
00:19:52,558 --> 00:19:54,959
So you're Irish?

234
00:19:54,961 --> 00:19:56,227
County Tipperary.

235
00:19:56,229 --> 00:19:58,496
Is that near Mexico?

236
00:19:58,498 --> 00:20:00,798
That's a good one.

237
00:20:00,800 --> 00:20:02,066
Actually south of Dublin.

238
00:20:02,068 --> 00:20:05,169
What do you do
for a livin' out here?

239
00:20:05,171 --> 00:20:08,906
I give backcountry eco tours
to tourists that want, uh..

240
00:20:08,908 --> 00:20:10,875
... you know like a deeper
experience of the wilderness

241
00:20:10,877 --> 00:20:14,412
you know, somethin' more than
campin' in a parking lot.

242
00:20:14,414 --> 00:20:15,980
Yeah? That's cool.

243
00:20:15,982 --> 00:20:17,748
I mean,
you and Jenn are doin' it

244
00:20:17,750 --> 00:20:20,251
so it must be cool, right?

245
00:20:20,253 --> 00:20:23,921
How much would
somethin' like that cost?

246
00:20:23,923 --> 00:20:25,489
I wouldn't know.

247
00:20:27,526 --> 00:20:29,460
You don't know
how much it costs?

248
00:20:31,863 --> 00:20:33,965
I only know how much
they pay me, Alex.

249
00:20:41,707 --> 00:20:45,443
Okay, so they're already
parboiled, we just need
to put 'em on for a few minutes.

250
00:20:47,012 --> 00:20:48,279
Hang on.

251
00:20:57,389 --> 00:20:58,689
Oh, my..

252
00:21:02,294 --> 00:21:03,261
I'm sorry.

253
00:21:03,263 --> 00:21:04,862
Oh!

254
00:21:06,932 --> 00:21:08,733
Alright, then.

255
00:21:08,735 --> 00:21:11,535
Let's see what we've got here.

256
00:21:11,537 --> 00:21:13,771
Uh, I can do that.
No, I got it.

257
00:21:14,740 --> 00:21:16,874
This smells delicious.

258
00:21:16,876 --> 00:21:19,277
Yeah. There's, uh, garlic, rosemary

259
00:21:19,279 --> 00:21:21,746
and there's some thyme.

260
00:21:21,748 --> 00:21:23,547
You're a luck man, Alex.

261
00:21:23,549 --> 00:21:24,849
I know.

262
00:21:25,984 --> 00:21:27,618
<i>So what are your plans?</i>

263
00:21:27,620 --> 00:21:30,488
You guys gonna do some amazing
hikes, see some spots, what?

264
00:21:30,490 --> 00:21:32,256
Uh, I think..

265
00:21:32,258 --> 00:21:34,325
You know, we live
really hectic lives

266
00:21:34,327 --> 00:21:36,494
so I think we're just gonna,
you know, relax.

267
00:21:36,496 --> 00:21:38,396
Stay around here for a few days.

268
00:21:38,398 --> 00:21:39,664
Yep.

269
00:21:39,666 --> 00:21:41,499
Alright.

270
00:21:41,501 --> 00:21:44,035
You're really grabbin' life
by the balls, Alex, aren't ya?

271
00:21:46,104 --> 00:21:49,240
I'm just sayin'.
You know, if..

272
00:21:49,242 --> 00:21:51,776
...if I had a beautiful woman
here like Jenn, I'd..

273
00:21:51,778 --> 00:21:53,811
<i>... wanna take her to some
spots that weren't on the...</i>

274
00:21:53,813 --> 00:21:56,080
the tourist trail, right?

275
00:21:56,082 --> 00:21:58,115
As a matter of fact, Jenn

276
00:21:58,117 --> 00:22:01,419
there is this absolutely
gorgeous waterfall

277
00:22:01,421 --> 00:22:03,354
I mean, really beautiful.

278
00:22:03,356 --> 00:22:04,522
<i>You've probably
been there, right, Alex?</i>

279
00:22:04,524 --> 00:22:06,324
Yeah, totally.

280
00:22:06,326 --> 00:22:07,825
Then you know which side
of the waterfall

281
00:22:07,827 --> 00:22:10,961
to climb down on.

282
00:22:10,963 --> 00:22:12,263
The right side.

283
00:22:14,533 --> 00:22:15,933
Right side.

284
00:22:18,437 --> 00:22:19,804
Good guess, Alex.

285
00:22:19,806 --> 00:22:22,139
I wasn't guessing.

286
00:22:22,141 --> 00:22:24,709
Oh, you see these tourists are
always tryin' to go down the left side.

287
00:22:24,711 --> 00:22:27,778
I mean, they think it's safer.
Fuckin' idiots!

288
00:22:27,780 --> 00:22:30,014
There's also a, uh..

289
00:22:30,016 --> 00:22:32,516
... it's frozen... frozen arrow.

290
00:22:32,518 --> 00:22:34,885
In Blackfoot Trail.
Hmm.

291
00:22:34,887 --> 00:22:37,355
<i>I mean, if it were me..</i>

292
00:22:37,357 --> 00:22:40,658
... I'd want to take you
to all those spots.

293
00:22:40,660 --> 00:22:43,527
You sure you don't
need a guide?

294
00:22:43,529 --> 00:22:45,262
I already have one.

295
00:22:46,631 --> 00:22:48,065
Let's eat.

296
00:23:06,318 --> 00:23:08,686
Alright.

297
00:23:08,688 --> 00:23:11,055
That was fun.
Yeah, thanks for the fish.

298
00:23:15,927 --> 00:23:18,162
Alright.

299
00:23:18,164 --> 00:23:20,731
Well, now, I'm ready.
Cheers.

300
00:23:20,733 --> 00:23:22,066
Goodnight.

301
00:23:23,502 --> 00:23:24,735
Say, Alex..

302
00:23:25,837 --> 00:23:28,072
..you know, earlier..

303
00:23:28,074 --> 00:23:30,441
...you said something.

304
00:23:30,443 --> 00:23:32,743
It was a misunderstanding.

305
00:23:34,513 --> 00:23:35,946
You wanna explain that to me?

306
00:23:35,948 --> 00:23:37,681
Uh, it was nothing.

307
00:23:37,683 --> 00:23:39,583
Come on, he's a big boy.

308
00:23:39,585 --> 00:23:41,852
Let him answer.

309
00:23:41,854 --> 00:23:44,922
It's just a funny thing to say.

310
00:23:44,924 --> 00:23:46,590
What'd you mean by it?

311
00:23:46,592 --> 00:23:48,759
I'm not sure I understand
what you're getting at.

312
00:23:48,761 --> 00:23:50,528
Oh, yes, you do.

313
00:23:52,063 --> 00:23:55,099
What...was the misunderstanding?

314
00:24:02,541 --> 00:24:04,942
Is it important?

315
00:24:04,944 --> 00:24:06,744
I won't be fuckin' askin' if it wasn't.

316
00:24:06,746 --> 00:24:07,945
It's on me, okay.

317
00:24:07,947 --> 00:24:09,113
I was just...
Jenn.

318
00:24:14,786 --> 00:24:18,155
Well, I come back here..

319
00:24:18,157 --> 00:24:20,057
... and I find my girlfriend
talkin' to this guy...

320
00:24:22,227 --> 00:24:24,028
... and I'm not sure it's a good idea.

321
00:24:27,632 --> 00:24:29,500
That's all.

322
00:24:29,502 --> 00:24:31,302
I mean, I don't know you.

323
00:24:32,904 --> 00:24:34,972
So what was
the misunderstanding?

324
00:24:39,311 --> 00:24:41,045
You can be some nut.

325
00:24:43,181 --> 00:24:45,182
She convinced me otherwise.

326
00:24:49,754 --> 00:24:51,489
Like I said, Alex..

327
00:24:55,827 --> 00:24:57,561
... you're a lucky guy.

328
00:25:01,666 --> 00:25:03,634
I'm sorry.

329
00:25:03,636 --> 00:25:05,102
Jenn, I, uh...

330
00:25:06,338 --> 00:25:07,705
... I think you dropped something.

331
00:25:07,707 --> 00:25:09,406
I got it.

332
00:25:11,109 --> 00:25:12,076
Thanks.

333
00:25:24,690 --> 00:25:26,790
Why don't you invite him to the house next time.
That'd be fun.

334
00:25:26,792 --> 00:25:28,526
I said I'm sorry.

335
00:25:30,996 --> 00:25:33,197
Should we worry about him?
What's that?

336
00:25:33,199 --> 00:25:37,501
Should we worry about him
comin' back, or I don't know..

337
00:25:37,503 --> 00:25:39,470
No, he's just,
he's just weird.

338
00:25:43,742 --> 00:25:45,476
But I'm bringing my axe.

339
00:25:45,478 --> 00:25:47,478
And I'm gonna sleep with it in
case your fuckin' dinner guest

340
00:25:47,480 --> 00:25:50,714
wants to come back for,
you know, dessert or something.

341
00:25:50,716 --> 00:25:52,449
You're mad.

342
00:25:55,186 --> 00:25:57,555
Jenn, I don't understand you.

343
00:25:57,557 --> 00:25:58,722
What?

344
00:25:58,724 --> 00:26:01,058
You invite a total stranger..

345
00:26:01,060 --> 00:26:03,327
...to eat dinner with us
our first night on this trip.

346
00:26:03,329 --> 00:26:06,897
Okay, I... I didn't know
what to do.

347
00:26:06,899 --> 00:26:08,899
I was just being kind.

348
00:26:11,270 --> 00:26:13,170
I'm sorry.

349
00:26:13,172 --> 00:26:14,939
Just stay here.

350
00:26:14,941 --> 00:26:17,575
If he turns around
and comes back, you yell for me.

351
00:26:56,581 --> 00:26:58,282
Oh, my God.

352
00:26:58,284 --> 00:27:00,985
That smells amazing.

353
00:27:00,987 --> 00:27:01,986
Wow!

354
00:27:03,755 --> 00:27:05,322
Thank you.

355
00:27:07,792 --> 00:27:10,828
Remember the survey that we took
on the way over here?

356
00:27:10,830 --> 00:27:12,630
The first question was about
how many times

357
00:27:12,632 --> 00:27:15,332
your boyfriend has made
breakfast in bed for you?

358
00:27:15,334 --> 00:27:16,333
Remember that?
Really?

359
00:27:16,335 --> 00:27:17,835
Yeah, and I had to write zero.

360
00:27:17,837 --> 00:27:20,738
Well, I guess I'll have to
change that from zero to one.

361
00:27:20,740 --> 00:27:22,239
One, huh?
Mm-hmm.

362
00:27:22,241 --> 00:27:25,009
Was it really zero?
Yeah.

363
00:27:25,011 --> 00:27:26,644
You embarrassed?
Little bit.

364
00:27:26,646 --> 00:27:29,513
This isn't even in bed...
Believe me this counts.

365
00:27:32,250 --> 00:27:33,751
Thank you.

366
00:27:37,756 --> 00:27:40,190
What is it about this place
that's so amazing?

367
00:27:40,192 --> 00:27:41,925
Blackfoot Trail?
Yeah.

368
00:27:41,927 --> 00:27:43,927
Why's it called that anyway?

369
00:27:43,929 --> 00:27:46,196
Uh, the local tribes called it that
because when the trail ends

370
00:27:46,198 --> 00:27:48,532
it circles around
this really small lake.

371
00:27:48,534 --> 00:27:50,834
And the earth around
the lake is black.

372
00:27:50,836 --> 00:27:52,770
So when they hunted
they followed animal tracks

373
00:27:52,772 --> 00:27:55,339
in the black earth
and called it Blackfoot Trail.

374
00:27:55,341 --> 00:27:58,208
So what's the lake called?

375
00:27:58,210 --> 00:28:00,644
I don't know.
Seriously?

376
00:28:00,646 --> 00:28:03,681
No, no, no, picture it,
picture it, picture it, alright?

377
00:28:03,683 --> 00:28:05,883
You come up
this steep rocky trail

378
00:28:05,885 --> 00:28:07,718
and then all of a sudden
it levels off

379
00:28:07,720 --> 00:28:11,288
and it's this beautiful,
pristine lake.

380
00:28:11,290 --> 00:28:13,457
<i>When I was a kid
this was my favorite place</i>

381
00:28:13,459 --> 00:28:16,293
<i>in the whole world.</i>

382
00:28:16,295 --> 00:28:17,995
<i>Now it looks so out of place
that high up.</i>

383
00:28:17,997 --> 00:28:20,998
It's like out of some fantasy
novel or something, you know.

384
00:28:21,000 --> 00:28:23,701
Mmm. Yeah, I've a feeling your
geeky side is about to come out.

385
00:28:23,703 --> 00:28:25,803
What geeky side?
What geeky side?

386
00:28:25,805 --> 00:28:28,005
The one that made me watch
"Legend" four times.

387
00:28:28,007 --> 00:28:30,074
"Just wait for the part where
Tom Cruise is waiting by the lake

388
00:28:30,076 --> 00:28:31,542
for the big white unicorn
to come out."

389
00:28:31,544 --> 00:28:33,243
It's an awesome scene.
What are you talking about?

390
00:28:33,245 --> 00:28:34,945
Yeah, indeed.
Ha!

391
00:28:42,520 --> 00:28:43,887
All good?

392
00:28:44,989 --> 00:28:46,290
Yeah.

393
00:29:01,506 --> 00:29:04,708
Of course,
you're going that way.

394
00:29:04,710 --> 00:29:06,443
This is the way.

395
00:29:59,898 --> 00:30:01,131
Fuck.

396
00:30:38,870 --> 00:30:39,937
<i>Aah!</i>

397
00:30:52,550 --> 00:30:53,550
<i>Fuck.</i>

398
00:31:01,227 --> 00:31:02,960
Let me see it.

399
00:31:07,398 --> 00:31:09,233
Alex, it's disgusting.

400
00:31:11,870 --> 00:31:13,036
Ugh!

401
00:31:13,038 --> 00:31:14,538
It's pretty bad.

402
00:31:31,589 --> 00:31:32,589
<i>Aah!</i>

403
00:31:33,858 --> 00:31:35,826
Oh, fuck!
Are you ready?

404
00:31:39,998 --> 00:31:41,498
Sorry.

405
00:31:42,834 --> 00:31:43,901
That's not good.

406
00:31:43,903 --> 00:31:45,702
Oh.

407
00:31:45,704 --> 00:31:47,037
To think you're laughing
about it.

408
00:31:47,039 --> 00:31:48,906
Oh, why not?

409
00:31:50,041 --> 00:31:51,041
Ugh!

410
00:31:51,043 --> 00:31:53,076
<i>Aah!</i>

411
00:31:53,078 --> 00:31:55,112
<i>Just don't touch the toe.
Don't touch the...</i>

412
00:31:55,114 --> 00:31:56,246
Here, let me... let me finish it.

413
00:31:56,248 --> 00:31:57,781
It looks..

414
00:31:57,783 --> 00:32:01,184
It looks terrible.
It looks okay.

415
00:32:01,186 --> 00:32:03,487
What you got there?
You could use some new socks.

416
00:32:04,923 --> 00:32:07,758
Stupid place.
Oh, thanks, babes.

417
00:32:09,227 --> 00:32:10,193
<i>Okay.</i>

418
00:32:17,602 --> 00:32:18,602
Mmm.

419
00:33:09,120 --> 00:33:10,187
Alex.

420
00:33:11,422 --> 00:33:12,389
Alex.

421
00:33:23,168 --> 00:33:24,334
Alex.

422
00:33:24,336 --> 00:33:25,335
Alex.

423
00:33:26,170 --> 00:33:27,437
Alex, get up.

424
00:33:27,439 --> 00:33:29,373
Hmm?
Listen.

425
00:33:29,375 --> 00:33:30,507
What?
Just listen.

426
00:33:30,509 --> 00:33:31,508
Hmm?
What is that?

427
00:33:31,510 --> 00:33:32,609
What?

428
00:33:34,712 --> 00:33:36,513
Someone's throwing shit
at our tent.

429
00:33:36,515 --> 00:33:38,181
What?

430
00:33:38,183 --> 00:33:39,316
Just listen.

431
00:33:40,386 --> 00:33:42,452
What is that?
That?

432
00:33:43,489 --> 00:33:45,622
Oh, that's acorns.

433
00:33:45,624 --> 00:33:47,891
Just fallin' from the trees
on our tent.

434
00:33:47,893 --> 00:33:49,593
It's fine.
Just go back to sleep.

435
00:33:59,638 --> 00:34:01,138
Oh!

436
00:34:02,473 --> 00:34:04,207
That's not an acorn.

437
00:34:07,879 --> 00:34:09,246
What is it?

438
00:34:10,248 --> 00:34:11,915
Do you think it's him?

439
00:34:11,917 --> 00:34:13,817
Let's just listen for a bit, okay?

440
00:34:29,368 --> 00:34:31,668
Fuck! I swear,
now you got me all paranoid.

441
00:34:31,670 --> 00:34:33,937
Maybe he came back.
He's throwing stones at the tent or something stupid.

442
00:34:33,939 --> 00:34:35,839
No, no, no, it could be anything.

443
00:34:41,279 --> 00:34:43,013
Well, whatever it is, it stopped.

444
00:34:46,117 --> 00:34:48,785
So, let's just go back to sleep,
okay? It's fine.

445
00:34:49,887 --> 00:34:51,021
It stopped.

446
00:35:46,511 --> 00:35:48,378
That wasn't there last night, was it?

447
00:35:49,147 --> 00:35:51,248
No.

448
00:35:51,250 --> 00:35:53,783
I wanna go home.
I don't wanna be here anymore.

449
00:35:53,785 --> 00:35:56,353
Jenn, come on, don't overreact, okay?

450
00:35:56,355 --> 00:35:59,623
An acorn did that?

451
00:35:59,625 --> 00:36:03,326
Oh, come on, I've waited
so long for this trip.

452
00:36:03,328 --> 00:36:07,998
We're here and when you get
there, you'll love it.

453
00:36:10,635 --> 00:36:12,102
I promise.

454
00:36:13,871 --> 00:36:16,139
Yeah, okay.

455
00:36:16,141 --> 00:36:19,276
Can you do this for me?
Yes.

456
00:36:19,278 --> 00:36:21,378
Thank you.
Alright.

457
00:36:27,853 --> 00:36:31,321
She's a very good artist.
I have no idea why you don't give her a chance.

458
00:36:31,323 --> 00:36:33,023
What do you mean?
And she's a great performer.

459
00:36:33,025 --> 00:36:35,659
Ah, you know,
it's just not my thing.

460
00:36:35,661 --> 00:36:37,894
I don't...
Oh, hey.

461
00:36:37,896 --> 00:36:39,896
Hang on a second.

462
00:36:43,301 --> 00:36:44,301
<i>What?</i>

463
00:36:50,174 --> 00:36:53,176
This is wintergreen.
Uh-huh.

464
00:36:53,178 --> 00:36:54,911
And you can eat this.

465
00:36:57,348 --> 00:37:00,383
Mm. Tastes like spearmint gum.

466
00:37:00,385 --> 00:37:01,418
You want some?
No.

467
00:37:01,420 --> 00:37:02,419
You sure?
Yes.

468
00:37:02,421 --> 00:37:03,553
An animal probably peed on it.

469
00:37:05,090 --> 00:37:06,256
<i>Your loss.</i>

470
00:37:09,727 --> 00:37:10,794
What's that smell?

471
00:37:23,074 --> 00:37:24,307
It's nothin'.

472
00:37:34,452 --> 00:37:35,452
Babe.

473
00:37:53,971 --> 00:37:55,972
Oh, my God. Alex!

474
00:37:59,410 --> 00:38:00,543
I mean, what..

475
00:38:08,919 --> 00:38:09,886
No.

476
00:38:42,420 --> 00:38:43,486
Ah!

477
00:38:48,826 --> 00:38:51,094
Oh, God. Get off me.

478
00:38:55,767 --> 00:38:57,100
Oh, my God.

479
00:38:58,336 --> 00:39:00,170
Ow!

480
00:39:00,172 --> 00:39:02,005
<i>I found it!</i>

481
00:39:02,007 --> 00:39:03,573
Thank God!

482
00:39:14,652 --> 00:39:15,819
Uh-oh!

483
00:39:18,222 --> 00:39:21,358
What is so funny?

484
00:39:21,360 --> 00:39:23,893
Looks like you have a little
piece of poo on your face.

485
00:39:23,895 --> 00:39:25,729
Yeah 'cause I just fell down on it.

486
00:39:25,731 --> 00:39:28,998
You fell? You okay?
I'm fine.

487
00:39:29,000 --> 00:39:31,000
Shouldn't we be saving that
or something?

488
00:39:31,002 --> 00:39:32,736
Ah, well, we've got plenty
of water at the lake.

489
00:39:32,738 --> 00:39:35,271
I brought the drops.
Here.

490
00:39:39,643 --> 00:39:42,245
Thank you.
You're welcome.

491
00:39:42,247 --> 00:39:44,981
This is it?
Yeah, just up there.

492
00:39:44,983 --> 00:39:47,217
It's a real bitch to get up, isn't it?

493
00:39:47,219 --> 00:39:48,752
I know.

494
00:39:48,754 --> 00:39:50,720
But it's worth it.

495
00:39:50,722 --> 00:39:52,555
Alright.
Come on!

496
00:39:52,557 --> 00:39:54,591
I'm comin'.
Come on!

497
00:40:03,601 --> 00:40:05,101
Come on!

498
00:40:33,898 --> 00:40:34,864
Alex..

499
00:40:44,809 --> 00:40:47,210
<i>Where's the lake?</i>

500
00:40:47,212 --> 00:40:49,078
I can't believe this.

501
00:40:49,080 --> 00:40:50,447
Alex...
I don't...

502
00:40:50,449 --> 00:40:52,882
I don't understand.
This can't be it, right?

503
00:40:52,884 --> 00:40:56,052
Fuck! I was sure.
I was like a fucking 100% sure. I was...

504
00:40:56,054 --> 00:40:57,654
<i>Can you look at me, please?</i>
Just let me think.

505
00:40:57,656 --> 00:41:00,156
Just let me think.
Let me think. Let me think.

506
00:41:01,559 --> 00:41:04,294
Fuck! God damn it!
What the fuck is this?

507
00:41:09,233 --> 00:41:11,401
Please tell me
you have a map in your bag.

508
00:41:11,403 --> 00:41:14,237
I never needed a map.
Oh, we do now.

509
00:41:14,239 --> 00:41:16,039
I don't have one.

510
00:41:17,074 --> 00:41:18,475
So, then, where are we?

511
00:41:18,477 --> 00:41:20,009
I obviously don't know, right?

512
00:41:20,011 --> 00:41:23,313
But you said that you've
done this, like, so many times

513
00:41:23,315 --> 00:41:25,582
You said it was, like,
a few years ago you did this.

514
00:41:25,584 --> 00:41:27,684
Yeah, I've been to the park
a bunch of times!

515
00:41:27,686 --> 00:41:30,653
The trail, Alex.
You said you did the trail.

516
00:41:30,655 --> 00:41:31,721
Yeah.

517
00:41:33,090 --> 00:41:34,824
Not since high school, but..

518
00:41:46,136 --> 00:41:48,238
<i>It's not, uh...</i>
<i>I've put it here. I...</i>

519
00:41:49,039 --> 00:41:51,040
I put it right here.

520
00:41:55,279 --> 00:41:57,247
It's not, uh..

521
00:41:59,850 --> 00:42:00,817
I took it out.

522
00:42:00,819 --> 00:42:02,719
What?

523
00:42:02,721 --> 00:42:04,487
Your phone.

524
00:42:04,489 --> 00:42:06,789
I took it out.

525
00:42:06,791 --> 00:42:09,158
Where is it?

526
00:42:09,160 --> 00:42:11,794
In the car.
Why would you do that?

527
00:42:11,796 --> 00:42:13,696
I didn't want you
on that thing

528
00:42:13,698 --> 00:42:16,032
the whole time
when we're here.

529
00:42:16,034 --> 00:42:17,734
I didn't reach for that once.

530
00:42:17,736 --> 00:42:20,637
I... I wanted to bring it
in case we needed it.

531
00:42:20,639 --> 00:42:22,906
Which we do.

532
00:42:22,908 --> 00:42:24,474
<i>You can't get reception
out here anyway...</i>

533
00:42:24,476 --> 00:42:26,209
Well, I would have
loved to try.

534
00:42:40,024 --> 00:42:43,826
When was the last time you were
sure of where you were?

535
00:42:43,828 --> 00:42:46,896
I was sure the whole time.
<i>No. Think, Alex.</i>

536
00:42:47,765 --> 00:42:49,332
<i>When was it?</i>

537
00:42:51,702 --> 00:42:52,936
I don't...

538
00:42:54,038 --> 00:42:56,406
Maybe the fork in the trail

539
00:42:56,408 --> 00:42:58,141
The first one,
the second one?

540
00:43:04,014 --> 00:43:05,348
First one.

541
00:43:06,750 --> 00:43:08,451
Are you serious?

542
00:43:08,453 --> 00:43:09,519
<i>Just... come on, don't freak out.</i>

543
00:43:09,521 --> 00:43:11,421
I don't want to be
freaking out right now.

544
00:43:11,423 --> 00:43:14,591
But we are in the middle
of fucking nowhere.

545
00:43:14,593 --> 00:43:16,726
We don't have anything.
We don't have a... we don't have a map.

546
00:43:16,728 --> 00:43:18,728
We don't have a cell phone.
We don't have anything.

547
00:43:18,730 --> 00:43:21,397
We haven't seen anyone
in so long!

548
00:43:21,399 --> 00:43:23,299
<i>This is... it's okay.</i>
Why...

549
00:43:23,301 --> 00:43:26,436
Why did we have to come so far
on my first camping trip?

550
00:43:26,438 --> 00:43:28,571
Why couldn't it just have been
a regular trip?

551
00:43:28,573 --> 00:43:30,139
Why do you always
have to show off.

552
00:43:30,141 --> 00:43:31,474
I'm not showing off...
<i>Or something.</i>

553
00:43:31,476 --> 00:43:32,875
<i>Why do you always try to impress me?</i>

554
00:43:32,877 --> 00:43:35,211
<i>Look, 'cause I'm not
fucking impressed right now!</i>

555
00:43:35,213 --> 00:43:37,480
Good!

556
00:43:37,482 --> 00:43:38,748
I'm not trying
to fucking impress you!

557
00:43:38,750 --> 00:43:41,117
Alex, could we
be honest for a second?

558
00:43:41,119 --> 00:43:42,885
I'd love to be honest for once.

559
00:43:44,655 --> 00:43:46,623
I wish I never came.

560
00:43:46,625 --> 00:43:48,591
This whole thing was a mistake.

561
00:43:48,593 --> 00:43:49,759
Okay?
<i>Come on, Jenn, don't...</i>

562
00:43:49,761 --> 00:43:51,928
And we should be
going home tomorrow.

563
00:43:51,930 --> 00:43:53,796
But you fucked it up.

564
00:43:53,798 --> 00:43:56,332
You always fuck it all up.
You're such a fucking loser.

565
00:44:01,639 --> 00:44:04,240
The stupid lake!
Why did we have to come here?

566
00:44:04,242 --> 00:44:06,209
I don't even care why.

567
00:44:11,415 --> 00:44:12,382
Why?

568
00:44:14,151 --> 00:44:15,885
I was gonna propose to you.

569
00:44:19,790 --> 00:44:20,757
God!

570
00:45:20,017 --> 00:45:21,250
I'm really sorry.

571
00:45:26,890 --> 00:45:28,124
I had no idea.

572
00:45:39,403 --> 00:45:41,003
It's okay.

573
00:45:41,005 --> 00:45:43,506
Umm, we should
probably make camp.

574
00:45:47,945 --> 00:45:49,879
Okay.
Okay.

575
00:45:49,881 --> 00:45:50,913
Sounds good.

576
00:48:40,751 --> 00:48:42,018
Was that a..

577
00:48:42,020 --> 00:48:43,452
No, no, no, no.
It was a raccoon.

578
00:48:43,454 --> 00:48:44,854
Look, you can tell me
the truth.

579
00:48:44,856 --> 00:48:46,622
No, I saw the little shit
last night.

580
00:48:54,198 --> 00:48:55,531
Shit.

581
00:49:04,441 --> 00:49:06,242
<i>Is this right?</i>

582
00:49:06,244 --> 00:49:09,412
Yeah. We just need to take a
turn at that overgrown trail.

583
00:49:09,414 --> 00:49:11,547
Didn't seem this far down.

584
00:49:11,549 --> 00:49:12,815
No, we're good.
We're good.

585
00:49:14,084 --> 00:49:15,151
Watch your step.

586
00:49:15,153 --> 00:49:16,619
Watch your step there.

587
00:49:38,342 --> 00:49:39,909
Sh... shit.

588
00:49:39,911 --> 00:49:44,246
Should we go back?

589
00:49:44,248 --> 00:49:46,816
I don't know.

590
00:49:46,818 --> 00:49:51,854
What are the chances this
leading to something?

591
00:49:51,856 --> 00:49:53,322
Pretty good.
Right, it's provincial park.

592
00:49:53,324 --> 00:49:54,924
It's gotta lead somewhere.

593
00:50:32,729 --> 00:50:33,729
Oh.

594
00:50:36,533 --> 00:50:37,800
Here.

595
00:50:40,504 --> 00:50:42,671
Thank you.

596
00:50:48,245 --> 00:50:49,545
What is that?

597
00:50:57,320 --> 00:50:59,321
Bear bed.

598
00:51:02,592 --> 00:51:03,659
Okay.

599
00:51:06,063 --> 00:51:07,863
Okay.

600
00:51:07,865 --> 00:51:10,366
Let's go as far as
we can before dark.

601
00:51:10,368 --> 00:51:12,935
Right?

602
00:51:12,937 --> 00:51:15,871
Come on.

603
00:51:15,873 --> 00:51:16,939
Let's go, Alex.

604
00:51:41,698 --> 00:51:42,765
I'm so sorry.

605
00:51:48,738 --> 00:51:50,940
Did you mean those
things you said?

606
00:51:52,609 --> 00:51:54,176
No, I didn't.

607
00:51:57,114 --> 00:51:58,747
'Cause, Jenn, I mean if
that's what you feel abo...

608
00:51:58,749 --> 00:52:00,316
No.

609
00:52:04,321 --> 00:52:07,389
I should have never said that.

610
00:52:07,391 --> 00:52:08,891
I was just really mad.

611
00:52:11,094 --> 00:52:12,828
I'm sorry.

612
00:52:15,799 --> 00:52:17,533
I love you.

613
00:52:21,605 --> 00:52:22,838
Do you wanna see it?

614
00:52:24,741 --> 00:52:25,908
The ring?

615
00:52:26,510 --> 00:52:27,910
<i>Yeah.</i>

616
00:52:29,946 --> 00:52:31,514
If you want to.

617
00:52:46,163 --> 00:52:49,765
No, no, no, no, don't.
No. Actually, just...

618
00:52:51,168 --> 00:52:52,868
... wait.

619
00:52:57,207 --> 00:52:58,340
Okay.

620
00:53:06,650 --> 00:53:08,617
So hungry.

621
00:53:10,554 --> 00:53:15,257
I think I... I think I have
half a protein bar left in here.

622
00:53:17,127 --> 00:53:21,330
And this is all we have?
This is it?

623
00:53:21,332 --> 00:53:22,398
Yeah.

624
00:53:23,700 --> 00:53:25,501
Oh, wait a second.

625
00:53:25,503 --> 00:53:26,969
Except for, uh..

626
00:53:33,577 --> 00:53:36,078
Mm-mm.
Ta-da.

627
00:53:36,080 --> 00:53:39,348
Come on. Really?

628
00:53:39,350 --> 00:53:41,350
Yeah.

629
00:53:41,352 --> 00:53:45,721
You want some?
Yeah.

630
00:53:45,723 --> 00:53:48,157
Ooh, straight top.

631
00:53:52,395 --> 00:53:54,663
You first.

632
00:53:54,665 --> 00:53:58,067
Okay.

633
00:53:58,069 --> 00:53:59,101
To us.

634
00:54:00,503 --> 00:54:01,971
To us.

635
00:54:06,509 --> 00:54:08,877
Mm, that is so good.

636
00:54:08,879 --> 00:54:10,579
Have some. It's great.

637
00:54:15,452 --> 00:54:16,585
That is good.

638
00:54:23,627 --> 00:54:24,994
I know this sucks.

639
00:54:26,630 --> 00:54:28,764
Could be worse.

640
00:54:28,766 --> 00:54:31,533
<i>How is that?</i>

641
00:54:31,535 --> 00:54:32,601
At least we're together.

642
00:54:39,276 --> 00:54:40,175
I mean it.

643
00:54:48,151 --> 00:54:49,218
Come here.

644
00:55:28,758 --> 00:55:29,825
What is that, Alex?

645
00:55:30,927 --> 00:55:33,429
I don't know.

646
00:55:41,304 --> 00:55:43,339
Alex, do you think it's a bear?

647
00:55:45,809 --> 00:55:46,809
Hey!

648
00:56:02,125 --> 00:56:03,692
<i>Is it gone?</i>

649
00:56:03,694 --> 00:56:05,127
Let's get back
in the tent.

650
00:56:05,129 --> 00:56:06,362
Okay.

651
00:56:07,731 --> 00:56:09,031
<i>Okay. Let's go.</i>

652
00:56:31,488 --> 00:56:34,022
It's okay.

653
00:56:34,024 --> 00:56:37,326
We scared it off.
We're good.

654
00:56:37,328 --> 00:56:38,994
Okay? We're good.

655
00:57:14,798 --> 00:57:16,799
Hi.
Hi.

656
00:57:18,134 --> 00:57:20,469
So, I was thinking..

657
00:57:20,471 --> 00:57:22,871
...that I should phone
down in the front desk

658
00:57:22,873 --> 00:57:24,907
and order us some room service.

659
00:57:24,909 --> 00:57:26,175
Maybe a couples massage?

660
00:57:32,615 --> 00:57:33,949
Deep tissues.

661
00:57:39,155 --> 00:57:41,156
We're gonna be okay.

662
00:57:43,226 --> 00:57:44,226
I know.

663
00:57:52,235 --> 00:57:54,002
We should get going, okay?
Mm-hmm.

664
00:58:10,254 --> 00:58:12,454
<i>What? Alex.</i>

665
00:58:12,456 --> 00:58:14,323
Shh.

666
00:58:14,325 --> 00:58:17,960
<i>What?</i>
Stay quiet.

667
00:58:17,962 --> 00:58:22,531
You're scaring me. What?
<i>Stay quiet. Stay quiet.</i>

668
00:58:22,533 --> 00:58:23,932
Did he come back?

669
00:58:24,934 --> 00:58:26,435
Shh.

670
00:58:30,006 --> 00:58:33,775
<i>What the fuck is he doing?</i>

671
00:58:33,777 --> 00:58:35,777
What the fuck is he doing?

672
00:58:42,285 --> 00:58:43,719
Did it come back?
Is it outside?

673
00:58:43,721 --> 00:58:45,454
Yeah.

674
00:58:45,456 --> 00:58:47,055
Shh.

675
00:58:52,395 --> 00:58:54,796
Please move on. Please
move on. Please move on.

676
00:58:54,798 --> 00:58:57,566
<i>Please move on. Please move on.
Please move on.</i>

677
00:58:57,568 --> 00:58:59,735
<i>Please move on. Please move on.
Please move on.</i>

678
00:58:59,737 --> 00:59:01,103
Please move on.

679
00:59:13,016 --> 00:59:14,583
Oh, fuck!
<i>What?</i>

680
00:59:14,585 --> 00:59:15,918
Fuck! Fuck!

681
00:59:15,920 --> 00:59:18,020
Is it out there?
Did it come back?

682
00:59:18,022 --> 00:59:19,555
<i>What do we do? We don't
even have food in here.</i>

683
00:59:19,557 --> 00:59:21,924
I know. Where's my axe?

684
00:59:25,895 --> 00:59:27,095
What the fuck! Where's my axe?

685
00:59:27,097 --> 00:59:29,364
You put in your bag?

686
00:59:29,366 --> 00:59:31,233
I left my bag by the fire.

687
00:59:33,670 --> 00:59:35,504
I cannot believe
this is happening.

688
00:59:35,506 --> 00:59:37,172
What do we do?

689
00:59:37,174 --> 00:59:38,840
What do we do?

690
00:59:38,842 --> 00:59:42,010
We don't even have
food in here.

691
00:59:42,012 --> 00:59:43,378
Alex.

692
01:00:08,237 --> 01:00:09,905
Alex!

693
01:00:46,976 --> 01:00:47,976
Get behind me.

694
01:00:47,978 --> 01:00:49,411
Get behind me.

695
01:00:55,818 --> 01:00:56,952
Get the fuck out!

696
01:00:56,954 --> 01:00:58,186
Just get out!

697
01:01:06,996 --> 01:01:08,163
<i>Spray it!</i>

698
01:01:21,310 --> 01:01:22,778
I'm gonna wrap it.
Ah.

699
01:01:22,780 --> 01:01:24,646
I know, just...
Ah!

700
01:01:26,883 --> 01:01:29,851
<i>Okay. Okay, okay.</i>

701
01:01:30,988 --> 01:01:33,288
It's okay. It's okay.

702
01:01:33,290 --> 01:01:34,623
<i>I'm gonna wrap it.</i>

703
01:01:40,530 --> 01:01:42,330
It's okay.
Jenn.

704
01:01:42,332 --> 01:01:43,198
<i>Jenn, I can't feel my foot.</i>

705
01:01:43,200 --> 01:01:44,399
It's okay.

706
01:01:47,371 --> 01:01:50,639
It's okay. It's okay.

707
01:01:50,641 --> 01:01:51,707
I can't feel my foot.

708
01:01:51,709 --> 01:01:55,343
We're gonna crawl out of here if we have to.
You hear me?

709
01:01:55,345 --> 01:01:57,312
My God!
I'm gonna fucking die out here!

710
01:01:57,314 --> 01:01:59,047
No, you're not!
I'm gonna fucking die!

711
01:01:59,049 --> 01:02:01,416
Alex! You're fine!

712
01:02:01,418 --> 01:02:03,585
Alex, you're gonna be fine.

713
01:02:18,701 --> 01:02:19,735
No!

714
01:02:19,737 --> 01:02:20,802
Alex!

715
01:02:44,560 --> 01:02:47,362
<i>Run, Jenn! Run!</i>

716
01:05:35,865 --> 01:05:37,532
Help!

717
01:05:38,968 --> 01:05:40,635
Help!

718
01:05:42,571 --> 01:05:44,406
Help!

719
01:05:44,408 --> 01:05:45,840
Anybody!

720
01:10:17,246 --> 01:10:18,813
Help!

721
01:10:18,815 --> 01:10:20,715
Help!

722
01:11:21,610 --> 01:11:23,044
Ah!

723
01:12:32,481 --> 01:12:33,548
Uh.

724
01:14:33,168 --> 01:14:34,235
Fuck!

725
01:15:21,817 --> 01:15:22,850
<i>Fuck!</i>

726
01:16:06,695 --> 01:16:07,595
Uh!

727
01:16:08,830 --> 01:16:09,830
Ooh.

