You ready?
- How am I doing?
- Sure you want to know?
"Does your boyfriend
always get his way?"
Yes.
"Does he admit
when he's wrong?"
Never.
Does your boyfriend know how
to build a fire with no matches?
Answer is D, who cares.
A, yes. Very well.
Sorry, that question's
not on here.
- It should be in there.
- Sorry.
So you're still zero.
- No-o-o!
- Oh, yeah-h-h!
Put your hands on the wheel.
- Hello?
- Hey.
- Just give me a second, will you?
- Yeah, sure.
- How you doin'?
- Good, good, good.
Uh, we're reserved under Louis.
- What's the name?
- Alex Louis.
Yeah, sign in here.
You're ready to go.
Your canoe will be
right down there by the water.
Bring it back Monday at five.
That's right,
back to work Tuesday.
- Need a map?
- No, I'm good.
You don't want a map?
No. No.
I know this park well.
It's kinda end of
the season, right?
I mean the weather
can change on you..
Just turn on a dime.
Less people.
Amen to that.
You mind me askin' you,
Mr. No Map..
Where you're headed?
Blackfoot Trail.
I can't wait to show her.
It's her first time here.
It's gonna be awesome.
I got some bad news for you,
I'm really sorry about this
but Blackfoot Trail's
closed for the season.
- Why?
- Had to.
I mean, so many yahoos
you know, trampin' around there,
disrespecting everything.
This is a treasured site.
I don't have to tell you
I guess.
And Parks and Recreation
want to keep it that way.
Look, going to Blackfoot Trail
is kinda the whole point
of this trip.
It's 500 bucks
if you're caught up there. Each.
That'll be a 1000 bucks
expensive little camping trip.
Alright.
Jenn, you ready?
- Yeah.
- Oh, hang on.
Hey, rodeo,
here's your medical kit
and there's a whistle in there,
try to bring that back
and I'll try not to charge you.
Thousand bucks?
You're pretty good.
Bye. You have a nice trip.
Thanks.
- Really?
- Last one.
Come on, babe.
This is really important.
You know, we've been waiting
forever for this.
I'm..
Just... just give me..
They're all important.
Can't wait till we get back?
Okay, I'm done. Okay?
Alright.
I don't believe you, but..
Well, putting it away,
so it's..
Oh, hang on, hang on.
Let's take a picture.
Just to mark the departure.
- Put it to good use, right?
- Fine.
Okay.
- Good.
- Yeah.
- One of us looks good.
- Alright.
- Hey.
- Hey, have a good one.
- Thanks a lot.
- Fuck!
- You okay?
Oh, fuck, fuck that!
Fuckin' hurt like a bitch.
You sure you're okay?
Yeah. Yeah, yeah,
I'll just walk it off.
This is for you.
You look scared anyway.
Feel safe.
I probably won't need it.
Got it taken care of already.
Look what I got.
- When did you get that?
- I got it a few days ago.
- You're not gonna need it.
Do you wanna have a good time on this trip
or do you want me to be freaking out?
- This is what makes me feel safe.
- Okay. Okay.
Well, if you can have it
it's useless in your bag.
Give it to me. Thanks.
Just gonna clip it
to your belt, alright?
And you're not gonna need it.
Bear spray.
Wonder what other goodies
you have in there.
- Nothin'.
- Let's see.
I don't have anything in there.
Hey, there's nothing.
- Oh, come on.
- What?
Seriously?
- This is a road flare.
- I know what it is.
Yeah. This is for when your car breaks
down on the side of the highway.
- Mm-hmm.
- You know this.
I know you know this.
Jenn, come on, if you wanted a flare,
I could've picked up a pen flare.
They sell them
at any camping store.
- Here's your flare.
- Thank you.
- You ready?
- Think so.
Okay.
Oh, my God.
- You good?
- Yes.
- Huh?
- What, sorry, what?
Jenn, you know
we'd be lucky to see
anything bigger
than a chipmunk, right?
Mm-hmm.
- Hi.
- Hey.
Pfft! No!
Hey, look at that.
That's cute.
We should take it.
- Here's a good spot.
- Yeah.
Counselor, back up, please.
Tryin' to turn me on right now?
Is it working?
Oh, yeah. It's pretty hot.
Speaking of..
Do you remember the little
swimming hole we walked by?
- Nope, I don't. No.
- Really?
- You said you would.
- I didn't say that.
Yes, you did.
- I said maybe.
- No, no, no.
You said yes.
Come on, babes.
No. It's like when you say, "Do you
want to order Chinese food tonight?"
And I go, "Maybe,"
and then we get Italian.
It's like that.
I'm gonna be
all lonely by myself.
Well, no one's making you
do this.
Stop it!
Oh, my God, please.
What if there's..
Don't leave me hangin', babe.
Okay, okay. Fine.
- You ready?
- No.
Come on.
5...4...3, 2, 1!
Whoo!
Aah! Whoo!
- Jenn, come on!
- No!
- Whoo!
- It's freezing.
Whoo!
I'm gonna get some more wood
before it gets too dark.
Okay, I'll come help you.
No, no, I'll be back
in a second.
Okay. Yeah.
- Hello.
- Oh.
How long have you been?
Oh, at this time..
What?
Hey. Uh, this is Alex.
Alex this is Brad.
- Brad, right?
- Yeah. Hi, how are you?
I'm good. Thanks.
Were you just walkin' by or..
Oh, yeah, I was comin' up
the trail
and I ran into your friend here
and she invited me over
for a chat.
Yeah. Turns out that he also
kind of grew up
in a park, uh, the woods.
And he's got a ton of fish
so I thought maybe we could
all have dinner tonight.
Couldn't eat 'em all
if I wanted to.
I mean, I could try, but..
I just gotta
put a shirt on, alright?
- Okay.
- Yeah.
So you were sayin'..
- Jenn..
- Yeah?
- Would you come help me here for a sec?
- Sure.
- What's up?
- Come on in.
Okay?
What's goin' on?
You comfortable with this?
What? Him?
Yeah, I don't know,
this guy could be..
I was talkin' to him
for like 10 minutes. He's great.
He's great. Hmm.
Well, he's a liar.
- Why is he a liar?
- Woods?
What the woods of Ireland?
Come on, come on.
What does that have to do
with anything?
Did you invite him
or he invited himself?
I did.
I can do that, I can do that. It'd
be really awkward, but I'll do it.
You'd never be able
to do that. I know you.
What do you need help with?
I obviously don't need help.
Oh, I guess it wasn't obvious
because..
You told me to come in here.
You know, I don't wanna
bother you all, so..
Probably better if I just be on
my way and... have a nice trip.
- Oh, no, no, no. Stay.
- No, no, no.
No, no, no.
You're gonna stay..
And you're gonna have
some dinner with us.
- Yeah?
- Of course.
Yeah, it was just, it was just
a misunderstanding, that's all.
Well, alright, then.
Let's do it.
Oh-ho-ho-ho-ho!
Mm-mm.
- You wanted fish.
- Mm-hmm.
I thought it was illegal
to fish these lakes.
Grandfather law.
So that's when, like an, old law
applies to existing situations
but then a new one applies
to all the future ones?
I know what
a grandfather law is.
Okay. Sorry.
- Lawyer.
- Yeah, I got that.
What about you, Alex?
What do you do?
Well, um, right now I'm, uh..
My buddy has
a landscaping business..
So I'm... I'm working
with him.
Are you Mexican?
I didn't mean anything by that.
I just thought that's a job
that the Mexicans do here.
Well, what he does
is pretty high end.
And actually he's starting
a new company soon, so..
It's great.
He's really talented.
Well done you, Alex.
- Trout looks good.
- It does, right?
Yeah, and lucky for me
if I cannot find any fish
I got a license to kill a deer.
Oh, cool.
Fuck me tryin' to get
a license for that these days.
You guys have anything we can
cook for sides with these?
Yeah, you know, I could, um..
Maybe fry the veggies
or potatoes?
- Yeah, veggies sound good.
- Okay.
Well, I say the potatoes.
Why don't we do both?
You know, Alex..
Let's eat the potatoes.
I'll get 'em.
So you're Irish?
County Tipperary.
Is that near Mexico?
That's a good one.
Actually south of Dublin.
What do you do
for a livin' out here?
I give backcountry eco tours
to tourists that want, uh..
You know like a deeper
experience of the wilderness
you know, somethin' more than
campin' in a parking lot.
Yeah? That's cool.
I mean,
you and Jenn are doin' it
so it must be cool, right?
How much would
somethin' like that cost?
I wouldn't know.
You don't know
how much it costs?
I only know how much
they pay me, Alex.
Okay, so they're already parboiled, we
just need to put 'em on for a few minutes.
Hang on.
Oh, my..
I'm sorry.
Oh!
Alright, then.
Let's see what we've got here.
- Uh, I can do that.
- No, I got it.
This smells delicious.
Yeah. There's, uh, garlic,
rosemary
and there's some thyme.
You're a luck man, Alex.
I know.
So what are your plans?
You guys gonna do some amazing
hikes, see some spots, what?
Uh, I think..
You know, we live
really hectic lives
so I think we're just gonna,
you know, relax.
Stay around here
for a few days.
Yep.
Alright.
You're really grabbin' life
by the balls, Alex, aren't ya?
I'm just sayin'.
You know, if..
If I had a beautiful woman
here like Jenn, I'd..
Wanna take her to some
spots that weren't on the..
The tourist trail, right?
As a matter of fact, Jenn
there is this absolutely
gorgeous waterfall
I mean, really beautiful.
You've probably
been there, right, Alex?
Yeah, totally.
Then you know which side
of the waterfall
to climb down on.
The right side.
Right side.
Good guess, Alex.
I wasn't guessing.
Oh, you see these tourists are always
tryin' to go down the left side.
I mean, they think it's safer.
Fuckin' idiots!
There's also a, uh..
It's frozen... frozen arrow.
- In Blackfoot Trail.
- Hmm.
I mean, if it were me..
I'd want to take you
to all those spots.
You sure you don't
need a guide?
I already have one.
Let's eat.
Alright.
That was fun.
- Yeah, thanks for the fish.
Alright.
Well, now, I'm ready.
Cheers.
Goodnight.
Say, Alex..
..you know, earlier..
You said something.
It was a misunderstanding.
You wanna explain that to me?
Uh, it was nothing.
Come on, he's a big boy.
Let him answer.
It's just a funny thing to say.
What'd you mean by it?
I'm not sure I understand
what you're getting at.
Oh, yes, you do.
What... was the misunderstanding?
Is it important?
I won't be fuckin' askin'
if it wasn't.
It's on me, okay.
- I was just...
- Jenn.
Well, I come back here..
And I find my girlfriend
talkin' to this guy..
And I'm not sure
it's a good idea.
That's all.
I mean, I don't know you.
So what was
the misunderstanding?
You can be some nut.
She convinced me otherwise.
Like I said, Alex..
You're a lucky guy.
I'm sorry.
Jenn, I, uh..
I think you dropped something.
I got it.
Thanks.
Why don't you invite him to the
house next time. That'd be fun.
I said I'm sorry.
Should we worry about him?
- What's that?
Should we worry about him
comin' back, or I don't know..
No, he's just, he's just weird.
But I'm bringing my axe.
And I'm gonna sleep with it in
case your fuckin' dinner guest
wants to come back for,
you know, dessert or something.
You're mad.
Jenn, I don't understand you.
What?
You invite a total stranger..
To eat dinner with us
our first night on this trip.
Okay, I... I didn't know
what to do.
I was just being kind.
I'm sorry.
Just stay here.
If he turns around
and comes back, you yell for me.
Oh, my God.
That smells amazing.
Wow!
Thank you.
Remember the survey that we took
on the way over here?
The first question was about
how many times
your boyfriend has made
breakfast in bed for you?
Remember that?
- Really?
Yeah, and I had to write zero.
Well, I guess I'll have to
change that from zero to one.
- One, huh?
- Mm-hmm.
- Was it really zero?
- Yeah.
- You embarrassed?
- Little bit.
- This isn't even in bed...
- Believe me this counts.
Thank you.
What is it about this place
that's so amazing?
- Blackfoot Trail?
- Yeah.
Why's it called that anyway?
Uh, the local tribes called it
that because when the trail ends
it circles around
this really small lake.
And the earth around
the lake is black.
So when they hunted
they followed animal tracks
in the black earth
and called it Blackfoot Trail.
So what's the lake called?
- I don't know.
- Seriously?
No, no, no, picture it,
picture it, picture it, alright?
You come up
this steep rocky trail
and then all of a sudden
it levels off
and it's this beautiful,
pristine lake.
When I was a kid
this was my favorite place
in the whole world.
Now it looks so out of place
that high up.
It's like out of some fantasy
novel or something, you know.
Mmm. Yeah, I've a feeling your
geeky side is about to come out.
- What geeky side?
The one that made me watch
"Legend" four times.
"Just wait for the part where Tom
Cruise is waiting by the lake
for the big white unicorn
to come out."
It's an awesome scene.
What are you talking about?
- Yeah, indeed.
- Ha!
All good?
Yeah.
Of course,
you're going that way.
This is the way.
Fuck.
Aah!
Let me see it.
Alex, it's disgusting.
Ugh!
It's pretty bad.
Aah!
- Oh, fuck!
- Are you ready?
Sorry.
That's not good.
Oh.
To think you're laughing
about it.
Oh, why not?
Ugh!
Aah!
Just don't touch the toe.
Don't touch the..
Here, let me... let me
finish it.
It looks..
- It looks terrible.
- It looks okay.
- What you got there?
- You could use some new socks.
- Stupid place.
- Oh, thanks, babes.
Okay.
Mmm.
Alex.
Alex, get up.
- Hmm?
- Listen.
- What?
- Just listen.
- Hmm?
- What is that?
What?
Someone's throwing shit
at our tent.
What?
Just listen.
- What is that?
- That?
Oh, that's acorns.
Just fallin' from the trees
on our tent.
It's fine.
Just go back to sleep.
Oh!
That's not an acorn.
What is it?
Do you think it's him?
Let's just listen
for a bit, okay?
Fuck! I swear,
now you got me all paranoid.
Maybe he came back. He's throwing
stones at the tent or something stupid.
No, no, no,
it could be anything.
Well, whatever it is,
it stopped.
So, let's just go back to sleep,
okay? It's fine.
It stopped.
That wasn't there last night,
was it?
No.
I wanna go home.
I don't wanna be here anymore.
Jenn, come on,
don't overreact, okay?
An acorn did that?
Oh, come on, I've waited
so long for this trip.
We're here and when you get
there, you'll love it.
I promise.
Yeah, okay.
- Can you do this for me?
- Yes.
- Thank you.
- Alright.
She's a very good artist. I have no
idea why you don't give her a chance.
- What do you mean?
- And she's a great performer.
Ah, you know,
it's just not my thing.
- I don't...
- Oh, hey.
Hang on a second.
What?
- This is wintergreen.
- Uh-huh.
And you can eat this.
Mm. Tastes like spearmint gum.
- You want some?
- No.
- You sure?
- Yes.
An animal probably peed on it.
Your loss.
What's that smell?
It's nothin'.
Babe.
Oh, my God. Alex!
I mean, what..
No.
Ah!
Oh, God. Get off me.
Oh, my God.
Ow!
I found it!
Thank God!
Uh-oh!
What is so funny?
Looks like you have a little
piece of poo on your face.
Yeah 'cause I just
fell down on it.
- You fell? You okay?
- I'm fine.
Shouldn't we be saving that
or something?
Ah, well, we've got plenty
of water at the lake.
I brought the drops.
Here.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- This is it?
- Yeah, just up there.
It's a real bitch to get up,
isn't it?
I know.
But it's worth it.
- Alright.
- Come on!
- I'm comin'.
Come on!
Alex..
Where's the lake?
I can't believe this.
- Alex..
- I don't..
- I don't understand.
- This can't be it, right?
Fuck! I was sure. I was like
a fucking 100% sure. I was..
-  Can you look at me, please?
- Just let me think.
Just let me think.
Let me think. Let me think.
Fuck! God damn it!
What the fuck is this?
Please tell me
you have a map in your bag.
- I never needed a map.
- Oh, we do now.
I don't have one.
So, then, where are we?
I obviously don't know, right?
But you said that you've
done this, like, so many times
You said it was, like,
a few years ago you did this.
Yeah, I've been to the park
a bunch of times!
The trail, Alex.
You said you did the trail.
Yeah.
Not since high school, but..
- It's not, uh..
-  I've put it here. I..
I put it right here.
It's not, uh..
I took it out.
What?
Your phone.
I took it out.
Where is it?
- In the car.
- Why would you do that?
I didn't want you on that thing
the whole time when we're here.
I didn't reach for that once.
I... I wanted to bring it
in case we needed it.
Which we do.
You can't get reception
out here anyway...
Well, I would have
loved to try.
When was the last time you were
sure of where you were?
- I was sure the whole time.
-  No. Think, Alex.
When was it?
I don't..
Maybe the fork in the trail
The first one, the second one?
First one.
Are you serious?
Just... come on,
don't freak out.
I don't want to be
freaking out right now.
But we are in the middle
of fucking nowhere.
We don't have anything. We don't have a...
we don't have a map.
We don't have a cell phone.
We don't have anything.
We haven't seen anyone
in so long!
- This is... it's okay.
- Why..
Why did we have to come so far
on my first camping trip?
Why couldn't it just have been
a regular trip?
Why do you always
have to show off.
- I'm not showing off...
-  Or something.
Why do you always
try to impress me?
Look, 'cause I'm not
fucking impressed right now!
Good!
I'm not trying
to fucking impress you!
Alex, could we
be honest for a second?
I'd love to be honest for once.
I wish I never came.
This whole thing was a mistake.
- Okay?
-  Come on, Jenn, don't...
And we should be
going home tomorrow.
But you fucked it up.
You always fuck it all up.
You're such a fucking loser.
The stupid lake!
Why did we have to come here?
I don't even care why.
Why?
I was gonna propose to you.
God!
I'm really sorry.
I had no idea.
It's okay.
Umm, we should
probably make camp.
- Okay.
Sounds good.
Was that a..
No, no, no, no.
It was a raccoon.
Look, you can tell me
the truth.
No, I saw the little shit
last night.
Shit.
Is this right?
Yeah. We just need to take a
turn at that overgrown trail.
Didn't seem this far down.
No, we're good.
We're good.
Watch your step.
Watch your step there.
Sh... shit.
Should we go back?
I don't know.
What are the chances this
leading to something?
Pretty good.
Right, it's provincial park.
It's gotta lead somewhere.
Oh.
Here.
Thank you.
What is that?
Bear bed.
Okay.
Let's go as far as
we can before dark.
Right?
Come on.
Let's go, Alex.
I'm so sorry.
Did you mean those
things you said?
No, I didn't.
'Cause, Jenn, I mean if
that's what you feel abo...
No.
I should have never said that.
I was just really mad.
I'm sorry.
I love you.
Do you wanna see it?
The ring?
Yeah.
If you want to.
No, no, no, no, don't.
No. Actually, just..
Wait.
Okay.
So hungry.
I think I... I think I have
half a protein bar left in here.
And this is all we have?
This is it?
Yeah.
Oh, wait a second.
Except for, uh..
- Mm-mm.
- Ta-da.
Come on. Really?
Yeah.
- You want some?
- Yeah.
Ooh, straight top.
You first.
Okay.
To us.
Mm, that is so good.
Have some. It's great.
That is good.
I know this sucks.
Could be worse.
How is that?
At least we're together.
I mean it.
Come here.
What is that, Alex?
I don't know.
Alex, do you think it's a bear?
Hey!
Is it gone?
Let's get back in the tent.
Okay.
Okay. Let's go.
It's okay.
We scared it off.
We're good.
Okay? We're good.
- Hi.
So, I was thinking..
That I should phone
down in the front desk
and order us some room service.
Maybe a couples massage?
Deep tissues.
We're gonna be okay.
I know.
- We should get going, okay?
- Mm-hmm.
What? Alex.
Shh.
-  What?
- Stay quiet.
- You're scaring me. What?
-  Stay quiet. Stay quiet.
Did he come back?
Shh.
What the fuck is he doing?
Did it come back?
Is it outside?
Yeah.
Shh.
Please move on. Please
move on. Please move on.
Please move on.
- Oh, fuck!
-  What?
Fuck! Fuck!
Is it out there?
Did it come back?
What do we do? We don't
even have food in here.
I know. Where's my axe?
What the fuck! Where's my axe?
You put in your bag?
I left my bag by the fire.
I cannot believe
this is happening.
What do we do?
We don't even have
food in here.
Alex.
Alex!
Get behind me.
Get the fuck out!
Just get out!
Spray it!
- I'm gonna wrap it.
- Ah.
- I know, just..
- Ah!
Okay. Okay, okay.
It's okay. It's okay.
I'm gonna wrap it.
- It's okay.
- Jenn.
Jenn, I can't feel my foot.
It's okay.
It's okay. It's okay.
I can't feel my foot.
We're gonna crawl out of here
if we have to. You hear me?
My God!
I'm gonna fucking die out here!
- No, you're not!
- I'm gonna fucking die!
Alex! You're fine!
Alex, you're gonna be fine.
No!
Alex!
Run, Jenn! Run!
Help!
Anybody!
Ah!
Uh.
Fuck!
Uh!
Ooh.