BRUCE:  There was a time above.
A time before.
There were perfect things,
diamond absolutes.
How things fall.
Things on Earth.
And what falls...[WIND HOWLING]
Master Wayne!
...is fallen.Bruce!
[PANTING]
Bruce, it's all right.
Bruce, please.
[CONTINUES PANTING]
[GUN COCKING]
[GROANS]
[GROANING]
[GUN FIRES]
[SCREAMING INAUDIBLY]
[GASPING]
Martha.
[GROANING]
[WINGS FLAPPING]
[BATS SQUEAKING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[BATS SQUEAKING LOUDLY]
[GASPING]
[SCREECHING]
[GRUNTING]
BRUCE:  In the dream,
they took me to the light.
A beautiful lie.
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[ENGINE ROARING]
[SIRENS WAILING]
Jack.Bruce.
Jack, listen to me.
I want you to get everyone
out of the building right now.
You understand?Oh, my God
WOMAN:  Stay away
from the windows!
[PANICKED SHOUTING]Let's go. Come on.
Start moving now, people.
Let's go.
The boss wants us
out of the building,
so let's make it happen.
Jack. Jack!
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[CAR ALARMS BLARING]
[JACK BREATHING HEAVILY]
[JACK GASPS]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
[PANTING]
[CELL PHONE BEEPS]
OPERATOR:  We're sorry.
All circuits are busy now.
Will you please
try your call again later?
Heavenly God,
creator of Heaven and Earth,
have mercy on my soul.
[PANICKED SHOUTING][BRUCE GASPS]
Jack!
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
WALLACE:  Mr. Wayne!
Mr. Wayne!
I can't feel my legs.
[GRUNTS]I can't feel my legs.
We need help over here!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Help me.
I can't feel my legs.
You're gonna be okay.
You hear me?
Wallace? What do
they call you, Wally? Huh?
You're the boss, boss.
MAN: All right.
You're gonna be okay.
Easy, easy. Come on.
[WALLACE GROANING]
Oh, my God.
I can't move my leg.
My God.
I can't feel my legs.
[BRUCE GRUNTS]
It's okay.
You're gonna be okay.
You're okay. All right? Huh?
[SIRENS WAILING]
You know what?
We're gonna find your mom.
Where is she?
[SONIC BOOM]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
[WIND HOWLING]
[LOIS GROANS]
Um...
Are you a terrorist, General?
They did not tell me
the interview
was with a lady.
I'm not a lady.
I'm a journalist.
GENERAL AMAJAGH:  What I am
is a man with nothing
except a love of my people.
Oh... Don't open...
You just exposed...
Who's paying for these
security contractors,
General?
Who pays for the drones
that pass over
our heads at night?
One question begs another.
Yes?
[BEEPING]
CIA.
They're tracking us!
You!
[SPEAKING OTHER LANGUAGE]
No![JIMMY IN OTHER LANGUAGE]
It's okay, Lois.
[GUNSHOT ECHOES]
I...
I didn't know.
Ignorance is not
the same as innocence,
Miss Lane.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER
IN OTHER LANGUAGE]
[GUNFIRE][PEOPLE SCREAMING]
[INDISTINCT SHOUTING
IN OTHER LANGUAGE]
Get up! Stand up!
[GASPING]
[ENGINES REVVING]
Move out!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Take one step,
you will see
the inside of her head.
KAHINA:  The women
in the village heard a noise.
Like the sky cracked open.
He came down.
So many dead.
Even worse came after.
The government attacked.
No mercy in the villages.
[SOBS]
My parents tried to run.
The world has been
so caught up
with what Superman can do
that no one has asked
what he should do.
Let the record show
that this committee
holds him responsible.
KAHINA:  He'll never
answer to you.
He answers to no one.
Not even, I think, to God.
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
[SIRENS WAILING][HORNS HONKING]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Hey.Hey.
I was gonna cook.
Surprise you.
They held hearings
about what happened.
They're saying that--I don't care.
I don't care
what they're saying.
The woman I love could have
been blown up or shot.
Think of what
could have happened.
Well, think about
what did happen.
I didn't kill those men,
if that's what they think.
If that's
what you're saying.
No, I'm saying
I want to understand
what happened.
I'm saying thank you
for saving my life.
I'm saying there's a cost.
I just don't know
if it's possible.
Don't know
if what's possible?
For you to love me
and be you.
What are you doing?
[LAUGHS] Clark!
Clark, you're going
to flood the apartment.
Mmm-hmm.
[LAUGHING]
[BATS SCREECHING]
[SIRENS WAILING][TIRES SCREECHING]
[POLICE RADIO CHATTER]
DISPATCHER:  Reports of screams
coming from vacant home
at 1939 Harborway.
Possible shots fired.
[DOOR CREAKING]
[WHISPERS] Go.
[WOMEN CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY
IN OTHER LANGUAGE]
OFFICER RUCKA: It's okay.
It's okay.
[STAMMERS] We're gonna help.
We're here to help.
We're gonna get you
out of here. Okay?
[ALL WHIMPERING]
I don't understand.
[CESAR SCREAMS][WOMEN GASP]
CESAR:  Please don't.
Please don't.
Please.
I don't know who he is.
I don't know who he is!
No!
[CESAR GROANING]
[CONTINUES GROANING]
[GASPS]
[GRUNTS]
[GROANS]
Christ!
I saw him.
I never saw him before.
I... I didn't know.
You almost
took my face off.
How about you don't
shoot the good guys, huh?
Oh. Oh.
Jesus Christ.
He branded him.
BRUCE: You still working?
You're getting slow
in your old age, Alfred.
Comes to us all,
Master Wayne.
Even you got
too old to die young.
And not for lack of trying.
[IN DEEP VOICE]
Funnel-ferry butterbar.
Funnel-ferry--
There's nothing wrong
with the microphone.
It's this new layer
of armor.
I'll just have to rewire.
So, last night
was productive?
No. He's too low-level.
He knew nothing.
This is the man
who knows things.
Anatoli Knyazev.
He's Russian.
Contracts all over the globe,
but he's based out of
the port of Gotham.
Weapons
and human trafficking.
ALFRED:  So the
White Portuguese
is a Russian.
That's the theory.
No. The theory is that
the Russian will lead me
to the man himself.
If he is, indeed,
a "him."
You don't even know
if he exists.
Could be a phantasm.
One that wants to bring
a dirty bomb into Gotham?
Ah, high-stakes round.
New rules.
We're criminals, Alfred.
We've always been criminals.
Nothing's changed.
Oh, yes, it has, sir.
Everything's changed.
Men fall from the sky.
The gods hurl thunderbolts.
Innocents die.
That's how it starts, sir.
The fever. The rage.
The feeling
of powerlessness.
It turns good men cruel.
KENT SHOCKNEK ON TV:  Justice
turned dark across the harbor,
when police found
an alleged sex trafficker
apparently tortured and
branded by the Gotham Bat.
The man is the second criminal
found bearing the bat brand.
The first victim,
an accused child predator,
later was assaulted in prison
and remains in critical care
from his injuries.
One source tells Metropolis 8
that many believe the mark
of the bat brand
in prison essentially
is a death sentence.
In other news, the mayor...
PLAYER:  John, get D.
Ooh. Ah. Ahoy, ahoy!
I did not know
you were here.
Man on the marquee.Yeah, don't believe it.
My father named the company
after himself.
He was the Lex in front of
the Corp. How you doin'?
Oh, really great.
Really great?
Good. Good. Uh, follow me.
You know, Dad was
born in East Germany.
He grew up eating,
uh, stale crackers.
And every other Saturday,
he had to march in a parade
and wave flowers at tyrants.
So, I think it was providence
that his son, me,
would end up with this.
One of my Rebuild Metropolis
crews found it.
Little souvenir from
the Kryptonian World Engine.
What does a rock have to do
with homeland security?
Homeland security? Hmm.
No, no, no, ma'am,
planetary security.
EMMET:  The fragment is
of a radioactive xenomineral.
We suspected it might
have bio-interactions,
so we took the sample
to AMRIID,
where they keep the remains
of the Kryptonian decedent.
And, when we exposed
General Zod to the mineral,
this happened.
Profound biodegradation.
Decaying Kryptonian cells.
We concluded the mineral
could be weaponized
if a large enough
sample was found.
And then,
among the fishes, a whale.
Ah!
Lying at the bottom of
the Indian Ocean.
Emerald City.
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
Beautiful.
Now, Rocky is radioactive,
but what he needs from you
is an import license.
And why would we want to
weaponize this material?
LEX:  As a deterrent.
A silver bullet
to keep in reserve,
to use against
the Kryptonians,
so the day does not come,
madam,
when your children are waving
daisies at a reviewing stand.
SENATOR BARROWS:
Last I looked,
the only one of those
flying around up here
was Superman.
Ha-ha, yes. Superman.
Yeah, but there are, uh...
There are more of them.
The metahuman thesis.
LEX:  Yes,
the metahuman thesis.
More likely than not
these exceptional beings
live among us.
The basis of our myths.
Gods among men upon
our little blue planet here.
Now, you don't have to
use a silver bullet.
But if you forge one...
[INHALES]
[IN SOUTHERN ACCENT]
Well, then
we don't have to depend
upon the kindness of monsters.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[GRUNTING]
Sir, get down.
Sir, I said get down!
Now!
[ALL GASPING]
Can we get
some backup here?
Hey! Hey!
Don't do it!
Hey!
Lois! Crime lab, on three.
This is Lane.PERRY:  Kent.
You're Sports today.
I want you to follow up
on football.
"Underdog Dreams Dashed:
"Ten Yards Between
Gotham and Glory."
Hey. Are you guys
watching this?
Emergency responders
quickly created
a precautionary perimeter
around Heroes Park
while they brought
the man down
from this beloved monument.
The suspect
has been identified
as Wallace Vernon Keefe.
I work for Bruce Wayne!
REPORTER:  He'll be arraigned
on charges of vandalism,
resisting arrest,
and the felony charge of
making terrorist threats.
That carries
up to 40 years in prison.
PERRY: Poor son of a bitch.
REPORTER:  Metropolis News 8.
PERRY: Jenny.Hmm.
Headline: "End of Love Affair
with Man in the Sky,
"question mark."
Okay.
SENATOR BARROWS:
There are ways
we can help each other.
[SIGHS] Would you step
into my office here?
Yes.
What's your wish list?
Uh...
Access to the wreck of
the crashed Kryptonian ship?
Done.
The complete remains of
the dead alien for testing.
[LEX SNIFFLES]
You want Zod's body?
Okay.
[DOOR OPENS]
Mmm.
It's cherry.
Mmm-mmm.
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[CROWD CHEERING]
Let's go. Come on!
Let's go! Come on!
[CHEERING CONTINUES]
[GRUNTING CONTINUES]
[CROWD APPLAUDING]
[MAN BOOING]
[CORK POPS]
Thank you.
[MAN LAUGHING]
The house treats
luck like an insult.
Good luck for one is always
his brother's misfortune.
[BRUCE SPEAKING RUSSIAN]
Three nights with
a Bolshoi ballerina,
that line was
all she taught me.
Not all, I'm sure.
Good evening.
CLARK:  It's like a one-man
reign of terror.
This Bat vigilante has been
consistently targeting
the port
and the adjacent projects
and tenements.
And, as far as I can tell,
the cops are
actually helping him.
"Crime Wave in Gotham."
Other breaking news:
"Water, Wet."
Did you file
the football yet?
Why aren't we covering this?
Poor people
don't buy papers?[CHUCKLES]
People don't buy papers,
period, Kent.
Perry, when you
assign a story,
you're making a choice
about who matters.
And who's worth it.
Good morning, Smallville.
The American conscience died
with Robert, Martin, and John.
Sorry. I'm sorry.
No match.
My guys in the crime lab
never seen one before.
It's called a bullet.
You shoot people with them.
Recovered from the scene
of the firefight
in the desert.
Not sold anywhere
commercially in the world,
even black market.
PERRY:  So?
So who gave
prototype military rounds
to Tuareg fighters
in the Sahara?
The Ask, Lois.
Flight to D.C. tonight.
Couple of days there.
Go.
Coach. No extra legroom.
Economy plus.
Coach!
LEX:  Senator.
My dad always said
that Kentucky mash
was the secret to health.
[SLURPS] Mmm.
This was his room.
I left it
just the way it was.
It's silly.
The magical thinking
of orphan boys.
I'm blocking the import
license for your mineral.
[TAPPING GLASS]
[MOCKING]
The redcapes are coming.
Hmm...
[DRUMMING FINGERS ON TABLE]
You and your hearings.
Galloping through
the streets to warn us.
One if by land,
two if by air.
[DRUMMING STOPS]Mmm.
Do you know the oldest lie
in America, Senator?
Can I call you June?
You can call me
whatever you like.
Take a bucket of piss and
call it Granny's Peach Tea.
Mmm-hmm.
Take a weapon
of assassination
and call it deterrence.
You won't fool a fly or me.
I'm not gonna drink it.
You don't think
Dad would mind, do you?
If I changed just...
Just one thing in this room?
Because that
should be upside-down.
We know better now,
don't we?
The devils don't come
from Hell beneath us. No.
No, they come from the sky.
[BLOOD DRIPPING]
[BATS SCREECHING]
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
[FAUCET RUNNING]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
Wrong room, miss.
Secretary Swanwick,
you haven't been
returning my phone calls.
Miss Lane,
if you'd like an interview,
Major Farris is
just outside that door.
You're treating me
like a stranger?
I'm treating you
like a reporter.
All right. Is the US
providing experimental
military arms
to rebels in Africa?
You know,
with balls like yours,
you belong in here.
What's your source on this?
A tin foil hat?
No, not tin.
But it's metal.
Fired in
the Superman incident.
Experts at the Pentagon
can't ID it.
We haven't been
told the truth.
Here's the truth.
A reporter got greedy
for a scoop
and went where
she shouldn't have.
Superman acted like
some rogue combatant
to rescue her,
and people died.
Don't invent a conspiracy
theory to put back his halo.
Or yours.
Major.FARRIS: Sir.
Oh.
I hope the next generation
of Waynes
won't inherit
an empty wine cellar.
[QUIETLY]
Not that there's likely
to be a next generation.
Thank you, sir.
[ALFRED SIGHS]
This is every call made
from the Russian's phone.
Two mentions of business
with the White Portuguese.
And it's continually
transmitting
blacked-out data
to the personal residence
of Alexander Luthor.
You think Lex Luthor
is the White Portuguese?
[SNIFFS]
I can't see that
he needs the income
from imported arms.
Regardless, I'll need to
put a leech at his house,
and I'm gonna need the suit.
The Bat interrogated
six people
and came away with nothing.
It was Bruce Wayne
that got the information.
Well, Bruce Wayne can't break
into Lex Luthor's house.
Bruce Wayne won't have to.
He's been invited.
[REPORTERS CLAMORING]
[CAMERA CLICKING]
Who's that?
You must be new to
the "let them eat cake" beat.
That is Bruce Wayne.
LEBLANC:  Philanthropist,
bibliophile...
True friend of
the Library of Metropolis.
Mr. Lex Luthor.
[ALL APPLAUDING]
Me? Ah. Okay.
Nicky. Uh...
You're embarrassing me.
Um...
Speech, speech. Uh...
Blah, blah, blah. Uh...
Open bar.
[CHUCKLES]  The end.
Uh...[GUESTS LAUGHING]
The word "philanthropist"
comes from the Greek.
Meaning a lover of humanity.
Uh, it was coined
about 2,500 years ago.
All right.
Where am I going, Alfred?
Go past the elevator.
Do a left.
That's right, must be.
It's in the service corridor
in the basement.
Go down the stairs.
LEX:  Gods and men.
Prometheus went with us.
And he ruined Zeus' plan
to destroy mankind,
and for that he was
given a thunderbolt.
[IMITATES THUNDERBOLT ZAPPING]
Hmm, that seems unfair.
Um... On a serious note,
the Library of Metropolis...
Go to the stairs.
You saw them
on your way in.
Down the stairs.
LEX:  But at one time,
Dad could not buy them. No.
My father could not afford
books growing up.
He had to root
through the garbage
for yesterday's newspaper.
[TV PLAYING]
All right. You got
the kitchens on your right.
Do a left.
Right in front of you.
That's where you want to be.
May I help you,
Mr. Wayne?
Uh, I just...
I thought the bathroom was
down here. I must have...
That last martini was two
too many, I think. [CHUCKLES]
Men's room is upstairs.
Great. I'm okay.
I like those shoes.
[DOOR CLOSES]
I can't stay
down here, Alfred.
ALFRED:  Go upstairs
and socialize.
Some young lady
from Metropolis
will make you honest.
[SCOFFS]
In your dreams, Alfred.
LEX:  Books are knowledge,
and knowledge is power,
and I am... [LAUGHS]
No. Uh, um...
No. What am I? I...
What was I saying? No.
The bittersweet pain
among men
is having knowledge with
no power, because...
Because that is paradoxical!
And, um... [LAUGHS]
Thank you for coming.
[CLEARS THROAT]
[SCATTERED APPLAUSE]
Please drink. Drink.
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
Mr. Wayne? Mr. Wayne?
Clark Kent,  Daily Planet.
Uh, my foundation has
already issued a statement
in support of books.
Sir?Um...
Wow. Pretty girl.
Bad habit. Don't quote me.
All right?
What's your position on
the Bat vigilante in Gotham?
Daily Planet.
Do I own this one?
Or is that the other guy?
Civil liberties are being
trampled on in your city.
Good people
are living in fear.
Don't believe everything
you hear, son.
I've seen it, Mr. Wayne.
He thinks he's above the law.
The Daily Planetcriticizing
those who think
they're above the law
is a little hypocritical,
wouldn't you say?
Considering every time
your hero saves
a cat out of a tree,
you write
a puff piece editorial
about an alien who,
if he wanted to,
could burn
the whole place down.
There wouldn't be
a damn thing we could
do to stop him.
Most of the world doesn't
share your opinion, Mr. Wayne.
Maybe it's
the Gotham City in me.
We just have a bad history
with freaks
dressed like clowns.
LEX:  Boys![CLAPS]  Um!
Bruce Wayne meets
Clark Kent. Ha!
I love it. I love bringing
people together.
How are we?
Lex.Hello. Good.
Hi, hello, Lex,
it is a pleasure. Ow!
Wow! That is a good grip!
You should not pick a fight
with this person. Huh.
So, after all these years,
we finally got you
over to Metropolis.
Well, I thought
I'd come drink you dry.
Well, you're welcome.
You should hop the harbor
more often, though.
I'd love to show you my labs.
Maybe we could
partner on something.
My R and D is up to
all sorts of no good.
That's seven minutes.
Looks like
the transfer's complete.
Mr. Luthor.Yes?
The governor.Governor.
Excuse me.Next time.
Governor! Hi!
GOVERNOR:
Lex, it's good to see you.
[REPORTER SPEAKING SPANISH
ON TV]
BRUCE: Excuse me.
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
[ENGINE REVVING]
[SIGHS]
VIKRAM GANDHI: [ON TV]
We, as a population
on this planet, have been
looking for a savior.
90% of people believe
in a higher power,
and every religion believes
in some sort of
messianic figure.
And when this savior character
actually comes to Earth,
we want to make him abide
by our rules?
We have to understand that
this a paradigm shift.
We have to start thinking
beyond politics.
ANDREW SULLIVAN:
Are there any
moral constraints
on this person?
We have international law.
On this Earth,
every act is a political act.
CHARLIE ROSE:
Is it really surprising
that the most powerful man
in the world
should be
a figure of controversy?
Uh, to have
an individual engaging
in these state-level
interventions
should give us all pause.
GLEN WOODBURN:
Human beings have a horrible
track record of following
people with great power
down paths that led to
huge human atrocities.
GANDHI:  We have
always created icons
in our own image.
What we've done is we project
ourselves onto him.
The fact is, maybe he's not
some sort of devil
or Jesus character.
Maybe he's just a guy
trying to do the right thing.
NEIL deGRASSE TYSON:
We're talking about a being
whose very existence
challenges our own sense
of priority in the universe.
And you go back
to Copernicus,
where he restored the Sun
in the center of
the known universe,
displacing Earth.
And you get to
Darwinian evolution,
and you find out we're not
special on this Earth,
we're just one among
other lifeforms.
And now we learn
that we're not even
special in the entire universe
because there is Superman.
There he is.
An alien among us.
We're not alone.
CHARLIE ROSE:  Are you,
as a United States senator,
personally comfortable saying
to a grieving parent,
"Superman could have
saved your child,
"but on principle,
we did not want him to act"?
I'm not saying
he shouldn't act.
I'm saying he shouldn't
act unilaterally.
What are we
talking about here, then?
Must there be a Superman?
There is.
GUARD:  Keefe.
You made bail.
Open two.
Who paid?
Who the hell are you?
Just a man.
Yeah? Well, what do you want?
To help you
stand for something.
Your three o'clock's here.
He made me half a man.
Let me face him.
PERRY:  So.
I logged into your Dropbox
to find copy.
There's copy all right.
But nothing about football.
Nothing about, uh,
the friends of
the Metropolis Library,
just the goddamn
Gotham Bat thing
I told you not to pursue.
If the police won't help,
the press has to do
the right thing.
You don't get to decide
what the right thing is.
When the  Planetwas founded,
it stood for something, Perry.
And so could you
if it was 1938,
but it's not 1938.
WPA ain't hiring no more.
Apples don't cost a nickel.
Not in here, not out there.
You drop this thing!
Nobody cares about Clark Kent
taking on the Batman.
JAMES HARMON:
It's the Sword of Alexander.
It's the blade that
cut the Gordian knot.
It's a triumph.
DIANA: Yes.
JAMES:  Enjoy.DIANA:  Thank you.
It's a fake.
The real one was sold
in '98 on the black market.
And now it hangs--
Over the bed of
the Sultan of Hajar.
Excuse me.
Excuse me, miss.
The other night
you took something
that doesn't
belong to you.
Stealing's not polite.
Is it stealing if you steal
from another thief?
Who are you?
Someone interested
in the same man you are.
Is that right?
I believe Mr. Luthor
has a photograph
that belongs to me.
Did you get it?
As it happens, no, I didn't.
The data you copied has
military-grade encryption.
You know,
I bet with that dress,
9 out of 10 men will let you
get away with anything.
But you're the 10th?
I'm guessing
I'm the first
to see through that
babe-in-the-woods act.
You don't know me,
but I've known
a few women like you.
Oh, I don't think you've ever
known a woman like me.
You know, it's true what
they say about little boys.
Born with no natural
inclination to share.
I didn't steal your drive.
I borrowed it.
You'll find it in the glove
compartment of your car.
Mr. Wayne.
[BEEPING]
[TYPING]
Did you get it?
The rock?
Yeah, we got it.
[GUN COCKS]
I'm sorry.
[GRUNTS]
Get down! Get down now!
No!
[ALL GRUNTING]
[GROANING]
[GRUNTING CONTINUES]
[GROANS]
[GASPS]
[RUMBLING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[GRUNTS]
She was my world.
And you took her from me.
[SCREAMS]
[GASPS]THE FLASH: Bruce!
Bruce! Listen to me now!
It's Lois!
It's Lois Lane!
She's the key!
Am I too soon?
[GRUNTS IN ANNOYANCE]
I'm too soon!
You're right about him!
You've always
been right about him!
Fear him! Fear him!
Find us, Bruce!
You have to find us!
[GASPS]
BRUCE:  TheWhite Portuguese
is not a man.
It's a ship.
Master Wayne,
since the age of seven
you have been
to the art of deception
as Mozart to
the harpsichord.
But you've never been
too hot at lying to me.
The  White Portugueseis not
carrying a dirty bomb.
What is it carrying?
It's a weapon.
It's a rock.
A mineral capable of
weakening Kryptonian cells.
The first sample big enough
to mean something
turned up in the Indian Ocean
three months ago.
It is now aboard
the  White Portuguese
being delivered
to Lex Luthor.
Who I am going
to steal it from.
To keep it out
of Luthor's hands.
To destroy it.
No.
You're gonna go to war?
That son of a bitch brought
the war to us two years ago.
Jesus, Alfred. Count the dead.
Thousands of people.
What's next? Millions?
He has the power to wipe out
the entire human race,
and if we believe
there's even
a 1% chance that
he is our enemy,
we have to take it
as an absolute certainty.
And we have to destroy him.
But he is not our enemy.
Not today.
20 years in Gotham, Alfred.
We've seen
what promises are worth.
How many good guys are left.
How many stayed that way.
PERRY:  Kent,
I want to talk to you.
Kent!
Where does he go?
Where does he go, Jenny?
I don't...
I don't know.
Clicks his heels
three times,
goes back to Kansas,
I suppose.
Son of a...
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
I don't have a halo
over me, Mr. Secretary.
I went into the desert,
people died.
It keeps me awake. It should.
If you think that Superman
is a murderer,
then throw it away.
But I don't believe
you think that.
[SHIP HORN BLOWING]
[BEEPING]
Move out!
[TIRES SCREECHING]
Go, go, go, go!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
No!
[ENGINE REVVING]
[GRUNTS]
[TRAIN HORN BLARING]
[GUNFIRE]
[YELLS]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[GUNFIRE CONTINUES]
[BEEPING]
[HORN BLARING]
Where is he?
[ENGINE REVVING]
[BEEPING]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[CAR ALARM BLARING]
[BATMAN BREATHES HEAVILY]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
[CAR ALARM STOPS]
Next time they shine
your light in the sky,
don't go to it.
The Bat is dead. Bury it.
Consider this mercy.
BRUCE:  Tell me.
Do you bleed?
You will.
[ENGINE REVVING]
[BEEPING]
FINCH:  How do
we determine what's good?
In a democracy,
good is a conversation,
not a unilateral decision.
[CAMERAS CLICKING]
So I urge Superman to come
to this Hill of the People
tomorrow
to see those
who have suffered.
The world needs to know
what happened in that desert.
And to know
what he stands for.
How far will he
take his power?
Does he act by our will
or by his own?
MARTHA:  People hate
what they don't understand.
But they see what you do,
and they know who you are.
You're not a killer,
a threat.
I never wanted this world
to have you.
[SIGHS]
Be their hero, Clark.
Be their monument.
Be their angel.
Be anything
they need you to be.
Or be none of it.
You don't owe
this world a thing.
You never did.
C.I. thinks
the desert was a setup.
Somebody wanted Superman
to look guilty.
[SIGHS]
The bullet?
The metal was developed
by a private company.
What company?
LexCorp.
Lex Luthor?
He also had private
security contractors
at the desert compound.
Go on record.
Not a chance.
It's classified.
I happen to like my job.
It doesn't make sense.
You said that the ambush was
arranged to frame Superman,
but how could they know
that he'd show up in the...
[GASPS]
In the middle of the desert.
Thank you.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER][BEEPING]
SOLEDAD O'BRIEN:
The Senate hearing
is expected to get underway
any minute now.
And of course the big
unknown in all of this is
will Superman show up?
That is what they're
really waiting to see.
Mr. Keefe. Mr. Keefe.
Soledad O'Brien,
"In the Moment."
Quick question for you.
You're heading in
to meet with the senators.
What will you tell them?
I've come here
to tell them to wake up.
This is flesh and blood.
He has delivered a war here.
And this...
This is what war looks like.
I have nothing.
SOLEDAD:  There are
plenty of people, sir,
who would say
he's their hero.
He is not a hero.
Grace, can you get
Greg up here please?
Right now.
LEX:  Senator!
Hi, you.
Don't go anywhere.
I want to talk to you.
Uh, you know what?
Mercy, you go in
and make sure
no one takes my seat.
So what you been up to?
I'm just here
to tell my story.
That I was willing to finance
a Kryptonian deterrent,
but a certain junior senator
from Kentucky
decided to block it.
Yes, the chair of
the committee on Superman
is soft on security.
Greg, why hasn't he
been getting our checks?
He is, Mr. Wayne.
He gets a check from
the Victims Fund
every month.
He returns them.
DANA BASH:
...who lost both his legs
in those horrific events
in Metropolis that
happened two years ago.
Jesus.
Why haven't I seen this?
GREG:  I'm sorry.
I'll get to the bottom of it.
BASH:  And there he is.
Superman is here.
He is actually
at the United States Capitol.
This is really
a historic moment.
Now we expect that
Superman will give
some kind of a statement
to the Senate,
to the American people,
and, of course, to the world.
He's here. He came.
He's above the Capitol.Ah.
You are gonna be on the
hot seat in there, Junebug.
I grew up on a farm.
I know how
to wrestle a pig.
Do you know the oldest lie
in America, Senator?
It's that power
can be innocent.
Good luck.
Oh, miss...[PEOPLE CLAMORING]
Rudy, she's good to go.
[PEOPLE CHEERING]
Get out! Get out!
Superman! Superman!
Another one came
this morning, Mr. Wayne.
[PEOPLE MURMURING]
[DOOR OPENS]
Let me say
at the outset
that I'm grateful
to our witness
for coming before us today.
This is
how a democracy works.
We talk to each other.
We act by the consent
of the governed, sir.
I have sat here before
to say that
shadow interventions
will not be tolerated
by this committee.
Neither will lies.
Because today
is a day for truth.
Because only by speaking...
Only by working together
can we...
[STAMMERS]  Can we...
Can we create a free,
and a...
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
[GASPS]
REPORTER:  Oh, my God!
[WOMAN SHRIEKS]
[HORSE NEIGHS]
[PEOPLE CONTINUE SCREAMING]
[WOMAN SOBBING]
REPORTER:  We're back
at the nation's Capitol,
where something is happening.
[PAPER RUSTLING]
[CHILD SCREAMS]
[SIRENS WAILING]
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
REPORTER ON TV:  Capitol police
are confirming to CNN
that the suspected bomber is
Wallace Vernon Keefe.
Now these sources...
Clark, it's me again.
Can you...
...could have gotten
the explosive device
into the hearing
by concealing them
inside his wheelchair.
As for Superman,
he was in the room,
but obviously
failed to stop him.
I didn't see it, Lo.
I was standing right there
and I didn't see it.
Clark, there are people
behind this.
I'm afraid I didn't see it
because I wasn't looking.
All this time,
I've been living my life
the way my father saw it.
Righting wrongs for a ghost.
Thinking I'm here to do good.
Superman was never real.
Just the dream of
a farmer from Kansas.
That farmer's dream
is all some people have.
It's all that
gives them hope.
This means something.
It did on my world.
My world
doesn't exist anymore.
[SONIC BOOM]
[DISTORTED VOICES]
KRYPTONIAN SHIP VOICE:
Welcome.
Analysis reveals ship
operating at 37% efficiency.
Would you
like to assume command?
Yes, I would.
[CLEARS THROAT]
Very well. Let's begin.
The Kryptonian archive
contains knowledge
from 100,000 different worlds.
Good.
Teach me.
[GRUNTING]
[CONTINUES GRUNTING]
[YELLS]
[BRUCE CONTINUES GRUNTING]
KRYPTONIAN SHIP VOICE:
Alexander Luthor,
your security override
has been accepted.
Genesis Chamber ready
to analyze genetic sample.
Acknowledging presence
of genetic material.
Analyzing.
I've identified the host as
General Zod of Kandor.
[KNIFE OPENING]
[GROANS]
[BLOOD DRIPPING]
Acknowledging presence
of foreign genetic material.
Analyzing.
You flew
too close to the sun.
Now look at you.
KRYPTONIAN SHIP VOICE:
Advising. Action forbidden.
It has been decreed
by the Council of Krypton
that none will ever again
give life to a deformity
so hateful to sight
and memory.
The desecration
without name.
And where is
the Council of Krypton?
Destroyed, sir.
Then proceed.
Very well. Preparing chrysalis
and commencing metamorphosis.
JENNY:  "And so we are
left to wonder
"if Superman was aware of
the threat and did nothing,
"was he then complicit
in the Capitol tragedy?"
Still no Kent?
"His disappearance
raises questions."
No.
"How could he simply
have disappeared
"at a time when we,
as a nation,
"need him more than ever?"
[CHANTING]  Burn him! Burn him!
Burn him! Burn him!
Something, isn't it?
We men of Kansas
live on a pancake,
so we come to the mountains.
All downhill from here,
down to the floodplain.
Farm at the bottom
of the world.
I remember one season
the water came bad.
I couldn't have been 12.
Dad had out the shovels
and we went at it all night.
[CHUCKLES] We worked till,
I think, I fainted.
But we managed
to stop the water.
We saved the farm.
Your grandma baked me a cake.
Said I was a hero.
Later that day we found out
we blocked
the water all right.
We sent it upstream.
The whole Lang farm
washed away.
While I ate my hero cake,
their horses were drowning.
I used to hear them
wailing in my sleep.
Did the nightmares ever stop?
Yeah.
When I met your mother.
She gave me faith that
there's good in this world.
She was my world.
I miss you, son.
I miss you too, Dad.
ALFRED: You know
you can't win this.
It's suicide.
I'm older now than
my father ever was.
This may be the only thing
I do that matters.
20 years of
fighting criminals
amounts to nothing?
Criminals are
like weeds, Alfred.
Pull one up,
another grows in its place.
This is about
the future of the world.
This is my legacy.
My father
sat me down right here.
Told me what Wayne Manor
was built on.
Railroads, real estates,
and oil.
The first generation
made their fortune
trading with the French.
Pelts and skins.
They were hunters.
NANCY GRACE:  We gotta
wait for more evidence,
but the question
still remains,
where is he?
If Superman
was not involved,
if he's got nothing to hide,
then why hasn't he been seen
since the day
of this tragedy?
[BOTTLES RATTLING]
[SIGHS]
[ENGINE STARTS]
[ENGINE REVS][GASPS]
[WHIMPERS][TIRES SCREECH]
[SCREAMING]
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
[GRUNTS]
[RUMBLING]
The night is here.
Excuse me.
Don't I know...
Plain Lo in the morning.
Lola in slacks.
[SIGHS]
Lois Lane.
[LEX SNIFFLES]
Mmm. Come see the view.
Um... [SNIFFLES]
Mmm-mmm.
Now the secret to the height
is the building material.
It's light metals
which sway a bit
in the wind.
Hmm.
And you know something
about LexCorp metals,
don't you, Miss Lane?
I've proven what you've done.
Wow, you're feisty.
Unfortunately,
that will blow away.
Like sand in the desert.
You're psychotic.
That is
a three-syllable word
for any thought too big
for little minds.
Hmm.
Next category: circles.
Round and round
and round they go
to find Superman.
[GRUNTS] Wrong category, boy.
No, no, triangles.
Yes,
Euclid's triangle inequality.
The shortest distance
between any two points
is a straight path.
And I believe
the straightest path
to Superman
is a pretty little road...
[SNIFFS] Mmm.
...called Lois Lane.
[GASPS]
[SCREAMING]
[GASPING]
You came back.
Boy, do we have
problems up here!
[CLEARS THROAT]
[TICKING]
[STAMMERS]
The problem of...
Of evil in the world.
Uh, the problem of
absolute virtue.
I'll take you in
without breaking you.
Which is more
than you deserve.
The problem of you
on top of everything else.
You above all.
Ah, because
that's what God is.
Horus. Apollo.
Jehovah. Kal-El.
Clark Joseph Kent.
See, what we call God depends
upon our tribe, Clark-Joe.
Because God is tribal.
God takes sides.
No man in the sky intervened
when I was a boy
to deliver me from Daddy's
fist and abominations. Mmm.
I figured out way back,
if God is all-powerful,
he cannot be all-good.
And if he is all-good,
then he cannot
be all-powerful.
And neither can you be.
They need to see
the fraud you are.
With their eyes.
The blood on your hands.
What have you done?
Hmm. And tonight, they will.
Yes. Because you, my friend,
have a date. Hmm.
Across the bay.
Ripe fruit, his hate.
Two years growing.
But it did not take much
to push him over, actually.
Little red notes, big bang.
You let your family die!
And now you will fly to him.
And you will battle him.
To the death.
Black and blue. Fight Night!
The greatest gladiator match
in the history of the world.
God versus man.
[THUNDER RUMBLES]
Day versus night.
Son of Krypton versus
Bat of Gotham.
You think I'll fight him
for you?
Hmm, yes, I do. I think
you will fight-fight-fight
for that special lady
in your life.
She's safe on the ground.
How about you?
Close, but I am
not talking about Lois.
No. Every boy's special lady
is his mother.
[GASPS]
Martha, Martha, Martha.
Hmm.
Why, the mother of a flying
demon must be a witch.
The punishment for witches,
what is that?
That's right. Death by fire.
Mmm. [CHUCKLES]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Where is she?
I don't know!
I would not
let them tell me!
Uh-uh-uh!
If you kill me,
Martha dies.
And if you fly away, mmm,
Martha also dies.
But if you kill the Bat...
Martha lives.
There we go.
There we go. Hmm.
And now God
bends to my will.
[HELICOPTER APPROACHING]
Ooh, now the cameras
are waiting at your ship.
For the world to see
the holes in the holy.
Yes, the Almighty comes clean
about how dirty he is
when it counts.
To save Martha,
bring me
the head of the Bat.
Ah.
Mother of God,
would you look at the time?
When you came here,
you had an hour.
Now it's less.
[TICKING]
ANDERSON COOPER:  Brooke
Baldwin is on the scene.
Brooke,
you're live on the air.
What are you seeing?
There's something
happening at the ship.
It's sending
massive power surges.
ERIKA ERICKSON:  Police
helicopters surrounding
the area.
They've created a barricade
around
this containment center.
And we're trying to get
a little bit closer here
to find out what's going on.
It is absolute chaos.
You can see that lightning,
those surges of electricity.
They seem to be getting
stronger by the minute.
Daily Planet.
Lois. I have to go
to Gotham to convince
him to help me.
Who?
Or he has to die.
Clark.
No one stays good
in this world.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[COMPUTER BEEPS]
2400 hours and 2 minutes.
Subject declining rapidly.
All procedural interventions
have failed.
Outcome
will be death.
[SWITCHES TAPE RECORDER OFF]
[YELLS]
Dr. Silas Stone suspending
all clinical protocol.
US Gov, object 6-19-82
is successfully activated.
[WHIMPERING]
[SCREAMING]
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
LOIS:  I need
a chopper to Gotham.
Call the heliport.
Chopper? We can
barely afford a bicycle.
You wanna chase a story?
Go to the ship.
Superman's probably
there already.
Perry, it's not for a story.
Jenny, get her
a chopper to Gotham.
And forget the heliport.
Put it on the goddamn roof.
On the roof, Lois!
Where are we headed?
There!
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
[SIRENS WAILING]
Well, here I am.
Bruce. Please.
I was wrong.
You have to listen to me.
Lex wants us to...
[HIGH-PITCHED RINGING]
[GROANING]
You don't understand.
There's no time!
I understand.
[GROANING]
[GRUNTS]
[PANTING]
[GROANS]
CLARK: Stay down!
If I wanted it,
you'd be dead already.
[GRUNTS]
[WHIRRS]
[CHOKING]
Breathe it in.
That's fear.
You're not brave.
[GRUNTS]
Men are brave.
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[GROANS]
[GASPS]
[GRUNTS]
[CLARK GROANING]
[CHOKES]
[GRUNTING]
[GROANING]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[YELLS]
[GROANING]
[CHOKING]
[GRUNTING]
[GROANS]
I bet your parents taught you
that you mean something.
That you're here for a reason.
My parents taught me
a different lesson,
[GRUNTING] dying in the gutter
for no reason at all.
[GROANS]
[SCREAMS]
[YELLS]
[CONTINUES GROANING]
They taught me the world
only makes sense
if you force it to.
[HELICOPTER APPROACHING]
[GRUNTS]
[GROANS]
You were never a god.
You were never even a man.
[STRAINING]
You're letting him
kill Martha.
[CHOKING]
What does that mean?
Why did you say that name?
Find him.
Save
Martha.
THOMAS:  Martha.
[PEARLS CLATTERING]
[SCREAMING INAUDIBLY]
Martha.
Why did you say that name?
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
Martha!
Why did you say that name?
Clark! Stop!
Please! Stop!
Why did you say that name?
It's his mother's name!
It's his mother's name.
[PANTING]
[GRUNTS]
[SIRENS WAILING]
ERICKSON: We're not
getting any answers.
We're still right outside
the containment center.
A dangerous situation.
Military and
police personnel
surrounding the area.
[MARTHA PANTING]
CLARK:  Luthor.
He wanted
your life for hers.
She's losing time.
The scout ship seems to be
drawing power from the city.
It's got to be Lex.
They need you at that ship.
I'll find her.
My mother needs me. Wait.
I'll make you a promise.
Martha won't die tonight.
ALFRED:  Master Wayne.
Alfred.
Uh, I'm sorry
for listening in,
but I've tracked
the Russian's phone
to a warehouse near the port.
You're locked onto it.
KNYAZEV: I'm afraid
this is goodbye.
And every time
we say goodbye,
you die a little.
[BAT PLANE APPROACHING]
MAN 1: Take it downMAN 2: Go! Go!
You have to take it, Alfred.
Ah, right.
Commencing drone mode.
Thermal imaging
is showing me
two dozen hostiles
on the third floor.
Why don't I drop you off
on the second?
[BAT PLANE APPROACHING]
[DOOR SLAMS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[PANICKED SHOUTING]
[BEEPING][GASPS]
[GROANING]
[YELLS]
[GROANS]
[SCREAMING]
[GROANING]
[GASPS]
[SCREAMS]
[MAN YELLING][GUN FIRING]
[ALL GRUNTING]
[SCREAMS]
[GRUNTING]
[GROANS]
[SCREAMS]
[GROANING]
[WHIMPERING]
Drop it.
I said drop it!
I'll kill her.
Believe me, I'll do it.
I believe you.
[SIGHS]
It's okay.
I'm a friend of your son's.
[PANTING]
I figured. The cape.
[TICKING]
[DINGS][EXPLOSIONS]
[GASPS]
"Late, late,"
says the White Rabbit.
KRYPTONIAN SHIP VOICE:
30 seconds to animation.
Right, wabbit?
Hmm. Out of tricks,
out of time.
And one Bat head short.
KRYPTONIAN SHIP VOICE:
20 seconds to animation.
[PHONE RINGS]Ah. That'll be the cook.
Excuse me.
Uh, Gotham Roast.
Well done.
Hello. Break the bad news.
BRUCE:  I'd rather do
the breaking in person.
KRYPTONIAN SHIP VOICE:
10 seconds to animation.
You've lost.
Nine, eight, seven...
I cannot let you win.
I gave the Bat
a fighting chance to do it,
but he was not
strong enough.
So, if man
won't kill God...
KRYPTONIAN SHIP VOICE:
...two, one.
...the devil will do it!
[MACHINE WHIRRING]
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLING]
[ELECTRICITY CONTINUES
CRACKLING]
[GASPS][PEOPLE EXCLAIMING]
JENNY:  Perry!
PERRY: All right.
Stay calm, everybody!
We're getting reports
there are total blackouts
in the north and to
the northwest of the city.
Federal authorities
are trying to determine
if this is part of
a larger terrorist attack.
Ancient Kryptonian
deformity.
Hmm. Blood of my blood.
[GROWLING]
Born to destroy you.
Your Doomsday.
[GROWLING CONTINUES]
[ROARING]
Now God is good
as dead.
[ROARING]
Oh!
[ROARING CONTINUES]
[GRUNTING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLING]
[CLARK GROANING]
[PANTING]
[GROWLING]
[HELICOPTER APPROACHING]
[GRUNTING]
[SNARLING]
[GROANING]
[CLARK GRUNTING]
[HELICOPTER APPROACHING]
[DOOMSDAY GROWLING]
POTUS joining.
SWANWICK:  Mr. President.
PRESIDENT:  What the hell
is it, Calvin?
COOPER:  These are
live images from the top
of the LexCorp tower
in downtown Metropolis.
Military aircraft
are on the scene.
This thing emerged from
the Kryptonian crash site
just moments ago.
Thankfully though,
the work day is over
in the downtown core.
It's nearly empty.
Now military aircraft.
Those are Apache helicopters.
They have now just arrived.
The images that...
[DOOMSDAY ROARING]
We've, uh...
We just lost connection
with Metropolis 8 News.
Now, it's not clear
what just happened.
What's happening there,
Alfred?
[EXHALES]
How best to describe it?
ANNOUNCER:  Metropolis airspace
has been closed briefly.
FLIGHT ATTENDANT: Excuse me?
We kindly ask that
you stay in your seats.
Excuse me?
Miss Prince?
[DOOMSDAY ROARING]
[GRUNTING]
Sir. Look,
they've cleared the city.
Looks like he's taking it
into space.
We can go straight
to Key Red, Mr. President.
Not yet. Are you crazy?
They're high enough
that we can nuke 'em
with no casualties, sir.
One casualty, Mr. President.
Superman.
[PRESIDENT SIGHS]
PRESIDENT:  God have mercy
on us all.
[SIGHS IN RELIEF]
[ALARM BLARING]
Key is hot.Key is hot.
CHAIRMAN OF JOINT CHIEFS:
Red birds are
armed to deploy, sir.
PRESIDENT:  Fire at will.
Three, two, one...
[DOOMSDAY GRUNTS]
[DOOMSDAY ROARING]
Oh, God.
Projectile 1. Impact.
Stryker's Island,
east of Metropolis.
That's uninhabited.
Projectile 2...
No apparent reentry.
PRESIDENT:  Projectile 2?
Superman, Mr. President.
Projectile 2 was Superman.
SIGNALS OFFICER:  Sir.
It's moving.
[DOOMSDAY GROWLING]
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLING]
[DOOMSDAY ROARING]
SWANWICK:  The shockwaves
are getting stronger.
Every time we hit it,
we make it more powerful.
We can't attack.
PRESIDENT:  What are
you saying, Calvin?
I'm saying it's unkillable.
[SIGHS]
[BEEPING]
[RAPID BEEPING]
[DOOMSDAY GROWLS]
[GROANS]
Master Wayne,
are you receiving me?
BRUCE:  Alfred.
It's Kryptonian.
Only Kryptonite weapons
can kill it.
They might.
If you had any left.
I got one round left.
The spear. Alfred, the spear.
It's pure Kryptonite.
It's back in Gotham.
If I can penetrate the skin,
the spear will kill it.
It would in theory.
I've gotta get it to
chase me back to the city.
Back to the Kryptonite.[ENGINE REVVING]
[GRUNTING]
[DOOMSDAY GROWLING]
[GROANING]
[PANTING]
[DOOMSDAY ROARING]
Oh, shit.
[GRUNTS]
[PANTING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[GROANS]
Why did you bring him
back to the city?
BRUCE:  The port
is abandoned.
There's a weapon here
that can kill it.
Did you find the spear?
I've been a little busy.
This thing, this creature,
seems to feed on energy.
CLARK: This thing is
from another world.
My world.
I've killed things
from other worlds before.
Is she with you?
I thought she was with you.
[DOOMSDAY ROARING]
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLING]
[SIRENS WAILING]
[GASPING]
[PANTING]
[DOOMSDAY GROWLS]
[DIANA YELLING]
[GRUNTS]
[DIANA GRUNTING]
[DOOMSDAY ROARING]
[CLARK GRUNTING]
[GROANING]
[YELLS]
[MUFFLED SCREAMS]
[DOOMSDAY GROWLING]
[YELLING]
[BANGING]
[MUFFLED SCREAMS]
[COUGHING]
[PANTING]
[DOOMSDAY GROWLING]
[BRUCE GRUNTS]
[BRUCE GROANING]
[DOOMSDAY ROARING]
[PANTING]
Clark!
[WHIMPERING]
[GRUNTS]
[COUGHS]
Clark!
Clark! Are you all right?
[DIANA GRUNTING]
[CHUCKLES]
[YELLS]
[GRUNTS]
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLING]
[DIANA SCREAMS]
[DOOMSDAY ROARING]
[BOTH PANTING]
I love you.
No. No, Clark, you can't.
This is my world.
No, Clark, don't.
You are my world.
No.
Please. Clark!
[DOOMSDAY GROWLING]
[GRUNTING]
[YELLING]
[PANTING]
[YELLS]
[GROANS LOUDLY]
[GROANING]
[DOOMSDAY ROARING]
[GRUNTING]
[GROANING]
[CLARK YELLING]
[PANTING]
[CRYING]
[ELECTRIC RAZOR WHIRRING]
[SNIFFLES]
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Hi.
Clark had this sent here,
so he could surprise you.
[JET ENGINE ROARING]
All those circuses back east
burying an empty box.
They don't know
how to honor him,
except as a soldier.
I've failed him in life.
I won't fail him in death.
Help me find
the others like you.
Perhaps they don't
want to be found.
They will.
And they'll fight.
We have to stand together.
[SIGHS]
100 years ago,
I walked away
from mankind.
From a century
of horrors.
Man made a world
where standing together
is impossible.
Men are still good.
BRUCE:  We fight. We kill.
We betray one another.
But we can rebuild.
We can do better.
We will.
We have to.
The others like me.
Why did you say
they'll have to fight?
Just a feeling.
[CELL DOOR OPENS]
SUPERMAX GUARD:  Turn around
and face the wall.
Place your forehead
against the wall.
Put your hands
behind your back,
so that I can come in
and restrain you.
Whatever you do,
wherever you go,
I'll be watching you.
But the bell's
already been rung.
And they've heard it.
Out in the dark.
Among the stars. Hmm.
Ding dong, the god is dead.
[GRUNTS]
[DOOR BUZZING]
But a bell cannot be unrung!
He's hungry. He's found us.
And he's coming!
Ding, ding, ding, ding, ding,
ding, ding, ding, ding.
Ding, ding, ding, ding, ding.
Ding, ding, ding, ding, ding,
ding, ding, ding, ding.