So he survived. What's the worry?
He didn't even lose a limb,
an eyeball, bladder control.
The point is listen to them.
They've lost faith in old symbols.
They're ready to bond with you,
the icon of the future.
If it works, don't fix it.
We'll celebrate tonight
at my annual Max-querade Ball.
Shreck and Cobblepot...
the visionary alliance. Come on.
When it came time...
to ensure the safety of our fair city...
did the Mayor have a plan?
No!
He relied on a man.
A Batman.
A ticking time-bomb
of a costumed freak...
Our prime concern
is this ghastly grotesque.
But let's not forget
about repairing the Batmobile.
There's security to consider.
It's not as though we can take it
to any old Joe's body shop, is it, sir?
Security?
Who let Vicki Vale into the Batcave?
I'm sitting there working,
and I turn around...
and there she is. "Hi, Vick. Come on in."
- Ready?
- I think I'll take the stairs.
[Suspenseful instrumental music]
PENGUIN: You ask me
am I up here for personal glory?
No.
I toiled for many years...
in utter obscurity
beneath your boulevards.
The glory that I yearn to recapture...
is the glory of Gotham!
How can this be accomplished?
I know you're all concerned.
Hey, just relax.
I'll take care of the squealing,
wretched, pinhead puppets of Gotham!
I didn't say that.
You gotta admit,
I played this stinking city...
like a harp from hell!
[Crowd booing]
Get out of here!
Why is there always someone who
brings eggs and tomatoes to a speech?
[Looming instrumental music]
There he is!
My babies.
Did you miss me?
Great speech, Oswald.
My name is not Oswald! It's Penguin!
I am not a human being!
I am an animal! Cold-blooded!
Crank the AC!
Where are my lists? Bring me the names!
It's time.
These are the names
of the first-born sons of Gotham City.
Just like I was.
And like me, a terrible fate waits for them.
Tonight, while their parents party...
they'll be dreaming away...
in their safe cribs...
their soft beds...
and we will snatch them...
carry them into the sewer...
and toss them
into a deep, dark, watery grave.
Penguin?
I mean, killing sleeping children,
isn't that a little...
No, it's a lot.
Mr. Wayne, a reminder.
Tonight is that loathsome party
hosted by the odious Mr. Shreck.
May we RSVP
in the resoundingly negative?
Not interested.
Although...
Selina Kyle might be there.
[Upbeat dance music playing]
Ingenious costume.
Let me guess.
Trust fund goodie-goodie.
Feeling good?
Well, you almost made a monster
the mayor of Gotham City.
I am the light of this city...
and I am its mean, twisted soul.
Does it matter who's mayor?
- It does to me.
- Yawn.
[SIow rhythmic music playing]
Hi.
I'm sorry about yesterday, but I had...
a pretty big deal come through.
Fall through, actually.
It's okay.
I had to go home and feed my cat.
So no hard feelings, then?
Actually...
semi-hard, I'd say.
There's a big, comfy California King
over in Bedding.
What do you say?
You mean, take off our costumes?
I guess I'm tired of wearing masks.
Me, too.
Let me ask you something.
Why'd you come tonight?
- You first.
- To see you.
That's lovely.
I really wish I could say the same,
but I came for Max.
What do you mean? You and...
Not you and Max.
Me and Max.
No. This and Max.
Don't give me
a killing-Max-won't-solve-anything speech.
Because it will.
Aren't you tired of this
sanctimonious robber-baron...
always coming out on top
when he should be six feet under?
I'm sure you have a lot of problems
with your boss...
but who the hell do you think you are?
I don't know anymore, Bruce.
A kiss under the mistletoe.
Mistletoe can be deadly if you eat it.
But a kiss can be even deadlier...
if you mean it.
Oh, my God.
Does this mean we have to start fighting?
Let's go outside.
[Tense instrumental music]
- Are you okay?
- I'm all right.
You didn't invite me, so I crashed!
- What do you want?
- Right now, my troops...
are fanning out across town...
for your children! Yes!
For your first-born sons!
The ones you left defenseless at home...
so you could dress up like jerks...
get juiced and dance...
badly!
I've personally come...
for Gotham's favorite son:
Mr. Chip Shreck.
You're coming with me,
you great white dope...
to die way down in the sewer.
Not Chip. If you have an iota
of human feeling, take me instead.
I don't. So, no.
I'm the one you want. Ask yourself.
Isn't it Max Shreck
who manipulated and betrayed you?
Isn't it Max, not Chip...
who you want to see immersed
to his eyeballs in raw sewage?
Okay, you got a point.
I'll let the little prince live for now.
In the duck!
This is gonna be good...
to cut down a whole crop
of Gotham's most promising...
before their prime.
You ask me, how do I lure them in?
A little Pied Penguin action.
And you get to watch them sink...
into a deep puddle...
of your industrial byproducts.
Then you join them.
[Eerie instrumental music]
[Baby crying]
Would you hurry up
and get those kids loaded already?
Right this way, kiddies. Come on.
Come with me.
So, where are all the children?
"Batman."
My dear penguins...
we stand on a great threshold.
It's okay to be scared.
Many of you won't be coming back.
Thanks to Batman, the time has come...
to punish all of God's children.
First, second, third, and fourth-born!
Why be biased?
Male and female!
Hell, the sexes are equal...
with their erogenous zones
blown sky-high!
Forward march!
The liberation of Gotham...
has begun!
[Valiant instrumental music]
ALFRED: The penguins
are moving above ground.
POODLE LAD Y: Penguin army
approaching launch destination...
at Gotham Plaza.
One minute until ignition.
They wouldn't put me on a pedestal...
so I'm laying them on a slab!
The penguins seem to be converging
on Gotham Plaza.
Thirty seconds until ignition.
Estimated casualties after launch:
100,000 people.
The penguins have reached
Gotham Square.
Fifteen seconds to ignition.
Ready when you are, sir.
I've got the coordinates.
Ten, nine, eight, seven...
- All right. Let's turn them around.
- Yes, sir.
Something is wrong.
Something has jammed the signal.
They seem to be turning around.
There is also something coming this way.
Very large. Very fast.
Who's there?
All right,
I'm homing in on the signal's origin.
You're just jealous
because I'm a genuine freak...
and you have to wear a mask!
You might be right.
But what it all comes down to is,
who's holding the umbrella?
My babies!
[Suspenseful instrumental music]
I don't know what you want, but I know I
can get it for you with a minimum of fuss.
Money, jewels...
a very big ball of string.
- Your blood, Max.
- My blood?
I gave at the office.
A half-pint. I'm talking gallons.
MAX: Let's make a deal.
Other than my blood,
what can I do for you?
Sorry, Max. A die for a die.
You're not just saving a life,
you're saving...
Shut up. You're going to jail.
Don't be naive. The law doesn't apply
to people like him or us.
Wrong on both counts.
Why are you doing this?
Let's just take him to the police.
Then we can go home...
together.
Selina...
don't you see?
We're the same.
Split, right down the center.
Selina, please.
Bruce...
I would love to live with you
in your castle...
forever, just like in a fairy tale.
I just couldn't live with myself.
So don't pretend this is a happy ending.
Selina Kyle.
You're fired.
And Bruce Wayne...
why are you dressed up like Batman?
Because he is Batman, you moron.
Was.
Don't.
You killed me, the Penguin killed me,
Batman killed me.
That's three lives down.
You got enough in there to finish me off?
One way to find out.
Four, five.
Still alive!
Six, seven.
All good girls go to heaven.
[Satirical laughter]
Two lives left.
I think I'll save one for next Christmas.
But in the meantime...
how about a kiss, Santie Claus?
[Valiant instrumental music]
Shit! I picked a cute one.
The heat's getting to me.
I'll murder you momentarily.
But first...
I need a cool drink...
of ice water.
[Solemn instrumental music]
[Serene instrumental music]
Alfred, stop the car.
[Curious instrumental music]
Well, come what may,
merry Christmas, Mr. Wayne.
Merry Christmas, Alfred.
"Goodwill toward men."
And women.
English - SDH