CHASE: I have something for you.
It's on the table.
I hope you like it.
Call it clinical intuition.
I thought your dreams
might need changing.
My parents were murdered
in front of me...
when I was just a kid.
I don't...
remember a lot of what happened...
but what I do comes to me
in my dreams, flashes.
There's a new element now though,
I haven't seen before.
It's a red leather book.
Something else.
My dreams are coming to me
when I'm awake now.
Bruce, you're describing
repressed memories.
Images of a forgotten pain
that's trying to surface.
[Kettle whistle blowing]
Oh, damn. Wait, I'll be right back.
Is it possible...
there's an aspect of your parents' death
that you haven't faced?
You were so young when it happened.
Maybe I'll leave you two alone.
This goes way beyond taking
your work home, doesn't it, Doctor?
All right.
I think he's fascinating.
Clinically.
Why does a man do this?
It's as if he's cursed
to pay some great penance.
What crime could he have committed
to deserve a life of nightly torture?
It's more than just...
professional interest, isn't it, Chase?
Bruce, are you jealous?
No.
I can't be jealous of Batman.
I want to be close,
but you won't let me near.
What are you protecting me from?
You want to know me?
You want to know who I am?
I guess...
we're all two people.
One in daylight,
and the one we keep in shadow.
Rage, violent...
passion.
[Beeping]
Excuse me.
I'm kind of busy.
I'm sorry to bother you, sir.
I have some rather distressing news
about Master Dick.
Is he all right?
I'm afraid Master Dick has gone traveling.
He ran away?
Actually, he took the car.
He boosted the Jag?
Not the Jaguar.
The other car.
- The Bentley?
- No, sir.
The other car.
[Upbeat rock music]
Come for a little ride
in my love machine, babies.
[Slow pop music]
Chill, this is Batman.
Open up, Batman.
Wait a minute. That's not Batman.
What're you talking about?
That's Batboy.
It ain't the Bat!
[Woman screaming]
Go, go!
Hey! Let her go!
Who the hell are you?
I'm Batman.
So I forgot my suit, all right?
- Come on, run!
- Wait.
Doesn't Batman ever kiss the girl?
- Go.
- Thanks, you saved my life.
I could definitely
get into this superhero gig.
Batman!
Bastard!
It should've been you! It's your fault!
If you'd have told Two-Face
who you were at the circus...
they'd still be alive!
If Bruce Wayne could've given his life
for your family, he would have.
All I can think about every second
of the day is getting Two-Face.
He took my whole life.
When I was out there tonight...
I imagined it was him that I was fighting...
even when I was fighting you.
And all the pain went away.
- Do you understand?
- Yes, I do.
Good. 'Cause you gotta help me find him.
And when we do...
I'm the one who kills him.
So, you're willing to take a life?
As long as it's Two-Face.
Then it will happen this way:
You make the kill.
But your pain doesn't die with Harvey,
it grows.
So you run out into the night
to find another face and another...
and another...
until one terrible morning
you wake up and realize...
that revenge has become your whole life...
and you won't know why.
You can't understand.
Your family wasn't killed by a maniac.
Yes, they were.
We're the same.
If we're the same, Bruce, help me.
Train me, let me be your partner.
No.
I can't.
You still have a choice.
Look, Bruce, I'm a part of this,
whether you like it or not.
[Photographers clamoring]
REPORTER: Tonight, all of Gotham society
has turned out for Edward Nygma's...
gala unveiling of his New Improved Box.
- Thanks, Al.
- My pleasure, sir.
They'll be dining and dancing
the night away...
on the glamorous roof of the Ritz Gotham.
[Upbeat instrumental music playing]
Mr. Nygma,
what's it like to have your face...
on the cover of every magazine
in Gotham?
Edward, how does it feel to be
the city's newest, most eligible bachelor?
Gotham must know!
There's Bruce Wayne!
Brucie!
Eddie, he is too cute.
How come you don't look
so good in that suit?
Shut up. You're here to work.
- How's my mole?
- Fine.
What about rumors of a NygmaTech
takeover of Wayne Enterprises?
NygmaTech's stock is outselling
Wayne Enterprises' 2-to-1.
- Are you yesterday's news, Bruce?
- Yes.
Bruce, old man.
The press were just wondering
what it feels like...
to be outsold, outclassed,
out-coiffed and...
generally outdone in every way.
Hello, Edward. Congratulations.
Great party. Nice suit.
Wit. Good.
- And you are?
- Chase.
And what a grand pursuit you must be.
I'm Bruce Wayne, Miss...
You can call me anything you want.
Ladies and gentlemen, the future!
My New Improved Box offers
fully interactive holographic fantasies.
[Audience exclaiming in surprise]
Edward, you're dashing and a genius.
How do you create these images, hon?
That, my dear, is my little secret.
Fully interactive holographs.
Only a high-frequency carrier wave,
beamed directly into the brain...
could create such images.
Yeah, and you wish you'd thought of it.
Yes, don't be a sore loser, Brucie.
- Step inside. Give it a try.
- Edward...
if you can introduce images
into the mind...
what prevents you
from extracting images out of the mind?
Too timid to try my machine? Just say so.
Shall we dance?
Naughty, naughty.
Looking for something?
I was just wondering how you turn it off.
Clever.
- Thanks.
- My pleasure.
COMPUTER: Good evening, Mr. Wayne.
Relax.
Tell me your dreams.
Tell me your fantasies.
Tell me your secrets.
Tell me...
your deepest, darkest...
fears.
No. No!
TWO-FACE: Relax, folks!
It's only an old-fashioned
low-tech stickup!
We're interested in the basics!
Cash, jewelry, cellular telephones.
Hand them over nice and quietly,
and no one will be hurt.
Emergency, Alfred.
Yes, sir?
Be calm, everybody!
Just be calm!
Excuse me!
You're ruining my big party!
Are you insane?
We're sick of waiting for you
to deliver the Batman, dear boy.
Patience, O Bifurcated One.
Patience, hell, we want him dead!
And nothing brings out the Batman
like a little murder and mayhem!
The least you could have done
is let me in on the caper.
We could have organized this, planned it,
pre-sold the movie rights.
[Glass shattering]
Batman!
Your entrance was good, his was better.
The difference? Showmanship.
Emergency, Alfred.
Oh, sir. I could be fired for this, sir.
Perhaps they'll have me back
at Buckingham Palace.
All right, boys! Phase Two!
My place, midnight.
Nothing like a bad case of gas!
Why can't you just die?
Hi.
What the hell did you think
you were doing?
You got a real gratitude problem,
you know that, Bruce?
I need a name. Batboy? Nightwing?
I don't know, what do you think?
What's a good sidekick name?
How about
"Dick Grayson, college student"?
Screw you. I just saved your life.
You owe me.
You were totally out of control.
You're going to get yourself killed.
- You're looking at your new partner.
- No.
Whenever you go out at night,
I'll be watching.
And wherever Batman goes,
I'm gonna be right beside him.
I mean, how are you gonna stop me?
I can stop you.
[Clears throat]
Al, hang this next to the Batsuit...
where it belongs.
And you're encouraging him.
Young men with a mind for revenge
need little encouragement.
They need guidance.
You, above all, should know
the consequences of the life you choose.
Even Chase calls being Batman a curse.
Perhaps the lady's just what
the doctor ordered.
She seems lovely and wise.
I've never been in love before, Alfred.
Go to her.
Tell her how you feel.
She wants Batman, not Bruce Wayne.
Let the lady decide.
I'm sorry.
I can't believe this.
I've imagined this moment
since I first saw you.
Your eyes.
Your lips.
Your body.
And now I have you...
and I'm wishing you were somebody else.
I guess a girl has to grow up sometime.
I've met someone.
He's not you.
I hope you can understand.
I understand.
Well...
That's just what I said.
Then I taught my doggie a new trick:
How to map the human mind.
Would you like to see what our old friend
Bruce Wayne has in his head?
Riddle me this.
What kind of man has bats on the brain?
- Go ahead. You can say it.
- You're a genius.
Oh, stop.
So, from this day on...
Batman is no more.
You can't just quit. I mean...
there's monsters out there.
Batman has to protect the innocent.
I've dedicated my life
to helping strangers I've never met.
Faces I've never seen.
Well, the innocent aren't
faceless anymore.
You can't tell me what I'm gonna do
with the rest of my life.
My dad told me
that every man goes his own way.
My way goes to Two-Face.
You gotta help me.
And if you do find Harvey...
and then you kill him, what next?
Exactly.
Then you'd be alone, like me.
No, you've got to let this go.
Listen to me, Dick. I'm your friend.
I don't need a friend right now, all right?
I need a partner.
Two-Face has got to pay.
Please.
Chase is coming over for dinner.
I'm going to tell her...
everything.
Come on upstairs. We'll talk.
- Good evening, Dr. Meridian.
- Good evening, Alfred.
- Happy Halloween.
- Happy Halloween to you.
I asked you here tonight...
because there's something
that I wanted to tell you.
I wanted to tell you something, too.
What I wanted...
Go ahead, you go first.
All right, okay.
Trick or treat!
All my life, I have been...
I have been attracted
to a certain kind of man.
The wrong kind of man.
And, I mean, look what I do
for a living, right?
And since I met you, I...
Oh, God.
Why am I so nervous?
And don't eat too much tonight...
or you'll be sick in your beds.
[Comical instrumental music]
Happy Halloween!
Bruce, what's wrong?
It's happening again.
Flashes.
My parents' death.
Your memories are trying
to break through, don't fight them.
I want to tell you something.
- Something I've never told anyone.
- It's all right.
It's all right. I'm here.
CHASE: I'm here.
BRUCE: The night of my parents' wake...
the priest's words gave no comfort.
Of course.
There, on my father's desk, the red book.
His journal.
He had written in it every day of my life.
But now he'd never write in it again.
At that moment, I knew
my life would never be the same.
I raced out into the storm...
trying to outrun the rage.
The pain.
Then I fell.
I fell forever.
The cave was monstrous.
It must have been there for centuries.
And there, deep in the shadows...
I saw...
It was coming toward me.
I was scared at first, but only at first.
The figure in the dark was my destiny.
It would change my life forever.
I would use its image to strike terror...
into the hearts of those who did evil.
I would ensure what happened to me
would never happen to anyone else again.
I would have my revenge.
Bruce, what are you trying to tell me?
Chase, I'm...
Twick or tweet!
Trick.
Remember the plan.
Seize and capture.
- No killing.
- That goes double for you.
If I was a superhero...
where would I hide?
Spank me.
COMPUTER: Intruder alert!
RIDDLER: "Intruder alert!"
Shut up!
Now, that's impressive!
You know, it's always risky introducing
a tamed animal into the wild.
They may have trouble adapting
to their new environment.
[Laughing mockingly]
[Traditional baseball instrumental music]
Somebody tell the fat lady she's on in five.
Joygasm!
Get the girl!
No!
Don't kill him.
If you kill him...
...he won't learn nothing.
Bruce!
Master Bruce.
How are you, young man?
You haven't called me that for a long time.
Old habits die hard.
Are you all right?
- Where's Chase?
- I'm afraid they've taken Dr. Meridian.
Master Dick has run away.
The cave has been destroyed.
And there's another riddle.
I'm coming, my sweet.
Like the jacket?
It keeps me safe
when I'm jogging at night.
Batman will come for me.
Batman?
Batman, you say?
Coming for you?
I'm counting on it!
What is that? Where's that coming from?
- There.
- Who the hell is doing that?
The Riddler.
"We're five little items
of an everyday sort.
"You'll find us all in a tennis court."
In...
"A, E, I, O, U." Vowels.
Not entirely unclever, sir.
But what do a clock, a match...
chess pawns, and vowels
have in common?
What do these riddles mean?
Every riddle has a number in the question
and they arrived in this order:
13, 1, 8, and 5.
ALFRED: 13, 1, 8, and 5.
What do they mean?
Perhaps letters of the alphabet?
Of course, 13 is "M."
1 would be "A," 8 would be "H"
and 5 would be "E."
"M-A-H-E."
Perhaps 1 and 8 are 18.
18 is "R."
"M-R-E."
How about "Mr. E"?
- Mystery?
- And another name for mystery?
Enigma.
Mr. E. Nygma.
Edward Nygma.
Stickley's suicide was obviously
a computer-generated forgery.
You really are quite bright,
despite what people say.
Are all the Batsuits destroyed, Alfred?
All except the prototype
with the sonar modifications you invented.
But you haven't tested it yet.
Tonight's a good night.
What do you suggest, Alfred? By sea...
or by air?
Why not both?
Who's your tailor?
I took the liberty, sir.
"R"? What's that stand for?
Robin.
Riddler and Two-Face can make
a pretty lethal combination.
I figured you could use a hand.
Two against two are better odds.
I can't promise I won't kill Harvey.
A man's got to go his own way.
A friend taught me that.
Not just a friend.
A partner.
He's not coming.
Shut it down.
Wait a minute!
Hey, go!
Go.
A-14.
Hit!
- Sweet.
- B-12.
Hit! And my favorite vitamin, I might add.
- That sinking feeling.
- I like this game.
C-9.
You sunk my battleship.
Who, me?
[Beeping]
This is your captain speaking.
Please return to your seats.
We will be experiencing turbulence.
I got him.
I hope they can find the little black box.
Now...
the real game begins.
Holy rusted metal, Batman!
The ground, it's all metal.
It's full of holes, you know. Holey.
Robin, wait.
The whole island's moving.
Looking for us?
That was for my mother!
My father!
My brother!
And this is for me.
Finally, justice is served!
Let us die!
You're a man after our own heart, son.
I'll see you in hell.
I'd rather see you in jail.
Oh, good boy.
The Bat has taught you very well.
Noble. Stupid...
but noble.
Riddle me this.
Riddle me that.
Who's afraid of the big black bat?
No more tricks, Edward.
Very well, then.
Let's get real.
Release Chase.
This is between you and me.
And me. And me!
You've been sucking Gotham's
brain waves...
and now you've devised a way
to read men's minds.
You betcha!
Soon my little Box will be on
countless TVs around the world...
feeding me credit-card numbers,
bank codes...
sexual fantasies, and little white lies.
Into my head they'll go.
Victory is inevitable.
For if knowledge is power...
then a God am...
I!
Was that over the top? I can never tell.
By the way, I've seen your mind, freak!
Yours is the greatest riddle of all.
Can Bruce Wayne and Batman
ever truly coexist?
We'll find out today!
But first, let's meet our contestants.
Behind curtain...
number one...
the absolutely fabulous
Dr. Chase Meridian.
She enjoys hiking, getting her nails done...
and foolishly hopes to be
the love of Bruce's life.
And behind curtain number two...
Fatman's one and only partner.
This acrobat turned orphan...
likes Saturday morning cartoons
and dreams of one day being...
bare naked with a girl.
And below these contestants...
my personal favorite:
A watery grave!
Just one little touch...
and five seconds later
these two day-players are...
gull feed on the rocks below.
Not enough time to save them both.
Which one will it be, Batman?
Bruce's love?
Or the Dark Knight's junior partner?
[Imitating clock ticking]
There is no way for me
to save them or myself.
This is all one giant deathtrap.
Judges?
I'm sorry. Your answer must be
in the form of a question.
- But thank you for playing.
- Wait.
- I have a riddle for you.
- For me?
Really?
Tell me.
I see without seeing.
To me, darkness is as clear as daylight.
What am I?
Please!
You're as blind as a bat!
Exactly.
Bummer.
Thanks.
All those heroics for nothing.
No more riddles,
no more curtains one and two.
Just plain curtains.
Aren't you forgetting something, Harvey?
Your coin.
You're always of two minds
about everything.
Yes, of course. You're right, Bruce.
Emotion's always the enemy
of true justice.
Thank you.
You've always been a good friend.
[Exclaiming]
Why?
Why can't I kill you?
Too many questions.
Poor Edward.
I had to save them both.
You see,
I'm both Bruce Wayne and Batman.
Not because I have to be.
Now, because I choose to be.
DR. BURTON: Thank you for responding to
my request for a consultation, Dr. Meridian.
Edward Nygma has been screaming
for hours...
that he knows the true identity of Batman.
Edward?
Who...
is it?
It's Dr. Meridian. Chase.
Do you remember me?
How could I forget?
Dr. Burton tells me...
you know who Batman is.
I can't tell you if you don't say "please."
Edward, please. Who is Batman?
I'm Batman.
[Laughing maniacally]
Your secret is safe.
He is definitely a wacko.
Wacko. Is that a technical term?
Listen...
I won't be needing this anymore.
Thank you for giving me a new dream.
Don't work too late.