[Suspenseful instrumental music]
[Rhythmic rock song]
Thank you. Hi.
I'd like to go to the Adelphi Hotel.
- Excuse me.
- I'm sorry. This is my cab.
I was here first!
Oh, God.
Taxi!
Let's go across. Come on.
We'll get one down the road. Hurry.
For God's sake, Harold,
can we please just get a taxi?
I'm trying to get a... Taxi!
We're going the wrong way!
Put that away. We'll look like tourists.
Hi, honey.
We'll never get a cab.
Let's cut over to Seventh.
- Seventh is that way.
- I know where we are!
Hey, mister. Give me a dollar.
- Come on.
- How about it? One dollar.
Are you deaf? You don't speak English?
Come on! Up here.
Hey, lady...
do the kid a favor. Don't scream.
Hey, all right.
American Express card.
"Don't leave home without it."
Get out of here.
Let's beat it, man. I don't like it up here.
What, are you scared of heights?
I don't know.
After what happened to Johnny Gobs...
Look, man, Johnny Gobs got ripped
and took a walk off a roof. No big loss.
No, man, that ain't what I heard at all.
I heard that the Bat got him.
The Bat? Give me a break, will you?
Five stories. Straight down.
There wasn't no blood in the body.
No shit. It was all over the pavement.
- I'm getting out of here, man.
- Shut up, man. Listen to me.
There ain't no Bat.
You shouldn't have turned the gun
on that kid.
You want your cut of this money or not?
Now shut up! Shut up.
Don't kill me! Don't kill me, man!
Don't kill me!
I'm not going to kill you.
I want you to do me a favor.
I want you to tell
all your friends about me.
What are you?
I'm Batman.
Across this nation...
the words "Gotham City"
are synonymous with crime.
Our streets are overrun,
our public officials are helpless.
As mayor, I promise to root out
the source of this corruption...
Boss Carl Grissom.
Now, our new District Attorney,
Harvey Dent...
will carry out that promise. Harvey?
Thank you, Mayor Borg. Thank you.
People of Gotham City...
I'm a man of few words.
But those words will count,
and so will my actions.
Police Commissioner Gordon
has informed me...
that he has targeted those businesses...
suspected of fronting for
the syndicate in this city.
Before the week is out...
we are going to knock down their doors...
and shed the light of the law
on that nest of vipers.
Together, we can make this city
safe for decent people.
Decent people shouldn't live here.
They'd be happier someplace else.
Pretty tough talk about Carl.
Don't worry about it.
If this clown could touch Grissom,
I'd have handed him his lungs by now.
If Grissom knew about us...
he might hand you something.
Don't flatter yourself, angel.
He's a tired old man.
He can't run this city without me.
And besides...
he doesn't know.
You don't worry about anything,
do you, Jack?
You look fine.
I didn't ask.
Yeah. Hanging on.
No. Let me guess.
Giant, menacing, supernatural form.
Kind of like a bat.
That's it. What are they seeing up there?
They're drinking Drano.
It's a little weird, Lieutenant.
Thanks for the tip.
Christ. Knox.
Hello, It. Eckhardt,
I hear we just had us another Bat attack.
That's what, eight sightings now
in just under a month?
I hear the Commissioner's
even opened a file. True?
Sorry, Knox.
These two slipped on a banana peel.
I'm telling you, man, a giant bat!
Don't be writing this stuff
in the newspaper, Knox.
It'll ruin your already useless reputation.
Lieutenant, every punk in this town
is scared stiff.
Do you know what they say?
They say he can't be killed.
They say he drinks blood.
- They say...
- I say you're full of shit, Knox.
You can quote me on that.
Is there a 6-foot bat in Gotham City?
And if so, is he on the police payroll?
And if so, what's he pulling down,
after taxes?
Brought you a little snack, Eckhardt.
- Why don't you broadcast it?
- Shut up and listen.
Harvey Dent has been sniffing around
one of our front companies.
That's my territory.
If there's a problem, I deal with it.
Your problems are our problems.
I answer to Grissom, not to psychos.
Why, Eckhardt,
you ought to think about the future.
You mean when you run the show?
You ain't got no future, Jack.
You're an A-1 nut-boy,
and Grissom knows it.
Better be sure.
See?
You can make a good decision
when you try.
Where you been spending your nights?
I don't care how deeply in debt
this festival is, I want a parade.
I want hot dogs, balloons,
the whole schmeer.
We're gonna celebrate this
200th anniversary proudly and publicly.
We may be celebrating
in bankruptcy court.
This festival's $250,000 in the red
and we haven't seen one balloon.
You fill this square with people,
and the businesses will come back here.
I think a lot of people might stay away,
Mayor. They're scared.
They won't be scared
when you get Grissom in that courthouse.
I promised that, remember?
Welcome, Count Dracula.
- Had any sightings of Bigfoot lately?
- Hey, Knox...
- they buried your story on the Batman.
- That's what they do to garbage.
This is Pulitzer Prize stuff, guys.
Hey, Knox. I got something for you.
Very funny. You should have a little bit
more gore under the fangs, though.
What a dick.
Hello, legs.
I'm reading your stuff.
Well, I'm reading yours.
Hi, I'm Vicki Vale.
Yeah, photographer. Vogue, Cosmo. Yeah.
Listen, if you want me to pose nude,
you're gonna need a long lens.
Actually, I was in the Corto Maltese.
A girl could get hurt doing this stuff.
So, what brings you here?
I'm here to see some of the wildlife
in Gotham City.
Wildlife? Like what?
Like... bats.
- Who sent you?
- Nobody, really.
I just loved your story, and...
I like bats.
Yeah?
My pictures, your words.
Pulitzer Prize material. Just think.
Okay, you're a visionary.
You're also the only one who believes me.
I need something tangible.
Gordon's got a file on this.
I can't even get him on the phone.
Bruce Wayne's benefit.
He'll be there, right?
Yeah. I don't seem to be
on the guest list. No.
Yes. Vale, will you marry me?
- No.
- Will you buy me lunch?
- Maybe.
- I eat light.
Say this...
son of a bitch...
makes a connection with us
and with Axis Chemicals.
What kind of damage are we looking at?
If he ties us in with Axis Chemicals,
we're dead and buried.
We should move immediately.
I say we break into the place...
trash the office...
and make off with the records
and say it was industrial espionage.
Jack.
Smart thinking. That's the way to go.
In fact...
I'd like you to handle
this operation personally.
Me?
Hello, sweetheart.
I wonder if you'd mind
waiting in the next room?
That's all, gentlemen. Thank you.
Carl...
can we get somebody else to do this?
The fumes in that place...
Jack.
It's an important job.
I need someone I can trust.
You are my number one guy.
Now...
don't forget...
your lucky deck.
My friend...
your luck is about to change.
Police Department.
Get me It. Eckhardt.
Can I help you, sir?
Thanks. Thank you very much.
That's very nice of you.
Here you go.
- Good evening, ma'am.
- A little crowded.
Excuse me.
Could you tell me
which of these guys is Bruce Wayne?
I'm not sure.
Thanks anyway.
Oh, certainly.
Eight. I can make that eight.
- I can make that eight.
- Place your bets, please.
Commissioner!
Mrs. Gordon, you look lovely.
How about that rumor that
Commissioner's got a file on the Batman?
That's not true, is it?
Knox, for the ninth time, there is no Bat.
If there were,
we would find and arrest him.
Would you confirm him?
Be straight with me, Commissioner.
- How you making out?
- Not good at all.
Mr. Dent, I love that tie.
We were discussing the pros and cons
of winged vigilantes. What's your stand?
Mr. Knox, we have enough problems
in this city...
without worrying about
ghosts and goblins.
Pardon me, but that's not a denial.
Excuse me, dear. I'll be back.
Isn't anybody going to go on record?
- Your Honor, great suit.
- No comment.
- Robert, what's up?
- Anonymous tip.
Napier's cleaning out Axis Chemicals.
Why wasn't I told about this?
Who's in charge?
- Eckhardt, sir.
- Oh, my God!
Come on, let's go.
KNOX: Commissioner Gordon?
Commissioner Gordon?
Wait, wait.
Living room, dining room, arsenal.
Look at this stuff.
Who is this guy?
He gives to all these humanitarian causes,
and then collects all this stuff.
He probably does it to get chicks.
They like him for his big charity balls.
Don't leave out his very large bankroll.
Now, remember, the more they've got,
the less they're worth.
Then this guy must be
the most worthless guy in America.
Check this out. He must have been
King of the Wicker People.
Where'd this come from?
I have no idea.
It's Japanese.
How do you know?
Because I bought it in Japan.
- Who are you?
- Sorry. Bruce Wayne.
Alexander Knox.
I read your work. I like it a lot.
Thanks. Can I have a grant?
- Vicki Vale.
- Hi.
- Bruce Wayne.
- Are you sure?
Yeah, this time.
I've seen your photographs
from Corto Maltese, haven't I?
Right.
You've got a wonderful eye.
Some people think she has two.
This is an amazing house.
I'd like to shoot it sometime if you...
We need to open a few more cases of
the champagne. Will that be all right?
Sure. Go ahead.
Open, what, six? Six?
- Six is good.
- Okay.
That's great, six, thanks.
Anyway, you gonna be staying
in Gotham for a while?
I'd love to. I'm intrigued by
Alex's giant bat stories.
Oh, right. The Batman.
That's a little bit light after the war
in Corto Maltese, isn't it?
- What do you do for a living?
- Well, I'm involved...
Sir, Commissioner Gordon
was compelled to leave.
Okay, thank you.
Very unexpectedly, sir.
Will you two excuse me?
I think perhaps this way, sir.
Alfred, they need some more wine
in the front room...
and someone named Mrs. Daley
needs a copy of the menu.
And give Knox a grant.
Nice talking with you, Wayne.
The rich...
You know why they're so odd?
Because they can afford to be.
Look at this mirror.
Maybe it should be Bruce Vain.
- Robert, what's up?
- Anonymous tip.
Napier's cleaning out Axis Chemicals.
If we could put our hands on him,
we'd have Grissom.
Why wasn't I told about this?
Who's in charge?
- Eckhardt, sir.
- Oh, my God!
Come on, let's go.
ECKHARDT: All right. Take a good look.
This is the guy.
All right, get a good look.
Shoot to kill. You know what I mean?
All right, let's move out.
We've been ratted out here, boys.
Watch it.
Freeze!
You, left. You take the right. Move it.
What the hell's going on?
What are you trying to do?
Blow the collar?
I'm in charge here, not Carl Grissom.
This is Commissioner Gordon.
I want him taken alive.
I repeat. Any man who opens fire
on Jack Napier will answer to me.
Let me down!
Oh, my God!
He went that way!
See if you can get up on the catwalk
on that side.
You take that side. Be careful.
Be very careful.
Jesus!
Let him go, or I'll do Gordon!
Nice outfit.
Come on, Jack, let's go!
Come on!
Come on, Jack.
Eckhardt!
Think about the future.
God damn it, we had him.
Hold it right there!
- Who is this guy?
- I don't know.
Until we find out, keep a lid on it.
Wait. If there's no Bat, then who dropped
this guy, Napier, into the acid?
Suicide? Wait, I want to get this on tape.
Hello?
He hung up. What have you got?
Here's the inner city,
there's Axis Chemicals...
and here's the sightings so far.
Maybe Batman has
some kind of flight pattern or something.
That's all I can think of.
This is very good. I'll tell you what...
tonight, first I'll take you to dinner,
then we'll walk the trail.
No can do. I got a date. With Bruce Wayne.
Wayne! Wayne! Oh, no!
The guy's a stiff. He's a rich stiff,
but you could do much better.
Thanks for being so concerned. Bye.
How's the soup?
Excuse me?
The soup. How is it?
It's great.
Could you pass the salt?
Sure.
Thanks.
Did you have a hard time
finding the house?
- No, it was no problem.
- Good.
Do you like eating in here?
Yeah.
You want to know the truth, I don't think
I've ever been in this room before.
Do you want to get out of here?
Yes.
There was young Master Bruce...
leading his gray pony
with me on its back...
like a sack of old potatoes, covered in mud
and nursing a sprained ankle.
That was the first and last time
I gave him a riding lesson.
I think I've embarrassed him
for long enough.
I'm off to bed.
Please, leave everything.
I'll tidy up in the morning.
- Good night, miss.
- Good night, Alfred.
- Good night, sir.
He's really wonderful. He loves you a lot.
Alfred's great.
I couldn't find my socks without him.
He sort of reminds me of my grandfather.
Were you close to him?
Yeah, I used to spend summers with him
and my grandmother.
They had a house on the lake.
Nothing like this, but...
it was fun.
- That sounds nice.
- Yeah.
What about your family?
Actually, Alfred is my family.
This house and all this stuff
really doesn't seem like you at all.
Some of it is very much me.
Some of it isn't.
That dining room is definitely not you.
The dining room isn't.
- Let's see how we did.
- Yeah.
Oh, my God!
Mirror.
Mirror!
[Sobbing]
You understand that the nerves
were completely severed.
[Laughing hysterically]
You see what I have to work with here.
[Echoing laughter]
There's an awful lot of stairs in this place.
My feet are killing me.
Okay.
I feel a little drunk.
And you're not anything.
One drink and I'm flying.
Why are you afraid of flying?
[Tense instrumental music]
That you, sugar bumps?
Who the hell are you?
It's me.
"Sugar bumps."
Jack.
Thank God, you're alive!
I heard you'd been...
Fried?
Is that what you heard?
You set me up over a woman.
A woman!
You must be insane.
Don't bother.
Your life won't be worth spit!
I've been dead once already.
It's very liberating.
You should think of it as therapy.
Jack, listen.
Maybe we can cut a deal.
Jack?
Jack is dead, my friend.
You can call me...
Joker.
And as you can see...
I'm a lot happier.
[Lively carnival music]
What a day.
[Metal squeaking]
Gotham City.
It always brings a smile to my face.
"Winged freak...
"terrorizes..."
Wait till they get a load of me.
Ooh.
I've got an idea.
How about lunch at my place?
I'll show you some photos.
Sure. Okay.
Wait a minute. No, I can't. I can't make it.
Okay, we'll do it later in the day.
Hold on a second.
I can't make it then, either.
I've got a very important meeting today.
What's wrong?
Nothing's wrong.
Really. I've just got to go out of town
on business for a few days.
- Okay, we'll do it when you get back.
- All right.
I got to go. I'm late.
Bye.
Jesus.
- It's nice to see you again, ma'am.
- Nice to see you, too.
I'll talk to you guys when you get back.
Back, Miss Vale?
We're going to be here for quite a while.
Well, bye.
JACK: Honey...
you'll never believe
what happened to me today.
JACK: So, gentlemen, that's how it is.
Until Grissom resurfaces...
I'm the acting president.
And I say, starting
with this anniversary festival...
we run this city into the ground.
Why don't we hear this from Grissom?
Yeah.
And what's with that stupid grin?
Life's been good to me.
What if we say "no"?
Well, Tony...
nobody wants a war.
If we can't do business, we'll just
shake hands and that'll be it.
Yeah?
Yeah.
[Mechanical whirring]
I got a live one here.
[Singing] There'll be a hot time
in the old town tonight
Antoine got a little hot under the collar.
You're crazy.
Haven't you ever heard of
the healing power of laughter?
- Now get out of here!
- You heard him. Let's go! Move it!
You think it over.
Let's go, come on. Get out of here.
Move it!
I want you to go down to the Globe,
follow that reporter Knox.
Take your camera.
See what he knows about this Batman.
And, Bob...
remember, you...
are my number one guy.
Yes, sir.
Your pals...
they're not bad people.
Maybe we...
ought to give them
a couple of days to think it over.
No?
Grease them now?
Okay.
You are a vicious bastard, Rotelli.
I'm glad you're dead.
I'm glad he's dead.
I need that.
I'm losing confidence in you.
I thought we were a team.
This wouldn't be a personal issue
for you, would it?
I just want you to do your job.
I am doing my job.
Me, too. I'm protecting my partner.
There's nothing in these files. No photos,
no histories, no nothing. Who is this guy?
Who cares?
Forget about Bruce Wayne.
I'm on to Batman.
They should be out here any second.
I can't wait to hear the explanation
for this one.
Here he comes, man.
What is this affidavit you filed?
Grissom gave you all his businesses?
Mr. Grissom asked me,
as a personal favor...
to take over the operation
of his businesses until he returns.
That's a pretty big favor.
You two must have been very close.
Very close.
Did you do a little time together
as children?
[Tense instrumental music]
Our accountants are looking into it.
We assure you, the affidavit is legitimate.
I smell fresh ink, guys.
You can prove all this?
What am I asking? Of course you can.
We have witnesses. Grissom's signature
is perfectly legitimate.
It is legitimate.
I saw it. I was there.
I saw it all.
He reached up with his dead hand...
and signed it in his own blood.
And he did it... with this pen.
Hello, Vinnie. It's your uncle Bingo.
Time to pay the check.
The pen...
is truly mightier than the sword.
Get down!
Doesn't this gang war dampen the city's
plans for the 200th anniversary festival?
The festival opens.
The police are gonna stop these gangsters.
Mr. Dent, what do you think
about the theory...
that the mysterious Batman
is a mob enforcer killing these men?
I don't have any comment.
Batman.
Can somebody tell me
what kind of a world we live in...
where a man dressed up as a bat...
gets all of my press?
This town needs an enema!
Alfred?
May I have a glass of water?
I'm relieved that you're home, sir.
Miss Vale telephoned.
She was rather concerned.
I feel that there's a certain weight
that lifts when she is here.
Alfred...
why don't you marry her?
That's not exactly what I had in mind, sir.
I can't go on with that right now.
If not now...
when?
I don't know.
I just found out Jack Napier's still alive.
He's running Grissom's men. I need
all the information the police have on him.
- Yes, sir.
- Thank you.
Alfred?
She is great, isn't she?
Yes, sir.
- City room, Knox.
- Hi.
I want you to check something out for me.
Find out what's so special about the alley
at Pearl and Phillips Streets.
- Pearl and Phillips?
- Yeah.
You got it.
Okay, bye.
Mr. Wayne.
[Chuckling softly]
[Whistling happily]
So much to do and so little time.
The photos.
Who's that loss?
It's Knox.
Bad tie. No style.
Stop the press!
- Who is that?
- That's Vicki Vale.
She's the photographer
who's working with Knox.
That girl has style.
¡Jesús marimba!
A lovely beast like that running around...
could put steam in a man's strides.
She's dating some guy named Wayne.
She's about to trade up.
It's hard to stay inside the lines.
I'm about...
to get a new girl, Bobby.
I'm of a mind to make some mooky.
- Phone book.
- Yes, sir.
So much to do...
and so little time.
Have you shipped
a million of those things?
Yes, sir.
Ship them all! We're going to
take them out a whole new door!
Ten seconds to transmission.
Five, four...
three, two, one.
Cue music.
Cue Becky.
Good evening.
The fashion world was stunned today...
by the sudden deaths of models
Candy Walker and Amanda Keeler.
Cause of death has been attributed to
a violent allergic reaction...
although authorities have not ruled out
the possibility of drug use.
Peter.
And plans continue
for the city's 200th birthday...
as Mayor Borg announced today
at the unveiling...
This just in.
Three mysterious deaths
at a beauty parlor...
[Becky laughing]
At a beauty parlor in Gotham
were discovered today.
What the hell's going on?
Becky, this is hardly the...
Kill the camera.
This is Rene on the news floor.
I need some paramedics up here now.
New and improved Joker products!
With a new secret ingredient.
Smylex!
What is this?
Now, let's go over...
to our blind taste test.
Love that Joker.
- Where's it coming from?
- I don't know.
He don't look happy.
He's been using brand X.
But with new and improved Joker brand...
I get a grin again...
and again.
That luscious tan...
those ruby lips...
and hair color so natural,
only your undertaker knows for sure.
I know what you're saying:
"Where can I get these fine, new items?"
That's the gag.
Chances are, you bought them already!
Love that Joker.
So, remember...
put on a happy face.
[Laughing hysterically]
- The information you requested.
- Thank you.
"Jack Napier, assault with
a deadly weapon, age 15.
"Results of psychological profile...
"violent mood swings, highly intelligent,
emotionally unstable.
"Aptitudes include science, chemistry,
and art."
Chemistry.
- Alfred, let's go shopping.
- Yes, sir.
Six new deaths, with no clues
as to the Joker's deadly weapon.
And what is the pattern?
Foods, alcohol,
or beauty and hygiene products?
Cologne, mouthwash,
underarm deodorant?
Or worse yet, there may be no pattern.
The search goes on
through Gotham's shopping nightmare.
We are going to have a festival if I have to
get a shotgun to get people there myself.
Do you hear the words coming out of
my mouth? The festival is on!
And you find out what this madman
is poisoning us with.
And fast. Do you read me?
We're working on it.
I need all the help I can get.
Bruce, hi. It's Vicki.
I'm sorry, but I'm gonna be 10 minutes late
to the museum.
I'll see you when I get there. Bye.
Sir, a message from Miss Vale.
She'll be 10 minutes late
in meeting you at the museum.
Okay, fine, thank you.
Wait a minute, Alfred.
I'm not meeting her today.
Jack, where are you going?
Daddy's going to make some art, darling.
Excuse me. Mr. Wayne's table?
Yes. He hasn't arrived yet.
We have a table waiting.
Miss Vale, this just arrived for you.
[Screaming]
Gentlemen!
Let's broaden our minds. Lawrence.
[Upbeat pop music playing]
Give him a shave.
Terence, brush.
The one-dollar bill.
Hold it!
I kind of like this one, Bob. Leave it.
You can take that off now, I think.
You're beautiful
in an old-fashioned kind of way.
But I'm sure we can make you more today.
Is that your portfolio?
I'm meeting someone
who wants to see my work.
[Romantic instrumental music playing]
Crap.
Now that's good work.
The skulls, the bodies.
You give it such a glow.
I don't know if it's art, but I like it.
Let me tell you
what I'm thinking about, sweetie.
I was in the bath one day...
when I realized
why I was destined for greatness.
You know how concerned people are
about appearances.
This is attractive, that is not.
That is all behind me.
I now do what other people only dream.
I make art. Until someone dies.
See?
I am the world's first
fully-functioning homicidal artist.
What do you want?
My face on the one-dollar bill.
You must be joking.
Do I look like I'm joking?
Well...
Listen.
We mustn't compare ourselves
to regular people. We're artists.
For instance, let me challenge you
with a little piece I did.
Bob. Alicia.
You will take pictures
and record my work.
You will join me in the avant-garde
of the new aesthetic.
Jack, you said I could watch you
improve the paintings.
I'm in trouble now.
Why is she wearing a mask?
She's just a sketch, really.
Alicia, sit down.
Show the lady why you wear the mask.
You see, Miss Vale, Alicia's been
made over in line with my new philosophy.
So now, like me...
she is a living work of art.
I'm no Picasso, but do you like it?
It's great.
So, what can I do for you?
A little song, a little dance.
Batman's head on a lance.
Tell me, what do you know about...
I don't know anything about Batman.
Really?
Well, how about a little "you and me"?
You're insane.
I thought I was a Pisces. Come on.
Let's make up. Have a little...
whiff of my posy.