Can I persuade you
to take a sandwich
with you, sir?
I'll get drive-through.
[Police officer]
Back up! Everyone, back up!
You're counting on
the Winged Avenger
to deliver you from evil,
aren't you, my friend?
Are you going
to kill me?
Maybe, maybe not.
You could say we're of
two minds on the subject.
Heh heh!
You a gambling man?
What say we flip for it?
One man is born a hero,
his brother a coward.
Babies starve,
politicians grow fat,
holy men are martyred,
and junkies grow legion.
Why?
Why? Why? Why? Why?
Luck!
Blind, stupid,
simple, doo-dah,
clueless luck!
[Chuckles]
[Moans]
The random toss.
The only true justice.
Let's see what justice
has in store for you.
[Chuckles]
Oh. It's like
the touch of God.
Wait. Wait. Wait.
Ho-ho.
Fortune smiles.
Another day
of wine and roses.
Or, in your case,
beer and pizza. Hah!
Out of here, guys!
B-but you said
you'd let me live!
True, true
and so you shall.
There's nothing
better than live bait
to trap a bat!
Get some sort
of communication.
What if we get
some kind of horn?
Hot entrance.
Two-Face?
Two guards dead,
a third hostage.
Didn't see this one
coming.
We should have though.
The Second Bank
of Gotham on the...
Second anniversary of
the day I captured him.
How could Two-Face resist?
I'm Chase Meridian.
I asked Dr Meridian
to consult on this case.
She's specializes in...
Abnormal psychology,
multiple personalities.
I read your work.
Insightful.
Naive,
but insightful.
I'm flattered.
Not every girl makes
a superhero's night table.
Can we reason with him?
He's holding innocent people
up there.
No. He'll slaughter them
without thinking twice.
A trauma powerful enough
to create an alternate
personality
leaves the victim...
Where rules
of right and wrong
no longer apply.
Exactly.
Like you.
I could write some paper
on a grown man
who dresses like
a flying rodent.
Bats aren't rodents,
Dr Meridian.
Really?
I didn't know that.
You areinteresting.
And call me Chase.
[Helicopter]
By the way,
do you have a first name,
or do I just call you Bats?
Let's start this party
with a bang!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Very punctual,
even for his own funeral!
Boys...
kill the bat!
Ha ha...hah!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Ha ha.
Hoo hoo hoo hoo!
[Ding dong]
Blast him!
Open sesame.
[Growls]
Aah!
[Muffled screaming]
Ow!
It's a trap!
[Groaning]
Oh, no!
Aah!
[Crowd screaming]
Attention, citizens
of fair Gotham!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
When we open that safe,
we'll have everything
we ever wanted--
enough cash to rain down
upon fair Gotham,
a glorious flood of chaos!
And, of course,
you, my boy...dead!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Oh, no!
It's boiling acid!
We're serving
the very same acid
that made us
the men we are today!
Oh! Oh!
No!
Hold on.
Yes!
Ha ha! Haul away!
Ha ha ha ha!
Yes! Haul away!
Give me your hand.
Don't let go!
Oh!
Aah!
Going to have
to borrow this.
Huh?
Hey! Hey!
That's my hearing aid!
Thanks.
[Whimpering]
Wow! My shoes
are melting! Oh!
Oh!
No more!
Ah! Aah!
No! Aah!
Help! Oh!
Hang on.
Hang on?
Aah!
[Coughs]
Get him down.
Get him down!
Take it easy
with him, fellas.
You'll be all right,
young man.
Just stay calm.
Easy does it.
Ha ha!
This'll fix him!
Hang on, Batty!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Face!
Ha ha!
No!
Let's see...
Yes!
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
Oh, happy day!
Ha ha ha ha!
Farewell forever to that
pointy-eared night rat!
Ha ha ha ha!
Face!
Hey, Face!
Hmm?
Gaa!
No!
You need help, Harvey.
Give it up.
Have the good taste to die!
Ha ha!
See ya!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Ha ha ha ha!
[Gasps]
[Woman newscaster]
Despite a valiant effort
last night by Batman,
Harvey Two-Face
is still at large
and extremely dangerous.
In other news,
billionaire Bruce Wayne
has extended his trendsetting
profit-sharing program
to the employees
of the highly successful
electronics division
of Wayne Enterprises.
[Ding]
Mr. Wayne.
Hello, Fred.
Your inspections
are a departmental
highlight.
Oh, my God, it's him!
I am a winner.
Ha ha ha ha ha.
Bioremediation.
Alternative fuel...
Mr. Wayne,
look at that time.
Perhaps we should get
to R & D as soon as possible.
Mister...
Oh...Bruce Wayne.
No, that's, uh, my name.
And you are?
Nygma.
Edward.
Edward Nygma.
You hired me personally.
Just like I tell everyone.
We've never actually met,
but your name was
on the hiring slip.
I have it.
I'm going to need
that hand back, Ed.
Oh, yes,
of course.
I'm sorry.
It's just that...
you're my idol.
Back to work, Edward.
And some people
have been trying
to keep us apart.
Back to work, Edward.
It's okay. So, Mr. Nygma,
what's on your mind?
Precisely.
What's on
all our minds?
Brain waves.
Hee!
The future
of Wayne Enterprises...
is brain waves.
I apologize, Mr. Wayne.
I terminated his project
this morning!
It's okay.
I have it!
Voila!
Huh?
My invention beams
any TV signal
directly into
the human brain.
By stimulating neurones--
manipulating brain waves,
if you will--
this device makes
the audience feel like
they're inside the show.
Why be brutalized
by an uncaring world?
Did you say manipulating
brain waves?
Well, I...
[Panting]
Yes.
Hmm.
But s-someone like you
would...
never need it.
Someone so...
intelligent,
witty...
and charming.
I just need
some additional funding
for human trials.
Let me show you,
please!
I want a full set
of technical schematics
on this, okay?
We'll be full partners
in this, Bruce.
Look at us.
Two of a kind!
Call my assistant Margaret.
She'll set something up.
Uh...
that's not going
to be good for me.
I need an answer now.
I think I deserve it.
I'm sorry, Ed.
Then the answer is no.
Tampering with
people's brain waves...
mind manipulation...
it just raises
too many questions.
Sorry.
Thanks, everybody.
Keep up the good work.
Factory looks great.
All right, everyone,
back to work.
We'll discuss this later!
You were supposed
to understand.
I'll make you
understand.
Lock.
Chair.
Alfred.
I saw the signal, sir.
All is ready.
[Ding]
Commissioner Gordon?
He's at home.
I sent the signal.
What's wrong?
Last night at the bank,
I noticed something
about Two-Face.
His coin.
It's his Achilles' heel.
It can be exploited.
I know.
You called me here
for this?
The Bat signal
is not a beeper.
I wish I could say that
my interest in you was...
purely professional.
Are you trying
to get under my cape?
A girl can't live
by psychoses alone.
It's the car, right?
Chicks love the car.
What is it about
the wrong kind of man?
In grade school, it was
guys with earrings.
College--motorcycles,
leather jackets.
Now...
ohh!
Black rubber.
Try a fireman.
Less to take off.
I don't mind the work.
Pity I can't see
behind the mask.
We all wear masks.
My life's an open book.
You read?
I don't blend in
at a family picnic.
We could give it
a try.
I'll bring the wine...
you bring
your scarred psyche.
Direct, aren't you?
You like strong women.
I've done my homework.
Or do I need skin-tight vinyl
and a whip?
I haven't had
that much luck
with women.
Maybe you
just haven't met
the right woman.
[Door opens]
I saw the signal.
What's going on?
Nothing.
[Chase clears throat]
False alarm.
Are you sure?
Women.
Aah!
[Chuckles]
Okay.
Now I've got it!
Hah!
Too many questions.
There's too many questions.
There's just too many--
[Whimpering]
I'll show you it works!
What the hell
is going on here?
I told you, this project
is terminated!
I'm calling security!
Caffeine will kill ya!
[Ping]
Rise and shine,
little guinea pig.
What are you doing,
Nygma? Untie me!
This won't hurt a bit.
At least,
I don't think it will.
What are you doing?
Nygma,
you touch that switch--
Which one--this?
[Electronic buzzing]
Ahh.
Ooh.
[Joyful cry]
Ohh.
Losing resolution.
More power.
Aah!
Uhh-uhh-uhh-uhh!
Whoo-hoo-hoo-hoo!
[Yelling gibberish]
[Imitating fish]
Ub-dub ub-dub. Ahh.
Ahh.
Yeeeee.
Edward Nygma,
come on down!
You're
the next contestant
on...
Brain Drain!
Um, gee, ooh, ah.
I'll take what's inside
thick skull number one!
What have we got
for him, Johnny?
Ooh, Stickley!
I'm having a breakthrough!
And a breakdown.
Maybe!
Nevertheless, I'm smarter.
I'm a genius.
No...several geniuses.
A gaggle,
a swarm,
a flock of freakin' Freuds!
Riddle me this, Fred!
What is everything
to someone
and nothing
to everyone else?
Your mind, baby!
And now mine pumps
with the power of yours!
♪ I'm suckin' up your IQ
♪ Vacuuming the cortex
♪ Feedin' off your brain
Fred!
[Sucking sounds]
Unh!
[Gasps]
Aah!
W-what a rush!
What the hell
just happened?
[Gasps]
A very surprising
side effect.
While you were
mesmerized by my 3-d TV,
I utilized
your neural energy
to grow smarter.
Bruce Wayne was right!
You demented, bizarre,
unethical toad!
It is brain manipulation!
I'm reporting you
to the FCC...
the human
experimentation board,
the A.M.I.,
and the police!
Hee hee!
You are going up
on charges...
to court, to jail,
to a mental institution
for the rest of your
twisted little life!
But first, Nygma,
you are fired!
Do you hear me?
Fired!
Oh...
I don't think so.
Unh!
Ah...
ah...
ah...ah...
ah!
Aah!
No!
Oh!
Hang on!
Ahh!
Oh.
Fred!
Babe!
You are fired...
or should I say...
terminated?
Aah!
Surf's up, big kahuna!
[Splash]
Ooh! Nice form,
but a little rough
on the landing.
He may have to settle
for the bronze.
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Questions, Mr. Wayne?
My work
raises too many questions?
Why hasn't anybody...
put you in your place?
[Woman newscaster]
Harvey Dent,
once Gotham's
district attorney,
was horribly scarred
by underworld kingpin
boss Moroni.
Although Batman
tried to save him,
Dent's left brain damage--
[Telephone rings]
Transformed him
into a violent criminal...
Wayne Manor.
Has vowed to destroy
the Dark Knight.
Harvey Two-Face...
Ah.
That was
Commissioner Gordon, sir.
There's been an accident
at Wayne Enterprises.
Horrible way to die.
Yes.
The video surveillance
cameras are down here.
We'll dredge the river,
but with that current,
I doubt we'll find the body.
Why?
Oh, why?
I just
can't believe it.
Two years working in
the same office.
He was like my father...
my brother...
or a cousin that visits
all the time!
Get a grip, Edward.
I found this
in my cubicle.
The handwriting
matches his exactly,
as does
sentence structure
and spelling.
I couldn't possibly
continue on here.
The memories...
oh!
This is last night's
security log.
[Sobbing]
There's Stickley.
[Glass breaking] Aah!
Pretty
cut-and-dried.
Yep.
Definitely suicide.
Thanks for your help, Bruce.
We'll be in touch.
Stickley a suicide.
It doesn't make sense.
Thanks.
I want full benefits
for his family.
Suicide's not covered
by our corporate
insurance policy.
I know. Full benefits.
Gossip Gerty's called
a record 32 times.
Who are you taking
to the charity circus?
I'll let you know.
What's this?
I don't know.
I didn't see anyone.
"If you look
at the numbers on my face,
you won't find 13 anyplace."
That's hideous.
What does it mean?
It's a riddle.
Numbers on my face, 13...
1 through 12.
The answer
is a clock.
Who would send you
a riddle?
That, Maggie,
is the riddle.
♪ Oo-oo-oo-oo-ooh
♪ You're sorta
stuck where you are ♪
♪ But in your dreams
♪ You can
buy expensive cars ♪
♪ Or live on Mars
and have it your way ♪
Ha ha ha ha!
♪ You hate your boss
at your job ♪
Guess what I did
today.
♪ But in your dreams
♪ You can
blow his head off ♪
♪ In your dreams,
show no mercy ♪
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Wayne...Manor.
Hmm!
See you soon.
Dr Meridian, please.
Thank you.
[Punching]
Uhh...
[Punch]
Uhh. Uhh.
Uhh. Uhh. Uhh!
Uhh!
[Punch]
I, uh...
I...guess I'm early.
I have
an appointment.
I'm Bruce Wayne.
Good.
You can afford
to buy me a new door.
I--I'm sorry.
I...
You, uh, sounded
like you were in...
in, uh...
uh...
you know, trouble.
I prefer healthy
expressions of violence,
as opposed to
breaking and entering.
So...
how can I help you,
Mr. Wayne?
Oh. Uh, someone's been
sending me love letters.
I--one in my office
and one last night
at my home.
I--Commissioner Gordon
thought
you might give me
your expert opinion.
Clock.
"Tear one off
and scratch my head.
What once was red
is black instead."
A match.
My opinion is
this letter writer's
a total wacko.
Wacko.
That a technical term?
Patient may suffer from
obsessional syndrome
with potential
homicidal tendencies.
Does that work
better for you?
So what you're saying is
this guy's a total wacko.
Exactly.
He's
obsessed with you.
His only escape
may be to purge
the fixation.
To kill me.
I think you
understand obsession
better
than you let on.
You have a thing
for bats?
Oh, that's a Rorschach,
Mr. Wayne, an ink blot.
People
see what they want.
I think
the question would be
do you have a thing
for bats?
Still playing with dolls,
doctor?
She's a Malaysian
dream warden.
Some cultures
believe she protects
you from bad dreams.
It's silly to you,
I'm sure.
You look so sad.
Do you need one?
Me? No. Why would I?
You're not exactly
what you seem,
are you, Bruce Wayne?
What is it
you really
came here for?
Yikes. Time's up.
That's usually my line.
Listen, I'd love
to stay here chatting--
Hmm. Would you?
I'm not so sure.
I've got to get you
out of those clothes.
Excuse me?
And into a black dress.
Tell me, doctor,
do you like the circus?
Ladies and gentlemen,
boys and girls
of all ages,
welcome to the Greatest
Show on Earth!
Bruce, who is this
beautiful young woman
you're with?
Dr Chase Meridian.
A doctor?
What kind of doctor?
For Gotham
Children's Hospital,
let's thank our largest
single donor--
Bruce Wayne!
Ladies and gentlemen--
70 feet above the ground,
performing feats of
unimaginable aerial skill,
the flying Graysons!
Listen, I'm going
rock climbing
this weekend.
Would you
like to join me?
Oh, um...
I'd like to.
I--I--I love climbing.
I mean,
I really love it.
But?
I've met someone.
That's fast work.
You just moved here.
Well, you could say
he just kind of
dropped out of the sky,
and...bang.
I think he felt it,
too.
Sure did.
What?
Well, who wouldn't?
And now...
Richard, the youngest
flying Grayson,
will perform the
awe-inspiring death drop.
[Audience gasps]
Without the safety
of a net.
Okay. Let's go.
You'll
be all right?
[Cheers and applause]
Ladies and gentlemen!
The new management
of The Circus International
invites you to forget
this good clean wholesome
all-American fun
and join us
in a celebration
of absolute chaos
and true justice!
Bring it on now!
Ha ha ha ha!
Tonight, a new act for
your personal amazement.
We call it massacre
under the big top.
Ha ha ha!
If we may
direct your attention
to the middle
of the center ring.
Inside this
harmless-looking orb
are 2--that's 2--
hundred sticks of TNT,
and in our innocent hand,
a radio detonator.
What the hell
do you want?
Want, Mr. Mayor?
One simple thing--Batman,
bruised, broken, bleeding.
In a word--
dead!
Ah ha ha ha ha ha
ha ha ha ha ha!
Batman?
Who do we have
before us?
Gotham's finest--
well-to-do, influential.
Surely one of you knows
who Batman is.
Hell, odds are one of you
pasty-faced twits is Batman!
You have...two minutes!
Harvey!
[Amid screaming]
I'm Batman!
Bruce!
Ha ha! Ha ha ha!
We could stop him.
Go out on the rigging.
Be careful,
boys.
Don't worry, mom.
Go to work,
boys! Ha ha!
Ha!
Our kind of day!
Reach for it! Stop it!
Oh, my God.
Aah!
Ha ha!
[Gasp]
Bruce, good of you
to take him in.
He hasn't anyone now.
We've had him
filling out papers
all day.
He hasn't slept.
He hasn't even eaten.
Welcome, Master Grayson.
I'm Alfred.
How you doing, Al?
There's a room prepared
for you upstairs.
Perhaps you'd like
something to eat first.
Okay. I'm out of here.
Excuse me?
Telling that cop
I'd stay here
saved me a truckload
of social service interviews
and charities,
so, uh, no offence,
but no, thanks. See you.
Take it easy, Al.
Where will you go?
The circus
must be halfway to
Metropolis by now.
Get a fix on Two-Face,
then I'll kill him.
Killing Two-Face won't
take the pain away.
It'll make it worse.
Look, spare me the sermon,
all right, Bruce?
I don't need your advice
or your charity.
Nice bike.
Hang out at a lot
of biker bars?
You're almost on empty.
Why don't you fill it up
in the garage?
There's
not a gas station
around for miles.
Pump's over here.
Is this a garage
or a car museum,
Bruce?
Wow.
It's a 1917 Harley.
Yep.
Indian classic.
Fully restored.
This is a Vincent
Black Knight.
They only made like
a hundred of these.
101, actually.
She's my favorite.
You've got
two of them.
Yeah. That one
doesn't run, though.
Throttle
sticks on this one.
Alfred's actually
a very good mechanic,
but some of these
need a lot of work.
Someone
were to fix them up,
they could
keep one as a fee.
Anyway, have a nice trip.
I'm sure you'll
land on your feet.
Is the young master
leaving?
Pity.
I'll just toss this
away, then.
Perhaps
the dogs are hungry.
Hey, Al, wait up.
[Gunshot]
"And where there is hatred,
I bring love..."
"And where there is misery,
I will bring hope.
And where
there are shackles..."
"Where there is sadness,
I will bring joy."
Master Bruce?
Master Bruce.
Just like my parents.
It's happening again.
The monster comes
out of the night.
A scream, two shots.
I killed them.
What did you say?
He killed them.
Two-Face.
He slaughtered
that boy's parents.
No. No, you said "I."
"I killed them."
[Alarm sounds]
Take care
of the kid.
Certainly, sir.
Can I help you settle in,
Master Grayson?
No.
Thanks. I won't
be staying long.
Oh.
Is this a robin?
My brother's wire
broke once.
I, uh, swung out
and grabbed him.
My father said
I was his hero.
I flew in
like a robin.
Some hero
I turned out to be.
Ah, but your father
was right.
You are a hero,
I can tell.
Throw this away,
will you, Alfred?
I won't be
needing it anymore.
I think I'll just
put it in here.
Broken wings
mend in time.
One day, Robin
will fly again.
I promise.
Ha ha ha!
Ha ha!
Ah ha ha!
Wait!
Aah!
[Loud sob]
We'll drive, thank you.
Heh heh heh!
Ha ha!
Y-ah!
Aah!
Oh...aah!
The Puzzler.
The Gamester.
Okay.
Captain Kill.
Question Mark Man.
No, no.
Ah ha ha ha ha!
Oh...
thank you.
Thank you so much.
[Sirens]
The Bat's stubborn refusal
to expire...
is driving us insane!
Don't worry, baby.
Ha ha ha!
You'll kill him
soon.
Besides...
I made your
favorite tonight--
sparkling champagne...
Oh.
And yummy
poached salmon
with little itty-bitty
quail eggs and a...
creamy...
dreamy...
Mmm!
lemon soufflé.
No,
Imade your
favorite--
a charred heart
of black boar,
a side of raw
donkey meat,
and a
sterno-and-grain
alcohol.
Straight up,
baby! Ha ha ha
ha ha ha!
Perfect. Ha ha.
Ladies, you spoil us.
We're of two minds
about what to eat first.
[Ding]
What?
I hope you made
extra.
Who the hell
are you?
Just a friend.
But you can call me...
"The Riddler."
I'll call you dead
is more like it!
How did you find us
here? Talk!
If I talked,
what would keep you
from slaying me,
o segregated one?
By the way,
that's never going
to heal if you
don't stop picking.
Oh. Let's see
if you bleed green.
Harvey...
Ha ha!
I don't think
it's me
you want to kill.
That's just too easy
for someone
as powerful as you
and...
you.
But Batman...
ohh!
There's a challenge.
Kill the Bat! Sounds
like a good idea.
But have you
thought it through?
A few bullets,
a quick splash of blood,
and then what?
Wet hands and...
post homicidal
depression.
[Whimper]
Why not humiliate
him first?
Expose his frailties.
And then when
he's at his weakest...
crush him!
Ha...ha.
I see that...
sparkle
in your left eye.
Heh!
I can help you
get Batman.
That is,
if you'll...
spare my life for
just a few moments.
Eh...
heh.
Thank you.
I simply love what
you've done with this place.
Heavy metalmeets
House and Garden.
Ha ha ha!
Beautiful!
It's so dark
and gothic and...
disgustingly
decadent...
[Hiss]
Yet so bright
and chipper and...
conservative.
[Whistles]
It's so...
you!
And yet so... ♪ You!
Heh heh!
Very few people are both
a summer and a winter,
but...
you pull it off
nicely.
Ha!
[Gunshot]
What's the point,
big boy?
Has anybody
ever told you
you have a serious
impulse control problem?
This...
is the point.
[Buzzing]
This is how
I found you.
Let me demonstrate.
This is your brain
on the box.
Thisis mybrain
Does anybody else feel
like a fried egg?
I'll have a bit more,
thank you.
Oh, there's more, but
only the first one's free.
Here's the bargain.
You will help me
steal production capital
so I can put a box
on every TV in town
and become Gotham's
cleverest carbon-based
life form!
And in return...
Is everybody
paying attention?
I will help you solve
the greatest riddle
of all...
the mother
of all riddles.
Who is...
Batman?
Mmm.
You have broken
into our hideout.
You have violated
the sanctity
of our lair.
For this we should
crush your bones
into powder.
However, you pose
a most interesting
proposition.
Therefore,
heads, we accept,
and tails, we blow
your damn head off.
[Panicky chatter]
Ha ha! Ah, ha ha!
Yeah!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Ah! Here's a good one.
No, no, no!
There...
is a good one.
Leave that, Master Dick.
I'll attend to it.
I'm not used to being
waited on, Al.
Oh! Don't shoot me,
please!
Don't you eyeball me!
Give me that!
All the money!
Right now!
Aah!
Hey, Two-Face,
show me how
to punch a guy.
It's dirt simple,
my boy.
Ball up the fist,
reach way back,
and assert yourself.
Ooh!
That looks like fun.
Let me try!
Ball up the fist.
Reach way back.
Assert yourself.
Ow!
100,220...
100 and...
I lost count!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
And in Gotham last night,
another robbery perpetrated
by the city's
green-suited menace,
resulting in
millions in diamonds stolen
with no sign of Batman.
Teamed with Two-Face,
this new criminal's
pattern of marking
his crimes with puzzles
has Gothamites calling him
"The Riddler."
Apparently,
you and Batman have
a common enemy.
That was with
the morning mail.
"The eight of us
go forth not back
to protect our king
from a foe's attack."
Chess pawns.
Clock.
Matches. All physical objects,
manmade.
Small in size,
light in weight.
What's the connection?
With all
due respect, sir,
I think that's
why they call him
"The Riddler."
Unh.
May I help you,
Master Grayson?
This is the only
locked door around here.
What do you got
back there?
Master Wayne's dead wives.
The silver closet.
On your way.
Now you...
can be part
of the action!
Nygma tech brings the toy
of 3-D entertainment
into your living room!
Ladies and gentlemen,
let me tell you...
my vision.
The box...
in every home
in America...
and one day,
the world!
In local news,
Edward Nygma's 3-D box
has become
the rage of Gotham.
Rioting occurred last night
at electronic stores
which were sold out.
There's hardly a home
without the Nygma tech box.
Critics have claimed
the box turns Gothamites
into zombies.
But Edward Nygma
just shrugs,
"That's what they said
when TV was invented."
[Machine hums]
Huh huh huh huh huh!
Master Dick?
Up here, Al.
Just checking, young sir.
Now!
Whoa! Whoa!
Aah!
Unh!
Intruder alert!
Oh, I have something
for you.
It's on the table.
I hope you like it.
Call it
clinical intuition.
I thought your dreams
might need changing.
My parents were murdered
in front of me
when I was just a kid.
I don't...
remember a lot
of what happened,
but...
what I do
comes to me
in my dreams.
Flashes.
There's a new element
now, though,
I haven't seen before.
It's a red leather book.
Something else.
My dreams are coming to me
when I'm awake now.
Bruce, you're describing
repressed memories...
Images
of a forgotten pain
that's trying
to surface.
[Teapot whistles]
Damn. Wait.
I'll be right back.
[Whistling stops]
Is it possible
there's an aspect
of your parents' death
you haven't faced?
I mean,
you were so young
when it happened.
Maybe I ought to
leave you two alone.
This goes way beyond
taking your work home,
doesn't it, doctor?
All right.
I think
he's fascinating.
Clinically.
Why does a man
do this?
It's as if he's cursed
to pay some great penance.
Now, what crime
could he have committed
to deserve a life
of nightly torture?
It's more than just...
professional interest,
isn't it, Chase?
Bruce, are you jealous?
No. I--
I can't be jealous
of Batman.
I want to be close,
but you won't
let me near.
What are you
protecting me from?
Do you want
to know me?
You want to know
who I am?
I guess...
We're all two people.
One in daylight,
and the one we keep
in shadow.
Rage,
violence...
passion.
[Pager blips]
Excuse me.
Kind of busy.
Sorry to bother you, sir.
I have some rather
distressing news
about Master Dick.
Is he all right?
I'm afraid Master Dick
has, uh...gone travelling.
[Bruce]
He ran away?
Actually,
he took the car.
He boosted the Jag?
Not the Jaguar.
The othercar.
The Bentley?
No, sir.
The othercar.
["smash it up"
by The Offspring playing]
Wow!
Hoo hoo!
[Taunting shouts]
Whoo!
Aah, ha ha!
[Shouting]
[Chicano accent]
Goin' for a little ride
in my love machine, baby.
Whoo!
Yii! Yii!
Chill, dudes.
It's Batman.
Whoo!
Open up, Batman!
Batman!
Now, wait a minute!
That's not Batman.
What are you
talking about?
That's Batboy.
Ha ha!
It ain't
the Bat.
Aahhh!
Aah!
Whoo!
Eee!
Woo woo!
Hey!
Hey, let her go!
Hey, hey!
Whoo!
Boo!
Yii yii yii!
Wahh!
Whoo!
Who the hell are you?
I'm Batman.
Ha ha!
Ha ha!Ha ha!
Hey,
so I forgot my suit,
all right?
[Shouting]
Come on, run!
Wait. Doesn't Batman
ever kiss the girl?
Let's go.
[Girl]
Thanks. You
saved my life.
I could definitely get
into this superhero gig.
[Whistles]
[Shouting]
Come on!
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
[Shouting]
Aaaahhhh!
Batman!
Bastard!
It should've been you!
It's your fault!
If you'd told Two-Face
when you were
at the circus,
they'd still be alive!
[Gasping]
If Bruce Wayne
could've given his life
for your family,
he would have.
All I can think about
every second of the day
is getting Two-Face.
He took my whole life.
And when I was
out there tonight,
I imagined it was him
I was fighting,
even when I was
fighting you.
And all the pain
went away.
Do you understand?
Yes, I do.
Good...'cause you
got to help me find him.
And when we do...
I'm the one
who kills him.
So you're willing
to take a life.
Long as it's Two-Face.
Then it will happen
this way.
You make the kill.
But your pain doesn't
die with Harvey.
It grows.
So you run out
into the night to find
another face...
and another,
and another...
until one terrible
morning, you wake up
and realize
that revenge has become
your whole life.
And you won't know why.
You can't understand.
Your family wasn't killed
by a maniac.
Yes, they were.
We're the same.
Well, if we're the same,
Bruce, help me.
All right? Train me.
Let me be your partner.
No.
I can't.
You still have
a choice.
Look, Bruce,
I'm part of this
whether you like it
or not.
Here he comes now!
The whole crowd,
over this way, please.
[Female newscaster]
And tonight, all
of Gotham society
has turned out
for Edward Nygma's
gala unveiling
of his new, improved box.
Thanks, Al.
My pleasure, sir.
They'll be dining and dancing
the night away
on the glamorous roof
of the Ritz Gotham.
Mr. Nygma!
What's it like
to have your face
on the cover
of every magazine?
Oh! Ha!
Edward,
how does it feel
to be the city's
newest, most
eligible bachelor?
Gotham must know!
Oh! There's Bruce Wayne!
Brucie!
Over here!Bruce Wayne!
Oh, Eddie,
he is too cute.
How come you
don't look so good
in that suit?
Shut up.
You're here to work.
How's my mole?Fine.
Mr. Wayne.
What about rumors
of a Nygma Tech take-over
of Wayne Enterprises?
Nygma Tech stock
is outselling Wayne
Enterprises 2 to 1.
Are you yesterday's
news, Bruce?
Yes, yes, yes!
Bruce, old man.
The press
were just wondering
what it feels like
to be outsold, outclassed,
outcoifed, and...
generally outdone
in every way.
Hello, Edward.
Congratulations.
Great party.
Nice suit.
Oh. Wit. Good.
And you are?
Chase.
And what a grand pursuit
you must be.
I'm Bruce Wayne, Miss...
Oh. Ha ha.
You can call me
anything you want.
Ladies and gentlemen...
the future!
My new, improved box
offers fully interactive
holographic
fantasies.
[Fanfare]
[Woman]
Oh!
[Applause]
Edward, you're dashing
and a genius.
How do you create
these images, Hon?
That, my dear, is
my little secret.
Oh!
Oh!Oh!
[Applause]
Fully interactive
holographs.
Only a high frequency
carrier wave
beamed directly
into the brain
could create
such images.
Yeah, and you wish
you thought of it.
Don't be
a sore loser.
Step inside.
Give it a try.
Edward...
if you can introduce
images into the mind,
what prevents you
from extracting images
out of the mind?
Ohhh...
too timid to try
my machine?
Just say so.
Shall we dance?
Naughty, naughty.
Looking
for something?
I was just--
just wondering
how you turn it off.
Ah.
Clever.
Thanks.
My pleasure.
Good evening, Mr. Wayne.
Relax.
Tell me...
your dreams.
your fantasies.
Tell me your secrets.
Tell me...
your deepest...
darkest...
fears.
No! No! No! No!
[Crowd shouting]
Ha ha!
[Blows into gun]
[Two-Face]
Relax, folks!
It's only an old-fashioned,
low-tech stickup!
We're interested
in the basics--
cash, jewellery,
cellular telephones.
Hand them over
nice and quietly,
and no one
will be hurt!
Emergency, Alfred.
Yes, sir.
Be calm, everybody!
Just be calm!
Excuse me.
[Screaming
and shouting]
You're ruining
my big party!
Are you insane?
We're sick of waiting
for you to deliver
the Batman, dear boy.
Patience,
o bifurcated one.
Patience, hell!
We want him dead!
And nothing brings
out the Batman
like a little
murder and mayhem, baby.
At least you could've
let me in on the caper.
We could've
organized this,
planned it...
presold
the movie rights.
[Glass breaking]
Batman! Yeah!
Your entrance was good.
His was better.
The difference?
Showmanship.
Emergency, Alfred.
Oh, sir. I could
be fired for this, sir.
Perhaps they'll have me
back at Buckingham Palace.
Hee hee hee hee.
Hee hee hee--aah!
All right, boys,
phase two!
My place...midnight.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Ha ha!
Hee hee ha!
Hee ha!
Whoo!
Ha ha!
Ha ha ha ha ha.
Ha ha ha ha! Whoo!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Nothing like a bad
case of gas. Ha ha!
Ah ha ha ha ha
ha ha ha!
Ha ha ha--
Why can't you just die!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Ha ha ha ha!
Hi.
What the hell
were you doing?
You got a real
gratitude problem.
I need a name--
Batboy, Nightwing.
What do you think?
What's a good
sidekick name?
How about "Dick Grayson,
college student?"
Screw you!
I just saved your life.
You owe me.
You're totally
out of control.
You're looking
at your new partner.
No!
Whenever
you go out at night,
I'll be watching.
Wherever Batman goes,
I'll be right
beside him.
How will you stop me?
I can stop you.
Ahem.
Al,
hang this next
to the Batsuit...
where it belongs.
And you're
encouraging him.
Young men with a mind
for revenge need
little encouragement.
They need guidance.
You, above all, should
know the consequences
of the life you choose.
Even Chase calls
being Batman a curse.
Perhaps the lady is just
what the doctor ordered.
She seems
lovely and wise.
I've never been
in love before, Alfred.
Go to her.
Tell her how you feel.
She wants Batman,
not Bruce Wayne.
Let the lady
decide, hmm?
I'm sorry. I...
I can't
believe this. I...
I've imagined this moment
since I first saw you.
Your...your eyes.
Your lips.
Your body.
And now I
have you, and...
I'm wishing you
were somebody else.
Oh!
I guess a girl has
to grow up sometime.
I've met someone.
He's...
Well, he's--
he's not you.
I hope you
can understand.
I understand.
Well...
Aah!
[Sobbing]
That's just what I said.
Then I taught my doggy
a new trick.
How to map
the human mind.
Would you like to see
what Bruce Wayne
has in his head? Hmm?
Whooooo!
Riddle me this.
What kind of a man
has bats on the brain?
Ooh ooh ooh!
Ha ha ha!
Go ahead,
you can say it.
You're a genius.
Oh, stop!
So, from this day on,
Batman is no more.
You can't just quit.
There's monsters out there.
Batman has to
protect the innocent.
I've dedicated my life
to helping strangers
I've never met,
faces I've never seen.
Well, the innocent
aren't faceless anymore.
You can't tell me
what I'm going to do
with the rest of my life.
My dad told me that
every man goes his own way.
Well, my way
goes to Two-Face.
You got to help me.
And if you
do find Harvey
and then you kill him,
what next?
[Sighs]
Exactly.
Then you'd be alone,
like me.
No, you've
got to let this go.
Listen to me, Dick,
I'm your friend.
I don't need a friend.
I need a partner.
Two-Face
has got to pay.
Please.
Chase is coming over
for dinner.
I'm going
to tell her...
everything.
Come on upstairs.
We'll talk.
Good evening,
Dr Meridian.
Good evening, Alfred.
Happy Halloween.
Happy Halloween
to you.
Well, I asked you
here tonight
because there's something
I wanted to tell you.
I wanted to tell you
something, too.
Um...
What I wanted--
Go ahead.
You go first.
All right, okay., um...
trick or treat!
All my life,
I have been...
I've been attracted to
a certain kind of man.
Uh, the wrong
kind of man.
And, I mean, look
what I do for a living,
right?
And since--
since I met you, I...
Oh, God.
Why am I so nervous?
Oh!
And don't eat
too much tonight,
or you'll be sick
in your beds.
Happy Halloween!
Bruce, what's wrong?
It's happening again.
Flashes--my...
parents' death.
Your memories are
trying to break through.
Don't fight them.
I want to
tell you something,
something I've
never told anyone.
It's all right.
I'm here.
And where
there is wrong,
I may bring
the spirit
of forgiveness.
The night of
my parents' wake,
the priest's words
gave no comfort.
Of course...
there on
my father's desk,
the red book.
His journal.
He'd written in it
every day of my life.
But now he'd never
write in it again.
At that moment I knew
my life would
never be the same.
I raced out
into the storm,
trying to
outrun the rage,
the pain.
And then I fell.
I fell forever.
The cave was monstrous.
It must have been
there for centuries.
And there,
deep in the shadows...
I saw...
it was coming toward me.
I was scared at first,
but only at first.
The figure in the dark
was my destiny.
It would change
my life forever.
I would use its image
to strike terror
into the hearts of
those who did evil.
I would ensure
what happened to me
would never happen
to anyone else again.
I would have my revenge.
Bruce, what are you
trying to tell me?
Chase, I--I'm...
Trick or treat!
Trick.
Ha ha ha.
Remember the plan--
seize and capture.
No killing.
That goes
double for you.
Ha ha ha ha.
If I was a superhero,
where would I hide?
Spank me.
Intruder alert!
Shut up!
Now that's impressive!
You know,
it's always risky
introducing a tamed
animal into the wild.
Hee hee hee hee hee.
They may have trouble
adapting to their new
environment.
Hmm.
Hee hee hee hee hee
hee hee hee.
Yeah!
Somebody
tell the fat lady
she's on in five.
Joygasm!
Aah!
Get the girl!
No!
Don't kill him.
If you kill him...
he won't learn nothin'.
Bruce!
Master Bruce?
How are you,
young man?
You haven't called me
that for a long time.
Old habits
die hard.
Are you
all right?
Where's Chase?
I'm afraid they've
taken Dr Meridian.
Master Dick
has run away,
the cave has
been destroyed,
and there's
another riddle.
Uhh!
I'm coming,
my sweet.
Hah!
Like the jacket?
It keeps me safe
when I'm jogging
at night.
Ha ha ha.
Batman will
come for me.
[English accent]
Batman?
Batman, you say?
Coming for you?
Hoo hoo hoo hoo hoo!
Rrrr! Rrrr!
I'm...
counting on it!
What is that?
Where's that coming from?
There!
Who the hell's
doing that?
The Riddler.
In a-e-i-o-u.
Vowels.
Not entirely
unclever, sir,
but what do a clock,
a match,
chess pawns, and vowels
have in common?
What do
these riddles mean?
Every riddle has a
number in the question,
and they arrived
in this order--
13, 1, 8, and 5.
What do they mean?
Perhaps letters
of the alphabet.
Of course,
13 is "M."
1 would be "A,"
8 would be "H,"
5 would be "E."
M-a-h-e.
Perhaps 1 and 8
are 18.
18 is "R."
M-r-e.
How about...
"Mr. E."?
Mystery.
An another name
for mystery?
Enigma.
Mr. E. Nygma.
Edward Nygma.
Stickley's suicide
was obviously
a computer-generated forgery.
You really
are quite bright,
despite what people say.
Were all the Batsuits
destroyed, Alfred?
All except the prototype
with the sonar modifications
you invented.
But you haven't
tested it yet.
Tonight's
a good night.
What do you suggest,
Alfred, by sea...
or by air?
Why not both?
Who's your tailor?
I took
the liberty, sir.
"R"?
What's that stand for?
Robin.
Riddler and Two-Face
can make a pretty lethal
combination.
I figured you
could use a hand.
Two against two
are better odds.
I can't promise
I won't kill Harvey.
A man's got
to go his own way.
A friend taught me that.
Not just a friend...
A partner.
Ohh! Whoo-hoo!
Whoa!
He's not coming.
Shut it down.
Wait a minute!
Hey!
Go!
Go! Go!
Hee hee hee.
Ha ha ha ha.
A-14.
Hit!Sweet.
B-12.
Hit! And my favorite
vitamin, I might add.
Ha ha ha.
Oh. Ha ha ha.
Oh, that
sinking feeling.
I like this game.
C-9.
Aah!
You sunk my battleship!Who, me?
Ha ha ha ha ha!
This is your captain speaking.
Please return to your seats.
We will be experiencing
turbulence.
Ha ha ha ha!
Aah!
I got him!
I hope they can find
the little black box.
Now...
the real game begins.
Holy rusted metal,
Batman!
Huh?
The ground--
it's all metal.
It's full
of holes, you know?
Holy.
Oh.
Robin, wait!
The whole island's
moving.
Ha ha!
Looking for us?
That was
for my mother!
My father!
My brother!
And this is
for me!
Aah!
Finally,
justice is served.
Let us die.
You're a man
after our own heart, son.
I'll see you in hell.
I'd rather see you
in jail.
Oh, good boy.
Good boy.
The Bat has taught him
very well.
Noble.
Stupid, but noble.
Riddle me this,
riddle me that.
Who's afraid
of the big black bat?
No more tricks,
Edward.
Very well, then.
Let's get real.
Release Chase.
This is between
you and me.
And me.
And me!
Ha ha ha ha!
You've been sucking
Gotham's brain waves,
and now you've
devised a way
to read men's minds.
Ha ha ha!
You betcha!
Soon my little box
will be
on countless TVs
around the world,
feeding me
credit card numbers,
bank codes,
sexual fantasies,
and little
white lies.
Into my head
they'll go.
Victory
is inevitable.
For if knowledge
is power,
then a god...
am...
[Deep voice]
I.
[Inhaling]
Was that over the top?
I can never tell.
Ha ha ha ha!
By the way,
I've seen your mind.
Freak!
Yours is the greatest
riddle of all.
Can Bruce Wayne and Batman
ever truly co-exist?
We'll find out today!
But first...
let's meet our contestants.
Behind curtain
number one...
the absolutely fabulous
Dr Chase Meridian.
She enjoys hiking,
getting her nails done,
and foolishly hopes
to be the love of Bruce's life.
Ha ha!
Ha!
And behind curtain
number two...
Fatman's
one-and-only partner.
This acrobat-turned-orphan
likes Saturday
morning cartoons
and dreams
of one day
being bare naked
with a girl.
Ha!
Hee hee!
And below
these contestants,
my personal favorite--
a watery grave!
Just one little touch
and five seconds later,
these two day-players
are gull feed
on the rocks below.
Ha!
Not enough time
to save them both.
Ooh!
Which one will it be,
Batman,
Bruce's love,
or the Dark Knight's
junior partner?
[Imitates clock ticking]
There is no way for me
to save them or myself.
This is all
one giant death trap.
Judges?
[Imitates buzzer]
I'm sorry. Your answer
must be in the form
of a question.
Wait.
I have a riddle
for you.
For me?
Really?
Ha ha ha!
Tell me.
I see without seeing.
To me, darkness
is as clear as daylight.
What am I?
Please!
You're as blind
as a bat!
Exactly.
Aah!
Nooooo!
Nooo!
Eeeeeaaaaah!
Bummer.
[Muffled scream]
Uh!
Thanks.
Ha ha ha ha!
All those heroics
for nothing.
No more riddles,
nor curtains one and two,
just plain curtains.
Ha ha ha ha!
Aren't you forgetting
something, Harvey?
Your coin.
You're always of two minds
about everything.
Yes, of course.
You're right, Bruce.
Emotion's
always the enemy
of true justice.
Thank you.
You've always been
a good friend.
Aah!
Why?
Why can't I kill you?
Ohh.
Too many questions.
Poor Edward.
I had to save them
both.
You see, I'm both
Bruce Wayne
and Batman,
not because
I have to be.
Now, because
I choose to be.
Aah!
Thank you
for responding
to my request
for a consultation,
Dr Meridian.
Edward Nygma
has been screaming
for hours
that he knows
the true identity
of Batman.
Edward?
Who...is it?
It's Dr Meridian.
Chase.
Do you remember me?
How could I forget?
Dr Burton tells me
you know who Batman is.
I can't tell you
if you don't say please.
Edward, please,
who is Batman?
I'm Batman!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Ha ha ha ha!
Your secret is safe.
He's definitely a wacko.
Wacko? Is that
a technical term?
[Laughs]
Listen...
I won't be needing
this anymore.
Thank you
for giving me
a new dream.
Don't work too late.
♪ You don't know how
you took it ♪
♪ You just know
what you got ♪
♪ Oh, Lordy,
you been stealin' ♪
♪ From the thieves,
and you got caught ♪
♪ In the headlights
♪ Of a stretch car
♪ You're a star
♪ Dressin'
like your sister ♪
♪ Livin' like a tart
♪ They don't know
what you're doin' ♪
♪ Babe, it must be art
♪ You're a headache
in a suitcase ♪
♪ You're the new star
♪ Oh, no,
don't be shy ♪
♪ You don't have
to go by ♪
♪ Hold me
♪ Thrill me
♪ Kiss me
♪ Kill me
♪ You don't know
how you got here ♪
♪ You just know
you want out ♪
♪ Believin' in yourself
almost as much as you doubt ♪
♪ You're a big smash
♪ You wear it
like a rash ♪
♪ Star
♪ Oh, no, don't be shy
♪ It takes
a crowd to cry ♪
♪ Hold me
♪ Thrill me
♪ Kiss me
♪ Kill me
Hey!
♪ Oh, oh
♪ Ahh, ahh, ahh
♪ Doo doo
♪ Doo doo doo
♪ There used to be
a greying tower ♪
♪ Alone on the sea
♪ You became
♪ The light
on the dark side of me ♪
♪ And love remained
♪ A drug lasting
high enough to fear ♪
♪ But did you know
that when it snows ♪
♪ My eyes become large
♪ And the light
that you shine ♪
♪ Can't be seen?
♪ Baby
♪ I compare you
to a kiss ♪
♪ From a rose
on the grave ♪
♪ Ooh, the more
I get of you ♪
♪ Strange how it feels
♪ Yeah
♪ And now that
your rose is in bloom ♪
♪ A light
hits the gloom ♪
♪ On the grave
♪ Baby, I compare you
to a kiss ♪
♪ From a rose
on the grave ♪
♪ Ooh, the more
I get of you ♪
♪ Strange how it feels