[Penguin's mother moaning]
[Baby crying]
[Penguin's father screaming]
[Eerie instrumental music]
[Looming instrumental music]
Merry Christmas.
[Eerie instrumental music]
[Baby crying]
Merry Christmas.
PAPERBOY: Penguin sighting! Check it out!
Man or myth?
What is he? Today's edition.
Another Penguin sighting.
Another Penguin sighting! Check it out!
Grotesque penguin-man living in Gotham
sewers. Read all about the latest sighting.
Could I have your attention, Gotham City?
It is time for tonight's lighting of the tree.
[Crowd cheering]
How about that?
[Christmas carol playing]
[Creepy instrumental music]
PAPERBOY: Part man, part penguin.
All horrifying!
Find out for only 50 cents. Come on!
Read about the possible terror
beneath our feet. Check it out, people!
Read about it! Today's issue.
Read about the latest sighting
of the penguin creature.
Missing link between man and bird.
My dear boy...
sometimes it's a diversion
to read such rubbish.
Most of the time, it's a waste of time.
Whatever. Today's issue, the Penguin.
Check him out. Man or myth?
The Globe. Right here. 25 cents.
MAYOR: Well, here's hoping.
Maybe with a little luck,
Gotham will have...
its first merry Christmas
in a good long while.
I feel almost vulgar
in this yuletide context...
mentioning the new power plant.
But if we're gonna break ground,
when we gotta break ground...
I'll need permits, variances, tax incentives.
That sort of pesky nonsense.
Power plant?
Max, all our studies show us
we've got enough power...
to get us into the middle
of the next century.
Your analysts are talking growth
at 1% per annum.
That's not growth. That's a mild swelling.
Imagine a Gotham City...
of the future, lit up like a blanket of stars...
but blinking on and off...
embarrassingly low on juice.
Frankly...
I cringe, Mr. Mayor.
Sorry, any plans you've got will
have to go to the usual committees...
through the usual channels.
I have a suggestion.
Well...
actually, really, just more like a question.
I'm afraid we haven't
properly housebroken Miss Kyle.
In the plus column, though...
she makes a hell of a cup of coffee.
Dad.
Mr. Mayor. It's time to go down
and bring joy to the masses.
"Actually, more of a question."
You stupid corn dog.
Oh, God. Corn dog.
All right. Give us some room.
Wait, let him through, please.
I have enough signatures from Shreck
employees alone to warrant a recall.
That's not a threat, just simple numbers.
Maybe. But you don't have an issue, Max.
And you sure as hell
don't have a candidate.
Hello, Mr. Shreck!
Thank you very much,
ladies and gentlemen.
From those of us at City Hall
to each and every one of you...
happy holidays.
We have with us tonight
a man who really needs no introduction.
He's given so much to our city.
Will you welcome, please,
Gotham 's own Santa Claus: Max Shreck.
Pick up those contracts
from Personnel and...
pick up the dry cleaning, paper towels...
Oh, darn!
Forgot my speech.
Remind me to take it out
on what's-her-name.
Santa Claus? Afraid not.
I'm just a poor schmo who got lucky.
And sue me if I want to give some back.
I only wish I could hand out more
than just expensive baubles.
I wish I could hand out world peace...
and unconditional love...
wrapped in a big bow.
PENGUIN: Oh, but you can.
Oh, but you will.
Merry Christmas.
- Great idea.
- Not mine.
[Circusy instrumental music]
Let's go!
What're you waiting for? The signal!
[Thrilling instrumental music]
We want the big guy!
The guy who runs the show!
- What do you want?
- Not you!
- Shreck!
- You'll have to go through me.
- Chip.
- Dad, go! Save yourself!
Dad, go!
[Circusy instrumental music]
Shut up!
You take one step closer,
Mr. Man-bat and...
You missed.
Wow.
The Batman.
Or is it just Batman?
Your choice, of course.
Well, that was very brief.
Just like all the men in my life.
I know, what men?
Then again, there's you.
But you need therapy.
[Police siren wailing]
Thanks for saving the day, Batman.
I'm afraid the Circus Gang is back.
We'll see.
They almost made off with
our mover and shaker, Max Shreck, but...
Where is that insufferable son of a bitch?
[Looming instrumental music]
Hi.
I believe the word you're looking for is...
Actually, this is all just a bad dream.
You're at home in bed...
heavily sedated, resting comfortably...
dying from the carcinogens
you've personally spewed...
in a lifetime of profiteering.
Tragic irony or poetic justice?
You tell me.
My God, it's true.
Penguin Man of the sewer.
Odd as it may seem, Max...
you and I have something in common.
We're both perceived as monsters.
But somehow...
you're a well-respected monster...
and I am, to date, not!
Frankly, I feel that's a bum rap.
I'm a businessman.
Tough, yes.
Shrewd, okay.
But that does not make me a monster.
Don't embarrass yourself, Max!
I know all about you.
What you hide, I discover.
What you put in your toilet...
I place on my mantle. Get the picture?
What, is that supposed to hypnotize me?
No, just give you a splitting headache.
It's not working.
You big baby! Just blanks.
Would I go through all this trouble tonight
just to kill you?
No, Max.
I have an entirely other purpose.
I'm ready, Max.
I've been down here too long.
It's time for me to ascend...
to re-emerge...
with your help...
your know-how...
your savvy.
I wasn't born in the sewer, you know.
I come from...
Like you.
And, like you, I want some respect!
A recognition of my basic humanity.
But most of all...
I want to find out who I am
by finding my parents...
learning my human name.
Simple stuff that the good people
of Gotham take for granted!
And...
exactly why am I going to help you?
Well...
Let's start.
What have we here? Let's see.
A batch of toxic waste...
from your clean textile plant.
There's a whole lagoon of this crud
in the back.
That could have come from anywhere.
What about the documents that prove you
own half of the firetraps in Gotham City?
If there were such documents...
that's not an admission.
I would have seen to it
they were shredded.
Good idea.
A lot of tape and a little patience
make all the difference.
By the way...
how's Fred Atkins, your old partner?
Fred?
Fred's actually...
I believe he's on extended vacation.
He's good.
Good.
Hiya, Max. Remember me?
I'm Fred's hand!
You want to greet any other body parts?
Remember, Max...
you flush it, I flaunt it.
You know what, Mr. Penguin, sir?
I think perhaps...
I could help orchestrate
a little welcome-home scenario for you.
Once we're both back home,
perhaps we can help each other out.
You won't regret this, Mr. Shreck.
Honey, I'm home!
I forgot. I'm not married.
[Cat mewing]
Miss Kitty.
Back from more sexual escapades
you refuse to share?
Not that I'd ever pry.
Drink your dinner.
What?
How can anyone be so pathetic?
Yes, to you I seem pathetic.
But I'm a working girl.
Gotta pay the rent. Maybe if you were
chipping in instead of stepping out.
Selina, dear, it's your mother.
Just calling to say hello.
Yeah, right, but...
But I'm disappointed
you're not coming home for Christmas.
I want to discuss just why you insist
on languishing in Gotham City...
as some lowly secretary.
Lowly assistant.
Selina, about that Christmas getaway
we planned...
I'll be going alone. Dr. Shaw says I need
to be my own person, not an appendage.
Some appendage!
The party never stops
on Selina Kyle's answering machine.
Guess I should've let him win
that last racquetball game.
Hello, Selina Kyle.
We're calling to tell you
about exciting new Gotham Lady perfume.
It makes women feel like women
and the men have no complaints, either.
Hi, Selina.
This is yourself calling
to remind you, honey...
that you have to come
all the way back to the office...
You stupid corn dog!
... unless you remembered to bring home
the Bruce Wayne file.
Because the meeting's on Wednesday.
Working late?
I'm just boning up for your Bruce Wayne
meeting in the morning.
I pulled all of the files
on the proposed power plant...
and Mr. Wayne's hope for investment.
And I even opened the protected files and...
How industrious.
How did you open protected files...
may I ask?
I figured your password was "Heraldo,"
your chihuahua, and it was.
This is all very interesting,
though a bit on the technical side.
I mean, about how the power plant
is a power plant in name only...
since, in fact, it's going to be a big, giant...
capacitor.
And that, instead of generating power,
it'll sort of be sucking power from...
Gotham City and storing it...
stockpiling it.
Which is a very novel approach, I'd say.
And who would you say this to?
Nobody.
What did curiosity do to the cat?
I'm no cat.
I'm just an assistant.
A secretary.
And a very good one.
Too good?
Listen, it's our secret. Honest.
How can you be so mean
to someone so meaningless?
This power plant...
is my legacy. It's what I leave behind...
for Chip.
Nothing must prevent that.
Okay.
Go ahead. Intimidate me,
bully me, if it makes you feel big.
I mean, it's not like you can just kill me!
Actually, it's a lot like that.
You know, for a second there,
you really frightened me.
Really?
Honey, I'm home.
I forgot. I'm not married.
Selina, this is your mother. Call me.
Selina, this is your mother.
Why haven't you called me back?
Hello, Selina Kyle.
We're just calling to make sure
you've tried Gotham Lady perfume.
One whiff of this at the office and
your boss will ask you to stay after work...
for a candlelight staff meeting for two.
Gotham Lady perfume.
Exclusively at Shreck's department store.
[Eerie instrumental music]
I don't know about you,
Miss Kitty, but I feel...
so much yummier.
Well, ladies and gentlemen...
I stand before you once again...
to denounce the urban chaos we seem
to have to live with in our great city.
It's got to stop.
And it's going to stop.
Our community is coming apart...
in a season
when it should be coming together.
I don't care what the cynics may say.
This is the Christmas season.
It should be a time of healing.
And I tell you that, not only as an official...
but as a husband and a father.
Last night's violence
will not happen again.
[Circusy instrumental music]
I'm not really one for speeches,
so I'll just say, "Thanks."
No! It's the hideous Penguin Man.
Here, take the baby.
Just don't hurt me, please.
This was the remarkable scene
only minutes ago in Gotham Plaza.
The mysterious Penguin saving the life
of the Mayor's baby and...
- announcing his presence to the world.
- All I want in return...
is a chance to find my mom and dad.
A chance to find out who they are...
and thusly, who I am.
And then, with my parents...
try to understand why.
Why they did what I guess
they felt they had to do...
to a child who was born...
a little different.
A child who spent his first Christmas...
and many since...
in a sewer.
Mr. Wayne? Is something wrong?
No.
His parents.
Again, this scene,
direct from Gotham Plaza...
where we have just witnessed...
I hope he finds them.
Here he is, standing alongside
Gotham 's leading citizen, Max Shreck.
How about a statement?
People want to know.
- Penguin's not to be disturbed.
- This is a public place.
- Take a walk. Move!
- You're violating the First Amendment.
- Breaching the freedom of the press!
- Wait a minute.
What about the freedom
to rediscover your roots...
with dignity and privacy?
What's the deal, Mr. Shreck?
Is the Penguin a personal friend?
Yes, he's a personal friend
of this whole city, so have a heart.
Give the Constitution a rest, okay?
It's Christmas.
"Red Triangle Circus put on a swell show
with fierce lions.
"Circus return for two-week...
"Kids will love..."
Thanks.
- It's cold!
- It's vichyssoise, sir.
It's supposed to be cold.
"Circus is back with a freak show.
May not be suitable for kids.
"Featuring a poodle lady...
"the world's fattest man...
"and aquatic bird-boy."
Why are you now determined to prove...
that this Penguin is not what he seems?
Must you be
the only Ionely man-beast in town?
"The circus folded its tents yesterday...
"perhaps forever, after numerous reports
of missing children in several towns.
"Police have closed down
the Red Triangle's fairgrounds.
"However, at least one
freak-show performer vanished before...
"he could be questioned."
I suppose you feel better now, sir.
No.
Actually, I feel worse.
Why're you still out?
Are you concerned about that strange,
heroic Penguin person?
I think he knows who his parents are.
There's something else.
[SIow instrumental music]
Penguin!
Can we get a statement from you?
So, Mr. Penguin...
A penguin is a bird that cannot fly.
I am a man.
I have a name.
Oswald Cobblepot!
Mr. Cobblepot, you'll never get a chance
to settle up with them?
True.
I was their number one son...
and they treated me like number two.
But it's human nature to fear...
the unusual.
Perhaps when I held...
my Tiffany baby rattle...
with a shiny flipper...
instead of five chubby digits...
they freaked.
But I forgive them.