"You don't need hands
as long as you've got heart.
"My heart is filled with love.
I feel 5 feet tall."
- He's like a frog that became a prince.
- No, he's more like a penguin.
Now, pretty little thing.
Nice and easy.
I just love a big, strong man
who's not afraid to show it...
with someone half his size.
Be gentle, it's my first time.
Tic-tac-toe.
Thanks. L...
You make it so easy, don't you?
Always waiting for some Batman
to save you.
I am Catwoman.
Hear me roar.
I'd offer you coffee, but my assistant
is using her vacation time.
Good time, too.
Everyone but the bandits will be
slacking off till after New Year, anyway.
- I'm not sure I like the inference, Bruce.
- Sorry, Max. I didn't realize I made one.
I'm pushing this power plant now
because it'll cost more later.
A million saved is a million earned.
I commissioned this report. I thought
you might want to take a look at it.
The point is, Max, Gotham City has
a power surplus. I'm sure you know that.
My question is...
what's your angle?
Power surplus? Bruce, shame on you.
No such thing.
One can never have too much power.
If my life has a meaning,
that's the meaning.
Yeah, well, I'm gonna fight you on this.
I've already spoken to the Mayor...
- and we see eye to eye.
- Mayors come and go.
Blue bloods tire easy.
You think you could go 15 rounds
with Muhammad Shreck?
Well, I guess we're gonna find out.
Of course, I don't have a crime boss
like Cobblepot in my corner, so...
Crime boss? Shows what you know...
Mr. To-the-manor-born-
with-a-silver-spoon.
Oswald is Gotham's new golden boy.
If his parents hadn't 86'd him...
you two might have been bunkies
at prep school.
Oswald controls the Red Triangle Gang.
I can't prove it yet, but we both...
Wayne, I'll not stand for mudslinging
in this office.
If my assistant was here, she already
would have escorted you out...
Anywhere he wants.
Preferably some nightspot, grotto...
or secluded hideaway.
- Nice suit.
- Thanks.
Selina.
That's my name, Maximillions.
Don't wear it out,
or I'll make you buy me a new one.
This is Bruce Wayne.
- Yeah, we've met.
- Have we?
Oh, I'm sorry. You know what?
I mistook me for somebody else.
You mean, mistook me.
I mistook... Yeah. Isn't that what I said?
No, I don't think so.
What happened?
Did you injure yourself on that ski slope?
Is that why you cut short your vacation?
Came back?
It's a blur.
I mean, not complete amnesia. I remember
Sister Mary Margaret puking in church...
and Betsy Riley saying
it was morning sickness.
And I remember the time
I forgot to wear my underpants to school...
and the name of the boy
who noticed was Ricky Friedburg.
He's dead now.
But last night, complete blur.
Couldn't you just die?
Selina, please...
show out Mr. Wayne.
With pleasure.
Your coat, Mr. Wayne.
Right.
You don't seem like the type
who does business with Mr. Shreck.
No, you don't seem like the type
that takes orders from him.
Well, that's a long story.
I could free up some time.
- I'm listed.
- I'm tempted.
I'm working.
I'm leaving.
- Dad, you buy that blurry business?
- Women.
Nothing surprises me, Chip.
Except your late mother.
Who'd have thought
Selina had a brain to damage?
Bottom line?
She tries to blackmail me,
I'll drop her out a higher window.
Meantime, I've got badder fish to fry.
Oswald, it's Max.
You're home?
How've you been?
Your extended family?
Good to have a family.
I'd much rather not be disturbed now.
Come on downstairs, Oswald.
I have a surprise.
I don't like surprises.
Come on down.
Don't peek.
You'll spoil it.
Yes. Adulation is a cross to bear.
God knows, I know.
But someone's got to supplant our
standing-in-the-way-of-progress mayor.
And don't deny it, Mr. Cobblepot,
you've got the magic.
Your charisma's bigger than both of us.
Come on down.
Mayor?
Mayor.
Elections happen in November.
Is this not late December?
Don't worry about it.
I want you to meet Jen and Josh,
my image consultants.
Here.
Reclaim your birthright.
I'm Jen. Hi.
Okay, let's see.
What I'd like to do first
is put these little glove thingies on you.
Our research tells us
that voters like fingers.
So if we wanna just lose this...
We'll do it another time then, okay?
Not a lot of reflective surfaces
down in the sewer?
Still, could be worse.
My nose could be gushing blood.
Your nose could be...
What do you mean by that?
Oh, God!
Everybody, back to work!
Let's make a mayor!
You're right, we missed
the regularly scheduled election...
but elected officials can be recalled,
impeached...
- given the boot. Look at Nixon.
- Agnew.
Then think of you...
Oswald Cobblepot, filling the void.
I'd like to fill her void.
We're gonna need signatures
to overturn the ballot. I can supply those.
- Teach her my French flipper trick.
- Oswald, we need one more thing.
A platform?
Stop global warming. Start global cooling.
Make the world a giant icebox.
I like it. But to get the Mayor recalled,
we have to have a catalyst, a trigger.
You're doing great, Mayor Cobblepot.
Your table is ready, Mayor Cobblepot.
I need you, Oswald. I need you now.
That's the biggest parasol I've ever seen.
Soon. One incident like the Gulf of Tonkin
or the Reichstag fire.
You want my old friends up there...
to drive the Mayor into a foaming frenzy?
- Exactly.
- Sounds fun.
But...
I mustn't get sidetracked, Maxie.
I've got my own things to tend to.
Sidetracked? Oswald,
this is your chance to fulfill a destiny...
your parents carelessly discarded.
Reclaim my birthright, you mean?
Imagine, as mayor,
you'd have the ear of the media...
access to the captains of industry...
unlimited poontang.
You drive a hard bargain, Maxie.
All right, I'll be mayor.
Burn, baby, burn!
[Fast-paced instrumental music]
- Who is she?
- What is she?
I don't know whether to open fire
or fall in love.
You poor guys.
Always confusing your pistols
with your privates.
Don't hurt us, lady.
Our take-home's less than $300.
You're overpaid. Hit the road.
Go ahead and hit me.
Admiring your handiwork?
Touring the riot scene.
Gravely assessing the devastation.
Upstanding mayor stuff.
You're not the mayor.
Things change.
What do you want?
The direct approach.
I admire that in a man with a mask.
You don't really think you'll win, do you?
Things change.
Meow.
I saw her first. Gotta fly.
How could you? I'm a woman.
I'm sorry. L...
As I was saying, I'm a woman
and can't be taken for granted.
Life's a bitch, now so am I.
Who are you?
Who's the man behind the bat?
Maybe you can help me find...
the woman behind the cat.
No, that's not you.
There you are.
Saved by Kitty Litter.
[Snickering]
Bastard!
Alfred...
bring me some antiseptic ointment,
would you?
Coming. Are you in pain, sir?
No. Not really.
Meow.
Thank you.
I may have saved the Mayor's baby...
but I refuse to save a mayor...
who stood by, helpless as a baby...
while Gotham was ravaged by a disease...
that turned Eagle Scouts
into crazed clowns...
and happy homemakers into catwomen.
Thank you.
Oswald Cobblepot, the mystery man-beast
who's been romancing Gotham...
today made his bid to run Gotham.
Thank you.
Mr. Cobblepot, you are the coolest
role model a young person could have.
And you're the hottest young person
a role model could have.
Here.
Wear a button.
Let me just get it on there.
Thank you.
I could really get into this mayor stuff.
It's not about power,
it's about reaching out to people...
touching people, groping people.
- Penguin...
- My name's not Penguin!
It's Oswald Cobblepot.
Oswald, there's somebody here
to see you.
Just the pussy I've been looking for.
It's chilly in here.
- I'll warm you.
- Down, Oswald.
We need to talk.
You see, you and I
have something in common.
Sounds familiar.
Appetite for destruction?
Contempt for the czars of fashion?
Wait, don't tell me.
Naked sexual charisma?
Batman.
The thorn in both our sides.
The fly in our ointment.
Ointment?
I've got scented or unscented.
I'll come back later.
Perchance, are you a registered voter?
I am a mayoral prospect.
I have but one pet cause today.
Ban the bat.
Oh, him again. No bother.
He's already history. Check it out.
We're gonna disassemble his Batmobile
and turn it into an H-bomb on wheels.
No.
He'd have even more power as a martyr.
To destroy Batman, we must first
turn him into what he hates the most.
Namely, us.
You mean, frame him?
Not even in office yet
and already an enemies list?
Those names are not for prying eyes.
Why should I trust
some cat-broad, anyway?
Maybe you're just a screwed-up sorority
chick who's getting back at her daddy...
for not buying her that pony
when she turned sweet 16.
Nice birdie.
Nice kitty.
Look, Batman napalmed my arm.
He knocked me off a building just when
I was starting to feel good about myself.
I want to play an integral part
in his degradation.
A plan is forming.
I want in.
The thought of busting Batman
makes me feel all...
dirty.
Maybe I'll just give myself a bath
right here.
I challenge the Mayor...
to relight the Christmas tree
in Gotham Plaza tomorrow night.
Sir, shall we change the channel
to a program with some dignity and class?
The Love Connection perhaps?
Not that I have any faith in the Mayor.
But I hope and pray that Batman...
will be present to preserve the peace.
Thank you very much.
Subtle.
Why are you doing this?
Selina?
Hi. I'm sorry, I didn't mean to scare you.
Scare me? No.
I was just scaring myself, actually.
I don't see how, but...
It's nice to see you out in the real world,
away from Shreck.
Well, it's nice to be here.
You all right?
You look like maybe you have
the holiday blues or something.
No.
Boy, the news these days. Weird.
I heard on TV that...
Catwoman is thought to weigh
140 pounds.
I don't know how these hacks
sleep at night.
It's not even accurate. "Batman blows it"?
He probably saved millions of dollars
in property damage alone.
You're not going to that, are you?
The relighting of the tree thing?
No. I wouldn't be caught dead there.
It's going to be a hot time
on the cold town tonight.
You got kind of a dark side, don't you?
No darker than yours, Bruce.
Listen, why don't you come over
and we can watch it together on TV?
- What?
- The tree-lighting ceremony.
I can't. I have to be somewhere tonight.
How about if you come over
for an early dinner. Let's say 5:00?
Let's say 6:00?
Okay, 5:00.
5:00. You and me. Okay?
[Sinister instrumental music]
The tree lights up,
and then I push the button.
No, wait.
I press the button,
and then the tree lights up.
- Who are you?
- Talent scout.
Come in.
You know, I don't just light trees.
I'm an actress, as well.
What is that thing?
A camera or something?
Say cheese.
Cheese.
Thanks, Alfred.
I'm sure he's wonderful company...
but doesn't the gold-plated bachelor bit
get a little stale?
A lot like the Ionely secretary syndrome,
I guess.
- Executive assistant.
- Sorry.
Secretary.
Any girlfriend?
Sure.
You mean, as in serious?
No. Had one, didn't work.
What went wrong?
Hang on, I think I know.
- You kept things from her.
- No, I told her everything.
And the truth frightened her?
There are two truths, you know?
She had trouble reconciling them,
because I had trouble...
reconciling them.
- See, Vicki thought...
- Vicki?
Ice skater or stewardess?
No, she was a photojournalist.
Was Vicki right
about your difficulty with duality?
If I say yes, then...
you're gonna think of me as...
a Norman Bates, Ted Bundy type and...
Well, you might not let me kiss you.
It's the so-called normal guys
who always let you down.
Sickos never scare me.
At least they're committed.
[Romantic instrumental music]
- You can't do that.
- Neither can I.
The Ice Princess has been kidnapped.
Commissioner Gordon...
can you confirm for us
the reports we're hearing...
of Batman's suspected involvement
in the abduction?
This evidence is purely circumstantial.
This was found, stained with blood,
in the missing girl's dressing room.
- I gotta get out of here.
- No, it's your house.
Hold on. Just sit for a second and relax.
I'll be right back.
- Alfred, I've got to get down to the plaza.
- I saw it.
I know.
He's practically begging me to show up.
Which is why I hoped you'd snub him.
No, I can't. There's been a kidnapping.
Here's what I want you to do.
Shit!
Tell Selina, you know, Miss Kyle in there,
tell her I had to go out of town.
Tell her there's a big business deal
that came up. No, you know what?
Let her know, not in some kind of dumb,
be-my-girlfriend kind of way...
- I will relay the message.
- Great.
- Miss Kyle...
- Alfred.
- Mr. Wayne told me to tell you that...
- Mr. Wayne?
Bruce, yes.
Would you tell him for me that...
I've been going through
a lot of changes and...
No. Just that...
this is not a rejection, my abruptly leaving.
In fact, he makes me feel the way...
I hope I really am.
No.
Could you just make up a sonnet
or something, a dirty limerick?
- One has just sprung to mind.
- Thanks.
- This way, ma'am.
- Sorry.
[Dramatic instrumental music]
Where is that?
Ladies and gentlemen.
Please, if I could have your attention
for just a minute.
Folks, I know that to many of you...
Gotham seems a bit beleaguered
these days.
But I want you to know
that your elected officials...
and your police department
have the situation well in hand.
[Circusy instrumental music]
- Gotta hurry.
- Thank you.
It was set up to look like I did this.
No sweat. I'll just tell the police...
I was kidnapped by an ugly birdman
with fish breath.
Did somebody say "fish"?
I haven't been fed all day.
Eat floor.
High fiber.
Hey, stud...
- I thought we had something together.
- We do.
Gotta go. Girl talk.
She let me go. I think
'cause I reasoned with her, girl to girl.
Be careful. Don't move.
Lawn dart!
Rats with wings, do your thing.
Batman pushed the Princess!
Hold your fire!
You're catnip to a girl like me.
Handsome, dazed...
and to die for.
Mistletoe can be deadly if you eat it.
But a kiss can be even deadlier
if you mean it.
You're the second man
who killed me this week.
But I've got seven lives left.
I tried to save you...
Seems like every woman you try to save
ends up dead.
Or deeply resentful.
Maybe you should retire.
Damn.
Outstanding.
You're Beauty and the Beast...
in one luscious Christmas gift pack.
You said you were going to scare
the Ice Princess.
She looked pretty scared to me.
Touch of the bubbly?
So what are we waiting for?
Let's consummate our fiendish union.
What are you talking about?
Oh, come on. Can't you picture?
It's dark in the mayor's mansion.
I'm bushed,
so here you come into the bedroom...
twitching your little tail...
my slippers in one hand,
a dry martini in the other.
Oh, please.
I wouldn't touch you to scratch you.
You lousy minx!
I ought to have you spayed!
You sent out all the signals!
And I don't think I like you anymore!
Goodbye, my unintended. Go to heaven.
Thank you.
There he is!
Don't adjust your sets.
Welcome to
the Oswald Cobblepot School of Driving.
Gentlemen, start your screaming.
Maybe this is a bad time to mention this,
but my license has expired!
Just relax.
I'll take care of the squealing,
wretched, pinhead puppets of Gotham!
You gotta admit,
I played this stinking city...
like a harp from hell!
Helpless old lady at 12:00 high.
That's funny.
Now I'm a little worried.