Improved by KID
Resynced by KID
Enjoy the movie(s) / show(s)
There was a time above.
A time before.
There were perfect things,
diamond absolutes.
How things fall.
Things on earth.
And what falls...
Master Wayne!
...is fallen. Bruce!
Bruce, it's all right.
Bruce, please.
Martha.
In the dream, they
took me to the light.
A beautiful lie.
Jack. Bruce.
Jack, listen to me.
I want you to get everyone
out of the building right now.
You understand? Oh, my God.
Stay away from the windows!
Let's go. Come on. Start
moving now, people. Let's go.
The boss wants us out of the
building, so let's make it happen.
Jack. Jack!
We're sorry.
All circuits are busy now. Will
you please try your call again later?
Heavenly God,
creator of heaven and earth,
have mercy on my soul.
Jack!
Buddy hands! Everybody
show me! Good job!
Come on, guys.
Hold on tight.
Go.
Mr. Wayne!
Mr. Wayne! I can't feel my legs.
I can't feel my legs.
We need help over here!
Help me. I can't feel my legs.
You're gonna be
okay. You hear me?
Wallace? What do they
call you, Wally? Huh?
You're the boss, boss.
All right. You're gonna be okay.
Easy, easy. Come on.
Oh, my God. I can't move my leg.
My God. I can't feel my legs.
It's okay. You're gonna be okay.
You're okay. All right? Huh?
You know what? We're
gonna find your Mom.
Where is she?
All that wind is bad luck.
Blood in the sky.
Oh, there she is!
Miss Lane.
Miss Lane. Jimmy Olsen.
Photographer. Obviously.
Where's Heron?
Uh, trouble at the border.
So, uh, how'd you land it?
This is, like, pioneer stuff.
Amajagh's never
given an interview.
You know what heron always says
when we're on assignment together?
Not a goddamn thing.
I like Heron.
Let's go.
Passports. Electronics.
Phones. Camera.
Your fixer said that the
General approved photos.
Um...
Are you a terrorist, General?
They did not tell me the
interview was with a lady.
I'm not a lady.
I'm a journalist.
What I am is a man with nothing
except a love of my people.
Who's paying for these
security contractors, General?
Who pays for the drones that
pass over our heads at night?
One question begs another.
Yes?
Say what you're saying, General.
It's just a camera.
The United States has declared its
neutrality in your country's civil war
both in policy and in principle.
Oh, don't open...
You just exposed...
These pious American fictions...
...spoken like truth.
Okay. That's my film.
Men with power obey neither
policy nor principle, Miss Lane.
No one is different.
No one is neutral.
CIA.
They're tracking us!
You!
You're CIA?
What? No. No!
You brought him here!
No, he's a photographer.
No!
It's okay, Lois.
Talon's down, sir.
Python, we have lost
our asset on the ground.
Repeat, we have lost
There's still a civilian in the
compound. We'll extract her.
Negative. RPA to engage.
Stand down and get black.
There'll be friendlies
in the blast zone, so...
Call off the goddamn drone.
Stand down is an order. Python?
Let's move!
I...
I didn't know.
Ignorance is not the
same as innocence,
Miss Lane.
Get up! Stand up!
Quickly. He's coming.
Inbound 2 Mikes.
Passing python now.
Move out!
Target locked. You
are clear to engage.
Armed hot and in range.
Three.
Two. One.
Link's been hit.
By what?
Take one step,
you will see the
inside of her head.
The women in the
village heard a noise.
Like the sky cracked open.
He came down. Then came fire.
Even worse came after.
The Government attacked.
No mercy in the villages.
My parents tried to run.
The world has been so caught
up with what Superman can do
that no one has asked
what he should do.
Let the record show that this
committee holds him responsible.
He'll never answer to you.
He answers to no one.
Not even, I think, to God.
58 to nothing.
Metropolis, again,
blowing out Gotham city.
Really, only the diehards
are left in the stands.
Delta Charlie 27. Reports of
screams coming from vacant home
at 1939 Harborway.
Tom, it's been great
working with you.
I want to thank our
producer and director.
Now wait a second. I
don't even want to suggest...
Delta Charlie 27, respond.
Just take a knee.
They're lining up as if clarkson
is gonna throw it deep here.
- Don't tell me, Dave.
- Going to the end zone!
- This is unnecessary.
- Delta Charlie 27.
- Zeke Baker is open.
- Baker with a touchdown catch!
I can't believe I
just watched that.
Delta Charlie 27. Do you copy?
10-4. We're on it.
And now a fight breaks out.
Gotham city, you know how
they are about their football team.
Things could get
ugly in the city tonight.
Go.
It's okay.
We're gonna help.
We're here to help.
We're gonna get you
out of here. Okay?
I don't understand.
Please don't. Please don't.
Please. I don't know who he is.
I don't know who he is!
No!
Oh, fuck.
Christ!
I saw him.
I never saw him
before. I... I didn't know.
You almost took my face off.
How about you don't
shoot the good guys, huh?
Oh. Oh.
Jesus Christ.
He branded him.
Hey. Hey.
I was gonna cook.
Surprise you.
They held hearings
about what happened.
They're saying
that... I don't care.
I don't care what
they're saying.
The woman I love could
have been blown up or shot.
Think of what could
have happened.
Well, think about
what did happen.
I didn't kill those men,
if that's what they think.
If that's what you're saying.
No, I'm saying I want to
understand what happened.
I'm saying thank
you for saving my life.
I'm saying there's a cost.
I just don't know
if it's possible.
Don't know if what's possible?
For you to love me and be you.
Clark!
Clark, you're going
to flood the apartment.
Mmm-hmm.
You still working?
You're getting slow
in your old age, Alfred.
Comes to us all, Master Wayne.
Even you got too
old to die young.
And not for lack of trying.
Funnel-ferry butterbar.
Funnel-ferry...
There's nothing wrong
with the microphone.
It's this new layer of armor.
I'll just have to rewire.
So, last night was productive?
No. He's too low-level.
He knew nothing.
This is the man
who knows things.
Anatoli Knyazev. He's Russian.
Contracts all over the globe,
but he's based out
of the port of Gotham.
Weapons and human trafficking.
So the white
Portuguese is a Russian.
That's the theory.
No. The theory is that the Russian
will lead me to the man himself.
If he is, indeed, a "him."
You don't even
know if he exists.
Could be a Phantasm.
One that wants to bring
a dirty bomb into Gotham?
Ah, high-stakes round.
New rules.
We're criminals, Alfred.
We've always been
criminals. Nothing's changed.
Oh, yes, it has, sir.
Everything's changed.
Men fall from the sky.
The Gods hurl thunderbolts.
Innocents die.
That's how it starts, sir.
The fever. The rage.
The feeling of powerlessness.
It turns good men cruel.
John, get D.
Ooh. Ah. Ahoy, ahoy! I
did not know you were here.
Man on the Marquee.
Yeah, don't believe it.
My father named the
company after himself.
He was the Lex in front of
the Corp. How you doin'?
Oh, really great.
Really great? Good.
Good. Uh, follow me.
No, uh, Dad started saying
that he named the company,
uh, after his kid
at investor pitches.
Rich old ladies. They thought
it was very cute, you know?
"Write check for Lex."
You know, Dad was
born in East Germany.
He grew up eating,
uh, stale crackers.
And every other Saturday,
he had to march in a parade
and wave flowers at Tyrants.
So, I think it was
Providence that his son, me,
would end up with this.
One of my rebuild
Metropolis crews found it.
Little souvenir from the
Kryptonian world engine.
What does a rock have to
do with homeland security?
Homeland security? Hmm.
No, no, no, ma'am,
planetary security.
The fragment is of a
radioactive xenomineral.
We suspected it might
have bio-interactions,
so we took the sample to amriid,
where they keep the remains
of the Kryptonian decedent.
And, when we exposed
General Zod to the mineral,
this happened.
Profound biodegradation.
Decaying Kryptonian cells.
We concluded the mineral
could be weaponized
if a large enough
sample was found.
And then, among
the fishes, a whale.
Ah!
Lying at the bottom
of the Indian ocean.
Emerald city.
Beautiful.
Now, rocky is radioactive,
but what he needs from
you is an import license.
And why would we want
to weaponize this material?
As a deterrent.
A silver bullet to
keep in reserve,
to use against the Kryptonians,
so the day does not come, Madam,
when your children are waving
daisies at a reviewing stand.
Last I looked, the
only one of those
flying around up
here was Superman.
Ha-ha, yes. Superman.
Yeah, but there are, uh...
There are more of them.
The metahuman thesis.
Yes, the metahuman thesis.
More likely than not
these exceptional
beings live among us.
The basis of our myths.
Gods among men upon
our little blue planet here.
Now, you don't have
to use a silver bullet.
But if you forge one...
Well, then
we don't have to depend
upon the kindness of monsters.
There are ways we
can help each other.
Would you step
into my office here?
Yes.
What's your wish list?
Uh...
Access to the wreck of the
crashed Kryptonian ship?
Done.
The complete remains of
the dead alien for testing.
You want Zod's body?
Okay.
Mmm.
It's cherry.
Mmm-mmm.
Because the time has come
for the world to hear
the other side of the story.
They say that Superman is a
hero. Okay, but whose hero?
If Superman were here right now,
what would you
want to say to him?
That my family, too, had dreams.
To look him in his eye
and ask him how he decides...
...which lives count.
And which ones do not.
Sir, get down.
Sir, I said get down!
Now!
Can we get some backup here?
Hey! Hey! Don't do it!
Hey!
Lois! Crime lab, on three.
- This is Lane.
- Kent.
You're sports today.
I want you to go to
Gotham, follow up on football.
"Underdog dreams dashed: Ten
yards between Gotham and glory."
Oh, um, watch yourself
over there in Gotham.
Don't let them take
your lunch money.
Hey. Are you guys watching this?
Emergency responders
quickly created
a precautionary perimeter
around heroes park
while they brought the man
down from this beloved monument.
The suspect has been identified
as Wallace Vernon Keefe.
I work for Bruce Wayne!
He'll be arraigned on
charges of vandalism,
resisting arrest,
and the felony charge
of making terrorist threats.
That carries up to
40 years in prison.
Poor son of a bitch.
Metropolis News 8.
Jenny. Hmm.
Headline: "End of love
affair with man in the sky,
"question mark (?)."
Okay.
Is she in?
No, she's been gone.
What'd she do, officer?
Oh, I'm not a cop.
I'm a reporter.
The young lady living here...
She hasn't been back.
In fact, if she's smart, then
she's got out of this city.
And you need to get
out of here before dark.
Unless you want to run into him.
Don't listen to that nonsense.
Only people scared of him,
people who got reason to be.
Scared of who?
There's a new
kind of mean in him.
He is angry.
And he's hunting.
Show 'em what you got!
Let's go. Come on!
Throw a punch, will ya?
Let's go! Come on!
Thank you.
The house treats
luck like an insult.
Good luck for one is always
his brother's misfortune.
Three nights with
a Bolshoi Ballerina,
that line was all she taught me.
Not all, I'm sure. Good evening.
It's like a one-man
reign of terror.
This Bat vigilante has been
consistently targeting the port
and the adjacent
projects and tenements.
And, as far as I can tell, the
cops are actually helping him.
"Crime wave in Gotham."
Other breaking
news: "Water, wet."
Did you file the football yet?
Why aren't we covering this?
Poor people don't buy papers?
People don't buy
papers, period, Kent.
Perry, when you assign a story,
you're making a choice
about who matters.
And who's worth it.
Good morning, Smallville.
The American conscience died
with Robert, Martin, and John.
Sorry. I'm sorry.
No match. My guys in the
crime lab never seen one before.
It's called a bullet. You
shoot people with them.
Recovered from the scene
of the firefight in the desert.
Not sold anywhere
commercially in the world,
even black market.
So?
So who gave
prototype military rounds
to Tuareg fighters
in the Sahara?
You're the reporter. Tell me.
I think that the us government
is arming the rebels
while claiming to support
the elected government.
The ask, Lois.
Flight to D.C. tonight.
Couple of days there.
Go.
Coach. No extra legroom.
Economy plus.
Coach!
So, why didn't you tell me?
You're digging up snakes, Lo.
It's kind of dangerous.
That is why I didn't tell you.
Lane, don't you
have a plane to catch?
Yes, sir.
Benefit for the
library of Metropolis.
Someone on the committee
requested that Clark Kent cover it.
Probably some old charity
crone who's got a thing for nerds.
Senator.
Little bourbon before lunch?
My driver's
outside. I can't stay.
No bourbon?
Kentucky girl like yourself?
Hmm.
My Dad always said
that Kentucky mash
was the secret to health.
Mmm.
This was his room.
I kept it just the same.
Mmm.
"Maybe one day Dad'll come back
if I just keep everything the same."
That is silly.
The magical thinking
of orphan boys.
I'm blocking the import
license for your mineral.
The redcapes are coming.
Hmm...
You and your hearings.
Galloping through
the streets to warn us.
One if by land,
two if by air.
Mmm.
Do you know the oldest
lie in America, Senator?
Can I call you June?
You can call me
whatever you like.
Take a bucket of piss and
call it granny's peach tea.
Mmm-hmm.
Take a weapon of assassination
and call it deterrence.
You won't fool a fly or me.
I'm not gonna drink it.
You don't think Dad
would mind, do you?
If I changed just... Just
one thing in this room?
Because that should
be upside-down.
We know better now, don't we?
The Devils don't come
from Hell beneath us. No.
No, they come from the sky.
Oh.
I hope the next
generation of Waynes
won't inherit an
empty wine cellar.
Not that there's likely
to be a next generation.
Thank you, sir.
This is every call made
from the Russian's phone.
Two mentions of business
with the white Portuguese.
And it's continually
transmitting blacked-out data
to the personal residence
of Alexander Luthor.
You think Lex Luthor
is the white Portuguese?
I can't see that he needs the
income from imported arms.
Regardless, I'll need to
put a leech at his house,
and I'm gonna need the suit.
The bat interrogated six people
and came away with nothing.
It was Bruce Wayne
that got the information.
Well, Bruce Wayne can't
break into Lex Luthor's house.
Bruce Wayne won't have to.
He's been invited.
Who's that?
You must be new to the
"let them eat cake" beat.
That is Bruce Wayne.
Philanthropist, bibliophile...
True friend of the
library of Metropolis.
Mr. Lex Luthor.
Me? Ah. Okay.
Nicky. Uh...
You're embarrassing me. Um...
Speech, speech. Uh...
Blah, blah, blah. Uh...
Open bar.
The end.
Uh...
The word "philanthropist"
comes from the Greek.
Meaning a lover of humanity.
Uh, it was coined
about 2,500 years ago.
All right. Where
am I going, Alfred?
Go past the elevator.
Do a left.
That's right, must be.
It's in the service
corridor in the basement.
Go down the stairs.
Gods and men.
Prometheus went with us.
And he ruined Zeus'
plan to destroy mankind,
and for that he was
given a thunderbolt.
Hmm, that seems unfair.
Um... on a serious note,
the library of Metropolis...
Go to the stairs. You saw them
on your way in. Down the stairs.
But at one time, Dad
could not buy them. No.
My father could not
afford books growing up.
He had to root through the
garbage for yesterday's newspaper.
All right. You got the
kitchens on your right.
Do a left.
Right in front of you.
That's where you want to be.
May I help you, Mr. Wayne?
Uh, I just...
I thought the bathroom
was down here. I must have...
That last martini was
two too many, I think.
Men's room is upstairs.
Great. I'm okay.
I like those shoes.
I can't stay down here, Alfred.
Go upstairs and socialize.
Some young lady from Metropolis
will make you honest.
In your dreams, Alfred.
Books are knowledge,
and knowledge is
power, and I am...
No. Uh, um...
No. What am I? I...
What was I saying? No.
The bittersweet pain among men
is having knowledge
with no power, because...
Because that is
paradoxical! And, um...
Thank you for coming.
Please drink. Drink.
Mr. Wayne? Mr. Wayne?
Clark Kent, Daily Planet.
Uh, my foundation has
already issued a statement
in support of books.
Sir? Um...
Wow. Pretty girl. Bad
habit. Don't quote me.
All right?
What's your position on
the Bat vigilante in Gotham?
Daily Planet. Do I own this
one? Or is that the other guy?
Civil liberties are being
trampled on in your city.
Good people are living in fear.
Don't believe
everything you hear, son.
I've seen it, Mr. Wayne.
He thinks he's above the law.
The Daily Planet criticizing those
who think they're above the law
is a little hypocritical,
wouldn't you say?
Considering every time your
hero saves a cat out of a tree,
you write a puff piece editorial
about an alien
who, if he wanted to,
could burn the whole place down.
There wouldn't be a damn
thing we could do to stop him.
Most of the world doesn't
share your opinion, Mr. Wayne.
Maybe it's the
Gotham city in me.
We just have a bad history
with freaks dressed like clowns.
Boys! Um!
Bruce Wayne
meets Clark Kent. Ha!
I love it. I love bringing
people together.
How are we?
Lex. Hello. Good.
Hi, hello, Lex, it
is a pleasure. Ow!
Wow! That is a good grip!
You should not pick a
fight with this person. Huh.
So, after all these years, we
finally got you over to Metropolis.
Well, I thought I'd
come drink you dry.
Well, you're welcome. You should
hop the Harbor more often, though.
I'd love to show you my labs.
Maybe we could
partner on something.
My R and D is up to
all sorts of no good.
That's seven minutes.
Looks like the
transfer's complete.
Mr. Luthor. Yes?
The Governor. Governor.
Excuse me. Next time.
Governor! Hi!
Lex, it's good to see you.
Excuse me.
We, as a population
on this planet,
have been looking for a savior.
90% of people believe
in a higher power,
and every religion believes
in some sort of
messianic figure.
And when this savior character
actually comes to earth,
we want to make him
abide by our rules?
We have to understand
that this a paradigm shift.
We have to start
thinking beyond politics.
Are there any moral
constraints on this person?
We have international law.
On this earth, every
act is a political act.
Is it really surprising
that the most powerful
man in the world
should be a figure
of controversy?
Uh, to have an
individual engaging
in these state-level
interventions
should give us all pause.
Human beings have
a horrible track record
of following people
with great power
down paths that led to
huge human atrocities.
We have always created
icons in our own image.
What we've done is we
project ourselves onto him.
The fact is, maybe he's not some
sort of Devil or Jesus character.
Maybe he's just a guy
trying to do the right thing.
Neil deGrasse Tyson: We're talking
about a being whose very existence
challenges our own sense
of priority in the universe.
And you go back to copernicus,
where he restored the sun
in the center of
the known universe,
displacing earth.
And you get to
darwinian evolution,
and you find out we're
not special on this earth,
we're just one
among other lifeforms.
And now we learn
that we're not even
special in the entire universe
because there is Superman.
There he is. An alien among us.
We're not alone.
Are you, as a United
States Senator,
personally comfortable
saying to a grieving parent,
"Superman could
have saved your child,
"but on principle, we
did not want him to act"?
I'm not saying he shouldn't act.
I'm saying he
shouldn't act unilaterally.
What are we talking
about here, then?
Must there be a Superman?
There is.
Hello?
Mom?
Clark!
What is it?
What's wrong?
No. Nothing. I just...
Hi.
How come Dad never left Kansas?
Well, he just...
You know how he was.
"What do I need to travel for?
"I'm already there."
Just wish it was more simple.
My baby boy.
Nothing was ever simple.
An odd little duck.
Hmm!
I've never seen
a metal like this.
Could be Darpa Black Box.
Who could find out?
Nobody who'd want to.
Maybe they gave them out
to the rebels to test in theater.
Using live soldiers
as Guinea pigs?
This is what makes
you such a good reporter.
Stuff like this
still shocks you.
It don't come off!
Prisoner transfer!
You can't put me in General,
man. They gonna kill me.
Hey, you can't
bring me to General.
You should be thanking
the tax payers of Metropolis
for taking in your branded ass.
Sign here, please.
I'm marked, man.
You know what they do to
people with this on them?
He's only a criminal.
This way! Let's go!
They're gonna kill me!
- They're gonna kill me!
- Let's go!
Keefe.
You made bail.
Open two.
Who paid?
Who the hell are you?
Just a man.
Yeah? Well, what
the fuck do you want?
To help you stand for something.
Your three o'clock's here.
He made me half a man.
My wife
walked out on me.
I can't even piss standing up.
Let me face him.
You'll take care of it?
Good.
What?
Wrong room, Miss.
Secretary Swanwick,
you haven't been
returning my phone calls.
Miss Lane, if you'd
like an interview,
Major Farris is just
outside that door.
You're treating
me like a stranger?
I'm treating you
like a reporter.
All right. Is the us providing
experimental military arms
to rebels in Africa?
You know, with balls like yours,
you belong in here.
What's your source
on this? A tin foil hat?
No, not tin. But it's metal.
Fired in the Superman incident.
Experts at the
Pentagon can't ID it.
We haven't been told the truth.
Here's the truth.
A reporter got
greedy for a scoop
and went where
she shouldn't have.
Superman acted like
some rogue combatant
to rescue her, and people died.
Don't invent a conspiracy
theory to put back his Halo.
Or yours.
- Major.
- Sir.
So.
I logged into your
dropbox to find copy.
There's copy all right.
But nothing about
football. Nothing about, uh,
the friends of the
Metropolis library,
just the goddamn
Gotham Bat thing
I told you not to pursue.
If the police won't help, the
press has to do the right thing.
You don't get to decide
what the right thing is.
When the Planet was founded,
it stood for something, Perry.
And so could you if it
was 1938, but it's not 1938.
WPA ain't hiring no more.
Apples don't cost a nickel.
Not in here, not out
there. You drop this thing!
Nobody cares about Clark
Kent taking on the Batman.
So apparently Superman
doesn't want us to think of
him as American anymore.
And really, why would we?
Aside from the red
and blue costume.
And, I don't know,
the fact that he has
one-third of the USA's
initials on his chest.
I assume the only
reason he's not wearing
the declaration of
independence as a cape is...
He thinks it's too on-the-nose.
What is going on back here? No.
Guys, come on. Let's go.
Get yourselves together
and get out there.
Get those glasses
on those trays.
We got thirsty people out there.
I wonder, would you excuse us?
There's something I'd
like to show you. I'm sorry.
Now some scholars insist
that it never happened...
But I believe it's the action
perfectly in keeping with a king
who was also a psychopathic killer.
For me, it's the culmination
of 40 years curating.
And I can't believe it,
but I've finally got it here.
It's the sword of Alexander.
It's the blade that
cut the Gordian Knot.
It's a Triumph.
Yes.
- Enjoy.
- Thank you.
It's a fake.
The real one was sold
in '98 on the black market.
And now it hangs...
Over the bed of
the Sultan of Hajar.
Excuse me.
Excuse me, Miss.
The other night you took
something that doesn't belong to you.
Stealing's not polite.
Is it stealing if you
steal from another thief?
Who are you?
Someone interested in
the same man you are.
Is that right?
I believe Mr. Luthor has a
photograph that belongs to me.
Did you get it?
As it happens, no, I didn't.
The data you copied has
military-grade encryption.
You know, I bet with that dress,
9 out of 10 men will let
you get away with anything.
But you're the 10th?
I'm guessing I'm the first
to see through that
babe-in-the-woods act.
You don't know me,
but I've known a
few women like you.
Oh, I don't think you've
ever known a woman like me.
You know, it's true what
they say about little boys.
Born with no natural
inclination to share.
I didn't steal your drive.
I borrowed it.
You'll find it in the glove
compartment of your car.
Mr. Wayne.
Did you get it?
The rock?
Yeah, we got it.
I'm sorry.
Get down! Get down now!
No!
She was my world.
And you took her from me.
Bruce!
Bruce! Listen to me now!
It's Lois!
It's Lois Lane!
She's the key!
Am I too soon?
I'm too soon!
You're right about him!
You've always
been right about him!
Fear him! Fear him!
Find us, Bruce!
You have to find us!
The white Portuguese
is not a man.
It's a ship.
Master Wayne,
since the age of seven
you have been to
the art of deception
as Mozart to the harpsichord.
But you've never been
too hot at lying to me.
The white Portuguese is
not carrying a dirty bomb.
What is it carrying?
It's a weapon.
It's a rock.
A mineral capable of
weakening Kryptonian cells.
The first sample big
enough to mean something
turned up in the Indian
ocean three months ago.
It is now aboard
the white Portuguese
being delivered to Lex Luthor.
Who I am going to steal it from.
To keep it out of
Luthor's hands.
To destroy it.
No.
You're gonna go to war?
That son of a bitch brought
the war to us two years ago.
Jesus, Alfred. Count the
dead. Thousands of people.
What's next? Millions?
He has the power to wipe
out the entire human race,
and if we believe there's even a
1% chance that he is our enemy,
we have to take it as
an absolute certainty.
And we have to destroy him.
But he is not our enemy.
Not today.
20 years in Gotham, Alfred.
We've seen what
promises are worth.
How many good guys are left.
How many stayed that way.
14 hours.
My name is Clark Kent.
I'm from the Daily Planet.
I'm trying to find out what
happened to an inmate, a Santos.
I can't give out
that information.
Mommy!
Mrs. Santos?
May I ask you a few questions?
He wasn't my husband.
But I know what he did.
But he was a father.
He was that, too.
They took him out
of Gotham Central.
They moved him to Metropolis.
But inside they know.
They know the mark all
over. Guards don't care.
Bat's the judge.
One man decides who lives.
How is that justice? Talk to me.
Help me change it.
With what? Your pen?
A man like that,
words don't stop him.
You know stops him?
A fist.
Kent, I want to talk to you.
Kent!
Where does he go?
Where does he go, Jenny?
I don't... I don't know.
Clicks his heels three times,
goes back to Kansas, I suppose.
Son of a...
Turn it!
Move out!
Go, go, go, go!
No!
Where is he?
Next time they shine
your light in the sky,
don't go to it.
The Bat is dead. Bury it.
Consider this mercy.
Tell me.
Do you bleed?
You will.
I don't have a halo
over me, Mr. Secretary.
I went into the
desert, people died.
It keeps me awake. It should.
If you think that
Superman is a murderer,
then throw it away.
But I don't believe
you think that.
How do we determine what's good?
In a democracy,
good is a conversation,
not a unilateral decision.
So I urge Superman to come
to this hill of the
people tomorrow
to see those who have suffered.
The world needs to know
what happened in that desert.
And to know what he stands for.
How far will he take his power?
Does he act by our
will or by his own?
People hate what
they don't understand.
But they see what you do,
and they know who you are.
You're not a killer, a threat.
I never wanted this
world to have you.
Be their hero, Clark.
Be their monument.
Be their angel.
Be anything they need you to be.
Or be none of it.
You don't owe
this world a thing.
You never did.
This is Deniros. Transfer
available to Kane Avenue.
Please, mind your step.
I have to speak to
the Senator today.
You cannot see
I need to speak to
her before the hearing.
Do you understand
how important this is?
I cannot let you
see the Senator.
Please, I need to speak to her.
Please, Madam. I beg of
you! Please don't do this!
This is so important!
Come with me. Don't touch me!
Please! I'm sorry.
She wouldn't leave.
I didn't tell you the truth.
C.I. Thinks the
desert was a setup.
Somebody wanted
Superman to look guilty.
The bullet?
The metal was developed
by a private company.
What company?
LexCorp.
Lex Luthor?
He also had private security
contractors at the desert compound.
Go on record.
Not a chance. It's classified.
I happen to like my job.
It doesn't make sense.
You said that the ambush was
arranged to frame Superman,
but how could they know
that he'd show up in the...
In the middle of the
desert. Thank you.
The Senate hearing is expected
to get underway any minute now.
And of course the big
unknown in all of this is
will Superman show up?
That is what they're
really waiting to see.
Mr. Keefe. Mr. Keefe.
Soledad o'Brien, in the Moment.
Quick question for you.
You're heading in to
meet with the Senators.
What will you tell them?
I've come here to
tell them to wake up.
This is flesh and blood.
He has delivered a war here.
And this...
This is what war looks like.
I have nothing.
There are plenty of people, sir,
who would say he's their hero.
He is not a hero.
Grace, can you get
Greg up here, please?
Right now.
An anonymous source
can verify everything
I told you about what
happened in Nairomi.
An anonymous source? Run it.
Luthor engineered the desert.
It was an ambush for Superman.
Trust your reporter.
Think Watergate.
Yeah, and you
need to think litigate.
If you're wrong, Luthor will
sue the paper out of existence.
You need proof.
No. It needs to run now.
Before the hearing.
If Superman knows, it
might change what he says.
I am not going to risk the paper
so that you can
pass notes in class
to the man that rescued you.
McGraw: He paid her?
Not only paid her.
He threatened her.
Gave her a script to learn.
Her parents are alive back home.
But the girl's got a conscience.
He's been using the committee
as his puppet theater. Senator!
Hi, you.
Don't go anywhere.
I want to talk to you.
Uh, you know what?
Mercy, you go in
and make sure no
one takes my seat.
So what you been up to?
I'm just here to tell my story.
That I was willing to finance
a Kryptonian deterrent,
but a certain junior
Senator from Kentucky
decided to block it.
Yes, the chair of the committee
on Superman is soft on security.
Greg, why hasn't he been getting
our checks? He is, Mr. Wayne.
He gets a check from the
victims fund every month.
He returns them.
...who lost both his legs
in those horrific
events in Metropolis
that happened two years ago.
Jesus.
Why haven't I seen this?
I'm sorry. I'll get
to the bottom of it.
And there he is.
Superman is here.
He is actually at the
United States Capitol.
This is really a
historic moment.
Now we expect that
Superman will give
some kind of a
statement to the Senate,
to the American people,
and, of course, to the world.
He's here. He came.
He's above the Capitol. Ah.
You are gonna be on the
hot seat in there, Junebug.
I grew up on a farm.
I know how to wrestle a pig.
Do you know the oldest
lie in America, Senator?
It's that power can be innocent.
Good luck.
Oh, Miss...
Rudy, she's good to go.
Get out!
Get out! Get out!
Superman! Superman!
Another one came this
morning, Mr. Wayne.
Let me say at the outset
that I'm grateful to our witness
for coming before us today.
This is how a democracy works.
We talk to each other.
We act by the consent
of the governed, sir.
I have sat here before to
say that shadow interventions
will not be tolerated
by this committee.
Neither will lies.
Because today
is a day for truth.
Because only by speaking...
Only by working
together can we...
Can we...
Can we create a free, and a...
Oh, my God!
We're back at the
Nation's Capitol,
where something is happening.
Excuse me.
Excuse me, officer.
Member of the press.
Can you let me in, please?
Breathe slowly and deeply.
You're gonna be fine.
Thank you. I'm gonna
need a little room to work.
Ma'am, it appears you've
suffered a head injury.
I'm gonna need you to
follow my light with your eyes.
Master Wayne.
Mr. Wayne!
...in the Senate hearing room
where Superman was testifying.
This is a catastrophic
situation at our Nation's Capitol.
We don't have exact numbers yet,
but I can tell you that
more than a dozen people
have died in this explosion.
First responders
are at the scene.
They are still
bringing victims out.
Now initially, Superman was
helping bring victims out after the blast
but he seems to
have disappeared...
...raising questions.
Carrie Birmingham, reporting
live from the Nation's Capital.
Capitol police are now confirming
that the blast was caused
by an explosive device
inside the hearing room.
Run that one more time for me.
Can you enhance
that? There you go, sir.
Capitol police are
confirming to CNN
that the suspected bomber is.
Wallace Vernon Keefe.
Now these sources...
Clark, it's me again. Can you...
...could have gotten the
explosive device into the hearing
by concealing them
inside his wheelchair.
As for Superman,
he was in the room,
but obviously
failed to stop him.
I didn't see it, lo.
I was standing right
there and I didn't see it.
Clark, there are
people behind this.
I'm afraid I didn't see it
because I wasn't looking.
All this time,
I've been living my life
the way my father saw it.
Righting wrongs for a ghost.
Thinking I'm here to do good.
Superman was never real.
Just the dream of a
farmer from Kansas.
That farmer's dream
is all some people have.
It's all that gives them hope.
This means something.
It did on my world.
My world doesn't exist anymore.
Welcome.
Analysis reveals ship
operating at 37% efficiency.
Would you like to
assume command?
Yes, I would.
Very well. Let's begin.
The Kryptonian archive contains
knowledge from 100,000 different worlds.
Good.
Teach me.
Alexander Luthor,
your security override
has been accepted.
Genesis chamber ready
to analyze genetic sample.
Acknowledging presence
of genetic material.
Analyzing.
I've identified the host
as General Zod of Kandor.
Acknowledging presence
of foreign genetic material.
Analyzing.
You flew too close to the sun.
Now look at you.
Advising. Action forbidden.
It has been decreed
by the council of Krypton
that none will ever again
give life to a deformity
so hateful to sight and memory.
The desecration without name.
And where is the
council of Krypton?
Destroyed, sir.
Then proceed.
Very well. Preparing chrysalis
and commencing metamorphosis.
"And so we are left to wonder
"if Superman was aware
of the threat and did nothing,
"was he then complicit
in the capitol tragedy?"
Still no Kent?
"His disappearance
raises questions."
No.
There are still so many
unanswered questions.
Chief among them, whether
Superman was involved
in the planning of this attack.
I mean, here's an individual
who has unlimited power,
yet did nothing to stop the bomber
just a few feet away from him.
It just doesn't add
up for investigators.
Burn him, burn him, burn him.
For twenty American,
he didn't see you.
Same for me.
Now one FBI official
familiar with this case
told me they found quote,
"a jackpot of bomb-making
materials inside Keefe's apartment."
What they need
to determine now is
whether he had any help in the
planning and execution of the bombing.
And they haven't
ruled out the idea
that Superman was
a co-conspirator.
Now, my sources are
telling me they are getting
a barrage of anonymous
and credible tips
with all roads in
this investigation
leading to the
Kryptonian visitor.
All right, Lois. You gotta go.
He didn't know he was gonna die.
He just bought groceries.
The wheelchair and
the bullet from the desert
were made from the same metal.
I know. The desert. The hearing.
Everywhere Superman
goes, Luthor wants death.
But, Luthor goes
through all of that trouble...
Creates a bomb
out of a wheelchair,
and then alters it
to reduce the blast?
What do you mean?
The inside of the chair
was lined with lead.
You couldn't stop it.
You couldn't see it.
Something, isn't it?
We men of Kansas
live on a pancake,
so we come to the mountains.
All downhill from here,
down to the floodplain.
Farm at the bottom of the world.
I remember one season
the water came bad.
I couldn't have been 12.
Dad had out the shovels
and we went at it all night.
We worked till,
I think, I fainted.
But we managed
to stop the water.
We saved the farm.
Your grandma baked me
a cake. Said I was a hero.
Later that day we found out
we blocked the water all right.
We sent it upstream.
The whole lang farm washed away.
While I ate my hero cake,
their horses were drowning.
I used to hear them
wailing in my sleep.
Did the nightmares ever stop?
Yeah.
When I met your mother.
She gave me faith that
there's good in this world.
She was my world.
I miss you, son.
I miss you too, Dad.
You know you can't win this.
It's suicide.
I'm older now than
my father ever was.
This may be the only
thing I do that matters.
20 years of fighting
criminals amounts to nothing?
Criminals are
like weeds, Alfred.
Pull one up, another
grows in its place.
This is about the
future of the world.
This is my legacy.
My father sat me
down right here.
Told me what Wayne
manor was built on.
Railroads, real
estates, and oil.
The first generation made their
fortune trading with the French.
Pelts and skins.
They were hunters.
So falls the house of Wayne.
We gotta wait for more evidence,
but the question still remains,
where is he?
If Superman was not involved,
if he's got nothing to hide,
then why hasn't he been seen
since the day of this tragedy?
You can't point a finger and...
I'm not pointing anything,
Warren. Look. Ten fingers, see?
If there is going
to be a criminal...
The night is here.
Excuse me.
Don't I know...
Plain lo in the
morning. Lola in slacks.
Lois Lane.
Mmm. Come see the view.
Um...
Mmm-mmm.
Now the secret to the height
is the building material.
It's light metals which
sway a bit in the wind.
Hmm.
And you know something about
LexCorp metals, don't you, Miss Lane?
I've proven what you've done.
Wow, you're feisty.
Unfortunately,
that will blow away.
Like sand in the desert.
You're psychotic.
That is a three-syllable word
for any thought too
big for little minds.
Hmm. Next category: Circles.
Round and round and round
they go to find Superman.
Wrong category,
boy. No, no, triangles.
Yes, Euclid's
triangle inequality.
The shortest distance
between any two points
is a straight path.
And I believe the
straightest path to Superman
is a pretty little road...
Mmm. Called Lois Lane.
You came back.
Boy, do we have
problems up here!
The problem of...
of evil in the world.
Uh, the problem
of absolute virtue.
I'll take you in
without breaking you.
Which is more than you deserve.
The problem of you on
top of everything else.
You above all.
Ah, because that's what God is.
Horus. Apollo. Jehovah. Kal-El.
Clark Joseph Kent.
See, what we call God depends
upon our tribe, Clark-Joe.
Because God is
tribal. God takes sides.
No man in the sky
intervened when I was a boy
to deliver me from Daddy's
fist and abominations. Mmm.
I figured out way back,
if God is all-powerful,
he cannot be all-good.
And if he is all-good,
then he cannot be all-powerful.
And neither can you be.
They need to see
the fraud you are.
With their eyes.
The blood on your hands.
What have you done?
Hmm. And tonight, they will.
Yes. Because you, my
friend, have a date. Hmm.
Across the bay.
Ripe fruit, his hate.
Two years growing.
But it did not take much
to push him over, actually.
Little red notes, big bang.
You let your family die!
And now you will fly to
him. And you will battle him.
To the death.
Black and blue. Fight night!
The greatest gladiator match
in the history of the world.
God versus man.
Day versus night.
Son of Krypton
versus Bat of Gotham.
You think I'll
fight him for you?
Hmm, yes, I do. I think
you will fight-fight-fight
for that special
lady in your life.
She's safe on the
ground. How about you?
Close, but I am not
talking about Lois.
No. Every boy's special
lady is his mother.
Martha, Martha, Martha.
Hmm.
Why, the mother of a flying
demon must be a witch.
The punishment for
witches, what is that?
That's right. Death by fire.
Mmm.
Where is she?
I don't know! I would
not let them tell me!
Uh-uh-uh! If you
kill me, Martha dies.
And if you fly away,
mmm, Martha also dies.
But if you kill the bat...
Martha lives.
There we go. There we go. Hmm.
And now God bends to my will.
Ooh, now the cameras
are waiting at your ship.
For the world to see
the holes in the Holy.
Yes, the almighty comes clean
about how dirty he
is when it counts.
To save Martha,
bring me the head of the Bat.
Ah.
Mother of God, would
you look at the time?
When you came
here, you had an hour.
Now it's less.
Brooke Baldwin is on the scene.
Brooke, you're live on the
air. What are you seeing?
There's something
happening at the ship.
It's sending massive
power surges.
Police helicopters
surrounding the area.
They've created a barricade
around this containment center.
And we're trying to
get a little bit closer here
to find out what's going on.
It is absolute chaos.
You can see that lightning,
those surges of electricity.
They seem to be getting
stronger by the minute.
Daily Planet.
Lois. I have to go to Gotham
to convince him to help me.
Who?
Or he has to die.
Clark.
No one stays good in this world.
But as of right now, much of the
city remains in the dark tonight.
Much chaos. Much confusing happening
on the streets of Metropolis tonight.
Those helicopters are
still surrounding the area.
I don't know if you can still
see those bolts of lightning...
2400 hours and 2 minutes.
Subject declining rapidly.
All procedural
interventions have failed.
Outcome
will be death.
Dr. Silas stone suspending
all clinical protocol.
US gov, object 6-19-82
is successfully activated.
I need a chopper to Gotham.
Call the heliport.
Chopper? We can
barely afford a bicycle.
You wanna chase a story?
Go to the ship.
Superman's probably
there already.
Perry, it's not for a story.
Jenny, get her a
chopper to Gotham.
And forget the heliport.
Put it on the Goddamn roof.
On the roof, Lois!
Where are we headed?
There!
Well, here I am.
Bruce. Please.
I was wrong. You
have to listen to me.
Lex wants us to...
You don't understand.
There's no time!
I understand.
Stay down!
If I wanted it, you'd
be dead already.
Breathe it in.
That's fear.
You're not brave.
Men are brave.
I bet your parents taught
you that you mean something.
That you're here for a reason.
My parents taught
me a different lesson,
dying in the gutter
for no reason at all.
They taught me the
world only makes sense
if you force it to.
You were never a God.
You were never even a man.
You're letting him kill Martha.
What does that mean?
Why did you say that name?
Find him.
Save.
Martha.
Why did you say that name?
Martha! Why did
you say that name?
Clark! Stop!
Please! Stop!
Why did you say that name?
It's his mother's name!
It's his mother's name.
We're not getting any answers.
We're still right outside
the containment center.
A dangerous situation.
Military and police personnel
surrounding the area.
Luthor.
He wanted your life for hers.
She's losing time.
The scout ship seems to be
drawing power from the city.
It's got to be Lex.
They need you at
that ship. I'll find her.
My mother needs me. Wait.
I'll make you a promise.
Martha won't die tonight.
Master Wayne.
Alfred.
Uh, I'm sorry for listening in,
but I've tracked
the Russian's phone
to a warehouse near the port.
You're locked onto it.
I don't deserve you, Alfred.
No, sir. You don't.
I'm afraid this is goodbye.
And every time we say
goodbye, you die a little.
- Take it down.
- Go! Go!
You have to take it, Alfred.
Ah, right.
Commencing drone mode.
Thermal imaging is showing me
two dozen hostiles
on the third floor.
Why don't I drop you
off on the second?
Drop it.
I said drop it!
I'll kill her.
Believe me, I'll do it.
I believe you.
It's okay. I'm a
friend of your son's.
I figured. The cape.
"Late, late," says
the white rabbit.
40 seconds to animation.
Right, wabbit?
Hmm. Out of tricks, out of time.
And one Bat head short.
30 seconds to animation.
Ah. That'll be the cook.
Excuse me.
Uh, Gotham roast. Well done.
Hello. Break the bad news.
I'd rather do the
breaking in person.
20 seconds to animation.
You've lost.
I don't know how to lose.
You'll learn.
I'll learn.
I don't hate the sinner.
- I hate the sin.
- 10 seconds to animation.
And yours, my
friend, is existing.
I cannot let you win.
I gave the bat a
fighting chance to do it,
but he was not strong enough.
So, if man won't kill God...
...two, one.
...the Devil will do it!
Perry!
All right. Stay calm, everybody!
We're getting reports
there are total blackouts
in the north and to the
northwest of the city.
Federal authorities
are trying to determine
if this is part of a
larger terrorist attack.
Ancient Kryptonian deformity.
Hmm. Blood of my blood.
Born to destroy you.
Your Doomsday.
Now God is good
as dead.
Oh!
Potus joining.
Mr. President.
What the hell is it, Calvin?
These are live
images from the top
of the LexCorp tower
in downtown Metropolis.
Military aircraft
are on the scene.
Are you hurt, Ma'am? I'm okay.
Good. You're gonna
be all right, okay?
This thing emerged from
the Kryptonian crash site
just moments ago.
Thankfully though,
the work day is over
in the downtown
core. It's nearly empty.
Now military aircraft. Those
are apache helicopters.
They have now just
arrived. The images that...
We've, uh... We just lost
connection with Metropolis 8 news.
Now, it's not clear
what just happened.
What's happening there, Alfred?
How best to describe it?
Metropolis airspace
has been closed briefly.
Excuse me?
We kindly ask that
you stay in your seats.
Excuse me?
Miss Prince?
Sir. Look, they've
cleared the city.
Looks like he's
taking it into space.
We can go straight to
key red, Mr. President.
Not yet. Are you crazy?
They're high enough
that we can nuke 'em
with no casualties, sir.
One casualty,
Mr. President. Superman.
God have mercy on us all.
Key is hot. Key is hot.
Red birds are
armed to deploy, sir.
Fire at will.
Three, two, one...
Oh, God.
Projectile 1. Impact.
Stryker's island,
east of Metropolis.
That's uninhabited.
Projectile 2...
No apparent reentry.
Projectile 2?
Superman, Mr. President.
Projectile 2 was Superman.
Sir.
It's moving.
The shockwaves
are getting stronger.
Every time we hit it, we
make it more powerful.
We can't attack.
What are you saying, Calvin?
I'm saying it's unkillable.
Master Wayne, are
you receiving me?
Alfred.
It's Kryptonian.
Only kryptonite
weapons can kill it.
They might. If you had any left.
I got one round left.
The spear. Alfred, the
spear. It's pure kryptonite.
It's back in Gotham.
If I can penetrate the
skin, the spear will kill it.
It would in theory.
I've gotta get it to chase
me back to the city.
Back to the kryptonite.
Oh, shit.
Why did you bring
him back to the city?
The port is abandoned.
There's a weapon
here that can kill it.
Did you find the spear?
I've been a little busy.
This thing, this creature,
seems to feed on energy.
This thing is from
another world.
My world.
I've killed things from
other worlds before.
Is she with you?
I thought she was with you.
Clark!
Clark! Are you all right?
I love you.
No. No, Clark, you can't.
This is my world.
No, Clark, don't.
You are my world.
No.
Please. Clark!
Hi.
Clark had this sent here,
so he could surprise you.
"The dead shall live.
"My slain shall rise again.
"Awake and sing,
ye that dwell in dust.
"For thy dew is like
the dew of morning.
"And the earth shall
give birth to her dead."
Ah, I need a ride
back to the house.
I forgot my checkbook
to pay the funeral director.
They said it's
all taken care of.
By whom?
Anonymous donor.
All those circuses back
east burying an empty box.
They don't know
how to honor him,
except as a soldier.
I've failed him in life.
I won't fail him in death.
Help me find the
others like you.
Perhaps they don't
want to be found.
They will. And they'll fight.
We have to stand together.
100 years ago, I walked
away from mankind.
From a century of horrors.
Man made a world where
standing together is impossible.
Men are still good.
We fight. We kill.
We betray one another.
But we can rebuild.
We can do better.
We will.
We have to.
The others like me.
Why did you say
they'll have to fight?
Just a feeling.
Prisoner A-C-23-19-40.
The Warden wants to speak
to you, so stand to your feet.
I'm gonna say
this one more time.
The Warden wants to speak
to you, so stand to your feet.
Turn around and face the wall.
Place your forehead
against the wall.
Put your hands behind your back,
so that I can come
in and restrain you.
Whatever you do,
wherever you go,
I'll be watching you.
Oh...
Look at us.
This is how it all caves in.
Civilization on the Wayne
manor's out the window.
Mmm?
But who would believe me? I...
I'm insane.
I'm not even fit to stand trial.
That's right.
We have hospitals that treat
the mentally ill with compassion.
But that's not
where you're going.
I arranged for you to get transferred
to Arkham Asylum in Gotham.
I still have some friends there.
They're expecting you.
But the bell's
already been rung.
And they've heard it.
Out in the dark.
Among the stars. Hmm.
Ding dong, the God is dead.
But a bell cannot be unrung!
He's hungry. He's found us.
And he's coming!
Ding, ding, ding, ding,
ding, ding, ding, ding, ding.
Ding, ding, ding, ding, ding.
Ding, ding, ding, ding,
ding, ding, ding, ding, ding.
Improved by KID
Resynced by KID
Enjoy the movie(s) / show(s)