ISN'T THIS GREAT?
DON'T WORRY ABOUT A THING.
COME ON.
I'LL GET IT.
THANK YOU. HI.
I'D LIKE TO GO
TO THE ADELPHI HOTEL.
I'M SORRY.
THIS IS MY CAB.
SORRY.
TOUGH LUCK.
LISTEN, I WAS
HERE FIRST!
OH, GOD.
UH...OH, TAXI!
TAXI!
[HORN HONKS]
HEY!
LET'S GO ACROSS.
COME ON.
WE'LL GET ONE
DOWN THE ROAD.
COME ON, HONEY.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
FOR GOD'S SAKE,
HAROLD,
CAN WE JUST
GET A TAXI?
I'M TRYING
TO GET A--TAXI!
WE'RE GOING
THE WRONG WAY.
JIMMY,
PUT THAT AWAY.
WE'LL LOOK
LIKE TOURISTS.
HI, HONEY.
LET'S CUT OVER
TO 7th.
7th IS THAT WAY.
I KNOW WHERE WE ARE.
HEY, MISTER,
GIVE ME A DOLLAR.
COME ON.
HOW ABOUT IT?
ONE DOLLAR.
WHAT ARE YOU, DEAF?
DON'T SPEAK ENGLISH?
COME ON.
COME ON! UP HERE.
AAH!
HEY, LADY.
DO THE KID A FAVOR.
DON'T SCREAM.
AAH!
HEY, ALL RIGHT.
AMERICAN
EXPRESS CARD.
DON'T LEAVE HOME
WITHOUT IT.
HEY,
GET OUT OF HERE.
[SIREN]
LET'S BEAT IT, MAN.
I DON'T LIKE IT
UP HERE.
WHAT ARE YOU,
SCARED OF HEIGHTS?
I DON'T KNOW.
AFTER WHAT HAPPENED
TO JOHNNY GOBS--
LOOK, JOHNNY GOBS
GOT RIPPED
AND WALKED OFF A ROOF.
NO BIG LOSS.
NO, MAN. THAT AIN'T
WHAT I HEARD AT ALL.
I HEARD THAT
THE BAT GOT HIM.
THE BAT?
AW, MAN,
GIVE ME A BREAK.
FIVE STORIES
STRAIGHT DOWN.
THERE WASN'T
NO BLOOD
IN THE BODY.
IT WAS ALL OVER
THE PAVEMENT.
I'M GETTING
OUT OF HERE, MAN.
SHUT UP, MAN.
LISTEN.
THERE AIN'T
NO BAT.
WELL, YOU SHOULDN'T
HAVE TURNED THE GUN
ON THAT KID.
HEY! YOU WANT
YOUR CUT OR NOT?
NOW SHUT UP.
SHUT...UP.
[RUSTLING]
AAH!
OH, GOD.
DON'T KILL ME!
DON'T KILL ME, MAN!
I'M NOT GOING
TO KILL YOU.
I NEED A FAVOR.
TELL YOUR FRIENDS
ABOUT ME.
WHAT ARE YOU?
I'M BATMAN.
AAH!
[SIREN]
ACROSS THIS NATION,
THE WORDS "GOTHAM CITY"
ARE SYNONYMOUS
WITH CRIME.
OUR STREETS ARE OVERRUN,
OUR PUBLIC OFFICIALS
ARE HELPLESS.
AS MAYOR, I PROMISE
TO ROOT OUT
THE SOURCE
OF THIS CORRUPTION,
BOSS CARL GRISSOM.
NOW, OUR NEW
DISTRICT ATTORNEY
HARVEY DENT
WILL CARRY OUT
THAT PROMISE.
HARVEY?
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU, MAYOR BORG.
PEOPLE OF GOTHAM CITY,
I'M A MAN OF FEW WORDS,
BUT THOSE WORDS
WILL COUNT,
AND SO WILL
MY ACTIONS.
POLICE COMMISSIONER GORDON
HAS INFORMED ME
THAT HE HAS TARGETED
THOSE BUSINESSES
SUSPECTED OF FRONTING
FOR THE SYNDICATE
IN THIS CITY.
BEFORE THE WEEK IS OUT,
WE ARE GOING
TO KNOCK DOWN THEIR DOORS
AND SHED THE LIGHT
OF THE LAW
ON THAT NEST
OF VIPERS.
[APPLAUSE]
TOGETHER, WE CAN
MAKE THIS CITY SAFE
FOR DECENT PEOPLE.
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
DECENT PEOPLE
SHOULDN'T LIVE HERE.
THEY'D BE HAPPIER
SOMEPLACE ELSE.
PRETTY TOUGH TALK
ABOUT CARL.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
IF THIS CLOWN
COULD TOUCH GRISSOM,
I'D HAVE HANDED HIM
HIS LUNGS BY NOW.
IF GRISSOM
KNEW ABOUT US,
HE MIGHT HAND
YOUSOMETHING.
DON'T FLATTER
YOURSELF, ANGEL.
HE'S A TIRED OLD MAN.
HE CAN'T RUN THIS CITY
WITHOUT ME.
AND BESIDES...
HE DOESN'T KNOW.
YOU DON'T WORRY
ABOUT ANYTHING,
DO YOU, JACK?
YOU LOOK FINE.
I DIDN'T ASK.
YEAH, YEAH.
HANGING ON,
HANGING ON.
COMING THROUGH.
OHH, OH, OH.
NO, NO. LET ME GUESS.
GIANT, MENACING,
SUPERNATURAL FORM.
KIND OF LIKE A BAT.
THAT'S IT.
WHAT ARE THEY
SEEING UP THERE?
AHH, THEY'RE
DRINKING DRANO.
IT'S A LITTLE WEIRD,
LIEUTENANT.
THANKS FOR THE TIP,
DUANE.
EHH... KNOX.
HELLO, ECKHARDT.
I HEAR WE HAD
ANOTHER BAT ATTACK.
THAT'S, WHAT,
EIGHT SIGHTINGS
IN UNDER A MONTH?
THE COMMISSIONER'S
EVEN OPENED A FILE.
TRUE?
SORRY, KNOX.
THESE TWO SLIPPED
ON A BANANA PEEL.
I'M TELLING
YOU, MAN,
A GIANT BAT!
SURE YOU DID.
KEEP MOVING.
DON'T BE WRITING
THIS STUFF, KNOX.
IT'LL RUIN YOUR ALREADY
USELESS REPUTATION.
LIEUTENANT,
EVERY PUNK IN THIS TOWN
IS SCARED STIFF.
YOU KNOW
WHAT THEY SAY?
THEY SAY
HE CAN'T BE KILLED,
THAT HE DRINKS BLOOD--
I SAY YOU'RE
FULL OF STUFF, KNOX.
OH, UH...
YOU CAN QUOTE ME
ON THAT.
LIEUTENANT, IS THERE
A 6-FOOT BAT
IN GOTHAM CITY?
IS HE ON
THE POLICE PAYROLL?
W-WHAT'S HE PULLING DOWN,
AFTER TAXES?
BROUGHT YOU
A LITTLE SNACK,
ECKHARDT.
WHY DON'T YOU
BROADCAST IT?
SHUT UP
AND LISTEN.
HARVEY DENT'S
BEEN SNIFFING AROUND
ONE OF OUR
FRONT COMPANIES.
THAT'S MY TERRITORY.
IF THERE'S A PROBLEM,
I DEAL WITH IT.
YOUR PROBLEMS
ARE OUR PROBLEMS.
I ANSWER TO GRISSOM,
NOT TO PSYCHOS.
WHY, ECKHARDT,
YOU OUGHT TO THINK
ABOUT THE FUTURE.
OH, WHEN YOU
RUN THE SHOW?
YOU AIN'T GOT
NO FUTURE, JACK.
YOU'RE AN A-1
NUT BOY,
AND GRISSOM KNOWS IT.
BETTER BE SURE.
SEE?
YOU CAN MAKE
A GOOD DECISION
WHEN YOU TRY.
WHERE YOU BEEN
SPENDING YOURNIGHTS?
I DON'T CARE
HOW DEEPLY IN DEBT
THIS FESTIVAL IS.
I WANT A PARADE.
I WANT HOT DOGS,
BALLOONS,
THE WHOLE SCHMEER.
WE'LL CELEBRATE
THIS 200th ANNIVERSARY
PROUDLY AND PUBLICLY.
THIS FESTIVAL
IS $250,000 IN THE RED,
AND WE HAVEN'T SEEN
ONE BALLOON.
FILL THIS SQUARE
WITH PEOPLE.
THE BUSINESSES
WILL COME BACK.
A LOT OF PEOPLE
MIGHT STAY AWAY.
THEY'RE SCARED.
THEY WON'T BE SCARED
WHEN GRISSOM'S
IN THAT COURTHOUSE.
I PROMISED THAT,
REMEMBER?
WELL, WELCOME,
COUNT DRACULA.
HAD ANY SIGHTINGS
OF BIGFOOT LATELY?
AFRAID NOT.
THEY BURIED YOUR STORY
ON BATMAN.
THAT'S
WHAT HAPPENS
TO GARBAGE.
THIS IS PULITZER PRIZE
STUFF, GUYS.
HEY, KNOX,
I GOT SOMETHING
FOR YOU.
VERY FUNNY.
YOU SHOULD'VE HAD MORE GORE
UNDER THE FANGS, THOUGH.
WHAT A...
HELLO, LEGS.
I'M READING
YOUR STUFF.
WELL, I'M
READING YOURS.
HI. I'M VICKI VALE.
VICKI VALE.
YEAH, YEAH.
PHOTOGRAPHER.
VOGUE, COSMO.
IF YOU WANT ME
TO POSE NUDE,
YOU'LL NEED
A LONG LENS.
ACTUALLY, I WAS IN
THE CORTO MALTESE.
A GIRL COULD GET HURT
DOING THIS STUFF.
SO, UH, WHAT
BRINGS YOU HERE?
I'M HERE TO SEE
SOME WILDLIFE
IN GOTHAM CITY.
WILDLIFE?
LIKE WHAT?
LIKE...BATS.
WHO SENT YOU?
NO, NOBODY.
REALLY.
I JUST LOVED
YOUR STORY.
AND I--I...
I LIKE...BATS.
YEAH?
MY PICTURES,
YOUR WORDS--
PULITZER PRIZE
MATERIAL.
JUST THINK--
O.K. YOU'RE A VISIONARY.
YOU'RE ALSO THE ONLY ONE
WHO BELIEVES ME.
I NEED SOMETHING
TANGIBLE.
GORDON'S GOT
A FILE ON THIS.
I CAN'T EVEN GET HIM
ON THE PHONE.
BRUCE WAYNE'S BENEFIT--
HE'LL BE THERE?
YEAH, YEAH.
I DON'T SEEM TO BE
ON THE GUEST LIST.
NO...NO.
YES. YES.
VALE, WILL YOU
MARRY ME?
NOPE.
WILL YOU
BUY ME LUNCH?
MAYBE.
I EAT LIGHT.
SAY THIS...
SON OF A--
MAKES A CONNECTION
WITH US
AND WITH AXIS CHEMICALS.
WHAT KIND OF DAMAGE
ARE WE LOOKING AT?
IF HE TIES US IN
WITH AXIS CHEMICAL,
WE'RE DEAD AND BURIED.
WE SHOULD MOVE
IMMEDIATELY.
I SAY WE BREAK
INTO THE PLACE,
TRASH THE OFFICE,
AND MAKE OFF
WITH THE RECORDS
AND SAY
IT WAS INDUSTRIAL
ESPIONAGE.
JACK...SMART THINKING.
THAT'S THE WAY TO GO,
IN FACT.
I'D LIKE YOU TO HANDLE
THIS OPERATION PERSONALLY.
ME?
HELLO, SWEETHEART.
I WONDER IF
YOU'D MIND WAITING
IN THE NEXT ROOM?
THAT'S ALL, GENTLEMEN.
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU, GENTLEMEN.
CARL, UH...
CAN WE GET SOMEBODY
ELSE TO DO THIS?
I MEAN, THE FUMES
IN THAT PLACE...
JACK...
IT'S AN IMPORTANT JOB.
I NEED...
SOMEONE I CAN TRUST.
YOU ARE
MY NUMBER ONE GUY.
NOW...
DON'T FORGET...
YOUR LUCKY DECK.
MY FRIEND...
YOUR LUCK
IS ABOUT TO CHANGE.
POLICE
DEPARTMENT.
GET ME LIEUTENANT ECKHARDT.
CAN I HELP YOU,
SIR?
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THAT'S VERY NICE
OF YOU.
HOLD ON.
HERE YOU GO.
GOOD EVENING,
MA'AM.
A LITTLE CROWDED.
EXCUSE ME.
COULD YOU TELL ME
WHICH GUY IS BRUCE WAYNE?
WELL, I'M NOT SURE.
THANKS ANYWAY.
YEAH.
HUH? OH, CERTAINLY.
YOUR ROLL,
COMMISSIONER.
THANK YOU.
HERE WE GO.
8. 8!
I CAN MAKE THAT 8.
PLACE YOUR BETS,
PLEASE.
COMMISSIONER!
MRS. GORDON,
YOU LOOK LOVELY.
IS IT TRUE
THE COMMISSIONER HAS
A FILE ON THE BATMAN?
THERE IS NO BAT.
IF THERE WERE,
WE WOULD ARREST HIM.
WOULD YOU CONFIRM HIM?
HOW YOU
MAKING OUT?
NO GOOD AT ALL.
MR. DENT,
I LOVE THAT TIE.
GORDO AND I
WERE DISCUSSING
WINGED VIGILANTES.
WHAT'S YOUR STAND?
MR. KNOX, WE HAVE ENOUGH
PROBLEMS IN THIS CITY
WITHOUT WORRYING
ABOUT GHOSTS AND GOBLINS.
THAT'S NOT A DENIAL.
EXCUSE ME, DEAR.
I'LL BE BACK.
WON'T ANYBODY
GO ON RECORD?
UH, YOUR HONOR,
GREAT SUIT.
NO COMMENT.
ROBERT, WHAT'S UP?
ANONYMOUS TIP.
NAPIER'S CLEANING OUT
AXIS CHEMICALS.
IT'S FUNNY
THAT THE OWNERS
NEVER...
WHY WASN'T I TOLD?
WHO'S IN CHARGE?
ECKHARDT, SIR.
OH, MY GOD.
COME ON, LET'S GO.
COMMISSIONER GORDON.
HEY.
OOH HOO HOO!
WAIT A MINUTE.
LIVING ROOM,
DINING ROOM, ARSENAL.
LOOK AT THIS STUFF.
WHO IS THIS GUY?
HE GIVES TO ALL THESE
HUMANITARIAN CAUSES
AND THEN COLLECTS
ALL THIS STUFF.
HE PROBABLY DOES IT
TO GET CHICKS.
THEY LIKE HIM FOR
HIS BIG CHARITY BALLS.
YEAH, AND DON'T
LEAVE OUT HIS VERY
LARGE BANKROLL.
REMEMBER,
THE MORE THEY'VE GOT,
THE LESS THEY'RE WORTH.
THEN THIS GUY
MUST BE
THE MOST WORTHLESS
GUY IN AMERICA.
CHECK THIS OUT.
HE MUST HAVE BEEN
KING OF THE WICKER PEOPLE.
OH, OH,
WHERE'D THIS COME FROM?
I HAVE NO IDEA.
IT'S JAPANESE.
HOW DO YOU KNOW?
BECAUSE I BOUGHT IT
IN JAPAN.
WHO ARE YOU?
OH, SORRY.
BRUCE WAYNE.
ALEXANDER KNOX.
HI.
I READ YOUR WORK.
I LIKE IT.
OH, THANKS.
CAN I HAVE A GRANT?
VICKI VALE.
HI. BRUCE WAYNE.
ARE YOU SURE?
YEAH. THIS TIME.
I'VE SEEN
YOUR PHOTOGRAPHS
FROM CORTO MALTESE,
HAVEN'T I?
RIGHT.
YEAH, YOU'VE GOT
A WONDERFUL EYE.
SOME PEOPLE
THINK SHE HAS TWO.
THIS IS
AN AMAZING HOUSE.
I'D LIKE TO
SHOOT IT SOMETIME,
IF YOU--
MR. WAYNE,
WE NEED TO OPEN
MORE CASES
OF CHAMPAGNE.
WILL THAT BE ALL RIGHT?
OH, SURE, GO AHEAD.
OH, UH, OPEN,
WHAT--SIX? SIX?
YEAH. YEAH,
SIX IS GOOD.
O.K. YEAH.
THAT'S GREAT.
SIX. THANKS.
ARE YOU GOING TO BE
STAYING IN GOTHAM A WHILE?
I--I'D LOVE TO.
I'M INTRIGUED
BY ALEX'S GIANT
BAT STORIES,
SO I'VE DONE SOME--
OH, THE, UH, RIGHT.
BAT--THE BATMAN.
HMM. THE...YEAH.
THAT'S LIGHT AFTER THE WAR
IN CORTO MALTESE, ISN'T IT?
WHAT DO YOU DO
FOR A LIVING?
WELL, I'M INVOLVED--
SIR, COMMISSIONER GORDON
WAS COMPELLED TO LEAVE.
OH, O.K.
THANK YOU.
VERY UNEXPECTEDLY,
SIR.
WILL YOU TWO
EXCUSE ME?
UH, I--I THINK
PERHAPS THIS WAY, SIR.
OH, RIGHT.
ALFRED, THEY NEED WINE
IN THE FRONT ROOM,
AND SOMEONE
NAMED MRS. DALY
NEEDS A COPY
OF THE MENU.
OH, AND, UH,
GIVE KNOX A GRANT.
NICE TALKING
WITH YOU, WAYNE.
OH, THE RICH.
YOU KNOW WHY
THEY'RE SO ODD?
BECAUSE THEY
CAN AFFORD TO BE.
LOOK AT THIS MIRROR.
MAYBE IT SHOULD BE
BRUCE VAIN.
ROBERT, WHAT'S UP?
ANONYMOUS TIP.
NAPIER'S CLEANING OUT
AXIS CHEMICALS.
GOOD LORD,
IF WE COULD PUT
OUR HANDS ON HIM,
WE'D HAVE GRISSOM.
WHY WASN'T I TOLD
ABOUT THIS?
WHO'S IN CHARGE?
ECKHARDT, SIR.
OH, MY GOD.
COME ON, LET'S GO.
LET'S GO.
ALL RIGHT,
TAKE A GOOD LOOK.
THIS IS THE GUY.
ALL RIGHT,
GET A GOOD LOOK.
SHOOT TO KILL.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
ALL RIGHT,
LET'S MOVE OUT.
WE'VE BEEN
RATTED OUT HERE, BOYS.
WATCH IT.
FREEZE!
YOU GO LEFT.
YOU TAKE THE RIGHT.
MOVE IT.
MOVE IT, HUH?
WHAT THE HELL'S
GOING ON?
WHAT ARE YOU
TRYING TO DO,
BLOW THE COLLAR?
I'M IN CHARGE HERE,
NOT CARL GRISSOM.
THIS IS
COMMISSIONER GORDON.
I WANT HIM
TAKEN ALIVE.
I REPEAT,
ANY MAN WHO OPENS FIRE
ON JACK NAPIER
WILL ANSWER TO ME.
AAH!
LET ME DOWN!
UH! LET ME DOWN!
UH! UH!
LET ME DOWN!
OH, MY GOD.
GO THAT WAY!
GET UP ON THE CATWALK
ON THAT SIDE.
YOU TAKE THAT SIDE.
BE CAREFUL.
GEEZ!
LET HIM GO,
OR I'LL DO GORDON!
NICE OUTFIT.
COME ON, JACK,
LET'S GO!
COME ON!
COME ON, JACK!
ECKHARDT.
THINK ABOUT
THE FUTURE.
AAH!
DAMN IT,
WE HAD HIM!
HOLD IT RIGHT THERE.
WHO IS THIS GUY?
I DON'T KNOW.
UNTIL WE FIND OUT,
KEEP A LID ON IT.
WAIT. THERE'S NO BAT.
THEN WHO DROPPED NAPIER
INTO THE ACID?
SUICIDE?
I WANT TO GET THIS
ON TAPE.
HELLO?
HE HUNG UP.
O.K. WHAT DO YOU GOT?
HERE'S
THE INNER CITY,
AXIS CHEMICALS,
AND HERE'S
THE SIGHTINGS.
MAYBE BATMAN
HAS SOME KIND
OF FLIGHT PATTERN.
THIS IS VERY GOOD.
I'LL TAKE YOU
TO DINNER,
THEN WE'LL
WALK THE TRAIL.
NO CAN DO.
I GOT A DATE
WITH BRUCE WAYNE.
WAYNE?
OH, NO.
THE GUY'S A STIFF.
YOU COULD DO
MUCH BETTER.
THANKS FOR BEING
SO CONCERNED. BYE.
YOU...
HOW'S THE SOUP?
EXCUSE ME?
THE SOUP.
HOW IS IT?
OH, IT'S--IT'S GREAT.
COULD YOU PASS THE SALT?
SURE.
THANKS.
DID YOU HAVE
A HARD TIME
FINDING THE HOUSE?
UM...NO.
IT WAS NO PROBLEM.
GOOD.
DO YOU LIKE
EATING IN HERE?
OH, YEAH.
IF YOU WANT
TO KNOW THE TRUTH,
I DON'T THINK I'VE BEEN
IN THIS ROOM BEFORE.
DO YOU WANT
TO GET OUT OF HERE?
YES.
THERE WAS
YOUNG MASTER BRUCE
LEADING HIS GRAY PONY,
WITH ME ON ITS BACK
LIKE A SACK
OF OLD POTATOES,
COVERED IN MUD
AND NURSING
A SPRAINED ANKLE.
THAT WAS THE FIRST
AND LAST TIME
I GAVE HIM
A RIDING LESSON.
WELL, I THINK
I'VE EMBARRASSED HIM
FOR LONG ENOUGH.
I'M OFF TO BED.
BUT PLEASE
LEAVE EVERYTHING.
I'LL TIDY UP
IN THE MORNING.
GOOD NIGHT, MISS.
GOOD NIGHT, ALFRED.
GOOD NIGHT, SIR.
GOOD NIGHT,
ALFRED.
HE'S REALLY WONDERFUL.
HE LOVES YOU A LOT.
ALFRED'S
A GREAT ONE.
I COULDN'T
FIND MY SOCKS
WITHOUT HIM.
HE SORT OF REMINDS ME
OF MY GRANDFATHER.
OH? WERE YOU
CLOSE TO HIM?
YEAH. I USED
TO SPEND SUMMERS
WITH HIM
AND MY GRANDMOTHER.
THEY HAD A HOUSE
ON THE LAKE.
NOTHING LIKE THIS,
BUT, UM...
BUT IT WAS FUN.
THAT SOUNDS NICE.
YEAH.
WHAT ABOUT YOUR FAMILY?
WELL...
ACTUALLY,
ALFRED IS MY FAMILY.
THIS HOUSE
AND ALL THIS STUFF
DOESN'T SEEM LIKE YOU
AT ALL.
SOME OF IT
IS VERY MUCH ME.
SOME OF IT ISN'T.
THAT DINING ROOM
IS DEFINITELY NOT YOU.
NO, THE DINING ROOM
ISN'T.
LET'S SEE
HOW WE DID.
YEAH.
AACK.
MY GOD.
MIRROR.
MIRROR!
[MOANING]
YOU UNDERSTAND
THAT THE NERVES
WERE COMPLETELY
SEVERED, MR. NAPIER.
HEE HEE HEE HEE!
HEE HEE HA HA HA!
YOU SEE WHAT I HAVE
TO WORK WITH HERE.
HA HEE HEE HEE HEE!
[BULB SHATTERS]
HA HA HA HA!
HEE HEE HEE HEE HEE!
HA HA HA HA HA!
THERE'S AN AWFUL LOT
OF STAIRS IN THIS PLACE.
MY FEET ARE KILLING ME.
O.K.
WELL...
OOH.
I FEEL
A LITTLE DRUNK,
AND YOU'RE
NOT ANYTHING.
HEY, ONE DRINK
AND I'M FLYING.
WHY ARE YOU
AFRAID OF FLYING?
[CREAKING]
THAT YOU, SUGAR BUMPS?
WHO THE HELL ARE YOU?
IT'S ME...
SUGAR BUMPS.
JACK?
OH.
THANK GOD YOU'RE ALIVE.
I HEARD YOU'D BEEN--
FRIED?
IS THAT
WHAT YOU HEARD?
YOU SET ME UP
OVER A WOMAN.
A WOMAN!
YOU MUST BE INSANE.
DON'T BOTHER.
YOUR LIFE WON'T
BE WORTH SPIT!
I'VE BEEN DEAD
ONCE ALREADY.
IT'S VERY LIBERATING.
YOU SHOULD THINK OF IT
AS, UH...
THERAPY.
JACK...
LISTEN...
MAYBE WE CAN CUT A DEAL.
JACK?
JACK IS DEAD, MY FRIEND.
YOU CAN CALL ME...
JOKER.
AND AS YOU CAN SEE,
I'M A LOT HAPPIER.
AAH!
WOO HOO HOO HOO HOO!
[CLICK CLICK]
WHAT A DAY.
[SQUEAKING]
AH, GOTHAM CITY.
IT ALWAYS BRINGS
A SMILE TO MY FACE.
"WINGED FREAK...
TERRORIZES..."
WAIT TILL THEY
GET A LOAD OF ME.
OOH.
OOP.
HEY, I'VE
GOT AN IDEA.
HOW ABOUT LUNCH
AT MY PLACE?
I'LL SHOW YOU
SOME PHOTOS.
SURE. O.K.
WAIT A MINUTE.
NO, I CAN'T.
I CAN'T MAKE IT.
WE'LL DO IT LATER
IN THE DAY.
I CAN'T MAKE IT THEN,
EITHER.
I'VE GOT A VERY IMPORTANT
MEETING TODAY.
WHAT'S WRONG?
NOTHING'S WRONG.
I'VE GOT TO GO
OUT OF TOWN
FOR A FEW DAYS.
WE'LL DO IT
WHEN YOU GET BACK.
ALL RIGHT.
I'VE GOT TO GO.
I'M LATE.
BYE.
ALFRED.
IT'S NICE TO SEE YOU
AGAIN, MA'AM.
NICE TO SEE YOU, TOO.
WELL, I'LL TALK
TO YOU GUYS
WHEN YOU GET BACK.
BACK, MISS VALE?
WE'RE GOING TO BE HERE
FOR QUITE A WHILE.
OH, WELL, BYE.
HONEY?
YOU'LL NEVER BELIEVE
WHAT HAPPENED TO ME TODAY.
OH.
SO, GENTLEMEN,
THAT'S HOW IT IS.
UNTIL GRISSOM,
UH...RESURFACES,
I'M THE ACTING PRESIDENT,
AND I SAY,
STARTING WITH
THIS ANNIVERSARY FESTIVAL,
WE RUN THIS CITY
INTO THE GROUND.
WHY DON'T WE HEAR
THIS FROM GRISSOM?
YEAH.
AND WHAT'S WITH
THAT STUPID GRIN?
LIFE'S BEEN GOOD TO ME.
WHAT IF WE SAY NO?
WELL, TONY...
NOBODY WANTS A WAR.
IF WE CAN'T DO BUSINESS,
WHY, WE'LL JUST SHAKE HANDS,
AND THAT'LL BE IT.
YEAH?
YEAH.
WHOO!
OH, I GOT
A LIVE ONE HERE.
HA HA HA HA!
♪ OH, THERE'LL BE
A HOT TIME ♪
♪ IN THE OLD TOWN TONIGHT
AAH!
HA HA HA HA!
ANTOINE GOT A LITTLE HOT
UNDER THE COLLAR.
YOU'RE CRAZY.
HAVEN'T YOU EVER HEARD
OF THE HEALING POWER
OF LAUGHTER?
NOW GET OUT OF HERE!
YOU HEARD HIM!
LET'S GO!
AND THINK IT OVER.
UP! UP!
FASTER!
COME ON,
GET OUT OF HERE!
COME ON. MOVE IT.
BOB...
I WANT YOU TO
GO DOWN TO THE GLOBE,
FOLLOW THAT REPORTER KNOX.
TAKE YOUR CAMERA.
SEE WHAT HE KNOWS
ABOUT THIS BATMAN.
AND, BOB...
REMEMBER.
YOU...
ARE MY NUMBER ONE...
GUY.
YES, SIR.
THEY'LL BE OUT HERE SOON.
I CAN'T WAIT TO HEAR
THE EXPLANATION.
HERE HE COMES NOW.
SO WHAT'S THIS
AFFIDAVIT YOU FILED?
GRISSOM GAVE YOU
ALL HIS BUSINESSES?
MR. GRISSOM ASKED ME
AS A PERSONAL FAVOR
TO TAKE OVER
THE OPERATION
OF HIS BUSINESSES
UNTIL HE RETURNS.
THAT'S
A PRETTY BIG FAVOR.
YOU TWO MUST
HAVE BEEN CLOSE.
VERY CLOSE.
DID YOU DO TIME TOGETHER
AS CHILDREN?
OUR ACCOUNTANTS
ARE LOOKING INTO THIS.
WE ASSURE YOU THE AFFIDAVIT
IS LEGITIMATE.
I SMELL FRESH INK, GUYS.
YOU CAN PROVE ALL THIS?
WHAT AM I ASKING?
OF COURSE HE CAN.
WE HAVE WITNESSES.
GRISSOM'S SIGNATURE'S
PERFECTLY LEGITIMATE.
IT IS LEGITIMATE.
I SAW IT.
I WAS THERE.
I SAW IT ALL.
HE REACHED UP
WITH HIS DEAD HAND
AND SIGNED IT
IN HIS OWN BLOOD,
AND HE DID IT
WITH THIS PEN.
HELLO, VINNIE.
IT'S YOUR
UNCLE BINGO.
TIME TO PAY THE CHECK.
THE PEN IS TRULY MIGHTIER
THAN THE SWORD.
[GUNFIRE]
BRUCE!
WAYNE, GET DOWN!
DOESN'T THIS GANG WAR
DAMPEN THE CITY'S PLANS
FOR THE 200th
ANNIVERSARY FESTIVAL?
THE FESTIVAL OPENS.
THE POLICE WILL STOP
THESE GANGSTERS.
MR. DENT, WHAT
ABOUT THE THEORY
THAT THE
MYSTERIOUS BATMAN
IS A MOB ENFORCER
KILLING
THESE GANGSTERS?
I HAVE NO COMMENT NOW.
BATMAN.
CAN SOMEBODY TELL ME
WHAT KIND OF A WORLD
WE LIVE IN
WHERE A MAN
DRESSED UP AS A BAT
GETS ALL OF MY PRESS?
THIS TOWN NEEDS AN ENEMA.
[TOOT TOOT]
ALFRED...
MAY I HAVE
A GLASS OF...WATER?
I'M RELIEVED
YOU'RE HOME, SIR.
MISS VALE
TELEPHONED.
SHE WAS
RATHER CONCERNED.
I FEEL THAT THERE'S
A CERTAIN WEIGHT
THAT LIFTS
WHEN SHE IS HERE.
ALFRED...
WHY DON'T YOU
MARRY HER?
THAT'S NOT EXACTLY
WHAT I HAD IN MIND, SIR.
I KNOW.
I CAN'T GO ON WITH THAT
RIGHT NOW.
IF NOT NOW...
WHEN?
I DON'T KNOW.
I JUST FOUND OUT
JACK NAPIER'S STILL ALIVE.
HE'S RUNNING
GRISSOM'S MEN.
I NEED ALL THE INFORMATION
THE POLICE HAVE.
YES, SIR.
THANK YOU.
ALFRED...
SHE IS GREAT,
ISN'T SHE?
YES, SIR.
CITY ROOM. KNOX.
I WANT YOU TO CHECK
SOMETHING FOR ME.
FIND OUT
WHAT'S SO SPECIAL
ABOUT THE ALLEY
AT PEARL AND
PHILLIPS STREETS.
PEARL AND PHILLIPS?
YEAH.
O.K. O.K. BYE.
MR. WAYNE...
SO MUCH TO DO
AND SO LITTLE TIME.
THE PHOTOS.
WHO IS THAT LOSS?
IT'S KNOX.
BAD TIE.
NO STYLE.
STOP THE PRESS.
WHO'S THAT?
THAT'S VICKI VALE,
THE PHOTOGRAPHER
WORKING WITH KNOX.
NOW, THAT GIRL
HAS STYLE.
JESUS MARIMBA!
A LOVELY BEAST LIKE THAT
RUNNING AROUND
COULD PUT STEAM
IN A MAN'S STRIDES.
SHE'S DATING
SOME GUY
NAMED WAYNE.
SHE'S ABOUT TO TRADE UP.
HARD TO STAY
INSIDE THE LINES.
I'M ABOUT...
TO GET A NEW GIRL,
BOBBY.
I'VE OF A MIND
TO MAKE SOME MOOKIE.
PHONE BOOK.
YES, SIR.
SO MUCH TO DO...
AND SO LITTLE TIME.
[HORN HONKS]
HAVE YOU SHIPPED
A MILLION
OF THOSE THINGS?
YES, SIR.
SHIP THEM ALL!
WE'RE GOING
TO TAKE THEM OUT
A WHOLE NEW DOOR.
10 SECONDS
TO TRANSMISSION.
CUE MUSIC.
CUE BECKY.
GOOD EVENING.
THE FASHION WORLD
WAS STUNNED TODAY
BY THE SUDDEN DEATHS
OF MODELS CANDY WALKER
AND AMANDA KEELER.
CAUSE OF DEATH
HAS BEEN ATTRIBUTED
TO A VIOLENT
ALLERGIC REACTION,
ALTHOUGH AUTHORITIES
HAVE NOT RULED OUT
THE POSSIBILITY
OF DRUG USE.
PETER.
PLANS CONTINUE
FOR THE CITY'S
200th BIRTHDAY
AS MAYOR BORG
ANNOUNCED TODAY
THE UNVEILING--
THIS JUST IN.
THREE DEATHS
AT A BEAUTY
PARLOR--
HA HA HA.
AT A BEAUTY PARLOR
IN GOTHAM--
HA HA HA!
BARRY,
WHAT'S GOING ON?
BECKY, THIS IS
HARDLY THE...
BECKY.
KILL THE CAMERA.
THIS IS RENE,
NEWS FLOOR.
I NEED PARAMEDICS
UP HERE NOW.
NEW AND IMPROVED
JOKER PRODUCTS...
WITH A NEW
SECRET INGREDIENT--
SMYLEX.
WHAT IS THIS?
NOW, LET'S GO OVER...
TO OUR BLIND
TASTE TEST.
LOVE THAT JOKER!
WHERE'S IT COMING FROM?
I DON'T KNOW.
UH-OH.
NOW, HE DON'T
LOOK HAPPY.
HE'S BEEN USING
BRAND X.
BUT WITH NEW AND IMPROVED
JOKER BRAND,
I GET A GRIN
AGAIN...
AND AGAIN.
THAT LUSCIOUS TAN,
THOSE RUBY LIPS,
AND HAIR COLOR
SO NATURAL,
ONLY YOUR UNDERTAKER
KNOWS FOR SURE.
HA HA HA!
I KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE SAYING--
WHERE CAN I GET
THESE FINE NEW ITEMS?
WELL, THAT'S THE GAG.
CHANCES ARE,
YOU BOUGHT THEM ALREADY.
LOVE THAT JOKER!
SO REMEMBER--
PUT ON A HAPPY FACE.
HA HA HA!
THE INFORMATION
YOU REQUESTED, SIR.
THANK YOU.
AH, JACK NAPIER.
"ASSAULT WITH
A DEADLY WEAPON,
AGE 15.
"RESULTS OF
PSYCHOLOGICAL PROFILE.
"VIOLENT MOOD SWINGS,
"HIGHLY INTELLIGENT,
"EMOTIONALLY UNSTABLE.
APTITUDES INCLUDE SCIENCE,
CHEMISTRY, AND ART."
CHEMISTRY.
ALFRED,
LET'S GO SHOPPING.
YES, SIR.
SIX NEW DEATHS,
WITH NO CLUES
AS TO THE JOKER'S
DEADLY WEAPON.
AND WHAT IS
THE PATTERN?
FOODS, ALCOHOL,
OR BEAUTY AND
HYGIENE PRODUCTS?
COLOGNE, MOUTHWASH,
UNDERARM DEODORANT?
OR WORSE YET,
THERE MAY BE
NO PATTERN.
THE SEARCH GOES ON
THROUGH GOTHAM'S
SHOPPING NIGHTMARE.
WE'RE GOING
TO HAVE A FESTIVAL
IF I HAVE TO USE
A SHOTGUN MYSELF.
DO YOU HEAR ME,
DENT?
THE FESTIVAL IS ON.
YOU FIND OUT
WHAT THIS MADMAN
IS POISONING US WITH,
AND FAST.
DO YOU READ ME?
WE'RE WORKING ON IT.
I NEED ALL THE HELP
I CAN GET.
BRUCE, HI.
IT'S VICKI.
I'M SORRY,
BUT I'LL BE
10 MINUTES LATE
TO THE MUSEUM.
SEE YOU THERE. BYE.
SIR, A MESSAGE
FROM MISS VALE--
SHE'LL BE 10 MINUTES
LATE MEETING YOU
AT THE MUSEUM.
O.K. FINE. THANK--
WAIT, ALFRED.
I'M NOT MEETING
HER TODAY.
JACK...
WHERE ARE
YOU GOING?
DADDY'S GOING TO MAKE
SOME ART, DARLING.
EXCUSE ME.
MR. WAYNE'S TABLE?
YES, UH,
HE HASN'T
ARRIVED YET.
WE HAVE
A TABLE WAITING.
GREAT.
MAY I?
YES, THANK YOU.
MISS VALE,
THIS JUST ARRIVED
FOR YOU.
OH!
HEY, WHAT'S--
OHH!
AAH!
OH!
GENTLEMEN...
LET'S BROADEN OUR MINDS.
LAWRENCE...
[PARTYMANPLAYS]
♪ OH, YEAH
GIVE HIM
A SHAVE.
♪ YEAH
TERENCE, BRUSH.
♪ ALL HAIL
♪ THE NEW KING
IN TOWN ♪
♪ YOUNG AND OLD
♪ GATHER 'ROUND
♪ YEAH
♪ BLACK AND WHITE
♪ RED AND GREEN
♪ THE MAN
♪ OH, YEAH
♪ THE FUNKIEST MAN
♪ YOU EVER SEEN
♪ TELL YOU WHAT
HIS NAME IS ♪
♪ PARTYMAN
♪ ROCK A PARTY LIKE
♪ NOBODY CAN
♪ RULES AND REGULATIONS
♪ NO PLACE
IN THIS NATION ♪
♪ PARTYMAN
♪ PARTY PEOPLE,
SAY IT NOW ♪
♪ YEAH
THE $1.00 BILL.
♪ SOMEBODY HOLLER
IF YOU WANNA PARTY ♪
WAIT.
I KIND OF LIKE
THIS ONE, BOB.
LEAVE IT.
♪ GET IT UP
♪ OH, YEAH--
YOU CAN TAKE THAT
OFF NOW, I THINK.
OH...
YOU'RE BEAUTIFUL...
IN AN OLD-FASHIONED
KIND OF WAY,
BUT I'M SURE WE CAN
MAKE YOU MORE "TODAY."
IS THAT
YOUR PORTFOLIO?
I'M MEETING SOMEONE
WHO WANTS TO
SEE MY WORK.
CRAP.
CRAP, CRAP.
AHH.
NOW, THAT'S GOOD WORK.
THE SKULLS,
THE BODIES--
YOU GIVE IT
SUCH A GLOW.
I DON'T KNOW
IF IT'S ART,
BUT I LIKE IT.
LET ME TELL YOU WHAT
I'M THINKING ABOUT,
SWEETIE.
IN THE BATH ONE DAY,
I REALIZED WHY
I WAS DESTINED
FOR GREATNESS.
YOU KNOW HOW
CONCERNED PEOPLE ARE
ABOUT APPEARANCES.
THIS IS ATTRACTIVE,
THAT IS NOT.
WELL, THAT
IS ALL BEHIND ME.
I NOW DO
WHAT OTHER PEOPLE
ONLY DREAM.
I MAKE ART...
UNTIL SOMEONE DIES.
SEE?
I AM THE WORLD'S FIRST
FULLY FUNCTIONING
HOMICIDAL ARTIST.
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
MY FACE ON
THE $1.00 BILL.
YOU MUST BE JOKING.
DO I LOOK LIKE
I'M JOKING?
NO.
LISTEN...
WE MUSTN'T
COMPARE OURSELVES
TO REGULAR PEOPLE.
WE'RE ARTISTS.
FOR INSTANCE,
LET ME CHALLENGE YOU
WITH A PIECE I DID.
BOB.
ALICIA.
YOU WILL TAKE PICTURES
AND RECORD MY WORK.
YOU WILL JOIN ME
IN THE AVANT-GARDE...
OF THE NEW AESTHETIC.
JACK, YOU SAID
I COULD WATCH YOU
IMPROVE
THE PAINTINGS.
OH, I'M IN TROUBLE NOW.
WHY IS SHE
WEARING A MASK?
WELL, SHE'S JUST
A SKETCH, REALLY.
ALICIA, SIT DOWN.
SHOW THE LADY
WHY YOU WEAR THE MASK.
YOU SEE, ALICIA'S
BEEN MADE OVER
IN LINE WITH
MY NEW PHILOSOPHY.
SO NOW, LIKE ME,
SHE'S A LIVING
WORK OF ART.
WHY, I'M NO PICASSO,
BUT DO YOU LIKE IT?
IT'S GREAT.
SO...
WHAT CAN IDO
FOR YOU?
OH, A LITTLE SONG,
A LITTLE DANCE,
BATMAN'S HEAD
ON A LANCE.
TELL ME,
WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT...
I DON'T KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT BATMAN.
REALLY?
WELL, HOW ABOUT
A LITTLE YOU AND ME?
YOU'RE INSANE.
I THOUGHT
I WAS A PISCES.
COME ON.
LET'S MAKE UP.
HAVE A LITTLE
WHIFF OF MY POSY.
AAH!
HELP ME!
OH!
OH, I'M MELTING!
HELP ME, I'M MELTING!
GOD!
AAH!
I'M MELTING!
HELP ME,
I'M MELTING.
AAH!
BOO!
HOLD ON.
AAH!
OOH.
WHERE DOES HE GET
THOSE WONDERFUL TOYS?
GET IN THE CAR.
WHICH ONE?
AAH!
LET'S GO.
SHIELDS.
AAH!
OH. AAH!
HOW MUCH DO YOU WEIGH?
ABOUT 108, I THINK.
HOLD ON.
AAH! OOH!
SEE THAT THING
ON MY BELT? GRAB IT.
DON'T LET GO.
AAH!
NO BLOOD.
HEY, WHO IS THIS GUY?
CHECK HIS WALLET.
WAIT A MINUTE.
WHAT IS THAT?
IT'S SOME KIND
OF BODY ARMOR.
HE'S HUMAN AFTER ALL.
TAKE OFF THE MASK.
SHOOT HER!
YAH!
AAH!
SHIELDS OPEN.
YOU WEIGH
MORE THAN 108.
OH, REALLY?
LET'S GO.
STOP.
WHERE ARE WE GOING?
AAH!
BE CAREFUL.
BATS.
THEY'RE GREAT SURVIVORS.
WHAT IS ALL THIS?
THE POLICE
HAVE GOT IT WRONG.
THEY'RE LOOKING
FOR ONE PRODUCT.
THE JOKER'S TAINTED
HUNDREDS OF CHEMICALS
AT THE SOURCE.
THEN WHOLE SHIPMENTS
OF PRODUCTS
WOULD BE POISONED,
AND WE'D ALL BE DEAD.
NO.
THE POISON ONLY WORKS
WHEN THE COMPONENTS
ARE MIXED.
HAIRSPRAY WON'T
DO IT ALONE,
BUT HAIRSPRAY MIXED WITH
LIPSTICK AND PERFUME
WOULD BE TOXIC
AND THEN TRACEABLE.
HOW DID YOU
FIGURE THIS OUT?
TAKE THAT
TO THE PRESS.
I MIGHT HAVE SOME
TROUBLE WITH THAT.
A LOT OF PEOPLE THINK
YOU'RE AS DANGEROUS
AS THE JOKER.
HE'S PSYCHOTIC.
SOME PEOPLE SAY
THE SAME THING ABOUT YOU.
WHAT PEOPLE?
WELL, I MEAN,
LET'S FACE IT.
YOU'RE NOT EXACTLY
NORMAL, ARE YOU?
IT'S NOT EXACTLY
A NORMAL WORLD, IS IT?
WHY DID YOU
BRING ME HERE?
YOU COULD HAVE
SENT THAT STUFF
TO THE PRESS YOURSELF.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
THERE IS SOMETHING ELSE
YOU HAVE THAT I WANT.
WHAT?
OH, HE TOOK THE FILM.
[RING]
YEAH?
ARE YOU O.K.? DO YOU
WANT ME TO COME OVER?
NO. NO, ALLIE.
IF I BRING
SOMETHING TO YOU,
CAN WE MAKE
THE EVENING EDITION?
JUST BARELY.
IS IT HOT?
OH. YEAH.
YEAH, IT'S REAL HOT.
YEAH. BYE.
COPY!
YES, SIR?
AVOID THE FOLLOWING
COMBINATIONS--
DEODORANTS
WITH BABY POWDER,
HAIRSPRAY, AND LIPSTICK.
SAFE PRODUCTS ARE FLYING IN
AS GOTHAM CITY GOES
ON A FORCED FAST.
ALL OF GOTHAM IS WONDERING
WHAT TO MAKE OF BATMAN--
FRIEND OR FOE?
I HAVE GIVEN A NAME
TO MY PAIN...
MYSTERIOUS FIGURE...
AND IT IS BATMAN.
YOU MUST POSSESS STRENGTH
TO INFLICT PAIN, BOB.
WE'VE GOT A FLYING MOUSE
TO KILL,
AND I WANT
TO CLEAN MY CLAWS.
SIR, MISS VALE
CALLED AGAIN.
DARE I SUGGEST
THAT YOUR PRESENT
COURSE OF ACTION
MIGHT SIMPLY STRENGTHEN
HER RESOLVE?
SHE IS QUITE TENACIOUS.
YOU'RE RIGHT ABOUT THAT.
AND IF I MAY SAY SO,
QUITE SPECIAL.
PERHAPS YOU COULD TRY
TELLING HER THE TRUTH.
[RINGS DOORBELL]
COMING.
HI.
MAY I COME IN?
THIS IS A NICE APARTMENT.
LOTS OF SPACE.
UH, LISTEN. I CAME OVER
TO CLEAR A FEW THINGS--
I DON'T KNOW WHO
YOU THINK YOU ARE.
YOU HURT ME.
I KNOW. LOOK--
I CALLED YOU. YOU LIED
ABOUT LEAVING TOWN.
LET ME TELL YOU WHY.
I'LL TELL YOU!
I THOUGHT
WE FELT SOMETHING.
I SLEPT WITH YOU.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
I DID THAT.
THEN YOU WOULDN'T
RETURN MY CALLS.
YOU MUST BE
SOME KIND OF--JERK.
YOU'RE A NICE GIRL,
AND I LIKE YOU A LOT,
BUT FOR RIGHT NOW,
SHUT UP.
I HAVE SOMETHING
I HAVE TO TELL YOU.
YOU KNOW HOW PEOPLE
HAVE DIFFERENT SIDES
TO THEIR PERSONALITY?
MM-HMM.
SOMETIMES A...A...
A PERSON WILL
HAVE TO ACTUALLY LEAD
A DIFFERENT LIFE.
OH, MY GOD,
YOU'RE MARRIED.
NO, I'M NOT MARRIED.
YOU SEE...
MY LIFE IS REALLY...
UM...
COMPLEX.
ALL RIGHT, LISTEN.
YOU KNOW HOW
A NORMAL PERSON GETS UP
AND...
GOES DOWNSTAIRS
AND EATS BREAKFAST
AND KISSES
SOMEBODY GOODBYE
AND GOES TO A JOB
AND...YOU KNOW.
NO.
ALL RIGHT, LOOK.
VICKI, WHAT I'M TRYING
TO TELL YOU IS...
HEY, IT'S O.K.
YOU CAN TELL ME.
O.K. AHEM.
WHAT?
[DOORBELL RINGS]
WHAT I'M TRYING
TO TELL YOU IS...
SEE, UH...
[RING]
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
AAH!
[BEAUTIFUL DREAMERPLAYS]
MISS ME?
NICE PLACE
YOU'VE GOT HERE.
LOTS OF SPACE.
UH, VICKI, WE'VE REALLY
GOT TO HAVE A TALK.
I'M VERY UPSET.
WE WERE HAVING DINNER.
I WAS A MAN DOING WELL
WITH A BEAUTIFUL WOMAN,
AND WITHOUT SO MUCH
AS AN APOLOGY,
YOU RAN OFF WITH
THAT SIDESHOW PHONY.
YOU KNOW, VICK...
I'VE RECENTLY HAD
A TRAGEDY IN MY LIFE.
ALICIA...
THREW HERSELF
OUT OF THE WINDOW.
OH, MY GOD.
BUT...
YOU CAN'T MAKE AN OMELET
WITHOUT BREAKING
SOME EGGS.
AAH!
WELL, MISS VALE,
ANOTHER ROOSTER
IN THE HENHOUSE.
TAKE THY BEAK
FROM OUT MY HEART.
[MUSIC STOPS]
BRUCE?
BRUCE WAYNE,
N'EST-CE PAS?
MOST OF THE TIME.
I know who you are.
LET ME TELL YOU ABOUT
THIS GUY I KNOW, JACK.
MEAN KID. BAD SEED.
HURT PEOPLE.
I LIKE HIM ALREADY.
NOW YOU KNOW
THE PROBLEM WAS...
HE GOT SLOPPY.
YOU KNOW? CRAZY.
HE STARTED TO LOSE IT.
HE HAD A HEAD FULL
OF BAD WIRING, I GUESS.
COULDN'T KEEP IT
STRAIGHT UP HERE.
HE WAS THE KIND OF GUY
WHO COULDN'T
HEAR THE TRAIN
UNTIL IT WAS 2 FEET
FROM HIM.
HMM.
YOU KNOW WHAT HAPPENED
TO THIS GUY, JACK?
WELL...
HE MADE MISTAKES.
THEN HE HAD
HIS LIGHTS OUT!
NOW YOU WANT
TO GET NUTS?
COME ON.
LET'S GET NUTS.
TELL ME SOMETHING,
MY FRIEND.
YOU EVER DANCED
WITH THE DEVIL
IN THE PALE MOONLIGHT?
WHAT?
I ALWAYS ASK THAT
OF ALL MY PREY.
I JUST LIKE
THE SOUND OF IT.
AAH!
NEVER RUB
ANOTHER MAN'S RHUBARB.
OH, MY DEAR, CHIN UP.
WHY IS IT EVERY TIME
I COME FOR YOU
SOMEBODY ALWAYS
GETS IN THE WAY?
I'LL NEED
A MOMENT ALONE, BOYS.
I'M ONLY LAUGHING
ON THE OUTSIDE.
MY SMILE
IS JUST SKIN DEEP.
IF YOU COULD SEE INSIDE
I'M REALLY CRYING,
YOU MIGHT JOIN ME
FOR A WEEP.
AH--PBBBT!
OH, WHAT?
OH!
YOU WOULDN'T
BELIEVE IT.
YOU REALLY WOULDN'T.
WELL, WHILE YOU
WERE OUT ENTERTAINING,
I'VE BEEN HERE FINDING OUT
ABOUT YOUR STREET CORNER.
VALE...
I THINK YOUR FRIEND WAYNE
IS REALLY SCREWED UP.
MORE GOOD NEWS.
HERE.
OH, MY GOD.
HIS PARENTS WERE MURDERED
IN THAT ALLEY.
THAT'S WHY
HE WENT THERE.
POOR KID WATCHED
THE WHOLE THING HAPPEN
IN FRONT OF HIM.
LOOK AT THE LOOK
ON THE FACE.
IT WAS THE SAME
IN FRONT OF CITY HALL.
WHAT DO YOU SUPPOSE
SOMETHING LIKE THIS
DOES TO A KID?
VALE!
DON'T GET PERSONAL!
ALFRED, DID YOU
GET THE FILE
ON MY PARENTS?
IT'S ON YOUR TABLE,
SIR.
THANK YOU.
WHAT'S ON YOUR MIND,
ALFRED?
I HAVE NO WISH
TO FILL MY FEW
REMAINING YEARS
GRIEVING FOR THE LOSS
OF OLD FRIENDS...
OR THEIR SONS.
THE 200th ANNIVERSARY
BIRTHDAY GALA
HAS BEEN INDEFINITELY
POSTPONED.
WE SIMPLY CANNOT
GUARANTEE PUBLIC SAFETY--
JOKER HERE.
WE'VE GOT INTERFERENCE.
CALL THE OB UNIT.
NOW, YOU FELLAS
HAVE SAID SOME
PRETTY MEAN THINGS,
SOME OF WHICH
WERE TRUE
UNDER THAT FIEND
BOSS GRISSOM.
HE WAS A THIEF
AND A TERRORIST.
ON THE OTHER HAND,
HE HAD A TREMENDOUS
SINGING VOICE.
NOW...I CAN
BE THEATRICAL
AND MAYBE EVEN
A LITTLE ROUGH.
BUT ONE THING
I AM NOT
IS A KILLER.
I AM AN ARTIST.
I LOVE
A GOOD PARTY.
SO...TRUCE.
COMMENCE
AU FESTIVAL.
AND I'VE GOT A SURPRISE
FOR GOTHAM CITY.
AT MIDNIGHT,
I WILL DUMP
20 MILLION IN CASH
ON THE CROWD.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME.
I'VE GOT ENOUGH.
WE ARE NOT PREPARED
TO DISCUSS ANY DEALS.
YOU HEARD IT, FOLKS.
20 MILLION.
AND THERE WILL BE
ENTERTAINMENT.
THE BIG DUKEROO.
WITH ME IN ONE CORNER,
AND IN THE OTHER CORNER,
THE MAN WHO HAS
BROUGHT REAL TERROR
TO GOTHAM CITY--
BATMAN.
CAN YOU HEAR ME?
JUST THE TWO OF US.
MANO Y MANO.
I HAVE TAKEN OFF
MY MAKE-UP.
LET'S SEE IF YOU
CAN TAKE OFF YOURS.
AAH!
TELL ME, KID...
YOU EVER DANCED
WITH THE DEVIL
BY THE PALE
MOONLIGHT?
MAN, LET'S GO!
LET'S GO, JACK!
SEE YOU AROUND, KID.
THANKS.
HI.
TELL ME
IF I'M CRAZY...
BUT THAT WASN'T
JUST ANOTHER NIGHT
FOR EITHER OF US,
WAS IT?
I MEAN, WE--WE BOTH
GOT TO EACH OTHER,
DIDN'T WE?
WHY WON'T YOU
LET ME IN?
WHY?
YOU GOT IN.
I'VE LOVED YOU
SINCE I MET YOU,
BUT I DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO THINK
OF ALL THIS.
I REALLY DON'T.
SOMETIMES I DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO THINK.
IT'S JUST SOMETHING
I HAVE TO DO.
WHY?
BECAUSE
NOBODY ELSE CAN.
LOOK...
I TRIED TO AVOID
ALL THIS, BUT I CAN'T.
THIS IS HOW IT IS.
IT'S NOT
A PERFECT WORLD.
IT DOESN'T HAVE TO
BE A PERFECT WORLD.
I JUST GOT TO KNOW--
ARE WE GOING TO TRY
TO LOVE EACH OTHER?
I'D LIKE TO...
BUT HE'S OUT THERE
RIGHT NOW,
AND I'VE GOT
TO GO TO WORK.
INTO THE AIR,
JUNIOR BIRDMAN.
MISSED ME!
HA HA HA!
YEAH, WATCH ME!
♪ W, X, Y, Z
♪ OOH
♪ UH-HUH
♪ TRUST
♪ WHO DO YA?
♪ WHAT MAKES YOU FEEL
♪ ALL THE TRUST?
♪ I PUT THIS QUESTION
TO YA ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I WANT YOU
TO BE WITH ME ♪
♪ LOVE
♪ YOU CANNOT IMAGINE
♪ HOW MUCH I WANNA
GIVE TO YOU ♪
♪ HOT
♪ I'M GETTING
SO EXCITED ♪
♪ JUST THINKING ABOUT
ALL WE COULD DO ♪
♪ DIG IT NOW
♪ ANOTHER WORLD
AWAITS US ♪
♪ ANOTHER POWER TO SEE
♪ CLOSE
♪ DON'T WORRY
ABOUT NOBODY ELSE ♪
♪ FROM NOW ON,
YOU'LL BE HERE WITH ME ♪
♪ TRUST
♪ WHO DO YA?
♪ WHAT MAKES YOU
A REAL LOVER? ♪
♪ TRUST
♪ I PUT THIS QUESTION
TO YA ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I WANT YOU
TO BE WITH ME ♪
♪ MONEY
♪ HOW MUCH WILL
MAKE YOU HAPPY? ♪
♪ YOU CAN HAVE IT ALL
♪ IF IT'LL
SUIT YOU RIGHT ♪
♪ BUT NOTHIN'
♪ I SAID NOTHIN'
CAN TAKE THE PLACE ♪
♪ OF YOU AND ME
♪ KICKIN' IT TIGHT,
TIGHT ♪
♪ TRUST
♪ WHO DO YOU LOVE?
♪ WHAT MAKES YOU
A REAL LOVER? ♪
♪ TRUST
♪ I PUT THIS QUESTION
TO YA ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I WANT YOU
TO BE WITH ME ♪
♪ ME-E-E-E
♪ AAH
♪ AH
♪ YAY
♪ OH
GET THEM.
TAKE THE PICTURES.
GOTHAM'S GREED.
♪ TRUST
AND NOW, FOLKS,
IT'S TIME FOR
WHO DO YOU TRUST?
HUBBA, HUBBA, HUBBA.
MONEY, MONEY, MONEY.
WHO DO YOU TRUST?
ME? I'M GIVING AWAY
FREE MONEY.
AND WHERE IS THE BATMAN?
HE'S AT HOME
WASHING HIS TIGHTS!
WINGED BATTLE
FLIES THROUGH THE NIGHT
AND FINDS ME READY.
BOB, MASK.
MASKS!
PUT THEM ON NOW!
ALL RIGHT!
AND NOW...
COMES THE PART
WHERE I RELIEVE YOU,
THE LITTLE PEOPLE,
OF THE BURDEN
OF YOUR FAILED
AND USELESS LIVES.
BUT, AS MY PLASTIC SURGEON
ALWAYS SAID,
"IF YOU GOT TO GO,
GO WITH A SMILE."
OH, MY GOD.
SMYLEX GAS.
HE'S GOING
TO KILL EVERYBODY!
GET IN THE CAR.
GET IN THE CAR!
HURRY!
AAH!
WH-WH-WHOA!
OH, NO, NO!
MY BALLOONS.
THOSE ARE MY BALLOONS.
HE STOLE MY BALLOONS!
WHY DIDN'T
SOMEBODY TELL ME
THAT HE HAD ONE
OF THOSE...THINGS?
[GUNFIRE]
AHH.
COME ON, YOU GRUESOME
SON OF A BAT.
COME TO ME.
COME ON.
DARLING?
I'VE GOT TO GET YOU
TO THE CHURCH ON TIME.
YES, SIR?
GOTHAM CITY CATHEDRAL.
TRANSPORTATION FOR TWO.
RIGHT AWAY, SIR.
FIVE MINUTES.
BETTER MAKE IT 10.
O.K. 10 MINUTES.
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GO, MEN.
LET'S GO.
YOU MEN GO THAT WAY.
YOU MEN POINT
THOSE SEARCHLIGHTS
UP ON THE TOWER.
RIGHT NOW!
MOVE! MOVE!
IT CAN BE TRULY SAID
THAT I HAVE A BAT
IN MY BELFRY.
HA HA HA!
SHALL WE DANCE?
[YELLING]
[WALTZ PLAYS]
HAH!
AAH!
YOU KNOW,
WITHOUT YOU,
I JUST WOULDN'T
WANT TO GO ON.
AAH!
[WALTZ PLAYS]
IT'S AS THOUGH WE WERE
MADE FOR EACH OTHER.
BEAUTY AND THE BEAST.
OF COURSE, IF ANYONE ELSE
CALLS YOU BEAST,
I'LL RIP
THEIR LUNGS OUT.
MR. JOKER...
YOU SAY
SUCH BEAUTIFUL THINGS.
OH!
AND YOU'RE SO...
POWERFUL.
AND PURPLE!
OH! OH, I LOVE PURPLE.
EXCUSE ME.
HAVE YOU EVER DANCED
WITH THE DEVIL
IN THE PALE MOONLIGHT?
I'M GOING TO KILL YOU.
YOU IDIOT!
YOU MADE ME,
REMEMBER?
YOU DROPPED ME INTO
THOSE CHEMICALS.
THAT WASN'T EASY
TO GET OVER,
AND DON'T THINK
THAT I DIDN'T TRY.
I KNOW YOU DID.
OH!
OOH!
YOU KILLED MY PARENTS.
WHAT?
UH...
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
HUH?
I MADE YOU.
YOU MADE ME FIRST.
I WAS A KID WHEN I
KILLED YOUR PARENTS.
I SAY I MADE YOU,
YOU GOT TO SAY
YOU MADE ME.
HOW CHILDISH
CAN YOU GET?
WOULDN'T HIT A GUY
WITH GLASSES,
WOULD YOU?
AAH!
HA HA HA!
WHAT ARE YOU
LAUGHING AT?
HERE. LET ME
LEND YOU A HAND.
AAH!
NO!
HA HA HA!
LEND YOU A HAND.
WHOO!
OH, THEY DON'T MAKE THEM
LIKE THEY USED TO.
HA HA HA!
HEY, GANG!
HEY, BATSY!
HA HA HA!
WHOO HOO HOO HOO!
THERE HE IS!
DOWN THERE!
GO DOWN!
HOO HOO HOO!
HOO HOO!
WELL...
IT'S TIME TO RETIRE.
FEEL FREE TO DROP IN.
WOO! HA HA HA!
AAH!
SOMETIMES I JUST
KILL MYSELF.
HEY.
HEY!
COME ON!
AAH!
WHOO!
HA HA HA HA
HA HA HA HA!
OUR POLICE
HAVE ROUNDED UP
ALL THE JOKER'S MEN.
THE REIGN OF CRIME
IS OVER.
PUBLIC SAFETY
IN GOTHAM CITY
IS NO LONGER
A LAUGHING MATTER.
HEY, VALE,
AREN'T YOU COVERING
THIS PRESS CONFERENCE?
NOPE.
WELL, WHAT ABOUT
OUR PULITZER PRIZE?
WHAT ABOUT US?
WHAT ABOUT YOUR PICTURE
OF BATMAN?
TAKE CARE, ALLIE.
WE'VE RECEIVED A LETTER
FROM BATMAN THIS MORNING.
"PLEASE INFORM
THE CITIZENS OF GOTHAM
"THAT GOTHAM CITY HAS
EARNED A REST FROM CRIME,
"BUT IF THE FORCES
OF EVIL SHOULD RISE AGAIN
"TO CAST A SHADOW
ON THE HEART OF THE CITY,
CALL ME."
QUESTION.
HOW DO WE CALL HIM?
HE GAVE US A SIGNAL.
I THOUGHT CHAMPAGNE
WOULD BE IN ORDER, MA'AM.
HI, ALFRED.
MR. WAYNE TOLD ME
TO TELL YOU
THAT HE MIGHT
BE A LITTLE LATE.
MMM. HMM.
I'M NOT A BIT SURPRISED.