[PANTING]
[WOMAN SCREAMS]
OH! AHH! AHH!
[BABY CRIES]
[MAN] AAH!
[MEOW MEOW]
[YEOW]
MERRY CHRISTMAS.
AAH AAH.
[AWK AWK] [AWK AWK]
[BELL CLANGS]
PENGUIN SIGHTING.
CHECK IT OUT.
"MAN OR MYTH--
WHAT IS HE?"
TODAY'S EDITION.
ANOTHER PENGUIN SIGHTING.
CHECK IT OUT.
GROTESQUE PENGUIN MAN
LIVING IN GOTHAM SEWERS.
READ ALL ABOUT
THE LATEST SIGHTING.
[PUBLIC ADDRESS
SYSTEM SQUEALS]
COULD I HAVE YOUR ATTENTION,
GOTHAM CITY?
IT IS TIME FOR TONIGHT'S
LIGHTING OF THE TREE.
WHOO! YAY!
[WHISTLING]
WHOO! WHOO!
HOW ABOUT THAT?
♪ WE WISH YOU
A MERRY CHRISTMAS ♪
♪ AND A HAPPY NEW YEAR
PART MAN, PART PENGUIN.
ALL HORRIFYING.
FIND OUT
FOR ONLY 50 CENTS.
COME ON.
READ ABOUT
THE POSSIBLE TERROR
BENEATH OUR FEET.
CHECK IT OUT, PEOPLE.
READ ABOUT IT.
TODAY'S ISSUE.
READ ABOUT
THE LATEST SIGHTING
OF THE PENGUIN CREATURE.
HEY, MISSING LINK
BETWEEN MAN AND BIRD.
MY DEAR BOY,
SOMETIMES IT'S A DIVERSION
TO READ SUCH RUBBISH.
MOST OF THE TIME,
IT'S A WASTE OF TIME.
WHATEVER.
TODAY'S ISSUE--
THE PENGUIN.
CHECK HIM OUT.
"MAN OR MYTH?"
THE GLOBE.
RIGHT HERE. 25 CENTS.
WELL, HERE'S HOPING.
MAYBE WITH
A LITTLE LUCK,
GOTHAM WILL HAVE
A MERRY CHRISTMAS.
Coffee?
I FEEL ALMOST VULGAR
IN THIS YULETIDE CONTEXT
MENTIONING
THE NEW POWER PLANT,
BUT IF WE'RE GOING
TO BREAK GROUND
WHEN WE
GOT TO BREAK GROUND,
I'LL NEED PERMITS,
VARIANCES, TAX INCENTIVES,
THAT SORT OF PESKY NONSENSE.
POWER PLANT?
ALL OUR STUDIES SHOW
WE'VE GOT ENOUGH POWER
TO GET US INTO THE MIDDLE
OF THE NEXT CENTURY.
ANALYSTS PREDICT
1% GROWTH PER ANNUM.
THAT'S NOT GROWTH.
THAT'S A MILD SWELLING.
IMAGINE...
A GOTHAM CITY
OF THE FUTURE,
LIT UP LIKE
A BLANKET OF STARS,
BUT BLINKING ON AND OFF,
EMBARRASSINGLY LOW
ON JUICE.
FRANKLY...
I CRINGE, MR. MAYOR.
SORRY. ANY PLANS
YOU'VE GOT
WILL HAVE
TO GO TO THE
USUAL COMMITTEES,
THROUGH
THE USUAL CHANNELS.
UM, I HAVE
A SUGGESTION.
WELL...
ACTUALLY, REALLY JUST
MORE LIKE A Q-QUESTION.
I'M AFRAID WE HAVEN'T
PROPERLY HOUSEBROKEN
MS. KYLE.
HEH HEH HEH.
IN THE PLUS COLUMN,
THOUGH,
SHE MAKES A HELL
OF A CUP OF COFFEE.
HEH HEH HEH.
DAD.
MR. MAYOR.
IT'S TIME TO BRING JOY
TO THE MASSES.
GOD.
"ACTUALLY
MORE OF A QUESTION."
YOU STUPID CORN DOG.
OH, GOD.
CORN DOG. CORN DOG.
[SIGHS]
THERE HE IS NOW.
STAY BACK.
STAY BACK, PLEASE.
GIVE HIM SOME ROOM.
LET THEM THROUGH,
PLEASE.
I HAVE ENOUGH SIGNATURES
FROM SHRECK EMPLOYEES ALONE
TO WARRANT A RECALL.
THAT'S NOT A THREAT,
JUST SIMPLE NUMBERS.
MAYBE. BUT YOU DON'T
HAVE AN ISSUE, MAX,
AND YOU SURE DON'T
HAVE A CANDIDATE.
HELLO,
MR. SHRECK!
THANK YOU VERY MUCH,
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN.
FROM THOSE OF US
AT CITY HALL
TO EACH AND EVERY ONE
OF YOU, HAPPY HOLIDAYS.
HERE'S A MAN WHO REALLY
NEEDS NO INTRODUCTION--
HE'S GIVEN SO MUCH
TO OUR CITY.
WILL YOU WELCOME, PLEASE,
GOTHAM'S OWN SANTA CLAUS--
MAX SHRECK?
PICK UP THOSE CONTRACTS
FROM PERSONNEL
AND PICK UP
THE DRY-CLEANING,
THE PAPER TOWELS...
OH, DARN.
FORGOT MY SPEECH.
REMIND ME
TO TAKE IT OUT
ON WHAT'S-HER-NAME.
SANTA CLAUS. AFRAID NOT.
I'M JUST A POOR SCHMO,
GOT LUCKY.
AND SUE ME
IF I WANT TO GIVE SOME BACK.
[CHEERING AND APPLAUSE]
I ONLY WISH
I COULD HAND OUT MORE
THAN JUST EXPENSIVE BAUBLES.
I WISH I COULD HAND OUT
WORLD PEACE
AND UNCONDITIONAL LOVE...
WRAPPED IN A BIG BOW.
[CHEERING AND APPLAUSE]
OH, BUT YOU CAN.
OH, BUT YOU WILL.
MERRY CHRISTMAS.
GREAT IDEA.
NOT MINE.
AAH!
OH!
OH, HURRY!
[ENGINE REVS]
[TIRES SQUEAL]
AAH!
WHAT ARE YOU WAITING FOR?
THE SIGNAL.
WE WANT THE BIG GUY,
THE GUY WHO RUNS THE SHOW.
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
NOT YOU.
SHRECK.
YOU'LL HAVE TO
GO THROUGH ME.
OOH! OOH!
CHIP.
DAD, GO.
SAVE YOURSELF.
DAD, GO!
AAH! OH!
AAH!
OH!
AAH! AAH!
OOH! AH!
AAH!
[TIRES SQUEAL]
AAH! OH!
HEH HEH HEH.
NO--HELP!
SHUT UP!
TAKE ONE STEP CLOSER,
MR. MANBAT, AND I'LL...
YOU MISSED.
AAH!
WOW.
THEBATMAN.
OR IS IT
JUST BATMAN?
UH, YOUR CHOICE,
OF COURSE.
WELL, THAT WAS...
VERY BRIEF.
JUST LIKE ALL THE MEN
IN MY LIFE.
WHAT MEN?
WELL...
THEN AGAIN, THERE'S YOU,
BUT YOU NEED THERAPY.
[SIREN]
[ZAP]
OOH!
THANKS FOR SAVING
THE DAY, BATMAN.
I'M AFRAID
THE CIRCUS GANG
IS BACK.
WE'LL SEE.
THEY ALMOST MADE OFF
WITH OUR MOVER AND SHAKER
MAX SHRECK, BUT--
WHERE IS
THAT INSUFFERABLE
SON OF A BITCH?
[AWK]
HI.
I BELIEVE THE WORD
YOU'RE LOOKING FOR
IS...
AAH!
HEH HEH HEH.
ACTUALLY, THIS IS ALL
JUST A BAD DREAM.
YOU'RE AT HOME IN BED,
HEAVILY SEDATED,
RESTING COMFORTABLY,
DYING FROM
THE CARCINOGENS
YOU
PERSONALLY SPEWED
IN A LIFETIME
OF PROFITEERING.
TRAGIC IRONY
OR POETIC JUSTICE?
YOU TELL ME. ARRGH.
MY GOD,
IT'S TRUE.
PENGUIN MAN
OF THE SEWER.
ODD AS IT MAY SEEM, MAX,
YOU AND I HAVE SOMETHING
IN COMMON.
WE'RE BOTH PERCEIVED
AS MONSTERS.
BUT SOMEHOW...
YOU'RE A WELL-RESPECTED
MONSTER,
AND I AM, TO DATE...
NOT.
FRANKLY, I FEEL
THAT'S A BUM RAP.
I'M A BUSINESSMAN.
TOUGH, YES.
SHREWD? O.K.
BUT THAT DOES NOT
MAKE ME A MONSTER.
DON'T EMBARRASS
YOURSELF, MAX.
I KNOW ALL ABOUT YOU.
WHAT YOU HIDE,
I DISCOVER.
WHAT YOU PUT
IN YOUR TOILET,
I PLACE ON MY MANTEL.
GET THE PICTURE?
WHAT, IS THAT SUPPOSED
TO HYPNOTIZE ME?
NO. JUST GIVE YOU
A SPLITTING HEADACHE.
WELL, IT'S NOT WORKING.
ALL RIGHT.
OH, YOU BIG BABY.
JUST BLANKS.
WOULD I GO THROUGH
ALL THIS TROUBLE TONIGHT
JUST TO KILL YOU?
NO, MAX.
I HAVE AN ENTIRELY
OTHER PURPOSE.
I'M READY, MAX.
I'VE BEEN DOWN HERE
TOO LONG.
IT'S TIME FOR ME
TO ASCEND,
TO RE-EMERGE.
WITH YOUR HELP,
YOUR KNOW-HOW,
YOUR SAVVY.
I WASN'T BORN
IN THE SEWER, YOU KNOW.
I COME FROM...
LIKE YOU,
AND LIKE YOU,
I WANT SOME RESPECT,
A RECOGNITION OF
MY BASIC HUMANITY,
BUT MOST OF ALL,
I WANT TO FIND OUT
WHO I AM
BY FINDING MY PARENTS,
LEARNING MY HUMAN NAME,
SIMPLE STUFF THAT THE
GOOD PEOPLE OF GOTHAM
TAKE FOR GRANTED. AWK.
AND EXACTLY WHY
AM I GOING TO HELP YOU?
WELL...
LET'S START.
[AWK AWK]
NOW...
OOH, WELL,
WHAT HAVE WE HERE?
LET'S SEE.
OH!
A BATCH OF TOXIC WASTE...
FROM YOUR CLEAN
TEXTILE PLANT.
THERE'S A WHOLE LAGOON
OF THIS CRUD IN THE BACK.
THAT COULD HAVE COME
FROM ANYWHERE.
WHAT ABOUT THE DOCUMENTS
THAT PROVE YOU OWN
HALF THE FIRETRAPS
IN GOTHAM CITY?
IF THERE WERE
SUCH DOCUMENTS--
THAT'S NOT
AN ADMISSION--
I WOULD HAVE SEEN TO IT
THEY WERE SHREDDED.
OH...
GOOD IDEA.
A LOT OF TAPE
AND A LITTLE PATIENCE
MAKE ALL THE DIFFERENCE.
BY THE WAY,
HOW'S FRED ATKINS,
YOUR OLD PARTNER?
FRED?
FRED'S ACTUALLY--
I BELIEVE HE'S ON
EXTENDED VACATION.
HE'S--HE'S GOOD.
HE'S GOOD.
HIYA, MAX. REMEMBER ME?
I'M FRED'S HAND.
HEY, YOU WANT TO GREET
ANY OTHER BODY PARTS?
REMEMBER, MAX,
YOU FLUSH IT,
I FLAUNT IT.
YOU KNOW WHAT...
MR. PENGUIN, SIR?
I THINK PERHAPS I
COULD HELP ORCHESTRATE
A LITTLE WELCOME-HOME
SCENARIO FOR YOU.
ONCE WE'RE BOTH
BACK HOME,
PERHAPS WE CAN HELP
EACH OTHER OUT.
HEY, YOU WON'T
REGRET THIS, MR. SHRECK.
THERE YOU GO.
HONEY, I'M HOME!
I FORGOT.
I'M NOT MARRIED.
[MEOW]
MISS KITTY.
BACK FROM MORE
SEXUAL ESCAPADES
YOU REFUSE TO SHARE?
HMM?
[KISSING SOUNDS]
NOT THAT I'D EVER PRY.
[MEOW]
OH, DRINK YOUR DINNER.
WHAT?
HOW CAN ANYONE
BE SO PATHETIC?
YES, TO YOU
I SEEM PATHETIC,
BUT I'M A WORKING GIRL,
GOT TO PAY THE RENT.
MAYBE IF YOU CHIPPED IN
INSTEAD OF STEPPING OUT.
[TAPE REWINDS]
SELINA DEAR,
IT'S YOUR MOTHER.
JUST CALLING
TO SAY HELLO.
YEAH, RIGHT, BUT...
BUT I'M DISAPPOINTED
YOU'RE NOT COMING HOME
FOR CHRISTMAS.
I WANT TO DISCUSS
JUST WHY YOU INSIST
ON LANGUISHING
IN GOTHAM CITY
AS SOME LOWLY SECRETARY.
LOWLY ASSISTANT.
[BEEP]
SELINA, ABOUT THAT
CHRISTMAS GETAWAY
WE PLANNED...
I'LL BE GOING ALONE.
DR. SHAW SAYS I NEED
TO BE MY OWN PERSON
AND NOT AN APPENDAGE.
[BEEP]
[TAPE REWINDS]
SOME APPENDAGE.
WELL, THE PARTY NEVER STOPS
ON SELINA KYLE'S
ANSWERING MACHINE.
I GUESS I SHOULD HAVE
LET HIM WIN THAT LAST
RACQUETBALL GAME.
[COMPUTER VOICE]
HELLO, SELINA KYLE.
WE'RE CALLING
TO TELL YOU
ABOUT EXCITING NEW
GOTHAM LADY PERFUME.
IT MAKES WOMEN
FEEL LIKE WOMEN,
AND THE MEN HAVE
NO COMPLAINTS, EITHER.
[BEEP]
HI, SELINA. THIS
IS YOURSELF CALLING.
STUPID. I'M CALLING
TO REMIND YOU, HONEY,
YOU HAVE TO COME
BACK TO THE OFFICE
UNLESS YOU
REMEMBERED TO BRING HOME
THE BRUCE WAYNE FILE.
THE MEETING'S
ON WEDNESDAY.
WORKING LATE?
OH! UM...
I'M--I'M JUST BONING UP
FOR YOUR, UH,
BRUCE WAYNE MEETING
IN THE MORNING.
I PULLED ALL THE FILES ON
THE PROPOSED POWER PLANT
AND, UH, THE--
M-MR. WAYNE'S
HOPED-FOR INVESTMENT,
AND, UM, I EVEN OPENED
THE PROTECTED FILES AND--
HOW INDUSTRIOUS.
HOW DID YOU OPEN
PROTECTED FILES...
MAY I ASK?
UM...
WELL...
I FIGURED YOUR PASSWORD
WAS "GERALDO,"
YOUR CHIHUAHUA,
AND IT WAS.
HMM.
UM, THIS IS ALL
VERY INTERESTING,
THOUGH A BIT
ON THE TECHNICAL SIDE.
UM, I MEAN ABOUT
HOW THE POWER PLANT
IS A POWER PLANT
IN NAME ONLY.
AND SINCE, IN FACT,
IT'S GOING TO BE
A BIG GIANT, UM...
A BIG GIANT,
UH, CAPACITOR?
UH, AND THAT, UH,
INSTEAD OF
GENERATING POWER,
IT'LL SORT OF
BE SUCKING POWER
FROM, UM...
GOTHAM CITY...
AND STORING IT,
SORT OF...
STOCKPILING IT,
WHICH IS A VERY, UM,
NOVEL APPROACH, I'D SAY.
AND WHO WOULD YOU
SAY THIS TO?
UM...
NOBODY.
WHAT DID CURIOSITY
DO TO THE CAT?
I'M NO CAT.
I'M JUST
AN ASSISTANT...
UH, SECRETARY.
AND A VERY GOOD ONE.
TOO GOOD?
HMM.
LISTEN.
IT'S OUR SECRET.
HONEST.
HOW CAN YOU BE SO MEAN
TO SOMEONE SO MEANINGLESS?
THIS POWER PLANT
IS MY LEGACY.
IT'S WHAT
I LEAVE BEHIND...
FOR CHIP.
NOTHING MUST
PREVENT THAT.
O.K.
GO AHEAD.
INTIMIDATE ME.
BULLY ME IF IT
MAKES YOU FEEL BIG.
IT'S NOT LIKE YOU
CAN JUST KILL ME.
ACTUALLY,
IT'S A LOT LIKE THAT.
OH.
HUH?
WHAT?
HA HA HA!
YOU KNOW,
FOR A SECOND THERE,
YOU REALLY FRIGHTENED ME.
OH!
AAH!
HUH.
[MEOW]
HONEY, I'M HOME.
OH, I FORGOT.
I'M NOT MARRIED.
[MEOW]
[TAPE REWINDS]
SELINA,
THIS IS YOUR MOTHER.
CALL ME.
[BEEP]
SELINA, THIS
IS YOUR MOTHER.
WHY HAVEN'T YOU
CALLED ME BACK?
[BEEP]
HELLO, SELINA KYLE.
WE'RE JUST CALLING
TO MAKE SURE
YOU'VE TRIED
GOTHAM LADY PERFUME.
ONE WHIFF OF THIS
AT THE OFFICE,
AND YOUR BOSS
WILL BE ASKING YOU
TO STAY AFTER WORK
FOR A CANDLELIGHT
STAFF MEETING FOR TWO.
GOTHAM LADY PERFUME.
EXCLUSIVELY AT SHRECK'S
DEPARTMENT STORE.
AAH!
[MEOW]
[YEOW]
[MEOW MEOW]
[SEWING MACHINE RUNS]
I DON'T KNOW
ABOUT YOU, MISS KITTY,
BUT I FEEL SO MUCH YUMMIER.
WELL, LADIES AND GENTLEMEN--
AHEM--
I STAND BEFORE YOU
ONCE AGAIN
TO DENOUNCE THE URBAN CHAOS
WE SEEM TO HAVE TO LIVE WITH
IN OUR GREAT CITY.
IT'S GOT TO STOP,
AND IT'S GOING
TO STOP.
NOW, OUR COMMUNITY
IS COMING APART
IN A SEASON WHEN IT
SHOULD BE COMING TOGETHER.
I DON'T CARE WHAT
THE CYNICS MAY SAY.
THIS IS
THE CHRISTMAS SEASON.
IT SHOULD BE
A TIME OF HEALING,
AND I TELL YOU THAT
NOT ONLY AS AN OFFICIAL,
BUT AS A HUSBAND
AND A FATHER.
LAST NIGHT'S VIOLENCE
WILL NOT HAPPEN AGAIN.
OH! OH!
I'M NOT REALLY ONE
FOR SPEECHES,
SO I'LL JUST SAY...THANKS.
WAAH!
NO!
NO! IT'S THE HIDEOUS
PENGUIN MAN.
HERE. TAKE THE BABY.
JUST DON'T HURT ME.
WAAH!
COOCHIE-COOCHIE-COO.
AH!
COOCHIE-COOCHIE-COO!
[BABY CRYING]
COOCHIE-COO.
[BABY BABBLES]
OH!
UH.
AH.
THIS WAS THE
REMARKABLE SCENE
IN GOTHAM PLAZA.
THE MYSTERIOUS
PENGUIN
SAVING THE LIFE
OF THE MAYOR'S
BABY
AND ANNOUNCING
HIS PRESENCE
TO THE WORLD.
ALL I WANT IN RETURN
IS A CHANCE TO FIND
MY MOM AND DAD.
A CHANCE TO FIND OUT
WHO THEY ARE.
AND THUSLY, WHO I AM.
AND THEN...
WITH MY PARENTS,
TRY TO UNDERSTAND WHY...
WHY THEY DID
WHAT I GUESS THEY FELT
THEY HAD TO DO...
TO A CHILD...
WHO WAS BORN...
A LITTLE DIFFERENT.
A CHILD...
WHO SPENT HIS FIRST
CHRISTMAS...
AND MANY SINCE...
IN A SEWER.
MR. WAYNE,
SOMETHING WRONG?
NO.
UH...HIS PARENTS.
[ANNOUNCER]
AGAIN, THIS SCENE
DIRECT FROM GOTHAM PLAZA...
I HOPE HE FINDS THEM.
PENGUIN MAN
OF THE SEWER.
HERE HE IS,
STANDING ALONGSIDE
GOTHAM'S LEADING CITIZEN--
MAX SHRECK.
[REPORTER]
PEOPLE WANT TO KNOW.
HOW ABOUT A STATEMENT?
PENGUIN'S NOT TO BE
DISTURBED.
THE HALL OF RECORDS
IS A PUBLIC PLACE.
YOU'RE ABRIDGING
THE FREEDOM
OF THE PRESS!
WHAT ABOUT THE FREEDOM
TO REDISCOVER YOUR ROOTS...
WITH DIGNITY AND PRIVACY?
IS THE PENGUIN
A PERSONAL FRIEND?
YES, HE'S A PERSONAL
FRIEND--OF THIS WHOLE CITY,
SO HAVE A HEART.
GIVE THE CONSTITUTION
A REST, O.K.?
IT'S CHRISTMAS.
LET'S GO.
UH.
[MUTTERING]
[BATS SQUEAKING]
AH. "RED TRIANGLE
CIRCUS
"PUT ON A SWELL SHOW
WITH FIERCE LIONS..."
"CIRCUS RETURNED
FOR TWO-WEEK...
KIDS WILL LOVE..."
THANKS.
IT'S COLD.
IT'S VICHYSSOISE, SIR.
IT'S SUPPOSED TO BE COLD.
"CIRCUS IS BACK
WITH A FREAK SHOW.
"MAY NOT BE SUITABLE
FOR KIDS,
"FEATURING A POODLE LADY,
"THE WORLD'S FATTEST MAN,
AND AQUATIC BIRD BOY."
WHY ARE YOU NOW
DETERMINED TO PROVE
THAT THIS PENGUIN
IS NOT WHAT HE SEEMS?
MUST YOU BE THE ONLY
LONELY MAN-BEAST IN TOWN?
"THE CIRCUS FOLDED
ITS TENTS YESTERDAY,
"PERHAPS FOREVER,
"AFTER NUMEROUS REPORTS
OF MISSING CHILDREN.
"POLICE HAVE CLOSED DOWN
"THE RED TRIANGLE'S
FAIRGROUNDS.
"HOWEVER, AT LEAST ONE
FREAK SHOW PERFORMER VANISHED
BEFORE HE COULD BE
QUESTIONED."
I SUPPOSE YOU FEEL
BETTER NOW, SIR.
[SIGHING]
NO.
ACTUALLY, I FEEL WORSE.
[RING]
WHY ARE YOU
STILL OUT?
ARE YOU CONCERNED
ABOUT THAT STRANGE,
HEROIC PENGUIN
PERSON?
I THINK HE KNOWS
WHO HIS PARENTS ARE.
THERE'S SOMETHING ELSE.
O.K. STAY BACK.
SO, MR. PENGUIN...
PENGUIN!
OUT OF THE WAY!
SO, MR. PENGUIN--
A PENGUIN IS A BIRD
THAT CANNOT FLY!
I AM A MAN!
I HAVE A NAME.
OSWALD COBBLEPOT.
MR. COBBLEPOT.
YOU'LL NEVER GET
TO SETTLE UP WITH THEM, HUH?
TRUE.
I WAS THEIR NUMBER ONE SON,
AND THEY TREATED ME
LIKE NUMBER TWO,
BUT IT'S HUMAN NATURE
TO FEAR THE UNUSUAL.
PERHAPS WHEN I HELD MY...
TIFFANY BABY RATTLE...
WITH A SHINY FLIPPER
INSTEAD OF FIVE CHUBBY
DIGITS,
THEY FREAKED.
BUT I FORGIVE THEM.
PENGUIN FORGIVES
PARENTS!
"I'M AT PEACE!"
"YOU DON'T NEED HANDS
WHEN YOU'VE GOT HEART."
"MY HEART'S FILLED
WITH LOVE.
I FEEL 5 FEET TALL."
HE'S LIKE A FROG
THAT BECAME A PRINCE.
NO. HE'S MORE
LIKE A PENGUIN.
AAH!
HEY, NOW, NOW.
PRETTY LITTLE THING.
NICE AND EASY.
THERE.
YEAH.
I JUST LOVE
A BIG, STRONG MAN
WHO'S NOT AFRAID
TO SHOW IT
WITH SOMEONE HALF
HIS SIZE.
BE GENTLE.
IT'S MY FIRST TIME.
UNH!
TIC, TAC, TOE!
THANKS. I--
YOU MAKE IT SO EASY,
DON'T YOU?
ALWAYS WAITING
FOR SOME BATMAN
TO SAVE YOU.
I AM CATWOMAN.
HEAR ME ROAR.
[CAR HORNS HONK]
I'D OFFER YOU COFFEE,
BUT MY ASSISTANT'S
USING HER VACATION TIME.
GOOD TIME, TOO.
EVERYONE
BUT THE BANDITS
WILL BE SLACKING OFF
TILL AFTER
THE NEW YEAR ANYWAY.
NOT SURE I LIKE
THE INFERENCE,
BRUCE.
SORRY. DIDN'T REALIZE
I MADE ONE.
I'M PUSHING
THIS POWER PLANT NOW
BECAUSE IT'LL
COST MORE LATER.
A MILLION SAVED
IS A MILLION EARNED.
I COMMISSIONED
THIS REPORT.
I THOUGHT
YOU MIGHT WANT TO
TAKE A LOOK AT IT.
THE POINT IS, MAX,
GOTHAM CITY
HAS A POWER SURPLUS.
I'M SURE
YOU KNOW THAT.
MY QUESTION IS...
WHAT'S YOUR ANGLE?
POWER SURPLUS?
BRUCE, SHAME ON YOU.
NO SUCH THING.
ONE CAN NEVER HAVE
TOO MUCH POWER.
IF MY LIFE
HAS A MEANING,
THAT'S THE MEANING.
WELL, I'M GOING TO
FIGHT YOU ON THIS.
I'VE ALREADY SPOKEN
TO THE MAYOR.
WE SEE EYE-TO-EYE--
MAYORS COME AND GO.
BLUE BLOODS TIRE EASY.
YOU THINK YOU COULD
GO 15 ROUNDS
WITH MUHAMMAD SHRECK?
WELL, I GUESS
WE'LL FIND OUT.
OF COURSE, I DON'T
HAVE A CRIME BOSS
LIKE COBBLEPOT.
CRIME BOSS?
SHOW US WHAT
YOU KNOW,
MR. TO-THE-MANOR-BORN
WITH-A-SILVER-SPOON.
OSWALD IS GOTHAM'S
NEW GOLDEN BOY,
IF HIS PARENTS
HADN'T 86'd HIM,
YOU'D HAVE BEEN
PREP-SCHOOL BUNKIES.
OSWALD CONTROLS
THE RED TRIANGLE GANG.
I CAN'T PROVE IT,
BUT WE BOTH--
WAYNE, I'LL NOT STAND
FOR MUDSLINGING
IN THIS OFFICE.
IF MY ASSISTANT
WAS HERE,
SHE ALREADY WOULD
HAVE ESCORTED YOU--
ANYWHERE HE WANTS,
PREFERABLY
SOME NIGHTSPOT, GROTTO,
OR SECLUDED HIDEAWAY.
NICE SUIT.
THANKS.
SELINA.
SELINA, SELINA.
THAT'S MY NAME,
MAXIMILLIONS.
DON'T WEAR IT OUT,
OR I'LL MAKE YOU BUY ME
A NEW ONE.
SELINA...
THIS IS BRUCE...
WAYNE.
YEAH. WE'VE MET.
HAVE WE?
OH, I'M SORRY.
I MISTOOK ME
FOR SOMEBODY ELSE.
YOU MEAN MISTOOK ME.
I MISTOOK M--
UH, YEAH.
ISN'T THAT WHAT
I SAID?
NO. I DON'T THINK SO.
WHAT HAPPENED?
DID YOU INJURE YOURSELF...
ON THAT SKI SLOPE?
IS THAT WHY YOU CUT
SHORT YOUR VACATION
AND CAME BACK?
YOU KNOW, IT'S...
A BLUR.
I MEAN,
NOT COMPLETE AMNESIA.
I--I REMEMBER
SISTER MARY MARGARET
PUKING IN CHURCH
AND BETSY RILEY SAYING
IT WAS MORNING SICKNESS,
AND I REMEMBER THE TIME
I FORGOT TO WEAR
MY UNDERPANTS TO SCHOOL,
AND THE NAME OF THE BOY
WHO NOTICED
WAS RICKY FRIEDBURG.
HE'S DEAD NOW.
BUT LAST NIGHT--
COMPLETE BLUR.
COULDN'T YOU JUST DIE?
SELINA.
PLEASE.
SHOW OUT
MR. WAYNE.
WITH PLEASURE.
UM, YOUR COAT,
MR. WAYNE.
OH, RIGHT.
YOU DON'T SEEM
LIKE THE TYPE
WHO DOES BUSINESS
WITH MR. SHRECK.
AND YOU DON'T SEEM
LIKE THAT TYPE
WHO TAKES ORDERS
FROM HIM.
WELL, THAT'S
A LONG STORY.
YOU KNOW, I COULD
FREE UP SOME TIME.
I'M LISTED.
I'M TEMPTED.
I'M WORKING.
I'M LEAVING.
DAD, YOU BUY THAT
BLURRY BUSINESS?
WOMEN. NOTHING
SURPRISES ME, CHIP,
EXCEPT
YOUR LATE MOTHER.
WHO'D HAVE THOUGHT
SELINA HAD
A BRAIN TO DAMAGE?
BOTTOM LINE--
IF SHE TRIES
TO BLACKMAIL ME,
I'LL DROP HER OUT
A HIGHER WINDOW.
MEANTIME, I GOT
BETTER FISH TO FRY.
OSWALD.
IT'S MAX.
YOU HOME?
HOW YA BEEN?
YOUR
EXTENDED FAMILY.
GOOD TO HAVE
A FAMILY.
GRRR.
I'D MUCH RATHER NOT BE
DISTURBED NOW.
COME ON DOWNSTAIRS,
OSWALD.
I HAVE A SURPRISE.
I DON'T LIKE SURPRISES.
UHH.
COME ON DOWN.
AHH.
DON'T PEEK.
YOU'LL SPOIL IT.
TA-DA!
[MUTTERING]
HUH?
YES, ADULATION
IS A CROSS TO BEAR.
GOD KNOWS I KNOW.
BUT SOMEONE'S
GOT TO SUPPLANT
OUR
STANDING-IN-THE-WAY-
OF-PROGRESS MAYOR,
AND DON'T DENY IT,
MR. COBBLEPOT.
YOU'VE
GOT THE MAGIC.
YOUR CHARISMA'S
BIGGER THAN
BOTH OF US.
COME ON DOWN.
MAYOR?
MAYOR.
MAX, ELECTIONS
HAPPEN IN NOVEMBER.
IS THIS NOT LATE
DECEMBER?
DON'T WORRY
ABOUT IT.
I WANT YOU TO MEET
JEN AND JOSH,
MY IMAGE
CONSULTANTS.
HERE.
RECLAIM
YOUR BIRTHRIGHT.
I'M JEN.
HI.
O.K. LET'S SEE.
WHAT I'D LIKE
TO DO FIRST
IS PUT THESE LITTLE
GLOVE THINGIES ON YOU.
OUR RESEARCH TELLS US
THAT VOTERS LIKE FINGERS,
SO IF WE WANT
TO JUST LOSE THIS...
NO?
WE'LL DO IT ANOTHER
TIME, THEN. OKEY-DOKE?
NOT A LOT OF
REFLECTIVE SURFACES
DOWN
IN THE SEWER, HUH?
STILL...
COULD BE WORSE.
MY NOSE COULD BE
GUSHING BLOOD.
OOH!
YOUR NOSE COULD BE--
WHAT DO YOU MEAN
BY THAT?
AAH!
OH!
EVERYBODY!
BACK TO WORK.
LET'S MAKE A MAYOR!
YOU'RE RIGHT.
WE MISSED
THE REGULARLY
SCHEDULED ELECTION,
BUT PUBLIC OFFICIALS
CAN BE RECALLED,
IMPEACHED,
GIVEN THE BOOT.
LOOK AT NIXON,
AGNEW.
THEN THINK OF YOU,
OSWALD COBBLEPOT,
FILLING THE VOID.
I'D LIKE TO FILL
HERVOID.
WE'LL NEED
SIGNATURES
TO OVERTURN
THE BALLOT.
I CAN SUPPLY THOSE,
OSWALD.
TEACH HER MY FRENCH
FLIPPER TRICK.
OSWALD, WE NEED
ONE MORE THING.
A PLATFORM.
STOP GLOBAL WARMING.
START GLOBAL COOLING.
MAKE THE WORLD
A GIANT ICEBOX.
I LIKE IT,
BUT TO GET
THE MAYOR RECALLED,
WE HAVE TO HAVE
A CATALYST.
YOU'RE DOING GREAT,
MAYOR COBBLEPOT.
YOUR TABLE IS READY,
I NEED YOU, OSWALD.
I NEED YOU NOW!
OH, THAT'S
THE BIGGEST PARASOL
I'VE EVER SEEN.
SOON,
AN INCIDENT LIKE
THE GULF OF TONKIN
OR THE REICHSTAG
FIRE.
HUH?
HUH.
YOU WANT MY OLD
FRIENDS UP THERE
TO DRIVE THE MAYOR
INTO A FOAMING FRENZY.
EXACTLY.
SOUNDS FUN.
OH, BUT I...
I--I MUSTN'T
GET SIDETRACKED, MAXIE.
I GOT MY OWN THINGS
TO TEND TO.
SIDETRACKED, OSWALD?
THIS IS YOUR CHANCE
TO FULFILL A DESTINY
YOUR PARENTS
CARELESSLY DISCARDED.
RECLAIM MY BIRTHRIGHT,
YOU MEAN?
IMAGINE. YOU'LL HAVE
THE EAR OF THE MEDIA,
ACCESS TO CAPTAINS
OF INDUSTRY.
UNLIMITED POONTANG.
YOU DRIVE A HARD
BARGAIN, MAXIE.
ALL RIGHT.
I'LL BE MAYOR.
BURN, BABY, BURN!
STOP!
NO!
AAH!
UHH!
AAAAH!
WAH HA HA HA!
YEE-HA!
[GRRR]
UH!
ARRR!
WHO IS SHE?
WHATIS SHE?
I DON'T KNOW
WHETHER TO OPEN FIRE
OR FALL IN LOVE.
YOU POOR GUYS,
ALWAYS CONFUSING
YOUR PISTOLS
WITH YOUR PRIVATES.
DON'T HURT US, LADY.
OUR TAKE-HOME'S
LESS THAN 300.
YOU'RE OVERPAID.
HIT THE ROAD.
AAH!
YEAH.
GO AHEAD
AND HIT ME.
ADMIRING YOUR HANDIWORK?
TOURING
THE RIOT SCENE.
GRAVELY ASSESSING
THE DEVASTATION.
UPSTANDING MAYOR
STUFF.
YOU'RE NOT THE MAYOR.
THINGS CHANGE.
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
AH, THE DIRECT
APPROACH.
I ADMIRE THAT
IN A MAN
WITH A MASK.
YOU DON'T REALLY
THINK YOU'LL WIN,
DO YOU?
THINGS CHANGE.
MEOW.
I SAW HER FIRST.
GOT TO FLY.
HOW COULD YOU?
I'M A WOMAN.
I'M SORRY. I--I...
UH!
UHH.
AS I WAS SAYING,
I'M A WOMAN
AND CAN'T BE TAKEN
FOR GRANTED.
LIFE'S A BITCH.
NOW SO AM I.
AAH!
WHO ARE YOU?
WHO'S THE MAN
BEHIND THE BAT?
MAYBE YOU CAN
HELP ME FIND
THE WOMAN
BEHIND THE CAT.
NO.
THAT'S NOT YOU.
AHH.
THERE YOU ARE.
SAVED BY KITTY LITTER.
[LAUGHING]
OH. BASTARD.
ALFRED,
BRING ME SOME
ANTISEPTIC OINTMENT,
WOULD YOU?
COMING.
ARE YOU
IN PAIN, SIR?
NO.
NOT REALLY.
MEOW.
[APPLAUSE]
MAYOR.
I MAY HAVE SAVED
THE MAYOR'S BABY,
BUT I REFUSE TO SAVE
A MAYOR
WHO STOOD BY HELPLESS
AS A BABY
WHILE GOTHAM
WAS RAVAGED BY A DISEASE
THAT TURNED EAGLE SCOUTS
INTO CRAZED CLOWNS
AND HAPPY HOMEMAKERS
INTO CATWOMEN!
[APPLAUSE]
THANK YOU.
YEAH.
OSWALD COBBLEPOT,
WHO'S BEEN
ROMANCING GOTHAM,
TODAY MADE HIS BID
TO RUN GOTHAM.
THANK YOU!
MR. COBBLEPOT,
YOU'RE THE COOLEST
ROLE MODEL
A YOUNG PERSON
COULD HAVE.
AND YOU'RE THE HOTTEST
YOUNG PERSON
A ROLE MODEL COULD HAVE.
HMM...
HERE.
WEAR A BUTTON.
AHH. LET ME JUST...
GET IT ON THERE.
AHH...
THANK--THANK YOU.
THANK YOU.
I COULD GET
INTO THIS MAYOR STUFF.
IT'S NOT ABOUT POWER.
IT'S ABOUT REACHING OUT
TO PEOPLE, TOUCHING PEOPLE,
GROPING PEOPLE.
PENGUIN?
MY NAME'S NOT PENGUIN!
IT'S OSWALD COBBLEPOT.
OSWALD...
THERE'S SOME BODY
HERE TO SEE YOU.
OH. OH.
[GRUNTING]
JUST THE PUSSY I'VE
BEEN LOOKING FOR.
IT'S CHILLY IN HERE.
I'LL WARM YOU.
DOWN, OSWALD.
[SNIFF SNIFF]
WE NEED TO TALK.
YOU SEE,
YOU AND I HAVE
SOMETHING IN COMMON.
SOUNDS FAMILIAR.
UH, APPETITE
FOR DESTRUCTION?
CONTEMPT FOR THE
CZARS OF FASHION?
WAIT. DON'T TELL ME.
NAKED SEXUAL
CHARISMA?
BATMAN.
THE THORN IN BOTH
OUR SIDES,
THE FLY
IN OUR OINTMENT.
OINTMENT, UH-HUH.
I'VE GOT SCENTED
OR UNSCENTED.
I'LL COME BACK LATER.
PERCHANCE, ARE YOU
A REGISTERED VOTER?
I AM
A MAYORAL PROSPECT,
YOU KNOW.
I HAVE BUT ONE
PET CAUSE TODAY--
BAN THE BAT.
OH, HIM AGAIN.
NO BOTHER.
HE'S ALREADY
HISTORY.
CHECK IT OUT.
WE'LL DISASSEMBLE
HIS BATMOBILE
AND TURN IT INTO
AN H-BOMB ON WHEELS.
NO, NO.
HE'D HAVE EVEN MORE
POWER AS A MARTYR.
TO DESTROY BATMAN,
WE MUST FIRST
TURN HIM
INTO WHAT HE HATES
THE MOST,
NAMELY, US.
YOU MEAN FRAME HIM?
NOT EVEN IN OFFICE YET
AND ALREADY
AN ENEMIES LIST, HMM?
ARRR!
THOSE NAMES ARE
NOT FOR PRYING EYES.
HEY...
WHY SHOULD I TRUST
SOME CATBROAD
ANYWAY?
MAYBE YOU'RE
JUST A SCREWED-UP
SORORITY CHICK
WHO'S GETTING BACK
AT HER DADDY
FOR NOT BUYING HER
THAT PONY
WHEN SHE TURNED
SWEET 16.
[CHIRPING]
[WHISTLING]
[CLICKING TONGUE]
NICE BIRDIE.
YES.
MMM.
NICE KITTY.
LOOK, BATMAN
NAPALMED MY ARM.
HE KNOCKED ME
OFF A BUILDING
JUST WHEN I WAS
STARTING TO FEEL
GOOD ABOUT MYSELF.
I WANT TO PLAY
AN INTEGRAL PART
IN HIS DEGRADATION.
[MUTTERING]
A PLAN IS FORMING.
EEE! EEE! EEE! EEE!
I WANT IN.
THE THOUGHT
OF BUSTING BATMAN
MAKES ME FEEL ALL...
DIRTY.
MAYBE I'LL JUST
GIVE MYSELF A BATH
RIGHT HERE.
I CHALLENGE THE MAYOR
TO RELIGHT
THE CHRISTMAS TREE
IN GOTHAM PLAZA
TOMORROW NIGHT.
SIR, SHALL WE
CHANGE THE CHANNEL
TO A PROGRAM
WITH SOME DIGNITY
AND CLASS?
LOVE CONNECTION,
PERHAPS?
WITHOUT FEAR!
NOT THAT I HAVE ANY FAITH
IN THE MAYOR,
BUT I HOPE AND PRAY
THAT BATMAN WILL BE
PRESENT
TO PRESERVE THE PEACE.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
SUBTLE.
THANK YOU.
[APPLAUSE]
WHY ARE YOU
DOING THIS?
SELINA?
HUH?
HI. I'M SORRY.
I DIDN'T MEAN
TO SCARE YOU.
SCARE ME? NO.
I WAS SCARING MYSELF,
ACTUALLY.
I DON'T SEE HOW.
NICE TO SEE YOU OUT
IN THE REAL WORLD
AWAY FROM SHRECK.
YEAH. WELL, UH,
IT'S...NICE TO BE HERE.
YOU ALL RIGHT?
HMM?
MM-HMM.
YOU LOOK LIKE
MAYBE YOU HAVE
THE HOLIDAY BLUES
OR SOMETHING.
NO.
BOY...
THE NEWS THESE DAYS.
WEIRD.
I HEARD ON TV
THAT CATWOMAN IS THOUGHT
TO WEIGH 140 POUNDS.
I DON'T KNOW HOW THESE
HACKS SLEEP AT NIGHT.
IT'S NOT EVEN ACCURATE.
"BATMAN BLOWS IT?"
HE PROBABLY SAVED
MILLIONS OF DOLLARS
IN PROPERTY DAMAGE
ALONE.
YOU'RE NOT GOING
TO THAT, ARE YOU,
THE, UH, RELIGHTING
OF THE TREE THING?
I WOULDN'T BE
CAUGHT DEAD THERE.
IT'S GOING TO BE
A HOT TIME
IN THE COLD TOWN
TONIGHT.
YOU--YOU GOT KIND
OF A DARK SIDE,
DON'T YOU?
NO DARKER
THAN YOURS, BRUCE.
[HORN HONKS]
LISTEN, WHY DON'T
YOU COME OVER,
AND WE CAN WATCH
TOGETHER ON TV?
WHAT?
THE TREE-LIGHTING
CEREMONY.
I--I CAN'T.
I HAVE TO, UH,
BE SOMEWHERE TONIGHT.
COME FOR AN EARLY
DINNER. 5:00.
LET'S SAY 6:00.
O.K. 5:00.
5:00. YOU AND ME.
O.K.?
THE TREE LIGHTS UP.
THEN I PUSH THE BUTTON.
NO, NO. WAIT, WAIT.
I PRESS THE BUTTON,
THEN THE TREE LIGHTS UP.
I PRESS THE BUTTON...
WHO ARE YOU?
TALENT SCOUT.
COME IN.
YOU KNOW, I DON'T
JUST LIGHT TREES,
I'M AN ACTRESS ALSO.
OH, WELL.
WHAT IS THAT THING,
A CAMERA OR SOMETHING?
SAY CHEESE.
CHEESE.
THANKS, ALFRED.
I'M SURE HE'S
WONDERFUL...COMPANY,
BUT DOESN'T
THE GOLD-PLATED
BACHELOR BIT
GET A LITTLE STALE?
A LOT LIKE THE
"LONELY SECRETARY
SYNDROME," I GUESS.
EXECUTIVE ASSISTANT.
OH, SORRY.
SECRETARY.
ANY GIRLFRIEND?
SURE.
OH, YOU MEAN, UH,
AS IN SERIOUS?
UH, NO.
HAD ONE.
DIDN'T WORK.
WHAT WENT WRONG?
HANG ON.
I THINK I KNOW.
YOU KEPT THINGS
FROM HER.
NO. TOLD HER
EVERYTHING.
OH? AND THE TRUTH
FRIGHTENED HER?
WELL, THERE ARE
TWO TRUTHS...
YOU KNOW,
AND SHE HAD TROUBLE
RECONCILING THEM
BECAUSE
I HAD TROUBLE...
UM,
RECONCILING THEM.
YEAH.
SEE, VICKI THOUGHT--
VICKI?
ICE SKATER
OR STEWARDESS?
NO. SHE WAS, UM,
A PHOTOJOURNALIST.
WELL, WAS VICKI RIGHT
ABOUT YOUR...
DIFFICULTY WITH DUALITY?
SEE, IF I SAY YES,
THEN, UH...
YOU'RE GOING
TO THINK OF ME
AS A NORMAN BATES/
TED BUNDY TYPE,
AND, UH...
WELL,
YOU MIGHT NOT
LET ME KISS YOU.
IT'S THE SO-CALLED
NORMAL GUYS
WHO ALWAYS LET YOU DOWN.
SICKOS NEVER SCARE ME.
AT LEAST
THEY'RE COMMITTED.
WELL...YEAH.
I CAN'T DO THAT.
NEITHER CAN I.
THIS IS
A SPECIAL BULLETIN.
THE ICE PRINCESS
HAS BEEN KIDNAPPED.
CAN YOU CONFIRM
THE REPORTS
OF BATMAN'S
SUSPECTED
INVOLVEMENT
IN THE ABDUCTION?
THIS EVIDENCE
IS PURELY CIRCUMSTANTIAL.
THIS WAS FOUND
STAINED WITH BLOOD
IN THE MISSING GIRL'S
DRESSING ROOM.
I GOT TO
GET OUT OF HERE.
NO. IT'S YOUR HOUSE.
JUST SIT FOR
A SECOND AND RELAX.
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
ALFRED, I'VE GOT
TO GET DOWN
TO THE PLAZA.
I SAW.
HE'S PRACTICALLY
BEGGING ME TO SHOW.
SNUB HIM.
CAN'T. THERE'S BEEN
A KIDNAPPING.
HERE'S WHAT YOU DO.
Shit!
TELL SELINA--MISS KYLE--
TELL HER I HAD
TO GO OUT OF TOWN.
A BIG BUSINESS DEAL
CAME UP.
NO. YOU KNOW WHAT?
LET HER KNOW THAT--
NOT IN SOME KIND
OF DUMB,
"BE MY GIRLFRIEND"
KIND OF WAY--
I'LL RELAY THE MESSAGE.
MISS KYLE--
ALFRED!
MR. WAYNE TOLD ME
TO TELL YOU--
MR. WAYNE?
OH, BRUCE.
YES, UM...WOULD YOU
TELL HIM FOR ME
THAT I'VE BEEN GOING
THROUGH A LOT OF,
UM, CHANGES, AND--
NO.
UM, JUST THAT THIS
IS NOT A REJECTION,
MY ABRUPTLY LEAVING.
IN FACT, HE MAKES ME
FEEL THE WAY
I HOPE I REALLY AM.
NO. COULD YOU JUST
MAKE UP A SONNET
OR SOMETHING?
A DIRTY LIMERICK?
ONE HAS JUST
SPRUNG TO MIND.
THANKS.
UH, THIS WAY, MA'AM.
OH. OH, SORRY.
WHERE IS THAT?
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN.
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
PLEASE,
IF I COULD HAVE
YOUR ATTENTION.
NOW, FOLKS, I KNOW
THAT TO MANY OF YOU
GOTHAM SEEMS A BIT
BELEAGUERED THESE DAYS,
BUT I WANT YOU TO KNOW
THAT YOUR ELECTED OFFICIALS
AND YOUR POLICE DEPARTMENT
HAVE THE SITUATION
WELL IN HAND.
[MAYOR]
...IS UNHEARD OF.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
NOW, COMMISSIONER GORDON
HAS...
GOT TO HURRY.
THANK YOU.
I WAS SET UP.
I WAS KIDNAPPED
BY AN UGLY BIRD MAN
WITH FISH BREATH.
DID SOMEBODY SAY FISH?
I HAVEN'T BEEN FED
ALL DAY.
EAT FLOOR.
HIGH FIBER.
HEY, STUD,
I THOUGHT WE HAD
SOMETHING TOGETHER.
WE DO.
GOT TO GO.
GIRL TALK.
[BEEPING]
SH-SHE LET ME GO.
I REASONED WITH HER
GIRL TO GIRL.
BE CAREFUL.
DON'T MOVE.
LAWN DART!
AAH!
BATS WITH WINGS,
DO YOUR THING.
AAH!
BATMAN PUSHED
THE PRINCESS!
AAH!
AWK!
HOLD YOUR FI--
HOLD YOUR FIRE!
UH!
UH.
YOU'RE CATNIP
TO A GIRL LIKE ME.
HANDSOME,
DAZED,
AND TO DIE FOR.
MISTLETOE CAN BE DEADLY
IF YOU EAT IT.
MM, BUT A KISS
CAN BE EVEN DEADLIER
IF YOU MEAN IT.
YOU'RE THE SECOND MAN
WHO KILLED ME THIS WEEK,
BUT I'VE GOT
SEVEN LIVES LEFT.
I TRIED TO SAVE YOU.
SEEMS LIKE EVERY WOMAN
YOU TRY TO SAVE
ENDS UP DEAD...
OR DEEPLY RESENTFUL.
MAYBE YOU SHOULD RETIRE.
DAMN.
OHH.
OUTSTANDING.
YOU'RE BEAUTY
AND THE BEAST
IN ONE LUSCIOUS
CHRISTMAS
GIFT PACK.
YOU SAID YOU WERE
GOING TO SCARE HER.
SHE LOOKED
PRETTY SCARED TO ME.
TOUCH OF THE BUBBLY?
SO, WHAT ARE WE
WAITING FOR?
LET'S CONSUMMATE
OUR FIENDISH UNION.
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
OH, COME ON,
CAN'T YOU PICTURE?
IT'S DARK IN
THE MAYOR'S MANSION.
I'M BUSHED,
SO HERE YOU COME
INTO THE BEDROOM,
TWITCHING
YOUR LITTLE TAIL,
MY SLIPPERS
IN ONE HAND,
A DRY MARTINI
IN THE OTHER.
OH, PLEASE.
I WOULDN'T TOUCH YOU
TO SCRATCH YOU.
YOU LOUSY MINX!
YOU OUGHT TO
BE SPAYED.
YOU SENT OUT
THE SIGNALS.
AND I DON'T THINK
I LIKE YOU ANYMORE.
GOODBYE, MY UNINTENDED.
GO TO HEAVEN.
AAH!
THANK YOU.
THERE HE IS!
DON'T ADJUST YOUR SETS.
WELCOME TO
THE OSWALD COBBLEPOT
SCHOOL OF DRIVING.
GENTLEMEN,
START YOUR SCREAMING!
HA HA HA HA!
♪ TA DA DA-DUM...
MAYBE IT'S A BAD TIME
TO MENTION THIS,
BUT MY LICENSE IS EXPIRED.
JUST RELAX.
I'LL TAKE CARE
OF THE SQUEALING,
WRETCHED, PINHEAD
PUPPETS OF GOTHAM.
HA HA!
LOOK OUT!
HA HA HA HA!
YOU GOT TO ADMIT--
I'VE PLAYED
THIS STINKING CITY
LIKE A HARP
FROM HELL!
[BEEP]
HELPLESS OLD LADY
AT 12 O'CLOCK HIGH!
COME ON!
RRRRR!
THAT'S FUNNY.
NOW I'M A LITTLE WORRIED.
SO HE SURVIVED.
WHAT'S THE WORRY?
HE DIDN'T EVEN
LOSE A LIMB,
AN EYEBALL,
BLADDER CONTROL.
LISTEN TO THEM.
THEY'VE LOST FAITH
IN ALL SYMBOLS.
THEY'RE READY
TO BOND WITH YOU.
IF IT WORKS,
DON'T FIX IT.
WE'LL CELEBRATE
TONIGHT.
MY ANNUAL
MAX-QUERADE BALL.
SHRECK
AND COBBLEPOT--
THE VISIONARY
ALLIANCE.
COME ON.
WHEN IT CAME TIME
TO ENSURE THE SAFETY
OF OUR FAIR CITY,
DID THE MAYOR
HAVE A PLAN?
NO!NO!NO!
NO!
HE RELIED ON A MAN,
A BATMAN,
A TICKING TIME BOMB
OF A COSTUMED FREAK.
OUR PRIME CONCERN
IS THIS GHASTLY
GROTESQUE.
BUT LET'S NOT FORGET ABOUT
REPAIRING THE BATMOBILE.
THERE'S SECURITY
TO CONSIDER.
IT'S NOT AS THOUGH
WE CAN TAKE IT
TO ANY OLD JOE'S
BODY SHOP.
SECURITY?
WHO TOOK VICKI VALE
INTO THE BAT CAVE?
I'M SITTING THERE
WORKING,
AND I TURN AROUND--
THERE SHE IS.
HI, VICK.
COME IN.
READY?
I THINK I'LL
TAKE THE STAIRS.
YOU ASK ME,
AM I UP HERE
FOR PERSONAL GLORY?
NO.
I'VE TOILED
FOR MANY YEARS
IN HAPPY OBSCURITY
BENEATH YOUR BOULEVARDS.
THE GLORY THAT I YEARN
TO RECAPTURE
IS THE GLORY
OF GOTHAM!
HOW CAN THIS
BE ACCOMPLISHED?
I KNOW
YOU'RE ALL CONCERNED.
[RECORDING]
HEY, JUST RELAX,
I'LL TAKE CARE
OF THE SQUEALING,
WRETCHED, PINHEAD PUPPETS
OF GOTHAM.
HEH HEH!
I DIDN'T SAY THAT.
YOU GOTTA ADMIT,
I'VE PLAYED
THIS STINKING CITY
LIKE A HARP FROM HELL.
HEH HEH HEH HEH!
YOU GOTTA ADMIT,
I'VE PLAYED
THIS STINKING CITY
LIKE A HARP FROM HELL.
HEH HEH HEH HEH!
I'VE PLAYED
THIS STINKING CITY
LIKE A HARP FROM HELL.
I'VE PLAYED
THIS STINKING CITY
LIKE A HARP FROM HELL.
HEH HEH HEH HEH!
I'VE PLAYED
THIS STINKING CITY...
BOO!BOO!BOO!
BOO!
GET OUT OF HERE!
WHY'S THERE
ALWAYS SOMEONE
WHO BRINGS EGGS
AND TOMATOES
TO A SPEECH?
RRRRR!
THERE HE IS!
MY BABIES!
DID YOU MISS ME?
OH, DID YOU MISS ME?
GREAT SPEECH, OSWALD.
AND MY NAME
IS NOT OSWALD!
IT'S PENGUIN!
I AM NOT
A HUMAN BEING!
I AM AN ANIMAL!
COLD-BLOODED!
CRANK THE A.C.!
WHERE ARE MY LISTS.
BRING ME THE NAMES!
AH, IT'S TIME.
THESE ARE THE NAMES
OF THE FIRST-BORN
SONS OF GOTHAM CITY,
JUST LIKE I WAS.
AND LIKE ME,
A TERRIBLE FATE
WAITS FOR THEM.
TONIGHT,
WHILE THEIR PARENTS PARTY,
THEY'LL BE DREAMING AWAY
IN THEIR SAFE CRIBS,
THEIR SOFT BEDS,
AND WE WILL
SNATCH THEM,
CARRY THEM
INTO THE SEWER,
AND TOSS THEM INTO A DEEP,
DARK, WATERY GRAVE!
UH, PENGUIN.
I MEAN, KILLING
SLEEPING CHILDREN--
ISN'T THAT
A LITTLE, UH...
NO!
IT'S A LOT!
RRRRR.
MR. WAYNE,
A REMINDER.
TONIGHT IS THAT
LOATHSOME PARTY
HOSTED BY
THE ODIOUS
MR. SHRECK.
MAY WE RSVP
IN THE RESOUNDINGLY
NEGATIVE?
NOT INTERESTED.
ALTHOUGH...
SELINA KYLE
MIGHT BE THERE.
INGENIOUS COSTUME.
LET ME GUESS.
TRUST FUND
GOODY-GOODY.
FEELING GOOD, HUH?
YEAH, WELL, YOU ALMOST
MADE A MONSTER
OF THE MAYOR
OF GOTHAM CITY.
I AM THE LIGHT
OF THIS CITY,
AND I AM ITS MEAN,
TWISTED SOUL.
DOES IT MATTER
WHO'S MAYOR?
IT DOES TO ME.
YAWN.
HI.
LISTEN, I'M SORRY
ABOUT YESTERDAY,
BUT I HAD...
A PRETTY BIG DEAL
COME THROUGH--
FALL THROUGH,
ACTUALLY.
IT'S O.K.
I HAD TO GO HOME
AND...FEED MY CAT.
SO, UH...
NO HARD FEELINGS, THEN?
ACTUALLY...
SEMIHARD, I'D SAY.
There's a big, comfy
California king
over in bedding.
WHAT DO YOU SAY WE...
WE TAKE OFF OUR COSTUMES?
I GUESS I'M TIRED
OF WEARING MASKS.
ME, TOO.
LET ME ASK YOU SOMETHING.
WHY'D YOU COME TONIGHT?
YOU FIRST.
TO SEE YOU.
THAT'S LOVELY...
AND I REALLY WISH
I COULD SAY
THE SAME,
BUT I CAME FOR MAX.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
YOU--
NOT YOU AND MAX.
ME AND MAX.
NO.
THIS AND MAX.
NOW, DON'T GIVE ME
A KILLING-MAX-WON'T-
SOLVE-ANYTHING SPEECH,
BECAUSE IT WILL.
AREN'T YOU TIRED
OF THIS SANCTIMONIOUS
ROBBER BARON
ALWAYS COMING OUT ON TOP
WHEN HE SHOULD BE
6 FEET UNDER?
I'M SURE YOU HAVE
PROBLEMS WITH YOUR BOSS,
BUT WHO THE HELL
DO YOU THINK YOU ARE?
I DON'T KNOW ANYMORE, BRUCE.
OHH...
A KISS
UNDER THE MISTLETOE.
YOU KNOW...
MISTLETOE CAN BE DEADLY
IF YOU EAT IT.
A kiss can be
even deadlier...
if you mean it.
OH, MY GOD.
DOES THIS MEAN
WE HAVE TO
START FIGHTING?
LET'S GO
OUTSIDE.
AH, SON, I'M GLAD
YOU'RE ALL RIGHT.
YOU DIDN'T INVITE ME...
SO I CRASHED!
HA HA HA HA HA.
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
RIGHT NOW,
MY TROOPS ARE FANNING OUT
ACROSS TOWN
FOR YOUR CHILDREN.
YES!
FOR YOUR FIRST-BORN SONS,
THE ONES YOU LEFT
DEFENSELESS AT HOME
SO YOU COULD DRESS UP
LIKE JERKS,
GET JUICED,
AND DANCE BADLY.
HA HA HA HA...
I'’VE PERSONALLY COME
FOR GOTHAM'’S FAVORITE SON,
MR. CHIP SHRECK.
YOU'’RE COMING WITH ME,
YOU GREAT WHITE DOPE,
TO DIE
WAY DOWN IN THE SEWER.
NOT CHIP.
IF YOU HAVE AN IOTA
OF HUMAN FEELING,
TAKE ME INSTEAD.
ACH, I DON'’T, SO NO.
I'’M THE ONE
YOU WANT.
ASK YOURSELF--
ISN'’T IT MAX SHRECK
WHO MANIPULATED
AND BETRAYED YOU?
ISN'’T IT MAX,
NOT CHIP,
WHO YOU WANT TO SEE
IMMERSED
TO HIS EYEBALLS
IN RAW SEWAGE?
UHH...
UH...
O.K. YOU GOT A POINT.
I'’LL LET THE LITTLE
PRINCE LIVE FOR NOW.
IN THE DUCK!
COME ON.
AH!
THIS IS GOING TO BE GOOD--
TO CUT DOWN A WHOLE CROP
OF GOTHAM'’S MOST PROMISING
BEFORE THEIR PRIME.
HA HA HA...
YOU ASK ME, HOW DO I
LURE THEM IN?
HA HA HA HA...
A LITTLE
PIED PENGUIN ACTION.
AND YOU
GET TO WATCH THEM SINK
INTO A DEEP PUDDLE
OF YOUR INDUSTRIAL
BYPRODUCTS.
THEN YOU JOIN THEM.
HA HA HA HA HA.
[BABY CRIES]
WOULD YOU HURRY UP
AND GET THOSE KIDS
LOADED ALREADY?
[GASP]
WHUH--
RIGHT THIS WAY, KIDDIES.
COME ON.
COME WITH ME.
[SCREE-SCREE-SCREECH]
SO WHERE ARE
ALL THE CHILDREN?
"DEAR PENGUIN,
"THE CHILDREN REGRET
THEY ARE UNABLE
TO ATTEND.
BATMAN."
AAH!
MY DEAR PENGUINS,
WE STAND
ON A GREAT THRESHOLD.
IT'’S O.K. TO BE SCARED.
MANY OF YOU
WON'’T BE COMING BACK.
THANKS TO BATMAN,
THE TIME HAS COME
TO PUNISH
ALL GOD'’S CHILDREN.
FIRST, SECOND,
THIRD, AND FOURTH-BORN!
WHY BE BIASED?
MALE AND FEMALE!
HELL, THE SEXES ARE EQUAL
WITH THEIR EROGENOUS ZONES
BLOWN SKY-HIGH!
[PENGUINS SQUAWK]
FORWARD...
MARCH!
THE LIBERATION
OF GOTHAM
HAS BEGUN!
[SQUAWKING]
THE PENGUINS ARE MOVING
ABOVE GROUND.
PENGUIN ARMY APPROACHING
LAUNCH DESTINATION
AT GOTHAM PLAZA.
ONE MINUTE UNTIL IGNITION.
THEY WOULDN'’T PUT ME
ON A PEDESTAL,
SO I'’M LAYING THEM
ON A SLAB!
THE PENGUINS
SEEM TO BE
CONVERGING
ON GOTHAM PLAZA.
30 SECONDS UNTIL IGNITION.
ESTIMATED CASUALTIES
AFTER LAUNCH--
100,000 PEOPLE.
THE PENGUINS HAVE REACHED
GOTHAM SQUARE.
15 SECONDS TO IGNITION.
UNH...
READY WHEN
YOU ARE, SIR.
I'’VE GOT THE COORDINATES.
10...
9...
8...
7...
LET'’S TURN THEM AROUND.
YES, SIR.
[HIGH-PITCHED
JAMMING FREQUENCY]
SOMETHING IS WRONG.
SOMETHING HAS JAMMED
THE SIGNAL.
THEY SEEM TO BE
TURNING AROUND.
ARR-ARR-ARR...
ARGH...
[EEE]
HEY.
COME ON.
THERE IS ALSO SOMETHING
COMING THIS WAY...
VERY LARGE, VERY FAST.
ARRRRGH!
[CLICKING TONGUE]
[E-E-E-E-E]
AARRR, OH, GRRR,
ARRGH...
ARR, ARR, ARR, ARR, ARR...
[BATBOAT APPROACHES]
I'’M HOMING IN
ON THE SIGNAL'’S ORIGIN.
ARR, AR, AR.
AAH!
[ENGINE STARTS]
AAH! AAH!
YAAA!
YOU'’RE JUST JEALOUS
BECAUSE
I'’M A GENUINE FREAK,
AND YOU
HAVE TO WEAR A MASK!
YOU MIGHT BE RIGHT.
WHAT IT ALL
COMES DOWN TO IS,
WHO'’S HOLDING
THE UMBRELLA?
[BUZZING]
MY BABIES!
AAH!
[SCREE-EE-EE]
[EEE-EEE]
I DON'’T KNOW
WHAT YOU WANT,
BUT I CAN GET IT
FOR YOU
WITH A MINIMUM
OF FUSS.
MONEY...
JEWELS...
A VERY BIG
BALL OF STRING.
YOUR BLOOD, MAX.
MY BLOOD?
I GAVE AT THE OFFICE.
A HALF PINT.
I'’M TALKING GALLONS.
LET'’S MAKE A DEAL--
OTHER THAN MY BLOOD,
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
SORRY, MAX.
A DIE FOR A DIE.
YOU'’RE NOT JUST
SAVING A LIFE,
YOU'’RE SAVING--
SHUT UP.
YOU'’RE GOING TO JAIL.
DON'’T BE NAIVE.
THE LAW DOESN'’T APPLY
TO PEOPLE LIKE HIM...
OR US.
WRONG ON BOTH COUNTS.
WHY ARE YOU
DOING THIS?
LET'’S JUST TAKE HIM
TO THE POLICE.
THEN WE CAN
GO HOME...
TOGETHER.
[WHIP CRACKS]
SELINA...
DON'’T YOU SEE?
WE'’RE THE SAME.
SPLIT...
RIGHT DOWN
THE CENTER.
SELINA...
PLEASE.
BRUCE...
I WOULD--
I WOULD LOVE
TO LIVE WITH YOU
IN YOUR CASTLE...
FOREVER, JUST LIKE
IN A FAIRY TALE.
NO!
I JUST COULDN'’T
LIVE WITH MYSELF,
SO DON'’T PRETEND
THIS IS A HAPPY ENDING.
SELINA.
SELINA KYLE.
YOU'’RE FIRED.
AND BRUCE WAYNE.
WHY ARE YOU
DRESSED UP
LIKE BATMAN?
BECAUSE HE IS BATMAN,
YOU MORON.
WAS.
DON'’T.
YOU KILLED ME.
THE PENGUIN
KILLED ME.
BATMAN KILLED ME.
THAT'’S THREE LIVES
DOWN.
YOU GOT ENOUGH
TO FINISH ME OFF?
ONE WAY TO FIND OUT.
FOUR...FIVE...
I'’M STILL ALIVE!
SIX...SEVEN...
ALL GOOD GIRLS
GO TO HEAVEN.
[CLICK]
TWO LIVES LEFT.
I THINK I'’LL SAVE ONE
FOR NEXT CHRISTMAS...
BUT IN THE MEANTIME,
HOW ABOUT A KISS,
SANTY CLAUS?
OH...SHIT.
I PICKED A CUTE ONE.
OHH.
UHH...
THE HEAT'’S
GETTING TO ME.
I'’LL MURDER YOU
MOMENTARILY.
[GAGGING]
BUT FIRST...
I NEED A COOL DRINK
OF ICE WATER.
AGH...
[AWK AWK]
[AWK]
ALFRED, STOP THE CAR.
[MEOW]
WELL, COME WHAT MAY,
MERRY CHRISTMAS,
MR. WAYNE.
MERRY CHRISTMAS, ALFRED.
GOOD WILL TOWARD MEN.
AND WOMEN.
♪ FACE TO FACE
♪ MY LOVELY FOE
♪ MOUTH TO MOUTH
♪ RAINING HEAVEN'’S BLOWS ♪
♪ HAND ON HEART
♪ TIC-TAC-TOE
♪ UNDER THE STARS
♪ NAKED AS WE FLOW
♪ CHEEK TO CHEEK
♪ THE BITTERSWEET
♪ COMMIT YOUR CRIME
♪ IN YOUR DEADLY TIME
♪ IT'’S TOO DIVINE ♪
♪ I WANT TO BED
♪ I WANT
THIS BLISS, AH ♪
♪ BUT SOMETHING SAYS
I MUST RESIST ♪
♪ PR-R-R-R-R
♪ ONE MORE KISS
♪ BEFORE WE DIE
♪ FACE TO FACE
♪ AND DREAM OF FLYING
♪ WHO ARE YOU?
♪ WHO AM I?
♪ WIND IN WINGS
♪ TWO ANGELS FALLING
♪ TO DIE LIKE THIS
♪ WITH THE LAST KISS
♪ IT'’S FALSEHOOD'S FLAME ♪
♪ IT'’S A CRYING SHAME ♪
♪ FACE TO FACE
♪ THE PASSIONS BREATHE
♪ I HATE TO STAY
♪ AH, BUT THEN
I HATE TO LEAVE ♪
♪ AND YOU'’LL NEVER KNOW ♪
♪ YOU'’LL NEVER KNOW ♪
♪ YOU'’LL NEVER KNOW... ♪