Can I persuade you to take a sandwich
with you, sir?
I'll get drive-through.
You're counting on the winged avenger
to deliver you from evil...
aren't you, my friend?
Are you going to kill me?
Maybe, maybe not. You can say
we're of two minds on the subject.
Are you a gambling man?
What say we flip for it?
One man is born a hero,
his brother, a coward.
Babies starve, politicians grow fat...
holy men are martyred,
and junkies grow legion.
Why?
Luck!
Blind, stupid, simple, doo-dah...
clueless luck!
The wrath of toss.
The only true justice.
Let's see what justice has in store...
for you.
It's like the touch of God. Wait.
Fortune smiles,
another day of wine and roses.
Or, in your case, beer and pizza.
Out of here!
- But you said you'd let me live!
- Too true, and so you shall.
Nothing better than live bait to trap a bat.
What if we could get some kind of a horn?
Hot entrance.
Two-Face?
Two guards are dead.
He's holding a third hostage.
- Didn't see this one coming.
- We should have, though.
The Second Bank of Gotham on the...
Second anniversary
of the day I captured him.
How could Two-Face resist?
I'm Chase Meridian.
I asked Dr. Meridian to come to Gotham
to consult on this case.
She specializes in...
Abnormal Psychology,
multiple personalities.
I read your work.
Insightful. Naive, but insightful.
I'm flattered.
Not every girl
makes a superhero's night table.
Can we reason with him?
- He's holding innocent people up there.
- It won't do any good.
He'll slaughter them
without thinking twice.
Agreed.
A trauma powerful enough to create
an alternate personality leaves the victim...
In a world where normal rules
of right and wrong no longer apply.
- Exactly.
- Like you.
Let's just say,
I could write a hell of a paper...
on a grown man
who dresses like a flying rodent.
Bats aren't rodents, Dr. Meridian.
Really? I didn't know that.
You are interesting.
And call me Chase.
By the way, do you have a first name,
or do I just call you "Bats"?
Let's start this party with a bang!
Very punctual, even for his own funeral.
Boys, kill the bat!
Blast him!
Open sesame.
It's a trap!
Oh, no!
Attention, citizens of fair Gotham.
When we open that safe,
we'll have everything we ever wanted.
Enough cash
to rain down upon fair Gotham...
a glorious flood of chaos.
And, of course, you, my boy, dead.
Oh, no, it's boiling acid!
For your dying pleasure
we're serving the very same acid...
that made us the men we are today.
- No.
- Hold on.
Yes.
Haul away.
Yes, haul away.
- Give me your hand.
- Don't let go!
Gonna have to borrow this.
Hey, that's my hearing aid!
Thanks.
My shoes are melting!
No more!
- Hang on.
- Hang on?
Get him down.
Take it easy with him, fellows.
You'll be all right, young man.
Just stay calm.
Easy, just easy.
This'll fix him.
Hang on, Batty!
Let's see.
Yes.
Yes! Oh, happy day.
Farewell forever to that
pointy-eared night rat.
Face!
Hey, Face!
- Die!
- No!
You need help, Harvey. Give it up.
Have the good taste to die.
See you.
Despite a valiant effort last night
by Batman...
Harvey Two-Face is still at large
and extremely dangerous.
And in other news today,
billionaire Bruce Wayne...
has extended his trend setting
profit-sharing program...
to the employees of
the highly successful electronics division...
of Wayne Enterprises.
- Mr. Wayne.
- Hello, Fred.
Your inspections
are a departmental highlight.
Oh, my God, it's him.
I am a winner.
Bioremediation. Alternative fuel.
Mr. Wayne, look at that time.
Perhaps we should get to R & D
as soon as possible.
Mister...
Bruce Wayne.
No, that's my name. And you are?
Nygma.
Edward.
Edward Nygma. You hired me personally.
Just like I tell everyone.
We've never actually met,
but your name was on the hiring slip.
- I have it.
- I'm gonna need that hand back, Ed.
Yes, of course.
I'm sorry.
It's just that...
you're my idol.
Back to work, Edward.
And some people
have been trying to keep us apart.
- Back to work, Edward.
- It's okay.
So, Mr. Nygma, what's on your mind?
Precisely. What's on all our minds?
Brain waves.
The future of Wayne Enterprises...
is brain waves.
I'm gonna have to apologize, Mr. Wayne.
I personally terminated his project
this morning.
It's okay.
I have it.
Voilà.
My invention...
beams any TV signal
directly into the human brain.
By stimulating neurons,
manipulating brain waves, if you will...
this device makes the audience
feel like they're inside the show.
Why be brutalized by an uncaring world?
Did you say "manipulating brain waves"?
Yes.
But...
someone like you would never need it.
Someone so...
intelligent, witty...
and charming.
I just need a bit of additional funding
for human trials.
- Let me show you, please.
- Now, listen, Ed...
I want a full set of technical schematics
on this, okay?
I want you to know
we'll be full partners in this, Bruce.
Look at us. Two of a kind!
You call my assistant, Margaret.
She'll set something up.
That's not gonna be good for me.
I need an answer now.
I think I deserve it.
I'm sorry, Ed, then the answer is no.
Tampering with people's brain waves...
mind manipulation...
it just raises too many questions.
Sorry.
Thanks everybody, keep up the good work.
Factory looks great.
All right, everyone, back to work.
We'll discuss this later.
You were supposed to understand.
I'll make you understand.
Lock.
Chair.
- Alfred.
- I saw the signal, sir.
All is ready.
- Commissioner Gordon?
- He's at home.
I sent the signal.
What's wrong?
Last night, at the bank,
I noticed something about Two-Face:
His coin.
It's his Achilles' heel.
- It can be exploited.
- I know.
You called me here for this?
The Batsignal is not a beeper.
I wish I could say
that my interest in you was...
purely professional.
Are you trying to get under my cape,
Doctor?
A girl can't live by psychoses alone.
It's the car, right? Chicks love the car.
What is it about the wrong kind of man?
In grade school, it was guys with earrings.
College: Motorcycles, leather jackets.
Now...
black rubber.
Try a fireman. Less to take off.
I don't mind the work.
Pity I can't see behind the mask.
- We all wear masks.
- My life's an open book. You read?
I don't blend in at a family picnic.
We could give it a try. I'll bring the wine...
you bring your scarred psyche.
- Direct, aren't you?
- You like strong women.
I've done my homework.
Or do I need skintight vinyl and a whip?
I haven't had that much luck with women.
Maybe you just haven't met
the right woman.
I saw the signal.
- What's going on?
- Nothing.
False alarm.
Are you sure?
Women.
Okay...
now I've got it!
Too many questions.
There's too many questions.
There's just too many...
I'll show you it works.
What the hell is going on here?
I told you this project is terminated.
I'm calling security.
Caffeine will kill you!
Rise and shine, little guinea pig.
What are you doing, Nygma? Untie me.
This won't hurt a bit.
At least, I don't think it will.
What're you doing? Nygma!
- You touch that switch and...
- Which one? This?
Losing resolution.
More power.
Edward Nygma, come on down...
you're the next contestant on Brain Drain.
I'll take what's inside thick skull
number one!
What have we got for him, Johnny?
Stickley, I'm having a breakthrough...
and a breakdown, maybe!
Nevertheless, I'm smarter. I'm a genius.
No, several geniuses.
A gaggle, a swarm...
a flock of freaking Freuds.
Riddle me this, Fred.
What is everything to someone
and nothing to everyone else?
Your mind, baby!
Now mine pumps with the power of yours.
I'm sucking up your IQ...
vacuuming your cortex...
feeding off your brain.
Fred!
What a rush!
What the hell just happened?
A very surprising side effect.
While you were mesmerized
by my 3-D TV...
I utilized your neural energy
to grow smarter.
Bruce Wayne was right.
You demented, bizarre, unethical toad.
It is brain manipulation.
I'm reporting you to the FCC...
the Human Experimentation Board,
the AMI, and the police.
You are going up on charges...
to court, to jail...
and then to a mental institution,
for the rest of your twisted little life.
But, first and foremost, Nygma,
you are fired.
Do you hear me? Fired!
I don't think so.
Hang on!
Fred.
Babe!
You are fired.
Or should I say terminated?
Surf's up, big kahuna!
Nice form, but a little rough
on the landing.
He may have to settle for the bronze.
Questions, Mr. Wayne?
My work raises too many questions?
Why hasn't anybody...
put you in your place?
Harvey Dent,
once Gotham 's District Attorney...
was horribly scarred
by underworld kingpin, Boss Moroni.
Although Batman tried to save him...
Dent's left-brain damage
transformed him into a violent criminal...
who blames Batman, and who has vowed
to destroy the Dark Knight.
Harvey Two-Face is extremely dangerous,
repeat, extremely...
That was the Commissioner Gordon, sir.
There's been an accident
at Wayne Enterprises.
- Horrible way to die.
- Yes.
The video surveillance cameras
are down here.
We'll dredge the river,
but with that current...
I doubt we'll ever find the body.
Why? Oh, why?
I just can't believe it.
Two years working in the same office.
He was like my father, my brother...
or a cousin that visits all the time.
Get a grip, Edward.
I found this in my cubicle.
You'll find the handwriting matches
his exactly...
as does sentence structure and spelling.
I couldn't possibly continue on here.
The memories...
This is last night's security log.
There's Stickley.
Pretty cut-and-dry.
Yep, definitely suicide.
Thanks very much for your help, Bruce.
We'll be in touch.
Stickley's suicide. It doesn't make sense.
I want full benefits for his family.
Suicide's not covered
by our corporate insurance policy.
I know. Full benefits.
Gossip Gerty has called a record 32 times.
- Who are you taking to the Charity Circus?
- I'll let you know. What's this?
I don't know. I didn't see anyone.
That's hideous.
What does it mean?
It's a riddle.
"Numbers on my face... 13."
One through 12. The answer is "a clock."
Who would send you a riddle?
That, Maggie, is the riddle.
Guess what I did today?
Wayne Manor.
See you soon.
Dr. Meridian, please. Thank you.
I...
guess I'm early.
I have an appointment.
- I'm Bruce Wayne.
- Good.
Then you can afford to buy me a new door.
I'm sorry.
You sounded like you were in...
you know, trouble.
I prefer healthy expressions of violence...
as opposed to breaking and entering.
So, how can I help you, Mr. Wayne?
Someone's been sending me love letters.
One at my office,
and one last night at my home.
I...
Commissioner Gordon thought you might
give me your expert opinion.
Clock.
A match.
My opinion, this letter writer
is a total wacko.
Wacko?
That a technical term?
Patient may suffer
from obsessional syndrome...
with potential homicidal tendencies.
Does that work better for you?
So, what you're saying is
this guy's a total wacko.
Exactly.
He's obsessed with you.
His only escape
may be to purge the fixation.
To kill me.
I think you understand obsession
better than you let on.
You have a thing for bats?
That's a Rorschach, Mr. Wayne. An inkblot.
People see what they want.
I think the question would be,
do you have a thing for bats?
Still playing with dolls, Doctor?
She's a Malaysian dream warden.
Some cultures believe
she protects you from bad dreams.
It's silly to you, I'm sure.
You look so sad.
Do you need one?
Me? No. Why would I?
You're not exactly what you seem,
are you, Bruce Wayne?
What is it you really came here for?
Yikes, time's up.
That's usually my line.
Listen, I'd love to stay here chatting...
Would you?
I'm not so sure.
I've really got to get you
out of those clothes.
- Excuse me?
- And into a black dress.
Tell me, Doctor, do you like the circus?
Ladies and gentlemen...
boys and girls of all ages...
welcome to the greatest show on earth.
Bruce, who is this
beautiful young woman you're with?
- Dr. Chase Meridian.
- A doctor?
What kind of doctor?
... for Gotham Children's Hospital.
Let's thank our largest single donor:
Bruce Wayne!
Ladies and gentlemen...
70 feets above the ground...
performing feats
of unimaginable aerial skill...
the Flying Graysons.
Listen...
I'm going rock climbing this weekend.
Would you like to join me?
I'd like to...
I love climbing. I really love it.
But?
I've met someone.
That's fast work. You just moved here.
You could say he just kind of...
dropped out of the sky...
and bang!
I think he felt it, too.
- He sure did.
- What?
Who wouldn't?
And now...
Richard, the youngest flying Grayson...
will perform the awe-inspiring...
death drop...
without the safety of a net.
- Okay, let's go.
- You'll be all right.
Ladies and gentlemen...
at this time, the new management
of the Circus International...
invites you to forget this good, clean,
wholesome all-American fun...
and join us in a celebration
of absolute chaos...
and true jesters!
Bring it on, now!
Tonight, a new act
for your personal amazement...
we call it Massacre Under the Big Top.
If we may direct your attention
to the middle of the center ring.
Inside this harmless-looking orb are two...
that's two-hundred sticks of TNT.
And in our innocent hand,
a radio detonator.
- What the hell do you want, Harvey?
- Want, Mr. Mayor?
One simple thing: Batman...
bruised, broke, bleeding. In a word: Dead!
- Batman.
- Who do we have before us?
Gotham 's finest, well-to-do, influential...
surely one of you knows who Batman is.
Hell, odds are one of you pasty-faced twits
is Batman.
You have two minutes.
Harvey...
I'm Batman!
Bruce!
We could stop them.
Mitch, if we go out on the rigging.
- Be careful, boys.
- Don't worry, Mom.
Go to work, boys.
Our kind of day.
Reach for it! Stop it.
Oh, my God!
Bruce.
It's good of you to take him in.
He hasn't anyone now.
We've had him filling out papers all day.
He hasn't slept, he hasn't even eaten.
Welcome, Master Grayson. I'm Alfred.
How you doing, Al?
There's a room prepared for you upstairs...
but perhaps you'd like to get
something to eat first.
Okay, I'm out of here.
Excuse me?
Look, I figured,
telling that cop I'd stay here for a while...
saved me a truckload
of social service interviews and charities...
so, no offense, but no thanks. See you.
Take it easy, Al.
Where will you go?
The circus must be halfway to Metropolis,
by now.
I'll get a fix on Two-Face.
Then I'm gonna kill him.
Killing Two-Face won't take the pain away.
It'll make it worse.
Look, spare me the sermons,
all right, Bruce?
I don't need your advice
and I don't need your charity.
- Nice bike.
- Hang out at a lot of biker bars, Bruce?
I see you're almost on empty.
Why don't you...
fill it up in the garage. There's not
a gas station around here for miles.
Pump's over here.
Is this a garage or a car museum, Bruce?
Wow.
- It's a 1917 Harley.
- Yep.
Indian classic, fully restored.
This is a Vincent Black Knight.
They only made like 100 of these.
A hundred and one, actually.
She's my favorite.
- You've got two of them.
- Yeah, that one doesn't run, though.
Throttle sticks on this one.
Alfred's actually
a very good mechanic, but...
some of these need a lot of work.
Someone were to fix them up,
they could keep one as a fee.
Anyway, have a nice trip.
Sure you'll land on your feet.
Is the young master leaving?
Pity.
I'll just toss this away then,
perhaps the dogs are hungry.
Hey, Al, wait up.
Master Bruce?
Just like my parents.
It's happening again.
A monster comes out of the night,
a scream, two shots.
I killed them.
What did you say?
He killed them. Two-Face.
He slaughtered that boy's parents.
No. You said, "I killed them."
Take care of the kid.
Certainly, sir.
Can I help you settle in, Master Grayson?
No.
Thanks, I won't be staying long.
Is this a robin?
My brother's wire broke once
and I swung out and grabbed him.
My father said I was his hero.
I flew in like a robin.
Some hero I turned out to be.
But your father was right.
You are a hero. I can tell.
Throw this away, will you, Alfred?
I won't be needing it anymore.
I think I'll just put it in here.
Broken wings mend in time.
One day Robin will fly again.
I promise.
We'll drive, thank you.
The Puzzler?
The Gamester?
Captain Kill?
Question Mark Man?
Thank you. Thank you so much.
The Bat's stubborn refusal to expire...
is driving us insane!
Don't worry, baby.
You'll kill him soon.
Besides, I made your favorite tonight.
Sparkling champagne and...
yummy poached salmon
with little itty-bitty quail eggs...
and a creamy, dreamy...
lemon soufflé.
No, I made your favorite.
A charred heart of black boar...
a side of raw donkey meat...
and a Sterno and grain alcohol,
straight up, baby!
Perfect!
Ladies, you spoil us.
We're of two minds about
what to eat first.
- What?
- I hope you made extra.
Who the hell are you?
Just a friend.
But you can call me...
The Riddler.
I'll call you dead, is more like it!
How did you find us here? Talk!
But then if I talked...
what would keep you from slaying me,
O Segregated One?
By the way...
that's never going to heal
if you don't stop picking.
- Let's see if you bleed green.
- Harvey...
I don't think it's me you want to kill.
That's just too easy
for someone as powerful as you...
and you.
But Batman...
there's a challenge.
Kill the Bat! Sounds like a good idea.
But have you thought it through?
A few bullets, a quick splash of blood,
and then what?
Wet hands.
Post-homicidal depression.
- Why not humiliate him first?
- Yeah.
Expose his frailties.
And then, when he is at his weakest...
crush him!
I see that sparkle in your left eye.
I can help you get Batman.
That is, if you'll...
spare my life for just a few moments.
Thank you.
I simply love what you've done
with this place.
Heavy Metal meets House and Garden.
Beautiful.
It's so dark and Gothic and...
disgustingly decadent.
Yet so bright and chipper...
and conservative.
It's so you!
And yet, so you!
Very few people are
both a summer and a winter...
but you pull it off nicely.
What's the point, big boy?
Has anybody ever told you, you have
a serious impulse-control problem?
This is the point.
This is how I found you.
Let me demonstrate.
This is your brain on The Box.
This is my brain on The Box.
Does anybody else feel like a fried egg?
I'll have a bit more. Thank you.
There's more. But only the first one's free.
Here's the bargain.
You will help me steal production capital...
so I can put a Box on every TV in town...
and become Gotham's cleverest
carbon-based life form!
And in return...
Is everybody paying attention?
I will help you
solve the greatest riddle of all.
The mother of all riddles:
Who is Batman?
You have broken into our hideout.
You have violated the sanctity of our lair.
For this we should crush your bones
into powder.
However, you've posed
a most interesting proposition.
Therefore, heads, we accept, and tails,
we blow your damn head off.
Here's a good one.
No!
There is a good one.
Leave that, Master Dick. I'll attend to it.
I'm not used to being waited on, Al.
Don't shoot me, please.
Don't you eyeball me! Give me that!
Hey, Two-Face,
show me how to punch a guy.
It's dirt-simple, my boy.
Ball up the fist, reach way back...
and assert yourself.
That looks like fun. Let me try.
Ball up the fist, reach way back,
assert yourself.
$100,220...
$100 and...
I lost count!
In Gotham, last night...
another robbery perpetrated by
the city's green-suited menace...
resulting in millions in diamonds stolen,
with no sign of Batman.
Teamed with Two-Face...
this new criminal's pattern
of marking his crimes with puzzles...
has Gothamites calling him The Riddler.
Apparently, you and Batman
have a common enemy.
That was with the morning mail.
"The eight of us go forth, not back...
"to protect our king from a foe's attack."
Chess pawns. Clock. Match.
All physical objects, man-made.
Small in size, light in weight.
What's the connection?
With all due respect, sir, I think
that's why they call him The Riddler.
May I help you, Master Grayson?
How come this the only locked door
around this museum?
What've you got back there?
Master Wayne's dead wives.
The silver closet. On your way.
Now you can be part of the action!
NygmaTech brings the joy...
of 3-D entertainment
into your living room.
Ladies and gentlemen, let me tell you...
my vision.
The Box in every home in America...
and one day, the world.
In local news, Edward Nygma 's 3-D Box...
has become the rage of Gotham.
Rioting occurred last night
at electronics stores, which were sold out.
There is hardly a home
without the Nygma Tech Box.
Critics have claimed
The Box turns Gothamites into zombies.
But Edward Nygma just shrugs:
"That's what they said
when TV was invented. "
Master Dick!
Up here, Al.
Just checking, young sir.
Intruder alert.