Why are you back so early?
Aren't you supposed
to be recording a show?
Change of plans.
Me, too.
Drink this.
Didn't you eat?
I did, but I'm still starving.
Why are you eating
noodles instead of rice?
Just wanted something simple.
It's good, huh?
If you could stop time,
what would you do first?
If everyone else is frozen
and only you can move?
If time stopped, you wouldn't die.
Don't you want to live?
Not talking to me?
Too sorry to die and leave
the girl you love alone.
Okay, I can understand that much.
But still...
How can you marry her
off to someone else?
Isn't that going overboard?
You're not dead, yet.
- How can you watch that?
- Ah, Jenna?
Let's just stick to ourjobs.
What's love?
Like brushing your teeth.
Brushing your teeth?
But you do that alone.
Do you brush to show someone?
Why didn't you come yesterday?
Pardon?
I said, did you wait for me?
Well, just wondering
why you didn't come.
You fell in love with me, didn't you?
What?
Love makes you wonder
and wait for that person.
It's not that. If a patient
doesn't come, I wait.
Do you wonder about every patient?
Well...
You're blushing. It's love all right.
Hey, KANG Chul-kyu!
Yes, boss.
How much did you get from KIM Gap-sik?
Should've been more discreet!
Cat Girl's on your show 10 times a week!
Think people will stay still?
Someone wrote in to audit your show!
What's got into you all of a sudden?
You of all people!
When are you going to break it off?
In a rush?
You saw my medical records.
I want to keep playing.
But I guess you don't have that luxury.
Under one condition.
Now, what.
I'll tell you after I break it off.
A promise is a promise.
Since when was it no smoking in here.
No idea.
Our parents will be shocked.
I should be really angry
at a time like this, right?
Yell at you or something?
Funny, somehow I feel a little grateful.
I'm going out for a smoke.
So uncomfortable.
My engagement's off.
I don't have parents.
I was studying late at high
school in my senior year.
My homeroom teacher came
in and stared right at me.
Like someone who came
to take me on death row.
Like in the movies, you know?
Anyway, he told me
to go to the hospital right away.
When I asked why...
if he said my parents and
sister died in a car accident...
then I wouldn't have gone
and seen them like that.
I see...
K's been with me ever since.
K?
You saw him, Producer KANG Chul-kyu?
His name sounds too corny
so I just call him K.
At home, he's my Mom
At work, he's my Dad.
When I'm sad, he's my brother.
Sometimes he's like a lover.
Though he always chickens out.
Can I kiss you?
You wanna kiss me?
Stupid.
Let me see.
Oh, no.
That's right, I'm stupid!
Open the door. Are you okay?
Don't look! Stupid!
Stupid! Stupid! Stupid!
I was born to love you.
Heaven sent me to love you.
Cat Girl's 'lf
I could live again'
requested by
ID: Little Mermaid.
- You wrote this song, Cream?
- Yes.
Let's hear, 'lf I could live again'.
(Did you eat?)
(I'm almost done!)
Yes, boss.
Come to my office, now.
Okay.
Producer KANG!
KANG!
I heard everything. I'm going to
speak with the boss, right now!
How can he fire a genius like you!
I'm not getting fired.
Same difference.
- You can't go like this!
- I'm taking a break.
Really? That's not what I heard.
I'm going to the States
to study for a while.
Really? Guess there's
no use going to the boss.
Thank you for everything, Mr. KIM.
- Anytime. - You
too, Min-chul.
Give him the demo tape, Min-chul.
Producer CHOI! Hold on! Wait!
Min-chul...
It's a ballad.
Write up a good song.
What's marriage?
Marriage?
Marriage.
- Marriage...
- Wait!
A toothbrush holder.
What?
There's only one holder,
but many toothbrushes.
What's that got to do with marriage?
Being together as one like
toothbrushes in a holder.
Then I must be married, already.
Stupid! You can't be
married without a wedding.
Really?
I gotta pee.
No one else but Thee.
'Thee' is a lucky person.
Wanna hear it?
EUN Won and I living
together probably got to you.
But there's nothing to worry about.
I'm okay with that.
I'm thankful for
everything you did for her.
Let's get together often.
Go on trips together and stuff.
Sounds good.
She says she wants to pick
out her wedding dress with you.
Gotta love her wild ideas.
Why me?
I want what she wants.
Please do it for her.
And I hope it's the last
thing you ever do for her.
Sure. Please take good care of her.
Of course. She's my woman, now.
Let's drink.
What do you think?
Very pretty.
It's time for the groom-to-be
to try on his suit.
I'm not the groom.
Try it on.
Come up here.
Come here. Can you take a picture of us?
On three. One, two, three!
Wait out there. I'll
try on something else.
Why are all the clocks stopped?
No reason.
Can I turn one on?
Why?
No reason.
No reason?
Sure.
Jenna? I have a big favor to ask.
What is it?
I need to send flowers on her
anniversary for a few years.
She'll get suspicious, if
I lose touch altogether.
I had one more condition. Remember?
What is it?
Please die at my side.
You booked the tickets?
I'm running low on battery.
Hey.
What are you making?
My phone battery ran out.
I'll charge it and call you back later.
Bye.
Hi.
Why'd you leave me there like that?
It's for you.
Who do you think you are!
What's with you?
Who says you can touch my phone!
The hell you...
Who says you can do
whatever you want with me!
Can I help you?
Is K home?
K?
Someone's here.
She's pretty. I can
see why you love her.
You think she's happy?
What are you saying?
She didn't seem happy.
Can you send this for the next 3 years?
It's pretty.
Maybe too pretty.
It looks fake. Like your love.
Then what's real?
Real?
If you're hungry, you eat.
If you're hurting, you cry.
If you're having fun, you
laugh. Not hold it in like you.
You really wanna die like this?
No!
I don't want to die like this.
I want to live a happy life.
I want to be the one marrying EUN Won...
...instead of him, tomorrow.
But...
That's just a dream.
A sad dream.
I'm done with dreaming.
Sleep tight and sweet dreams.
Did you eat?
- Cream
Thanks.
I'm not talking to you.
I'm sorry.
For what?
For everything.
I'm sorry, too.
For what?
For everything.
I love you...
I like you.
Me, too.
That's some story.
KANG... amazing guy. I had no idea.
Is there anyway to reach
them? What about the dentist?
Wonder what happened to her.
Let's record it.
Really? I'll call right now.
No, the other song.
Oh, that song.
I gotta go, I'm late.
Get up and eat. I made breakfast.
What's this?
Ah, Vitamin ABC. It
helps me get smarter.
Where'd you get these pills?
They're my friends' pills.
Since when did your
friend start taking this?
Why?
The pain must've been
severe to take these pills.
What?
They're painkillers for
patients with cancer or leukemia.
Terminal patients.
Have you heard of
the hospice ward?
It's where dying patients stay...
with consent from their families.
Mom!
Watch the house while we're out.
See you later, sis!
No!
When I found out what
Vitamin ABC really was...
When I finally realized
what they were...
When my whole world
turned pitch dark before me...
What's wrong?
I died before K.
I met K a year after my
whole family passed away.
Though almost 3 hours passed...
he stood there frozen like stone.
Crying and looking in the
direction his mother went.
This will be enough to support you
till you're an adult, Chul-kyu.
He looked sadder
and more hurt than me.
He needed a hug
more than me.
Is there anything you want to tell me?
Like what?
A deep, dark secret?
Say anything. I'm ready to listen.
I like you.
Stupid idiot.
Do you have a wish?
What's with you?
Just curious all of a sudden.
If you could do anything
you want in the world.
K is dying.
Meet a great guy and get married.
Can't I marry you?
I'm not a great guy.
Then who is?
Someone who is healthy and nice.
Who knows how to take
care of his family.
I already met a great guy.
But K told me to
meet someone else.
He said that was his wish.
KANG Chul-kyu
When I heard K fainted...
I rushed over,
afraid I'll go crazy.
But I...
... couldn't even go crazy.
No, doc.
But she should know.
What are you going to do?
I don't know.
It feels like a needle
stuck in my throat.
Right here.
It gets stuck right here.
I can't say it.
She'll live on. Think of yourself.
She's different.
She needs someone beside her.
- Hello.
- There goes Mr. Perfect.
Glowing from head to toe!
I picked a man.
Which side did you drink from?
Pardon?
I'm engaged.
Stupid. You think I care
whether you're engaged or not?
Just play along and
meet me. For K.
Am I a bitch?
I don't have time
to worry about that!
The man I love is dying!
If I could be born again...
A ring? A pair of glasses?
A bed? A diary?
Born again as things like
that? What fun is that?
You can buy me. It'll
always be fun at your side.
What's wrong? Are you okay?
Let me see your hand.
Where are you going?
I made a deal with myself.
If he turns around,
I'd tell him everything.
If he turns around, I'd
hug him and stop everything.
But K didn't look back.
And there was nothing
I could do.
Why are you eating
noodles instead of rice?
Just wanted something simple.
- It's good, huh?
- Yeah.
As I sat eating the
noodles with him...
I'd think, 'Don't
die you bastard'
and drank some water instead.
'Tell me. Let me hold you!
I'll die with you! '
'I'll follow you and pay you back
for everything you did for me! '
Instead, I just drank the water.
And finished the noodles.
There's only one holder,
but many toothbrushes.
What's that got to do with marriage?
Being together as one like
toothbrushes in a holder.
Then I must be married, already.
Stupid! You can't be
married without a wedding.
Really?
Can we get married, soon?
Wait out there. I'll
try on something else.
The hell you...
Who says you can do
whatever you want with me!
I'm sorry.
I want to tell him I love him.
I want to open my mouth
and say I love him.
But I knew tears will fall
before I could say it.
So I kept silent, again.
When are you going to talk to me?
Didn't you hear me screaming
at you all this time?
What?
Stupid.
I didn't hear anything.
Then how can mutes love?
I love you.
Me, too.
We became a real couple.
Cuz we made it down the aisle.
Heaven's Gate Resting Place
Wait!
You never learn!
How can you write
with a brain like that?
This isn't kissing, is it?
Can you take a picture of us?
On three. One, two, three!
I was born to love you.
Heaven send me to love you.
- EUN
Won -
I'm making noodles.
Want some?
No, I gotta work.
You sure?
Yes, I'm working!
- Then I'm just making
one! - Okay.
Don't come beggin'later.
- Hey!
- What?
No eggs! Give me that.
Wonder who invented noodles.
You said you didn't want any.
Changed my mind.
Is there any rice?
Hold on. There's
some in the fridge.
Chul-kyu...
I'm coming to you.
Don't worry.
I trust you. You
were always my compass.
Remember when I said
I can see you
even when you're not with me?
Go wherever you want.
I'll find you, soon.
Don't get mad when you see me.
Don't ask me why I followed
you or get angry at me.
After everything to come to
you, if you get mad I'll cry.
When we meet again on the other
side, let's not cry again.
Wait for me.
I'll be right there.