Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
'Parashuram is the sixth avatar
of the Lord of the Universe.'
'In Treta Yuga Parashuram went
around the Earth twenty one times'
'and ended irreligiousness
and won over this land'
'which he donated to Kashyap Prajapati.'
'Gods, serpents prayed to Him
to give them shelter in this land.'
'Then he threw the divine axe
given by Lord Shiva into the ocean.'
'The ocean went back and
a wonderful new land was created.'
'The minerals of the ocean
made the land fertile.'
'Medicinal plants which are rare
grew in that forest.'
'One of the seven immortals Parashuram
made the land his meditation ground.'
'The land is Parshuramkshetra.'
'A miracle was noticed in that land.'
'The immensely powerful temple of
Lord Shiva that appeared on that land.'
Got scared?
Grandpa, do spirits exist?
- Do you believe in God?
- Yes.
Then you must believe in spirits.
How did spirits come in the temple
where God exists?
This is miracle.
You won't understand these miracles
if you think rationally.
You'll understand them if you feel them.
Why did you shut this powerful temple?
There's an unheard and unsung story
of this temple.
'From the banks of the ocean
few miles into the forest'
'appeared the powerful Shivalinga
which would protect us.'
'The place where holy Mother Ganges
continuously anoints Lord Shiva.'
There was a time when
the walls reverberated
with the sound of drums,
music, holy chants.
When any person leaves for heavenly abode
of Lord Shiva before time
the spirit resides on this Earth for ten
days until the final rites are performed.
The wish of the spirit can be fulfilled
within ten days
but it should be a righteous wish.
The fulfillment of the wish
depends on their actions.
If any family member of the deceased
worships the Lord from heart
the spirit of the dead person
enters the person
and the spirit fulfills his last wish.
Five decades back a son worshipped
Neelkanth Lord Shiva
'to fulfill the last wish
of his deceased father.'
'He was possessed by his father's spirit.'
'He killed his maternal uncle
who poisoned him.'
'People who witnessed
this incident were terrified.'
'The officers who investigated the case
were surprised and in dilemma.'
'It was not the son but the
father's spirit that killed the victim.'
'The main priest gave
this explanation and said'
'they couldn't ignore the belief
that was prevalent for ages.'
'So, the temple would remain closed
till the truth is revealed.'
'It was a legal decision.'
Since that day till now
the abhiseka of Lord Shiva
didn't stop despite the idol
not being worshipped.
The faith of the devotees didn't waver.
"Hail Lord Shiva!"
We've been here for a long time.
Why did he force us to come here?
He could've called us to the
police station for interrogation.
Why did he call us here?
What does he think?
Who does he think he is?
I could've called you at the
police station for interrogation.
But there's no guarantee that
you can go back home safely after that.
Sir, what's our mistake?
We are honest businessmen
who deal in petrol.
Two trucks are loaded
from the factory every time.
Those trucks are unloaded in your pumps.
How can a third truck pass the
check-post with the same permit?
The third truck doesn't belong to us.
But if I tell you whose truck it is
then I'll find my daughter dead, sir.
If you give me your complaint in writing,
I'll ensure you go back home safely.
Come out.
Bhavani!
Boss, please forgive us.
I would've spared him
if he interfered in my business.
But that tanker is my life.
Whoever messes with it won't be alive.
You must face the son
before you touch the father.
Rudra is always there
to protect Bhavani.
Don't you know that?
- Madam, please give me a cup of tea.
- Yes, please have a seat.
Let's go to a parlour for an hour.
- Massage parlour.
- Boss...
Excuse me. Please sit there.
Why is she staring at us?
- What if she doesn't offer free tea?
- We'll have coffee.
Boss, what is she doing?
Let's go from here.
She's cleaning the seat for us.
Be positive especially
when you are negative.
Shameless fellow!
Auntie, one tea.
Sorry, I've run out of milk.
Did the milkman forget to deliver
or did the buffalo run out of milk?
I don't have milk as you
didn't pay your dues.
You come to my stall daily
and gorge on biscuits.
You always have tea and coffee here.
Am I doing this for charity?
Worthless.
Did I ever condemn you
by saying such things?
You've said a lot.
- I've actually run out of milk today.
- Oh!
Sir, tea.
Milk tea.
How did she give him tea?
Hot samosas for you, have it.
Thank you.
Missing boy.
The newspaper is backdated.
Your name shouldn't have been Suvarna
but ominous lady.
Dial this number.
Hello.
Your son was missing. Right?
Yes, he was but we've found him.
Oh no! He has been found.
Boss, his son was found.
Pack your bags, we're going to the city.
Hi! I'm one and only Satish.
My name is also Satish.
But he doesn't have a son like you do.
If that's the problem
then visit a sexologist.
Why did you come to me?
We're sincere citizens
looking for your son.
Oh! Thank you.
I found my son one week after
this advertisement was given.
Why didn't you inform that?
What?
You published the missing report.
You should inform people
after he is found. Right?
You don't have any basic ethics?
- What?
- What's your problem?
We wake up early in the morning
and spend our money to search him.
Did you ask me before doing this?
Really?
There are other people doing the same.
Shall I call them?
What can I do about it?
Do you know the amount of time
and money my boss invested in this?
Well... time spent won't come back.
- But we can get back the money, right?
- Right.
- No... no...
- So, you don't want the money?
Cross the threshold
and then give the money.
Money makes money.
It's a small amount, please manage.
- Already taken.
- Here it is.
I'll publish the news that
my son has been found tomorrow.
He has understood it very fast.
Boss, how do you get such unique ideas?
When you run out of luck and money
you get such ideas naturally.
'The bus travelling from Bangalore
to Anantapur met with a serious accident'
'at Anantapur Ghat road.'
'The driver along with
all the passengers died on spot.'
'The relatives are mourning
at Anantapur Memorial Hospital'
'in front of the bodies of the victims.'
'The bus owner has promised
a compensation of 10 lakhs to each victim.'
We've to go there and mourn.
Where?
Come on, find.
What?
One unclaimed body.
Why do you want an unclaimed dead body?
- Because you can cry.
- I?
What happened to you?
Both numbers 14 and 15 seem
to be unclaimed dead bodies.
14.
Stop.
I guess the relative has gone
to smoke or have tea.
They can leave the body alone
but can't give up their vices.
- Let's wait for some time.
- Okay, boss.
- Is he your husband?
- No.
Okay, go.
This is your husband.
Go and mourn his death.
- What happened...
- Wait.
You should look messy and sad
before you start mourning.
- Come on, go.
- Look what has happened.
- Why did you leave us and go?
Did you give him loan
that you're mourning so loudly?
You carry on.
We're very sad.
I'm also very sad.
I couldn't tolerate the stench,
so I went and had few drinks.
- Do you suspect me?
- No.
But I suspect you.
The word 'fraud' is written
on your t-shirt.
That's 'Ford', idiot.
I don't care what it is.
If the victim is your brother then
tell me where he has moles on his body.
My brother is not a lady
that he'll wear sari.
He used to wear lungi,
that too high-waist.
If you claim that he is your brother
but can't say where he had moles
then how can I believe you?
We are mourning our brother's death.
And all you're bothered about
is moles on his body.
Jackson, pay him for his drinks
and tell him to go.
Oh no, my sister-in-law.
My sister-in-law has fainted.
Come on, write down the details quickly.
Okay, I will. She'll get up.
She'll get up soon.
Look, she has come back
into her senses.
Come on, go now.
Here's the cheque of 10 lakhs.
You can't bring back
my brother's life with this money.
So, you don't want the money?
I don't want it but
my sister-in-law needs it.
She'll have to stitch clothes
and earn for us.
Please leave me.
She's my sister-in-law.
It's the fact.
Bye, sir.
- Hey!
- Who is it?
- What do you want?
- Who will take the dead body?
Come on, start crying.
Look, we've got 10 lakhs.
- Wow!
- Pour some more, boss.
You are too much.
Boss...
Brother, I'm sure we share some relation
or how would we get 10 lakhs.
I can do anything for you.
Whatever you wish.
But I don't know who you are.
I'm drinking as I can't do
anything for you.
I would've done if I could.
I swear I would've done anything.
I swear on my mother,
I would've done it.
- Jackson...
- Yes?
I hope there are no tigers here.
Save the tigers.
Who is it?
Boss, shut up!
Lord Shiva, when a daughter is angry
she goes to her mother
and when she's upset
she goes to her father.
My husband was an honest police officer.
He died in an accident.
Nobody found his dead body till now.
Whenever I visualize
my husband's cheerful face
I fail to bear this trauma.
He was my sole support.
But he was snatched away from me.
Now you'll take incarnation and come
or send your representative.
But you'll help your daughter
to get justice.
If you actually exist then come
in any form to save religion.
The savior will definitely come some day.
He'll deceive death.
"Hey Bhimaa!"
He'll vanquish evil and
rule over hearts of people.
"Hey Bhimaa!"
He'll come riding the Nandi bull
like an incarnation of Lord Shiva.
He will definitely come.
"Hey Bhimaa!"
Who is he?
He has come riding a bull
like Lord Shiva.
I don't think so.
I guess he's an actor of some theatre group
who has come for some funds.
Hunter, give him some coins
and tell him to go.
Take this.
Hail Lord Shiva!
This is a special view.
Did you see Lord Shiva?
O Lord!
Do you think you're God
just because you thrashed one guy?
Come on, hit me. Let me see.
Don't cheat...
come before me and then fight.
He is over there and not here. Look.
He's not God, he's a policeman.
Correct answer.
Policeman.
You won't get what you want.
- I've an offer for you.
- Offer?
An offer to kill a policeman.
- I'll do it.
Hey... hey...
Why are you celebrating like wild animals?
Listen to the rules.
- Are there rules too?
- Yes.
The number of alphabets in your name
is the number of times you can hit me.
If you miss one,
I'll get the chance to punch you.
No case. No lock-up.
The wise will take up the opportunity
while the foolish will sit and wonder.
There are only two alphabets in his name.
Can he hit you only twice?
He's the goon of a particular region.
A goon doesn't have identity
without his territory.
There are six alphabets. Right?
You know everything, Lord.
Shut up!
You come.
I never miss my target.
I also don't miss my target.
Is this your hand or a hammer?
Check the damage and guess the power.
He has only one alphabet...
no other name.
One alphabet, one punch.
Shrinivas Ramanuj Parbrahma Yadav.
His ration card has a longer name.
Lucky guy. Fifteen punches. Come.
He is over there.
You should've hit harder and
water would've come out from underground.
My dear devotee,
water has already come out of underground.
That's enough.
Bonitas!
It's not an abusive word.
In Spanish it means beautiful lady.
Oh! Thank you.
Get tea for me. Please.
Sugar?
He doesn't need sugar.
He has a sweet smile. Let's go.
Boss, I guess you've
lot of women followers.
I won't tell you my name.
I'll come and directly kill you.
"Hey Bhimaa!"
O Lord!
Where is Bhavani who thinks
he's the only man on Earth?
His father is here.
Won't he meet me?
Why are you looking at me like this?
Did I thrash him while fighting?
There's a problem.
Where did the culprit escape?
Is this old man Bhavani?
I swear.
I swear on my mother.
Oh no!
I thought Bhavani is a wild creature
who wreaks havoc in the jungle.
But he turned out to be timid one.
Grandpa, is this true? Are you Bhavani?
Oh no!
What kind of joke is this?
How can I hit you?
You'll die if I sneeze.
You don't know my problem, old man.
I'm Bhavani.
I'll listen to your details later,
you listen to me first.
Old man, listen to me.
Whenever I'm posted at a new place
I do my job in half-day's time
and get transferred.
So, I requested the commissioner.
He told me that you're a dangerous man.
He said I wouldn't be able
to solve this case.
He shared these details
and sent me here.
But what did I see after coming here?
The entire matter was solved
in an hour's time.
If the commissioner finds out
then he'll transfer me
to some other place immediately.
I didn't open the zip till now...
of my bag.
I know you thought something else.
Pervert Bhavani!
Bhavani, give me an idea
so that I can stay back here.
Idea?
Tea for you.
- Got it.
- What did you get?
Idea!
What if you suffer
a heart attack right now?
Oh no!
What if you suffer it after a month?
Thank god!
- Cheers!
- Thank you.
If you delay the sorrow,
its impact decreases.
Listen, old man.
I've an offer for you.
I won't arrest you right now.
I'll spend a month long vacation here.
You can watch television,
go shopping with your family,
attend weddings, go to discos and pubs,
tell stories to your grandchildren...
then just carry on and do it, old man.
But there's a small change in the story.
Tell your granddaughter that the prince
won't come riding a horse this time.
He'll come on a bull.
If anybody disturbs me during my vacation,
I'll ensure to take out an entourage.
- Hey!
- Shut up!
Come and go behind the bars
after a month.
Or you won't be able to get up.
Bonita, thank you for your hospitality.
Sir, why did you come here
instead of going to the police station?
Why did you come here?
- To put this garland on you.
- Then go ahead and do it.
- Sir, what have you done?
- Why have you come here?
- To play the drum.
- Then play it.
Didn't you bring cheer girls with you?
- What? Cheer girls?
- Yes.
Sir, you've big demands.
But my budget is limited.
- Please adjust with Chintamani this time.
- Who is that?
Look behind.
So, you are Mani. Come, Mani.
Why did you stop?
Keep playing.
- Lord...
- Yes.
You asked our names
and then thrashed us
but you didn't tell your name.
A smart poet has written a song for me
for situations like this
on audience demand.
My title song.
All the rights are reserved by me.
"Play the drums and the
band on streets and lanes."
"Our carefree boss is here."
"He has great attitude.
Move aside."
"Bhimaa moves around
with temper and attitude."
"Remain silent"
"Or he'll get violent."
"If you do anything wrong.
He'll set things on fire."
"Don't question him."
"There's no doubt he's awesome."
"He has confused everybody.
Bhimaa is here."
I don't drink quarter, I drink water.
"He's strong. He's powerful."
"He's quiet, but he's a monster."
"He is powerful."
"He's trending."
"He's super."
"People are scared of him."
"He'll crush anyone."
"He's everybody's protector."
"He's awesome."
"Anybody who challenges him
will be vanquished."
"You can try but not overpower him."
"Play the drums and the
band on streets and lanes."
"Our carefree boss is here."
"He has great attitude.
Move aside."
"Bhimaa moves around
with temper and attitude."
"Remain silent"
"Or he'll get violent."
"If you do anything wrong.
He'll set things on fire."
"Don't question him."
"There's no doubt he's awesome."
"He has confused everybody.
Bhimaa is here."
Sir... sir... what are you doing?
This pump is illegal.
Shut it down.
Are you a rowdy or a police officer?
No doubt about it.
Rowdy police.
Dad, I heard the new SI came home
and threatened you.
I'll give him a befitting reply
I'll ensure he becomes your slave
and salutes you day and night.
Forget him.
Do you know how important
the work you're doing is?
Finish the task first, my son.
In the meantime,
I'll infuriate the fire of revenge.
Come back and burn him
into ashes with the fire.
Boss, you can use your connections
and get Bhimaa transferred
immediately, right?
Didn't you hear what he said?
He's used to getting transferred.
If I do the same,
how will he feel the pain.
After Rudra's arrival
the way he insulted me
before the entire village
I'll make sure he comes
to my feet and apologizes.
I'll make him rub his nose on the ground.
Till then let him do what he wants.
Mic testing. One. Two. Three.
What is he up to?
Is he planning to start a new drama?
Brothers and their sisters.
Sir, you're a handsome man.
The ladies won't pay attention
if you address them as sisters.
You are right. I forgot.
Hold on.
The old man in the corner.
Alcoholic Pandu who
puts up posters on walls.
Beautiful Kanta and Kanta Rao
who always stares at her.
Listen. Listen. Listen.
- My name is Bhimaa.
- So, your name is Bhimaa?
Where is your mace?
Somebody wanted to see the demo
how I got the mace.
- Do you want to see it?
- Forget it.
- I've an offer for all of you
- Offer?
If you lose anything, come to the
police station and file your complaint.
The policemen will loot us if we go there.
- We don't trust the police.
- Right.
You don't have to trust me.
Sit and lick a lemon.
What?
Rest of you can come to
the police station and take cash
in the place of your stolen goods.
Will you pay us in cash
for our stolen goods?
Hmm.
What is this?
We rob people but he
wants to give them money.
So, you'll give us cash
for the stolen goods.
I won't bring back your missing wife.
- I won't complain about it.
- He is right.
If you do so,
I'll put you behind the bars.
If anybody lodges false complaints
I'll thrash them badly.
This offer starts from today
and will be valid
till I'm posted here
only for your well-being.
Take advantage of the offer.
Come on, applaud. Louder.
Sir, I've heard you give cash
in return of stolen goods.
Mr. Rao, we've got a customer.
Attend him.
What's wrong with him?
He's talking like us.
Yes, tell me.
My wallet was stolen from Geetanagar,
bus number 12.
- So, it's a case of pick-pocketing.
- Yes, sir.
The thief has no mercy.
- Did you get what I said?
- Yes, I have understood.
Mr. Old Boy, how much money
did you have in the wallet?
10,000 sir.
- 10,000?
- Yes, sir.
- Mr. Rao...
Write down 10,500.
Why?
I'm sure this old boy
will buy a new wallet.
Thank you, sir.
- Note down, sir.
- I'm writing down.
Write down about the new wallet.
- I'll note it down, sir.
- Okay, sir.
Sir...
Oh! I forgot.
Manju...
The audience is waiting for your entry.
I'll hit you if you come in slow motion.
Boss, how can I help?
Settle the dues of old boy
with your golden hands.
We've lot of money.
Take this. It's a small amount.
Take it. Profit.
Mr. Rao, call your juniors
and take my autograph.
- Why?
- Do I need to explain?
Boss... will you tell them or shall I...
- We need witness for this settlement.
- Okay.
We'll do it. Sign here.
Mr. Rao, you took 10,500 rupees from me.
You'll return it next week
along with interest. The due is 15500.
You've signed the paper and
agreed to it in front of witnesses.
Thank you for this.
- Sir...
- What is this, sir?
What is this, sir?
Will you pay a mechanic
if he doesn't repair your vehicle?
Will you pay a doctor
if he doesn't treat you?
Why shall I pay the police officers
who don't do their job?
Don't you feel ashamed?
You've stopped feeling ashamed long back.
You treat people who come
to file complaints as your customers.
We may not be able to help them
but we should do our work honestly.
After all,
it's a petty case of pickpocket.
Pickpocket? Pickpocket, huh?
If a middle-class man's
hard earned money is stolen...
If he fails to pay
all his utility bills on time...
If he runs out of money...
Do you know how it feels?
When he takes money from money-lenders
and is unable to pay back...
...the money-lender comes home
and humiliates the women of the house.
Do you know how it feels?
The person feels humiliated.
For you, it's a petty case of pickpocket.
When rich men are robbed or banks
are looted it's considered significant.
If a poor man gets robbed
it's considered a petty case.
We don't offer service according to
the financial status of complainants.
Public service is a serious duty.
Police service is a
damn serious responsibility.
An ordinary man feels half-dead
when he loses his hard-earned money.
People who take bribe from helpless people
instead of giving them justice are devils.
If you're interested in catching thieves
and recovering stolen goods,
only then you'll get salary.
If you fail, I'll take the stolen money
along with interest from you.
- Did you get it?
- Yes, understood.
Mr. Rao, I'm sure it's Ranga
as the theft took place in 12B.
I'll get the wallet from him.
Please make sir wait here
until I come back.
Sir, please stay here.
I'll be right back.
Sir, stay here. I'll be back soon.
Ranga. Ranga.
Sir...
- Why are you hiding here?
- I'll send your commission in the evening.
I don't want commission.
The new SI has planned a new mission.
Where is the wallet that
you stole from bus number 12 B?
- It's inside my loincloth.
- Oh!
No... no... it's not in this loincloth.
It's in the other one.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
You confuse me a lot.
Go and get it quickly. - Yes.
From how many buses did
you steal all these wallets?
It's from only one bus.
- From only one bus?
- Yes.
You're not an ordinary thief.
What is this?
How did you steal a nose
ring from somebody's nose?
There was a young couple in the bus.
They were busy with their phones.
- I took advantage of it.
- You're a thief by birth.
Where is his wallet?
There's money in this one.
I'm sure this is his wallet.
- Okay, take it.
- I've found the wallet.
- Thank you. Bye.
- Okay.
What if anybody else
comes to file a complaint?
- Listen...
- I want this whole bundle. Got it?
Only this one. Right?
Only this one?
How many bundles do you have?
- Sir...
- Yes?
My loincloths?
I'll wash them and send them back.
Shut up, baldy.
Sir!
Sir, I'm here.
Sir, I've come.
- I've got the wallet.
- Oh god!
One complaint and we've
the robber's treasure here.
Here it is.
Here is his wallet. Take it, sir.
Sir, money.
Sir, take it.
- Brother, the paper.
- I've it.
Look.
Sir! somebody stole my slippers
worth thousands from the temple.
Keep quiet.
We'll handle this case.
Put the table outside.
If he comes inside we'll be in trouble.
This man will loot us.
Listen... listen...
If you wish to file a complaint, you don't
have to come inside the police station.
You can file your complaint
outside the police station.
- Stand in queue.
- Boss, you are great.
You've done a great job.
- You're so smart.
- I haven't used my brain yet.
- I'm in a vacation mood.
- Oh great! Fantastic, boss.
Sir, special tea for you.
- In which school do you study?
- Study?
They don't teach us anything
in government schools.
I can't afford to go to private school.
I'm an orphan, sir.
I survive by selling tea.
Boy, get two cups of tea for us.
Coming, sir.
- What is your name?
- Rama.
- Bye, brother.
- Stop!
- What did you say?
- Bye, brother.
'Hey! Call me brother.'
Call me brother once again.
- Brother.
- 'I know you'll never say it.'
Say it again.
Brother.
'One day you'll call me brother.'
- Mr. Rao...
- Yes?
- Please find out.
- What?
- Her details.
- Okay.
Understood, sir.
What are you looking at?
I want an information, Grandpa.
- Why did you address me as Grandpa?
- You don't look physically stable.
You're not young.
You are right.
What do you want?
I want to meet the best goon in town.
People come here to file
complaints against goons.
You want to meet a goon.
But why? Tell me.
I'll share my complaint with the goon.
Why?
Whenever you approach a goon for work,
they take money.
They do the task sincerely.
If you go to the police for help, they
ask for bribe before filing complaint.
They want more money
during the follow-up.
There's no guarantee
that your work will be done.
They don't have any fixed rate.
You've exposed the policeman
with your straightforward words.
- That's great.
- This is how I am.
- I don't shy from telling the truth.
- Understood.
Who is the best goon in town?
Come on, tell me.
There's only one goon in this area.
The others have taken
voluntary retirement and left.
Who is he?
The best goon in town is our sir Bhimaa.
My name is Vidya.
- You are very cute.
- What?
I mean... her name.
I am also beautiful.
Hey... it's a compliment
and not complaint.
No, it's a complaint.
A guy named Romeo is after me
and wants to marry me.
Did you accept his proposal?
Oh no! No!
I didn't accept his proposal.
He threatened to throw acid at me
if I rejected him.
Acid? I'll pour acid inside his pants.
Do it, but right now I need a bodyguard.
So, your body needs a guard. Right?
What did you say?
Sir is saying that he's
our sole guard and protector.
I think you're his personal assistant.
You're continuously singing praises of him
since I came here.
- It's our duty, ma'am.
- Did you hear it?
I can see it clearly.
Tell me how much you'll charge.
I won't let you increase the amount later.
- For what?
- To guard her body.
I won't charge anything for it.
Grandpa, I told you that
you can't rely in the police.
Sir, madam has already made her decision.
Don't hurt her feelings.
5000.
5000 rupees?
Won't you offer any discount?
We're not offering
any sale or discount here.
- Keep this money as advance.
- For what?
This advance is for me.
You attend to her problem.
Sir, the jeep is ready.
Sorry, sir. The tyres went flat just now.
Sir, take the bike.
You've made sure everybody in
the police station follows you blindly.
- The entire city.
- Okay, let's go.
Excuse me.
- Your phone number?
- I won't share it.
You'll be at my service
whenever I call you.
So, I'll call you.
These men start flirting
whenever they get a chance.
Give me one chance.
Look at her gait.
- Babu Rao...
- No sir, I'm Kutumb Rao.
- It's okay, Babu Rao.
- Okay, sir.
Oh! You want to know about madam?
She's a temporary teacher
and is pursuing her PhD in botany.
- Strict teacher and a good student.
- Good.
Why are you doing research
on plants and trees
when you should be romancing in gardens.
Sir...
Okay, sir.
I need to impress her.
"Hail lord Shiva!"
We were waiting for you.
Sir, you're playing with the globe?
Stop overthinking, Mr. Rao.
Hello.
- Is the security there?
- Yes.
- Security.
- Hey...
Sir, madam has called.
Oh!
Hello.
- Security...
- Yes?
The Romeo is standing in my
school's corridor with an acid bottle.
Keep him busy, I'm coming.
Come on, boys.
Boys, come on.
Drive faster.
Oh no! The police have come.
I'll deal with you later.
Hey Romeo, stop.
Get him.
So many of you are
trying to catch one man.
What's this overacting for?
Sorry, Vidya. He has managed to escape.
I knew that he would escape.
How? How did you know?
I knew it when you left the jeep here
and ran after him.
It's obvious that he'll escape.
Okay. Shall I drop you?
No, thank you.
He ran in this direction.
I'll go in the opposite direction.
He starts flirting the moment
he gets a chance.
Sir, when will you get chance?
I haven't got it yet,
but I'll get it soon.
Oh!
Sir, you caught the Romeo.
Why did you tell her
that he managed to escape?
This was my plan.
You can run after girls.
It's a thing every man does.
A male puts in lot of effort
to impress a female.
But he never threatens to kill her.
It becomes necessary to threaten
or the girls don't give in.
This is a part of the plan.
You're right. You must threaten them
or they don't listen.
Thank you, sir.
You've understood my point.
I love you.
- Pour it.
- What, sir?
Acid.
What? Acid?
Pour it on me. Pour it.
Instead of getting scared
he wants us to pour acid on him.
- Show it to me.
- Here you go, sir.
Sir, you pour it on me.
You pour it on me.
Burn me.
What kind of man is he?
Sir, what are you doing?
Please don't do this.
Sir, he'll die.
Please forgive him.
Sir, forgive him... Sir...
Forgive him.
He added some pills to baking soda.
That's it.
Oh, God! He's a lunatic.
Give me his phone.
Take it.
Here.
- By what name have you saved Vidya's name?
- Vidya, my love.
So Vidya, you've appointed
the police to protect you.
I'll come to your hostel tonight
and throw acid on you.
This is wrong.
This is crime.
What is wrong?
The story will get cooked
only if I light the fire.
- Hello.
- Hey security.
Sir, you've lit the fire.
It's very fast.
Vidya!
Hello.
The Romeo has message me.
He has threatened to come
to my hostel and throw acid on me.
Please come fast.
When did the police officers
become so handsome?
Shut up!
I'm ready to get arrested by him.
I guess he's a virgin.
Yes, you are right.
Sir, what does virgin mean?
- Are you from Hindi medium?
- Yes, sir.
One who hasn't got lucky
with a woman yet.
Sir, it means I'm also a virgin.
Forget it.
Do you know if you're a virgin?
Shut up!
- Soldiers...
- Yes, sir.
Enter the dragon.
- The target is there and not here.
- Oh!
Hey... hey...
do you plan to enter our room?
- Yeah.
- This is a ladies' hostel.
- Can't you see that?
- Really? Is it?
- Who are you?
- Security.
- Where should you be posted?
- At the gate.
Mosquitoes will bite them
if they remain posted outside.
Poor fellows! They'll be in pain.
Will you take care of them
if they come to our room?
No, friend.
Come on, let's go from here.
Let's go.
No... no...
Hey! Don't sleep.
How can we sleep after seeing
so many beautiful ladies?
He starts flirting
whenever he gets a chance.
I think the food got spoilt
due to too much heat.
Sir, I understand we are virgin.
What's the problem with madam
that she is still a virgin?
Idiot, do you know what
the word actually means?
What are you doing?
Go inside, madam.
Sir and we'll be here.
- Idiot...
- Yes, sir.
You're happy that you
sent her inside, right?
What will you do if I go inside her room
in five minutes?
Impossible.
Do you know what a great man said?
What did he say? Tell me.
There's no word celled
'impossible' in his dictionary.
Baking soda with some pills.
Sara, acid. Run!
Hey! What are you doing?
Killing mosquitoes.
He threw acid in my room
and you're busy killing mosquitoes?
Who am I?
Security.
Where should I be posted?
At the gate.
I had told you that if I stay close to you
I can protect you.
Let him come inside.
Come in.
- Devotee.
- Yes, my lord.
What did she say?
Madam is calling you inside.
Idiot, the food is not burnt.
When a tiger cooks the rice,
it'll always be nice.
He didn't understand what I said,
explain it to him.
"You've cast your magic spell."
"I'm lost in you."
"The God has created you
with lot of efforts."
"Look at His divine plans."
"They've brought us together."
"I went crazy the moment I saw you."
"You've cast your magic spell."
"I'm lost in you."
"The God has created you
with lot of efforts."
"I wonder how beautiful
these moments are."
Stop. Stop.
Hey... where are you going?
To meet Mr. Ravindra Verma.
He's an Ayurveda expert.
I'm doing my research under his guidance.
Okay. So, he's your teacher.
He's more than just a teacher.
He's like my father.
"Our stories will reverberate everywhere."
Hey Rama...
Brother...
I've got some new clothes for you.
Wear them.
- Why, brother?
- It's my birthday tomorrow.
Why are you gifting me clothes
on your birthday?
Just like that.
- Thank you, brother.
- "I'm lost in you."
"The God has created you
with lot of efforts."
When did this school start?
A police officer has come
as a savior for the poor kids.
Bhimaa.
Madam, please come.
My wife is waiting for me.
Say something now.
You say it.
I love you.
Don't worry, he'll recover.
Will her fever subside
if she takes this medicine?
Why did you bring her so late?
We came here at night
but somebody informed us that
Guruji is not here.
Don't you know that Guruji
doesn't meet anybody after sunset?
- He doesn't treat anybody after sunset.
- Why?
It's a sin to cut plants after sunset.
Don't panic.
- Drink this and your fever will subside.
- Drink it.
Guruji...
It's a rare plant.
It has miraculous healing powers.
We can save many lives
by using this plant.
Greetings, Guruji.
God resides in every human being.
Bless everybody with happiness.
Guruji, you're the reason
why we all are so happy.
We had visited many hospitals
and spent millions on her treatment.
But nobody could cure our daughter.
Your treatment has healed my daughter.
You are our god.
This is not my greatness.
This is the greatness of our land.
The Sanjeevani plant that can bring
a dead person back to life
grows on this land.
So, we can find medicines
for every disease.
Guruji, people say that there are
miraculous healing plants in the Himalayas.
Do you get your plants from there?
Not only in the Himalayas...
The stone on which you
are standing is also magical.
One of the seven immortals is Parashuram.
Parashuram lived in this land.
The plants you see here
have magical medicinal properties.
They can heal any disease.
If we try wholeheartedly,
we can find Sanjeevani also here.
Is that true, Guruji?
It's impossible for humans.
We need an avatar of the lord,
a super human to attain it.
Greetings.
My name is...
Bhimaa. You are the new SI in town.
I've heard you're doing
a remarkable job since you came here.
I wanted to meet you.
You've already met.
Are you happy?
Bhimaa, I've a small request.
An ancient temple of our town
has been locked for five decades.
We were waiting for you.
We've been trying to
open the temple for years.
There are legal cases
pending in the court.
A temple where we can't pray
is like a childless mother.
I can't see the temple locked
when it should be full of energy.
Will you help us open the temple?
Boss, Bhimaa is troubling us a lot.
Since he came to this village
he has made sure our business shut down.
If this continues,
he'll find out about our tankers.
Can I send the tanker?
Yes, send it.
Let's inform our men in the jungle.
They'll kill Bhimaa, boss.
Just give the order once, boss.
- Give me the register.
- Sir.
- Give it.
- Okay.
Give me the phone.
Give me the torch.
Boss...
Bhimaa is at the check post.
Sir!
Sir, they've permit
for these two vehicles.
Sir, shall I let them go?
Let them go.
Sir, you know Bhavani is doing this.
Yet why are you quiet about it?
Are you waiting for Rudra?
There's somebody else behind them.
Why did you tell me to stop here?
I've a small work.
Go to the police station.
I'll join you.
Boss, Ravindra Verma has asked
Bhimaa to help him open the temple.
What did you say?
"Hey Bhimaa!"
Tell Pandava to finish his work quickly.
Oh no!
What happened?
The tanker's driver
is not answering my calls.
Call him again.
"Hey Bhimaa!"
Boss, I called him many times
but he is not answering my calls.
What happened to the tanker?
Come on, tell me.
Sir, an accident has taken place.
We got a call from the control room.
They couldn't connect
with the ambulance driver.
I'll go and get it.
Both of you stay with sir.
Sir, both the driver and cleaner are dead.
- Chandra...
- Sir?
Sir!
Brother, please come quickly.
What happened? The ambulance
driver is lying drunk on the beach.
The tyres are stuck in the sand.
The ambulance is stuck
in the sand of the beach.
They won't spare us.
More of them can come.
Sir, there's a shortcut
to the beach through the jungle.
But how will we go there
with the children?
Brother, will we die?
Don't panic.
Death will get scared when
they see how brave you are.
As long as Bhimaa is alive,
nobody can harm you.
It's my promise to you.
Boss, we can't stop him.
You've to get into action.
Chandra, stop.
Sir!
Brother!
Go!
"Hey Bhimaa!"
"Hey Gangadhar, the lord of Gouri."
"I seek refuge only at your feet."
"Hey Lord Shankar, you're my world."
"I always have your blessings with me."
"I always think of you."
"You're my lord."
"My everything is yours."
"Hail Lord Shiva!
You are always with me."
You're the lord of the world."
"Hail Lord Shiva!
You are always with me."
You're the lord of the world."
Won't you have oblation?
It's okay.
May God always bless you.
I don't know what blessing I'll ask for.
Share your wish with the lord.
I'm sure He will appear before you.
He doesn't have time for it.
- Did you bring what I told you to get?
- Yes.
Why did you bring
only these many coconuts?
Uncle, I had no option.
Previously they used to give six
for hundred rupees.
The price has increased.
They gave only five.
You should've bargained with him.
Before I could tell him anything
he looked at me angrily.
My head is more precious than a coconut.
So, I kept quiet and came back.
You always remain quiet.
You should've got the priest's post
after your father.
But idiot Siddhant got it instead of you.
If you stay simple
people will take advantage of you.
Coconuts are hard
but we break and eat it.
He'll not listen to me.
Okay, put 50 coconuts in this bag.
But there are only five coconuts.
Yes, I know but I've mentioned fifty here.
Oh god! You're taking fifty coconuts
instead of five and robbing god.
You've lost common sense.
God is not a glutton that
he'll devour fifty coconuts alone.
It's for us.
Try to understand.
Do we need to think about our stomachs?
It may not be important for us
but it's important for my fiance.
Who is she, uncle?
Who else? It's Mandira.
Oh god! But she's Paro's mother.
Idiot! Don't you remember
what Chanakya said?
It doesn't matter if the woman is married
or a spinster.
It's important that she stays with us.
Did Chanakya really say this?
You don't understand.
If you share your views in Chanakya's name,
the opinion becomes important.
Why are you looking there?
Does she know you love her?
If she knew she would've
definitely paid attention to me.
- I didn't tell her.
- Are you scared to tell her?
Idiot! Before I confess my love for her,
I need to make sure I can feed her.
I'm earning so that I can marry her.
What's the use of falling in love
at this age?
Age is just a number.
Age doesn't matter in love.
- Okay, we're getting late.
- To confess my feelings for her?
- To make the calculations.
- Oh yes!
Hurry up,
I've to go to teach the students too.
I completely forgot.
Yeah!
Rama!
Children, silence.
The children are making so much noise.
Don't you find it irritating?
Can't you ask them to keep quiet?
If they don't enjoy life now,
then when will they enjoy it?
They'll always remain irritated
and angry like you when they grow up.
We shouldn't stop them from enjoying.
If you don't stop them,
they'll turn into idiots.
They are not idiots, they are God.
Our elders say that
God resides in children.
Sir, this God is biting me.
You are also God, bite her back.
A human is helpless between two Gods.
Rama!
Oh god!
Hey Rama!
What happened?
Tell me.
You don't love me even 10% of
how much you love the children.
I said 'I love you' to you several times.
Did you say that you love me even once?
Oh no! Keep quiet Paro.
When will you take me with you?
If I lift you, I'll sprain my hips.
Did you hear that? Rama cracked a joke.
When will you elope with me?
Are you sure you are a man?
What are you saying?
I always went to the boys' toilet
when I was in school.
Only beard and moustache
doesn't make a person a man.
You need to take care of others too.
Paro...
The idiot works with the
students of our school daily.
Hey! Whom did you call idiot?
What's this, Paro?
Don't talk to me rudely.
I would've been your father.
But I missed the timing.
Look... he is trying to romance
my mother at the age of retirement.
And you...
- How can I love your mother?
- Rama...
I can't do this.
I can't tolerate your stupid jokes.
I love you and I'll elope with you one day.
Oh no! This is wrong.
You're engaged to Bhattacharya,
the priest's son. Right?
My dad was threatening to commit suicide,
so I agreed to get engaged.
But I love you.
He can't take care of his clothes.
If anybody snatches it from him,
he readily gives it.
Is this true?
Won't you take any action
if somebody tries to snatch me from you?
Do your clothes and I have the same value?
Bhattacharya is watching us.
Hey Rama!
I warned you several times
not to go near Paro.
Engagement is equal to half-marriage.
I'm her half-husband.
Her mother is married
yet I consider her my wife.
Sarangi.
Rama!
Sarangi, look at him.
He's well-built yet
he is scared of this timid guy.
Look at him.
- What kind of man is he?
- Timid guy?
Hey!
Paro, how can you love this coward?
If I show you how I love him,
you'll get jealous.
Have you crossed the limit, Paro?
No... I've gone close to him.
Paro! How dare you? Come on.
- Rama!
- Rama, I'll teach you a lesson.
- Come on.
- Rama!
- I won't spare you.
I don't care who I get married to.
I'll come only to you.
I love you.
Why is her mother not like her?
Rama, listen to me. Don't give
so much freedom to the children.
They become stubborn.
- Hello, sir.
- Hello.
Why did you get scared?
The same thing won't happen every time.
Don't panic.
Inside. Outside.
Inside. Yeah!
The priest's son is defeating
all of us in the game of cards.
Is it written anywhere that
a priest's son can't play cards?
The police has come.
- Come on, let's go from here.
- Let's go.
Everybody is running away on seeing me.
But you are sitting here.
Aren't you scared?
I make others run away.
Bhimaa is not scared of anyone
and won't run.
Why are you so proud?
I don't know if I'm proud,
but there's no machine to measure me.
Naughty boy!
You've started playing cards
at a very young age.
Wait. I'll teach you a lesson.
Where are you running?
Stop! I'll teach you a lesson.
Stop crying, Rama.
Today is Paro's birthday.
I had saved one rupee with
much difficulty to buy a gift for her.
The rogue Bhimaa stole the one rupee.
Look... look there.
Bhimaa is coming.
Why are you crying?
- You stole one rupee from me.
- Who are you?
I'm Shankar Bhagwati's son Rama...
Shut up!
You are Bhimaa's brother.
You're more precious than Bhimaa.
You'll give a precious gift to Paro.
Take this. Ten rupees.
Ten rupees?
What happened?
Call me brother and only
then I'll give it to you.
I'll say it. Come on, give it to me now.
- Are you sure you'll call me brother?
- Yes, I'll call you brother.
Come on, let's run.
- Call me brother.
- Get lost.
One day you'll address me as brother.
I'll never call you 'brother'.
Buy peppermint for me, Rama.
I'll buy bangles for Paro first.
Give me a dozen bangles.
Hey! You pushed me. Right?
Now you've come here to buy bangles?
- Sir... sir... it was not me.
- I will not spare you.
- Please don't hit me.
- Trying to fool the police.
Priest, your son has been arrested.
Sir has called you at the police station.
What did you do, Bhimaa?
If anything happens to Rama,
I'll kill you.
Rama...
Sir... sir, please pardon me.
It's not Rama but Bhimaa
who made the mistake.
- Listen to me.
- I've brought him to apologize.
The constable hit the child by mistake.
Please forgive us.
Please have a seat.
Who hit you?
Leave me.
I always land in trouble because of you.
I don't like you.
Go away.
Hey stop!
Oh no!
- Leave it, my child.
- Did you see him? He's a devil.
He took birth in my family by mistake.
God must've punished me
for some past sins.
God hasn't punished you.
- You are blessed.
- What?
You're right.
Rama is aware of the rituals,
he'll serve God.
But Bhimaa is strong.
We need to guide him
in the right direction.
No, sir. He has ruined my life.
- Put him behind the bars.
- Listen to me.
If you don't mind,
I would like to adopt your son Bhimaa.
Do what you like,
I'll perform his last rites today.
I have only one son Rama.
You're dead for me.
Rama, let's go.
Hey Rama...
Address me as brother once.
Get lost.
Will you become a police?
Will you give me gun?
Gun?
What happened, Rama?
He's not here.
Yet his memories torment me.
I don't know what sins
I committed in past life
that I became Bhimaa's brother
in this life.
Either I've to die or kill him
to get rid of these memories.
Look there...
they've dropped somebody in the water.
Come on, jump quickly.
He's Bhimaa.
Carefully.
"Hail Lord Shiva!"
Brother Bhimaa...
You risked your life to save me.
I'll never forget this favour.
We're indebted to you forever.
There was a time when we were scared
that Bhavani's men would harm our
families and so we stopped fishing.
After you came here
their dominance subsided.
The environment in the village
completely changed.
Now we can leave our families in the
village and go to the ocean for fishing.
You are god-sent messiah.
What happened, brother?
Why are you sitting alone?
I've got special tea for you.
Call me brother once.
Brother.
Why do become happy when
I address you as brother?
- What is your name?
- Rama.
Rama, don't be upset
that you lost your father.
I'm here with you.
- You can share anything with me.
- Paro, what are you doing?
- What's going on?
- Dad...
Dad...
I told you several times not to spend time
with this useless fellow.
Your father pretends to
be a great scholar. Right? - No...
- He never let me do well in life.
- No.
Now, you're trying to trap my daughter.
If I see you around her again,
I'll kill you.
- Come with me. Come.
- Rama.
How dare you hit my brother?
I won't let you enter the temple.
You'll be punished
for being Bhimaa's brother.
Worthless fellow.
Come with me.
Rama, what happened?
Come on, tell me.
You won't let me live peacefully.
Why are you following me?
Whatever I do is for your well-being.
Your arrogant attitude
has made my life hell.
Hey Rama...
Do you know what's the
biggest curse of my life?
That I have the same face as you do.
If you come before me again or if
you try to talk to me, I'll kill myself.
I swear on Lord Shiva.
Address me as 'brother' once
and I'll go away from here.
Hey! Get lost from here.
Call me 'brother' once again.
Brother.
Bhimaa... what happened?
What happened, Bhimaa?
It's a poisonous weapon.
In ancient times pirates used
to use this dangerous weapon.
Since you fell in the ocean,
the poison didn't affect you.
They poisoned you and threw you
into the ocean yet you came back alive.
This proves that you're
not an ordinary man.
You're a person who
can manifest his own death.
Brother!
Brother, I hope you're fine.
I'm absolutely fine, my child.
We don't know who our parents are.
We don't know which village we come from.
If we go to anybody they
scold us and throw us out.
They beat us if we say that we're hungry.
You saved us and lovingly hugged us.
Your kind gesture made us cry, brother.
I get strength when
I address you as brother.
Where are the remaining children?
Children are very delicate.
They were mentally depressed
because of this fatal conflicts.
Bhimaa, you've saved these children
but there are many children whom
we couldn't save from that hell.
"Hey Bhimaa!"
It won't take me too long to kill you.
How dare you play with
the lives of children? Rascal!
Bhimaa, you're concerned
about those useless children.
You are blaming me that I've
ruined their lives. What nonsense!
You're safe because I don't have evidence.
The day I get evidence against you,
I'll crush you.
You are just SI. Don't show attitude.
It won't take me long to get you fired.
Come on, do it.
If you're brave enough then do it.
Do you think I'll become
silent after getting orders
from my senior and sit quietly at home?
The uniform has kept the
wild animal within me in control.
If I lose my uniform
I'll tear you apart into pieces.
You're alive because I'm quiet.
You'll lose your life if I call my army.
Come on, do it.
Let me see what you can do.
Will you send your men or hire goons?
If I take action the crematorium
grounds will be full.
Bhavani, my vacation is now over.
I've a final offer for you.
I'll kill you after I torture you and your
son the way you tortured the children.
No case. No charge sheet.
"Hey Bhimaa!"
Oh no! Bloody idiot.
He doesn't value time at all.
Hey Rama!
Rama!
Rama, stop.
- I've been calling you for so long.
- She's always after Rama.
Your fiance is getting married
in a week's time.
Don't you have the courage to stop it?
Loving someone silently isn't enough.
You should be brave enough
to get the love of your life.
She had given another
explanation two days back.
Don't trouble me daily by explaining
how a man should behave.
- Spare me.
- Really? So, this is what you think.
I've abandoned my family
and come to you with all my jewelry.
Look at you.
How dare you think of leaving me?
- Jewelry!
- Come on, tell me... tell me.
Rama, let's elope and start a new life.
He has already ruined his present life.
He can't start a new life.
If he stays with you
and keeps wasting his time
doing meaningless rituals,
his life won't change.
He'll learn things if I elope with him
and take him to a new place.
You want to take me away
from this village?
I don't know the way to any other village.
Oh god!
You don't have to know the route.
Be strong so that we can go.
Hey... is it so easy to be strong?
He was never brave.
How can he change so soon?
Come on, let's go.
Don't worry, I'm here.
Who is he?
Who are you?
Why did you interfere in our conversation?
I'm not interested in interfering
in matters of strangers.
I'm their childhood friend.
Rama, didn't you recognize me?
Who is he?
Somebody was stealing coconuts
from the temple two days back...
- Yes!
- I broke his head.
- Yes, he is the one.
- No... no... I'm their childhood friend.
Didn't you recognize me, Paro?
Who are you?
Are you Srinivas Sharma?
Vishwanath Shastri?
- Satish!
- Yes, Satish. - Satish.
- I'm Satish.
- Is he Satish?
He looked very ugly in childhood.
He is not handsome even now.
He's dark and ugly.
It's wrong to do body shaming.
Paro, when our teacher used to teach us
we would suck sugarcane under the bench.
Do you remember it?
Yes, he is right.
Every child does this.
Paro, this man looks fishy.
He is not at all like Satish.
Do you still doubt me, Paro?
Do you remember his cowardly
stories that I share with you?
You are Satish.
You've changed a lot.
You've also changed a lot.
- You've become more beautiful. Yes.
- Oh!
Rama is still a timid cowardly guy.
Will you still be like this?
Be brave and jump.
How can I jump if there's a trench below?
Nobody gives attention to me
in this village.
Why should I shift to another village?
Not at all.
Friendship is not just an ordinary bond,
it's a bond between two humans.
You won't have to beg
as long as I'm with you.
- What will you ask for in return?
- Your head.
I'll get them married and get him a job
of a priest in some renowned temple.
I'm not sure if he'll help me become
a priest or make me starve to death.
Rama, please accept it.
You can enter the temple
and we can start a family too.
Paro is always in hurry
since her childhood days.
But her mother is not in hurry.
But her father is.
- Rama! Paro, don't commit this sin.
- We will not spare him.
- I'll get you married to him today.
- You're absolutely right.
- Come here.
- No.
Leave him.
- Aren't you ashamed of eloping with him?
- Aren't you ashamed?
I told you that he doesn't
deserve to be one of us. - He's right.
You'll have to clean the temple stairs
if you become his wife.
Yes, that's what you'll have to do.
I had told you that they are very proud.
So, god has made him useless.
I'll get you married to
Bhattacharya tomorrow morning.
Marriage with you? Shame.
- Give me your blessings.
- Bless you.
If you come the wedding won't take place.
- Rama!
Tell me, Paro.
I'm getting married tomorrow morning.
If you don't come and
take me with you tonight,
I'll drink poison and commit suicide.
Instead of enjoying my wedding feast,
You'll enjoy my funeral lunch.
What shall you do now?
The only person in this world
who loves me is Paro.
I can do anything for her.
This is the power of love.
Once he takes a decision,
nothing can scare him.
If you had showed this courage earlier,
I would've become your
father-in-law long back.
Paro... Paro...
Talk softly or the mosquitoes
will get disturbed. - Got it.
- Paro...
- Shut up!
Call her.
Who is speaking?
Uncle, I'm Paro's friend Pari.
- Okay. So, you are Paro's friend.
- You are right.
Do you think I'm a fool?
Paro has only one friend, that's Rama.
You should've called
from a telephone booth.
Your number is saved in this phone,
you fool.
- Call her in her landline number.
- Okay. You're right.
Hello. Hello. Who is it?
Who is this? Please talk.
Tell her that you're Sarangi.
Sarangi?
Who is Sarangi?
Auntie doesn't even know that
there's somebody called Sarangi.
Sarangi, so you are the one
who makes the blank calls daily?
- You've landed me in trouble.
- How dare you flirt with women?
You idiot! Get lost. Hang up.
You should've romanced at a young age,
but you're doing it now.
Love has no age.
It's the feelings that matter. Got it?
- You are an old man.
- What have you done at a young age?
What shall I do now?
Come on, tell me quickly.
Tell him quickly.
Her parents will be in the hall.
Go inside through the rear entrance.
- Through the kitchen?
- Yes.
Come on, go.
If you had shown this courage earlier
we wouldn't have to wait so long.
- Let's go now.
- Uncle, take care of yourself.
We'll leave now.
We don't share any blood relation,
but you always called me uncle.
Now you're leaving me.
I'm feeling upset.
Okay, my son. Go. Come on, hurry up.
Go. Go.
Take care.
Won't you come with us?
I'll stay with my Mandira.
I bless that you start
getting calls from her very soon.
- Amen.
- Stop giving her missed calls now.
Where are you taking us?
I'll take you to a safe place.
We're going to your relative's place.
All my relatives abandoned me
in my childhood.
Which relative are you talking about?
You always have doubts. He said
that he would take us to a safe place.
Now keep quiet.
What are you waiting for?
- Drive fast. Come on, hurry up.
- That's the spirit.
Bye, Sarangi.
Come on, let's go.
"Hail lord Shiva!"
Paro, where did he go?
There's a miraculous
temple in this village.
He went there to make
arrangements of our wedding.
I'm sure he left his phone
as he was in hurry.
Paro, we took a rash decision
and left our village by trusting him.
Please think if we are
taking the right decision.
Rama...
Boss, I called you many times
but you didn't answer my calls.
We duped the bus owner
and took 10 lakhs from him.
The police has come
to know about our fraud.
They are looking for us.
We've escaped.
You also go underground.
Got it, boss.
I'll hang up.
Who are you?
You are helping us so that
you can steal our jewelry. Right?
Rama, I'm your friend Satish.
- Paro, why don't you tell him?
- Don't lie to me.
Do you know it's a sin to cheat a Brahmin?
Will you commit a heinous sin for money?
Yes, I accept that there was a time
when I only thought about money.
This is the first time
I'm helping someone.
You cheated us and
now you are giving excuses.
I didn't cheat you, Rama.
I've brought you to your family.
I don't have anybody in this world.
But you're the only one in his world.
Who are you talking about?
I hope it's not him.
Yes, I'm talking about him.
I'm talking about your own brother.
I'm talking about Bhimaa who always
fights for the well-being of people.
There's something which
only you can do for him.
So, I've brought you here.
Sir, the children you saved are orphans.
They've no identity so nobody
filed any missing complaint.
We tracked the phone
you gave us and found out that
it belongs to Bhavani's man.
He called the men of Tandav.
Tandav is Bhavani's right hand man.
Whoever went into the forest
to kill him never came back.
He's a monster in human form.
He can smuggle anything
from herbs to women.
He has strong political connections so
we never got the permission to raid him.
Tandav forcefully brought some foreigners
and made them board Rudra's boat.
Rudra will come back
to the village after two days.
Hey Bhimaa! Come out.
I was not here for some time
so you got the chance to act smart.
Come out.
I killed her husband.
A true man doesn't hurt a woman,
but respects her.
A man can't bear pain
so God created woman,
so never hurt her.
The day a woman turns into fierce goddess,
there'll be catastrophe.
"Hey Bhimaa!"
Sir, shall I put them behind the bars?
For what? To give them free food.
You're right.
Hey!
Understood, my Lord.
I'll take all of them to the hospital.
- Mani...
- Yes, sir.
- Take Nandini home safely.
- Okay, sir.
Tell your boss that
his son is safe with me.
Why did you come here?
Yes.
Bhimaa, what happened?
My shirt ripped off.
Take off your shirt.
What are you saying?
We shouldn't wear torn clothes.
It's okay. Doesn't matter. Forget it.
It's considered a bad omen.
- I don't believe in such things.
- I'm telling you, it's a bad omen.
Take it off.
If I remove my shirt
people will think I'm mad.
I don't have a spare shirt.
- We'll manage something. Hold on.
- Vidya...
This one is dirty.
Not this one.
This one is perfect, wear this.
Okay. Turn around.
Lovely!
What happened, boss?
You seem to be in a romantic mood.
But I'm still worried.
I'll tell you a story
to change your mood.
A story? Okay, tell me.
- The sky is a man... like me.
- Okay.
- The earth is a woman like you.
They are always upset
that they can never meet.
So, God couldn't tolerate their pain.
He created the ocean.
If you see from far you'll see
the earth meeting with the sky.
That's why I brought you here.
You narrate romantic stories really well.
I don't only tell stories.
I want to be close to you
like the sky that embraces the earth.
I've a small wish.
Sleep with your head on my chest.
You'll hear nothing but my heartbeats
and the sound of the waves.
Nobody should touch you except
the cool breeze and my warm breath.
Nobody should see us except the stars.
Somebody is staring at us from there.
Who is it?
Hey!
- Hello, sir.
- Who are you?
- Bhimaa, stop.
- Sir... sir... - Why are you scared?
- Did you steal?
- No sir, that's not the case.
Any person will panic on seeing police.
- What's in your hand?
- It's a plant, sir.
Open the box.
Mother plant.
Mother plant?
Where are you taking this to?
- I'm taking it to Ravindra Verma sir.
- Oh!
So, you're going to Guruji.
- Okay, take it.
- This is a rare plant.
How did you get it?
This plant is found only in this forest.
The plant on which maximum fireflies sit
on a new moon night is the mother plant.
Sir, I'm taking it with me.
It's time for Guruji to make medicines.
I must leave now.
Did Guruji call you at this time?
Yes, he called me.
Let's go, Vidya.
'Guruji doesn't meet anybody
after sunset.'
- Come on, let's go.
- No. Stop.
- I'll be back soon.
- Wait, I'll come with you.
No... you stay here.
Rudra is here.
I'll be back soon.
Hey! Listen to me.
Where are you going?
Please wait, I'll be back soon.
Okay, come back soon.
Yes.
There's a back entrance to the temple.
Does it work?
Will he come back to life?
If you would've known about me,
you wouldn't have asked this question.
Ayurveda is that great?
Ayurveda is great, of course.
But Ravindra Verma is greater.
If we make some chemical
changes in the mother plant then
we can make Sanjeevani medicine
as mentioned in Charak Samhita.
It's a divine medicine which
only Ravindra Verma can make.
But why children?
The bodies of children are delicate.
They're less polluted
and more immune and pure.
So, the results are remarkable.
Continue the experiment.
No!
"Hey Bhimaa!"
Brother!
Come on, lift the boat.
"Hey Bhimaa!"
Bhimaa!
Hey!
If you step forward,
she'll die a terrible death.
If I prick this half an inch inside,
her blood will clot
and her nerves will burst.
She won't shed tears but blood.
She won't be able to bear the pain.
She'll beg that I kill her.
Nothing can save her.
Do you know what's the value of a life?
Yes, I know the value of life
so I'm conducting experiments
to make the medicine that'll
bring dead people back to life.
You're not bringing back people to life.
You're killing innocent children.
Ants die when elephants walk.
Will they stop walking to save them?
Many petty creatures will be sacrificed
to attain a bigger purpose.
Let it happen.
You're not an elephant,
you're a mad animal.
This is not craziness.
This is my knowledge.
I'll make Sanjeevani and win over death.
I'll bring the world to my feet.
Ravindra Verma is the God of future.
God doesn't turn into a monster
for his selfish gains.
No God can bring a
dead person back to life.
I'm greater than God.
You've lost your mind.
You're not great.
You're a mental patient.
You are right.
We're patients.
Do you know what's our medicine? Money.
Money will cure us of everything.
This inspired us to work hard for days.
Now when we're going to get the result,
you've come to stop us.
If I step forward I know you'll kill her.
If I step further,
I'll kill you and you know it.
Let Vidya and the kids go.
I'll step back.
That's not enough.
What else do you want?
I want your life.
If my life can save so many lives,
then kill me.
No, Bhimaa!
Brother.
Bhimaa!
Please stop.
No, brother.
Bhimaa...
Ravindra Verma,
if any of them lose their life,
if you shed a drop of Vidya's blood,
then you'll be finished.
I'll come back again.
Kill me.
Brother.
This dead body should be found.
How?
It should look as if both of them
have died in an accident.
'I've a small wish.'
'Sleep with your head on my chest.'
'You should hear only my heartbeats
and the sound of the waves.'
'Nobody should touch you except
this cool breeze and my warm breath.'
'Nobody should watch us
except the stars.'
I think an accident has taken place.
Put the dead bodies in the burning bus
so that nobody finds the truth.
Our work will be done.
'SNL Bus travelling from
Bangalore to Anantapur'
'met with a serious accident
at Anantapur Ghat.'
Number 14. Unclaimed body.
Bhimaa is dead?
Rama...
Bhimaa is dead.
That day I got to know about your brother.
He sacrificed his life for a purpose.
I handed over my body to him
so that he can take revenge.
But...
Only a person from my family
can fulfill my incomplete task.
Somebody who has my blood.
My body is dead.
But my blood is still flowing
in somebody's veins.
My representative is alive
to take revenge for me.
My brother Rama.
Within ten days after my funeral
go to Mahendragiri temple
and make Rama remove the rudraksha
necklace and ask him to chant.
You've to make him do it.
Hey!
Rama!
No! Don't hit him.
Is he still alive?
Don't beat him.
Rama...
This is not him.
He is not Bhimaa, he's Rama.
How long will you take to make Sanjeevani?
Fool, poison came out first
during the churning of the ocean.
It'll take us time
to get the elixir we want.
Kill them and throw them into the ocean.
Don't do that.
We've conducted the experiments
on children till now.
Let's conduct the experiment on them now.
After that you can throw him
in the ocean.
No!
I'm not telling this
as I'm scared of losing my life.
I want you to call him
so that you can save lives.
Once... just remove the rudraksha
necklace once... and call Bhimaa.
I'm sure he's here waiting for you
to call him.
Your brother was killed in this place.
We must accept the fact that
they're doing a heinous crime
by killing children.
But it'll be a sin if you sit quietly
when you can save them.
The sin which can't be cleaned
even with your blood.
Look there.
Brother!
The girl is calling you brother.
Help!
She thinks that you are Bhimaa.
You always considered Bhimaa a devil.
God takes the form of devil
while slaying demons.
A man who kills to satisfy his pride
is a monster.
One who kills to save religion is God.
The final decision is yours.
Is your hatred for Bhimaa
and your stubbornness more important
than the faith of these children?
Bhimaa. You hate this name.
Get lost.
You detest his name.
Bhimaa!
But even now, he's our protector.
Only he can punish them.
Bhimaa!
Hey Rama, call me brother once.
Get lost.
I'm calling you with love.
My brother, Bhimaa.
Come.
"Hey Bhimaa!"
You owned a kingdom,
yet you were greedy.
An irreligious priest.
Whenever there is irreligiousness,
God will take incarnation
to slay the demon.
Your betrayal has helped me.
For the first time my brother Rama
called me brother.
I'm feeling proud.
You'll get joys in return
of the joy you gave me.
Joy of death.
"You are the beginning, the end."
"You're everything."
"We need not fear when you're with us."
"You are the beginning, the end."
"You're everything."
"We need not fear when you're with us."
"You are the beginning, the end."
"You're everything."
"We need not fear when you're with us."
"You are the beginning, the end."
"You're everything."
"We need not fear when you're with us."
"Hail Lord Shambhu!"
"The lord of destruction.
Hail Lord Shiva."
"Hail Lord Shambhu!"
"Hail Lord Shiva."
This is a strong bond.
I know that many spirits want
to take revenge against me
as I've killed many children.
Ghosts and spirits can't cross
this boundary and come inside.
I'm the future God.
You can't defeat me.
Whenever and wherever there
is decline in religious practice,
O descendant of Bharata
and rose of irreligion
at that moment I'll descend on Earth.
Do you think God will come here?
In which age are you living?
Will Lord Vishnu appear here?
Will he hear the pleas of Prahlad
and come here
in the incarnation of Narasimha?
Will he appear like Lord Shiva?
Come on, call Him.
Let me see if He comes.
Call Him.
Lord Rama vanquished Ravana
who was proud of his strength.
In order to vanquish a devil like you
in this Kalyug...
to kill the evil...
Parashuram is here.
"Hail Lord Shiva!"
Hanuman got Sanjeevani
so that he could save a life.
A fraud like you won't get it.
You'll get death from me.
I'm the future God.
I'll keep the world at my feet.
You said it, right?
I'll kill you and send you to hell.
Both were born from the same womb.
But they never walked together.
I was a fool and misunderstood
your love for me.
Please forgive me if you can.
I want to relive the moments
that I missed out in my childhood.
Rama, you've been blessed with a son.
Really?
What name will you give him?
"Hey Bhimaa!"
"You are the beginning, the end."
"You're everything."
"We need not fear when you're with us."
"You are the beginning, the end."
"You're everything."
"We need not fear when you're with us."