Port of San Fransokyo.
The winner!
By total annihilation.
Yama!
Who's next?
Where's the guts to stop me in the ring?
With little Yama!
Can I try?
I have a robot.
I built it myself.
Beat it kid!
House rules: You gotta pay to play.
Oh, is this enough?
What's your name, little boy?
Hiro?
Hiro Hamada.
Prepare your bot, Zero...
Two bots enter...
One might lives.
Fighters ready?
Fight!
That was my first fight.
Can I try again?
No one likes a sore loser little boy.
Go home.
I've got more money...
Fighters ready?
Fight!
Megabot!
Destroy.
- No more "Little Yama".
- But what?
This is not possible!
Hey, I'm as surprised as you are.
Beginner's luck.
Do you wanna go again?
Yama?
No one hustles Yama!
Wooh! Hey!
Teach him a lesson!
Hey fellas
Let's talk about this.
- Hiro, get on!
- Tadashi!
Ooh! Good timing.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
- Are you hurt?
- No!
Then, what are you thinking, knuckle head!
You graduated high school and you're 13
and this is what you're doing?
Hold on!
Bot fighting is illegal.
You're gonna get yourself arrested.
Bot fighting is not illegal. Betting on
bot fighting..that's..that's illegal.
But, so who could heed
I'm on a roll big brother.
And there is no stopping me!
Oh, no.
Hi, Aunt Cass.
Are you guys okay?
Tell me you're okay...
- We're fine.
- We're okay.
Oh Good.
Then what were you two
knuckle heads thinking?!
For 10 years, I heed the
best I could to raise you.
Have I been perfect? No!
Do I know anything about children? No!
Should I pick a book on parenting?
Probably?
Where I was going with this?
I had a point...
- Sorry.
- We love you, Aunt Cass.
I love you too!
I had to close up early because of you
two fellons on beat poetry night.
Stress eating because of you!
Come on, Mochi!
This is really good!
You'd better make this up to Aunt Cass,
before she eats everything in the cafe.
For sure!
And I hope you learned your lesson,
bone head.
Absolutely!
You're going bot fighting, aren't you?
There's a fight across town.
If I book I can still make it.
When are you gonna start doing something
with that big brain of yours?
What? Go to college like you?
So people can tell me stuff I already know?
Unbelievable!
Ahh! What would Mom and Dad say?
I don't know.
They are gone.
They died when I was 3, remember?
Hey!
- I'll take you.
- Really?
I can't stop you from going,
But I'm not gonna let you go on your own.
Sweet!
What are we doing at your nerd school?
Bot fights that way!
Gotta grab something.
Is this gonna take long?
Relax you big baby,
we will be in and out.
- Anyway, you've never seen my lab.
- Oh great! I get to see your nerd lab.
Heads up!
Wooh!
Wow...
electromag suspension?
Hey!
Who are you?
Gogo, this is my brother, Hiro.
Welcome to the nerd lab.
Yeah...
I've never seen electromag
suspension on a bike before.
Zero resistance
faster bike.
But...
Not fast enough.
Yet.
Ohh! Woohh! Do not move!
Behind the line please.
Hey, Wasabi.
This is my brother, Hiro.
Hello, Hiro.
Prepare to be amazed.
Catch!
- laser induced plasma?
- Oh, yeah!
With a little magnetic confinement for ah..
Ultra precision.
Wow, how did you find
anything in this mess?
I have a system. There is a place for
everything, and everything in its place.
- I need this!
- You can't do that!
This is anarchy!
Society has rules!
Excuse me!
Coming through!
Tadashi!
Oh my gosh, you must be Hiro!
I've heard so much about you!
Perfect timing!
That's a whole lot of tungsten carbide.
400 pounds of it.
Come here! Come here!
You're gonna love this.
A dash of per chloric acid.
A smidge of cobalt,
A hint of Hydrogen Peroxide...
super heated to 500 Kelvin, and...
Tadah!
It's really great, huh?
- So pink.
- Here's the best part.
Wooh!
I know right!
Chemical metal embrittlement!
Not bad, Honey Lemon.
Honey Lemon?
Gogo? Wasabi?
I spilled wasabi on my shirt
one time people. One time!
Fred is the one who comes up
with the nicknames.
Ah... Whose Fred?
This guy right here.
Ah! Ah! Don't be alarmed,
it is just a suit.
This is not my real
face and body.
The name is Fred.
School mascot by day but by night
I'm also a school mascot.
So, what's your major?
No! No! I'm not a student but I
am a major science enthusiast.
I've been turning to get honey
to develop a formula...
That can turn me into a
fire breathing lizard at will.
- But she says that's not science.
- It's really not.
Yeah, and I guess the shrink ray I ask
Wasabi for isn't science, either?
Is it?
Nope!
Well then, what about invinsible sandwich?
Hiro!
Imagine eating a sandwich but,
everybody just thinks you're crazy.
Just stop.
- Laser Eyes?
- What?
- Tingly fingers? Never gonna happen!
- Then what about grocery...
- So, what are you been working on?
- I'lll show you.
Duct Tape?
I hate to break it to you, Bro.
Already been invented.
Awww! Dude! Awww...
This is what I've been working on.
Hello, I am Baymax.
Your personal health care companion.
I was alerted to the need for medical
attention when you said:
Awww...
A robotic nurse?
On a scale of 1 to 10,
How would you rate your pain?
Physical, or emotional?
I will scan you now.
Scan complete.
You have a slight epidermal
abrasion on your forearm
I suggest an anti-bacterial spray.
Whoa, whoa...
What's in the spray specifically?
The primary ingredient is: "Bacitracin."
That's a bummer, I'm
actually allergic to that.
You're not allergic to Bacitracin.
You do have a mild allergy to:
Peanuts.
Not bad.
You've done some serious
coding on this thing huh!
Ahah! Programmed to over more
than 10,000 medical procedures.
This chip! Is what makes Baymax,
"Baymax."
Vinyl?
Yeah, going for a non-threatening
huggable kind of thing.
Looks like a walking marshmallow.
No offense.
I am a robot.
I can not be offended.
Hyperspectro Cameras?
Yup.
- Titanium skeleton.
- Carbon fiber.
Right.
Even lighter.
Killer actuators, where did you get those?
Machine them right here...
In house..
- Really?
- Yup.
- He can lift a thousand pounds.
- Shut up!
You have been a good boy,
have a lollipop.
Nice!
I can not deactivate until you say:
You are satisfied with your care.
Well then, I'm satisfied with my care.
He's gonna help a lot of people.
- Hey, what kind of battery does it use?
- Lithium lon.
You know, Super Capacitor
would charge way faster.
Burning the midnight oil, Mr. Hamada?
Hey, Professor, I actually
was finishing up.
You must be Hiro.
Bot fighter, right?
When my daughter was younger,
That's all she wanted to do.
May I?
Sure!
- Hmm!
Magnetic Bearing Servos.
Pretty sick huh?
Wanna see how I put them together?
Hey, genius!
He invented them!
You are Robert Callaghan?
Like as in, Callaghan cat most blind man.
Callaghan, laws of robotics?
That's right.
Ever think about applying here?
Your age wouldn't be an issue.
I don't know, he's pretty serious
about his career in bot fighting.
- Well, kind of serious.
- I can see why.
With your bot
winning must come easy.
Yeah, I guess.
Well, if you like things easy,
then my program isn't for you.
We push the boundaries of robotics here.
My students go on to shape the future.
Nice to meet you, Hiro.
Good luck with the bot fights.
You gotta hurry if you wanna
catch that bot fight.
I have to go here!
If I don't go to this nerd school.
I'm gonna lose my mind.
How do I get in?
Every year, the school has
a student showcase.
You come up with something that blows
Callaghan away. You're in.
But, its gotta be great.
Trust me...
It will be...
Nothing!
No ideas.
Useless empty brain.
Wow...
washed up at 14.
So sad.
I got nothing! Im done!
I'm never getting in!
Hey...
I'm not giving up on you.
- What are you doing?
- Shake things up.
Use that big brain of yours
to think your way out.
What?
Look for a new angle.
Ahhhh...
Wow, a lot of sweet tech here today.
How you feelin?
You're talking to an ex-bot fighter,
It takes a lot more than this to rattle me.
Yup, his nervous.
Oh! You have nothing
to fear little fella.
He's so tense.
- No! I'm not.
- Relax, Hiro...
Your tech is amazing!
Tell him, Gogo...
Stop whining, woman up.
I'm fine.
What you need, little man? Deodorant
breath mint, fresh pair of under pants?
- Under pants? You need serious help.
- Hey, I come prepared.
I haven't done laundry in 6 months.
One pair last me four days.
I go front, I go back, I go inside out
then I go front and back.
- Wow! That is both disgusting and awesome.
- Don't encourage him.
It's called "recycling".
Next Presenter: Hiro Hamada.
- Oh yeah! This is it!
- I guess I'm up.
Okay! Okay, photo! Photo!
Everybody say: "Hiro!"
Hiro!
- We love you, Hiro. Good luck!
- Don't mess it up.
Break a leg little man!
Science, yeah!
Alright! Bro. This is it!
Come on, don't leave me hanging.
What's going on?
I really wanna go here.
Hey...
You got this.
Hi...
My name is Hiro...
Sorry.
My name is Hiro Hamada.
And
I've been working on something
that I think is pretty cool.
I hope you like it.
This, is a microbot.
Breathe.
It doesn't look like much.
But...
when it links up with
the rest of its pals..
Things gonna get a little more interesting.
The Microbots are controlled
with this neurotransmitters.
I think about what I want them to do...
They do it.
The applications for
this tech are limitless.
Construction...
What use to take teams of people
working by hands for months or years.
Can now be accomplished by one person.
And that's just the beginning...
How about...
Transportation?
Microbots can move anything,
anywhere, with ease.
If you can think it...
microbots can do it.
The only limit is your imagination.
Microbots!
That's my nephew!
My Family!
I love my family!
Nailed it!
- You did it!
- You did it bad.
- Good job, Hiro.
- It blows my mind, dude.
They loved you.
That was amazing!
Yes.
With some development,
your tech could be revolutionary.
Alastair Krei.
May I?
Extraordinary.
I want your microbots at Krei Tech.
Shut up.
Mr. Krei is right.
Your microbots are an
inspired piece of tech.
You can continue to develop them...
Or you can sell them to a man whose
only guided by his own self interest.
Robert, I know how you feel about me.
- But it shouldn't affect you...
- This is your decision, Hiro.
But you should know,
Mr. Krei has cut corners
and ignored sound science
to get where he is.
That's just not true.
I wouldn't trust Krei Tech
with your microbots
or anything else
Hiro...
I'm offering you more money than any
fourteen year old could imagine.
I appreciate the offer, Mr. Krei.
But they are not for sale.
I thought you were smarter than that.
Robert.
Mr. Krei...
That's my brother's.
Oh, that's right.
I'm looking forward of
seeing you in class...
Alright geniuses!
Let's feed those hungry brains.
Back to cafes, dinner is on me.
Yes! Nothing is better than free food.
Aunt Cass...
Unless it's moldy.
- We'll catch up, okay?
- Sure.
I'm so proud of you!
- Both of you!
- Thanks, Aunt Cass.
I know what you gonna say.
I should be proud of
myself because I'm finally
using my gift for
something important..
No! No, I was just gonna tell you,
your fly was down for the whole show.
Haha, Hilarious!
What?
Ahh!
Welcome to nerd school!
Nerd!
Hey, I am...
I wouldn't be here
if it wasn't for you, so...
You know...
Thanks for not giving up on me.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm okay.
But Professor Callaghan is still in there.
Tadashi, No!
Callaghan's in there.
Someone has to help.
Tadashi!
Hey...
Sweetie...
Hey, Aunt Cass.
Mrs. Matsuda is in the cafe.
She is wearing
something super inappropriate
for an 80 year old.
It always cracks me up.
You should come down.
Maybe later.
Oh, the university called again.
It's been a few weeks
since classes started,
but they said its not
too late to register.
Okay, thanks.
I'll think about it.
Bot Fights.
Hi, Hiro!
We just wanted to check in
and see how you're doing.
We wish you were here, buddy.
Hiro, if I could have only one
super power right now...
It would be the ability to crawl through
this camera and give you a big hug.
Awww...
Hello, I am Baymax.
Your personal health care companion.
Hey...
Baymax, I didn't know
you were still active.
I heard a sound of distress.
What seems to be the trouble?
Oh, I just had my toe a little.
I'm fine.
On a scale of 1 to 10,
How would you rate your pain?
Zero?
I'm okay, really.
Thanks. You can shrink now.
- Does it hurt when I touch it?
- That's okay. No! No touching!
Ahh! Ahhh!
Awwww!
You have fallen.
You think?
On a scale of one...
On a scale...
On a scale of one to ten...
On a scale of one to ten,
How would you rate your pain?
Zero.
- It is alright to cry.
- No! No...
- Crying is a natural response to pain.
- I'm not crying.
- I will scan you for injury.
- Don't scan me.
- Scan complete.
- Unbelievable!
You have sustained no injuries.
However, your hormone and
neurotransmitter levels
indicate that you are
experiencing mood swings.
Common on adolescenes.
Diagnosis:
Puberty.
Whooh! What?
Okay, time to shrink now.
You should expect an increase in body hair.
Especially on your face, chest, armpits
, and...
Thank you, that's enough.
You may also experience strange
and powerful new urges.
Okay, let's go you back in your luggage.
I can not deactivate until you say:
You are satisfied with your care.
Fine, I'm satisfied with my...
Woooh ohh!
My microbot?
This doesn't make any sense.
Puberty can often be a confusing time for
young adolescent flowering into a manhood.
No!
The thing is attracted
with other microbot, but...
That's impossible, they were
destroyed in a fire.
Damn thing is broken.
Your tiny robot is trying to go somewhere.
Oh, yeah? Why don't you find
out where he is trying to go?
Would that stabilize your
pubescent mood swings?
Absolutely.
Baymax?
What?
Hiro?
Hey! Aunt Cass...
- Wow, you're up?
- Yeah, I figured it was time.
Are you registering for school?
Ah, yes. I've thought about what you said.
Really inspired me.
Oh, honey. That's so great!
Okay, special dinner tonight.
I leave up some chicken wings...
You know, with a hot sauce
that makes us faces numb.
Okay, sounds good.
Great!
Last hug.
Baymax!
Are you crazy?
What are you doing?
I have found where your
tiny robot wants to go..
I told you, its broken!
It's not trying to go...
Locked.
There is a window.
Please exercise caution. A fall from
this height could lead to bodily harm.
Oh, no.
Excuse me, while I let out some air.
Are you done?
Yes.
It will take me a moment to re-inflate.
Fine, just keep it down.
My microbots?
Someone's making more.
Hiro?
You gave me a heart attack.
My hands are equipped with defibrillators.
- Clear!
- Stop! Stop!
It's just an expression!
Oh, no!
Run!
Oh, come on!
I am not fast.
Yeah, no kidding!
Go! Go!
Come on!
Kick it down!
Punch it!
Go! Go!
Come on, go! go!
Move it!
Come on!
The window!
Suck it in!
Baymax!
Hiro?
Come on! Let's get out of here!
Go! Hurry!
Alright, let me get this straight.
A man in a kabuki mask attacked you
with an army of miniature flying robot.
Microbots!
Microbots.
Yeah, he was controlling
them telepathically
with a neurocranial transmitter.
So Mr. Kabuki was using ESP to
attack you and balloon man.
Did you file a report when your
flying robots was stolen?
No, I thought they were all destroyed.
Look, I know it sounds crazy but
Baymax was there too. Tell him.
Yes, officer. He is telling the tru... th.
What that...
What's wrong with you?
Low battery.
Whoa! Whoa, try to keep it ho..me
I am a health care, your personal Baymax...
Kid, How about we call your parents
and get them down here.
What?
Write your name and number down
in this piece of paper, and we can...
I gotta get you home to
your charging station.
Can you walk?
I almost scan you now.
Scan complete.
Health care.
Okay...
If my aunt asked, we are
at school all day, got it?
- We jump out of window.
- No, But be quiet! Shhh!
We jump out of window.
But you can't say things like
that in front of Aunt Cass.
Hiro?
You home, sweetie?
That's right!
I thought I heard you.
Hi!
Hey! Aunt Cass.
Oh, look at my little college man.
Ah! I can't wait to hear all about it.
Oh! It means its almost ready.
Weeeehh!
- You be quiet?
- Yeah, Weeeehhh!
Alright, get ready to have
your face melted.
We are gonna feel this things tomorrow.
You know what I'm saying?
Okay, sit down, tell me everything.
The thing is, since I
registered too late.
I've got a lot of school
stuff to catch up on.
What was that?
Mochi.
Oh! That darn cat.
Oh! Just take a plate for the road, okay?
- Don't work too hard.
- Thanks for understanding.
Hairy baby.
Alright, come on.
I'll carry on, I'm your personal Baymax.
One foot in front of the other.
This doesn't make any sense.
Tadashi.
What?
Tadashi's gone.
When will he return?
He is dead, Baymax.
Tadashi was in excellent health.
With a proper diet and exercise,
He should have lived a long life.
Yeah, He should have.
But there is a fire...
Now he's gone.
Tadashi is here.
No, people keep saying
he is not really gone.
As long as who remember him.
Still hurts..
I seen no evidence of physical injury.
It's a different kind of hurt.
You are my patient.
I would like to help.
You can't fix this one buddy.
Ah..What are you doing?
I am downloading a
database on personal lose.
Database downloaded.
Treatments include: Contact with friends,
and loved ones.
- I am contacting them now.
- No! No, don't do that.
- Your friends have been contacted.
- Unbelievable!
Now what are you doing?
Other treatments include: Compassion,
and physical reassurance.
I'm okay, really.
You will be alright.
Thanks, Baymax.
I am sorry about the fire.
It's okay, it was an accident.
Unless...
Unless it wasn't a...
Ah! Ah! The showcase, the guy in
the masked stole my microbots
and set the fire to cover his tracks.
He's responsible for Tadashi.
We gotta catch that guy.
It's alive, It's alive,
It's alive, It's alive!
If we're gonna catch that guy,
you need some upgrades.
Will apprehending the man in the
masked improve your emotional state?
Absolutely!
Let's work on your moves.
Now let's take care of this.
I have some concerns.
This armor may undermine my
non-threatening huggable design.
That's gotta be the idea buddy.
You look sick!
I can not be sick.
I'm a robot.
It's just an expression.
Data transfer complete.
I fail to see how karate makes me
a better health care companion.
You wanna keep me healthy, don't you?
Punch this.
Yes!
Hammer fist!
Side kick!
Knife hand!
Back kick!
Gummy Bears!
Yes!
Yeah, fist bump..
Fist bump is not in my fighting database.
No, this isn't a fighting thing.
It's what people do sometimes when
they are excited or pumped up.
Hey, now you're getting it.
I will add fist bump to my
care giving matrix.
Altight! Lets go get that guy.
Come on!
Get him, Baymax!
We're too late.
Your tiny robot is trying to go somewhere.
Come on.
Always wait one hour after
eating before swimming.
Hey!
Come on!
Your heart rate has increased dramatically.
Okay, Baymax.
Time to use those upgrades.
Hiro?
No! No, get out of here!
Go!
What are you doing out here?
Nothing! Just stop for a walk.
Helps my pubescent mood swings.
- Is that Baymax?
- Yeah, but you really...
Ahh! Why is he wearing
carbon fiber under pants?
I also know Karate.
- You guys need to go.
- No, don't push us away, Hiro.
We're here for you.
That's why Baymax contacted us.
Those who suffer a lose, requires
support from friends and loved ones.
Who would like to share
their feelings first?
Oh! I'll go!
Okay!
My name is Fred, and it
has been 30 days since...
Holy Mother of Megazod!
Am I the only one seeing this?
Aaahhh, My gosh!
Oh no!
Go! Baymax, get him!
No! No! No, what are you doing?
I'm saving your life.
Baymax can handle that guy.
Oh, no!
Wasabi!
Goodbye!
Hiro, explanation now!
He stole my microbots, he started the fire.
I don't know who he is!
Baymax, palm hill strike!
Hard left!
That Mask, black suit...
We are under attack from a
super villain people!
I mean, how cool is that?
I mean it's scary obviously, but how cool?
- Why are we stopped?
- The lights red.
There are no red lights in a car chase!
Why is he trying to kill us?
Why are you trying to kill us?
It's classic villain, we've seen too much!
.
Let's not jump to conclusions,
We don't know he is trying kill us.
Car!
He is trying to kill us!
Did you just put your blinker on?
You have to indicate your
turn, it's the law!
That's it!
Stop the car!
Baymax and I can take this guy!
Seat belts save lives.
Buckle up everytime.
Whoa!
What are you doing!
What are you doing?
I think we lose him.
Watch out!
Baymax, hold on!
- We are not gonna make it!
- We are gonna make it!
We made it!
Yes!
I told you we're gonna make it.
Your injuries require my attention
and your body temperatures are low.
We should get out of here.
I know a place.
Where are we?
Fred?
Where are you going?
Oh, welcome to Mi Casa.
It's French for "front door".
It's really not.
Listen, nitwit!
A lunatic in a mask just tried to kill us.
I'm not in the mood Fred.
Welcome home, Master. Frederick.
Heathcliff, my man!
Come on in guys.
We'll be safe in here.
Give me some.
Freddie?
This is your house?
I thought you lived
under a bridge.
Well, technically it belongs to my parents.
They are on a vacay in a family island.
We should totally go sometime.
For a luck!
You gotta be kidding me.
- Fred, do not touch!
- Fred.
If I wasn't just attacked
by a guy in a kabuki mask.
I think this would be the
weirdest thing I've seen today.
My brain hates my
eyes for saying this.
Your body temperature is still low.
Yeah, uh-huh.
Ahh! It's like spooning
a warm marshmallow.
Oh! It's so nice!
Ah yeah!
Ah! It's toasted.
Ahh! Good robot.
Do you know the meaning
of this symbol, friends?
Yes, it's a bird!
No! The guy in the mask was carrying
something with this symbol on it.
Apprehending the man in the mask will
improve Hiro's emotional state.
Apprehend him?
We don't even know who he is!
I have a theory.
Dr. Slaughter MD?
Actually, millionaire weapons designer,
Malcolm Chastletick.
The annihilator?
Behind the mask, industrialists.
Reed X worthy.
Baron von De-Struck?
Oh, just get to the point!
Don't you guys get it?
The man in the masked who attacked us,
Is none other than...
Voila!
Alastair Krei.
What?
Think about it, Krei wanted your
microbots and you said no.
Rules don't apply to a man like Krei.
There's no way!
The guy's too high profile.
Then who was that guy in the mask?
I don't know, we don't know
anything about him.
His blood type is AB negative.
Cholesterol levels are...
Baymax, you scanned him?
I am programmed to assess
everyone's health care needs.
Yes!
I can use the data from
your scan to find him.
Uh, you'd have to scan everyone in
San Fransokyo...
and that might take,
I don't know, forever?
No! No... No, I just have to look
for another angle.
Got it!, I'll scan the whole city
at the same time.
I just have to upgrade Baymax's sensor.
Actually, if we're gonna catch this guy.
I need to upgrade all of you.
Upgrade who now?
Those who suffer a lose, requires
support from friends and loved ones.
Oh wohhooh!
Okay! I like where this is heading.
We can't go against that guy!
We're nerds!
Hiro, we want to help,
But we're just us.
No!
You can be way more.
Tadashi Hamada is our best friend.
We're in.
Can you feel it?
Do you guys can feel these?
Our origin story begins.
We are gonna be Superhero!
Arms up!
The neurotransmitters must be in his mask.
We get the mask,
then he can't control the bots.
Game Over!
♪ They say we are what we are ♪
♪ But we don't have to be ♪
♪ I'm glad to hate you but ♪
♪ I do it in the best ways ♪
♪ I'll be the watcher ♪
♪ Of the eternal flame ♪
♪ I'll be the guard dog ♪
♪ Of all your fever dreams ♪
♪ I am the sand in the bottom ♪
♪ Half of the hourglass ♪
♪ Cause we could be immortals
♪ Immortals ♪
♪ Just not for long ♪
♪ For long ♪
♪ If we meet forever now ♪
♪ Pull the blackout curtains down ♪
♪ Just not for long ♪
♪ For long ♪
♪ We could be immor ♪
♪ Immortals ♪
♪ Immor ♪
♪ Sometimes the only payoff ♪
♪ For having any faith ♪
♪ Is when it's tested again and again ♪
♪ Everyday ♪
♪ I'm still comparing your past ♪
♪ To my future ♪
♪ Cause we could be immortals ♪
♪ Immortals ♪
♪ Just not for long ♪
♪ For long ♪
Super Jump!
I breathe fire!
♪Just not for long ♪
♪ For long ♪
♪ Cause we could be immor ♪
♪ Immortals ♪
♪ Immor ♪
Woohooo!
- I love it.
- Not bad.
Anybody else whose suit
riding up on them?
Hey guys!
Check this out.
I'd like to introduce,
Baymax 2.0.
Huh! He's glorious.
Hello.
Whoaah! Hold up!
Focus!
Show them what you got, buddy!
The Fist!
Show them the fist!
Balalala...
No!
Not that!
The thing!
The other thing.
Whoaah!
Rocket fist!
Make Freddie so happy.
That's just one of his new upgrades.
Baymax, wings!
No way!
Thrusters!
I fail to see how flying makes me a
better health care companion.
I fail to see how you fail to see,
that it's awesome!
Full thrust!
Whoaah!
Waah!
Hey big guy!
Let's just take this slow.
Up! Up! Up!
Thrust! Thrust! Thrust!
Too much thrust! Too much thrust!
Too much thrust!
No! No, no... back on!
Back on! On! On!
Up, up!
Ahhh!
Oh, man!
Maybe! Maybe enough flying for today.
What do you say?
Your neurotransmitter
levels are rising steadily.
Which means what?
The treatment is working.
Oh, no!
No, no!
Oooh, Baymax!
Yes!
Woohh...!
That was...
Sick.
It is just an expression.
Thats! Thats right buddy.
I am never taking the bus again.
Your emotional state has improved.
I can deactivate if you say:
You are satisfied with your care.
What?
No, I don't want you to deactivate.
We still have to find that guy.
So, fire up that super sensor.
Functionality improved.
1000% increase in range.
I have found a match.
On that island.
Killer view!
Yeah, If I wasn't terrified of heights,
I'd probably love this.
But I'm terrified of heights,
so I don't love it.
There.
Baymax, take us in.
Awesome!
Our first landing together as a team.
Guys, come on!
Quarantine?
Do you people know what quarantine means?
Quarantine, enforced isolation
to prevent contamination
that could lead to disease
or in some cases...
Death.
- Oh! There's a skull face on this one.
- A skull face!
Be ready.
He could be anywhere.
Cease fire!
That was a bird.
Well, at least we know
our gear works.
Six centreped friends lead
by Fred, their leader Fred.
Fred's Angels.
Harnessing the power of the sun with
the ancient amulet they found in the attic.
The amulet is green.
It's probably an emerald.
Fred, I'll laser hand you on the face!
Guys! Ssshhhh...
Any sign of him, Baymax?
The structure is interfering
with my sensor.
Perfect! The robot's broken.
Ah! Guys, you might wanna see this.
What do you think it is, genius?
Ah! I'm not sure.
But look.
Hiro!
Krei.
That's right, we were
asked to do the impossible.
That's what we did.
We re-invented the very
concept of transportation.
Friends, I present,
Project: "Silent Sparrow".
General, may I?
Wow, magic hat.
Teleportation, the transport of matter
spontaneously through space...
Not science fiction anymore.
Now, We didn't spend billions of
tax dollars to teleport hats.
Ladies and gentlemen,
you're here to witness history.
Ready to go for a ride, Abigail?
We've invited all these people.
Might as well, give them a show.
T minus 30 seconds to launch.
The castle is in position.
27.
Sir, we picked up a slight irregularity
in the magnetic containment field.
Mr. Krei, is there a problem?
No! No problem.
It's well within the parameters.
Let's move forward.
3... 2... 1...
Abigail.
Field breach, abort!
We lost all contact with the pod!
Oh, no!
- It's breaking up!
- The pilot is gone!
Portal 2 is down.
The magnetic containment field is down!
Krei, shut it down now!
I want this island sealed off!
The Government shutdown
Krei's experiment.
And he is using your microbots
to steal his machine back.
Krei is the guy in the mask.
Oh, no!
Baymax, get us out of here.
Go for the transmitter!
Behind his mask!
Baymax!
Okay, what's the plan?
It's fred time.
Super jump!
Gravity Crash!
Falling hard!
Seriously, what's the plan?
Get the mask!
Right behind you.
For real, what is the plan?
Hey!
You want to dance, masked man?
You'll be dance with this.
Hand over the mask or
your gonna taste of this!
And a little bit of that!
Ahah!
Wooh!
Hey, I did alright.
Is that all you got?
Oh, you got that too?
Get back into the fire!
It's over, Krei.
Professor Callaghan?
The Explosions.
You died.
No! I had yourmicrobots.
But, Tadashi...
You just let him die.
Give me the mask, Hiro.
- He went in there to save you.
- That was his mistake!
Baymax, destroy!
My programming prevents
me from injuring a human being.
Not anymore.
Hiro, this is not what..
Do it Baymax!
Destroy him!
No! Stop, Baymax!
No, stop!
His getting away!
Baymax!
My health care protocol has been violated.
I regret any distress I made have caused.
How could you do that?
I had him!
What you just did,
we never signed up for.
We said, we catch the guy.
That's it!
I never should've let you help me!
Baymax, find Callaghan!
My enhanced scanner has been damaged.
Wings!
- Hiro, this isn't part of the plan.
- Fly!
Hiro!
Your blood pressure is elevated.
You appear to be distress.
I'm fine.
There, is it working?
My sensor is operational.
Good, let's get...
What?
Are you going to remove
my health care chip?
Yes, open...
My purpose is to heal,
the sick and injured.
Baymax, open your access port.
Do you want me to terminate
Professor Callaghan?
Just open!
Will terminating Professor Callaghan,
improve your emotional state?
Yes! No! I don't know!
Open your access...
- Is this what Tadashi wanted?
- It doesn't matter!
- Tadashi programmed me to aid...
- Tadashi's gone!
Tadashi's gone.
Tadashi is here.
No, he is not here.
This is Tadashi Hamada.
And this is the first test of
my robotics project.
Hello! I am Baymax.
Stop! Stop!
The seventh's test of my robotics project.
Hello, I am...
Wait! Wait, Stop! Stop scan!
Stop!
Tadashi Hamada again.
And this is a 33rd test
of my robotics project.
I'm not giving up on you.
You don't understand this yet, but people
need you, so let's get back to work.
This is ah... Tadashi Hamada,
and this is a the 84th test...
What do you say big guy?
Hello, I am Baymax your personal
health care companion.
It works!
Oh, this is amazing!
It work!
I knew it, I knew it!
It worked, I can't believe!
I can't...
Okay! Alright! Big moment here.
Scan me.
Your neurotransmitter levels are elevated.
This indicates that you are happy.
I am, I really am...
Oh man! Wait my brother sees you.
You're gonna help so many people buddy.
So many.
That's all for now
I am satisfied with my care.
Thank you, Baymax.
I'm so sorry.
I guess I'm not like my brother.
Hiro.
Guys, I...
We are going to catch Callaghan.
And this time, we'll do it right.
Hey! But maybe don't leave your team
stranded on a spooky island next time.
Oh, man!
Nah! It's cool! Heathcliff picked
us up in a family chopper.
Hiro, we found something
you should see.
You almost got us all killed.
Krei! You did this!
You knew it wasn't ready!
Callaghan?
He was there?
He was such a good man.
What happened?
I don't know, but the answers
here somewhere.
Wait! Wait, stop!
There is!
With the pilot?
Hang on!
We've invited all these people.
We'll see.
The pilot was Callaghan's daughter!
- Callaghan blames Krei!
- This is a revenge story!
So what are we waiting for?
This beautiful new campus is the
culmination of a life long dream.
But none of these would have been possible
without a few bumps on the road.
Those setbacks, made us stronger...
and set us on the path
to a bright future!
What?
Setback?
Why is my daughter a setback?
Callaghan.
But you...
Your daughter, that was an accident.
No!
You knew it was unsafe!
My daughter is gone because
of your arrogance.
What are you doing?
You took everything from me when you
send Abigail on that machine.
Now I'm taking everything from you.
No! No! You can't.
You are going to watch everything
you built disappeared...
and then it's your turn.
Professor Callaghan!
Let him go!
Is this what Abigail would have wanted?
Abigail is gone!
This won't change anything.
Trust me. I know.
Listen to the kid, Callaghan. Please let
me go. I'll give you anything you want.
I want my daughter back!
Go for the mask!
Baymax!
ACTION!
Leaving into action!
Getting a little tight!
No!
- Too strong!
- No way out!
- Hiro! You beat him!
- Help!
- Hiro! Hiro!
- Hiro! Help!
That's it! I know how to beat him!
Listen up, use those big brain of yours,
and think your way around the problem!
Look for a new angle!
I can't go any further!
Wait a second, it's a suit!
Hello, sign.
Care to go for a little spin?
Double Spin!
And Back Spin!
Yeah!
Baymax!
Hiro!
I love that robot!
Okay, new plan.
Forget the mask.
Take out the bots, they'll get
sucked up into the portal.
Now! That is a plan!
- Honey, Fred, can you give us some cover?
- Like you have to ask.
- Let's do this Freddie!
- Smoke screen!
Ready?
And...
Dive!
Whoa, gravity is getting
a little weird here guys.
Let's use this!
Green Blaze of Fury!
Woman up!
Triple Sign Spin!
Now! The signs is on fire!
Wooo, now that's a chemical reaction!
Back Kick, Knife Hand, Round house.
Hammer fist!
This ends now!
Looks like you're out of microbots.
What?
Baymax!
Our programming prevents us
from injuring a human beings.
But we'll take that.
It's still on!
We have to shut it down.
We cant! The containment field is failing,
the portals gonna tear itself apart.
We need to get out of here now!
Baymax!
My sensors is detecting signs of life.
- What?
- Coming from there.
The life signs are female.
She appears to be in hyper sleep.
Callaghan's daughter.
She is still alive!
Abigail?
Lets go get her.
The portal is destabilizing!
You'll never make it.
She's alive in there.
Someone has to help.
What do you say, buddy?
Fine, makes me a better
health care companion.
Careful! There's Krei Tech
debris everywhere!
Look up!
I have located the patient.
Hurry!
Come on, buddy.
Let's get her home.
I'll guide you out of here. Let's go!
Be right.
Okay, to the left!
Har right!
Up and over!
Okay, level up!
Easy.
Woohoo, nice flying!
Almost there!
Baymax!
- My thrusters are inoperable.
- Just grab hold.
There is still a way I can
get you both to safety.
I can not deactivate until you say:
You are satisfied with your care.
No! No, wait!
What about you?
You are my patient. Baymax!
Your health is my only concern.
- Stop! No! No, im gonna figure...
- Are you satisfied with your care?
No, there's gotta be another way.
I'm not gonna
leave you here. I'll
think of something.
There is no time.
- Are you satisfied with your care?
- Please, No!
I can't lose you too.
Hiro...
I will always be with you.
I'm satisfied with my care.
Hiro!
Yeah, they made it!
Baymax?
Miss, can you hear me?
What is your name?
Abigail Callaghan.
Okay, Abigail. You're gonna be fine.
We're taking you to the hospital.
Move in!
A massive clean-up continues today at the
headquarters of Krei Tech Industry.
Reports are still flooding in about
a group of unidentified individuals.
Who prevented what could have been a
major catastrophe.
The whole city of San
Fransokyo is asking. Whose
are these heroes? And
where are they now?
- Hey!
- Hi!
Hey, sweetie.
Okay.
Last hug.
Bye.
Awww...
I am Baymax.
Your personal health care companion.
Hello! Hiro.
We didn't set out to be superheros.
But sometimes life doesn't go
the way you plan.
The good thing is, my
brother wanted to help
a lot of people and
that's what we gonna do.
Who are we?
♪ They say we are what we are ♪
♪ But we don't have to be ♪
♪ I'm glad to hate you ♪
♪ But I do it in the best way ♪
♪ I'll be the watcher ♪
♪ Of the eternal flame ♪
♪ I'll be the guard dog ♪
♪ Of all your fever dreams ♪
♪ I am the sand in the bottom half ♪
♪ Of the hourglass ♪
♪ I'll try to picture me ♪
♪ Without you but I can't ♪
♪ Cause we could be immortals ♪
♪ Immortals ♪
♪ Just not for long ♪
♪ For long ♪
♪ If we meet forever now ♪
♪ Pull the blackout curtains down ♪
♪ Just not for long ♪
♪ For long ♪
♪ We could be immor ♪
♪ Immortals ♪
♪ Immor ♪
♪ Sometimes the only payoff ♪
♪ For having any faith ♪
♪ Is when it's tested again ♪
♪ And again everyday ♪
♪ I'm still comparing your past ♪
♪ To my future ♪
♪ It might be over but ♪
♪ They're not sutures ♪
♪ I am the sand in the bottom ♪
♪ Half of the hourglass ♪
♪ I'll try to picture me ♪
♪ Without you but I can't ♪
♪ Cause we could be immortals ♪
♪ Immortals ♪
♪ Just not for long ♪
♪ For long ♪
♪ If we meet forever now ♪
♪ Pull the blackout curtains down ♪
♪ Just not for long ♪
♪ For long ♪
♪ We could be immor ♪
♪ Immortals ♪
♪ Immor ♪
♪ And if we meet forever now ♪
♪ Pull the blackout curtains down ♪
♪ We could be immortals ♪
♪ Immortals ♪
♪ Just not for long ♪
♪ For long ♪
♪ We could be immor ♪
♪ Immortals ♪
♪ Immor ♪
Dad...
I just wish I could share my
accomplishments with you.
You mean so much to me,
and honestly...
I have always felt the
distance where with you
being at the family island
all the time, and...
I just wish you could see ah...
Fred...
Son...
Dad...
I wear them front, I wear them back
I wear...
I go inside out, then
I go front and back.
Dad!
We have a lot to talk about.
SharePirate.Com Subs