(ALARM BLARING)
Nelson family, another
fun and successful robbery!
ALL: Yay!
Binky, take that priceless
artifact out of your mouth.
You don't know where
it's been. (WHIMPERING)
Walter, have you
seen Binky's pacifier?
Jeepers Christmas, Madge, we may
have left it behind in the museum.
Gosh, Binky, I hate to say
it, but that pacifier's gone.
Maybe it's time
to be a big boy.
(SIGHS)
(SUCKLING)
(RETCHING)
You're never
getting me back, Binky.
I've moved on.
(GASPS)
Hmm...
(GIGGLING)
(HORSE NEIGHING)
(GASPS)
(SHRIEKING)
(GIGGLES)
(BEEPING)
(GIGGLES) Huh?
(ALARM BEEPS)
Phew.
(ALARM WAILING)
Huh?
(STRUGGLING)
(SIGHING)
Huh?
(GASPS) Yeah!
(GIGGLES EXCITEDLY)
Well, well, well,
what do we have here?
(GASPS)
Hold the...
What in the...
Wait a minute.
You robbed the museum.
Nah-uh, Baby-face,
you ain't going anywhere
till you give me
that junk back.
(LAUGHING)
Give me your best shot.
Ha! You missed.
Give me the art back.
Now!
(CHUCKLES)
(GASPS)
No, no, no!
Honey, Walter, I just wanna
check on Binky. (YAWNING)
He's my favorite.
You see, Madge, he's forgotten
all about that pacifier.
Oh...
They grow up so fast.
We're great parents.
Top 10, Madge, top 10.
(DOOR CLOSES)
(GIGGLES)
(SUCKLING)
Hello? Hello?