1
00:00:27,062 --> 00:00:29,961
<i>They say, if you wanna
tell a story right,</i>

2
00:00:30,041 --> 00:00:32,347
<i>you gotta start
at the beginning.</i>

3
00:00:35,010 --> 00:00:37,451
<i>Too far? Fine.</i>

4
00:00:37,999 --> 00:00:40,971
<i>This is me, Harleen Quinzel.</i>

5
00:00:41,051 --> 00:00:43,992
<i>When I was a kid, my dad
traded me for a six-pack of beer.</i>

6
00:00:44,072 --> 00:00:45,846
<i>But however many times
he tried to ditch me...</i>

7
00:00:45,926 --> 00:00:48,535
<i>- Daddy!
- ...I kept coming back.</i>

8
00:00:48,752 --> 00:00:50,930
<i>Eventually,
he found me a new home.</i>

9
00:00:51,010 --> 00:00:54,483
<i>The good sisters of St.
Bernadette's taught me a lot.</i>

10
00:00:56,051 --> 00:00:59,358
<i>But I was never
an establishment kinda gal.</i>

11
00:00:59,546 --> 00:01:03,003
<i>All things considered, I did good.
I even went to college.</i>

12
00:01:03,083 --> 00:01:06,940
<i>Got my PhD.
Had my heart broken once or twice.</i>

13
00:01:07,020 --> 00:01:08,992
<i>Finding love, it's not easy.</i>

14
00:01:09,072 --> 00:01:12,909
<i>So I threw myself into my work,
became a psychiatrist.</i>

15
00:01:12,989 --> 00:01:17,765
<i>That's when I met him.
Mr. J. My Joker.</i>

16
00:01:18,010 --> 00:01:21,961
<i>Oh, I fell hard. Like out
of a plane without a parachute,</i>

17
00:01:22,041 --> 00:01:24,055
<i>right in your dumb
fucking face kinda hard.</i>

18
00:01:24,135 --> 00:01:26,971
<i>I lost all sense of who I was.</i>

19
00:01:27,051 --> 00:01:31,034
<i>I only had eyes for Puddin'.
We all know the saying,</i>

20
00:01:31,114 --> 00:01:34,909
<i>"Behind every successful man
"there's a badass broad."</i>

21
00:01:34,989 --> 00:01:38,055
<i>Well, that was me.
I was the brains behind some of</i>

22
00:01:38,135 --> 00:01:41,695
<i>Mr. J's greatest stunts.
Not that he let anyone know it.</i>

23
00:01:41,755 --> 00:01:42,488
Puddin'?

24
00:01:42,609 --> 00:01:46,368
<i>I guess all good things
have to come to an end.</i>

25
00:01:47,062 --> 00:01:48,142
<i>So...</i>

26
00:01:50,805 --> 00:01:53,020
<i>...we broke up.</i>

27
00:01:54,083 --> 00:01:56,909
<i>I handled it real mature.</i>

28
00:01:56,989 --> 00:02:00,389
<i>But Mr. J was
super broke up about it.</i>

29
00:02:03,093 --> 00:02:08,399
<i>I got an amazing new place
that was all mine.</i>

30
00:02:10,968 --> 00:02:13,034
<i>It gave me the space
to really reflect</i>

31
00:02:13,114 --> 00:02:15,420
<i>on the mistakes of my past.</i>

32
00:02:19,051 --> 00:02:22,378
<i>I had to find a new identity.</i>

33
00:02:23,083 --> 00:02:24,756
<i>A new me.</i>

34
00:02:28,041 --> 00:02:32,023
<i>It wasn't easy. But after a while,
I even opened myself up</i>

35
00:02:32,103 --> 00:02:35,378
<i>to the possibility
of new love.</i>

36
00:02:37,989 --> 00:02:41,849
Hi. Hello, nice baby.

37
00:02:45,252 --> 00:02:49,472
<i>- Here's the thing about new love...</i>
- I take payment-in-kind.

38
00:02:49,690 --> 00:02:52,316
<i>...you have to feed it.</i>

39
00:03:02,770 --> 00:03:05,003
<i>Soon enough,
I was back on my feet.</i>

40
00:03:05,083 --> 00:03:08,950
<i>Ready to move on,
to make new friends.</i>

41
00:03:09,030 --> 00:03:11,919
<i>She means fucking business!</i>

42
00:03:11,999 --> 00:03:13,065
<i>- Oh, here we go!</i>
- Whip me!

43
00:03:13,145 --> 00:03:16,950
<i>She has taken a whip from the
pivot, catapulted to the high side!</i>

44
00:03:17,030 --> 00:03:19,119
<i>Oh!</i>

45
00:03:26,072 --> 00:03:28,555
Yeah! Come on!

46
00:03:28,978 --> 00:03:32,545
<i>It was time for Gotham
to meet the new Harley Quinn,</i>

47
00:03:33,030 --> 00:03:35,075
<i>so I really
put myself out there.</i>

48
00:03:35,155 --> 00:03:38,472
Ride that pole
like you ride your man!

49
00:03:43,124 --> 00:03:45,992
God damn it.
Sit the fuck down.

50
00:03:46,072 --> 00:03:48,282
- What?
- I said...

51
00:03:48,363 --> 00:03:51,013
Sit your skinny ass down,
you dumb slut.

52
00:03:51,093 --> 00:03:53,093
Okay.

53
00:03:56,135 --> 00:03:58,878
You broke my fucking legs!

54
00:03:58,958 --> 00:04:00,958
Oh, boo-hoo.

55
00:04:04,134 --> 00:04:05,991
What?

56
00:04:06,071 --> 00:04:09,371
It's not a party without
a little drama, am I right?

57
00:04:09,436 --> 00:04:11,918
Come on! Turn it up!

58
00:04:11,998 --> 00:04:14,054
Shots on the house.

59
00:04:14,134 --> 00:04:18,074
Call me dumb.
I have a PhD, motherfucker.

60
00:04:18,154 --> 00:04:20,482
- Miss Quinn.
- Romy.

61
00:04:20,946 --> 00:04:23,033
- That was my driver.
- Oh, whoops.

62
00:04:23,113 --> 00:04:25,054
Well, I'm sure it was his fault.
Consider him fired.

63
00:04:25,134 --> 00:04:28,946
Consider me grateful. Especially
since I know you don't like me.

64
00:04:29,061 --> 00:04:31,939
I agitate his already delicate
sense of mental equilibrium.

65
00:04:32,019 --> 00:04:34,991
That and his obsessive-compulsive
need to be the center of attention.

66
00:04:35,071 --> 00:04:37,471
Will your paramour
be joining us this evening?

67
00:04:37,998 --> 00:04:41,461
Not tonight, Romy.
Not tonight.

68
00:04:41,967 --> 00:04:45,022
Well, enjoy yourself, Miss Quinn.
And do give the Joker my best.

69
00:04:45,102 --> 00:04:47,981
<i>Okay, fine, so I hadn't
told people about the breakup.</i>

70
00:04:48,061 --> 00:04:51,054
<i>- But you don't understand.</i>
- Find me a new driver.

71
00:04:51,134 --> 00:04:54,534
<i>Being Joker's girl
gave me immunity.</i>

72
00:04:55,040 --> 00:04:58,908
<i>I could do whatever I wanted
to whoever I wanted,</i>

73
00:04:58,988 --> 00:05:02,325
<i>and no one
ever dared to object.</i>

74
00:05:15,092 --> 00:05:19,377
And don't let him give you shit, okay?
You have to stick up for yourself.

75
00:05:38,154 --> 00:05:41,845
Oh, please. I give it a few days
before they're back together.

76
00:05:41,925 --> 00:05:44,835
<i> Even when I did try and tell
people, they didn't believe me.</i>

77
00:05:44,915 --> 00:05:47,835
Come on. She told me they're
really broken up this time.

78
00:05:47,915 --> 00:05:51,471
Sure they are, Shell. That's why she's
still wearing that tacky "J" necklace.

79
00:05:52,977 --> 00:05:56,897
She is going to be running right back into
his arms the minute he snaps his fingers.

80
00:05:56,977 --> 00:05:59,981
If not him, the next closest
alpha male with a pulse.

81
00:06:00,061 --> 00:06:03,050
Some people just aren't
born to stand on their own.

82
00:06:03,131 --> 00:06:04,981
- Oh, girl, let's drink. Come on.
- All right.

83
00:06:05,061 --> 00:06:07,908
<i>I knew I needed to find
some way to show the world</i>

84
00:06:07,988 --> 00:06:10,981
<i>that I'd cut ties with Mr. J
for good.</i>

85
00:06:11,061 --> 00:06:13,061
Harley!

86
00:06:14,956 --> 00:06:17,608
<i>Some people have the
Eiffel Tower, or Olive Garden.</i>

87
00:06:17,665 --> 00:06:20,975
<i>The Joker and I?
Our love bloomed in a highly toxic</i>

88
00:06:21,216 --> 00:06:23,603
<i>industrial processing plant.</i>

89
00:06:29,936 --> 00:06:33,454
<i>And luckily for me,
I have all my best ideas drunk.</i>

90
00:06:33,547 --> 00:06:36,683
I have the best idea!

91
00:06:45,009 --> 00:06:48,492
The fuck?
Hey! Hey! Come back here!

92
00:06:58,967 --> 00:07:01,356
This is
where it all began, Puddin'.

93
00:07:02,123 --> 00:07:04,471
You motherfucker!

94
00:07:31,092 --> 00:07:33,544
<i>It was the closure I needed.</i>

95
00:07:33,936 --> 00:07:37,450
<i>A fresh start.
A chance to be my own woman.</i>

96
00:07:50,113 --> 00:07:54,009
<i>But I wasn't the only dame
in Gotham looking for emancipation.</i>

97
00:07:55,061 --> 00:07:58,315
<i>This is our story.</i>

98
00:07:59,988 --> 00:08:03,336
<i>And I'm telling it,
so I'll start where I fucking want.</i>

99
00:08:05,061 --> 00:08:07,981
<i>- Meet the cop.</i>
- I got 50 says it was turf war.

100
00:08:08,061 --> 00:08:10,939
<i>- Not him.</i>
- Well, as always, you're wrong, Munroe.

101
00:08:11,019 --> 00:08:13,213
<i>Her. Renee Montoya.</i>

102
00:08:13,294 --> 00:08:16,835
<i>Raised on '80s cop shows,
she's always saying cheesy shit like...</i>

103
00:08:16,915 --> 00:08:20,939
There was only one shooter.
Inside.

104
00:08:21,019 --> 00:08:23,960
This guy shot out the glass.
Serrano.

105
00:08:24,040 --> 00:08:26,040
Yo. Hey.

106
00:08:26,967 --> 00:08:29,012
Have Ballistics check for a bullet
in one of those parked cars.

107
00:08:29,092 --> 00:08:32,022
<i>Ten years ago, she broke
a career-making case.</i>

108
00:08:32,102 --> 00:08:33,970
- Did I stutter?
- Go ahead.

109
00:08:34,050 --> 00:08:36,887
<i>But her partner at the time
took all the credit.</i>

110
00:08:36,967 --> 00:08:40,544
So while he made captain, she got stuck
at detective level with this idiot.

111
00:08:40,936 --> 00:08:43,866
- Okay, you think one guy got all four?
- Wait, wait, wait.

112
00:08:43,946 --> 00:08:45,939
I'm just saying, we got four
dead bodies here, you know.

113
00:08:46,019 --> 00:08:48,054
- One guy... Bullet holes.
- I'm trying to work.

114
00:08:48,134 --> 00:08:51,388
I'm sorry.
Go ahead and work. Go ahead.

115
00:08:55,936 --> 00:08:58,918
The shooter got close
before drawing. Six rounds.

116
00:08:58,998 --> 00:09:01,949
- Two for each of these three.
- Yo, mind your debt.

117
00:09:02,029 --> 00:09:04,554
I'm telling you.
That girl, Angelina, she's a princess.

118
00:09:04,598 --> 00:09:08,026
- Look at this. Is it Halloween?
- Hey. How you doing?

119
00:09:19,071 --> 00:09:21,377
And it wasn't about them.

120
00:09:21,946 --> 00:09:25,325
It was all about this guy,
right here.

121
00:09:29,019 --> 00:09:31,346
Do you know who I am?

122
00:09:32,050 --> 00:09:34,346
You fucking bitch.

123
00:09:43,081 --> 00:09:46,325
And this arrow through his throat...

124
00:09:47,977 --> 00:09:50,012
She wanted him to die slowly.

125
00:09:50,092 --> 00:09:52,513
- She?
- We got a hair.

126
00:09:53,061 --> 00:09:57,022
- And he's got a new assassin.
- Who does?

127
00:09:57,102 --> 00:10:00,043
Roman Beauvais Sionis.

128
00:10:00,123 --> 00:10:02,970
Jesus Christ.

129
00:10:03,050 --> 00:10:05,429
This is Montoya.
What the hell was that?

130
00:10:07,061 --> 00:10:09,061
Shit.

131
00:10:09,936 --> 00:10:11,876
Wow.

132
00:10:11,956 --> 00:10:15,346
Detective.
Found this necklace.

133
00:10:17,050 --> 00:10:19,050
Holy shit.

134
00:10:19,946 --> 00:10:21,946
Good work, Officer.

135
00:10:22,050 --> 00:10:24,050
What is it?

136
00:10:25,144 --> 00:10:28,897
- Harley Quinn and the Joker broke up.
- What?

137
00:10:28,977 --> 00:10:33,074
This was their spot. She just publicly
updated her relationship status.

138
00:10:33,154 --> 00:10:37,908
Harley Quinn just called
open season on herself.

139
00:10:37,988 --> 00:10:39,845
She did not
think this one through.

140
00:10:39,925 --> 00:10:42,074
<i>Yeah, no shit
I didn't think it through.</i>

141
00:10:42,154 --> 00:10:46,064
<i>I'm about to learn that a lot of
people in this city want me dead.</i>

142
00:10:46,144 --> 00:10:50,346
<i>And at the top of that list
is this guy.</i>

143
00:10:51,009 --> 00:10:54,502
Mr. Keo and his lovely
wife and daughter.

144
00:10:55,019 --> 00:10:59,534
You kinda forced my hand here.
Gotta say, I'm a little disappointed.

145
00:11:02,977 --> 00:11:07,346
I gave you a great pitch.
Didn't I?

146
00:11:09,071 --> 00:11:11,071
And I thought... Shh!

147
00:11:11,998 --> 00:11:14,928
I thought we could build
something beautiful together.

148
00:11:15,008 --> 00:11:17,324
I thought we could be family.

149
00:11:30,153 --> 00:11:32,522
I'm gonna set you free.

150
00:11:33,955 --> 00:11:35,955
Mmm...

151
00:11:36,924 --> 00:11:40,522
What about her?

152
00:11:45,526 --> 00:11:47,290
I think we can let her go.

153
00:11:47,294 --> 00:11:50,407
I mean, this is a pretty loud
fucking shitshow of a message.

154
00:11:55,153 --> 00:11:58,032
Baby. Aww.

155
00:11:58,112 --> 00:12:00,324
Don't cry.

156
00:12:01,153 --> 00:12:04,543
Thank you.
Thank you.

157
00:12:04,935 --> 00:12:06,935
You're welcome.

158
00:12:08,007 --> 00:12:09,927
Is that a snot bubble?

159
00:12:10,007 --> 00:12:12,042
- Ew. Gross.
- What?

160
00:12:12,122 --> 00:12:14,512
Oh, I've changed my mind.
Peel it off.

161
00:12:15,018 --> 00:12:17,018
No. No!

162
00:12:18,945 --> 00:12:23,011
<i>The wack job with the penchant
for peeling faces is Roman Sionis,</i>

163
00:12:23,564 --> 00:12:26,480
<i>aka Black Mask.</i>

164
00:12:29,018 --> 00:12:32,896
<i>The fact that he wants me dead
hasn't yet hit my radar.</i>

165
00:12:32,976 --> 00:12:35,553
<i>See, I was halfway across town,</i>

166
00:12:35,945 --> 00:12:39,512
<i>hungover,
and thinking about breakfast.</i>

167
00:12:41,028 --> 00:12:45,491
<i>Egg, bacon, American cheese.</i>

168
00:12:46,620 --> 00:12:50,886
<i>Soft, toasted buttered roll.</i>

169
00:12:50,966 --> 00:12:53,042
<i>Just a dash of hot sauce.</i>

170
00:12:53,122 --> 00:12:57,000
Not too much, Sal.
I wanna taste the cheese.

171
00:12:57,080 --> 00:13:00,439
<i>What a way to
start my new life.</i>

172
00:13:01,091 --> 00:13:05,553
<i>With the perfect egg sandwich.</i>

173
00:13:06,060 --> 00:13:08,060
Mmm!

174
00:13:08,153 --> 00:13:10,501
You're a lifesaver, Sal.

175
00:13:12,935 --> 00:13:16,418
And I'm good for the 75 cents,
okay? I promise.

176
00:13:16,924 --> 00:13:21,418
That's all the money I got
in the world, and it's so worth it.

177
00:13:24,101 --> 00:13:27,073
<i>I don't know if it's
the stray Armenian arm hair,</i>

178
00:13:27,153 --> 00:13:30,959
or the fact that his cheese slices
are always six months out of date,

179
00:13:31,039 --> 00:13:34,896
but no one makes
an egg sandwich like Sal.

180
00:13:34,976 --> 00:13:37,366
I mean it, Sal. No one.

181
00:13:52,419 --> 00:13:54,473
Freeze! Gotham PD.

182
00:13:54,488 --> 00:13:57,257
<i>Yeah, I don't think so.</i>

183
00:13:57,524 --> 00:13:59,914
Are you fucking kidding me?

184
00:14:02,955 --> 00:14:04,980
Yo! Police.

185
00:14:05,060 --> 00:14:08,959
<i>It had been six short hours
since my little stunt at Ace Chemicals</i>

186
00:14:09,039 --> 00:14:13,021
<i>announced to the world
that Mr. J and I were dunzo.</i>

187
00:14:13,101 --> 00:14:17,439
<i>The immunity I'd enjoyed
for so long was gone.</i>

188
00:14:18,080 --> 00:14:20,896
<i>Cops who never would've dared
come after me before</i>

189
00:14:20,976 --> 00:14:23,345
<i>were suddenly doing this.</i>

190
00:14:29,657 --> 00:14:31,907
- Ooh!
- Freeze!

191
00:14:31,987 --> 00:14:35,553
<i>And what's worse? Every person
I ever wronged now felt free</i>

192
00:14:35,924 --> 00:14:37,924
<i>to come and
take their pound of flesh.</i>

193
00:14:54,101 --> 00:14:57,480
<i>Turns out
I wronged a lot of people.</i>

194
00:14:59,122 --> 00:15:02,397
Come on, boy. Get him!

195
00:15:03,132 --> 00:15:05,132
Oh...

196
00:15:19,091 --> 00:15:21,091
Finally.

197
00:15:30,007 --> 00:15:32,073
<i>- And then...</i>
- We're gonna get through this, okay?

198
00:15:32,153 --> 00:15:34,397
<i>...tragedy struck.</i>

199
00:15:44,966 --> 00:15:48,653
<i>It took losing
something I truly love</i>

200
00:15:48,669 --> 00:15:51,853
<i>for me to see that
the target on my back</i>

201
00:15:51,945 --> 00:15:53,945
<i>was bigger than I thought.</i>

202
00:15:54,675 --> 00:15:55,990
Freeze!

203
00:15:56,070 --> 00:15:58,612
<i>With the walls
closing in around me,</i>

204
00:15:58,679 --> 00:16:03,335
<i>I made a carefully calculated,
highly strategic move.</i>

205
00:16:11,132 --> 00:16:14,886
<i>Fine. It was dumb luck.
But still...</i>

206
00:16:14,966 --> 00:16:16,966
<i>That felt pretty great.</i>

207
00:16:19,143 --> 00:16:22,844
Sorry for busting in on you like that,
but thanks for the shortcut.

208
00:16:22,924 --> 00:16:26,063
- See ya. Oh!
- There she is.

209
00:16:26,143 --> 00:16:29,209
- Harley Quinn.
- Yeah?

210
00:16:30,070 --> 00:16:33,948
- I've waited a long time for this.
- You have?

211
00:16:34,028 --> 00:16:37,501
Oh... I haven't had breakfast yet.

212
00:16:38,914 --> 00:16:42,376
- What did I do to you?
- Are you serious?

213
00:16:43,060 --> 00:16:45,060
Look at my face.

214
00:16:45,143 --> 00:16:48,355
Look at my face!

215
00:16:54,007 --> 00:16:56,007
Oh...

216
00:16:56,955 --> 00:16:59,580
- That wasn't me.
- But you dared him to do it.

217
00:16:59,607 --> 00:17:02,242
Yeah, but I dare a lot of people
to do a lot of things, okay?

218
00:17:02,243 --> 00:17:05,021
- Come on. I'm not even with him anymore.
- I know.

219
00:17:05,101 --> 00:17:09,924
That means there's
no one here to stop me.

220
00:17:11,101 --> 00:17:12,955
- Right.
- You're gonna die, Quinn.

221
00:17:13,053 --> 00:17:15,135
Ooh. A penny.

222
00:17:20,018 --> 00:17:22,345
They're shooting arrows now?

223
00:17:32,059 --> 00:17:34,608
Ah, crap. Him, too?

224
00:17:45,039 --> 00:17:47,039
Parley?

225
00:17:49,143 --> 00:17:52,959
Fuck, Montoya, you smell
like a dead rat's asshole.

226
00:17:53,039 --> 00:17:55,496
- Not today, Simpson.
- Hey, it's Detective Montoya.

227
00:17:55,577 --> 00:17:58,927
Respect your elders.
I mean, your elderly.

228
00:17:59,007 --> 00:18:01,073
You're only a few years younger than me,
and you're still behind that desk.

229
00:18:01,153 --> 00:18:02,927
You wanna go there?

230
00:18:03,007 --> 00:18:04,959
Come on. Empty your pockets.
All of it.

231
00:18:05,039 --> 00:18:07,063
Cassandra Cain,
back already?

232
00:18:07,143 --> 00:18:10,543
Thought by now you'd figure
out how not to get caught.

233
00:18:12,018 --> 00:18:14,018
What? No comeback?

234
00:18:16,976 --> 00:18:18,976
You all right?

235
00:18:19,132 --> 00:18:21,418
You smell like shit.

236
00:18:23,955 --> 00:18:25,955
Yo, Simpson.

237
00:18:26,048 --> 00:18:28,469
Any clean clothes
in lost and found?

238
00:18:30,933 --> 00:18:34,448
These are serious accusations,
Miss Montoya.

239
00:18:34,933 --> 00:18:37,968
The Sionis family name is on half
the museums and schools in Gotham.

240
00:18:38,048 --> 00:18:40,542
And that makes him
immune to the law, Captain?

241
00:18:40,933 --> 00:18:44,020
<i>Montoya's day is going
almost as badly as mine.</i>

242
00:18:44,100 --> 00:18:46,542
Remember the guy
who stole her promotion?

243
00:18:46,913 --> 00:18:49,937
That's him. He had four people
killed alone last night.

244
00:18:50,017 --> 00:18:53,958
If Sionis is such a mastermind, how'd he
get fired from his own fucking company?

245
00:18:54,038 --> 00:18:56,968
The Janus Corporation
is his father's company, thank you.

246
00:18:57,048 --> 00:18:59,062
And by the way,
they cut him off.

247
00:18:59,142 --> 00:19:01,958
Where does the DA's office
stand on all this?

248
00:19:02,038 --> 00:19:05,010
To make matters worse, the assistant DA?
That's her ex.

249
00:19:05,090 --> 00:19:07,552
The evidence that Sionis is
linked to these murders...

250
00:19:07,944 --> 00:19:09,970
There's a shipment coming in.

251
00:19:10,051 --> 00:19:12,010
- Drugs?
- A diamond.

252
00:19:12,090 --> 00:19:14,241
Wow, Montoya. Should we call
the Feds for backup?

253
00:19:14,308 --> 00:19:16,542
Listen,
I had a source at the club.

254
00:19:16,577 --> 00:19:19,906
His driver. He said that Roman
couldn't stop talking about this thing.

255
00:19:19,986 --> 00:19:22,010
And he said that he overheard
something about laser-encoding.

256
00:19:22,090 --> 00:19:26,062
Now, I did some research.
I think it's the Bertinelli diamond.

257
00:19:26,142 --> 00:19:28,999
You remember the Bertinelli
massacre, right?

258
00:19:29,079 --> 00:19:32,853
<i>Quick history lesson. Fifteen years
ago, one of the wealthiest</i>

259
00:19:32,933 --> 00:19:35,041
<i>Mafia families in Gotham
was gunned down.</i>

260
00:19:35,121 --> 00:19:37,947
<i>It was a power grab,
but the real target</i>

261
00:19:38,027 --> 00:19:42,231
<i>was the Bertinellis' super-secret
offshore bank accounts,</i>

262
00:19:42,236 --> 00:19:45,372
<i>the details of which were said
to be encoded in the atomic structure</i>

263
00:19:45,453 --> 00:19:49,874
<i>of a 30-carat diamond.
The rock was lost.</i>

264
00:19:49,954 --> 00:19:52,947
<i>And with it, the only key
to the Bertinelli fortune.</i>

265
00:19:53,027 --> 00:19:57,542
Which is exactly why Roman Sionis
is trying to get his hands on it.

266
00:19:57,975 --> 00:20:01,051
That's what makes him so dangerous.
He's already building an army.

267
00:20:01,131 --> 00:20:04,031
If he gets the diamond, he'll
have all the money and connections

268
00:20:04,111 --> 00:20:08,885
to bribe every single judge and cop
he needs to get a monopoly on the city.

269
00:20:08,965 --> 00:20:13,552
- You said you had someone on the inside?
- Yes. He's...

270
00:20:14,121 --> 00:20:17,864
- He's no longer there, but...
- So basically, you have nothing.

271
00:20:17,944 --> 00:20:19,937
You are trying to go after

272
00:20:20,017 --> 00:20:22,895
one of the most litigious and
wealthiest families in Gotham,

273
00:20:22,975 --> 00:20:24,926
and all you've got is
rumors and a hunch?

274
00:20:25,006 --> 00:20:28,926
Well, you know, the DA's office
is building a case against him, too.

275
00:20:29,006 --> 00:20:32,041
- Isn't that right, Miss Yee?
- If the DA is willing to throw himself

276
00:20:32,121 --> 00:20:36,020
- out in front of this, it's fine with me.
- Captain, no.

277
00:20:36,100 --> 00:20:40,552
Listen, Munroe, find me some tangible
connection to Sionis, all right?

278
00:20:40,944 --> 00:20:42,895
- Yes, sir.
- Wait, wait, wait. Captain.

279
00:20:42,975 --> 00:20:45,989
This is my case, okay? I've been
working on this for six months.

280
00:20:46,069 --> 00:20:50,386
We need something that we
can actually use, Detective.

281
00:20:50,965 --> 00:20:52,965
And, Miss Montoya,
we do have a dress code.

282
00:20:56,710 --> 00:20:58,875
Look, I'm sorry about
that, but I...

283
00:20:58,955 --> 00:21:01,937
That is my job you are fucking with.
What is wrong with you, Renee?

284
00:21:02,017 --> 00:21:04,506
- Me? He gave my case away.
- Oh, poor Renee.

285
00:21:04,551 --> 00:21:06,875
Why don't you pour yourself
a drink? It's almost noon.

286
00:21:06,955 --> 00:21:08,955
Wow.

287
00:21:10,965 --> 00:21:13,875
Jesus. Who the fuck is this?
What?

288
00:21:13,955 --> 00:21:16,885
<i>Why the fuck haven't you been picking
up your phone? We've got a situation.</i>

289
00:21:16,965 --> 00:21:19,864
- What... What situation?
- You didn't hear this from me,

290
00:21:19,944 --> 00:21:21,927
but you gotta find her
before someone else does.

291
00:21:22,007 --> 00:21:24,020
She's got the diamond, and
trust me, Roman will kill her.

292
00:21:24,100 --> 00:21:26,968
- My diamond? Who? Who's got it?
- This kid.

293
00:21:27,048 --> 00:21:30,000
She's a pickpocket.
Her name's Cassandra Cain.

294
00:21:30,080 --> 00:21:32,459
Holy fuck.

295
00:21:42,975 --> 00:21:45,072
- Can I help you?
- Why, yes. Yes, you can.

296
00:21:45,152 --> 00:21:48,323
I'm here to
report a terrible crime.

297
00:21:49,132 --> 00:21:51,542
And what terrible crime is that?

298
00:21:53,996 --> 00:21:55,996
This one.

299
00:22:12,142 --> 00:22:14,344
Hi, boys.

300
00:22:18,996 --> 00:22:20,996
Meeting's over.

301
00:23:18,944 --> 00:23:21,334
Run, piggy, run.

302
00:23:29,027 --> 00:23:31,027
Where can I find
Cassandra Cain?

303
00:23:32,566 --> 00:23:36,895
<i> Hold up, hold up. I'm telling
this all wrong. Let's rewind.</i>

304
00:23:36,975 --> 00:23:39,968
<i>For you to understand why me,
the cop, and that dame on the toilet...</i>

305
00:23:40,048 --> 00:23:41,041
Her name's Cassandra Cain.

306
00:23:41,121 --> 00:23:43,979
<i>...are all looking for
this Cain character.</i>

307
00:23:44,059 --> 00:23:46,480
<i>I gotta take you back
a few days,</i>

308
00:23:47,007 --> 00:23:50,438
<i>to that night I got shitfaced
at the Black Mask Club.</i>

309
00:23:52,975 --> 00:23:58,355
<i>This is a man's world</i>

310
00:24:00,121 --> 00:24:05,521
<i>This is a man's world...</i>

311
00:24:05,913 --> 00:24:09,521
<i>- This is Dinah Lance.</i>
- But it would be nothing

312
00:24:09,913 --> 00:24:14,521
<i>- But she prefers Black Canary.
- Nothing...</i>

313
00:24:14,608 --> 00:24:18,895
<i>- She's got a killer voice.
- Without a woman or a girl...</i>

314
00:24:18,975 --> 00:24:21,031
<i>But there was some other shit
going down that night.</i>

315
00:24:21,111 --> 00:24:22,916
...short notice like this.

316
00:24:22,996 --> 00:24:25,020
I'm not talking
superficial partnerships.

317
00:24:25,100 --> 00:24:29,511
I'm talking you and me
having each other's backs.

318
00:24:29,590 --> 00:24:33,052
The Golden Lions can't just
wander into Gotham National Bank.

319
00:24:33,132 --> 00:24:37,521
I can.
Loans, liquidity, laundering.

320
00:24:37,934 --> 00:24:40,875
Look, if you bring your boys
into the fold,

321
00:24:40,955 --> 00:24:43,968
there are no limits to what
we could achieve together.

322
00:24:44,048 --> 00:24:47,020
I'm building something special.

323
00:24:47,100 --> 00:24:49,916
I appreciate your offer,
Mr. Sionis.

324
00:24:49,996 --> 00:24:52,989
But with all due respect,

325
00:24:53,069 --> 00:24:55,459
the Golden Lions
are a family business.

326
00:24:55,934 --> 00:24:58,968
Fuck family. All due respect,
but fuck that.

327
00:24:59,048 --> 00:25:02,937
Family's a fucking illusion. You know
what my family gave me? Nothing.

328
00:25:03,017 --> 00:25:06,041
I know what everyone says.
"Here comes Roman Sionis.

329
00:25:06,121 --> 00:25:08,542
"He was handed life
on a silver spoon."

330
00:25:08,934 --> 00:25:10,875
"Gin and tonics at 5:00."
"I'll have the duck."

331
00:25:10,955 --> 00:25:13,490
Blah, blah, blah.
Fake fucking fucks.

332
00:25:15,027 --> 00:25:17,542
But look at me now.

333
00:25:17,934 --> 00:25:21,989
I've located the Bertinelli diamond.
I'm about to own this city.

334
00:25:22,069 --> 00:25:25,958
Not just the East End.
I am thinking big, baby.

335
00:25:26,038 --> 00:25:30,979
And I want you there with me.
We could make our own family.

336
00:25:31,059 --> 00:25:33,885
Mr. Sionis,
the Golden Lions have operated

337
00:25:33,965 --> 00:25:35,965
in Gotham
for nearly 100 years.

338
00:25:37,099 --> 00:25:39,520
We have no need
of your protection.

339
00:25:40,006 --> 00:25:42,468
He's gonna regret that.

340
00:25:50,985 --> 00:25:53,061
Will you sleep on it?
Will you do that for me?

341
00:25:53,141 --> 00:25:54,988
Run it by
that beautiful wife of yours,

342
00:25:55,068 --> 00:25:57,874
and I'll come see you at
the docks, day after tomorrow.

343
00:25:57,954 --> 00:25:59,954
Okay?

344
00:26:05,964 --> 00:26:10,051
<i>This is a man's world</i>

345
00:26:10,131 --> 00:26:12,853
<i>It would be nothing</i>

346
00:26:12,933 --> 00:26:14,933
<i>Without a woman or a girl...</i>

347
00:26:16,016 --> 00:26:18,894
Who's having a good time?
You are.

348
00:26:18,974 --> 00:26:21,894
<i>- Lost in the wilderness...</i>
- Food is good?

349
00:26:21,974 --> 00:26:24,999
- Do you need any more cocktails?
<i>- Lost in the bitterness...</i>

350
00:26:25,079 --> 00:26:29,468
- Your good health.
<i>- He's lost in the loneliness...</i>

351
00:26:30,131 --> 00:26:32,926
<i>He's lost</i>

352
00:26:33,006 --> 00:26:36,479
<i>This is a man's world</i>

353
00:26:36,954 --> 00:26:39,551
<i>It wouldn't be nothing</i>

354
00:26:48,995 --> 00:26:53,322
<i>Without a woman or a girl</i>

355
00:26:55,141 --> 00:26:57,988
<i>Canary's been singing
at Roman's club for years.</i>

356
00:26:58,068 --> 00:27:00,988
- Come on!
<i>- He calls her his little bird,</i>

357
00:27:01,068 --> 00:27:05,395
<i>and he's got her wrapped
right around his fancy little finger.</i>

358
00:27:10,026 --> 00:27:13,089
- Here you go, Canary.
- Thank you.

359
00:27:13,953 --> 00:27:16,510
How do you spell "mercenary"?

360
00:27:17,089 --> 00:27:19,322
Merceninny...

361
00:27:20,006 --> 00:27:22,006
Merceran?

362
00:27:27,985 --> 00:27:30,040
Singer lady woman!

363
00:27:30,120 --> 00:27:32,978
You're really, really good.

364
00:27:33,058 --> 00:27:35,058
Yeah.

365
00:27:40,078 --> 00:27:42,551
Know what a harlequin is?

366
00:27:44,943 --> 00:27:47,071
Janky-ass clown
with bad eye makeup?

367
00:27:47,151 --> 00:27:49,030
Oof!

368
00:27:49,110 --> 00:27:51,353
Ouch!

369
00:27:54,110 --> 00:27:57,333
A harlequin's role

370
00:27:58,026 --> 00:28:00,374
is to serve.

371
00:28:00,912 --> 00:28:02,884
An audience.

372
00:28:02,964 --> 00:28:05,343
A master.

373
00:28:07,151 --> 00:28:11,322
You know, a harlequin's
nothing without a master.

374
00:28:12,985 --> 00:28:17,551
And no one gives two fucks
who we are beyond that.

375
00:28:26,131 --> 00:28:30,099
Yeah, I don't know who you think
I am, lady, but I'm not her.

376
00:28:32,047 --> 00:28:34,406
Puddin' and I broke up.

377
00:28:41,120 --> 00:28:44,343
I haven't told that to anyone.

378
00:28:45,068 --> 00:28:47,019
Yeah.

379
00:28:47,099 --> 00:28:49,426
For good this time.

380
00:28:50,995 --> 00:28:54,520
And for the first time
in a long time,

381
00:28:55,953 --> 00:28:58,374
I'm all on my lonesome.

382
00:29:02,912 --> 00:29:04,912
It's great.

383
00:29:07,151 --> 00:29:09,468
Welcome to the club.

384
00:29:10,141 --> 00:29:12,019
Thanks.

385
00:29:12,099 --> 00:29:16,030
Hey, don't be lonesome.
How about another drink?

386
00:29:16,110 --> 00:29:17,988
- Yes!
- Yeah?

387
00:29:18,068 --> 00:29:19,873
- Yeah.
- It's on me.

388
00:29:19,953 --> 00:29:22,416
- Sure. Drinks!
- Hey, two shots.

389
00:29:25,047 --> 00:29:27,047
Hey.

390
00:29:36,078 --> 00:29:38,520
We're all good here.

391
00:29:51,912 --> 00:29:53,998
- I don't wanna go home.
- Oh, no? No.

392
00:29:54,078 --> 00:29:56,343
No.

393
00:29:57,943 --> 00:30:00,009
Let me know
if you're gonna get sick.

394
00:30:00,089 --> 00:30:02,946
Your chariot's arrived.
Oh, there you go.

395
00:30:03,026 --> 00:30:05,946
- Are we getting breakfast?
- Hey, buddy, I'm gonna need some help.

396
00:30:06,026 --> 00:30:08,884
This is my friend.
I told you all about...

397
00:30:08,964 --> 00:30:12,468
- Hey, get the door, man. There we go.
- Wait.

398
00:30:13,068 --> 00:30:15,853
- Isn't that Joker's girl?
- Not anymore.

399
00:30:15,933 --> 00:30:18,946
- Got room for one more?
- Hey.

400
00:30:19,026 --> 00:30:21,026
Huh?

401
00:30:23,078 --> 00:30:26,458
I don't need your help.
I got this.

402
00:30:27,006 --> 00:30:29,416
You got this?
You sure about that?

403
00:30:29,943 --> 00:30:31,943
Yeah, no wonder
everyone hates you.

404
00:30:34,974 --> 00:30:37,333
Uh...

405
00:30:46,985 --> 00:30:48,985
You got this!

406
00:30:49,922 --> 00:30:52,385
You motherfucker!

407
00:30:53,995 --> 00:30:55,995
Whoo!

408
00:30:58,964 --> 00:31:01,510
Well, well, well,
well, well, well.

409
00:31:02,047 --> 00:31:05,030
Could that be
our little Miss Lance?

410
00:31:05,110 --> 00:31:07,855
All these years,
I thought she was just a pretty face

411
00:31:07,936 --> 00:31:10,324
and a fine set of lungs.

412
00:31:11,026 --> 00:31:12,946
Ooh.

413
00:31:13,026 --> 00:31:17,489
Mr. Zsasz,
I've had an amazing idea.

414
00:31:25,099 --> 00:31:27,447
That's my little bird.

415
00:31:30,047 --> 00:31:33,520
Don't touch
what you can't afford, mister.

416
00:31:33,964 --> 00:31:35,964
Shut up.

417
00:31:36,953 --> 00:31:39,458
Oh, songbird.

418
00:31:40,026 --> 00:31:42,395
You drive
as good as you fight?

419
00:31:44,933 --> 00:31:47,915
- Who's asking?
- The boss.

420
00:31:47,995 --> 00:31:49,995
You're getting promoted.

421
00:31:52,151 --> 00:31:54,935
- You're his new driver.
- Huh. Thanks,

422
00:31:55,016 --> 00:31:57,946
but I think I'm good
with the singing gig.

423
00:31:58,026 --> 00:32:00,385
You'll be good
at the driving gig.

424
00:32:01,058 --> 00:32:05,061
Be here tomorrow.
9:00 a.m. Sharp.

425
00:32:05,141 --> 00:32:07,957
<i>So, that's how Canary
got herself a job</i>

426
00:32:08,037 --> 00:32:10,520
<i>driving around
Gotham's newest Godfather.</i>

427
00:32:11,089 --> 00:32:14,040
<i>A position, I might add,
that wouldn't have been vacant</i>

428
00:32:14,120 --> 00:32:17,406
<i>without the help of yours truly.</i>

429
00:32:24,110 --> 00:32:26,110
Morning.

430
00:32:36,477 --> 00:32:40,426
- You're the one who wanted the kid!
- I never wanted her!

431
00:32:42,131 --> 00:32:44,426
Let me guess. Parents?

432
00:32:44,995 --> 00:32:47,987
- Foster parents.
- Right.

433
00:32:48,067 --> 00:32:50,018
Sorry, kid.

434
00:32:50,098 --> 00:32:52,529
Sorry about your face.

435
00:32:53,036 --> 00:32:55,862
Shit, you do have something
on your face.

436
00:32:55,942 --> 00:32:59,404
You should've seen
the other guy.

437
00:33:01,140 --> 00:33:03,008
Uh...

438
00:33:03,088 --> 00:33:05,862
I want that kid out
of my fucking house!

439
00:33:05,942 --> 00:33:08,425
You know, kid, not every day
is gonna be like this.

440
00:33:09,036 --> 00:33:11,425
You just gotta hang in there.

441
00:33:17,077 --> 00:33:19,342
Get something to eat.

442
00:33:20,150 --> 00:33:23,415
Stay outta that.
It's not worth it.

443
00:33:32,015 --> 00:33:34,015
Don't talk to me like that.

444
00:33:36,098 --> 00:33:37,872
<i>Canary spends the next week</i>

445
00:33:37,952 --> 00:33:41,488
<i>settling in to her new job
as Roman's personal driver.</i>

446
00:33:50,129 --> 00:33:52,018
Ew. Okay.

447
00:33:52,098 --> 00:33:55,060
<i>What she didn't know is that
driving Mr. Face-peely-pants</i>

448
00:33:55,140 --> 00:33:57,914
<i>was gonna put her
right in the crosshairs</i>

449
00:33:57,994 --> 00:34:00,467
<i>of my favorite little piggy.</i>

450
00:34:01,036 --> 00:34:03,862
- Dinah Lance?
- Who the hell are you?

451
00:34:03,942 --> 00:34:07,404
I'm Renee Montoya,
detective with GCPD.

452
00:34:09,932 --> 00:34:13,457
Your predecessor
and I had an arrangement.

453
00:34:13,911 --> 00:34:14,987
Oh, really?

454
00:34:15,067 --> 00:34:19,425
He told me that there was a
shipment coming in. A diamond.

455
00:34:19,911 --> 00:34:21,911
A very special diamond.

456
00:34:23,015 --> 00:34:26,394
Yeah, not interested, lady.
Thanks for the coffee.

457
00:34:28,015 --> 00:34:30,015
Do you know
who you're working for?

458
00:34:30,140 --> 00:34:33,956
Damn right, I do. He's the man who
gave me a job. Took me off the streets.

459
00:34:34,036 --> 00:34:36,914
Yeah, well, he's also
a very dangerous man.

460
00:34:36,994 --> 00:34:39,872
A criminal. A murderer.

461
00:34:39,952 --> 00:34:42,973
What would your mother think of you
working for a guy like that, huh?

462
00:34:43,088 --> 00:34:47,060
You have the same power she had. Don't
you think she would want you to use it?

463
00:34:47,140 --> 00:34:49,039
The hell do you know
about my mother?

464
00:34:49,119 --> 00:34:52,070
Back in the day,
she used to help the GCPD.

465
00:34:52,150 --> 00:34:54,529
- She was a good woman.
- Yeah.

466
00:34:55,046 --> 00:34:57,049
She was a damn good woman.

467
00:34:57,129 --> 00:35:01,311
The kind of woman who put
everyone else's lives before her own.

468
00:35:01,921 --> 00:35:04,018
And when she was found
dead in the street,

469
00:35:04,098 --> 00:35:07,519
where the fuck were you
and your boys in blue then?

470
00:35:08,140 --> 00:35:12,049
Now you wanna come and knock on
my door and ask me to help you out

471
00:35:12,129 --> 00:35:14,509
and make
the same mistake she did?

472
00:35:16,088 --> 00:35:19,404
Yeah. Good luck with that.

473
00:35:20,129 --> 00:35:24,498
That's fair enough.
And I'm sorry for your loss.

474
00:35:25,952 --> 00:35:27,952
For the record,

475
00:35:28,088 --> 00:35:31,550
that would never happen
on my watch.

476
00:35:34,078 --> 00:35:36,530
The Sprang Bridge
Soldiers capituated.

477
00:35:36,994 --> 00:35:39,509
"Capitulated."
Of course they did.

478
00:35:39,901 --> 00:35:42,332
I told you that Keo scene
would send a message.

479
00:35:43,036 --> 00:35:46,925
It sure did, boss.
It sure fucking did.

480
00:35:47,005 --> 00:35:49,478
Crossbow Killer

481
00:35:50,098 --> 00:35:54,039
struck again last night.
Rossi and four of his guys.

482
00:35:54,119 --> 00:35:57,039
People don't kill people I own
without my permission.

483
00:35:57,119 --> 00:35:59,039
Why doesn't this crossbow guy
know that?

484
00:35:59,119 --> 00:36:00,946
- You know that!
- I know it.

485
00:36:01,026 --> 00:36:03,977
Why doesn't this crossbow guy?
Why don't I own the crossbow guy?

486
00:36:04,057 --> 00:36:06,498
- You should own him.
- I mean, I like crossbows.

487
00:36:07,098 --> 00:36:09,039
Oh, good morning.
Good morning.

488
00:36:09,119 --> 00:36:10,998
- Morning.
- Come in. Come in.

489
00:36:11,078 --> 00:36:13,904
We're just finishing up a
little business. Look around.

490
00:36:13,984 --> 00:36:15,935
- You're late.
- It's fine.

491
00:36:16,015 --> 00:36:17,925
Should she come back another
time, 'cause she's late?

492
00:36:18,005 --> 00:36:20,363
No. Isn't this stunning?

493
00:36:21,911 --> 00:36:24,550
That is a Chokwe mask.

494
00:36:25,067 --> 00:36:27,956
I got it when I was embedded
with the Mbangani tribe

495
00:36:28,036 --> 00:36:29,998
in Congo-Kinshasa.
Have you ever been?

496
00:36:30,078 --> 00:36:32,831
I've never been.
I've heard it's beautiful.

497
00:36:32,911 --> 00:36:38,039
It's dirty. Here, look at this.
Genuine tsantsa or shrunken head.

498
00:36:38,119 --> 00:36:41,852
Shuar of Ecuador. They're
amazing people. Surprisingly gentle.

499
00:36:41,932 --> 00:36:43,873
- I think you might like them.
- Really?

500
00:36:43,953 --> 00:36:47,914
They boil the heads of their enemies
and they make these little fellas.

501
00:36:47,994 --> 00:36:49,883
- Exquisite, aren't they? Look.
- Mmm-hmm.

502
00:36:49,963 --> 00:36:52,956
Look at those little ears.
And his little haircut.

503
00:36:53,036 --> 00:36:54,945
- Yeah, he's 1,000 years old.
- Wow.

504
00:36:55,025 --> 00:36:56,893
And now he's just an ornament
in my living room.

505
00:36:56,973 --> 00:36:58,945
- Ew! I love it.
- Yeah?

506
00:36:59,025 --> 00:37:00,893
These are
ancient acupuncture models.

507
00:37:00,973 --> 00:37:03,070
As you can see, they have
all the acupuncture points.

508
00:37:03,150 --> 00:37:06,550
And we found these
buried in the mountains.

509
00:37:06,942 --> 00:37:09,883
Ace Chemicals
got blown sky high last night.

510
00:37:09,963 --> 00:37:13,373
All right, all right, let's find
the Crossbow Killer. I get it.

511
00:37:13,932 --> 00:37:16,987
- Is he an acupuncture model, too?
- He is not an acupuncture model.

512
00:37:17,067 --> 00:37:20,060
This is a statue of me. It was made
by a very famous Gotham artist...

513
00:37:20,140 --> 00:37:22,457
Harley Quinn did it.

514
00:37:23,067 --> 00:37:25,530
Some kind of "fuck you"
to the Joker.

515
00:37:26,046 --> 00:37:28,046
They split.

516
00:37:28,150 --> 00:37:30,478
What's wrong with you, Victor?

517
00:37:31,036 --> 00:37:33,998
- Talk about burying the lede.
- Yeah.

518
00:37:34,078 --> 00:37:36,550
This is spectacular news!

519
00:37:37,088 --> 00:37:39,530
She doesn't belong to him,
she belongs to me.

520
00:37:39,921 --> 00:37:42,977
Have the boys go find her. Round her up,
bring her back. I want her.

521
00:37:43,057 --> 00:37:44,987
You, I have something
I want you to pick me up.

522
00:37:45,067 --> 00:37:47,530
Something super-duper
important, okay?

523
00:37:47,554 --> 00:37:49,790
- I'll go with you.
- Yeah, go with Victor.

524
00:37:49,871 --> 00:37:52,050
- It's just a pickup.
- No, he's harmless.

525
00:37:52,130 --> 00:37:54,478
Do as you're told. Go.

526
00:38:08,994 --> 00:38:11,998
- All right. We can go.
- I'll take that.

527
00:38:12,078 --> 00:38:15,953
- Mr. S said for me to hold on to it.
- Go get your car.

528
00:38:17,963 --> 00:38:21,050
<i>That rock. That rock's
about to become the key</i>

529
00:38:21,130 --> 00:38:25,394
<i>to whether or not I live to
enjoy my newfound independence.</i>

530
00:38:28,942 --> 00:38:31,883
- Get off me.
- What the hell are you doing here?

531
00:38:31,963 --> 00:38:35,369
You're not the only one who makes
money off of dumb, rich, white people.

532
00:38:35,450 --> 00:38:38,925
Well, you know what? One day you're
gonna pick the wrong pocket, sis.

533
00:38:39,005 --> 00:38:41,436
Okay. Whatever.

534
00:38:44,046 --> 00:38:46,425
Dumb-ass kids.

535
00:38:48,025 --> 00:38:50,353
Excuse me. Sorry.

536
00:38:59,984 --> 00:39:03,446
- I really like your earrings.
- Why, thank you.

537
00:39:04,994 --> 00:39:07,321
There's the thief.
There's the thief.

538
00:39:09,109 --> 00:39:12,998
- Get off of me!
- That little girl took my watch.

539
00:39:13,078 --> 00:39:15,394
I didn't do nothing.

540
00:39:17,942 --> 00:39:20,925
Where the fuck's the diamond?
I just fucking had it.

541
00:39:21,005 --> 00:39:23,005
Cass!

542
00:39:24,140 --> 00:39:25,862
Wait!

543
00:39:25,942 --> 00:39:27,942
Wait, wait!

544
00:39:28,140 --> 00:39:29,904
Halt!

545
00:39:29,984 --> 00:39:31,984
Fuck!

546
00:39:51,109 --> 00:39:56,018
<i>In the storytelling business,
this dummy swallowing that diamond</i>

547
00:39:56,098 --> 00:39:59,086
<i>is called a complication.</i>

548
00:40:00,035 --> 00:40:04,320
<i>A complication I didn't
exactly need right now.</i>

549
00:40:06,920 --> 00:40:08,920
Parley?

550
00:40:11,014 --> 00:40:13,997
- We lost the diamond.
- What?

551
00:40:14,077 --> 00:40:15,965
We're really sorry, Mr. S.
This kid...

552
00:40:16,045 --> 00:40:18,477
We never even
got our hands on it.

553
00:40:19,931 --> 00:40:21,861
Ow!

554
00:40:21,941 --> 00:40:23,913
Help!

555
00:40:23,993 --> 00:40:27,114
Get out! Get out of here!
You, too! Go!

556
00:40:27,195 --> 00:40:30,477
With your fucking sage
stinking my place up. Fuck off!

557
00:40:30,910 --> 00:40:33,069
- Here she is.
- She's a child!

558
00:40:33,149 --> 00:40:35,882
- She's just a kid.
- She's... What?

559
00:40:35,962 --> 00:40:37,986
We have Harley Quinn
downstairs, as requested.

560
00:40:38,066 --> 00:40:41,007
Fuck off! Get out.
Fucking out!

561
00:40:41,087 --> 00:40:44,840
Fuck! These are my things.
This diamond is my things.

562
00:40:44,920 --> 00:40:47,944
My things! Fucking fuck!
I don't ask for much, do I?

563
00:40:48,024 --> 00:40:49,861
- No.
- Why is this happening to me?

564
00:40:49,941 --> 00:40:51,941
Why?

565
00:40:52,910 --> 00:40:56,976
I'm gonna get your diamond back.
I promise.

566
00:40:57,056 --> 00:41:02,404
Why don't we go downstairs
and kill that Harley bitch?

567
00:41:03,118 --> 00:41:05,477
Blow off a little steam.

568
00:41:05,993 --> 00:41:08,549
Yeah, I have wanted to do that
for quite some time.

569
00:41:10,139 --> 00:41:13,435
Okay. I'll go get changed.

570
00:41:28,129 --> 00:41:30,414
Shit, Cass.

571
00:41:35,097 --> 00:41:38,518
I don't care what it
takes, I want my diamond back.

572
00:41:38,910 --> 00:41:40,944
We're working on it.

573
00:41:41,024 --> 00:41:44,310
Now, let's go have a little fun.

574
00:41:48,910 --> 00:41:53,069
Harleen Quinzel.

575
00:41:53,149 --> 00:41:55,149
Whoo!

576
00:41:56,024 --> 00:41:58,024
Hiya, Romy.

577
00:41:58,941 --> 00:42:00,996
Do you know why you're here?
Hmm?

578
00:42:01,076 --> 00:42:02,986
<i>When it comes to
me and Roman Sionis,</i>

579
00:42:03,066 --> 00:42:05,476
<i>there are a lot of possible
answers to this question.</i>

580
00:42:05,962 --> 00:42:08,871
<i>Breaking his driver's legs. There's
that time I called it an "expresso."</i>

581
00:42:08,951 --> 00:42:11,414
<i>Having a vagina in the first
place pisses this guy off.</i>

582
00:42:15,129 --> 00:42:17,996
<i>Constantly interrupting him,
like I'm doing right now.</i>

583
00:42:18,076 --> 00:42:20,329
- You're here because...
- Oh, God, stop.

584
00:42:20,427 --> 00:42:24,059
You're gonna do that thing where you open
up a weird-ass case of torture devices

585
00:42:24,139 --> 00:42:28,028
while inexplicably detailing your
master plan and how I don't fit into it.

586
00:42:28,108 --> 00:42:31,038
- I'm building a better...
- Seriously, you don't have to. Really!

587
00:42:31,118 --> 00:42:34,338
You're building a criminal empire because
Daddy kicked you out of Janus Corp.

588
00:42:34,375 --> 00:42:36,007
And you think this is a big
"fuck you," but in actuality

589
00:42:36,087 --> 00:42:37,996
it's a very misguided attempt
to win back his respect.

590
00:42:38,076 --> 00:42:41,871
I get it. You're really not
as complicated as you think.

591
00:42:41,951 --> 00:42:43,892
And you're really not as
clever as you think, because

592
00:42:43,972 --> 00:42:45,944
- now I'm gonna slice your...
- Oh, Jesus Christmas.

593
00:42:46,024 --> 00:42:49,089
Now you're gonna say that you
wanna kill me to set an example.

594
00:42:49,170 --> 00:42:52,459
- Christ, you're boring.
- I wanna kill you...

595
00:42:52,540 --> 00:42:55,435
- Shit.
- ...because without the Joker around,

596
00:42:56,951 --> 00:42:58,951
I can.

597
00:43:01,097 --> 00:43:05,903
For all your noise and bluster,
you're just a silly little girl

598
00:43:05,983 --> 00:43:08,642
with no one around
to protect her.

599
00:43:12,527 --> 00:43:14,228
- Whoa. Wait.
- What?

600
00:43:14,315 --> 00:43:15,965
- Don't kill me.
- Ha! Right.

601
00:43:16,045 --> 00:43:19,861
No, no, no. Seriously. Romy, Roman.
Come on. There's gotta be something,

602
00:43:19,941 --> 00:43:21,941
something we can figure out.
Hey!

603
00:43:22,056 --> 00:43:24,059
Wait, wait!
You lost something, right?

604
00:43:24,139 --> 00:43:28,004
You lost something.
I heard you say it. A diamond.

605
00:43:32,910 --> 00:43:34,910
Yeah.

606
00:43:35,056 --> 00:43:37,049
I can help you find it.

607
00:43:37,129 --> 00:43:40,518
Seriously. Look in my pocket.

608
00:43:43,910 --> 00:43:45,910
Other pocket.

609
00:43:54,045 --> 00:43:55,965
I'm starting up
my own business.

610
00:43:56,045 --> 00:43:58,045
See what it says?
Second from the bottom.

611
00:44:02,004 --> 00:44:04,424
I know the East End
better than anybody.

612
00:44:05,035 --> 00:44:07,965
You want this diamond back?
I'm your gal.

613
00:44:08,045 --> 00:44:11,840
Mr. J once lost a rare photograph
of a nude Eleanor Roosevelt,

614
00:44:11,920 --> 00:44:13,955
and I found it in a bird's
nest in Robinson Park.

615
00:44:14,035 --> 00:44:16,017
If you let me go,

616
00:44:16,097 --> 00:44:20,017
just for now,
I'll get you that rock back.

617
00:44:20,097 --> 00:44:22,518
What have you got to lose?
If your boys find it first,

618
00:44:22,910 --> 00:44:24,459
swear to God,
you can kill me later.

619
00:44:24,551 --> 00:44:26,955
Pinky swear.
Cross my heart, hope to fart.

620
00:44:27,035 --> 00:44:29,035
You're so tiresome!

621
00:44:30,024 --> 00:44:35,017
If you want my mercy, shut that hole
in the middle of your face and listen.

622
00:44:35,097 --> 00:44:38,383
You're gonna
get me my diamond.

623
00:44:44,004 --> 00:44:48,903
<i>A kiss on the hand
May be quite continental</i>

624
00:44:48,983 --> 00:44:52,539
<i>But diamonds are
a girl's best friend</i>

625
00:44:53,931 --> 00:44:56,059
<i>A kiss may be grand</i>

626
00:44:56,139 --> 00:45:00,518
<i>But it won't pay the rental
On your humble flat</i>

627
00:45:00,910 --> 00:45:03,529
<i>Or help you at the automat</i>

628
00:45:05,993 --> 00:45:07,913
<i>Diamonds</i>

629
00:45:07,993 --> 00:45:08,934
<i> I will be waiting.</i>

630
00:45:09,014 --> 00:45:09,965
<i>Diamonds</i>

631
00:45:10,045 --> 00:45:11,007
<i>Diamonds</i>

632
00:45:11,087 --> 00:45:12,924
<i> The diamond.</i>

633
00:45:13,004 --> 00:45:13,996
<i>Diamonds</i>

634
00:45:14,076 --> 00:45:16,069
Romy, Roman.

635
00:45:16,149 --> 00:45:18,393
<i>I will be waiting.</i>

636
00:45:19,962 --> 00:45:21,017
<i>But diamonds</i>

637
00:45:21,097 --> 00:45:24,383
<i>Diamonds are a girl's best</i>

638
00:45:28,004 --> 00:45:30,404
I'll give you till midnight.

639
00:45:31,066 --> 00:45:34,038
And then I'm gonna peel off
that pretty face

640
00:45:34,118 --> 00:45:36,445
and pickle it.

641
00:45:36,972 --> 00:45:38,972
Okay?

642
00:45:41,056 --> 00:45:44,059
<i>Call me old-fashioned,
but I always thought the guy</i>

643
00:45:44,139 --> 00:45:46,456
<i>was meant to
get the girl a diamond.</i>

644
00:45:51,139 --> 00:45:54,038
I won't let you down, Romy.
I promise.

645
00:45:54,118 --> 00:45:56,059
Let's make it half a mil.

646
00:45:56,139 --> 00:45:58,871
It's more fun
if she's got competition.

647
00:45:58,951 --> 00:46:01,549
Send it to
every mercenary in Gotham.

648
00:46:02,024 --> 00:46:03,986
Oh, hey, you're that singer
no one listens to.

649
00:46:04,066 --> 00:46:06,518
Hey, you're the asshole
no one likes.

650
00:46:24,056 --> 00:46:26,944
Jesus. Who the fuck is this?
What?

651
00:46:27,024 --> 00:46:29,903
<i>We've got a situation.
This kid, she's got the diamond.</i>

652
00:46:29,983 --> 00:46:31,892
Her name's Cassandra Cain.

653
00:46:31,972 --> 00:46:33,972
Holy fuck.

654
00:46:36,941 --> 00:46:38,830
Where can I find
Cassandra Cain?

655
00:46:38,910 --> 00:46:40,910
<i>Okay. Now we're good.</i>

656
00:46:44,045 --> 00:46:46,045
Cell seven.

657
00:46:50,108 --> 00:46:52,549
Thanks, doll. You're a peach.

658
00:46:55,066 --> 00:46:57,066
Hey, I know that guy.

659
00:47:15,128 --> 00:47:17,995
<i>Access denied. Access denied.</i>

660
00:47:18,075 --> 00:47:20,455
<i>Access denied. Access denied.</i>

661
00:47:21,117 --> 00:47:22,933
<i>Access denied.
Access denied. Denied.</i>

662
00:47:23,013 --> 00:47:26,350
<i>Denied. Denied. Denied.
Denied. Denied. Denied.</i>

663
00:47:29,023 --> 00:47:31,361
Hmm. Perfect.

664
00:47:46,075 --> 00:47:49,037
- Hold up, hold up. Remember me?
- She stole my car!

665
00:47:49,117 --> 00:47:50,891
- Harley Quinn.
- Hey, Quinn!

666
00:47:50,971 --> 00:47:52,839
- Let us out, see what happens.
- Don't mind me, guys.

667
00:47:52,919 --> 00:47:54,860
- You killed my chinchilla!
- Here for the kid.

668
00:47:54,940 --> 00:47:56,870
What's up, girl?
You're the reason I'm in here!

669
00:47:56,950 --> 00:47:59,891
- Yeah, sorry about that.
- You're dead!

670
00:47:59,971 --> 00:48:02,943
- I'm gonna kill you, Quinn!
- Hey, kid.

671
00:48:03,023 --> 00:48:05,058
- You're that psycho from the roller derby.
- Yeah, yeah.

672
00:48:05,138 --> 00:48:07,908
- Are you Cassandra Cain?
- Yeah.

673
00:48:20,034 --> 00:48:22,034
I need to know where...

674
00:48:32,909 --> 00:48:35,961
- Hold, please.
- Harley...

675
00:49:56,013 --> 00:49:58,013
Hmm.

676
00:50:01,065 --> 00:50:03,330
I got you, you little shit.

677
00:50:04,075 --> 00:50:06,075
Who are you guys?

678
00:50:06,992 --> 00:50:08,992
Go, go, go.

679
00:50:11,075 --> 00:50:13,075
Keep the kid alive.

680
00:51:11,013 --> 00:51:13,013
Mmm!

681
00:52:14,044 --> 00:52:16,044
A little help.

682
00:52:22,044 --> 00:52:24,044
Mmm...

683
00:52:34,013 --> 00:52:36,361
Does she have to keep running?

684
00:53:04,940 --> 00:53:07,548
Roman,
you trustafarian fuckbag.

685
00:53:09,971 --> 00:53:11,985
- You!
- You!

686
00:53:12,065 --> 00:53:14,361
Step away from the kid.

687
00:53:15,013 --> 00:53:18,829
- Drop it.
- The phone?

688
00:53:18,909 --> 00:53:20,909
Sure.

689
00:53:33,992 --> 00:53:35,992
Mmm.

690
00:53:54,909 --> 00:53:56,829
Whoa.

691
00:53:56,909 --> 00:54:00,382
Oh, good. You're awake.
Toss that for me, will ya?

692
00:54:13,107 --> 00:54:15,891
What the fuck?

693
00:54:15,971 --> 00:54:17,870
Who did I just blow up?

694
00:54:17,950 --> 00:54:19,891
Either someone
who wants me dead,

695
00:54:19,971 --> 00:54:23,339
or someone looking to collect the
half-million dollar reward on your head.

696
00:54:23,908 --> 00:54:26,848
- Half a million dollars?
- Yeah.

697
00:54:26,928 --> 00:54:29,433
Do I look like I'm
worth half a million dollars?

698
00:54:29,918 --> 00:54:31,838
- Not really.
- You've got the wrong kid.

699
00:54:31,918 --> 00:54:35,057
- Now, uncuff me.
- Oh, sure.

700
00:54:35,137 --> 00:54:38,970
- As soon as you give me the diamond.
- What diamond?

701
00:54:44,991 --> 00:54:46,991
Fuck you!

702
00:54:47,991 --> 00:54:49,991
Look at me.

703
00:54:52,043 --> 00:54:55,880
What? I don't know
nothing about no diamond.

704
00:54:55,960 --> 00:54:57,963
The inflection in your voice,
the way you can't hold eye contact,

705
00:54:58,043 --> 00:54:59,859
and the fact that
you're a filthy little thief,

706
00:54:59,939 --> 00:55:03,869
all suggest that you do. Now, you
can give it to me, or I can give you

707
00:55:03,949 --> 00:55:07,067
to the man that diamond belongs to. But
trust me when I say, you're not gonna like

708
00:55:07,147 --> 00:55:09,308
what he's gonna do to ya.

709
00:55:09,908 --> 00:55:12,433
Now, hand it over.

710
00:55:12,970 --> 00:55:15,433
Yeah, not gonna happen.

711
00:55:16,928 --> 00:55:19,026
- Come again?
- I said I can't.

712
00:55:19,106 --> 00:55:21,674
- One more time.
- I can't give it to you.

713
00:55:22,009 --> 00:55:24,516
- Why not?
- Because I ate it, okay?

714
00:55:31,928 --> 00:55:33,928
Yes.

715
00:55:34,012 --> 00:55:36,405
What are we even doing here?

716
00:55:36,423 --> 00:55:39,308
There are two ways that
diamond's coming outta ya.

717
00:55:39,949 --> 00:55:41,949
This way,

718
00:55:42,137 --> 00:55:44,401
or this way.

719
00:55:46,074 --> 00:55:49,918
That's what I thought.
Also, I'm outta groceries.

720
00:55:52,991 --> 00:55:56,318
So, how long you been
a mercenary?

721
00:55:56,918 --> 00:55:58,584
Hey, where did you get...

722
00:55:58,646 --> 00:56:00,847
You're so busy
looking at my right hand,

723
00:56:00,939 --> 00:56:02,828
you haven't even
thought about my left...

724
00:56:02,908 --> 00:56:05,308
Your left hand is
cuffed to mine.

725
00:56:09,064 --> 00:56:11,422
I'll have to learn that one.

726
00:56:12,053 --> 00:56:13,911
Can we get this?

727
00:56:13,991 --> 00:56:16,036
You're not gonna try
to run, are you?

728
00:56:16,116 --> 00:56:18,547
Look, if there's really
a half mil on my head,

729
00:56:18,939 --> 00:56:21,921
I figure I'm better off with the person
who's not gonna cut me open.

730
00:56:22,001 --> 00:56:24,890
Fine. But if you try to run,
I will kill you.

731
00:56:24,970 --> 00:56:27,412
I do not care
that you're a kid.

732
00:56:29,991 --> 00:56:31,991
I saw that.

733
00:56:32,085 --> 00:56:34,984
Seriously though,
how'd you get to be here?

734
00:56:35,064 --> 00:56:38,537
I mean,
shopping at fancy-ass stores,

735
00:56:38,928 --> 00:56:42,046
you're making bank,
you have your own business.

736
00:56:42,126 --> 00:56:46,859
How'd you do it? Come on, tell me.
Woman to woman.

737
00:56:46,939 --> 00:56:50,890
Being a pickpocket's fine and
all, but I got real potential.

738
00:56:50,970 --> 00:56:52,901
I mean, how do I be like you?

739
00:56:52,981 --> 00:56:56,526
Well, except for the crazy
part. But other than that.

740
00:56:57,022 --> 00:56:59,984
Number one, no one is like me.

741
00:57:00,064 --> 00:57:03,036
If you wanted to even come close,
you would have to go to medical school.

742
00:57:03,116 --> 00:57:07,911
Become a psychiatrist, work in an
asylum. Fall in love with your patient,

743
00:57:07,991 --> 00:57:10,973
break said patient out of said asylum.
Begin a life of crime.

744
00:57:11,053 --> 00:57:13,057
Jump into a vat of chemicals
to prove yourself to a madman.

745
00:57:13,137 --> 00:57:15,015
Get arrested by the Batman.

746
00:57:15,095 --> 00:57:16,942
Go back to jail, get out of
jail with a bomb on your neck.

747
00:57:17,022 --> 00:57:18,838
Save the world, go back to
jail, and break out of jail

748
00:57:18,918 --> 00:57:20,973
before breaking up
with the aforementioned madman

749
00:57:21,053 --> 00:57:23,360
and going out on your own.

750
00:57:25,918 --> 00:57:29,067
Number two...
Six bucks for tap water

751
00:57:29,147 --> 00:57:33,033
with a fucking cucumber stick in it?
That's crazy.

752
00:57:34,001 --> 00:57:36,401
I'm not shopping
at this store.

753
00:57:38,012 --> 00:57:42,067
I'm robbing this store.
Consider this your first lesson.

754
00:57:42,147 --> 00:57:45,318
Paying is for dummies.

755
00:57:51,033 --> 00:57:52,828
Whoa, whoa, whoa!

756
00:57:52,908 --> 00:57:54,908
Move it!

757
00:57:59,918 --> 00:58:01,918
Whoops. Ah...

758
00:58:03,147 --> 00:58:06,464
This is Doc's Place.
And this is Doc.

759
00:58:09,022 --> 00:58:10,911
Lotus flower!

760
00:58:10,991 --> 00:58:13,067
- Hiya, Doc. How are ya?
- Good.

761
00:58:13,147 --> 00:58:15,859
He's the Taiwanese grandpa
I never had.

762
00:58:15,939 --> 00:58:19,057
He knows everything and everyone. Nothing
happens around here, let me tell you,

763
00:58:19,137 --> 00:58:23,526
without Doc knowing about it.
And he happens to be the only person

764
00:58:24,053 --> 00:58:25,942
who actually cares about me.

765
00:58:26,022 --> 00:58:27,859
- I do?
- Yes, you do.

766
00:58:27,939 --> 00:58:31,036
She's been ordering #32
with extra chili for many years.

767
00:58:31,116 --> 00:58:34,869
Lesson number two,
you always want extra chili with #32.

768
00:58:34,949 --> 00:58:36,846
So you don't have
to taste his cooking.

769
00:58:36,871 --> 00:58:39,464
Lotus flower, you have to get
upstairs before someone sees.

770
00:58:39,928 --> 00:58:44,328
- Everyone's looking for you. And you.
- We know.

771
00:58:44,408 --> 00:58:47,422
I'm telling you, if you want
boys to respect you,

772
00:58:47,502 --> 00:58:49,870
you have to show them
that you're serious.

773
00:58:50,398 --> 00:58:52,912
Blow something up.
Shoot someone.

774
00:58:53,564 --> 00:58:56,006
Nothing gets a guy's attention
like violence.

775
00:58:56,398 --> 00:58:58,370
Shut that door. Lock it.

776
00:58:58,450 --> 00:59:00,902
Keep your sticky paws
to yourself, okay?

777
00:59:11,439 --> 00:59:14,547
This place... Well, it ain't much,
but it's better than a prison cell.

778
00:59:14,627 --> 00:59:16,943
...is so fucking dope.

779
00:59:18,585 --> 00:59:21,526
Oh, shit. Is that
a hyena in a bathtub?

780
00:59:21,606 --> 00:59:24,964
I named him Bruce after
that hunky Wayne guy.

781
00:59:25,398 --> 00:59:27,505
He's my little dumpling,
aren't you?

782
00:59:27,585 --> 00:59:32,027
Aren't you, my little baby?
Aren't you, Brucey? Yes.

783
00:59:32,418 --> 00:59:34,418
I love you.

784
00:59:35,543 --> 00:59:38,557
I never said that.
I love you both equally.

785
00:59:38,637 --> 00:59:43,808
Who, that? It's Cass.

786
00:59:45,595 --> 00:59:47,595
You're so pretty.

787
00:59:49,408 --> 00:59:51,408
Who's this?

788
00:59:51,491 --> 00:59:53,422
It's a beaver.

789
00:59:53,502 --> 00:59:55,502
Hmm.

790
00:59:57,408 --> 01:00:01,829
Does Brucey want a treat?
Does Brucey want a treat?

791
01:00:03,460 --> 01:00:05,460
What's this?

792
01:00:08,491 --> 01:00:10,870
It's art. Don't touch.

793
01:00:13,502 --> 01:00:15,505
He your ex or something?

794
01:00:15,585 --> 01:00:17,881
You don't know who that is?

795
01:00:18,606 --> 01:00:20,359
The Joker.

796
01:00:20,439 --> 01:00:24,515
The Clown Prince of Crime?
My former partner in madness?

797
01:00:24,595 --> 01:00:27,370
The Harlequin of Hate?
The Jester of Genocide?

798
01:00:27,450 --> 01:00:31,870
- You've never heard of him?
- Well, sounds like a dick.

799
01:00:34,512 --> 01:00:36,512
Huh.

800
01:00:45,533 --> 01:00:47,533
Milk.

801
01:00:57,491 --> 01:01:01,370
<i>I'm not going soft
or nothing, but I gotta admit,</i>

802
01:01:01,450 --> 01:01:03,902
it was kinda nice
having the kid around.

803
01:01:14,502 --> 01:01:17,370
Give me a #32. Mild.

804
01:01:17,450 --> 01:01:19,839
Uh... Yeah, sure.

805
01:01:22,877 --> 01:01:27,651
{\an8}I've been told that you know all
the scum of this disgusting city.

806
01:01:28,291 --> 01:01:30,624
{\an8}I need you to help me find someone.

807
01:01:35,532 --> 01:01:38,932
{\an8}I know everybody,
apparently, except for you.

808
01:01:40,511 --> 01:01:43,817
- Who are you?
- They call me...

809
01:01:45,490 --> 01:01:46,431
H...

810
01:01:46,511 --> 01:01:48,441
<i>My bad.
I should've introduced you.</i>

811
01:01:48,521 --> 01:01:50,521
<i>I'll make it quick.</i>

812
01:01:54,428 --> 01:01:59,421
<i>Meet the daughter of the richest,
most powerful Mafia don in Gotham City.</i>

813
01:01:59,501 --> 01:02:02,015
<i>Helena Bertinelli.</i>

814
01:02:02,407 --> 01:02:04,901
<i>Yep, that Bertinelli.</i>

815
01:02:06,469 --> 01:02:10,036
<i>One day, she comes home to find
her whole family in the living room.</i>

816
01:02:10,428 --> 01:02:12,428
Momma.

817
01:02:13,511 --> 01:02:17,901
<i>Anyone and everyone with
Bertinelli blood is there.</i>

818
01:02:19,542 --> 01:02:22,525
<i>Oh, and that?
That's Stefano Galante.</i>

819
01:02:22,605 --> 01:02:26,901
<i>The guy making the play
for the Bertinelli turf and fortune.</i>

820
01:02:50,480 --> 01:02:53,514
<i>When one of the goons
finds the kid alive,</i>

821
01:02:53,594 --> 01:02:58,379
<i>the big softy sneaks her outta
there and hides her away in Sicily.</i>

822
01:02:58,459 --> 01:03:02,403
<i>Where she is raised by his own
father and brother.</i>

823
01:03:02,484 --> 01:03:04,638
<i>Both assassins.</i>

824
01:03:11,438 --> 01:03:15,828
<i>She spends the next 15 years
thinking only of revenge.</i>

825
01:03:16,459 --> 01:03:18,459
<i>So, she starts training.</i>

826
01:03:19,636 --> 01:03:22,410
<i>When she was ready,
and by "ready" I mean</i>

827
01:03:22,490 --> 01:03:29,483
<i>a badass motherfucking killing
machine, she moves back to Gotham.</i>

828
01:03:29,563 --> 01:03:31,563
<i>Starts working
on that kill list.</i>

829
01:03:39,605 --> 01:03:42,026
<i>She has the murder stuff down,
but the rest?</i>

830
01:03:42,417 --> 01:03:45,546
Do you know who I am?
Do you know who I am?

831
01:03:45,626 --> 01:03:47,626
<i>Still a work in progress.</i>

832
01:03:49,584 --> 01:03:53,327
- Do you know who I am?
- The Crossbow Killer.

833
01:03:53,407 --> 01:03:56,400
- They call me...
- The Crossbow Killer.

834
01:03:56,480 --> 01:04:00,535
- They call me...
- The Crossbow Killer?

835
01:04:00,615 --> 01:04:02,807
They call me...

836
01:04:05,480 --> 01:04:09,369
- Huntress.
<i>- She calls herself Huntress.</i>

837
01:04:09,449 --> 01:04:11,932
<i>Fucking fabulous, if you ask me.</i>

838
01:04:12,438 --> 01:04:14,942
And who are you looking for?

839
01:04:21,407 --> 01:04:24,337
- Great club.
- Quinn got the girl.

840
01:04:24,417 --> 01:04:27,890
- And?
- And they disappeared.

841
01:04:29,490 --> 01:04:31,849
Fuck!

842
01:04:32,574 --> 01:04:34,574
Fuck!

843
01:04:40,574 --> 01:04:42,838
What is she laughing at?

844
01:04:44,438 --> 01:04:46,556
- Is she laughing at me?
- She is.

845
01:04:46,636 --> 01:04:49,004
No, she's not. She's...

846
01:04:49,009 --> 01:04:51,421
What are you laughing at,
Erika?

847
01:04:51,459 --> 01:04:55,535
- You gotta hear this. It's hilarious.
- Get on the table.

848
01:04:55,615 --> 01:04:57,379
- Oh.
- Ooh.

849
01:04:57,459 --> 01:04:59,817
You're being a total kook.

850
01:05:00,553 --> 01:05:02,828
Get on the fucking table.

851
01:05:04,469 --> 01:05:07,046
This is my club. Get up now.

852
01:05:07,605 --> 01:05:09,828
- Okay.
- Now.

853
01:05:11,626 --> 01:05:13,817
Whoa.

854
01:05:15,521 --> 01:05:17,521
Now, dance.

855
01:05:22,594 --> 01:05:25,026
Dance. Dance, Erika!

856
01:05:25,417 --> 01:05:27,417
Okay.

857
01:05:34,438 --> 01:05:36,932
This dress is fucking hideous.

858
01:05:38,490 --> 01:05:40,490
Take it off.

859
01:05:41,501 --> 01:05:43,501
Take your dress off.

860
01:05:45,448 --> 01:05:47,838
Get up there
and fucking cut it off her.

861
01:05:48,480 --> 01:05:50,473
Do it now!

862
01:05:50,553 --> 01:05:54,535
Take her fucking dress off.
Just rip it off her. Hurry up!

863
01:05:54,615 --> 01:05:59,504
- Hurry up! Fucking do it.
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry.

864
01:05:59,584 --> 01:06:01,584
Do it.

865
01:06:04,448 --> 01:06:07,046
Yeah. Beautiful.

866
01:06:22,542 --> 01:06:25,036
You wouldn't betray me,
would you?

867
01:06:27,511 --> 01:06:29,483
I was just gonna
go look for the girl.

868
01:06:29,563 --> 01:06:32,125
Oh, no, no, no. I want you to
stay here with me.

869
01:06:32,179 --> 01:06:34,828
I want you to stay here
with me close.

870
01:06:35,438 --> 01:06:37,921
You soothe me, little bird.

871
01:06:52,417 --> 01:06:54,525
Oh, good. You got it.
Did you trace the messages?

872
01:06:54,605 --> 01:06:57,389
You stole evidence
from an active crime scene,

873
01:06:57,469 --> 01:07:01,493
and then had it sent to my office.
Renee, what were you thinking?

874
01:07:01,573 --> 01:07:06,452
Roman is the one that put a price
on the kid's head. Okay? I had to.

875
01:07:06,532 --> 01:07:09,452
- I can't get into it right now...
- Renee, you need help.

876
01:07:09,532 --> 01:07:13,420
- What are you talking about?
- She's right.

877
01:07:14,469 --> 01:07:17,911
You are a good cop, Montoya,
but you've lost your way.

878
01:07:18,584 --> 01:07:20,400
What?

879
01:07:20,480 --> 01:07:23,525
I'm sorry. Okay?
You gave me no choice.

880
01:07:23,605 --> 01:07:25,942
- Did you sell me out?
- I'm sorry.

881
01:07:26,490 --> 01:07:28,490
You're suspended.

882
01:07:28,646 --> 01:07:31,046
Your badge and your gun, now.

883
01:07:35,469 --> 01:07:38,514
<i>If you've ever watched
any cop movie ever,</i>

884
01:07:38,594 --> 01:07:41,389
you know that
this is when shit gets real.

885
01:07:41,469 --> 01:07:47,005
What's the point of the badge,
when it means fuck all anyway?

886
01:07:49,417 --> 01:07:51,327
Right, Captain?

887
01:07:51,407 --> 01:07:55,026
No cop ever gets anything done
until after they've been suspended.

888
01:07:57,490 --> 01:08:01,932
<i>Which would've had me worried,
only I had more pressing concerns.</i>

889
01:08:02,438 --> 01:08:05,901
<i>And that is why you should never
partake in paying federal income taxes.</i>

890
01:08:06,490 --> 01:08:08,490
Hey, you'll ruin your nails.

891
01:08:11,490 --> 01:08:14,525
- Thank you.
- Anyway, lesson 37.

892
01:08:14,605 --> 01:08:16,605
Why...

893
01:08:17,553 --> 01:08:22,368
- You said they wouldn't find us.
- Chillax. No one knows we're here.

894
01:08:22,448 --> 01:08:25,026
Harleen Quinzel,
this is Gotham Police.

895
01:08:25,417 --> 01:08:27,337
Okay. So they know.

896
01:08:27,417 --> 01:08:29,417
Let's scram.

897
01:08:30,584 --> 01:08:33,400
- Open the door.
- Holy back door, Beavy.

898
01:08:33,481 --> 01:08:35,473
This is getting outta hand.
Bruce, come here.

899
01:08:35,553 --> 01:08:37,553
I can hear you!
Open the door.

900
01:08:38,469 --> 01:08:40,452
What is that?

901
01:08:40,532 --> 01:08:42,984
See you in hell, Harley!

902
01:08:45,520 --> 01:08:47,806
Get under the table!

903
01:08:49,479 --> 01:08:51,420
Bruce? Bruce!

904
01:08:51,500 --> 01:08:53,500
Come here! No!

905
01:09:03,427 --> 01:09:05,427
Bruce?

906
01:09:06,458 --> 01:09:08,910
Come here, boy. Bruce?

907
01:09:11,510 --> 01:09:13,510
Bruce?

908
01:09:14,427 --> 01:09:16,427
Bruce?

909
01:09:17,427 --> 01:09:19,388
This doesn't make sense.

910
01:09:19,468 --> 01:09:23,503
It doesn't make sense. I don't
understand. No one knew we were here.

911
01:09:23,583 --> 01:09:25,868
No one knew we were here,
except...

912
01:09:26,468 --> 01:09:29,510
Doc. Oh, my God. Doc?

913
01:09:30,541 --> 01:09:32,941
Doc? Where is he?

914
01:09:34,437 --> 01:09:37,598
Doc?
I can't find Bruce.

915
01:09:37,679 --> 01:09:39,927
I can't find him. I...

916
01:09:45,625 --> 01:09:47,492
No.

917
01:09:47,572 --> 01:09:51,545
- I'm sorry, lotus flower.
- You sold me out?

918
01:09:51,625 --> 01:09:54,952
Too many people offering me
too much money.

919
01:09:56,500 --> 01:09:59,004
I have enough now
to open up a new restaurant.

920
01:09:59,593 --> 01:10:03,336
- A really nice one.
- But, Doc,

921
01:10:03,416 --> 01:10:05,357
it's me.

922
01:10:05,437 --> 01:10:07,437
It's just business.

923
01:10:34,437 --> 01:10:37,827
<i>This next bit
ain't very pretty.</i>

924
01:10:38,510 --> 01:10:40,565
- You're right.
- Harley?

925
01:10:40,645 --> 01:10:42,816
He's right.

926
01:10:44,499 --> 01:10:46,499
Business is business.

927
01:10:47,406 --> 01:10:49,406
I've got the kid.

928
01:10:49,510 --> 01:10:52,430
But I'm gonna need to renegotiate
the terms of our deal.

929
01:10:52,510 --> 01:10:56,544
If I hand her over, I want everyone
who's after me to back off.

930
01:10:56,624 --> 01:11:00,367
<i>Quinn,
bring me the rock now</i>

931
01:11:00,447 --> 01:11:02,367
and I guarantee your safety.

932
01:11:02,447 --> 01:11:05,544
I own this town.
You'll have my protection.

933
01:11:05,624 --> 01:11:07,451
Fine.

934
01:11:07,531 --> 01:11:11,962
Meet me at Amusement Mile.
The Booby Trap. In one hour.

935
01:11:21,499 --> 01:11:23,499
Quit judging.

936
01:11:25,624 --> 01:11:27,624
Zsasz!

937
01:11:33,593 --> 01:11:37,482
Come on, kid.
Let's get you somewhere safe.

938
01:11:37,562 --> 01:11:39,562
We got them.

939
01:11:42,583 --> 01:11:44,503
Little bird!

940
01:11:44,583 --> 01:11:47,889
You're gonna be
driving Mr. Zsasz tonight.

941
01:11:48,406 --> 01:11:51,983
Go. Fetch. Amusement Mile.
The Booby Trap.

942
01:11:52,489 --> 01:11:54,489
Do we have to bring them back?

943
01:11:54,614 --> 01:11:58,035
I think you can manage
a couple of little girls.

944
01:11:59,489 --> 01:12:01,489
Just bring me back my diamond.

945
01:12:48,447 --> 01:12:50,447
What is it?

946
01:12:50,562 --> 01:12:52,562
Nothing.

947
01:13:04,604 --> 01:13:07,482
- Pull over.
- What?

948
01:13:07,562 --> 01:13:10,858
Pull the fucking car over now.

949
01:13:12,562 --> 01:13:14,920
I gotta take a leak.

950
01:13:17,583 --> 01:13:20,482
<i>She betrayed you, boss.
She betrayed you.</i>

951
01:13:20,562 --> 01:13:25,024
- Are you sure?
<i>- Your little bird's a fucking rat.</i>

952
01:13:32,499 --> 01:13:34,837
You want me to kill her?

953
01:13:38,272 --> 01:13:40,920
No. No. No.

954
01:13:41,416 --> 01:13:43,416
I'll come to you.

955
01:14:18,541 --> 01:14:21,024
I thought we were friends.
And you...

956
01:14:21,479 --> 01:14:24,513
You saw what it's like for me out there.
I didn't have a choice.

957
01:14:24,593 --> 01:14:27,972
And if you go before he gets here,
everything will be fine.

958
01:14:29,572 --> 01:14:31,430
Harley.

959
01:14:31,510 --> 01:14:34,014
I'm sorry, kid. I am.

960
01:14:44,437 --> 01:14:46,437
That was fast.

961
01:14:48,572 --> 01:14:50,409
She's in...

962
01:14:50,489 --> 01:14:54,889
- Where's Cassandra Cain?
- You? Again?

963
01:15:03,572 --> 01:15:06,430
- Are you drunk?
- Come on.

964
01:15:06,510 --> 01:15:08,510
Okay.

965
01:15:29,624 --> 01:15:31,827
Right in the tit.

966
01:15:37,468 --> 01:15:39,847
Where's Cassandra Cain?

967
01:15:40,499 --> 01:15:42,499
Cass.

968
01:15:48,458 --> 01:15:50,972
You killed my sandwich!

969
01:15:58,405 --> 01:16:00,405
Bye-bye, birdie.

970
01:16:00,613 --> 01:16:02,613
Ow!

971
01:16:03,592 --> 01:16:05,450
No fair.

972
01:16:05,530 --> 01:16:09,523
- Was that really necessary?
- You don't know her like I do.

973
01:16:09,603 --> 01:16:11,603
Cass?

974
01:16:15,262 --> 01:16:18,491
Oh, thank God.
I'm gonna get you outta here.

975
01:16:18,571 --> 01:16:22,436
Did she really tape you
to a damn toilet?

976
01:16:23,519 --> 01:16:24,481
Hmm.

977
01:16:24,561 --> 01:16:26,825
This is nice.

978
01:16:27,436 --> 01:16:29,436
You're still conscious.

979
01:16:31,415 --> 01:16:35,909
You can still feel? Look at me.
Are you a good girl, now?

980
01:16:37,446 --> 01:16:41,878
"I'm a good girl.
I'm a good girl."

981
01:16:52,519 --> 01:16:56,377
I got one
for all the little birds

982
01:16:56,457 --> 01:16:59,930
I helped fly away
from this world.

983
01:17:00,405 --> 01:17:02,940
I'm saving
a special spot for you.

984
01:17:04,415 --> 01:17:06,415
Right here.

985
01:17:10,540 --> 01:17:12,554
- You're gonna have to be quiet.
- Hi.

986
01:17:12,634 --> 01:17:14,867
What are you guys doing?

987
01:17:18,519 --> 01:17:21,439
Oh, I know
where the diamond is.

988
01:17:21,519 --> 01:17:24,909
Is that rock still inside you?

989
01:17:27,519 --> 01:17:29,519
Oh, God.

990
01:17:32,425 --> 01:17:34,425
Stop.

991
01:17:35,519 --> 01:17:38,554
- The hell, Zsasz?
- Cut her open.

992
01:17:38,634 --> 01:17:41,533
- Stop fucking around.
- You heard me.

993
01:17:41,613 --> 01:17:43,836
Cut her fucking open.

994
01:17:44,478 --> 01:17:47,034
Okay. No, no. No, no, no.
See, she's just a kid.

995
01:17:47,498 --> 01:17:50,564
- You're a filthy fucking rat.
- I'm a rat?

996
01:17:50,644 --> 01:17:54,564
I knew you couldn't be
trusted. Roman's little bird.

997
01:17:54,644 --> 01:17:56,961
You little fucking bird.

998
01:17:57,540 --> 01:18:00,023
That's why he needs me
to look out for him.

999
01:18:01,634 --> 01:18:05,013
That's why he needs me
to take care of him.

1000
01:18:06,592 --> 01:18:09,502
You know you're just
being paranoid, Zsasz.

1001
01:18:09,582 --> 01:18:11,345
- Yeah?
- Mmm-hmm.

1002
01:18:11,425 --> 01:18:13,425
Prove it to me.

1003
01:18:13,540 --> 01:18:16,013
Rip open her little tummy.

1004
01:18:16,405 --> 01:18:19,961
- Yeah, that's not gonna happen.
- Now! Rip it open!

1005
01:18:33,509 --> 01:18:35,898
You piece of shit!

1006
01:18:43,592 --> 01:18:45,592
Freeze!

1007
01:18:48,613 --> 01:18:50,836
Don't fucking move.

1008
01:18:52,561 --> 01:18:54,846
Who the fuck are you?

1009
01:19:01,498 --> 01:19:04,356
- Go get the kid.
- All right.

1010
01:19:04,436 --> 01:19:06,398
- Whoa, whoa, whoa!
- Back the fuck up!

1011
01:19:06,478 --> 01:19:08,481
- Get away from me. All of you.
- Put that shit down.

1012
01:19:08,561 --> 01:19:11,013
Shoot them, kid.

1013
01:19:11,405 --> 01:19:14,554
You, put that stupid-ass
Robin Hood piece of shit down!

1014
01:19:14,634 --> 01:19:17,533
- Cass, it's okay. Just calm...
- Don't move!

1015
01:19:17,613 --> 01:19:19,512
Okay.

1016
01:19:19,592 --> 01:19:21,564
I don't know
what the fuck is going on.

1017
01:19:22,316 --> 01:19:27,446
But I know that this shit stick...
just tried to gut me.

1018
01:19:27,634 --> 01:19:29,634
And you.

1019
01:19:31,478 --> 01:19:33,478
Thought you were different.

1020
01:19:35,592 --> 01:19:37,805
I'm sorry, kid.

1021
01:19:39,571 --> 01:19:42,836
I'm just a terrible person,
I guess.

1022
01:19:49,425 --> 01:19:51,325
Ooh!

1023
01:19:51,405 --> 01:19:52,450
Ooh, I'm back.

1024
01:19:52,530 --> 01:19:55,554
Okay, I feel like I've just walked in on
something I don't give two shits about.

1025
01:19:55,634 --> 01:19:58,387
This guy's dead, so I'm just
gonna get outta your hair. Cool?

1026
01:19:58,467 --> 01:20:01,429
No. Wait. She's lying.
She works for Sionis.

1027
01:20:01,509 --> 01:20:03,888
Excuse me? I work for Sionis?

1028
01:20:05,415 --> 01:20:07,523
I'm not letting you
sell the kid to him.

1029
01:20:07,603 --> 01:20:10,564
I wasn't going to sell the kid.
I was going to trade the kid.

1030
01:20:10,644 --> 01:20:12,523
Yeah. To save
your own stupid skin. Huh?

1031
01:20:12,603 --> 01:20:15,543
I'm not proud of what I did,
but I had half the city after me.

1032
01:20:15,623 --> 01:20:19,470
- Even the fucking Crossbow Killer.
- I'm not the Crossbow Killer!

1033
01:20:19,550 --> 01:20:21,550
Whoa.

1034
01:20:22,530 --> 01:20:25,387
They call me...
Helena Bertinelli.

1035
01:20:25,467 --> 01:20:28,470
For fuck's sake.
As in the Bertinelli massacre?

1036
01:20:28,550 --> 01:20:32,888
Sheesh kebab. That is
childhood trauma, right there.

1037
01:20:38,457 --> 01:20:40,457
<i>I killed Galante.</i>

1038
01:20:44,405 --> 01:20:46,405
I killed his firing squad.

1039
01:20:50,540 --> 01:20:53,003
I killed Victor Zsasz.

1040
01:20:58,603 --> 01:21:00,878
And now I'm done.

1041
01:21:02,425 --> 01:21:04,425
Bravo.

1042
01:21:08,530 --> 01:21:10,398
So if you don't mind,
I'm gonna leave now.

1043
01:21:10,478 --> 01:21:12,478
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.

1044
01:21:12,603 --> 01:21:16,429
I hate to be the one to break it to
you, sweetheart, but you are not done.

1045
01:21:16,509 --> 01:21:19,418
Who do you think funded
Galante's little power grab, huh?

1046
01:21:19,498 --> 01:21:21,356
Galante was working with Sionis.

1047
01:21:21,436 --> 01:21:23,481
Roman killed your whole family
looking for that rock.

1048
01:21:23,561 --> 01:21:25,992
You don't think
he's gonna kill this kid?

1049
01:21:26,530 --> 01:21:29,366
That diamond is our
only chance of stopping him.

1050
01:21:29,446 --> 01:21:32,971
You guys.
Hey, I think you should see this.

1051
01:21:35,290 --> 01:21:36,242
Oh.

1052
01:21:36,322 --> 01:21:38,617
It's Sionis.

1053
01:21:50,322 --> 01:21:52,628
We're fucked.

1054
01:21:53,155 --> 01:21:55,155
He bought himself an army.

1055
01:22:03,322 --> 01:22:05,322
They're all here for me.

1056
01:22:06,374 --> 01:22:08,628
Aren't they?

1057
01:22:15,176 --> 01:22:17,094
- No.
- They're not?

1058
01:22:17,157 --> 01:22:19,059
No, they're not.

1059
01:22:19,207 --> 01:22:22,189
Do you know what that means? That means
he's not just after the kid anymore.

1060
01:22:22,269 --> 01:22:26,314
He's after all of us. He's sure as hell
after me. I just robbed him.

1061
01:22:26,394 --> 01:22:29,784
You just betrayed him.
You just killed his BFF.

1062
01:22:30,176 --> 01:22:33,262
And you're dumb enough
to be building a case against him.

1063
01:22:33,342 --> 01:22:36,844
So, unless we all wanna
die very unpleasant deaths

1064
01:22:36,925 --> 01:22:40,207
and let Roman go finger-fishing
in the kid's intestinal tract,

1065
01:22:41,238 --> 01:22:45,137
- we're gonna have to work together.
- With you?

1066
01:22:45,217 --> 01:22:48,075
Yeah.
We're gonna work together,

1067
01:22:48,155 --> 01:22:50,155
and we'll get outta here
in one piece, okay?

1068
01:22:53,384 --> 01:22:55,565
Okay.

1069
01:22:56,207 --> 01:22:58,680
Yeah. Okay.

1070
01:23:01,249 --> 01:23:04,117
- Sure.
- Yes!

1071
01:23:04,197 --> 01:23:08,249
But we are gonna need
some serious hardware.

1072
01:23:11,227 --> 01:23:13,752
Will this do?

1073
01:23:15,449 --> 01:23:18,452
No. Not at all.

1074
01:23:20,206 --> 01:23:22,668
We're dead.
We're fucking dead.

1075
01:23:22,723 --> 01:23:26,251
That slimy jizznozzle! I can't believe
he took it all! - We're fucked.

1076
01:23:26,331 --> 01:23:28,773
- Fuck!
- Uh, there's this.

1077
01:23:35,237 --> 01:23:37,237
Okay.

1078
01:23:48,175 --> 01:23:52,689
Friends, brothers,
men of Gotham.

1079
01:23:53,373 --> 01:23:57,700
I have funded you.
I've protected you.

1080
01:23:58,289 --> 01:24:01,773
I've scratched your backs
and kept you outta jail.

1081
01:24:02,300 --> 01:24:05,554
Well, now it's time
to say thank you.

1082
01:24:06,289 --> 01:24:11,793
Go show those little bitches
you don't mess with Roman Sionis.

1083
01:24:12,289 --> 01:24:15,773
Half a mil to whoever
brings me the girl alive.

1084
01:24:16,164 --> 01:24:18,575
The rest you can kill.

1085
01:24:24,206 --> 01:24:26,206
Dope.

1086
01:24:27,206 --> 01:24:30,762
Oh, no, no, no. Not that one.
Sentimental value. Try this.

1087
01:24:33,196 --> 01:24:35,813
- You're kidding.
- What? Gotta take care of the girls.

1088
01:24:35,863 --> 01:24:38,126
Isn't this fun?
It's just like a sleepover.

1089
01:24:38,206 --> 01:24:40,230
We should order pizza.
Make cosmos.

1090
01:24:40,310 --> 01:24:42,679
- Harley, focus. Yeah.
- Okay.

1091
01:24:43,373 --> 01:24:46,220
Hey, nice. What the hell is up
with this bow and arrow shtick?

1092
01:24:46,300 --> 01:24:49,961
It's not a fucking bow and arrow.
It's a crossbow. I'm not 12.

1093
01:24:50,010 --> 01:24:53,136
- Love this chick. She's got rage issues.
- I don't have rage issues.

1094
01:24:53,216 --> 01:24:55,783
You know,
psychologically speaking,

1095
01:24:56,175 --> 01:24:58,230
vengeance rarely brings
the catharsis we hope for.

1096
01:24:58,310 --> 01:24:59,261
Yeah.

1097
01:24:59,341 --> 01:25:02,648
Are we ready?
Bad guys, just outside.

1098
01:25:06,341 --> 01:25:08,575
Shit. Get down.

1099
01:25:09,373 --> 01:25:11,564
Down here!

1100
01:25:12,383 --> 01:25:14,095
Cass!

1101
01:25:14,175 --> 01:25:16,178
- Follow me!
- Go, go, go, go!

1102
01:25:16,258 --> 01:25:18,258
Go!

1103
01:25:22,196 --> 01:25:24,196
Holy shit!

1104
01:25:44,300 --> 01:25:46,084
What?

1105
01:25:46,164 --> 01:25:48,126
You are so cool.

1106
01:25:48,206 --> 01:25:50,206
Okay. This way.

1107
01:25:58,279 --> 01:26:00,279
Get ready, ladies.

1108
01:26:10,362 --> 01:26:13,241
Don't worry. You're gonna make it.
Okay? Okay.

1109
01:26:13,321 --> 01:26:16,313
What the... Go! Go, go, go!

1110
01:26:16,393 --> 01:26:18,393
Fuck.

1111
01:26:20,248 --> 01:26:22,248
Shit.

1112
01:26:31,237 --> 01:26:33,237
Whoa. Shit!

1113
01:26:52,185 --> 01:26:54,185
Motherfucker.

1114
01:27:06,331 --> 01:27:08,282
Let me go!

1115
01:27:08,362 --> 01:27:10,637
Gotcha.

1116
01:27:11,289 --> 01:27:12,251
This way!

1117
01:27:12,331 --> 01:27:14,178
Come on. Come on. It's okay.
Come on.

1118
01:27:14,258 --> 01:27:16,199
You shouldn't
have to see this.

1119
01:27:16,279 --> 01:27:19,168
Here, hold on to this for me, okay?
That's all you think about.

1120
01:27:19,248 --> 01:27:21,248
Just close your eyes
and hold it tight. Okay?

1121
01:27:22,196 --> 01:27:24,627
Here. Get down. Come on.
You'll be safe.

1122
01:28:06,268 --> 01:28:08,268
Canary!

1123
01:28:09,175 --> 01:28:11,084
You okay?

1124
01:28:11,164 --> 01:28:13,164
We gotta go this way!

1125
01:28:14,393 --> 01:28:16,157
Ugh. More?

1126
01:28:16,237 --> 01:28:18,799
When the fuck did she have
time to do a shoe change?

1127
01:28:18,819 --> 01:28:20,479
Come on.

1128
01:28:26,331 --> 01:28:28,331
Thanks.

1129
01:28:41,227 --> 01:28:43,227
Duck!

1130
01:28:46,320 --> 01:28:48,313
- Hair tie?
- Yeah.

1131
01:28:48,393 --> 01:28:50,564
Ah, fuck!

1132
01:28:55,195 --> 01:28:57,195
I got him!

1133
01:28:59,362 --> 01:29:01,362
Get back here, kid!

1134
01:29:04,393 --> 01:29:06,606
Who's got the kid?

1135
01:29:19,154 --> 01:29:21,154
Get down!

1136
01:29:30,279 --> 01:29:33,585
Please, no more.

1137
01:29:38,132 --> 01:29:41,237
- So, forgive me yet?
- Get off me!

1138
01:29:45,227 --> 01:29:47,261
Anyone else hungry?
I know a great taco spot.

1139
01:29:47,341 --> 01:29:49,074
- I'm starving.
- I love tacos.

1140
01:29:49,154 --> 01:29:51,154
Really?

1141
01:29:58,310 --> 01:30:00,168
Down! Get down!

1142
01:30:00,248 --> 01:30:02,115
You're okay.
You're okay.

1143
01:30:02,195 --> 01:30:04,658
Just breathe. Just breathe.
Let me check it.

1144
01:30:07,154 --> 01:30:09,240
- Get off!
- I got you.

1145
01:30:09,320 --> 01:30:11,115
Ooh!

1146
01:30:11,195 --> 01:30:13,762
Aren't you glad you wore that?
Sexy and bulletproof.

1147
01:30:14,154 --> 01:30:16,313
Harley! No! Get off me!

1148
01:30:16,393 --> 01:30:19,302
- Harley!
- They got the kid. Shit!

1149
01:30:19,382 --> 01:30:23,563
We can't let them get her.
I trust you.

1150
01:30:24,226 --> 01:30:26,414
- One bullet?
- Please help me!

1151
01:30:26,447 --> 01:30:29,605
- Has anyone got any bullets?
- Fuck! I'm out.

1152
01:30:30,194 --> 01:30:32,667
I can't get out there.
I just need to get through.

1153
01:30:33,194 --> 01:30:37,083
- We gotta go. We gotta move.
- Guys, they're in the car.

1154
01:30:37,163 --> 01:30:40,594
- They're getting away.
- Get in there! -Get off!

1155
01:30:42,330 --> 01:30:44,302
Shit! I'm out.

1156
01:30:44,382 --> 01:30:46,626
Guys, come on.
They're closing in.

1157
01:30:47,392 --> 01:30:50,730
Canary, you know
what you have to do!

1158
01:30:51,247 --> 01:30:54,563
Cover your ears!
You better get her back.

1159
01:31:14,226 --> 01:31:16,657
<i>Told ya she had
a killer voice.</i>

1160
01:31:37,361 --> 01:31:39,361
Need a ride?

1161
01:32:04,361 --> 01:32:06,361
Get her!

1162
01:32:36,392 --> 01:32:38,730
Oh!

1163
01:32:49,257 --> 01:32:51,260
- Whip me!
- What?

1164
01:32:51,340 --> 01:32:53,340
- Whip me!
- Okay.

1165
01:33:01,153 --> 01:33:04,292
- Kid!
- Harley!

1166
01:33:04,372 --> 01:33:06,372
Shoot her!

1167
01:33:14,267 --> 01:33:17,615
- Harley!
- Hit the brakes!

1168
01:33:37,163 --> 01:33:39,163
No!

1169
01:33:51,330 --> 01:33:53,330
Uh-oh.

1170
01:34:19,361 --> 01:34:21,361
Kid!

1171
01:34:33,184 --> 01:34:35,184
Harley!

1172
01:34:52,246 --> 01:34:55,176
Well, we always did share
a love of the dramatic.

1173
01:34:55,256 --> 01:34:57,256
Didn't we?

1174
01:34:58,361 --> 01:35:00,656
And look at us now.

1175
01:35:01,423 --> 01:35:04,239
But don't you see?
You're trying to kill me.

1176
01:35:04,319 --> 01:35:06,792
I'm the only one
who can protect you!

1177
01:35:09,392 --> 01:35:12,166
You know you can't
stand on your own, Quinn.

1178
01:35:12,246 --> 01:35:14,246
You're not the type!

1179
01:35:14,402 --> 01:35:17,740
But me? You need me!

1180
01:35:32,298 --> 01:35:35,667
Here's the thing, Romy baby.

1181
01:35:37,298 --> 01:35:41,312
Your protection is based on the fact
that people are scared of you.

1182
01:35:41,392 --> 01:35:43,761
Just like
they're scared of Mr. J.

1183
01:35:49,256 --> 01:35:51,761
But I'm the one
they should be scared of.

1184
01:35:52,204 --> 01:35:54,281
Not you, and not Mr. J.

1185
01:35:54,361 --> 01:35:57,740
'Cause
I'm Harley fucking Quinn.

1186
01:36:05,277 --> 01:36:07,277
Shit.

1187
01:36:08,215 --> 01:36:11,281
- That was super embarrassing.
- Hmm. Sure was.

1188
01:36:11,361 --> 01:36:15,636
You think you can beat me?
You're a fucking moron.

1189
01:36:16,402 --> 01:36:18,698
I'm sorry, kid.

1190
01:36:19,236 --> 01:36:22,708
And I'm sorry I tried to sell you.
That was a dick move.

1191
01:36:24,246 --> 01:36:26,246
For what it's worth,

1192
01:36:27,215 --> 01:36:30,688
you made me want to be
a less terrible person.

1193
01:36:31,329 --> 01:36:32,291
Ew.

1194
01:36:32,371 --> 01:36:36,166
If we're apologizing for shit,
I should tell you something.

1195
01:36:36,246 --> 01:36:40,156
- Excuse me!
- I stole something from you.

1196
01:36:40,236 --> 01:36:43,322
- You slippery-fingered little turd.
- I took your ring.

1197
01:36:43,402 --> 01:36:45,594
My ring?

1198
01:36:47,402 --> 01:36:49,402
Dope.

1199
01:37:09,194 --> 01:37:12,019
- Cass! Harley!
- We're okay.

1200
01:37:16,204 --> 01:37:18,204
- You okay?
- Yeah.

1201
01:37:18,308 --> 01:37:20,618
- He's gone?
- Mmm-hmm.

1202
01:37:20,627 --> 01:37:24,625
- Good. Fuck that guy.
- Yeah. Tacos?

1203
01:37:25,866 --> 01:37:28,322
No, but seriously.
You were very impressive with that bow.

1204
01:37:28,402 --> 01:37:31,155
- Very impressive.
- It's a crossbow.

1205
01:37:31,235 --> 01:37:33,321
- I appreciate that. Thank you.
- Morning margaritas!

1206
01:37:33,401 --> 01:37:35,123
Thank you. I got you.

1207
01:37:35,203 --> 01:37:38,175
- You drink, right, kid?
- I don't think so.

1208
01:37:38,255 --> 01:37:40,306
And I love that fucking
name, Huntress.

1209
01:37:40,331 --> 01:37:41,356
- Really?
- Yeah.

1210
01:37:41,412 --> 01:37:44,280
- Oh, great name.
- Wow.

1211
01:37:44,360 --> 01:37:47,175
Um... I really like
how you were able

1212
01:37:47,255 --> 01:37:49,727
to kick so high
in those tight pants.

1213
01:37:49,790 --> 01:37:52,300
- Yeah, that is cool.
- Thanks.

1214
01:37:52,380 --> 01:37:55,603
Thanks for the car.

1215
01:37:56,349 --> 01:37:58,217
You're welcome.

1216
01:37:58,297 --> 01:38:02,645
Kid, if that burrito doesn't
make you shit, I don't know what will.

1217
01:38:04,235 --> 01:38:06,235
Give me a minute.

1218
01:38:06,422 --> 01:38:08,165
Yes!

1219
01:38:08,245 --> 01:38:10,593
Right.

1220
01:38:11,979 --> 01:38:14,142
I've given her prune juice,
laxatives.

1221
01:38:14,148 --> 01:38:16,232
I mean, the kid's got
a stomach made of steel.

1222
01:38:16,283 --> 01:38:18,352
And you know what?
I owe you an apology.

1223
01:38:18,432 --> 01:38:20,311
Me?

1224
01:38:21,088 --> 01:38:23,832
I underestimated you.
And I'm sorry.

1225
01:38:25,659 --> 01:38:27,659
I'm used to it.

1226
01:38:27,742 --> 01:38:31,059
Uh, Harley!
Bring the colander.

1227
01:38:32,679 --> 01:38:36,027
- Ladies.
- Have fun with that.

1228
01:38:36,721 --> 01:38:39,132
So, what now?

1229
01:38:39,669 --> 01:38:42,693
Sionis is gone, but it's just a matter
of time before some other asshole

1230
01:38:42,773 --> 01:38:45,568
- tries to finish what he started.
- Right.

1231
01:38:45,648 --> 01:38:48,986
We gotta clean this city
from the inside out.

1232
01:38:49,607 --> 01:38:52,683
Does she always talk like the cop in
a bad '80s movie, or is that just me?

1233
01:38:52,763 --> 01:38:55,610
- Fuck you. And fuck you.
- What?

1234
01:38:55,690 --> 01:38:59,537
- I mean, we were amazing there.
- Yeah! Hell yeah!

1235
01:38:59,617 --> 01:39:02,579
I agree completely.
So I'll do that, as well.

1236
01:39:02,659 --> 01:39:04,652
- Thank you.
- Right.

1237
01:39:04,732 --> 01:39:06,732
Whoa. Whoa, whoa!

1238
01:39:08,690 --> 01:39:11,752
- She stole my fucking car!
- What?

1239
01:39:14,794 --> 01:39:17,585
- I'm sorry.
<i>- I know what you're thinking.</i>

1240
01:39:17,645 --> 01:39:20,537
You think I'm a dick
after all that.

1241
01:39:20,617 --> 01:39:23,693
But you heard what the cop
said. Sionis is gone.

1242
01:39:23,773 --> 01:39:29,121
And those guys?
They're gonna be just fine.

1243
01:39:29,721 --> 01:39:33,506
<i>Montoya's boss picked up
the gangbangers at the Booby Trap.</i>

1244
01:39:33,586 --> 01:39:36,527
<i>And took all the credit
while he was at it.</i>

1245
01:39:36,607 --> 01:39:38,607
<i>Again.</i>

1246
01:39:43,586 --> 01:39:46,652
<i>It was the kick in the balls she needed
to see that she had nothing to prove</i>

1247
01:39:46,732 --> 01:39:49,027
<i>to those blowhard assholes.</i>

1248
01:39:49,617 --> 01:39:52,017
<i>She quit the same day.</i>

1249
01:39:56,627 --> 01:39:58,610
<i>We got the secret bank codes
off the diamond.</i>

1250
01:39:58,690 --> 01:40:01,163
<i>And Huntress
got her family money back.</i>

1251
01:40:02,607 --> 01:40:05,690
<i>She's using it to fund
a little crime-fighting outfit.</i>

1252
01:40:08,575 --> 01:40:11,986
<i>They call themselves
the Birds of Prey.</i>

1253
01:40:12,627 --> 01:40:15,204
<i>I call them
dorky little do-gooders.</i>

1254
01:40:17,732 --> 01:40:21,714
<i>The rock itself was worth a
chunk of change, so I pawned it.</i>

1255
01:40:21,794 --> 01:40:24,506
<i>And I invested the cash
in a little startup</i>

1256
01:40:24,586 --> 01:40:26,586
<i>making waves in the East End.</i>

1257
01:40:29,742 --> 01:40:31,662
<i>Oh! And I found Bruce.</i>

1258
01:40:31,742 --> 01:40:34,526
<i>He was wandering
around Chinatown.</i>

1259
01:40:34,606 --> 01:40:38,121
<i>I guess it proves the theory that
hyenas really do have nine lives.</i>

1260
01:40:58,659 --> 01:41:02,017
<i>Yeah, yeah.
I made the kid my apprentice.</i>

1261
01:41:02,565 --> 01:41:04,565
<i>Call me a softy.</i>

1262
01:41:05,565 --> 01:41:07,565
I dare ya.

1263
01:41:10,752 --> 01:41:12,752
Mmm!

