[young man] Before Rome,
before Babylon,
before the pyramids,
there was Kahndaq.
The first self-governing people
on Earth,
Kahndaq was a center of power
and enlightenment.
For centuries, they thrived.
-But then...
-[people screaming]
...came King Ahk-Ton.
Using the army to seize power,
Ahk-Ton became a tyrant.
But he had
even darker ambitions.
Obsessed with dark magic,
Ahk-Ton's real goal was
to forge the Crown of Sabbac.
If infused with the powers
of the six demons
-of the ancient world...
-[thunder crashing]
...it would make Ahk-Ton
invincible.
To make the crown,
he needed Eternium.
A rare mineral
of magic properties,
-found only in Kahndaq.
-[miners grunting]
So he enslaved his own people...
...and forced them to dig.
[grunting with effort]
Eternium.
[miners yelling in Kahndaqi]
[young man, in English] Kahndaq
was teetering on the brink.
[men shouting in Kahndaqi]
[young man]
What they needed...
Get off him!
[shouting subsides]
[young man] ...was a hero.
Why are we fighting each other?
Remember who our real enemy is!
Come with me.
Look!
Eternium.
Let me see that.
-[tools clattering]
-[birds calling in distance]
The King thanks you.
He's supposed to reward him.
Is that right?
I want what I'm owed.
Hm.
You want a reward?
-[miner grunts]
-[boy gasps]
The King thanks you for your service.
[miner screaming]
[panting]
You want the King's reward too?
No, but my son accepts the King's mercy.
I won't always be here to protect you.
I don't need protection.
I want to be free.
If we fight together,
we could overthrow the King.
Let someone else be the hero...
...the graveyards are full of them.
Stop dreaming and go back to work.
[miners grunting]
[young man] Someone
to hold the hopes of the people.
Even when all hope seems lost.
If we had more heroes...
...then maybe our freedom
wouldn't be a dream.
[soldier yells]
Freedom!
-[boy grunts]
-[soldiers yell]
[miners yelling, cheering]
[young man] King Ahk-Ton
knew that this spark
could quickly ignite a fire.
And so, he ordered
that it be snuffed out.
[crowd chanting]
They thought they were
getting a martyr.
Instead...
-[murmurs in Kahndaqi]
-...they got a miracle.
[low voices chanting]
[young man]
The Council of Wizards,
the magical guardians
of the Earth...
You have been chosen.
[young man]
...sought to restore the balance.
The stamina of Shul!
-They empowered him with the gifts
-The swiftness of Heru!
-Of the ancient gods.
-The strength of Amon!
And turned a boy...
The wisdom of Zehuti!
The power of Aten!
-The courage of Mehen!
-...into a champion.
"Shazam!"
[thunder crashing]
Hurry.
Give it to me!
[young man] But the crown
had already been completed.
Give it to me!
[people chattering excitedly]
[young man] And when the Champion
arrived at the palace
to challenge him...
...King Ahk-Ton summoned
its demonic power.
In the ensuing battle,
the palace was destroyed,
but the Champion was victorious.
The wizards hid
the Crown of Sabbac
so that it would never again
fall into the hands of man.
And the Champion
was never heard from again.
["Bullet With Butterfly Wings"
by Smashing Pumpkins playing]
Today, Kahndaq is occupied
by international mercenaries,
the Intergang, the latest
in a series of foreign invaders.
But legend says,
whenever Kahndaq needs him most,
the Champion will return to
restore freedom to the people.
It has been a long, long wait.
[horn honks]
[soldier] Hey!
[vendors shouting, indistinct]
Show me your papers.
[horn blaring]
[checkpoint soldier]
Move it along!
[checkpoint leader]
Have your documentation ready.
[indistinct chatter]
[driver] It's all our
three documents, yeah?
Don't judge the picture,
it's after my girlfriend
broke up with me.
[soldier 2] Open the back.
Need a look inside.
-[indistinct chatter]
-[faint radio chatter]
Yeah, it's unlocked, man.
It's just a bunch of old TVs.
I'm an electrician.
-Hey!
-[young man grunting]
Watch where you're going.
You know the drill,
back of the line.
Come on, man,
you see me every day.
[checkpoint leader]
And every day I tell ya,
if it's got wheels,
it's a vehicle.
Back of the line, mate.
You're not my mate.
I'm heartbroken.
Now, go on, piss off.
No, what you are
is a neo-imperialist enforcer,
from halfway around the world,
sent here to steal
my country's natural resources,
strip-mine our sacred lands,
pollute our water,
oppress our heritage,
and make us wait in lines
all day.
-[bangs van door]
-Hey, boss man. Can I go?
Hey!
Go on, get out of here.
-Yeah, yeah.
-[thumps door twice]
[driver] Adrianna, we're clear.
Kahndaq isn't safe
for us anymore.
Let's just move the crown first,
and then we can
worry about safe.
I got Intergang
watching my house.
I gave up my job
at the university
and moved four times.
It doesn't mean I'm gonna
abandon my country.
I'm just saying, no one stays
a step ahead of them forever.
We can't wait for things
to cool down this time.
If I'm right, they're days away
from finding it.
[thudding]
What are you doing?
I want to come with you.
You know it's too dangerous.
You shouldn't have
gotten involved.
Come on, I want to help you
beat those bastards.
Adrianna,
keep your head down, please.
-You want to be a hero, huh?
- I do, yeah.
Go home, do your homework.
Your time will come one day,
but not today, son.
Go!
Go, little man. You did good.
That would get you a fortune
on the black market.
Is that real Eternium?
Show us a little magic.
It doesn't work like that,
it's unrefined.
You guys should get some rest.
I thought Intergang
seized all the old relics.
Hey, come on. Stop it.
I'm just curious how she got it.
My grandmother gave it to me.
How did she get it?
It's not a museum piece.
It's a family heirloom,
going all the way back
to the days
when Kahndaq was free.
You happy now?
Cool story.
And all I inherited
was a sweater.
That's not true. Baba left you
his van and his bald spot.
You know, some women
like a bald spot.
Curly on the outside,
smooth on the inside. You know?
[man] Are you sure about this?
[Adrianna] The inscriptions
we found are clear.
And I'm positive
about that translation.
There is something
inside that mountain.
-[wind blowing]
-[birds calling]
[man] What if it really
is the crown? Then what?
It's a source of great power.
Who gets to keep it?
No one.
We hide it again someplace else.
Get it out of the country
if we have to.
It is too dangerous
for anyone to have.
This is it?
Not yet.
-Are you coming?
-Eh, bad knee. I'll keep watch.
['Baby Come Back" by Player
playing on car stereo]
[slurping drink]
[rock crumbling]
This way. Almost there.
"Men were given the gift
of magic,
but their hearts
were too easily corrupted.”
[pebbles, dirt clattering]
Keep reading.
"The ultimate power
was banished from the Earth
and hidden... here."
Until now.
[man] This mountain has kept
the Crown of Sabbac safe
for five thousand years.
We're 100 percent,
totally, like, no take-backs
certain that we want to move it?
We don't have a choice.
What happened to Ishmael?
[dirt clattering]
Great.
Don't worry, I'll find him.
['Baby Come Back"
continues playing]
[singing along]
♪ Baby come back ♪
♪ Oh, baby... on me ♪
♪ I was wrong ♪
♪ And I just can't live
Without you ♪
♪ Baby come back... ♪
[man screaming]
Samir?
Samir, what happened?
-[choking, muttering]
-What?
I can't hear you.
What are you saying?
[gunshot]
Don't move! Unless you want
to join your mate.
-[mercenary] Stay where you are!
-[men shouting, indistinct]
Oh, hey. Oh, hey. Hey...
-[Ishmael] "Turn back.”
-[gasps]
-[sighs in relief]
-That's what it says, no?
Yes.
Where is Samir?
Claustrophobic. Needed some air.
-Is this the way to the crown?
-I think so.
[Adrianna] It's a tomb.
"Speak not his power,
so he may suffer
a dreamless sleep
for all eternity." Teth Adam.
The slave who became champion
and defeated the king.
The legend was true.
Kahndaq...
really did have a hero once.
If he was such a hero,
why'd they bury him down here?
The crown.
[panting]
[exhales]
[grunts loudly]
[panting]
[sighs]
[Ishmael struggling]
[head mercenary] It's over.
Now, give me the crown.
Run, Addy! Run!
-[grunts]
-[machine gun fire]
-[head mercenary] Hold fire!
-[gunfire ceases]
Don't hit the crown! Get her!
[grunts]
-[mercenary] Go! Move.
-[mercenary 2] Circle around!
-Get down!
-[grunting]
-Say goodbye to your brother.
-[panting]
In five...
-...four...
-[gasping]
.three...
...two...
...one...
[Adrianna] I'm over here.
One? You let them get to one?
[Adrianna panting loudly]
[struggling]
[grunts in pain]
Any last words?
Please tell my son...
"Mightiest of mortals...
...god of gods,
Six Immortal Elders by name..."
What?
-"Shazam!"
-[loud rumbling]
[men screaming]
Who the hell is that?
You wouldn't believe me
if I told you.
[men muttering fearfully]
[rocks hissing]
[tense muttering]
Check him out.
Boss say you go.
Chief say your turn.
[seething under breath]
Hey, amigo.
Let me see your hands.
[grunting, choking]
-[screaming]
-[electricity crackling]
Open fire!
Your magic is weak.
Go. Go.
[men screaming]
[screaming, grunts]
[agonized scream]
[screaming]
We need immediate backup!
Send everything you've got!
[body crashes]
[gunfire continues]
[man yelling, screams]
Ishmael!
[screaming]
[gunfire echoing]
[mercenaries screaming]
[gasping]
[Adrianna] Let's go!
[brother]
This is as fast as I can go.
[helicopters whirring]
Samir! What happened?
What didn't happen!
[panting]
Samir fell off of a cliff.
I had a gun to my head.
Ishmael is buried
under a mountain.
And you summoned
some flying magic man.
All for what? Nothing!
-Oh.
-Not for nothing.
Light him up.
Shit! Where the hell
did he come from?
Rotor out! Go! Go!
-[engine whining]
-I can't maintain altitude!
[both screaming]
[men shouting]
[yelling]
["Paint It Black"
by Rolling Stones playing]
[bullets whining]
[all screaming]
Oh, shit.
[Adrianna] Stop! Stop the van!
[window cranks creaking]
[panting nervously]
Behind you!
Did he just catch a rocket?
[gasping]
[debris whistling]
[panting softly]
God willing,
we won't see him again.
[gasps]
[Adrianna exhales]
Wait. Hey! Hey!
What are you doing?
Don't touch him,
he's made of lightning.
[Adrianna] Good point.
You get him,
you're the electrician.
[flybike pilot]
Raptor team, come in.
What's your status?
[head mercenary coughing]
Help me. [panting]
I told you to make it look real,
not punch me in the face.
-[head mercenary gasping]
-[gunshot]
[flybike pilot, over radio]
Raptor team, come in.
What's your status?
Status is that everyone is dead.
Ishmael, is that you?
What happened?
The crown wasn't the only thing
waiting for us down here.
-Do you have it?
-No.
But I know who does.
Copy that.
We're en route to your location.
[lead mercenary, on recording]
We need immediate backup.
Send everything you've got!
[TV reporter]
This rare, magical mineral
has been mined for centuries...
[TV reporter 2]
...reports of an Eternium blast.
It is unknown who or why...
[TV reporter 3]
...decimated a number of troops.
[TV reporter 4]
...an unidentified male.
This being is somehow able
to harness...
What do you think?
I think this loose cannon
needs to be locked down
before innocent people
start getting hurt.
Oh, and good morning
to you, too.
Shove it up your ass, Carter.
He's been asleep
for 5,000 years.
He'll be disoriented at first.
The longer he has to adapt,
the harder it will be
to take him down.
Wheels up in 30.
Who's on the team?
[bicycle rattling]
-[beeping]
-[female voice] Welcome.
Please state your name
for identification.
Uh, hi. I'm Maxine Hunkel.
I'm here to see Mr. Hall.
Confirmed. Welcome, Maxine.
Thanks!
[Carter] Maxine Hunkel,
aka Cyclone.
Wind manipulation powers,
computer skills, smart as hell.
Basically a tornado
with a 167 IQ.
Sounds delightful.
But please tell me
you found someone
who can pack a punch.
That's where Atom Smasher
comes in.
Al Rothstein, nephew
to the original Atom Smasher.
-Inherited his uncle's powers.
-[phone vibrating]
-How's my suit? Does it fit?
-No, yeah. It's perfect.
Thank you again
for letting me borrow it.
You know, I used to watch you
all the time as a kid?
This is literally the only thing
that I'd ever wanted in my--
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Don't let anything happen to it.
It's vintage.
And don't let anything
happen to you, either.
Don't do anything crazy.
You listen to Carter.
I'm gonna make you proud,
Uncle Al. I promise.
They seem green.
That's why I called in Kent.
Kent's been out of action
for a little while,
but I can't do this without him.
Takes magic to fight magic
and the man's got
nearly god-level powers.
It might take
a lot more than that.
Are you sure they can take him?
Waller, you find us a cell
that can hold him...
...we'll take care of the rest.
Good luck.
This is gonna be fun.
[grunting]
-[sharp scream]
-[gasps]
[exhales]
-[chauffeur] We're here, sir.
-[groans] Hm?
Oh, right.
Was I staring again?
Only half an hour or so, sir.
Maybe next time, honk the horn.
Of course, sir.
[Cyclone] So what's the op?
[Hawkman] We're headed to Kahndaq
to apprehend and contain
a Class-A rogue metahuman.
[Atom Smasher]
I didn't bring a passport.
We don't need passports.
We're the Justice Society.
[Cyclone] Is this entirely made
out of Nth metal?
[Hawkman]
Everything down to the screws.
Completely indestructible.
I'll be in the cockpit
if you need me.
It's pretty cool.
You got any snacks?
It takes a lot of energy
to smash atoms.
[jet powering up]
Here.
Oh! Thanks.
I'm Al, by the way.
Maxine.
[electronics humming]
[chewing] What do you do?
Wind. You?
I grow.
Cool.
[woman wailing]
[sobbing]
[young man] Whoa!
Don't worry about that.
I can get another one.
Uh, my mom's
not much of a doctor,
but you should probably
leave th--
[laughing] Or do that.
I know you have a lot
to catch up on.
But I was thinking
we could help each other.
-Move.
-I'm Amon, by the way.
I didn't ask for your name.
You're Teth Adam, right?
Everyone in Kahndaq
knows your story.
-I said move.
-My mom said you took out
a bunch of Intergang soldiers
in the desert.
Because they wouldn't move
out of my way.
So you can really fly
and stop bullets,
'cause that's really crucial
to my plan.
And is it really you stopping
the bullets or is it the suit?
Wait, what's your top speed?
I'm sure you're fast,
but how fast?
Like Flash fast?
Wait, did you really not have
mirrors back then?
Wow, I guess a lot does change
in 5,000 years.
Five thousand years?
Yeah, that's how long
you were in the tomb.
Until my mom woke you up.
So you've got stopping bullets,
check; flying, check;
and lightning thing,
that's a big check.
[traffic humming faintly]
I don't know this place.
This is your home.
Then my home is gone.
What happened to the crown?
-Too much?
-[sighs]
[Adrianna] You know it's
cursed with demons, right?
[music from "The Good, The Bad,
and The Ugly" playing on TV]
"Life is the...
only path to death.”
No shit.
"Teth Adam was a Bronze Age
Kahndaqi demi-god.”
"He defeated King Ahk-Ton
in approximately 2,600 BC."
There. That's you. See?
That's the statue
they built of you.
And now you're back.
Our country's been oppressed
by one invader after another
ever since you left.
My point is,
Kahndaq still isn't free.
We could really use a superhero
right about now.
I'm no hero.
[Amon] What?
Superman, Batman, Aquaman...
You're way more stacked
than any of them.
And they're not coming
to Kahndaq to save us.
But you could stop Intergang
all by yourself,
just like you did King Ahk-Ton.
You're our only hope.
-[Karim exclaims]
-[gasps]
[dramatic music
continues on TV]
[gasping]
-Wizards.
-[chuckles]
I can fix it. Don't worry.
I'm not a wizard.
[tense breathing]
[laughing] Hey, Mom. He's awake.
I told you
not to go in your room.
It was you who spoke.
You woke me.
I didn't have a choice.
I'd be dead if it hadn't worked.
The men in my tomb,
they were your enemies?
Yes.
Then your enemies
are vanquished,
condemned to the eternal sleep
of the damned.
Actually, we still have a lot of
enemies that need vanquishing.
Then destroy them.
Intergang have guns and flybikes
and Eternium rockets.
We have my mom.
Prove your strength.
Destroy your enemy
and all he cares about.
Make him beg for mercy,
but deny it
until his final breath.
Interesting, okay?
I appreciate
what you did for me,
but I do not want you
teaching my son violence.
I understand.
You want his father
-to teach him violence.
-[coughs]
-Gross, that's my brother.
-That's my sister.
-His father's dead.
-I'm sorry.
Who do you want
to teach him violence then?
Yeah, Mom. Who do you want
to teach me violence?
No one.
I want a champion to help
free Kahndaq from Intergang.
Please, help us.
[panting]
[Amon] Wait! Wait.
-Where are you going?
-I shouldn't be here.
You don't feel any loyalty
to us at all?
Not really, no.
You're not seeing
the full possibilities here.
I don't know what it was like
in ancient times,
but having superpowers is
kind of a big deal in our world.
Maybe clean up your outfit
a little bit,
get a cape, change your name.
Teth Adam is a very strong name.
It's a little outdated.
And you definitely
need a catchphrase.
Something blackout
bad-ass to say
right before you absolutely
cook some dude.
I don't waste words on the dead.
Well, yeah, kind of like that,
but more catchy.
I was thinking, like,
"Tell them the Man in Black
sent you."
-Them?
-You know, gods, demons...
Whoever's waiting for us
in the afterlife.
And you wear a lot of black, so
we should really lean into that.
My point is,
you could be famous.
Magazines, lunch boxes,
video games.
And the superhero industrial
complex is worth a lot of money.
I don't need a box for my lunch.
Anyone you've ever known
is dead.
What else are you gonna do?
[people exclaiming]
Wait! Where are you going?
[people chattering excitedly]
Waller's file needs a bit
to be desired.
Most of this was
considered a myth
until yesterday afternoon.
He's a bad man, Kent.
What else do you need to know?
When you've seen as many
different futures as I have,
you cease to believe
in absolutes.
[wry chuckle]
What are you laughing at?
I'm not laughing.
That was a smirk.
I know. That's how you laugh.
I've missed having you around
to spout old cryptic shit
like that.
Almost as much as I've missed
having you around
to ignore all my advice.
Carter...
This is not a very good plan.
Yeah, well...
A bad plan is better than
no plan at all.
If only there were
a third option.
[sucking on mint]
[Cyclone] I wouldn't touch that
if I was you.
Why not?
"Cause that helmet
is from another planet.
It's millions of years old.
It chooses who it lets touch it.
-Like Kent?
-Yeah.
Like, Kent is literally
possessed when he puts it on.
What happens
if I touch it anyway?
Soul crushing terror?
Or... something.
So we should probably
put a towel on it, right?
[Hawkman] Coming up on it.
Ready stations in five.
Hey, why is this Adam dude
so pissed off?
He's not some dude.
He's a weapon
of mass destruction.
You don't have to
raise your hand.
Question: if he's so powerful,
how are we supposed to stop him?
If we can get him
to say the word, "Shazam,”
Teth Adam will lose his power.
And we're hoping since he's had
a few thousand years
to sleep it off,
we can peacefully negotiate
the terms of his existence.
From the footage you showed us,
he doesn't really seem like
a "peacefully negotiate"
kind of guy.
Correct.
Look alive.
We're here.
[sighing]
-[entry bell chimes]
-[townspeople chattering]
[sobbing]
[wailing]
Forgive me.
[indistinct chatter]
[Amon] This is a message
-for all Intergang soldiers.
-Hey! Stop!
Kahndaq has its own
official superhero now.
[grunting loudly]
Teth Adam!
[quietly] Please.
-There he is! Move!
-[people exclaiming]
-Teth Adam!
-[checkpoint leader] Move!
-Teth Adam--! [grunting]
-[grunts]
Get up!
Who's gonna save you now, mate?
The statue?
[Adrianna] That's my son.
He's just a boy.
He doesn't know what he's doing.
What are you doing?
Hang on. I recognize you.
Where is the crown?
-[grunting]
-Let's go!
[Adrianna grunts]
[crowd murmuring]
[screaming]
You could've showed up
a bit sooner.
But that was dope.
We need backup down here.
[gun clicking]
[music from "The Good,
The Bad and The Ugly" playing]
[grunting]
[screaming]
[screams, grunts]
[Amon laughs]
Tell them
the Man in Black sent you.
Well, yes, but not to me.
Say it to the bad guys.
But before you zap them.
-Catchphrase, then Kill.
-Yes.
[machine guns firing]
[tower soldiers screaming]
[grunts]
He's here.
You sense his presence?
No.
I assume he's the only person
in Kahndaq that can do that.
[Cyclone gasps]
[soldiers gasping, whimpering]
Fate and I'll take the lead.
Listen...
Now, you two hang back
'til we call you.
We're the anvil,
you're the hammer.
You're ready.
-[soldiers screaming]
-Uh, he just dropped the, um...
-[soldiers screaming faintly]
-Shit!
[wind whistling]
Be prepared.
[electronic alert beeping]
Um...
[screaming]
[both yelling]
Behind you!
[soldiers yelling]
[grunts]
[crowd jeering]
Let us be!
I don't know their crimes,
but whatever they are,
these men should face
due process.
[crowd cheering]
Then let the gods
make their judgment.
-Yeah!
You don't look like
an Intergang.
We're the Justice Society.
Our mission is to protect
global stability.
We're here to restore peace
to Kahndaq.
And we will use force
if necessary.
Force is always necessary.
[Dr. Fate] Teth Adam.
We know who you are
and what you are capable of.
There's no place for you
in the world of man.
You have two choices:
Kneel or die.
I was a slave until I died.
Then I was reborn a god.
I kneel before no one.
[grunts]
Fate, give me a distraction.
[people screaming]
Just say, "Shazam."
We all go home.
[grunts]
I don't have a home.
[loud grunt]
[grunting with effort]
[strained grunt]
[yelling]
[shuddering grunt]
[both grunting]
Whoo!
Look at that suit. It's cool.
-Thanks. You, too.
-Thank you.
It was a hand-me-down.
It was from my uncle.
[Teth Adam & Hawkman grunting]
[Atom Smasher] Hawkman just
does not give up, does he?
[Cyclone] Nope.
[Hawkman yelling]
[loud impact boom]
Amon, where are you going? Wait!
To help him!
[grunts]
[chuckles]
[Dr. Fate] Cyclone, Smasher,
now is your time.
-[beeps]
-Let's roll!
What are you doing?
Hey! Hey, hey, hey!
[grunts]
[Adrianna cries out]
[sharp yell]
[groaning]
No!
[both grunting]
I'll be right there!
[gasps]
[guttural roaring]
[thunder crashing]
You have the Crown of Sabbac.
[loud impact]
[Dr. Fate grunts]
[roaring]
[grunting]
[all grunting]
[Dr. Fate] I can't hold him
much longer.
[yelling]
Move!
[sharp grunt]
[crackling energy builds]
I'm coming!
I'm zeroing in on your location!
[booming explosion]
[car alarms wailing]
[frustrated growl]
[grunting]
-[reverberating rumble]
-[gasps]
[crying out]
I got him! Guys, I got him.
It's, uh... it's me, Al.
In case you didn't recognize me.
There's something different
about you.
Can't quite put my finger on it.
You know, it's probably because
I'm six stories tall now.
But you-- You're like a tornado.
I thought the two of you
did great work.
First time out--
[clicks teeth] Bravo.
Thanks. I mean, I got a little
turned around back there,
but, uh,
it all worked out, right?
You're damn right it did.
Let's hope Waller
has that cell ready for him.
[powerful rumbling]
[televisions crackling]
[grunting] You want me
to keep my hand here, right?
You'd better not let him up.
[rumbling increases]
Uh... what do I-- what do I do?
Guys?
[loud grunt]
Whoo-hoo!
[crowd, chanting]
Long live the Champion!
[chanting continues]
[breath rumbling]
Yeah, he's definitely
still breathing.
Long live the Champion!
[chanting continues]
[chanting subsides]
Where are you going?
We need to go after him.
We're not strong enough.
Oh, well, maybe next time
use your powers of prediction
to figure that out
before we get our asses kicked.
I'm working on it.
Miss?
Excuse me, you mind
if I look in your bag?
Yes, I do mind.
Where are you going
with this, Kent?
She's got the Crown of Sabbac.
[Hawkman]
One catastrophe at a time.
We can't give him
a chance to regroup.
He's been spotted
entering the palace.
It's safe to say he's not
going there to surrender.
Why do you want Teth Adam
to surrender?
He's the Champion of Kahndaq.
Who are you?
The Justice Society?
We have been living
under military occupation
for 27 years,
and never seen you before.
You didn't come when Intergang
invaded our country,
when they stole our resources
and killed my husband.
But now, we finally
have our own hero
and you decide to fly down here
and save us?
Thank you, but... we're covered.
Go and protect international
stability someplace else.
Oh, and second,
I don't have the crown.
Let me spell it out for you.
Teth Adam can't be
Kahndaq's champion
because he is not a hero.
Tell that...
...to all the people
he just liberated.
I know what this looks like.
I... I do.
But I can assure you that my t--
-[loud crashing]
-[gasps]
[all exclaiming]
I am so sorry.
Was that expensive?
Me and you.
When we get back to the ship...
-Yes, sir.
-Me and you.
I...
Can we please
just see the crown?
I don't have it.
[indistinct chatter]
[horns honking]
We don't have time for this.
Teth Adam first, then the crown.
You don't have
any authority here.
Teth Adam has done nothing--
Teth Adam is not
who you think he is.
And how would you know?
We have access to ancient texts
that have been kept secret
for centuries.
And what exactly do these
supposed ancient texts say?
They say that his rage
nearly destroyed Kahndaq.
And we flew
all the way over here
to stop it from happening again.
[Hawkman]
You want to go in there alone?
Are you sure?
You want to go in and fight
Teth Adam again, be my guest.
But if you actually want
to resolve things peacefully,
without destroying
the rest of my city,
I'm your only shot.
[Teth Adam] You brought
the invaders with you.
They only want to talk.
They can talk. I won't listen.
When I was a little girl,
my grandmother told me the story
of how the Champion came
to this exact spot
to free the enslaved people
of Kahndaq
by defeating King Ahk-Ton
in battle.
But according
to the Justice Society,
that's not really what happened.
They say that you didn't
come here to seek justice.
Hurry.
Give it to me!
[crowd exclaiming]
[Adrianna] That you came
to exact revenge.
And in your anger...
[energy crackling]
Don't kill me.
I can give you anything you want.
This is what I want.
[Adrianna] ...your power grew
until it became uncontrollable.
[people screaming]
And the Council of Wizards
was forced to deem you unworthy
of the gifts that
you were granted.
We have chosen recklessly...
...and humanity has paid the price.
And now, Teth Adam...
...you must pay.
[energy building]
[yelling]
It wasn't your tomb
that I opened, was it?
It was your prison.
And now there's a statue of you.
Out of the hope that someday
Kahndaq's champion would return.
But it's built on a lie,
isn't it.
[Teth Adam]
I never said I was a hero.
I never claimed to be anything.
You may not have been a hero.
But that doesn't mean
that you can't be one now.
I will hear them out.
But if they choose to fight,
they choose to die.
[door unlocks, opens]
Uncle Karim!
I can't believe you're
sitting around watching TV
when the most epic day ever is--
-[Ishmael] In here, little man.
-[gasps]
Ishmael! My mom said
you got buried in the tomb.
Funny story, he didn't.
-[laughs]
-Where's Adrianna?
She's back at the square--
We should go bail her out
right now.
But she's the one
who sent me home
to make sure the crown's safe.
It is safe, okay?
Somewhere else.
Definitely not here.
Let-- Okay--
-Put the bag down.
-What are you doing?
Back away.
Put the bag down, now.
Give him the bag.
[crown clanking]
Very good. Back away.
Back away.
Okay, I'm--
[bag unzips]
[Ishmael] It's all going
to be okay, little man.
Let me teach you some history
that you've never learned
in one of your mother's classes.
When we had a powerful king,
Kahndaq used to be something
much better than free.
It used to be great.
Run, Amon, run!
[both men grunting]
-[gunshot]
-[Karim grunts loudly]
[panting]
[loud grunt]
Crash the building.
I lost the kid.
He has the crown.
[Atom Smasher chewing]
[Hawkman] We're here
to negotiate the terms
of your peaceful surrender.
I'm not peaceful.
Nor do I surrender.
[Dr. Fate] What have your powers
ever given to you?
Nothing but heartache.
You have no idea.
Then why are you making this
hard on us?
We both know
you're not supposed to be here.
It is you who
is not supposed to be here.
I want you all to leave Kahndaq
and never return.
Gladly,
with you as our prisoner.
How 'bout I rip
your little wings off instead?
I'd like to see you try.
Okay, more fighting
won't solve this.
-I disagree.
-Me, too.
Looks like we found
common ground.
This can only end one way.
[cell phone buzzing]
-[Amon] Mom?
-Amon.
I got home and Ishmael
was in the kitchen.
Ishmael's dead.
No, he shot Uncle Karim,
and he's after the crown.
[terse chatter]
[female soldier] Ground forces...
I'm hiding in our building,
and Intergang's here.
They're coming!
Intergang are after my son.
They don't want him,
they want the Crown of Sabbac.
I know you're not a hero.
But you're not a monster,
either.
I don't care what anyone says.
You saved me in that cave.
You didn't know me and your
first instinct was to save me.
I'm begging you.
Please, save my son.
[soldier]
Check the whole place clean.
[soldier 2]
Cover all access points!
-Keep looking!
-[indistinct radio chatter]
[soldier 3] Area's clear.
There! Take him!
[soldier 4]
Right there, right there!
[grunting loudly]
Move, move!
Don't shoot him, I need him!
[men shouting indistinctly]
[yelling]
[both shouting]
[grunts]
[soldier 5] He's going down,
he's going down!
[Amon grunts]
[gun cocking]
[yells]
[flybike pilot]
End of the road, kid!
[soldiers shouting]
Release the child.
-Whatever you say.
-[Amon yelling]
-[yelling]
-[Teth Adam grunts]
Yes! Thank you!
But maybe be more careful
with your word choice next time.
[men screaming]
Oh! And remember
your catchphrase!
-[gunfire]
-[men screaming]
Time to go, Amon.
[gunfire continues]
-Where's the crown?
-What crown?
-You want to be brave, eh?
-I want you to go to hell.
That's the plan, little man.
We're gonna go for a ride.
Come on.
[pilot yelling in pain]
[pilot gasping, panting]
Put me down! Put me down!
You should be more careful with
your word choice next time.
And tell them that
the Man in Black--
[horn blaring]
[car alarms wailing]
He's right behind me.
Where the hell is everybody?
Mom?
[Adrianna] Amon, where are you?
No, no, no. What?
I'm in one of their bikes.
What bikes?
[grunts]
[pilot grunting, screaming]
[Adrianna exclaims]
Amon!
Can you hear me?
Mom, I'm okay.
Shit!
Activate infrared.
[Hawkman grunts]
[Hawkman] What are you doing?
Searching for the child.
No, you're murdering people.
How else do I find the child?
I can help you, but no more
extrajudicial killings.
I don't need any help.
-[pilot yells]
-[Hawkman grunting]
[Hawkman, over radio]
Smasher, Cyclone!
What are you waiting for?
-Come on, let's go!
-Uh, okay.
Okay. I got this. I got this.
On the count of three.
One, two...
This feels a lot higher
than last time.
Whoa!
Ah! That was not cool!
-[tires squealing]
-Whoa, whoa, whoa. Hey.
Hey, guys. Slow down.
-[bullets ricocheting]
- I got you! I got you!
[powerful exhale]
[loud grunt]
[alarm beeping]
[grunting]
Hey, careful, dude!
I almost hit you.
[Hawkman grunts]
-[sharp grunt]
-[people exclaiming]
[Atom Smasher]
I am so sorry. I just--
I don't really have
peripheral vision in the mask.
It's my uncle's.
I'll get it tailored.
Me and you.
Roger that.
[yelps, whimpering]
[screaming]
[panting]
[Karim gasping, panting]
-Who are you?
-Call me Dr. Fate.
How bad is it, Doc? Am I dying?
I'm not that kind of doctor.
But don't worry,
I can see the future.
This isn't how you're
going to die.
How do I die, then?
Just stay away from electricity.
Wait, what? I'm an electrician.
How the hell
am I supposed to do that?
[sighing]
[engines whining]
[pilot yelling]
[yelling]
[pilot grunting]
[murmuring in Mandarin]
[grunting]
[grunts]
[whispering] Oh, God.
The Champion's coming for you.
You know that, right?
I'm counting on it.
[gasping, panting]
[grunts]
Please don't. [screaming]
Teth Adam. Where are you?
You followed me?
My mind and body can exist
in different places
at the same time.
Did you find the boy?
Caught one of the bikes,
but he didn't have the child.
Bring me the prisoner.
I'll break his mind.
Uh...
You killed him, didn't you.
[pilot screaming in distance]
[faint impact]
He didn't make it.
[Cyclone] The bullet's extracted.
The tissue damage
has been repaired.
Blood pressure, 120 over 81.
Heart rate's at 74 bpm.
He'll be back on his feet
in no time.
[exhales]
That is insane.
The nanobots did
most of the work.
No, no, no. I'm not gonna
let you downplay this.
I literally just witnessed
a miracle.
Mm-mm. [chuckles]
What? I say something stupid?
No, it's just you can transform
your molecular structure,
grow a hundred times
your own size.
You're an impossibility
and the world still amazes you.
-[chuckles]
-I don't know, it's...
It's cool.
Thank you.
But it's not as cool
as nanobots.
That's how you
do your wind thing.
Well, the "wind thing"
is called aerokinesis.
And the nanobots were injected
into my bloodstream
by this really
messed-up scientist
who kidnapped me
when I was 15.
I'm... so sorry.
No, you're good.
It seems like you
really turned it around.
Found your calling.
Hoping this is mine.
[crying softly]
[Dr. Fate] There's no point
in dwelling in the past.
It's already moved on from you.
Why did you say that?
You were blaming yourself
for trusting Ishmael.
Your thoughts are better spent
on the things you can change,
not those you can't.
[whispering] You see the future?
Tell me how I get my son back.
By trusting us.
Karim will live.
We will save Amon.
It's what we do.
I suppose they didn't have doors
in your day.
Well, of course we did.
That's how we entered rooms.
What I did there
is called sarcasm.
Where is Amon? Did you find him?
Not yet, but I will.
The men who took him
will suffer.
[soldiers grunting]
Maybe these guys can help.
There's an upside
to keeping prisoners.
They can answer our questions.
What did you do with my son?
[soldier grunting in pain]
-[blows landing]
-[men grunting]
-Adrianna. Adrianna.
-[panting]
I've learned that
in this modern world,
we shouldn't hurt our prisoners.
We should treat them
with dignity, respect.
[Adrianna] No.
Let's start with just
one simple question.
-Can either of you fly?
-[both gasp]
-[screaming]
-Shit.
I think I'll sit this one out.
[soldiers screaming]
[thunder crashing]
Tell me what you did with Amon.
You'd better not drop
those prisoners.
I'm not going to drop them.
I'm going to drop one of them.
Whoever answers first lives.
Where is he?
I don't know.
[screaming]
He's at our mine in the desert.
I can show-- [screaming]
-[Hawkman grunts]
-[gasping in fear]
[second soldier screaming
in distance]
Oh, you gotta be kidding me.
You said you wouldn't
hurt the prisoners.
That was sarcasm.
No, technically,
it was just a lie.
Intergang have a mine
in the desert.
-Amon is there.
-I know it.
It's near
the Al Hadidiyah Mountains.
Let's go.
[soldiers screaming, grunting]
I told you, stop killing people!
They look alive to me.
Because I saved them.
Well, that's why I waited
until you were there.
I got the information I needed,
no one died.
I did it your way.
He does have a point.
I know it got lost
in all the confusion,
but we still have some issues
to settle here.
We know where Amon is.
We have to go.
There is no "we" here.
There are only heroes
and there are villains.
You think yourself a hero,
but you would let these
criminals go free,
knowing that many more
will suffer at their hands
unless we end them now.
Heroes don't kill people.
Well, I do.
Here we go.
[both grunting]
[sharp grunt]
[yells]
[yelling]
[Hawkman yells, grunts]
[Teth Adam grunts in pain]
Is that what I think it is?
[Hawkman]
23 pounds of pure Eternium,
much denser than
typical artifacts of the period.
King must have had
a really strong neck.
No, it snapped
when I killed him.
What's that?
There's writing on the inside
of the rim.
"Life is the only path
to death."
That's what it says.
Life is the only path to death.
Well, that's
surprisingly obvious.
Could it have another meaning?
What if it means, like, um...
"Life is short.
You gotta hold on
to what you love."
Stop.
Deep.
It doesn't matter what it means.
It should be buried
under the ocean for eternity.
That's not far from what
we had in mind
for you when this is over.
Or I could bury you with it.
We can't get rid of it now.
It's the one thing
that Intergang wants.
Believe me,
I know more than anyone
what this crown is capable of.
But we have to keep it
until my son is safe.
Adrianna...
Trust me,
we will get your son back.
They don't care about him.
They just want to defeat me.
Hand it over.
We can't risk letting the crown
fall into the wrong hands.
We'll find another way.
No.
You like to split the world
into good and bad,
but that's easy to do when
you're the one drawing the line.
All I care about is Amon.
And until he is safe,
we're all on the same side.
And you...
you will work together.
Set a course
for the Al Hadidiyah Mountains.
We'll go in at dawn.
I hope you can be a team player.
I love teams.
That was sarcasm again, yes?
Very much so.
Good. Just checking.
A wise man
once told me a bad plan
is better than no plan at all.
That was before we had
a very bad plan.
Let it go.
I'd rather be fighting with him
than against him.
He's a murderer, Kent.
If he turns on us,
that kid is as good as dead.
You don't get to decide
who lives or dies.
That's... up to Fate.
What's the helmet telling you?
Somebody's gonna die.
Who is it, Atom Smasher?
It's Atom Smasher.
Surprisingly, no.
Is it me?
[intense scream]
When it's time for you and I
to say goodbye, you'll know.
All I can tell you is...
There's still time
to change the future.
Let's use it.
Hm.
Well, I guess we're sticking
with the very bad plan.
[Hawkman] The Al Hadidiyah Mine
is Intergang's
most valued asset.
I'm gonna land us right here,
cut off their access
to reinforcements.
But the perimeter of the mine
creates a natural fortress.
There's only one way in,
one way out.
We'll be an easy target
for their flybike patrol.
Communication is key.
We keep in step
or we get outflanked.
We move through the mine,
inch by inch,
until we find Amon.
This is where you come in.
Are you ready-- Damn it.
["Power" by Kanye West playing]
[soldier screams]
Or we could just do that.
[man yelling, screams]
[grunting]
[Ishmael] Pure Eternium shield.
Unbreakable,
even with your powers.
Amon!
You hurt him,
I will kill all of you.
[chuckling] Nobody has to die.
We just want the crown.
We don't have it.
Believe me, nothing good
will come from that crown.
No crown, no negotiation.
I have it.
It's right here.
Release my son, you can have it.
What do you think you're doing?
Intergang killed my husband.
I'm not letting them
take my son, too.
[sharp grunt]
[Adrianna gasps]
Not your son. Not your country.
Not your decision to make.
Stop there!
It's okay.
Nothing is gonna happen to you.
Hand it over, now.
I'm sorry, Mama.
No.
Now, let Amon go.
[Ishmael] I thank you.
And I thank your friends
for returning the crown
to its rightful owner.
What kind of Champion of Kahndaq
sides with foreign invaders?
You have what you want.
Let him go.
Ishmael, what are you doing?
Taking back what's mine.
I'm the last living descendant
of King Ahk-Ton the Great.
And you have just given me
everything I need
to become the next...
king of Kahndaq.
My family passed
the knowledge on, you know,
one to the next.
The crown,
crafted by our ancestors,
stolen by the wizards
and hidden away.
But still a source
of great power,
if only we can wield it.
[strained laughter]
[sniffles]
They say when Hurut died,
you wept like a baby.
I wonder if you'll
do the same for them.
Please, Ishmael.
Sorry, Amon.
Fate, get ready.
Death is the only path to life.
Amon!
[roaring]
[yelling]
[screaming]
[Teth Adam roaring]
[slow building growl]
[roar building in intensity]
[loud grunt]
[Adrianna's breath shaking]
Amon!
[gasping]
He's alive.
But we need to get him
to the medical bay.
-Where is he shot?
-It wasn't a bullet.
[Teth Adam] It was me.
[breath shaking]
Come.
We're going with you.
Just find the crown.
Get it on the cruiser.
I found the crown.
But, um... it's not alone.
How long we gonna
keep doing this?
There's no point in fighting.
We both know no one can stop me.
You're right.
Only you can.
Ishmael said you cried
when Hurut died.
Who's Hurut?
Hurut was a true Champion
of Kahndaq.
And he was also... my son.
I won't always be here to protect you.
I don't need protection.
I want to be free.
Freedom is for the birds.
Let someone else be the hero...
...the graveyards are full of them.
[people yelling,
shouting in distance]
[soldiers shouting, grunting]
[Teth Adam, in English]
I tried to protect him.
[grunting fiercely]
[inhales softly]
[Teth Adam]
But I wasn't strong enough.
[wizards] Shazam!
[Teth Adam] The wizards decided
that he would be their champion.
But after the Champion's
many victories,
the king went after
what Hurut loved the most.
[yelling]
-[Teth Adam] Our family.
-[screaming]
[woman screams]
[Teth Adam coughs]
Hold on, Father.
Stay with me.
[Teth Adam grunts softly]
[coughing weakly]
With my powers...
...you'll be safe.
I couldn't protect your mother.
Repeat what I say.
-Shazam.
[thunder crashing]
[Teth Adam]
Instead of battling the king...
Instead of saving Kahndaq...
Hurut chose to save...
...me.
[arrows clattering]
[bow string creaking]
[Teth Adam]
But he couldn't save himself
from the king's assassins.
[yelling in Kahndaqi]
[Teth Adam, in English]
The powers were not a gift
from the wizards...
[whispering in Kahndaqi]
[Teth Adam, in English]
...but a curse.
[powerful yell]
Born... out of rage.
The statue of the Champion
isn't you.
It's Hurut.
My son dreamt of a better world.
That's why he saved me.
But the world was only
a better place with him in it.
Kahndaq needed a hero.
Instead, it got me.
All this power...
And the only thing
I can do with it is hurt people.
I will speak the word
my son gave me...
...and I will give up my power.
And when I do, you must ensure
I never speak it again.
Shazam.
[thunder echoing]
Some men are not meant...
...to be heroes.
Hey!
[chuckling] So beautiful.
Surprised to see us?
Surprise is a dirty word
in this business.
Are you sure you can handle him?
You're the one who can
see the future,
you'll tell me if we can't.
Just be careful with this one.
You know,
they say the gods created us,
but we're the ones
who always wind up burying them.
Waller sends her regards.
[Dr. Fate] They'll know
how to deal with him.
To keep him
from regaining his powers,
they'll keep him
in suspended animation.
As long as he's submerged,
he won't be able to speak.
He'll never say
another word again.
Hey! There he is.
Not all heroes wear capes,
but I think you earned this.
-[laughs]
-Well, statistically,
most heroes don't wear capes.
But yeah, try it on.
Yeah, looks pretty good.
[light wind blowing]
That's a nice touch.
[mimics wind]
[faint, distorted voices
chanting]
[voices whispering, indistinct]
[distant rumble of thunder]
[powerful scream]
[pained exhale]
[Dr. Fate moans]
Kent.
-Kent!
-[gasps]
Mission accomplished?
My vision hasn't changed.
But Teth Adam's
out of the equation.
Kent, if this isn't over,
I need to know what's coming.
What is the helmet telling you?
My vision has always shown me
a great calamity.
The world in flames.
We can stop it...
...but you die.
You should've told me sooner.
I have no fear of death.
That's precisely
why I didn't tell you.
The world needs
the Justice Society.
The world needs you.
But you can't choose
who lives and dies.
That's Fate, right?
[rueful chuckle]
That sounds familiar.
I remember seeing
my first airplane.
It was an RAF deployment,
headed to the Western Front.
Everyone on my street
came out to see them off.
Mm.
But I didn't cheer.
Even though I was only a boy.
I knew where they were headed,
and what awaited them.
Thanks to this,
I've lived longer
than I could've
ever have hoped for.
I've seen the world change
in more ways
than I could've imagined.
I'm still a sentimental fool.
And I don't want
my friend to die.
[sighs]
[groaning]
Ishmael said, "Death is the only
path to life."
But that's not
what the inscription says.
Right. "Life is the only
path to death."
Maybe he got it backwards,
like he read it in a mirror
or something.
That's it.
In Kahndaqi mythology,
the souls of the damned
are sent
to the Rock of Finality.
The underworld
IS a mirror to our own.
Here, turn the crown around.
Now mirror the letters.
See? That's what I missed.
"Death is the only
path to life."
[gasping]
[Adrianna] He kidnapped Amon
on purpose,
because he knew
that Teth Adam would kill him.
And he believed
the Champion's magic
would send him
to the Rock of Finality.
As life is the path to death.
[demon] Now your death
is a path to life.
[demon 2]
The wizards have their champion,
now we have ours.
[demon 3] You will take
the throne of Kahndaq
and unleash hell on Earth!
[demons] Speak our name.
"Sabbac."
[screaming]
[Dr. Fate] What
the bloody hell is that?
[Hawkman] Readout says
it's the demon, Sabbac.
Get me closer.
Now, right now!
We're 100 miles out,
give me 20 seconds!
The King has returned!
The throne will be mine!
Brace yourselves!
[roaring]
[all yelling]
Hold on!
[alarm beeping]
[grunts]
[Sabbac grunting]
-[straining]
-[people shouting]
[Hawkman straining]
[people shouting, screaming]
[scattered shouts, yelling]
[Sabbac, in English]
Now prepare to die.
[sharp grunt]
[both grunt]
Wait, wait, where's Uncle Karim?
[Atom Smasher coughing]
[yells]
[angry groan]
[grunts]
[Hawkman] No matter what happens,
he does not sit on that throne.
-[Atom Smasher] Copy that.
-[Cyclone] We're on it!
Heads up!
[loud grunt]
[sharp growl]
[both grunting]
[sharp yell]
[aggressive grunt]
[Atom Smasher grunting loudly]
Activate infrared.
[Atom Smasher grunts]
[Cyclone cries out]
Sabbac, show yourself!
-[people yelling]
-Adrianna! Amon!
[Sabbac yells]
That's for my cruiser.
-[grunts heavily]
-[Sabbac screams]
[growling]
[grunts]
[growls]
[Sabbac grunts]
[gasping]
[groaning]
[Dr. Fate] This is it.
We can't win, Carter.
Yeah, but the world burns
if we don't. Right?
Bad plan is better than
no plan at all.
[panting]
[thudding]
[shield resonating]
No, no, no. What are you doing?
Giving us a third option.
It's supposed to be me.
I didn't tell you
my whole vision, old friend.
I did see your death.
But I also found a way
to prevent it.
It has been
an extraordinary life,
but always with one foot
in the future.
Carter, for the first time
in 100 years,
when I look ahead...
...I see nothing.
No, Kent.
And...
...it's...
...beautiful.
Wait, Kent!
Goodbye...
Kent! [grunting loudly]
...my dear friend.
Kent! [grunts]
[Hawkman] Hit it from every side.
[yelling] Kent!
[grunting]
No!
[growling]
I am Dr. Fate, sorcerer,
agent of the Lords of Order,
defender against darkness
and chaos,
but even my powers
cannot defeat you.
[Sabbac grunting]
There's no one that
can defeat me.
[grunting]
[Dr. Fate, echoing]
There is one... There is one...
Teth Adam.
I know you can hear me.
The battle your son
was meant to fight is upon us.
Now you are the only one
who can defeat
the Demon Champion.
[all yelling]
-[blow thudding]
-[soldier grunting]
[grunting]
[Dr. Fate] You have the power
to be the destroyer
of this world.
But you can also be its savior.
[all grunting with effort]
[yells]
[Dr. Fate] You believe
you are not a worthy champion
because the wizards
did not choose you.
But Fate does not make mistakes.
Neither did your son.
[growling]
[grunting]
[Dr. Fate]
We were wrong about you.
The world doesn't always need
a white knight.
Sometimes it needs
something darker.
[heavy grunt]
[soldier yells]
[gunshots]
[muffled grunt]
[Dr. Fate] Don't you dare
give up on us now.
The world needs you.
[guns firing]
[sharp grunt]
[explosive grunting]
[muffled yell]
[growling]
[angry grunt]
[exhales]
Kent!
[explosive grunt]
[grunting]
[roaring]
[gasping]
No!
[exhales shakily]
[panting deeply]
[roaring]
[yelling wildly]
Mom? What's happening?
[zombies moaning]
It's Sabbac.
He commands the Legions of Hell.
Whatever happens...
...you stay behind me.
[growling]
['Baby Come Back"
playing on car stereo]
[creatures grunting on impact]
♪ Baby come back ♪
[grunts]
Don't worry,
I die by electricity!
[Karim laughs]
You want some Kahndaq?
Come and get it!
No, no. No.
-Don't send me home, I can help.
-I know.
But you can do better
than swinging a stick.
[grunting with effort]
[zombies screeching]
-[Adrianna grunting]
-[monsters snarling]
[weeping softly]
The Gods have brought us together again.
It's not your time, Father.
Hey!
What are you all
standing around for?
This is our chance.
With these hands,
we built Kahndaq.
And with these hands,
we will set it free!
The people need a hero.
No, Father.
They need to be free.
What are we waiting for?
[grunting]
[yelling]
[crowd cheering]
Say the word.
Shazam.
[Hawkman groaning in pain]
The people of Kahndaq
rise up against you!
[roaring]
[people screaming]
[grunts]
[people exclaiming happily]
Yes!
[grunts, panting]
I got this.
Go get him.
[screaming]
[heavy grunt]
You know what I have to do.
Beat his ass!
Let the fate of Kahndaq
be decided
by a true battle of champions.
Let's end this.
[roaring]
[both grunting]
-[Sabbac groans]
-[yelling]
[zombies growling]
It's a lot of them.
-It's a bit more than I thought.
-Yeah.
Just a bit.
[grunting]
[deep yell]
Hey, Mom!
[people chattering excitedly]
These are our streets! Our city!
-Free Kahndaq!
-[all yelling]
[Sabbac grunts]
The wizards' powers
were wasted on you.
You are not a hero.
No. I'm not.
-[pained grunt]
-But he is.
[groaning in pain]
[sharp grunt]
[yelling in agony]
You cannot stand against me.
I am Kahndaq's true champion.
I learned this trick
from an old friend.
[growling]
[howling]
[all yelling]
[zombies growling]
[grunting]
[Sabbac growling]
[breath heaving]
You can control it!
[both screaming]
You have to!
[roaring in pain]
[Teth Adam yelling]
Tell them
the Man in Black sent you.
[Sabbac howling]
[Teth Adam roaring]
[powerful grunt]
[cheering wildly]
-Yes!
[groaning]
I never thought I'd be happy
to see you.
I'm only here because of him.
That makes two of us.
[gasps]
[panting]
See you around, old friend.
Think you can keep him
out of trouble?
As long as no one
comes looking for it.
[Hawkman] Fair enough.
Just be careful.
The kind of justice you dish out
can darken your soul.
It's his darkness
that lets him do
what heroes like you cannot.
[dry chuckle]
I guess we'll find out,
won't we?
I thought we made
a pretty good team back there.
Just saying.
We made a great team.
[light chuckle]
[stammers]
-Maybe we could--
-Don't push it.
[Cyclone] Smasher, let's go.
[Kahndaqi people, chanting]
Long live the Champion!
You could lead them.
[chanting continues faintly]
How does it feel?
Wrong.
[Amon] So... what now?
Does this mean you're finally
gonna be our hero?
Kahndaq has always had heroes.
And it still does.
What it needs now
is a protector.
Thank you, Teth Adam.
[Teth Adam]
Perhaps that name is a little...
...old-fashioned.
So what should we call you?
Okay, "Black Adam."
My name is Amanda Waller.
Congratulations,
you have my attention.
This is gonna be
your only warning.
You don't want to stay
in my prison, that's fine.
Kahndaq is your prison now.
You step one foot outside of it
you will not live to regret it.
There's no one on this planet
that can stop me.
[Waller] I can call in a favor
and send people
who aren't from this planet.
Send them all.
As you wish.
[thunder rumbling]
It's been a while since anyone's
made the world this nervous.
Black Adam.
We should talk.