Who are you?
Prove to me you are one of us.
My King.
Come, baby brother.
Baby brother.
Tell him who you are.
Onward!
Praise the ancestors.
Onward.
My son.
What is wrong my son?
I am not ready.
Have you not prepared...
...to be king your whole life?
Have you not trained and studied,
been by my side?
Sophia, hello.
Good to see you.
Who are these two?
My friends from Kenya.
Very deep pockets. They're good.
Good for trouble...
...like you?
Thank you.
Over here.
One whiskey, please.
Stand down.
I've been made.
Murderer!
King!
The world watches.
We can't let him talk to Klaue alone.
Better to let him talk to Klaue
alone for 5 minutes...
...than to make a scene here.
If he touches you again,
I'm going to impale him to this desk.
Where is that?
Back there.
Something is happening out back.
My King!
My King.
Who are you?
Tell us what is going on.
Speak.
My goodness.
Who are you?
I am N'Jadaka, son of Prince N'Jobu.
Son of N'Jobu?
You're lying!
The descendent of N'Jobu.
Thank you.
I cannot.
Praise the ancestors.
My son.
Why?
Shields!
Lock!
Get him down!
Get the necklace!
Charge!
White Wolf!