Hey, Nat!
We're both upside down.
And I bet you're gonna fall down first.
No, you will.
You can't hold it much longer.
Told you you'd fall down first.
I told you! I told you!
Told you so!
Mommy!
What happened?
She fell on her knee.
- Oh, you bump your knee?
- Mmm-hmm.
Oh...
Kiss it better.
There we go.
Oh, come on, little one.
Get up. You're okay.
Come on.
You're a brave girl.
Your pain only makes you stronger.
- Right, you?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
- Look!
Forest stars.
Yeah. You know what?
Those are actually
part of the Lampyridae family.
And the glow, the glow that you see,
that comes from
a chemical reaction called...
bioluminescence.
Come on, time for dinner.
Bio-goomin-feasants?
"Bio-goomin-feasants."
That's right.
Dinner!
Come on, dinner, big girl!
I want mac and cheese.
Oh, you want mac and cheese?
Okay. Well, I want...
caviar and champagne.
Grab the napkins.
You take this. Thank you.
Oh, would you grab
the ranch dressing for Dad?
Okay.
Green beans
are my favorite vegetable.
Dad's home!
Hey, Dad.
Hey, baby.
Everything okay?
How was everybody's day?
Mommy taught me
about lamp bugs.
- Lamp bugs.
- And I fell and hurt my knee,
- but it doesn't hurt anymore.
- Mmm-hmm.
And we also saw
fireflies in the backyard.
That was my favorite part
- of the whole day.
- No.
Yelena,
we see fireflies every year.
How long do we have?
I don't know. Like, an hour, maybe.
I don't wanna go.
Don't say that.
Girls...
you remember when I told you that
one day we would have that big adventure?
- Today's the day.
- Yay!
All right, let's go.
I'm sorry.
- Come on, we gotta hurry.
- Thank you.
- I don't have my shoes.
- Thank you, baby.
That's okay. You don't need your shoes.
- But I'm still hungry.
- Yeah? Guess what?
I got Fruit Roll-Ups in the car.
No, leave it, leave it, leave it.
Go wait in the car.
- You have it?
- Yeah.
- It's the only copy?
- It's the only one not on fire.
Where are we going?
Home.
Mommy, you're silly.
We just left home.
I want my song.
♪ Bye, bye, Miss American Pie ♪
♪ Drove my Chevy to the levee ♪
♪ but the levee was dry ♪
♪ Them good old boys ♪
♪ were drinking whiskey and rye ♪
♪ Singing, "This'll be the day that I die" ♪
♪ "This'll be the day that I die" ♪
Come on, Yelena.
Hurry up, baby.
Let's go. Come on, Nat.
Hurry up. We gotta go.
We gotta go.
Come on, you gotta run.
Come on. Honey, honey.
- Go with your mom. Go with your mom.
- Okay.
- Nat, hurry up!
- I'm coming!
Okay. Seat belts.
Okay.
Why isn't Dad in the plane?
He's coming. He's coming, baby.
He's coming.
Mom?
Mom!
I need you up here.
- Okay.
I need you to pull right.
Mom, you've got blood on you.
It's okay, baby.
Hit the accelerator there.
Hold it steady, hold it steady.
You're gonna pull back at 55 knots.
Let's count together.
45, 50...
Pull back.
You can do it!
All your strength.
Okay.
Get up, Mommy.
Pain only makes you stronger, remember?
The Red Guardian returns.
The Red Guardian returns triumphant.
Please, please, I beg you.
No more undercover work.
I wanna get back in the action.
I want my suit back.
I wanna get back in it.
General Dreykov,
it's been over three years.
Forgive me mom.
I'm scared.
Never let them take your heart.
Did you get it?
And the North Institute?
Ashes.
It's gonna be okay.
How is Melina?
She'll live. She's strong.
- Mommy?
- Mom?
- Daddy!
- I'll handle this.
- Daddy! Daddy!
- Yelena!
- Daddy!
- Get away from her!
Don't touch her!
I will shoot.
I will kill you all!
Don't touch her.
Honey.
You're gonna need to hand me that gun.
I don't wanna go back there.
I wanna stay in Ohio.
You can't take her.
You can't.
She's only six.
You were even younger.
It's okay.
Come here.
You're gonna be all right.
Do you know why
it's gonna be all right?
'Cause my girls are
the toughest girls in the world.
You're gonna take care
of each other, okay?
And everything,
everything's gonna be fine.
That one, she has fire in her.
What was her name?
Natasha.
Ah... Natasha.
No!
Remove all the defects.
That one
and her.
No!
Yelena!
Take it! Take it! No!
No!
The Red Room is your home now.
Get off me! No!
Undercover spies in our communities.
They took on false identities,
even raised families...
- They're topside, sir!
- Tier 1 has LOS!
We've got all exits covered.
All right. Stay alert.
I'm sending in alpha squad.
Natasha Romanoff is in violation
of the Sokovia Accords.
She assaulted the king of Wakanda.
Make an example out of her.
- Yeah?
- Don't do this.
Do what?
Come after me.
I mean, you're embarrassing yourself.
It looks desperate.
Thought maybe you'd be
calling me to cut a deal.
'Cause from my vantage point,
it's the federal fugitive
who's desperate.
From my vantage point,
you look like you could use some bed rest.
What is this, your second triple bypass?
I wouldn't worry about me.
We got Barton, we got Wilson
and that other guy,
the incredible shrinking convict.
Rogers is on the run.
You got no friends.
Where you gonna go?
I've lived a lot of lives
before I met you, Ross.
You shouldn't have gone
to all this trouble. I'm done.
Romanoff?
Got an empty nest,
Secretary Ross.
Her tracker, sir.
Eyes on target.
Waiting for the package.
I have sights on collateral one.
Firing in place of three.
Five, four...
She made us.
Target deployed smoke.
She's on foot with the package.
Stay high. I'm going to ground.
Oksana.
Oh, no.
What did I do?
Free the others.
Yelena, we need a status report.
Yelena,
we need a status report.
Converge on team leader.
General Dreykov,
we have a deserter.
Permission to activate
Taskmaster Protocol?
Smile.
After the Sokovia Accords
the hunt is on
for the remaining Avengers...
Steve Rogers and Natasha Romanoff
are currently on the run.
You're in my bed.
I'm... I'm not even under the covers.
Did you get everything on my list?
Got passports, entry visas,
a couple of local driver's licenses.
Mix and match, you should be able to
stretch it to 20 or so identities.
Fanny Longbottom?
- What?
- What, are you 12?
That is a legitimate name.
We've got a generator outside.
It's petrol-powered. And the septic tank
will need a flush in a couple of weeks,
but, you know,
I've got a guy coming for that.
You have to haul your rubbish into town.
It's just a 20-minute drive.
I've got your basic hardware kit
stashed under the stairs.
Thanks.
Are you okay?
Why wouldn't I be?
I hear things. You know, something
about the Avengers getting divorced...
Ugh. It's fine.
I'm actually better on my own.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Because you can tell me, you know.
That's the way
the whole friends thing works.
I know. I have friends.
People who have friends don't call me.
And I don't pay you to worry.
Oh, hey.
What's all this junk?
Oh, just some mail and personals
from the Budapest safe house.
Budapest?
Yeah. Budapest.
- No, it's "Budapest."
- Budapest.
Budapest.
- It's "Budapest." Sh.
- Whatever.
I knew you weren't going back there,
so I've got someone else in the flat now.
Sorry you went through the trouble.
I would've told you to chuck it.
Well, if you don't want it,
throw it in the rubbish.
You're not
a sportsman, Mr. Bond.
Why did you break up the encounter
with my pet python?
Because I discovered
he had a crush on me.
Moonraker 1
on preset launch program...
Oh, great.
...minus two minutes.
Retract crew access...
I'm pretty sure Ross
has no jurisdiction here.
And you should know I'm a better shot
when I'm pissed off.
You're not here for me.
Oh, shit.
I know you're out there.
I know you know I'm out here.
Then why are you skulking about
like it's a minefield?
'Cause I don't know
if I can trust you.
Funny,
I was going to say the same thing.
So, we gonna talk
like grown-ups?
Is that what we are?
Put it down before I make you.
You put yours down.
Watch your step.
Stay down. Stay down.
Stay down.
Stop.
Truce.
You've grown up.
No shit.
You had to come
to Budapest, didn't you?
I came here
because I thought you wouldn't.
But since you're here,
what bullet does that?
Not bullets. Arrows.
Ah, right.
If you didn't think I'd come here,
why'd you send me this?
You brought it back here?
I'm not here trying to be your friend,
but you need to tell me what that is.
It's a synthetic gas.
The counteragent to chemical subjugation.
The gas immunizes
the brain's neuropathways
from external manipulation.
Maybe in English next time?
It's an antidote to mind control.
Real mature.
Why don't you take it
to one of your super-scientist friends?
They can explain it to you.
Tony Stark, maybe?
Oh, yeah. We're not really
talking right now, so...
Great. Perfect timing.
Where's an Avenger when you need one?
I don't wanna be here.
I'm on the run.
You could've gotten me killed.
Well, what was I supposed to do?
You're the only superhero person
that I know.
That was the whole reason
I sent it to you.
I kept checking the news,
expecting to see Captain America
bringing down the Red Room.
What?
Taking down the Red Room?
What are you talking about?
It's been gone for years.
Dreykov's dead.
I killed him.
You don't actually believe that, do you?
You really do believe that.
Dreykov's dead.
It took almost destroying the entire city
just to get to him.
If you're so sure,
then tell me what happened.
Tell me exactly.
We rigged bombs.
- Who's "we"?
- Clint Barton.
Killing Dreykov was the final step
in my defection to S.H.I.E.L.D.
Simple as that?
Yeah, sure, "simple."
That's what I'd call imploding
a five-story building
and then shooting it out
with the Hungarian Special Forces.
Took 10 days in hiding
before we could even get out of Budapest.
And you checked the body?
Confirmed the kill?
There was no body left to check.
You're forgetting Dreykov's daughter.
Where are we trying to get?
Motorbike! East side
of the building.
They're going east, to the roof.
Copy, in pursuit.
I got you!
No!
Hey.
Don't move. You're hurt.
Let me help you.
I don't wanna do this.
- What are you doing?
- He's making me.
Do you believe me now?
How many others?
Enough.
Which one's yours?
Black. Brown seat.
Where are my keys?
...ah, bitch.
Any day now.
Are you okay?
Fantastic.
You can't just steal a guy's car.
So you want me to chase him down
and un-steal it?
- Okay. Any time now, please.
- Shut up.
Okay, you got a plan,
or shall I just stay duck-and-cover?
Yeah, my plan was to drive us away.
That's a shit plan.
You're welcome.
Oh, shit. He's back.
Put your seat belt on.
You're such a mom.
Natasha, no.
I think I'm bleeding. I'm...
No. Not now, trust me.
You okay?
Yeah. Great plan.
I love the part
where I almost bled to death.
This is cozy.
Barton and I spent two days
hiding out up here.
That must have been fun.
Who the hell is that guy?
Dreykov's special project.
He can mimic anyone he's ever seen.
It's like fighting a mirror.
Dreykov only deploys him
for top-priority missions.
This doesn't make any sense.
Well, the truth rarely makes sense
when you omit key details.
What is that supposed to mean?
You didn't say one word
about Dreykov's daughter.
You killed her.
I had to.
I needed her to lead me to Dreykov.
We need confirmation
Dreykov's in the building.
His car is pulling up now.
Dreykov's daughter was collateral damage.
I needed her to be sure.
Natasha, we clear?
All clear.
And here you are, not so sure.
I needed out.
The Red Room's still active. Where is it?
I have no idea.
He moves location constantly.
And every widow is sedated
on entry and exit for maximum security.
I'm just finding it hard to believe
that he could stay off my radar.
Well, it's not smart to attack an Avenger
if you want to stay hidden.
I mean, the clue is in the name.
Dreykov kills you,
one of the big ones comes to avenge you.
Wait, what are the big ones?
Well, I doubt the god from space
has to take an ibuprofen after a fight.
Where did you think I was all this time?
I thought that you got out
and were living a normal life.
And you just never made contact again?
Honestly, I thought
you didn't wanna see me.
Bullshit.
You just didn't want
your baby sister to tag along,
whilst you saved the world
with the cool kids.
You weren't really my sister.
And the Avengers
aren't really your family.
- Why do you always do that thing?
- Do what?
The thing you do when you're fighting.
The... Like, the...
This thing that you do
when you whip your hair
when you're fighting
with the arm and the hair.
And you do, like,
a fighting pose.
It's a...
It's a fighting pose.
You're a total poser.
I'm not a poser.
Oh, come on.
I mean, they're great poses,
but it does look like
you think everyone's looking at you, like,
all the time.
All that time that I spent posing,
I was trying to actually do something good
to make up for all the pain
and suffering that we caused.
Trying to be more
than just a trained killer.
Well, then you were fooling yourself
because pain and suffering is every day
and we are both still a trained killer.
Except I'm not the one
that's on the cover of a magazine.
I'm not the killer
that little girls call their hero.
That gas,
the counteragent,
it was synthesized in secret
by an older widow
from Melina's generation.
I was on the mission to retrieve it,
and she exposed me
and I killed the widow that freed me.
Did you have a choice?
What you experienced
was psychological conditioning.
I'm talking about chemically
altering brain functions.
They're two completely different things.
You're fully conscious,
but you don't know which part is you.
I'm still not sure.
- Is that all there is left?
- Mmm-hmm.
It's the only thing that can stop Dreykov
and his network of widows.
He takes more every day.
Children who don't have anyone
to protect them.
Just like us when we were small.
Maybe one in 20 survives the training,
becomes a widow.
The rest, he kills.
To him, we are just things.
Weapons with no face
that he can just throw away.
Because there is always more.
And no one's even looking for him,
thanks to you and Alexei.
Alexei?
"Dad."
Did you ever look
for your parents? Your real ones?
Well, my mom abandoned me
in the street like garbage.
What about you?
They destroyed my birth certificate,
so I reinvented it.
My parents still live in Ohio.
My sister moved out west.
Is that right?
You're a science teacher.
You're working part-time, though,
especially after you had your son.
Your husband, he renovates houses.
That is not my story.
What is your story?
I never let myself be alone
long enough to think about it.
Did you ever wish for kids?
I want a dog.
Where you gonna go?
I don't know.
I don't really have
anywhere to go back to,
so I guess anywhere.
- Don't.
- Don't what?
You're going to
give me some big hero speech,
I can feel it.
Speeches aren't really my thing.
Huh.
It was more like an invitation.
To go to the Red Room and kill Dreykov?
Yeah.
Even though the Red Room
is impossible to find
and Dreykov is too slippery to kill?
Yeah.
That sounds like a shitload of work.
Yup.
Could be fun, though.
I saw where he put the keys.
Top drawer, green cabinet.
You know, this is
the first piece of clothing
I've ever bought for myself.
That?
Yeah. You don't like it?
Is that like a...
Is it army surplus, or...
Okay, it has a lot of pockets.
But I use them all the time,
and I made some of my own
modifications.
- Oh, yeah?
- Whatever.
Shut up. The point is, I've never...
I've never had control
over my own life before, and now I do.
I want to do things.
Hmm...
I like your vest.
I knew it. I knew you did.
It's so cool, right?
It's good. Yes. I like it.
And you can put so much stuff in there.
You wouldn't even know.
I really don't know where
the Red Room is, though.
- I'm sorry.
- I know.
But I think I know somebody who does.
Oh, yeah? Who?
We're gonna need a jet.
I said we needed a jet.
Yeah, you know what you didn't give me?
Time.
Or money. I'm not made of jets.
I thought you were
supposed to be the best.
Like a real pro.
Oh, I beg your pardon, tsarina.
Was the free flat
and lifetime supply of kissel
- not to your liking?
- Ha!
Don't let her wind you up.
No, I take exception
to impugning my professionalism.
Well, you did set me up with a generator
that crapped out after six hours.
You, too, huh? Tag team.
Aw, he's sensitive.
See why you keep him around.
Where's the rest?
Voilà.
Ooh.
Oh, I stashed that, like, five years ago.
How is it?
It's dry.
It's really dry.
You know, you're getting dangerously close
to running out your tab.
Supplies I can tally, but you bring me
attention from the authorities,
all my prices go up.
What's that supposed to mean?
Your mate, Secretary Ross,
has been sniffing around my affairs
to the point at which I've got
contacts declining my calls.
I'm a private contractor.
You are sensitive.
You're a very annoying individual.
- I'll make it up to you.
- Mmm-hmm.
That's what you say every time.
So, I have the nuclear code.
But there he is.
- Captain America!
- America.
Finally, the Red Guardian's time has come!
I grab hold of his shield
and face to face, it's a test of strength.
Oh... Oh, no.
Oh...
That guy think he going to beat me.
Anyway, this shield, you know,
that he carries with him
like a precious baby blanket, you know?
I use it to my advantage.
I take it
and I push him out the window.
And I make my escape. Huh?
What year was this?
I don't know.
Like, '83, '84.
I know.
Captain America was
still frozen in ice then.
Are you calling me a liar, Ursa, huh?
Alexei Shostakov! Mail Call.
Oh, no.
Uh-oh.
Alexei Shostakov! Mail Call.
Aw, look at the big bear.
Gonna cry, little girl?
The famed "Red Guardian."
When you write back, tell your
fans to use more butter.
Take it!
Come on.
Red Guardian forward!
The trumpet is calling!
Today is your lucky day, Alexei.
Move to the door on the south wall.
What's up with you?
Can't you read?
Go left.
Just don't make a scene.
The Red Guardian is escaping!
You made a scene, didn't you?
What now?
We're gettin' you outta here.
Go to the upper level.
Move your ass, super soldier.
He's never going to make it.
Get me closer.
You got a better idea?
Natasha.
Such a poser.
Seriously?
Whoo!
Sorry!
What are you doing?
Are you kidding me?
Back up!
We're both doing
a really good job.
No.
Okay. Enough of this.
Ha!
Whoa...
This would be a cool way to die.
Tell me that's a good sign for us!
Move your ass!
Get us outta here!
Huh.
Wait!
Yes!
I need some help up here!
Farewell, douchebags.
Oh, that was exciting.
Oh, I'm so proud of you girls.
Oh, you can't hear me, huh?
Okay.
Ah...
Wow.
Okay.
Why the aggression, huh?
Is it your time of the month?
I don't get my period, dipshit.
I don't have a uterus.
Or ovaries.
Yeah. That's what happens
when the Red Room
gives you an involuntary hysterectomy.
They kind of just go in and they rip out
all of your reproductive organs.
They just get right in there
and they chop them all away.
- Everything out, so you can't have babies.
- Okay, okay. Okay! Okay!
You don't have to get
so clinical and nasty.
Oh, well, I was about to talk about
- fallopian tubes, but okay.
- No.
It means so much to me
that you came back for me.
No. No. You're gonna tell us
how to get to the Red Room.
Huh.
Whoa, look at you, huh? All business.
Trust me, this isn't pleasure.
Little Natasha,
all indoctrinated into the Western agenda.
I chose to go west to become an Avenger.
'Cause they treated me like family.
Really? Family?
Well, where are they now?
Where is that family now?
Tell me where the Red Room is.
I have no idea.
Okay?
Come on. You and Dreykov were like...
- Dreykov?
- Yeah.
General Dreykov, my friend, huh?
Gives me glory...
Soviet Union's first
and only super soldier.
I could have been more famous
than Captain America.
Then he buries me in Ohio
on that stupid mission.
Three years!
So tedious, boring me to tears.
No offense, huh?
Then puts me in prison
for the rest of my life. Why, huh?
Why? Why would he put me in...
You know why?
'Cause maybe I want to talk
about the withering of the state.
Or maybe I don't like
his hair or something
and I say something casually about that.
Maybe, you know,
I want the Party
to feel actually like a party
instead of this sourpuss organization.
But instead, no.
He puts me in prison
for the rest of my life.
He just runs off and hides, huh?
I'm not even the one who, uh, you know...
I'm not the one who killed his daughter.
Can we throw him
out the window now?
I think we should wait
till we get to a higher altitude.
All right.
Why not ask Melina where it is?
Wait, Mom Melina?
We thought she was dead.
You cannot kill a fox that swift.
- Ew.
- What?
She was the scientist, the strategist.
I was the muscle.
She worked directly for Dreykov
far more than I ever did.
Wait. Are you telling me that Melina
is working for the Red Room present day?
She works remotely outside St. Petersburg.
Uh...
I don't think we have enough
fuel for St. Petersburg.
No, we're good. We'll make it.
Okay.
You should've brought
the Avengers' superjet.
I swear, if I hear
one more word from him,
- I will kick him in the face.
- He's the worst.
Natasha.
Natasha. Natasha.
Come here, I want to ask you something.
- Come, it's important.
- What?
Did he talk to you about me?
What?
You know, trading war stories?
Who? What are you talking about?
Captain America.
My great adversary
in this theater of geopolitical conflict.
Not so much a nemesis.
More like a contemporary, you know?
Coequal.
I always thought there was
a great deal of mutual respect...
Wait. You haven't seen
either one of us in 20 years
and you're gonna ask me about you?
What is with this tension?
Did I do something wrong?
Is that a serious question?
I only ever loved you girls.
I did my best to make sure
you would succeed
to achieve your fullest potential,
- and everything worked out.
- Everything worked out?
Yes. For you, yes.
We accomplished our mission in Ohio.
Yelena, you went on to become
the greatest child assassin
the world has ever known.
No one can match your efficiency,
your ruthlessness.
And Natasha,
not just a spy,
not just toppling regimes,
destroying empires from within,
but an Avenger.
You both have killed
so many people.
Your ledgers must be dripping,
just gushing red.
I couldn't be more proud of you.
Okay. You can... No.
Let go of me now.
You smell really bad.
So, are we there yet?
You'll know when we're there.
Slight right.
Straight on.
Right.
Slight right.
Oh, very good, my darling.
Yes, very good.
Yes, very good, my darling.
Back home where it's safe.
Come on. Go on.
Honey, we're home.
Come on, girls.
Welcome to my humble abode.
Make yourself at home.
Let's have a drink.
Hey, no funny business.
I am putting away my weapon.
Are there
any booby traps around here?
Anything we need to know about?
I didn't raise my girls to fall in traps.
You didn't raise us at all.
Oh, maybe so.
But if you got soft,
it wasn't on my watch.
Let's drink.
Okay.
Still fits.
Oh, my God.
I never washed it once.
Come and drink.
Rise, you workers of salvation
Family
back together again.
- Mmm.
- Seeing as our
family construct
was just a calculated ruse
that only lasted three years,
I don't think that we can use
this term anymore, can we?
Agreed. So, here's what's gonna happen...
Okay. A reunion then, huh?
And, uh...
I want to say something
right off the bat.
You haven't aged a day, huh?
You're just as beautiful and as supple
as the day they staged our marriage.
You got fat.
But still good.
I just got out of prison. I, uh...
- I have a lot of energy.
- Oh!
Please don't do that.
So, here's what's gonna happen.
Natasha, don't slouch.
- I'm not slouching.
- Yes, yes, you are.
I don't slouch.
You're going to get a back hunch.
- Listen to your mother.
- Oh, my God, this...
Up, up.
All right, enough. All of you.
I didn't say anything.
That's not fair.
- Here's what's gonna happen...
- I don't want any food.
Eat a little something,
Yelena, for God's sake.
You're gonna tell us
the location of the Red Room.
You know, it's like when you told them
that they could stay up late
to catch Santa Claus.
What? That was fun. You know,
"He come down the chimney, girls.
"Look out. Where is he?"
You wait for him,
and then when the cookies are gone,
then you see he's there.
No, no. What? I want them
- to follow their dreams.
- No good.
Reach for the stars, girls.
Finding Dreykov is not a fantasy.
It's unfinished business.
You can't defeat a man
who commands the very will of others.
You never saw the culmination
of what we started in America.
Nor did you.
Natasha, always focus, focus.
Get what you want.
Come in.
Did that pig just open the door?
Yes. It did.
Good boy, Alexei.
Good boy.
You named a pig after me?
You don't see the resemblance?
See, he sits just like dog.
Amazing. Now, watch.
It's a little weird, to me.
Stop breathing.
We infiltrated
the North Institute in Ohio.
It was a front
for S.H.I.E.L.D. scientists.
Actually, it was Hydra scientists
at that time.
In conjunction with
the Winter Soldier project,
they had dissected
and deconstructed the human brain
to create the first and only
cellular blueprint of the basal ganglia.
Was the hub for cognition.
Voluntary motor movement,
procedural learning.
We didn't steal weaponry or technology.
We stole the key to unlocking free will.
What are you doing?
Oh, I am explaining
that the science is now so exact,
the subject can be instructed
to stop breathing
and has no choice but to obey.
Okay, you made your point.
That's enough.
Yes, all right. Well, don't worry,
Alexei could've survived
11 more seconds without oxygen.
Good boy. Now, you go back,
back home where it's safe.
You go. You go back home,
Good boy, Alexei.
The world functions on a higher level
when it is controlled.
Dreykov has chemically subjugated agents
planted around the globe.
And do you know who they test it on?
Hmm...
No. That's not my department.
Ah, come on, come on.
- Don't lie to them. Hmm?
- I'm not lying.
You're Dreykov's architect, huh?
What were you?
If I was his architect,
you were his partner.
You were his business partner.
No, no, no. I was patsy!
- Don't give me that...
- He sell me ideology.
- Stop with the politics.
- All the while, bigger...
Shut up! You are an idiot.
And you're a coward.
You're a coward.
And our family was never real,
so there's nothing to hold on to.
We're moving on.
Never family, huh?
In my heart, I am simple man.
And I think that for a couple
deep undercover Russian agents
I think we did pretty great
as parents, huh?
Yes, we had our orders,
and we played our roles to perfection.
Who cares? That wasn't real.
- What?
- That wasn't real. Who cares?
Don't say that.
Please don't say that.
It was real.
It was real to me.
You are my mother.
You were my real mother.
The closest thing I ever had to one.
The best part of my life was fake.
And none of you told me.
And those agents
you chemically subjugated
around the globe?
That was me.
Mmm.
And you, you got out.
Dreykov made sure no one could escape.
Are you gonna say anything?
No.
Don't touch me.
Yelena.
No.
- I had no idea.
- It's okay, it's okay.
I'll go talk to her.
I came in here
because I didn't want to talk.
Okay.
We, uh... We just sit.
We just sit.
Where are you going?
- To do this myself.
- Don't. You won't survive.
I wish I could believe that you cared.
But you're not even the first mother
that abandoned me.
No, you weren't abandoned.
You were selected by a program
that assessed
the genetic potential in infants.
I was taken?
I believe a bargain was struck,
your family paid off.
But your mother,
she never stopped looking for you.
She was like you in that way.
She was
relentless.
What happened to her?
Dreykov had her killed.
Her existence threatened
to uncover the Red Room.
Normally, the actions
of one curious civilian
wouldn't warrant an execution,
but, as I said, she was relentless.
I thought about her every day of my life.
Whether or not I admitted it to myself,
I did.
I've always found it best
not to look into the past.
Then why did you save this?
I remember this day.
We shot Christmas, Thanksgiving, Easter
and summer vacation all in one day.
- Different backdrops.
- Mmm.
I knew all the presents under the tree
were just empty boxes, but I didn't care.
I wanted to open every single one...
so just for a second it would feel real.
Let's stop this.
Why you doing this?
Why does a mouse born in a cage
run on that little wheel?
Do you know I was cycled
through the Red Room
four times before you were even born?
Those walls are all I know.
I was never given a choice.
But you're not a mouse, Melina.
You were just born in a cage,
but that's not your fault.
Tell me, how did you keep your heart?
Pain only makes us stronger.
Didn't you tell us that?
What you taught me kept me alive.
I'm sorry, I already alerted the Red Room.
They'll be here any minute.
So, there I am
ice fishing with my father.
It's very cold day
in this little ice shed.
Cold even for Russia, you know?
"Keep the vodka by the fire,"
my father would say to me.
Please stop talking.
- Please wait. Please wait.
- Please, no.
Please, I don't want to talk.
Please. Please.
There is a reason why
I'm telling you this, okay? Trust me.
I am reaching for fish.
Oh! I lose balance. Ah!
Splash!
My hands go in the river.
In this weather,
frostbite sets in quick.
My father, he go toilet on my hands.
Oh, my God.
Urine is 35 degrees Celsius,
staves off the frostbite.
How is this relevant?
You know,
fathers.
No. No.
You have done nothing
but tell me how bored you were.
I was the chore,
the job you didn't want to do.
To me?
To me, you were everything.
Exactly. You don't care.
You don't care.
The only thing you care about
are your stupid glory days
as the Crimson Dynamo,
and no one wants to hear about it.
It's the Red Guardian.
Get out.
Get out!
♪ I can't remember ♪
♪ If I cried ♪
♪ When I read about his widowed bride ♪
♪ Something touched me deep inside ♪
♪ The day ♪
♪ The music ♪
♪ Died ♪
♪ And they were singing ♪
♪ - Bye ♪
♪ - Miss American Pie ♪
♪ - American Pie ♪
♪ Drove my Chevy to the levee ♪
♪ - But the levee was dry ♪
♪ - Was dry ♪
♪ Them good old boys ♪
♪ Drinking whiskey ♪
♪ Singing ♪
♪ "This will be the day that I die" ♪
♪ "This'll be the day..." ♪
Get down.
They think...
I'm sorry.
Let's not keep him waiting.
Request clearance for landing.
Copy that.
You are cleared to land on bay 5.
Melina?
We're touching down in one minute.
Then why are we still going up?
Now you'll know how Dreykov stayed
above the radar all these years.
My God.
Look at you.
So, uh,
how was the family reunion?
Oh, it was awful.
They were clingy,
and too emotional, and needy.
- Just like old times, huh?
- Hmm.
Yelena Belova.
What's the deal with her?
She was the only one affected, right?
As far as I know, yes.
These gasses and antidotes,
it's a pain in my ass.
It's a problem. You need to sort it.
Hmm. I have nine pigs
that will require attending to
in my absence.
Don't give a shit about your pigs.
Cut her brain out...
Hmm? Identify the weakness.
This is a much less cool way to die.
Alexei.
What about Romanoff?
She's a traitor.
She turned her back on her people.
On her blood.
She had nothing.
I gave her home.
I gave her love.
Put that thing in her you do.
You know, uh, chemicals.
Turn her into one of your pigs.
Can you imagine what I could do
with an Avenger under my control?
Wouldn't you like to speak to her first?
When you look into the eyes
of a child you have raised,
no mask in the world can hide that.
Welcome home.
Now, now.
Don't go breaking my new toy.
Natasha.
I can't save us.
I need you to know that I'm sorry.
I pledged my life to a cause.
You know, I thought
I was being very brave.
Possibly the bravest.
But I wasn't being brave.
I was coward.
In Cuba,
when they came
and took you away from me...
No cause is worth that.
You should only sacrifice yourself
for something...
How did you do that?
I designed these cells myself.
What?
I bared my soul to you
and it was just you the whole time?
Yes, I'm afraid so.
But wait, shh, I'm on comms with Yelena.
Yelena, it's me. It's Mama.
You have a two-inch blade
concealed in your beltline.
What?
What are you going to do to me?
Outside right hip.
Keep her awake
for the cranial incisions.
You couldn't have told me sooner?
Don't throw a fit.
- There wasn't time.
- Okay, girls,
I'm having trouble hearing you,
but, Natasha,
there's something I need you to know.
I need you to know that I'm sorry.
No more excuses, okay?
I gave my life for a cause.
I thought I was being brave.
You don't have earpiece.
What?
No, she can't hear you.
- You don't have earpiece.
- Why not?
Because it wasn't part of the plan.
Oh, yeah?
Well, what was the plan?
So, once we're inside,
I'll activate my tracker
and Ross will come running.
You are aware that
you are still a global fugitive, yes?
You know the facility.
There must be some way to land it.
Instruct them to confine us on level zero.
Once I'm out,
I can activate the landing protocol,
we can descend within the hour.
Ah, problem.
I only have one earpiece set.
I'll give it to Yelena.
Where did he take the vials?
Probably down to cold storage.
Dreykov still has the widows
under his control,
so you have to expose them
to this antidote.
Yeah. Sure. Easy.
Is this your plan?
My plan is to kill you.
I'm alive.
So, what do we do now?
What was my mother's name?
Ah...
Where we buried her,
there was a tree...
Um...
A pink blossom.
Beautiful.
And there was a tombstone
with her name engraved on it.
What was her name?
Ah.
"Unknown."
You don't feel anything?
You feel anything
when I killed your daughter?
Is this your haunted past?
Really?
Thank you, Natasha.
You gave me my greatest weapon.
Say hello.
When your bomb exploded,
it nearly killed my Antonia.
I had to put a chip
in the back of her neck.
In the back of her neck.
Look at her.
You find it difficult to look at her?
I do.
She... She watches everything
and she can do it.
She's a perfect mimic.
And she fights
just like all of your friends.
Can she hear me?
What?
You want to make her feel better?
You want to tell her you're sorry?
Well, you should have thought of that
before you blew her face off.
But enough of all this bullshit.
Go to work.
I have rats in the basement. Go.
Go.
Well, that was a mistake.
Was it?
You just sent away the one thing
that would stop me from killing you.
Try, then.
Do it.
Is the safety on?
No.
Try your knife.
Ah...
You're in trouble.
How are you controlling me?
I'm not controlling you, Natasha.
Well, not yet.
But there is a pheromonal lock.
Smelling my pheromones prevents you
from committing violence against me.
I'm very upset with Melina.
It's a shame I have to kill her.
Come on, now.
If we're just going to
press buttons and hack computers...
- Yes.
- I mean, I don't know.
There's nothing for me to do.
I want to...
I want to break something.
Oh, you do?
Oh, there is something you can break.
Melina, if this is
the last time that we...
Ah, damn it.
That was disgusting.
Okay.
So, this was the big plan, huh?
Melina was going to land the Red Room
and hand me over to the authorities.
Oh, no, no, no.
So, what now, you're gonna fold me into
your pathetic little puppeteer act?
Pathetic, huh?
Yeah, what would you call it?
- I would call it...
- When was the last time
that you had a conversation with somebody
that wasn't forced to talk to you?
You ran away to fight in the wrong war.
The real war was fought here,
in the shadows.
You didn't fight in the shadows.
You hid in the dark.
Real power comes
from undetectable influence.
If no one's noticed, then why even do it?
You're nothing.
- Hmm.
- You have nothing.
There are 50 people on this planet...
Oh, stop it.
Don't tell me to stop!
If I don't tell you when to stop,
then how will you know when to shut up?
Come on.
Think I can't take a punch?
Oh.
- God damn it, you're weak.
- Weak?
I bet it's easier to be tough
in front of defenseless little girls, huh?
That's enough.
You wouldn't be so glib
if you had any notion
of the scope of what I've built.
I own this world. Me.
You seem desperate to impress me.
I don't need to impress you.
I don't need to impress anyone.
These world leaders, these great men,
they answer to me and my widows.
Look at them.
These girls were trash.
They are thrown out into the street.
I recycle the trash.
And I give them purpose.
I give them a life.
Melina, I found the location of the vials.
I've had a slight setback.
You'll need to get to the widows.
It's my network of widows
that help me control the scales of power.
One command,
the oil and stock markets crumble.
and a quarter of the planet will starve.
My widows can start and end wars.
They can make and break kings.
You control all of that from here?
And with you,
an Avenger under my control,
I can finally come out of the shadows
using the only natural resource
that the world has too much of.
Girls.
All from that little console?
Yeah.
Oh, you find this amusing?
Why are you smiling?
Don't take it personal, but, uh...
Thank you for your cooperation.
Even if you locate the database
and get him to show you the key,
you won't be able to take it from him.
For years, Dreykov has implemented
a pheromonal lock
in all widows, even me.
So, as long as we can smell him,
then we won't be able to hurt him.
Well, I'll just hold my breath.
Not enough.
This is basic science.
Natasha, to block receptors
in olfactory center,
you have to sever the nerve.
I can handle that.
You weren't quite strong enough, so...
I'll have to finish it myself.
What are you going to do?
Sever the nerve.
She's got a gun!
Melina!
Melina, stop there!
Drop to the ground!
Precisely what I was thinking.
Yelena, slight change of plan.
I completely demolished one of the engines
and we are going into a controlled crash.
Fantastic.
I'm heading to the widows now.
No.
We have to go.
Not so talkative now, are you?
You took my childhood.
You took my choices and tried to break me.
But you're never gonna do that
to anybody ever again.
Nobody leaves
this room until she's dead.
Make her suffer.
I don't wanna hurt you.
You don't wanna hurt me.
Hey.
Are you okay?
That looks like it hurts.
Okay. I take out on three, ready?
I'm sorry.
What do we do now?
Get as far away
from here as possible.
You get to make your own choices now.
We gotta get outta here.
We need to find Dreykov.
Are you coming?
I'm right behind you.
Wait, wait! I have to go back!
Yes!
Do you see the girls?
No!
We need to go back.
We've lost control.
Antonia.
No!
I'm gonna open the door.
You're gonna come after me.
It's okay. It's okay.
I know you're still in there.
And I'm not gonna leave you.
Okay.
Yelena!
She's on the wing!
Move! What are you waiting for?
Don't do it!
This was fun!
No!
Okay.
Let's go.
Enough.
I'm sorry.
Is he gone?
He's gone.
Yelena!
Yelena?
We're both upside down.
Forgive me little sister.
I should've come back for you.
You don't have to say that.
- It's okay.
- Hey. Hey.
It was real to me, too.
Thank you.
Everybody good?
I am clearly injured.
You got something to say?
I'd just mess it up.
Here comes the cavalry.
We're closing in on the target, sir.
So, what's our plan?
You guys go. I'll stay.
That's insanity. We fight.
We fight with you.
- I'll hold them off.
- Natasha, we fight.
We can't split up.
You're so pigheaded.
- You guys, go.
- Oh, my God.
Besides, if it can work out
with the four of us, you know,
there may be some hope for the Avengers.
Little bit.
Okay, well, if you're leaving,
then I guess you should take this.
I know how much you like it.
Shucks.
It does have a lot of pockets.
Very handy pockets, yeah.
He had widows implanted
all over the world.
Melina will need to copy the formula,
but you should be the one
to tell 'em it's over.
You came back for us.
We wouldn't leave you behind.
Thank you.
Hey.
Hey. You take care of yourself, okay?
Don't worry. I got this.
I know.
Don't worry.
We're bringing her with us.
Come. Come with us.
You ever not sleep?
I've been in six different time zones
in three days because of you.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah.
What, are you scrapping together
some parts?
What'd you get me this time,
like, an upside-down lawnmower?
You see what I can get you
with a bit of time and money?
Go on, say it.
I wanna hear it.
It would really be good for me
to hear it. Really.
I'm impressed.
Well, yeah.
You've always been
a really good friend to me.
That's what every man wants to hear.
Where you gonna go?
It's funny. My whole life,
I didn't think I had any family.
Turns out I got two, so...
One of them's a bit of a mess right now.
I'm gonna go break
a few of them out of prison
see if I can't help patch things up.
Come on, Fanny.
Wow. Sorry.
I'm allergic to the Midwest.
What this woman did,
honestly, I can't even imagine.
You're not supposed to be bothering me
on my holiday time, Valentina.
Oh, bothering you? Oh, no, no.
I'm just here paying my respects.
Hmm...
You know, coming here
makes you look desperate.
Okay.
I want a raise.
Oh, yeah. You and me both.
Believe me, you're gonna earn it.
I've got your next target.
Thought I'd hand-deliver it.
Maybe you'd like a shot at the man
responsible for your sister's death.
Kind of a cutie, don't you think?