i tell people my sister moved out west
you sciense teacher
your husband he renovate houses
you're thinking about moving
but you're gonna wait
until the interest rates go down
that's not my story
before i was an avenger
i mean mistakes
a lot of enemies
it's called science taskmaster
he controls the red room
there manipulated
fully conscious but no choices
i should have come back for you
how many others are there
enough
subtitle:reza hamzehpour
instagram:reza_hzp_
we have to go back where it all started
so the never do that to anyone again
we're family
we fight with you
you won't win
i was for the best
but look into past
okay you go to plan well shall i just say doggan
cuz my plan was to drive us away where
your plan sucks
at some point we all have to choose
between what the world wants you to be
who you are
and me my choice
i'm done morning
instagram:reza_hzp_
here's what's gonna happen
natasha dont slouch
I'm not slouching
you're going to get he back hucched
listen to your mother
oh my god
all right enough all you
it didn't say anything
that's not fair