[craft flying overhead]
[engines powering down]
Lieutenant Carapax,
tell me that
you've found the Scarab.
They're cutting into it now.
Ah! That's exciting.
[Carapax] I've had them working
around the clock
since we unearthed it
about two weeks ago.
[woman] Good.
Let's keep this thing airtight
until we're ready
to show the board.
Miss Kord. Miss Kord?
- Oh, Dr. Sanchez, hello.
- Sorry.
Hi. Actually,
that's not my name.
How much longer you think
it's gonna be?
We'll hit the center
before sunrise.
[woman] Well,
push your men harder.
I've searched for 15 years.
I don't want
to wait another second.
[Sanchez] Should've called before
making the trip out, Miss Kord.
This could be another decoy.
It's in there.
I can feel it.
[deep rumbling]
["Atrévete-te-te"
by Calle 13 playing]
[woman speaking on PA, indistinct]
[sighing]
[man] All right. Let's do this.
[woman speaking in Spanish
on PA, indistinct]
Excuse me, sir? How do I look?
Like you're six figures in debt.
Okay.
[in Spanish]
[scoffs]
[Alberto speaks Spanish]
We say nothing for now.
Let's enjoy this moment.
Before he knows.
I'll tell him.
[in Spanish]
What the hell? Why not?
Even good news
[in Spanish]
And this is pretty bad news.
I can be joyful.
[Rocío] Your job is the balloon.
[Milagro] Hope I can handle it.
Handle what?
- [all yelling joyfully]
- Hey, hey, hey!
The graduate is here!
[laughing]
- [Rocío] How was your flight?
- Good.
- Are you hungry?
- Of course.
Here. It's all they had.
- [Milagro] Welcome back, bro.
- Thank you.
- Nana! ¿Te gusta?
- [Nana laughing]
Me encanta. [smooching]
[in Spanish]
Now we hug!
[all murmuring happily]
[man] Hey, where's Uncle Rudy?
["La Chona" by Los Tucanes De Tijuana
playing]
[truck horn playing
"La Cucaracha"]
[engine stops]
[whistles sharply]
¡Eso, mi Rudy!
[Rudy] ¡Eso! Welcome back,
pinche college boy.
Hey! Come on. Get out the car
and give me a hug.
No. No hugs, man.
They got Big Brother watching.
There's cameras.
I knew you were gonna
say something.
[Rudy] Facial recognition.
Body imaging scanners.
[Milagro] Yeah, and they're
all so happy to finally catch you.
You see? It's that kind
of talk right there
that's gonna get us all busted.
Where'd you get this?
[Milagro] I bought it for Jaime.
A boy? We know it's a boy.
There's probably a bug in here.
Come on. What are you doing?
["Cumbia Poder"
by Celso Piña playing]
[playing trumpet]
Oh, my God!
I missed this so much.
[inhales deeply]
Good to know
some things don't change.
Mom and Dad
have something to tell you.
- Milagro.
- [Milagro] What?
Okay, he's had his tacos,
now let him have the truth.
The truth? What is it?
- We, eh...
- [Rocío] We...
We're losing the house.
[spits, coughs] What?
See?
- He didn't take it that bad.
- No, no, no, losing the house?
What does she mean,
losing the house?
- The landlord tripled the rent.
- They gave us three months
to come up with the money
or get out.
I am so sorry, flaquito.
No. Amá, don't be sorry.
It's not your fault.
It just means that
we're gonna have to
bust our ass at the shop, right?
Mmm... auto shop's gone.
- How?
- You can thank Kord for that.
- [Alberto] Brother.
- [Rocío] We couldn't keep up.
Especially since your dad, he...
He, uh... had a...
- [stammering] He...
- Dad had a heart attack.
What?
I'm fine!
[in Spanish]
At least the food's the same.
¿Qué no, cabezón?
Wait, why didn't you tell me?
You were working so hard,
mi amor.
We didn't want
to distract you from school.
Ma, I could have done something.
I could have come back.
I could have been here.
I could have...
[Alberto] Ánimo, Jaime.
We figured it out. We always do.
We have a lot
to be grateful for. Mira...
[in Spanish]
Yeah. And the last!
Yes, because you didn't apply.
[Milagro] What,
so I can get into debt
for the rest of my life?
No thanks.
[Milagro sighs]
What? 25 percent?
Mi amor,
these people make nothing.
We are broke.
[Alberto] Let's worry
about money tomorrow.
["Sin Ti" by Los Panchos playing]
[Milagro] Remember
how Mom taught us salsa
right there on the front porch?
[Jaime] You were always
better than me.
[Milagro] Yeah.
No, I still think you don't know
- how to dance salsa.
- [Jaime laughing]
[Jaime] Yeah, I got
two left feet. I can't help it.
[Milagro] Yeah.
Do you remember
your 21st birthday?
[Jaime groaning]
I remember the first half.
[sighing] I can't believe
we're losing this place.
[Milagro] It was rough.
[Jaime] Yeah, well,
I'm not leaving again.
- [distant chatter, laughter]
- [rooster crowing in distance]
What about grad school?
Well, that's not gonna
help the family.
I can't get us
into even more debt.
Ánimo, bro.
Okay, you always land
on your feet.
You're "Jaime."
Thank you, but...
[sighing] This wasn't how
it was supposed to happen, Mili.
What was supposed to happen?
I was supposed to make it out.
I was supposed to get all of us
out of here.
Thanks, bro,
but I like the Keys.
- You know what I meant.
- Yeah.
Doesn't it bother you
that they talk about progress
and get everything
while we have to sit here
and go broke?
You're a Mexican
in Edge Keys, carnal.
That progress is not for us.
Okay? The poor go over here
and the rich go over there,
until the rich want to be here
and push us out.
We used to have the other side
of the tracks
and now they want that too.
I still have a degree, right?
That's gotta mean something.
I'll get a job.
Not just any job,
but a prime job.
Yeah, I'm gonna get the money
to save this place.
[Jaime chuckles]
Don't look at me at like that.
Look, Mili, I'm telling you,
in five years,
we're gonna be rolling in it.
This is just gonna be
one of our houses.
We're gonna have the mansion
on the water
with the marble everywhere,
infinity pool.
Yeah, just watch, Mili.
Just watch.
["Será Que No Me Amas"
by Damiano playing]
[Milagro]
Excuse me, Mister Reyes?
You finish scraping the gum
off that lounger or what?
[groans]
This is bullshit.
Wow. "Thanks, Milagro,
for hooking me up
with this gig."
It's not my fault your future
didn't turn out
the way you wanted.
How am I supposed to
get experience
when nobody's gonna
give me a job?
Sounds like a "you" problem.
Seriously?
What? I'm keeping us employed,
you noob!
[Ms. Kord] Yes, yes,
we've finally found it.
Doctor Sanchez
is running tests on it now.
- With the actual code in hand...
- Hey.
We can move
beyond the prototype phase.
Check it out.
Yes, yes.
There goes Victoria Kord.
- Look at that walk.
- [Victoria speaking, indistinct]
She's kinda sexy in like a...
Cruella Kardashian sorta way.
- I'm gonna say hi.
- No...
Good afternoon, ma'am.
If you want, we could.
It's the breakthrough we've
been working towards, General.
Mm-hm.
We're invisible
to people like that, Jaime.
It's like our superpower.
Okay. Back to work.
I agree. That's a waste of time,
but General, I am telling you
what I'm gonna show
you tomorrow night
is gonna blow you away.
Yes. I look forward, also.
Bye.
[woman] Aunt Vicki?
[groaning sigh]
[exhales]
[Victoria] Jennifer,
what are you doing here?
I didn't know you were coming.
Oh, Carapax,
this is Ted's daughter.
My favorite niece, Jennifer.
So, to what do I owe
this unexpected pleasure?
[Victoria on TV]
The world has changed.
Kord Industries faces
an unprecedented challenge
to secure our assets,
both here and abroad,
from our promethium mines
in Guatamala,
to our real estate developments
right here in Palmera City.
Introducing the future
of private policing:
The OMAC,
the "One Man Army Corps."
Where are we going?
Gotta take a shit, bro.
Need you to be a lookout.
Wait, but the service restrooms
are out there.
Yeah, and I deserve a luxury
dump right now, all right?
[in Spanish]
I...
[Victoria on TV] Using
revolutionary Kord symbiotech,
the OMAC connects directly
into the human brain,
to create a self-contained
war unit,
allowing a single soldier
to harness the power of legions.
The OMAC ensures security
Kord can rely on.
A future we can control.
The OMAC.
[pleased sigh]
Think it works pretty well,
don't you?
[exhaling] So, this project
was shut down years ago.
Why have you relaunched it?
[chuckling] Jennifer, the OMAC
is the future of this company.
You should be so excited.
No, no, no. I really want
to know what's at Pago Island?
- That's classified.
- Mm.
It's a secret.
But I'll tell you,
what isn't classified
is what's gonna go on
at this party.
It's gonna be an amazing evening
with some
very interesting people,
so if you wanna come,
bring someone and it'll be fun.
All right, see you later.
[smooching]
I know what you're doing, Vicki.
We don't make weapons anymore.
Whoa, whoa, "We"?
Who's "we"?
You are nothing to this company.
You're an expense.
A brat in her daddy's
board seat,
jet-setting around the world
on the company's dime,
- doing your "charity work."
- My father would never...
Look, your father was handed
a company I built... my company.
Which he then proceeded
to almost sink
with his moronic inventions
and his reckless management,
and then after he'd
done all that,
you know what he did?
He just disappeared,
and left me
to pick up the pieces.
Your father
abandoned this company.
And he abandoned you.
I won't let you do this.
Don't get in my way, Jennifer.
Back away.
- I'm not afraid of you.
- [Victoria chuckles]
[whispering]
Maybe you should be.
- [Carapax growls]
- Hey, hey!
Uh, sh... she said
to back away, ma'am.
[growls]
[toilet flushing]
Oooh-whee!
That was lavish!
Oh, shit.
And who are you, handsome?
Jaime Reyes.
I think it's time to find
a new job, Jaime Reyes.
- I'm...
- You too, toilet. Go.
Ándale.
Thanks.
[Jaime] Where's the car?
[Milagro] Uh, 47 minutes.
Hey, are you okay? That was...
I appreciate the chivalry,
but I can take care
of myself, okay?
Totally. But I mean...
what a dick, right?
She's a Kord. They're all dicks.
[Jenny chuckles]
Jenny Kord.
We're not all dicks.
- Obviously. Yeah. Uh...
- [Jenny] Uh...
Look I'm...
I'm really sorry about this.
It's fine.
Give me your phone.
Let me give you my number.
Okay. Yeah.
Yeah. Come by
Kord Tower tomorrow.
Okay.
I might be able to get you a job
somewhere else in our company.
Yes. Oh, my gosh.
That'd be great.
I'll do anything. Really.
[chuckles]
Anything, huh?
Hey, you know
he has a degree, right?
- Pre-law.
- I... Yeah.
- You guys need any pre-lawyers?
- [laughs]
Okay.
- Text me.
- Okay.
Nice meeting you, Jaime Reyes.
Nice to meet you, too...
Jenny Kord.
I think she might be into you.
- [car starts]
- What? No.
[sweetly] Bye.
- You think?
- Yeah. Yeah.
She took one look
at your young Mexican-ass,
hero-of-the-moment vibe
and was into it.
Hey, you know what?
Maybe she'll pull you
out of poverty
like María la del Barrio.
Okay.
Except, she's
the rich white dude
and you're the María!
- Yeah. Okay.
- [laughs]
[singing in Spanish]
[woman singing on TV]
[humming along]
- [shouting with audience]
- [trumpet playing]
[man speaking Spanish]
["Deportivo" playing on phone]
- [sighs]
- [typing on phone]
[exhales deeply]
[song continues, muffled]
["Gracias a La Vida"
playing on radio outside]
[Jaime] You drinking?
- Just one.
- Okay.
- Don't tell your mother.
- [both chuckling]
Can't sleep?
No.
[in Spanish]
[sighing] Yeah.
I planted those nopales with
la Nana,
when you were a baby.
Look at them now.
Like you and la Mili,
grown and beautiful.
You okay?
Yeah.
Sorry, Apá, it's just
everything right now
feels so out of reach, and...
I feel like I failed you guys.
[Jaime sighs shakily]
We're on a journey, Jaime.
This house, the nopales,
el auto shop.
Everything.
They're just a stop
in the journey.
But this isn't the destination.
And what is it?
I don't know.
What's important is that
we go on this journey together.
Things don't last.
La familia, that's forever.
That lasts.
[in Spanish]
[both laughing]
- Everyone has a purpose.
- [Jaime sighs]
You just haven't found yours.
So what's your purpose then?
I'm still searching, too.
[chuckles]
But right now, it's this.
Talking to you, right here.
Ánimo, mijo.
[sighs heavily]
Okay.
["No Vamos" by Rainao playing]
[Jaime gasps]
[exhales nervously]
All right, okay, Jaime.
You got this.
[exhales]
[Alberto] ¡Ánimo, mijo!
God...
Thank you, Apá.
Ya, pues, you guys
can go, okay?
You're gonna be okay, flaquito.
You belong here.
Yeah, cabezón.
You look like an asshole
just like everybody else here.
[Nana, in Spanish]
[blessing in Spanish]
- Okay.
- [laughing]
- Bring your A-game, bro.
- Yeah.
Bring a Molotov cocktail
to burn this dump down!
Okay! ¡Ya!
Hey and get me a job too!
[all chanting]
Jaime, Jaime, Jaime...
They don't get out much.
- [all continue chanting]
- [beeping horn in rhythm]
[Victoria over loudspeaker]
Hello, I'm Victoria Kord,
and this is Kord industries,
a company with the planet
in its sight
and the future on its mind.
We are taking our
cutting edge technology...
Hi, nice to meet you.
Deliveries are downstairs.
Uh, no, no, no.
My name is Jaime.
Jaime Reyes.
I'm here to see Jenny Kord.
Do you have an appointment,
Jamie?
- It's Jaime, but...
- Sorry?
[stammering] Uh...
Yes, I do have an appointment.
She said to drop by,
so I'm sure I should...
- You can stand there.
- Okay.
Why don't you have a seat,
Jamie?
Okay. Thank you.
[clicks, beeps]
[door latches, beeps]
[device humming]
[Jenny] She found it.
[exhaling]
[machine stops humming]
[women chattering faintly]
Jenny?
[grunts] Uh... Okay...
[Sanchez] Okay.
Just me and you.
[chuckling]
No.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no...
No!
No, no, no, no, no!
[phone beeps]
There's been a security breach.
Lock the building.
Lock the building!
[elevator dings]
Jenny! Jenny.
What?
- [woman] Hey!
- [woman 2] Oh!
[man exclaims]
[Jaime] Jenny!
Oh... Sorry.
Hey, Jenny Kord!
It's me. Jaime from yesterday.
- I'm sorry, I'm in a rush.
- No, that's all good.
But you know, yesterday you said
you'd consider getting me a job
and, you know,
I can't leave without one
even if that sounds too...
Do you think you could pause
for one second? Please...
Look, Jaime,
this is really a bad time.
Okay. Let's, let's talk
while you have lunch.
- [alarm blaring]
- Please...
- [indistinct radio chatter]
- [guard] Stay on comms.
You said you'd
do anything, right?
Yeah. Basically, anything.
Here.
- Guard that with your life.
- Okay.
But do not open it.
Do not touch it!
Don't even look at it!
Okay. I'm just gonna
guard it with my life.
Yeah, you're a quick learner.
- Yeah.
- Good. Now go!
- Okay. Okay!
- Go, go, go!
Lock up the south entrances!
You two, with me!
[guards shouting, indistinct]
[guards chattering]
[indistinct radio chatter]
["El Rey" by Vicente Fernández
playing on radio]
[Milagro] So, you went in
to get us jobs,
and all you brought back
was a hamburger?
Okay, I don't think
it's a burger.
You haven't looked?
She said not to open it. I...
- Oh...
- [Milagro scoffs]
- [Rudy] She's not here.
- [Jaime] What?
[in Spanish]
[all chanting in Spanish]
Okay, okay. One look.
You guys are so childish.
[Rudy] What the hell is that?
[Milagro] Hmm.
[Rocío, in Spanish]
Why was she hiding it?
I don't know.
[Milagro] Hmm...
It's kind of a letdown.
The world's biggest tick.
[Rudy and Milagro chuckle]
Okay. You guys are the ones
who wanted to see it.
Hey, hey, hey!
Milagro. Okay, look.
Very mature, but she said
to not open it, so please...
Mmm, she said for you
to not open it, bro.
[exclaiming]
Stop, stop. Hey, oye.
[Rudy groans, speaks Spanish]
- It's heavy.
- Okay, okay.
I'm gonna use a motor,
all right?
- I'm gonna get my drill.
- Wait, wait!
Don't get the drill!
What are you doing?
God, I hate when you do that.
- [device humming]
- Whoa.
[Rudy] Whoa,
is that the new Tamagotchi?
[Milagro] How did you
get it to do that?
[Jaime] I don't know.
Amá.
I think it likes me.
What the hell!
[all screaming]
It doesn't like me!
Jaime, it's on your face!
It's on your face!
[yelling] Get it off!
[screaming] Alberto!
[yelling in Spanish]
Cabezón!
[Rudy shrieks]
[song continues playing]
[song stops]
[music playing faintly
on headphones]
[humming along with music]
[yelling]
[glass shattering]
What the hell?
[Rocío speaking Spanish]
[Jaime panting heavily]
[device whirring, muffled]
Where did it go?
[Rudy] Oh, man! I'm trying
to help you, cabezón!
I think it's inside of me.
[gasping]
Oh, my God! It's inside of me!
Inside you? How?
[in Spanish]
- [Jaime yelling]
- [all screaming]
[grunting in pain]
[screaming]
[all screaming]
He's possessed!
[Jaime groaning loudly]
[screaming]
Oh, my God.
[Rocío] Jaime!
[Jaime screaming] Milagro!
Jaime!
Rudy, what's going on?
[yelling]
[screaming, distorted]
He's moving.
- Jaime?
- He's moving.
No, no, no! No!
[yells]
Damn! Shit.
That scared
the frijoles outta me.
Are you okay, mijo?
[Rudy] Cabezón.
Jaime.
Flaquito.
[water sizzling]
What the f...
[female voice] Host acquired.
[Jaime] Who said that?
[female voice] System
configuration initializing.
[Jaime] Wait.
You don't hear that?
Don't look at him in the eyes.
[female voice] Analyzing host.
- Flaco?
- Mijo?
[Jaime]
There's a voice in my head.
- [female voice] Hello, Jaime.
- What is happening?
[female voice]
Begin systems check in three...
Systems check?
[female voice] ...two, one.
Thrusters engaged.
It's okay. It's gonna be okay!
[screaming]
[Jaime yelling]
What are you doing?
What's happening?
[female voice] Escape velocity
protocol engaged.
Whoa! Where are you taking me?
[female voice]
Crossing atmospheric layers.
[Jaime screaming]
Whoa, stop!
[female voice] Adjusting pressure
for host protection.
[Jaime panting]
Ay, virgencita, I'm in space.
I'm in space.
Oh, man, I'm in space.
[gasping]
[panting heavily]
What the hell is going on?
Wait, is that my house?
[female voice]
Testing re-entry systems.
Wait, wait, wait! No, no, no!
[screaming]
No, no, no, no!
[panicked gasping]
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God, I'm on fire!
[screaming]
Stop, stop, stop! Oh, God!
Fly, fly!
No. No, no, no.
[female voice]
Approaching contact.
Oh, my God, I'm gonna die!
[female voice]
Three hundred meters.
[Jaime] Padre Nuestro...
- Two hundred meters.
- ...que estás en el cielo...
- Santificado sea tu nombre...
- One hundred meters.
Venga a nosotros tu reino...
[Jaime screaming] Whoa!
[female voice]
Braking systems check complete.
Oh, thank God it's over.
Okay, you can take me home now.
[female voice]
Flight systems engaged.
Wait, wait, wait...
Don't engage!
Stop, stop, stop!
["Demolición" by Los Saicos playing]
[grunts, yelling]
Listen to me!
You've got the wrong guy!
I swear! I'm a nobody!
[Jaime spluttering]
Oh, come on!
[shrieks]
[female voice]
Testing acceleration systems.
Too fast! Too fast!
[Jaime] Watch out,
watch out, watch out!
- [man] What was that?
- [shockwaves booming]
I don't know what I'm doing!
[woman yells]
- Sorry about that.
- [truck roaring]
[female voice]
Fine-tuning flight control.
[yells]
[horns blaring]
Watch out. Watch out!
Pull up! Pull up!
Why are you doing this to me?
[female voice] Host overreacting.
Overreacting? You kidnapped me!
[in Spanish]
Twenty minutes, I think.
- Man, has it hit you yet?
- No.
- 'Cause it ain't hit me.
- Man, has it hit you?
- Nah, man.
[car horn honking]
[people exclaiming]
[Jaime groaning] My back!
[female voice]
Landing systems check complete.
[pedestrian] What was that?
- [Jaime] Are you guys okay?
- What did you do to my car, man?
Hey, hey,
do you have insurance, man?
Oh, I'm in so much trouble.
[female voice]
Threat approaching.
- [horn blaring]
- [Jaime gasps]
[yelling]
What the hell?
[people screaming, distorted]
[Jaime gasping]
[yelling]
- [people screaming]
- [tires skidding]
[people shrieking]
Oh, no, what did you do?
[female voice]
Host protection successful.
[Jaime] Hey, hey, look,
is anyone hurt?
Oh, no. Calm down.
I can explain.
There's nothing to worry about.
Oh, my God, there's a kid!
It wasn't me, I swear.
This is gonna sound crazy,
but I'm not in control...
[female voice]
Systems check complete.
Oh, no, not again.
[shockwave booms]
[people chattering excitedly]
I think it just hit me.
[newscaster speaking Spanish
on radio]
Let me explain that again.
He's technically
not a missing person,
but he is missing.
- But also, he is...
- Possessed!
- [Rocío murmuring in Spanish]
- [chiding in Spanish]
He exploded out of the roof.
With rockets on his back.
[Milagro] Shouldn't we be
out there looking for him?
- [Alberto speaks Spanish]
- No, no, no!
[drill whirring]
I'm on hold again.
[Jaime yelps, groaning]
[female voice]
Return landing successful.
Never mind. We found him.
[groaning]
[in Spanish]
[Rocío] Jaime?
[Milagro] Yo, put those
huevos away, bro.
[Nana cackling]
[in Spanish]
[Rudy, in Spanish]
[Rocío, in Spanish]
- It's Jamie, not Jaime.
- [Rocío yelps]
[all murmuring]
[Rudy] Oh, no.
[rooster crowing in distance]
[newscaster reporting
in Spanish on radio]
[sniffs]
[gasps] Huh?
What are you guys doing?
[comforting in Spanish]
[in Spanish]
He's alive.
Jaime. Do you feel okay, mijo?
Oh!
No. No way.
- [gasps]
- [Milagro] Jaime, listen,
- there's something on...
- No, not now, Milagro.
- Jaime, I'm serious.
- No, no, no. Not now, Milagro.
- Not now!
- There's something on your...
[Rudy] Hey, Jaime,
keep that blanket
now that it touched
your chorizo.
What is going on?
You can't fly.
You can't fly. Superman can fly.
Those people on that bus
were okay. They're fine.
Okay. This probably
happens all the time.
Yeah, she wouldn't
do this to me.
Yeah, right. Okay.
[inquisitive grunt]
[whimpers]
[Jaime screaming]
[Rocío speaks Spanish]
I tried telling him.
Okay, guys.
I-I need to go find Jenny Kord,
'cause she's gonna know how
to get this thing out of me.
Uh, where are my shoes?
Come on, where are my... shoes.
Not the 84s!
These were my favorite shoes.
Okay, okay.
Jaime, what happened?
Where did you go?
Amá, I don't know.
I think I cut a bus in half
and then...
- Cut what?
- ...and flew into orbit.
- ¿Cómo que flew into orbit?
- Apá, I don't know.
- That's why I need Jenny.
- I am calling the police.
No, no. Don't call the police.
No police.
They work for Kord.
What do you think
Kord's gonna do
when they figure out
that some Mexican kid
has that type of military tech
inside of him?
They're gonna lock his ass up.
And then they're gonna
wipe our minds,
so that we don't tell anybody.
And it's not like
the government isn't
used to locking up
Mexicans anyway.
I mean, this is sci-fi shit.
This is CIA.
- This is Area 51!
- Rudy, focus. What do you mean?
What I'm saying
is the government and Kord
are gonna be all over this,
and then they're gonna
start asking for documents.
And that includes you, Nana.
And that includes you, Alberto.
Okay then fine. I'm just gonna
have to go by myself then.
You are not leaving this house.
Amá, I'm 22!
Besides, what if she's
in danger?
What if she's in danger?
Jaime, you flew out of the roof.
- You don't understand.
- Ah, ah...
- He's into her.
- Oh, he totally is.
- No, I'm not.
- Oh!
- Stalked her Insta.
- Where'd I put my...?
She's Brazilian,
she lives at the Regent Tower.
And she's single, by the way.
Bit of a loner, though,
if you ask me. I mean...
She's single?
I thought you weren't into her.
What are you doing
with my phone?
You left it unlocked.
[in Spanish]
Yes, the María.
Yes, I said the same thing.
But María la del Barrio.
[in Spanish]
[singing in Spanish]
[all singing in Spanish]
- You hear that, flaco?
- Rudy!
¿Qué pasó?
[truck engine starting]
No. No, no.
No. No. No!
[Rocío] Jaime!
- No! No! No!
- [truck driving off]
Ma!
[in Spanish]
[scolding in Spanish]
["Cumbia Sampuesana"
by Celso Piña playing]
- [tires screeching]
- [horn honking]
[groaning] So itchy, this thing.
Ay, Okay.
No way.
What the...
Wait, what?
Jenny?
[tire squeals]
- [Jenny] Oh, my gosh.
- What are you doing here?
- Just go. They're coming.
- Who's them?
Them!
- [bullets striking]
- [Jenny shrieks]
- Oh, God. Okay!
- Let's go! Let's go!
[Jaime] Okay, okay! Oh, my God!
[Jenny] I told you to go!
You should have started with,
"they have guns."
- [Jaime yelling]
- Watch out!
[horn blaring]
[Jaime] Oh, Rudy's gonna kill me.
[Rudy screaming in distance]
- [Rudy] oh, my headlights!
- [glass breaking outside]
No! My mirrors!
What the hell, man? [shrieks]
What's wrong with you? ¡Cabezón!
Do you want some water?
[Rudy] My tailgate!
No, I'm... I'm good. I'm fine.
- [Alberto] Okay.
- [door opens]
What did you do to the Taco?
[clears throat]
And that... that's Rudy.
My name's César, okay?
And only my friends
call me Rudy.
- I'm Jenny.
- [mocking] "I'm Jenny."
Hi, Jenny.
We know who you are.
What are you doing here?
Thinking about turning our house
into a nuclear power plant?
I went swimming out there
by where your family
has that company.
My testicles are seven times
their normal size.
Shouldn't you be
pillaging cobalt
from some developing country
or something, Jenny?
- Where is it?
- Yeah.
- Allow me.
- [family exclaiming]
Rudy! What?
- What are you doing?
- [Milagro] Rudy!
[speaking Spanish]
[Rocío yelling in Spanish]
I thought the chingaderas
would come out.
- Come out?
- Jeez.
- What is he talking about?
- He's talking about this.
- [Nana exclaims]
- [gasping]
[gags] Oh, I forgot
how bad it looks.
[in Spanish]
No, it doesn't look that bad.
I've seen worse.
- Where?
- You don't wanna know.
Okay,
what the hell is this thing?
It's... it's called the Scarab.
It was given to my dad
when I was a kid, um...
It's some kind
of a world destroying weapon.
Oh, that's nice.
- Weapon?
- What did she say?
[Jaime groaning] What?
And did you know what was
gonna happen to my brother
when you stuck him with
this world destroying thing?
No, I swear to you,
I had no idea this would happen.
I mean, come on.
My father said it can't be
activated by just any person.
It has to choose you.
So I'm guessing it's chosen you.
[Rudy] No more blind dates.
Okay. So, how do we get it
to un-choose me?
I don't know.
But we better move fast,
because my aunt will kill us all
just to get it back.
- Kill us?
- [dismayed murmuring]
No, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean that.
She's the one who sent
the assassins.
- [Alberto questions in Spanish]
- Yeah.
[in Spanish]
[chattering in Spanish]
I'm so sorry I put you all
in this situation.
I had no idea it would activate.
Really. I didn't know.
- That's convenient.
- [all chattering]
But she already said
she didn't know.
She's a Kord, dude.
You seriously trust her?
[Alberto calming in Spanish]
We are going to figure it out.
We always do.
Come on, we are the Reyes.
We've dealt with harder things.
- We have?
- [Nana scolding in Spanish]
Ánimo. We can do this.
[Milagro murmurs]
Yeah. Yeah, Apá.
He's right.
Okay, so, how are we gonna
get this thing outta me?
You know, before it
busts another hole in our house.
- [Rocío] Exactly.
- [Jenny exhales]
There's a place where
we can get some answers.
But we need the key.
Okay, so where's the key?
At the Kord building.
And they're probably
on high alert over there
since I took the Scarab.
So, what are we talking about?
Laser-based security system?
Wide area motion imagery maybe?
Photonic emitters?
I really don't...
Because I've been
working on something
that I believe can help us.
And it's almost finished.
If I can get
the mechanical structure right.
Mm. I love you, Ma.
Give me a couple hours.
[people chattering, laughing]
[live band playing
"Tú Serás Mi Baby"]
- [champagne cork pops]
- [people laughing]
[singing in Spanish]
[man] You're aware that
if you deliver the OMAC,
you'd be the most powerful
weapons manufacturer
in the world.
If you buy into this, you can
call me whatever you want.
Oh, if it isn't
the devil himself.
[chuckles]
General,
this is Lieutenant Carapax.
He's been crucial to the
development of the prototype,
and I personally handpicked him
for his courage
during the anti-communist
counter-terrorism operations
in Guatemala.
He's the perfect recipient
for the OMAC,
and a product of the school
of the Americas.
Great to meet you, Lieutenant.
[Victoria chuckles]
Well, can't wait to see it
in action.
- When will it be ready?
- Oh, it's ready, isn't it?
We're just putting some
finishing touches on it.
[quietly] We have a problem.
Well, if you'll excuse us.
Have a cigar,
they're made by real Cubans.
[Victoria] You lost her? How?
My men saw someone helping her.
All right. I wanna find out
who she is working with now.
Because without the Scarab,
we can't complete the OMAC.
I'm on it.
I will bring the Scarab back.
This time I'll do it personally.
Well, I would hope so,
Carapax, because if not,
all your sacrifices
will have been in vain.
Just think of how much suffering
your body has been through.
I'm aware
of what you've done to it.
My God... What we've done.
Ignacio, I'm on your side.
Do you not remember what
it was like when I found you?
How badly crippled you were?
How broken?
I am just trying to fix you.
Okay?
Good.
I have to go back to the party.
Now, go get me that Scarab.
[Rudy chuckles]
That's it?
I call it, El Chapulín.
Why?
You know,
when you make something cool,
you can call yours
whatever you want, okay?
Here, be useful. Hold that.
[Jaime] You're sure
that this one works?
Thank you. Yes.
Unlike the junk that Kord makes,
my tech delivers.
Okay.
You could have just said yes.
Okay, cupcake, you wanna
hit that yellow switch there?
- [buzzes]
- [Rudy] Hit the yellow switch.
- I just did.
- [button clicking]
[Rudy mutters in Spanish]
Okay.
Well, at least I don't have to
open that annoying tailgate.
It's going on your tab.
So just give me, like, one step.
Just gotta give it a little...
[motor whining]
[playing quirky electronic
theme song]
- [Rudy] Oh, that's sexy.
- Great.
That's... that's great.
Uh, so it works.
- [device powering up]
- Uh, yeah, it works.
I'll keep the truck running.
- Let's go.
- [Rudy] Wow.
[Rudy mutters in Spanish]
[mocking] "So it works?"
[static crackling]
Guys!
Something's happening.
[quirky theme music playing]
[narrator speaking Spanish on TV]
What the hell is this?
[laughing]
¡El Chapulín Colorado!
[speaking Spanish]
[laughs]
[Victoria on speaker]
So join me and my little pals
and all of our Kord
subsidiaries...
[Jenny] The key's here.
...around the globe,
to build a better future.
A Kord future.
She seemed so different
back then.
Vicki and my grandfather started
Kord Industries together...
...and turned it
into a military powerhouse.
Then, when my grandfather died,
Victoria thought the company
would go to her.
But he left everything
to my dad instead.
- Seems kind of...
- Sexist?
[chuckling] Yeah.
Yeah.
Still, my father wanted
to steer the company
in a different direction.
So, Victoria became obsessed
with erasing my father's legacy.
Could I get a hand over here?
Yeah, sorry. What do you need?
- Just hold this.
- Okay.
There's a signal blocking
our feed.
We're being jammed out.
[Spanish dialogue looping on TV]
[line dialing]
Lieutenant Carapax?
We got a problem.
- This is the key?
- Yeah.
- [watch beeps]
- Okay, let's go.
Let's go.
["Armando Sanchez" by
Chalino Sanchez playing on radio]
[muttering in Spanish]
This is why I don't let anyone
drive the Taco!
[Jenny] To be honest, I didn't
think the Chapulín would work.
[Jaime] Yeah, that's Rudy.
He's like the Mexican Doc Brown.
[Jenny laughing] No kidding.
- Okay.
- [Jaime] So that's all you need?
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
I don't know why I thought
it was gonna be
way harder than that.
- [Jaime exhales]
- Oh, shit.
The Scarab, now!
What is he doing here?
[growls]
[Jaime] Should we run?
He's not slowing down.
- Watch out! Watch out!
- [Jenny yelps]
[female voice] Hola, Jaime.
[Carapax grunts]
Oh, my gosh. How'd you do that?
I have no idea.
[growling]
Oh, he's pissed.
[screaming]
What the hell is that thing?
The OMAC.
[growling]
[Carapax]
You're going to regret that.
[female voice] Defending host.
[Jaime] Oh, my God. Quick!
Go find Rudy!
- [female voice] Engaging threat.
- [Jaime] Engage? No!
[Carapax grunting]
[Jaime] Oh, shit!
[both grunting with impact]
[Jaime] Okay, wait, wait, wait!
No, no, no, wait! Don't!
[yelling, grunting]
What did you do that for?
I told you not to engage.
[OMAC whirring]
[female voice] I have
an arsenal at my disposal.
No! No weapons.
["Bidi Bidi Bom Bom" by Selena
playing on radio]
Ooh! And my song, too! Ay!
[shrieks]
- César!
- What?
- What the heck, where's cabezón?
- There!
[panting]
[Jaime] Hey! Calm down!
Oh, shit!
- Let's go, let's go, let's go.
- Let's go, let's go!
[breath rasping]
[Jaime] Let me talk to him.
[female voice] Verbal
communication is ill-advised
in a combat scenario.
Hey, man, look! I think this is
just one big misunderstanding...
[pained yell]
I didn't mean
to punch you back there.
I promise, I would never...
[loud grunt] I'm not
in control of this thing.
[Carapax grunts]
[Jaime] No, no, no,
let me explain!
Never mind. He's not listening.
[female voice] Permission
to take over host.
Yes! Anything!
[suit powering up]
[grunting, yells]
[female voice]
Watch and learn, Jaime.
Hey, w-w-wait, where you going?
Come on.
What the hell?
Whoa!
[both grunting]
Oh, my God. My hands are guns.
[Carapax groaning]
[female voice]
Threat neutralized.
[Jaime] Oh!
What's with the blades?
[female voice]
Eliminating threat.
No, no, no. Put the blades away.
[female voice] Would you
like to use a different weapon?
[Jaime] No. I mean,
we don't have to kill him.
[female voice]
Eliminating threat.
[Jaime] Are you even
listening to me?
[female voice]
Eliminating threat.
Stop! I'm not a killer.
[female voice]
Command accepted.
- [horn playing "La Cucaracha"]
- Oh!
[Rudy] ¡Cabezón!
Jaime!
Uncle Rudy.
[Jaime] No!
- Holy shit!
- [both yelling]
Rudy!
Where do you think you're going?
[Jaime] Hey! You guys
gotta get out of here!
[yells, grunts]
- [Rudy coughing]
- [Jenny groans]
[Rudy] What's with this guy?
What?
Stupid boy.
Did you think you could beat me?
[female voice]
Recommend lethal measures.
[Jaime] I told you, I'm not a...
[yelling]
[female voice] Warning,
host concussion detected.
[Jaime groaning]
[yells, grunts heavily]
[Carapax]
You should have finished me
when you had the chance.
[groans]
He's gonna kill him.
[pained grunt]
[Carapax growling]
- No. He's not.
- [revving engine]
Hold on.
- [engine roars]
- [yelling]
Please, just don't
hurt my family.
The love you feel
for your family
makes you weak.
César! What are you doing?
Okay, Kord girl.
When I tell you, pull that
handbrake and pull it hard.
- You ready?
- Oh, my gosh, this is insane.
[Rudy] Three, two, one.
Now!
[yells]
[explosive grunt]
[Rudy] Cabezón,
let's get outta here!
[groaning]
[tires screeching]
Is he okay? Jaime! Jaime!
Jenny! Snap out of it!
- Okay.
- [Jaime] Don't look, don't look!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
[panting]
I'm fine, Rudy. Thank you.
All right. I got a T-shirt.
On the side.
All right. Okay.
- [Rudy] Man...
- [panting]
Oh, that psycho
almost killed me.
You got the key?
- All right.
- Yeah.
Good. Now, let's go get
that Scarab taken out of you.
- Khaji-Da.
- ¿Khaji qué?
The Scarab's name is Khaji-Da.
How do you know?
I... Something happened
back there. My...
It's like I feel it in my mind.
Is that crazy?
[sighing]
You're becoming symbiotic.
- What?
- Okay, where to now?
- Take that exit.
- What? Hold on!
- No, no, no!
- [tires screeching]
[horn blaring]
[Rudy] Does anybody in this town
know how to drive?
[birds squawking]
[Rudy] Oh!
[Jaime] They're not gonna
look for you here?
[Jenny] No one's been here
since I was eight.
[hinges creaking]
- [watch beeps]
- [mechanism rumbling]
[Rudy] Yeah, I get it.
That makes sense.
[Rudy] So, your dad was all
obsessed with scarabs, huh?
Where are we?
[machinery humming]
No way.
Wait.
Ted Kord was Blue Beetle?
Wow!
What the hell is Blue Beetle?
[Rudy] Oh, you were a kid.
It's like Palmera's superhero.
Like Superman in Metropolis
or the Flash in Central City.
But just, uh...
I don't know,
maybe just not... not as good.
I can't believe
he was the Blue Beetle.
Oh, I get it though.
Eccentric billionaire, a genius.
El Escarabajo Azul.
Your dad was a great man.
I had no idea.
You can call me César or Rudy.
You can call me whatever
you want, I don't care.
Hey, how come all of this...
- Are you okay?
- I'm fine.
Um, what were you saying?
Yeah, how come this stuff
doesn't look more like...
Nicer? Less ridiculous?
No. But I mean...
Like, look at this.
It's like Batman's stuff, but...
...like if he had ADHD
or something.
Batman's a fascist.
The Blue Beetle,
he had a sense of humor.
[chuckles]
My dad was never able
to unlock the Scarab.
So instead, he built his own
tech to fight as Blue Beetle.
If there's a way to get it out,
it's in there.
- [knuckles crack]
- Let's crack into this sucker.
[sniffs]
[sniffing]
- Damn, you stink.
- This is your shirt.
Come on, I think there's some
of my dad's clothes upstairs.
[Rudy] That's a good idea.
This is gonna take a minute.
[typing]
[sighs]
Jeez.
When is this day gonna end?
[exhaling]
Whoa.
Ay. [chuckles]
[Jenny] Is everything okay?
Um, yes. Yeah.
Yeah, I'll be right out.
Yeah, I think they, uh...
I think they fit.
And they're comfy too, so...
Good.
It must have been so cool
growing up
in a place like this, no?
Honestly, it was...
it was pretty lonely
most of the time.
[Jaime] It was just
you three in here?
[Jenny] Yeah.
That was my mother's
last painting.
Why'd she stop?
My mom died when I was six.
Oh... We don't...
- I'm so sorry to...
- It's okay. No, it's okay.
It's fine.
What was she like?
She was great.
[sniffles]
She changed my dad's life.
She was the one who taught him
that the world
is a place to protect.
Nice.
But when my mom died, he...
he really went adrift.
He obsessed over the Scarab
and he would disappear
for days.
Sometimes weeks.
And one day, he...
he left and...
...didn't come back.
I'm so sorry, Jenny.
You're really lucky.
This house is...
it's full of stuff.
Your house is full of love.
[sniffles]
[voice breaking] Your family.
Yeah.
That's a home.
[crying softly]
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
Sorry for... for what?
I... I haven't talked about this
in a very long time.
Kinda feels nice to,
maybe, right?
Thank you.
Yeah.
You're a good listener.
My mom says it's 'cause
I got big ears.
[chuckling lightly]
Hey guys,
I found something that... Ho!
- Nothing happened.
- Her mom died.
I found something you guys
need to look at.
Uh, great.
That's great. Let's go.
Nice jammies, güey.
[sighs]
[Rudy] Okay. [groans]
I've gone through the files.
So... Ted had a professor,
this guy named Dan Garrett.
The Scarab chose
this Garrett guy
before it chose you, Jaime.
And pinche Ted,
ran tests on him to map out
how the Scarab would react
to the human body.
So, once this Scarab
goes up someone's ass...
It didn't go up my ass.
Okay. Well, it connects
to the brain
and that's what it's trying
to do to you, Jaime,
connect to your brain.
It's trying to become one
with you.
Why?
I think you should
ask it yourself.
I mean, this thing
has its own will.
[Jenny] It's sentient.
That's why it chooses a host.
That's why sometime
it does what you want
and sometime it doesn't.
Okay, well, who made it?
Can they help us?
[chuckles] This wasn't made
on Earth, cabezón.
- No way.
- Sí way.
It's alien.
I don't really like
the term "alien."
- You can use it, but I just...
- Whatever, Rudy. Come on.
What happened
to Ted's professor guy?
How did he get it out?
You might want to sit down.
- Or not. All right...
- Rudy, please. Focus.
I got good news
and I got bad news.
The good news is,
I figured out how to get it out.
- Fine.
- [chuckles]
And the bad news is
that you have to be dead.
- What?
- Dead.
[Jaime] What do you mean "dead"?
[Rudy] Okay, right now,
Jaime, look.
It's fusing itself
to every cell in your body.
It's completely coiled
around your brain.
And there's nothing on earth
that could remove it.
It's designed
to protect its host.
To keep it alive.
So you're saying that
this thing's in me forever?
- [sighing]
- [Rudy] No, it's not forever.
I mean, it's just until you...
...until you die.
[stammering]
I think it's kinda cool.
No, I mean, basically,
you are a superhero, cabrón.
I'm so sorry.
I had no way of knowing...
Oh, you had no idea.
So then what are my options now?
So, option one is
to become an android
for the rest of my life.
Or option two is to hand myself
over to a murderous
- billionaire psychopath?
- I'm so sorry.
All I wanted was a job.
- [Rudy] Maybe there's a...
- Maybe what, Rudy?
It's all bad news.
Okay, this shit just doesn't
get any better for us.
I don't understand
why you can't...
God. [sighs]
Whatever. I'm gonna...
I'm gonna go for a walk.
[Jenny] Jaime, just...
Let me go talk to him.
I think I know where he's going.
Cabezón, wait up.
[door opens, hinges creaking]
[groaning]
God.
There he is.
I knew I'd find you out here.
[chuckles] Like a cat, Jaime.
[questions in Spanish]
[sighs]
I'm sorry for yelling
at you, Rudy.
I shouldn't have yelled you,
but...
It's not lost on me
that your situation
is a little bit
out of the ordinary.
[light chuckle] Yeah, we're...
We're resilient people.
Life will continue to hit us
with curve balls, and...
...difference is, when we
get hit, we get stronger.
Look at your old man.
He brought me here from Sonora.
I was ten. I think he was 19.
And people think
crossing the border is hard.
Yeah, it's hard,
but you know what's harder?
The next 20 years after,
I mean, la chinga.
But your viejo would work
16 hours a day, bust his ass.
Any jale he could
get his hands on.
Jornalero, bus boy, waiter.
He was a mechanic,
era de todo, dishwasher.
[speaks Spanish]
And to get us all here
and to keep us all together.
And not that he wanted to,
he had to.
That's what we come from.
The universe has
sent you a gift, Jaime.
And you have to figure out
what you're going to do with it.
Maybe this did all happen
for a reason.
Maybe it's time
that we get our own hero.
And not just some
foot up our ass. [chuckles]
Hey, but what do I know, huh?
I'm just some failed promise
that sleeps
in his brother's living room.
Don't say that, man.
You're not a failed promise.
Come on, you're the shit!
You know it.
- I am the shit.
- Yeah. [chuckles]
And... and I love you.
And I love you too, cabezón.
Yeah, all right.
- [door creaks open]
- [Jenny] Guys?
[aircraft thrumming]
Do you hear that?
That's Victoria.
[Rudy] Where are they going?
Home.
[water running]
[Alberto] You're wasting
too much water.
[gentle music playing on radio]
[Rocío chiding Milagro
in Spanish]
[Milagro groaning]
[pleased chuckle]
[Milagro] It's always my fault.
[Alberto reassures Milagro
in Spanish]
[Milagro] Yeah.
[Rocío speaking Spanish]
[low rumbling]
[mug rattling]
[Rocío continues in Spanish]
[in Spanish]
[rumble of aircraft approaching]
[Alberto speaks Spanish]
[rattling intensifies]
[soldiers chattering faintly]
Guys?
I think there's somebody
at the window.
[siren wailing outside]
[tarp rustling]
[aircraft thundering overhead]
[man over PA] Jaime Reyes,
come out with your hands up.
Turn yourself in.
We are authorized
to use deadly force.
Jaime Reyes,
come out with your hands up...
[in Spanish]
We are authorized
to use deadly force.
Okay. Okay.
Um...
I'm gonna fly. I'm gonna fly.
Let's do this.
Yeah!
Yeah, no chance.
[grunting]
Now!
- Ay!
- Dude, no worries.
- Just take your time.
- Thanks, Jenny.
- You gotta force it to come out.
- What do you...?
[frustrated panting]
Oh. Oh.
[laughs]
- You're a genius.
- I know. What'd I say?
You said this thing's
gonna protect me, right?
- [Rudy] I...
- It's not gonna let me die?
No, no. I mean, when you die...
All right,
let's see if it works.
[Rudy] I wouldn't test it.
- No, no, no, Jaime!
- Wait, wait, wait, Jaime!
[yelling]
[chuckles]
Well, back to the Tacoma,
I guess.
Yeah.
[indistinct chatter]
[soldier] We have
the Reyes house surrounded.
The family's inside.
[Victoria] You know what to do.
Round them up!
Breach team, go.
On me.
We're in!
Fan out. Flash!
Clear!
- Get the light on.
- I got your left!
Back room, clear!
Clear!
- [family whimpering]
- Hands on your head. Don't move.
- Okay, okay.
- [soldier] Don't move!
- Don't touch my family!
- Get up!
Let's go! Up, up!
Hands up! Watch your two!
- [Milagro whimpers]
- Miss Kord, we found the family.
- [soldier] We got 'em coming out.
- [soldier 2] Take 'em out.
Let's go.
- [soldier] Drag them out!
- [soldier commands in Spanish]
[Milagro yelling]
Come on! Let's go, come on!
- [Rocío] Let her go!
- [soldier] Move, move!
[panicked, indistinct shouting]
- Let's go, let's go!
- [glass shattering]
[Rocío yelling]
[Nana shouting angrily
in Spanish]
Let's go!
Do not resist!
No! No! No!
[weapons cocking]
[Alberto shouting in Spanish]
[Nana shouting in Spanish]
[soldier] Get on the ground.
On the ground!
[soldier 2] Get down, now!
Let's go, now!
[soldier shouts in Spanish]
The kid's not there.
Find him!
[Milagro panting]
[soldier] Is he inside?
[in Spanish]
[soldier] Where is he?
[repeats Spanish]
Where is he?
I could use
that arsenal right about now.
[Khaji-Da]
Thought you'd never ask.
Hell, yeah!
[soldiers yelling]
[gasping]
[Jaime] Nice work, Khaji.
You guys okay?
- Jaime?
- Sorry I'm late, Mom.
Magnificent.
- [weapons cocking]
- Wait, what?
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Look, don't shoot.
I don't wanna hurt you guys.
[Victoria over radio] Fire!
God damn it! I said don't shoot.
- [Rocío yelps]
- [gunfire continues]
Oh, my God. I'm bulletproof.
Let's see what you can do.
Target the family.
- [Victoria over radio] Engage.
- [soldier] Take 'em out.
[yells]
[grunts] I got you guys.
Don't worry.
It's gonna be okay.
[straining]
Okay, let's see what you got.
[Khaji-Da] Eliminating threats.
What? No, Khaji, no killing.
Yeah, that's more like it.
[all yelling]
[grunting]
Get out of here.
Run!
[Alberto urging in Spanish]
[Khaji-Da]
Analyzing threat level.
Okay. Let's do this.
[grunting]
[yelling]
[laughs] Hell, yeah!
[all panting, whimpering]
[soldier] Down on the ground!
- [Milagro] ¡Papi!
- Mili!
- [soldier] We got one.
- [fearful gasping]
[in Spanish]
- [soldier] Stay down. Don't move.
- [panting]
Stay where you are.
[cursing in Spanish]
- [Milagro] No!
- [soldier] We got another one.
Dad!
Come to papa.
[all grunting]
Carapax, ready the claw.
[claw mechanism powering up]
[shaky whisper]
Daddy, I'm scared.
[weakly] Everything
is gonna be okay.
- [Khaji-Da] Jaime, your family.
- [soldier] Stay down!
[Jaime grunts]
Okay, come on, Papi.
Mili, get Dad outta here. Go!
- Go!
- Okay. Okay, let's go.
Ready.
[Khaji-Da] They have a weapon.
I suggest we retreat.
No way. They attack my family,
we're gonna finish this.
And...
[grunting in pain]
Dad.
Dad, no. Dad, what's wrong?
Dad! Dad!
[crying] No, no, no! Dad!
No!
No, no, no.
- Dad!
- [Milagro] No!
Now!
[yells]
Now, what's happening?
- [Khaji-Da] Symbiotic systems...
- Khaji, do something!
[sobbing] Dad, no!
Dad! ¡Apá!
- ¡Apá!
- Jaime!
[panting, whimpering]
No. No, no, no.
No.
No, Jaime.
- Jaime, watch out!
- [Jaime gasping for breath]
[yelling] You! You!
What do you want with us?
[screaming]
- [Milagro] Dad, no!
- [Jaime] What are you doing?
Get this thing off of me,
you psycho!
Mom!
- ¡Mami!
- [Rocío] Mili!
Alberto!
Alberto.
Let me go!
- Khaji, do something! [groans]
- I got him. Let's go.
¡Apá! [yelling]
[Rocío pleading in Spanish]
[calling for help in Spanish]
[Rocío yelling in Spanish]
[family crying]
[panting]
- [Rocío] Rudy. Rudy, Rudy.
- [speaking Spanish] Wake up.
[Jaime yelling, indistinct]
[groaning loudly] ¡Apá!
[weakly] I'm gonna come...
I'm gonna come get you.
[Rudy] Call an ambulance.
[sobs, echoing]
[sirens wailing]
[defibrillator charging]
- [medic] Clear!
- [paddles thumping]
[medic] Clear! Clear!
[faint voices, echoing]
[no audible dialogue]
[Milagro whimpering, sniffling]
[Rocío murmuring to Milagro]
[Nana speaking Spanish]
[in Spanish]
Mm?
[Milagro crying]
[Nana addressing Milagro
in Spanish]
[Milagro sniffles]
[in Spanish]
[continues in Spanish]
[Rudy agreeing in Spanish]
[crying] Nana is right, Mili.
We have to go and save Jaime.
How?
Okay, we don't even know
where they took him.
[Jenny] I might know where he is.
Please.
Come with me.
I can help.
[Jenny] Watch your step.
- [beeping]
- [doors rumbling]
All right.
Let's do this.
[paint can rattling]
[Rocío] Let's go.
[Milagro] Okay, okay.
I'm done, I'm done.
Okay, guys.
Let's hope this Kord tech works.
[motor thrumming]
[switches clicking]
[buzzer buzzes]
Hang on.
Okay...
[mechanism powers down,
powers back up]
- Dude!
- [systems humming]
[powers off]
[powers on]
- There.
- [female voice] Welcome back
to the Bug Ship, Teddy.
Oh, that's sexy.
[Rocío] Look at you.
- [Milagro] This is sick.
- [Rudy] Thrusters!
- Let's go get our boy.
- [Jenny] Let's do this.
[Rudy] Jenny.
- [Milagro] Whoa!
- [Nana laughs]
Okay.
Good, good, good. Good.
[speaking Spanish]
So, what's the plan
when we get there?
We'll burn that bridge
when we get to it.
[Milagro] That's not
how you say... Whoa!
[all yelling]
[cackling]
[Rudy] Amá, I'm flying!
Whoo!
[Victoria] After 15 years,
everything we've done,
every sacrifice we've made,
has led to this moment.
Finally, the power of the Scarab
will be ours.
[Sanchez] Almost there.
[Victoria] We are going
to change the world, Carapax.
Are you ready?
I'm ready.
[monitor beeping]
[Milagro groans]
[in Spanish]
Is this thing bulletproof?
[mutters in Spanish]
[in Spanish]
Well, do you guys
wanna see Dad's toys?
Wait, is that
Kabloom bubble gum?
[Jenny] Oh, no, no.
That's not what you think it is.
It's just a special prototype
my dad was designing for me
when I was little.
Do these things work?
Mm... some of them.
Sometimes.
- [glove beeps]
- Whoa.
[nervous chuckle]
Oh, that's the Bug Shield.
Try pressing another button.
[Milagro chuckles softly]
Yeah, you know what?
I think I'm keeping this one.
Okay, so, how are we
supposed to learn
how to use these things?
[heavy weapon clicks,
powering up]
[Milagro] Nana?
Hey. How do you know
how to hold that so perfectly?
[in Spanish]
- [cackling]
- [hairpin clatters]
[Jenny] This is where
they took Jaime.
Pago is a Caribbean island
off the coast of Cuba
that Kord bought from Batista
in the 50s.
The place is a fortress.
Okay, how the hell
are we gonna get in there?
[in Spanish]
What the hell?
Mili, one day, we gonna
have to talk about
Nana's revolutionary past.
Her what?
[in Spanish]
[laughing]
[Jenny] Yeah,
the generators are here.
- [Nana] Mm.
- We could blow them up
- and knock power out.
- [laughing]
[praising in Spanish]
[in Spanish]
Hmm?
- [Milagro] Damn, Nana.
- [Nana laughs intensely]
[sighs]
[breath echoing, faint]
[shuddering gasp]
Hey, who are you?
[gasps]
[Jaime] What're you doing?
Get me out of this thing,
please?
[Victoria] Is there a problem,
Sanchez?
[whispers] I'm sorry.
You're sorry? You're sorry?
What does that even mean?
Tell her to get me out of this!
Shh, shh, shh...
It's okay. It's okay.
Yeah. Listen, kid.
The Scarab chose you,
that's true.
But it doesn't belong to you.
It belongs to me.
But now that you've
activated it,
we can transfer its code
directly into the OMAC.
What are you even talking about?
No, no, Miss Kord.
It could kill him.
Oh, bummer.
Well, but sacrifices have to
be made for the greater good.
And this is yours, Jaime Reyes.
Do it, Sanchez.
With all due respect,
my name again is not Sanchez.
[Jaime] Hey, hey!
Get me outta this thing!
- [fly buzzing]
- Damn it.
[Bug Ship engines whining]
Bug.
- [Jenny] Rudy.
- [Rudy] Yeah, I see it.
[Jenny] You're going too fast!
[Rudy] Here goes nothing.
- Hold on, hold on!
- [all yelling]
- [Rudy] All right. All right.
- [all shrieking]
[gasps] Incoming!
Brace for impact!
[soldiers shouting]
[all screaming]
[groans loudly]
[panting]
[soldier] Let's go, let's go!
On the wall! Engage. Engage.
[Rocío] Rudy, do something.
Rudy, we need to move.
We need to move.
["Kickstart My Heart"
by Motley Crue playing]
[Rudy] Here we go!
- [all yelling]
- Whoa.
Okay, okay.
[shouting]
- Get out of the way. Sorry!
- [Nana shouting in Spanish]
[soldiers screaming]
- It's like I can't miss.
- Right there, right there.
[soldier groans]
[in Spanish]
- Twenty points!
- [Rudy] Whoo-hoo!
[soldiers grunting, screaming]
Activating cloaking system.
[Bug Ship voice]
Activating bug fart.
[Bug Ship farting explosively]
[yelps]
[soldiers coughing, gagging]
[Rudy] Take that!
Whoo!
- [soldiers yelling]
- [Jenny screams]
[Bug Ship squeaks]
[Jenny exhales]
- Yeah, this way.
- Okay.
Hey! Come on.
I know you can hear me.
[breathing heavily]
Just let me out!
[grunts explosively]
[Jaime struggling]
[panting]
[Victoria] I'll keep it safe.
Start the transfer.
And when it's complete,
kill the kid.
Get me out of here!
But, Miss Kord,
we could learn so much
from his connection
to the Scarab...
We can learn a lot more
if we take it off his corpse.
[Jaime] Let me out! No! No!
[screaming]
[screaming continues]
[indistinct radio chatter]
Milagro, here, hide!
[metallic rattling]
Holy shit.
Okay, I think we're good.
What the...?
Victoria, you crazy bitch.
[Milagro] What the hell is this?
[Jenny] Fully operational
OMAC systems.
Enough to build an entire army.
[Sanchez] Miss Kord, this...
this isn't looking good.
[Victoria] What's going on?
[Sanchez] Oh, no.
The Scarab download
is generating too much power.
Our systems are spiking.
[Victoria] What does it mean?
[Sanchez]
The transfer is killing him.
[Victoria] He can't die before
the transfer is completed.
His pulse is dropping.
Well, just fix it!
[gasping deeply]
[Alberto echoing] Hey, flaco.
Dad.
What's going on?
What are you doing here?
You know.
No. Apá.
[comforting in Spanish]
[in Spanish]
[speaks Spanish]
[Jenny] Milagro, here.
Help me with these.
[cracking, rumbling]
[gasps]
Jaime.
This is not your time.
You have to go back.
[in Spanish]
Please.
I understand everything now.
My destiny was
to be here with you.
In this moment.
To help you cross into it.
[in Spanish]
This is your purpose.
It's time for you
to accept your destiny, Jaime.
[breathing rapidly]
How am I gonna
do this without you?
[in Spanish]
How am I gonna know what to do?
[panting]
[in Spanish]
I love you too, Papi.
[speaks Spanish]
Something's happening.
What?
His brainwaves, they're syncing
with the Scarab's frequency.
Right there. They're connecting.
I need you, Khaji!
They're becoming one.
[panting]
[monitor beeping]
[Victoria] We've got the code?
[Sanchez]
The transfer's complete.
- The code is ours.
- [grunts]
It's working!
[Jaime panting]
[grunts]
[screaming]
[panting] Oh, no.
[soldier] Go, go, go!
[screaming]
[panting heavily]
[sharp groan]
[yelps]
Okay. Here we go.
[beeping]
[electronic ticking]
- [gasps]
- [beep]
- [Jenny] Okay, let's go.
- [Milagro] Yeah.
[Carapax screaming faintly]
- [grunts]
- [suit warbles, sputters]
No. No, no, no.
[Carapax yelling]
Sanchez, stop him!
[panting] Oh, shit.
[Carapax screaming]
[grunting]
What?
Get your family
and get off this island, okay?
- Wait, wait, wait. My family?
- Quickly!
- What do you mean my family?
- [door slams]
Go!
Sanchez, you moron.
What are you doing?
My name is not Sanchez, pendeja!
It's Jose Francisco Morales
Rivera de la Cruz!
- [Victoria] What are you doing?
- [grunting]
- [Jaime yells]
- [panting]
[Victoria] Stop him, Carapax.
Go. I'll be fine.
[gasps]
Okay, Khaji, come on.
- [loud thudding]
- [exclaiming]
Okay.
All right, Khaji, activate!
[Khaji-Da] Rebooting.
Rebooting? Are you kidding me?
[OMAC powering up]
Oh, God. Oh, no. Oh, no.
[gasping]
[yelling]
- Go, go, go.
- Okay, okay, okay.
[rumbling, cracking]
Milagro, wait.
- Oh, no, no, no.
- What's wrong? What's wrong?
- [Jenny] No, no, watch out!
- [Milagro screams]
Jenny.
Jenny?
Jenny!
[growling]
Finally, I can feel it.
[growling softly]
[exhales] Oh...
Now this look really suits you.
- [loud buzzing]
- [klaxon blares]
Okay.
[panting] Okay, Khaji.
All right, Khaji-Da.
You got this. You can do this.
Come on! Let's go! Let's go!
- [suit hums, then falters]
- [Khaji-Da] Still rebooting.
Come on!
[gasping]
[grunting with effort]
[soldier] Freeze!
- Stay right there!
- [weapons cocking]
Come on.
- [weapons powering up]
- Don't move.
[panting]
[soldier] Take him down.
- [powerful weapon firing]
- [soldiers screaming]
- [firing ceases]
- [Jaime gasps]
Nana?
[in Spanish]
[Jaime] Okay.
Where did you learn
to shoot like that?
[in Spanish]
[urging in Spanish]
[soldiers chattering]
[weapon clicks]
[soldier] Keep your eyes peeled.
[prolonged battle yell]
[in Spanish]
- [cackling]
- [soldiers screaming]
- [weapon spinning down]
[contented sigh, laugh]
[in Spanish]
[calling in Spanish]
[rocks clattering]
[muffled booming]
[coughing]
[coughing] Milagro!
[grunting]
[Victoria tutting]
Jennifer, Jennifer, Jennifer.
What a mess you have made.
[soldier] Let's go.
On your feet. Get up!
[Nana and Rocío
speaking Spanish]
Amá.
[Rocío speaking Spanish,
relieved]
[in Spanish]
- Yeah.
- [muffled booming]
- [muttering in Spanish]
- Sheez.
- Milagro.
- [Jaime] Where is she?
Milagro and Jenny.
They're in there.
[Jaime] Oh, you gotta
be kidding me.
Okay, I need to head
back in there, okay?
[Rudy] Yeah. What about the suit?
It's not working right now.
I can't deal with it.
- Jaime.
- Yes?
- [speaking Spanish]
- Okay.
Uh... Rudy, what's that
chongo thing called again?
Khaji-Da.
Right.
I know you can hear me,
Khaji-Da.
I want you both
to get it together.
Find your strength, mijito.
Use the pain we're feeling
and turn it into power.
I want you
to go back in there...
[in Spanish]
- [soldier grunts]
- [Milagro gasps]
- I found one of them.
- [beeping]
- [grunts]
- [yells]
[all grunting loudly]
Sick.
- Drop your weapon.
- Oh, goddamn it.
[gasps in pain]
[Jaime] Hey! ¡Pendejos!
["I Ain't Goin' Out Like That"
by Cypress Hill playing]
[suit powering up]
[Khaji-Da] Rebooting complete.
Get the hell away
from my sister.
- I'm out.
You ready Khaji?
[Khaji-Da, in Spanish]
Come on, let's get it.
Who's first?
[all grunting]
[gunfire]
[yells]
[Jaime] Oh, you want some?
[screams]
[grunts]
[pained yell]
Wait, wait, wait! Watch out!
Engage the target.
[soldiers yell]
Ha-ha! Let's go!
[panting]
Oh, man, there's more.
[huffing]
[soldiers grunting]
[Jaime yells]
Grab him!
What the hell?
Get 'em off of me!
[Khaji-Da] With pleasure.
[all yelling]
- Thanks, Khaji.
- [Khaji-Da] De nada.
Halt!
[Khaji-Da] One more left.
[yelping]
[Jaime] Get over here!
[soldier yells]
[pleased chuckle]
[panting]
[Jaime] Come on.
[chuckles] Come on.
Nice slap.
[in Spanish]
Okay, I deserve that one.
[Milagro] I thought
I'd never see you again.
I told you I wasn't
going anywhere.
- Well, you did.
- Yeah, that wasn't my...
[exclaiming in Spanish]
Rudy! Rudy!
Mili, oh, my God. Oh, my God.
You're safe.
I thought I lost you.
[Milagro] No, no. Look.
- [Milagro laughing]
- Hey, hey, hey.
Wait, wait, wait. Where's Jenny?
We got separated. I don't know.
Okay, we have to find her.
Okay, we're gonna find her
before the others do because I...
- [power surge humming]
- Watch out!
[Jaime yells]
What the hell was that?
[roaring]
[Khaji-Da]
OMAC incoming, Jaime.
Ah, crap. [grunts loudly]
[Jaime yelling]
[both grunting]
Get off!
[Jaime] Okay,
let's do this, Khaji!
Give me rockets or something.
[Khaji-Da]
Deploying blasters.
[Carapax groans]
Okay, now give me blades.
Ha-ha! Okay, now give me...
[pained grunt, yelling]
[Khaji-Da] Careful,
he's stronger than before.
- Okay, I get it.
- [roaring]
[Milagro] Okay,
which way do we go?
Go to the Bug Ship.
It's that way.
- But where are you going?
- I'm gonna get Cabezón. Go!
[both grunting loudly]
[Khaji-Da]
Critical wing damage.
[Jaime] Scratch my back?
Well, I'll scratch yours.
[Jaime yelling]
[Carapax grunting]
All right, big boy.
You do not deserve this power!
[blade clanging]
[Jaime] I thought you'd
hit harder than that.
[grunts with effort]
[Jaime] Okay, we need
something else, Khaji.
[Khaji-Da]
Accessing energy reactor.
[suit charging up]
[Jaime] There we go.
[grunting]
All right, you wanna dance, huh?
Now, give me a sword.
So I can make whatever
weapons I want?
[Khaji-Da] Whatever
you can imagine, I can create.
Let's party.
[yells, grunts]
[Khaji-Da] Ooh, nice choice.
- [Jaime] Let's go!
- [Carapax growling]
[yells]
[Jaime] Home run!
[grunting]
[Jaime] Ha-ha, yeah!
[laughs] Come on.
That's all you got?
[Khaji-Da] Let's not
get ahead of ourselves, Jaime.
[Jaime] Khaji, don't worry.
We got this.
[both grunting]
[triumphant yell]
[both straining]
[Jaime] Okay, this is a little
harder than I thought.
[grunting]
[pained grunt]
[Khaji-Da]
Regenerative systems critical.
What the hell?
[Carapax] There can
only be one of us.
[Jaime] Khaji, do something!
[both grunting]
[Jaime] What's wrong?
Can't breathe?
[Carapax growling]
[Jaime grunts, straining]
[Jaime yelling]
[Khaji-Da] Jaime,
I cannot protect you anymore.
[Khaji-Da] I'm sorry.
[Jaime groaning]
Khaji, Khaji, stay with me.
[screams]
[Carapax] You are still
a scared little boy.
[panting]
[screams]
[Carapax] I told you,
the love you feel
for your family
makes you weak.
[defiant scream]
[Carapax grunts in surprise]
Hey!
[in Spanish]
[Rudy] Come on! Come and get me.
[shouts in Spanish] Come on!
[panting]
Rudy.
Oh, shit.
[Jaime] No!
Rudy!
[bellowing]
Khaji-Da!
[growls]
Your OMAC has failed.
Jennifer, you don't know
what the OMAC is.
Carapax is just a prototype.
This is the only thing
that's important.
The Scarab code.
With this,
I can make a thousand Carapaxes.
This is the culmination
of my life's work.
This is the Kord legacy.
This is our legacy.
Not mine.
I'll make sure of it.
You're... you're gonna side
with that Edge Key trash
over your own family?
That Edge Key trash...
knows more about
family than you ever will.
I know. No, I know about family.
I know about my family
that overlooked me,
just the way that you are now,
because you are
just like your pathetic father.
Who didn't have the guts
to do what was necessary
for the greater good.
I wish that Ted were here now
to see this.
[in Portuguese]
- [grunts]
- [Victoria] Oh!
[yells]
[alarm beeping]
[struggling grunts]
[grunting, yelling]
[growls]
[screaming]
[Jaime] No! We're not done!
[violent grunts]
[Khaji-Da]
Jaime, threat disarmed.
You're losing control.
[Jaime] You think
that you could beat me? Huh?
You should have finished me
when you had the chance!
[gasps]
[Khaji-Da] OMAC neutralized.
Recommend to disengage.
[yelling]
[panting, grunts]
What are you doing?
[Khaji-Da]
We are not killers, Jaime.
- Let him go.
- [sobs]
What about Dad?
What about Rudy?
[Khaji-Da] During the transfer,
I unlocked his memories.
Let me show you.
[screaming]
[doctor] What if he doesn't
survive the procedure?
[Victoria] Then we'll just
get another one.
[doctor 2] It could kill him.
Sacrifices must be made
for the greater good.
[Ronald Reagan] This country is
confronting a brutal challenge,
from guerrillas
armed and supported
by others outside Guatemala.
[woman] The United States is
committed to restoring democracy
and to address the root causes
of the violent insurgency.
[Reagan] We know
about the problems
confronting Guatemala.
Perfect. Round them up.
[jet flying overhead]
[echoing] ¡Mamá!
[echoing] Ignacio!
[grunts]
[echoing scream]
[breathing shakily]
[Khaji-Da]
Do you understand now?
[yells]
Hey! Cabezón!
[groaning]
You're wrong.
That love that
I have for my family...
That's what makes me strong.
All right, give it to me.
Come on.
- This?
- Yes, that.
[screams] No!
Now what have you done?
No! No, no!
[Jaime panting] Jenny?
- [Jenny murmuring, relieved]
- It's okay.
Carapax, kill them.
Kill them both!
[in Spanish]
Okay.
[Victoria] What are you doing?
They're getting...
[Jaime] Okay.
[Jenny whimpers]
[Victoria] No.
Wait, Jenny, wait.
Go back to the Bug Ship.
I'll be right behind you.
- What?
- I promise.
We can be partners. Huh?
I'll f... I'll fix it.
I'll fix you.
We can find another Sanchez.
Huh?
Do you remember everything
that I've done for you?
[in Q'eqchi]
[Carapax's suit powering up]
[whispering] No.
Khaji, what's he doing?
[Khaji-Da] He's maxing out
the energy reactor in his suit.
I advise we back away.
[humming power intensifies]
[mother, echoing] Ignacio.
[laughs gently]
[in Q'eqchi]
[Victoria] What? What?
What, no! What are you doing?
Stop! No! No!
[in Q'eqchi]
Sacrifices must be made
for the greater good.
No! Please! No!
Ignacio, no!
[Khaji-Da] I suggest we run.
Okay. Oh, shit.
[yelling]
[Jenny grunts]
Milagro, pull!
[Rudy] Rocío!
¡Písale, cabrona!
[yelling]
[exhausted grunt]
[all panting]
- [Jaime chuckles weakly]
- [whispers] You okay?
Mili.
[Rudy] Cabezón.
Rudy?
- Rudy!
- [chuckles]
- How?
- Yeah. You know...
[in Spanish]
Amá.
- [Rocío speaks Spanish]
- Nana.
[in Spanish]
[all crying]
[crying softly]
It is a delicate moment
for Kord Industries.
And of course, we mourn
the loss of Victoria Kord.
But I'm looking forward.
As I was saying,
we will no longer make weapons.
What I want to do is honor
my father's legacy.
It's not about destruction,
it's about building
a better future.
It's not about taking
from the community,
but giving back
to the community.
What are we gonna do now?
Ánimo, Rudy, okay?
We're gonna get through this,
we always do.
[woman calling out in Spanish]
[man] Hey! The Reyes are here.
Guys.
[animated chatter in Spanish]
[in Spanish]
[indistinct chatter]
["Sabor A Mi"
by Trio Los Panchos playing]
[men chattering, laughing]
[indistinct chatter]
[Milagro] Nana.
[Nana grunting,
speaking Spanish]
Okay.
- [both laughing]
- [speaks Spanish]
[addresses family in Spanish]
[in Spanish]
Eh? [chuckles]
Where, Amá?
We don't have a house.
Rudy, we have half the Edge Keys
in our yard right now.
I'm sure they'll be happy
to help us out.
Of course they're going to help.
Yeah, until when?
Until Kord pushes us out?
[Jenny]
I wouldn't worry about that.
[pleased chattering]
[Nana] Jenny, Jenny.
Hi.
[in Spanish]
I think it's time
to return the Edge Keys
to the people
that made it great.
Sounds like the Reyes family's
rubbing off a little bit
on Jenny Kord, no?
[Jenny] Kord has a lot to learn
from the Edge Keys.
Starting with you, Rudy.
Wait a minute,
did you tell her to say that?
Rudy, I didn't say shit.
That sounds like something that
you would say to her to tell me.
And don't worry, Kord Industries
will fix and give you back
your house.
[Milagro makes happy sound]
[all chattering]
[man] Excuse me.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
- Here, Rudy.
- What's this?
I felt really bad,
so I got you a new tailgate.
[laughter, chattering]
How do you like that, cupcake?
Oh! Wow, it's blue.
A little on the nose, no?
- [Rocío] Rudy.
- Rudy. "Thank you."
- I'll think about it.
- [Jenny] Yeah, take a look.
- Come on, help me like it.
- [Milagro] I'm inheriting that.
All right, I gotta go.
Yeah.
How about I walk you out?
- Yeah, sure.
- Okay.
[exhales]
So, uh...
...when am I gonna
see you again?
Soon. I hope.
Where are you headed?
To my dad's.
I want to look at
my mom's paintings again.
I forgot how beautiful they are.
Cool, cool.
What if I gave you a ride?
[chuckles]
How?
[Khaji-Da]
I feel a surge of blood
rushing towards your mid-region.
Stop!
No, no, no. Not you.
Oh.
What's it saying?
Nothing.
["Nada Personal"
by Soda Stereo playing]
[suit humming]
[family hooting and cheering]
[all singing
"Jaime La Del Barrio" song]
[laughing]
Okay.
Hold on.
[nervous chuckle]
Okay.
[Jenny yelling]
[song continues]
[heavy thud]
[devices powering up]
["I'm All Out Of Love"
by Air Supply playing]
- [static crackles]
- [music skips and repeats]
[man over radio] Hello, hello?
Oh my God, it's working.
Okay. Um...
Whoever turned on my computer,
get a message
to my daughter, Jenny.
Jenny Kord.
Please,
tell her that I love her,
and that I'm sorry,
and her dad is alive.
Ted Kord is alive.
[quirky theme song playing]
[announcer speaking in Spanish]
[grunts]
Hmm...
[announcer continues in Spanish]
[groans]
[announcer continues]
[grunts]
[pleased laugh]
[Rudy] Oh, that's sexy.