The storm is too strong.
I can't get any closer.
The storm's too strong.
Too risky!
Go back. I repeat, go back!
It's too dangerous, Cem.
Cem, it's too dangerous.
BLUE CAVE
What shall we do?
You guys grab a table. I'll get the beers.
- Malt though, right?
- Alright.
- Hi, Serhat.
- Let's go over there.
Three beers, please.
Here you go, Sir.
- Ok.
- That's great. Thanks a lot, man.
- Did you book the same table?
- That one there.
Ah, that's perfect. Great.
Come on, son, for God's sake.
We're practically
dragging you to places like this. Huh?
Here we are. Come on, cheers.
Guys, cheers.
Hey, slow down.
Alright then, let's order again.
So, what do you think of the newcomers?
Great.
Pardon?
It's tough. I'm curious
to see which ones will last.
- Hey, what the hell are you staring at?
- Oh, nothing really.
Leave it out man, don't make it...
Don't look. Don't make it obvious!
Come on, man.
They're not going to be interested
in a soldier.
I'm going to have a word with them.
No, wait man.
Don't cause trouble.
Forget it. Seriously, Cem.
Ah, at last! Where have you been?
Come here. Hey!
Oh, brother...
Sorry bro, but the truth is a bit harsh.
Come and sit down.
Ok, forget it, you can stop staring now.
There are plenty of other girls.
- Serhat! Over here, my friend.
- Over here.
Forget about it.
- Ok. Here's the bill.
- Ah, the bill. It's your turn this time.
Come on guys let's go.
Get the bill and we'll leave.
It's ok. I'll pay.
Of course you will, pilot.
Cut it out, you've drunk too much again,
haven't you?
I haven't drunk too much.
Please stay.
I'll catch you up.
Don't go.
Goodbye.
Let's leave.
You go on. I'll catch you up.
- Shush.
- Hang on, man,
I haven't finished my drink yet.
Hello there.
- Hello.
- Good evening to you, too.
Evening.
You stayed.
Ah...
Because you've been staring all evening.
And your eyes even ate my food.
And now, just as my friends are leaving,
you say "don't go".
Isn't that comical? But a bit sad too.
Haha...
Have a good night.
- Are you going?
- Yes, I'm going.
- She's gone.
- Wait a minute.
- Where are you going, man?
Wait a minute.
Wait.
You can't just have a go at me and leave.
I didn't have a go at you.
- I just said good night.
- Good night?
Yes.
Do you always make this your
habit of questioning people?
I don't know... maybe.
- Do you have a boyfriend?
- Boyfriend? At the table?
A man and a woman sit next to each
other so they must be lovers, right?
That's a bit old-fashioned.
Can't they just be work friends?
I don't mean to be disrespectful.
- Don't you?
- No.
So staring at me all night isn't
disrespectful, but saying hello is?
- Ok, you understand me.
- Mmm.
I don't understand.
Well, why don't we assume
that we are lovers?
We come to a place like this
to have dinner. Just us.
Then a woman comes up
and says hello to me.
How would you feel?
That depends on your reply.
Oh, really?
- Mm-hmm.
- Mmm.
Ok. What's your name?
Alara...
Come on!
You go.
Haha! Well, the universe seems
to be working for you tonight.
- Alara.
- Mm-hmm.
Lovely.
And?
Cem.
- Cem.
- Mm-hmm.
Ok, Cem...
What else might you mean by saying hello?
I don't know.
But hello can lead to many other things.
Now it's getting late.
Mm-hmm.
You haven't done anything for two hours.
Pushing it just as I'm leaving...
- Not going to work.
- I don't know. I think it would.
Wait a minute, let's try this...
I'll ask you a question,
and you ask me one, ok?
And if you...
like my answer, then you give me
your number. What do you think?
- And if I don't like it?
- Then maybe I'll give you my number.
- Ha, that's bad.
- No, it's not.
That's bad, you're trouble.
Come on.
Come on...
Ask.
Man, I swear you're making a big mistake.
Give it to me.
Don't go anywhere.
I'll be back in ten minutes.
- I'll wait ten minutes, then I'm off.
- Ok.
- I have things to do.
- You got this.
Ten minutes.
- Let me show you what I wrote.
- Great, thank you.
I took care of five and six, as I said.
Four is left out.
But maybe there's nothing.
Maybe there's nothing to do.
No need, since you've taken care
of the others.
- Uh-huh.
- We agree, then?
- Mm-hmm.
- Take care.
- Thank you.
- See you.
Bye.
What are you doing here?
You didn't answer my phone calls.
- No.
- Why not?
What do you mean why not, Cem?
What you're doing is wrong.
What have I done?
Cem, this is where I work.
Can't I simply come to the museum
as a private citizen on a visit?
Besides, I have a very valuable
historical artefact here.
I've come to drop it off. There.
Whoa! Look, it's a museum,
you can't just lean on things.
Anyway... when are you going
to stop making fun of me?
Maybe when you start taking me seriously.
Excuse me,
is there anyone else working here?
Ok, will you leave? Please?
You're really upsetting me.
- Tell me why didn't you answer my calls?
- I just didn't.
- Why not?
- I just didn't. You only called once.
Then, two weeks later, you called
at some ridiculous hour.
Who calls at two in the morning
without texting first to see if it's ok?
Don't think I don't get it. I do.
I know what you're after,
but I don't have it.
Let me make this clear, I don't have it.
It's not like that.
It's really not like that, Alara...
No way.
Will you stop for a moment?
Wait a minute.
How did you know I was here?
I told you I'd find you.
- Mmm.
- Mm-hmm.
Mmm, in Istanbul I'd be impressed,
but it doesn't work in this tiny town.
You always like this?
- Like what?
- Defensive.
If it means resisting
a patriarchal system, then yes.
That's why I said I wasn't right for you.
That's why I said it wouldn't work
between us.
- Uh-huh.
- Now I have to get back to work.
I think it would work.
Maybe you shouldn't be quite so sure.
I've never been more sure of anything.
Remember the question I asked you?
Remember the answer I gave?
Cem, I did call you.
What?
What do you mean?
You heard me.
Your phone was off.
There was no signal.
I...
I honestly didn't know you called.
Anyway, you called two weeks later.
So?
You do understand, don't you?
Ok, then, let me make it up to you.
Come on.
- Meltem, dear.
- Yes?
Meltem.
Can I introduce you to Cem?
Nice to meet you.
Err...
He's brought in a very important
historical artefact for the museum.
Could you help him?
Make sure to take it to the back room.
- Of course yes, gladly.
- I'm going.
- I'd love to see it.
- No...
My business with Ms Alara isn't finished,
so I'm handing this artefact over to you.
- Sure.
- Please, take it to the back room,
- then we're finished...
- Ok.
- Ok, I'll wait for you in the back room.
- That's great, thanks.
- You are so bad.
- Why are you dragging this out?
We're just going out for dinner,
it's quite simple.
Is this a date or what?
I don't have much time
because Ms Meltem is waiting for me.
- Mm-hmm?
- So, come on.
- What?
- Give me a pen and paper.
I'm sure there's a pen
and paper in your bag.
Well...
- this is all I've got, that's like paper.
- Ok.
- Pen?
- Pen.
I'll find it. Just a second.
Pen.
Then we'll meet here
at eight o'clock tonight, ok?
- Here.
- You tore it.
Well, it's just the corner, no big deal.
Here.
Eight this evening.
It still has the price tag.
It looks genuine.
Looks genuine? Right!
I wanted to see you.
Why?
Isn't it completely obvious?
She's not coming.
I almost didn't recognise you.
You're here.
- You waited.
- Yes.
- Why?
- Why did you make me wait?
So I could be sure.
So you could be sure, eh?
- Ok.
- Why did you wait?
To be sure.
- So, if we're sure...
- We're sure.
What now?
I wonder how many women
you've pulled this trick on.
Do I look like that kind of guy?
I don't know what kind of guy you are.
So, what's your longest relationship?
- Eight years.
- Phew, wow that's a lot. Eight years.
Yes, and it's still going on.
- What do you mean? Won't he let go?
- No, we live in the same house.
What... do you mean?
My dog.
His name's Portos.
Ok.
- Mmm.
- Alright.
And you?
Your dog doesn't actually count,
so you didn't answer the question.
Four years.
And you?
- Seven months?
- Are you're asking me?
Seven months.
Oh... attachment problems?
Well, let's just say professional reasons.
Right, I didn't really ask you,
what is it you're doing in Foça?
I'm not in Foça. I'm in Uzunada.
A soldier.
Yes, I am.
Naval officer.
A soldier, eh?
That's a shame.
Mmm. So you liked me.
Mmm... I liked you much more with a beard.
Ok, got that.
And you?
Have you always lived in Foça?
No, my mum and I came here about six
years ago.
I'm an archaeologist.
There's excavations, and I like to go
to the museum, you know, once in a while.
I think it must be amazing
to bring the past back to life,
and if that's what excites you,
then I think that must be very meaningful.
You know what?
When we look at the stars,
we're looking at the past.
It's true.
You're a romantic soldier.
Yes, I like the sound of that.
Romantic soldier.
Your mum? What does she do?
She wrote literature.
I lost her three years ago.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
And your dad?
No. Let's hear about your parents.
So... did your father die, too?
I don't know. He may have.
Oh Yes, I've got daddy issues.
He left my mum and me when I was little.
Anyway, tell me about your parents.
Err...
I lost my mum when I was a child,
and my father was a troubled man,
who left in a troubled way.
Nice trick though.
What's that?
What you're up to.
Ah, huh... my only trick.
- Mmm.
- I waited a long time.
- Mmm, how long?
- Quite long.
Oh by the way...
I forgot this.
Cem, give it to me.
- Ok.
- Give it.
Calm down, I'll give it to you.
- Calmly.
- Ok, give it to me. Come on.
I just have a few questions.
So, I had a look at your notes.
Why were you looking at my notes?
Give it...
Here's the thing.
There's a place inside the heart.
- So...
- Mm-hmm.
Where is that?
- That's none of your business.
- I'm curious.
- Will you give it back?
- Tell me and I'll give it to you.
Tell me.
Where's the place inside your heart?
The Blue Cave.
- The Blue Cave!
- It's a special place.
- Special?
- Yes.
How special?
- Very special.
- How much?
- Very much.
That's how special this place is to me.
What's so special about it?
I'd only bring here the woman I'd marry.
- What?
- Mm-hmm.
I mean, I don't know whether
we'll get married or not.
Stop saying that.
We're not going to get married.
You're kind of enjoying it though.
Well, a little.
How's it going?
- Bad.
- Mmm.
Isn't it beautiful?
You wish it would stay like this.
But the sun fades too.
Do we know each other?
I don't always come across someone
who appreciates the view that much.
I wanted to say hello.
Do you live around here?
I've been around here for a long time.
So many people must pass through here.
Mm-hmm... yes, quite a few of them.
This place makes people feel good.
It heals them.
Do you think so?
Don't you believe me?
I gave that up a long time ago.
You're not living.
I'm not here for a revelation
or in some way to discover myself.
You're here though.
I made a promise.
To someone close?
We didn't have enough time.
And just like that, it disappears.
Light and darkness in eternal balance.
It's really that simple.
What is simple?
You can't control everything.
I know people like you.
You try to save everyone.
You try to protect everyone.
Actually, what happens just happens.
And what happens is good.
It's not your fault.
That's why this place is important.
Close your eyes.
- Excuse me?
- Close your eyes.
I lay on my right side.
I turn to my left.
May the angels be my witness.
To my religion, to my faith.
May they take me to Allah's place.
May Allah give peaceful sleep
to this subject of his.
Have a good journey.
The prayer.
My mum used to say it at night.
Mine too.
Actually, I loved this place too,
but I didn't stay there long.
But wait for it.
I'll show you one more place.
- Ah... look, here.
- Mm-hmm.
Cem, I wish I could have been there
when they first discovered the artefacts.
Imagine, 12,000 years ago.
12,000 years. It's mind-blowing.
Think about it. Imagine.
Boncuklu Tarla, right? Wow.
Soldier?
Maybe we should get you
a history award or something?
Well, considering all the missions
I've been on in that region...
I stayed there for almost two years.
Anyway, that's enough history.
Mmm...
I love the way you smell.
- Smell?
- Mm-hmm.
How do I smell?
- Like a cave.
- A cave?
- Mm-hmm.
- Ok.
What's it like?
Fresh.
Mysterious.
- Caves smell of mould.
- Cem...
Don't do that!
I get it, you're trying
to bring the conversation
round to that green cave somehow...
Not green, it's blue!
Why don't we go there? Mmm?
- Shall we go?
- Yes, let's.
Ok.
When shall we go?
- At the right time.
- You're an asshole.
Asshole.
I don't know about cave smells,
but I really like your taste.
Mmm...
- It reminds me of something.
- Mm-hmm.
I tell you what, it's incredible.
You go inside, open the tomb,
and you get goosebumps.
- It's extraordinary.
- You guys are really unbelievable.
Why didn't you let me know?
You know I'd have volunteered?
But he's so unpredictable. Huh?
The other day he goes:
"Let's go to Kazakhstan."
You know, he's always been like this.
What's wrong with that?
I think that's so good.
Well, let's get
to the important question now.
- Cem, dear.
- Mm-hmm.
You're actually the second candidate
Alara has brought here.
- Candidate?
- Second?
We're curious, what are you?
Who are you? Tell us.
So my predecessor didn't make it past
this meal, right?
- Mmm.
- I guess not.
- Sweetie, don't pressure the guy.
- What's wrong?
- He's a soldier, he can handle it...
- Demet... that's enough.
Your beer's finished,
- shall I pour you another one?
- Thanks.
Let's clear the plates away. Ok?
I'll help you with them.
- I'll take that empty one too.
- Ok.
- Thank you.
- I'll come and help you.
Got any assignments, at the moment?
Yes I do, actually.
A small mission in two days' time.
So is every mission,
you go on, a secret one?
Blue Homeland issue?
- What issue?
- Blue Homeland.
No, it's not an issue.
National Defence
starts in the Blue Homeland.
They're not all classified.
We don't talk about them on principle.
- Sure.
- I don't know. The topic's come up again.
Yes, she doesn't really like my job.
Rest assured, we know that.
- That's not true, Cem.
- Yes.
I'm just trying to get used to it.
Ok.
Alright, Cem.
- Mmm.
- Have you ever been married?
No.
Why not?
Are you afraid of marriage or something?
No... I...
I guess that I've never found
someone I wanted to marry
and have kids with.
Mmm, yes.
I mean, I guess it's difficult
because of your job.
Are we back to Cem's work?
Well, I have no idea what you do,
so I'll ask directly,
do you do covert operations?
- Bam, bam, bam...
- Emre, dear.
But... could you die?
I could. It's possible.
Doesn't that possibility scare you, Cem?
No.
It could happen to any of us.
Well...
Ok...
Let's say it happened to you.
- Ok.
- And those left behind?
Aren't you causing them the greatest pain?
Well, I'm not dying.
I'm doing my job.
Yes?
- Alara, I'm disturbing you...
- What do you want, Cem?
You.
I want you Alara.
I've been coming here for a long time.
Since I was a child.
I used to sit right here, daydreaming.
Maybe one day, I'll have a home here.
It's wonderful.
Do you like it?
I love it.
I hope you do.
Do you see that house?
- Mm-hmm?
- The house on the hill?
Mm-hmm, I see it, Cem.
The one in the clouds.
On the ocean.
It's ours now.
Ours? What do you mean?
Err...
I'm not really sure
how I'm supposed to do this.
Alara...
Now.
Alara.
Will you marry me?
Cem...
- Cem.
- Alara.
Even if we get married,
I don't want to be without you.
You won't be.
When I finish my tenth year,
then I'll quit.
And we'll be together.
It really won't work.
I told you when we first met
that it just wouldn't work between us...
It will. Come here.
- We can't.
- Yes, we can.
We can.
We...
I love you.
Hey, who are you? Huh?
We had a dog that looked a bit like you.
A long time ago.
Sometimes I don't understand time.
How did I get here?
When did I arrive?
I've no idea how long I've been walking.
Since Alara died,
I've lost touch with time.
I'm in a lonely dream.
Yes, you see, dog?
And now I'm going to the Blue Cave,
hoping to get closer to my dead wife.
Like a bloody idiot.
I want to be with you among the clouds.
I think you forget that I'm a sailor.
It's ok, we can see the sea from the sky.
You're so beautiful.
I love you so much.
I will never lose you.
- Let's go.
- We'll go.
Let's go to the Blue Cave.
Remember the first time we dated
at the amusement park?
You said you'd bring the woman
you were going to marry there.
Yes.
That's how I feel about this place.
- The Green Cave, yes.
- It's not green, it's blue.
I went there once when I was a child.
With my cousin.
They were going out
on a boat with their friends.
They took me along.
Then we went there.
When we entered the cave,
I felt something different.
There was a different life energy,
it seemed.
You get lost in it.
As if you're a part of everything.
You never went there again?
Mm-hmm, I didn't want to.
Cem...
ever since I met you,
you've been reminding me of that place.
It's like I'm in that cave again.
You're scaring me today.
You excite me so much.
With every breath I take,
I feel every cell trembling.
I feel like my whole body
is surrendering to you.
Hi there, can I be of help with anything?
Just checking my route, thanks.
Team up with us for a bit?
No, thanks.
Ah, what a cute little thing.
Ah, what's its name?
Dog.
Is your owner a very boring person, dog?
Huh?
He's not mine.
Ok then. Fine.
I'm not saying anything else.
Let's go!
Ok, coming.
- You coming too?
- No.
This is a hard route.
I mean, if you take a wrong turn,
It's pretty hard to turn back.
Thanks.
Where are you going?
The Blue Cave.
Oh...
the Blue Cave.
You know you're on the wrong path, right?
But you're lucky.
We're going that way.
Come with us and you can split whenever.
Ah...
- I'm Zeynep, what's your name?
- Cem.
Cem. You're either a Capricorn...
- or a Leo?
- Capricorn.
No. We wouldn't ever make it work.
I've heard that before.
Hey Zeynep, are you an Aries?
Yes, how did you know?
Well, Zeyneps are usually Aries.
Come here!
Come on!
- What do you say?
- To what?
- It's very high...
- It is.
Will you jump in with me?
Why?
The thrill.
Mmm. It wouldn't be so bad.
A little adrenaline rush.
I don't think it'll rise that much.
You're bad.
Sometimes you don't want to live.
I know exactly what you mean.
I don't feel like I'm living.
Did you touch her?
No.
You're a liar.
Alara.
- Alara, stop.
- Stop?
- Stop, Alara.
- Stop. Listen.
- Cut it out.
- Listen!
"Alara, I'm sorry it was my mistake.
Cem is not to blame at all.
It only happened once.
I think he must have told you.
I'm so ashamed.
Please forgive me."
Did she write that?
Yes, she wrote it.
That's why I want your version.
Did you touch her?
No.
Are you bored with me?
What are you talking about?
So why did you then?
Alara...
It isn't what you think.
You're disgusting.
- Alara...
- You're disgusting...
Alara...
- No, Alara. Don't call me Alara.
- Alara, please.
- Don't come near me.
- Please, listen to me.
- Get away from me.
I didn't cheat on you.
You don't have to sleep with someone
to be a cheat.
If I were to text with some guy,
some man every day...
Imagine if some man called me every day,
would you still trust me? Huh?
Answer me, say something for God's sake.
This girl is texting,
and she's texting me too!
Are you done?
What kind of person are you?
Because you don't know what happened.
You don't know.
Stop this. Will you please stop this?
She's your fellow soldier's girlfriend.
Please be aware that you actually
don't know shit!
I was standing
in front of my fellow soldier's tomb.
Stop it, will you?
I really just don't know what kind of man
you are anymore.
She just needed me.
You can't save everyone, Cem.
Are you always this cautious?
Can we not talk?
Ok.
Let's not talk.
You'll get cold here.
- Come on, get a little closer to the fire.
- I'm fine.
I know you're fine like this.
But...
Isn't that really the whole point?
I mean...
to experience what we don't know.
Some of us are like this.
- I'm like this.
- Is that so?
Oh, yes.
I lost someone very close to me.
But this...
helped me find out who I was.
I'm not here to discover myself.
I didn't come here to seek enlightenment
through the hidden meanings of life.
Ok.
It's alright.
Calm down.
Hello?
Didn't you have to leave in the morning?
There's a missing person.
They asked for support.
- Then what?
- We'll deploy for the mission.
See you in a few months then.
Alara...
I can't have a child with you.
Go to bed.
- Did you hear what I said?
- Go to bed, Alara.
Come on.
You're absent, Cem. You're not here.
What changed when we got married? Mmm?
What changed?
- Because of my job...
- Your job?
Always your job.
That is our biggest problem anyway.
What happened?
You were going to quit
when your tenth year was up. Mmm?
And you're still talking about going
on missions like...
I hope you're not misunderstanding me.
Because...
I'm so proud of you.
But I want to start having a family, Cem.
I want to have children.
And I don't want those kids to worry about
whether their father
will come home or not.
I'll quit.
Last mission.
After that, I'll put in my application
for instructor.
I don't believe you.
I was going to tell you
after I filed the petition...
Here.
Is this for real?
Yes, it's for real.
I love you so much.
- I'm sorry.
- Don't be.
Sorry.
- I'm so sorry.
- Don't be.
I know how much you love your job.
I love you more than anything. Ok?
I can't lose you.
I won't lose you.
We're going to start
a beautiful family here.
And then we'll go to the Blue Cave.
You're lying. It's been five years.
Ah...
I don't look very good from there, do I?
- How long have you been like this?
- I don't know.
I don't know.
Do you have any water?
Thanks.
What's your name?
Harun.
I don't do well with Haruns.
Now...
I'm going to poke your body
with a stick, is that ok?
Do whatever the hell you want,
just get me out of this fucking place.
- Come on.
- Ok.
Ok.
Ah...
- Two.
- Two what?
Broken.
I don't feel anything.
Harun...
- Push again.
- I am pushing.
Push harder.
Harder.
Harder!
- I just can't.
- Harder!
Come on, harder.
Am I going to die?
I don't know that, but look,
just hang in there a little longer.
I'll go get help and be right back. Ok?
Anybody here?
Help!
- Ah... want some?
- No.
Whisky and I don't get on.
Why don't you like whisky?
Lion's blood.
Must be something to do with my childhood.
Ah... I see.
You know what?
People...
often think about their regrets
in their final moments on earth.
I had a wife.
And a son.
I couldn't be a good husband...
or a good father.
Why not?
I was taking all my anger out on them.
That's what fathers usually do.
Yours too?
All fathers.
Mine used to beat me a lot. Huh...
He beat me every single day,
he beat me like drinking water.
But then...
it made me stronger, more powerful,
I thought.
Is that why you beat your son?
To make him a man.
- As you beat iron with fire.
- ..."beat iron with fire."
That's the idea.
Do you have a child?
- No.
- That's good. Fuck it, don't have one.
Do you regret it?
Yes.
I mean if I hadn't brought him
into the world,
he wouldn't be the cause of my sins now.
What is it you do?
I was in the Navy.
- Combat diver.
- Ah.
You surprise me.
Why?
I don't know, you don't come
across as a commando.
You can't even get me out
of this fucking place.
You can't save me, can you?
I don't know.
- I don't want to die.
- I know.
So answer me, honestly.
What the hell are you doing here?
My wife.
I came to see my wife.
Where's your wife?
She died.
If you think about your regrets
before you die,
then you've lived a peaceful life.
Yes.
Regret shows itself when you lose.
Never looking into her eyes again.
Never hearing her voice again.
I watch everything we've been through,
like a movie in my mind.
I try not to forget anything.
Every time I watch that movie,
it's part of my grief.
Simple things.
Why did we fight?
Why didn't I just hug her
instead of dragging it out?
I should've just kissed
her a million times.
Regrets.
Yes.
Harun?
The thing is... err...
I consulted my fellow doctors
- to re-evaluate the results.
- Mmm.
The results indicate
that Mrs Alara's condition is...
Cardiac Sarcoma.
That is...
heart cancer.
Cancer?
Unfortunately...
it's a very rare disease,
but... this is what she has.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
Why are you apologising?
We had such plans.
You never used to say such silly things.
We'll go to that Blue Cave on foot.
We'll lie on our backs...
and we'll get lost.
And then we'll go there with our children.
Children?
Five of them.
Where I put the heart on the map...
I'll be waiting for you there.
Right there.
Shh...
Ok. I love you so much.
Hey, kid!
Come here!
Wait!
Ask.
Why me?
I'm glad it's you.
Your question?
Are you feeling what I'm feeling?
Oh, yes.
I love you so much.
Don't worry Cem,
there's nothing to be afraid of.
What's happening here?
Who are you?
It doesn't matter who I am.
But what you're going through right now...
that matters.
What? What's happening?
You had an accident a few minutes ago.
And right now, your brain is painting
this conversation.
The things you want to see...
Everything's being painted like a dream
in your mind.
But I...
But I've been walking for weeks,
and I've seen so many people.
Who did you see, Cem?
Think. Who have you met?
I lay on my right side...
I turn to my left.
May the angels be my witness
to my religion, to my faith.
May they take me to Allah's place.
May Allah grant peaceful sleep,
to his servant, Cem.
Cem!
Cem.
Is that why you beat your son?
To make him a man.
- As you beat iron with fire.
- ..."beat iron with fire."
That's the idea.
"I'm sorry, it was my mistake.
It only happened once,
I think he must have told you.
I'm so ashamed.
Please forgive me."
- Did she write this?
- Yes, she wrote it.
She's your fellow soldier's girlfriend.
Did you touch her?
Goodnight.
Missing person case.
Come on, Cem.
Come on, buddy.
Come on, lion!
Come back. Stay with me. Cem!
I'm sorry, Cem.
Alara? Did Alara die as well?
No, Cem.
What do you mean, no?
I buried her.
I buried her with my own hands.
A dream.
Was Alara ever ill?
No, Cem.
It was an illusion you created
in your mind.
We don't usually see ourselves
dying in a dream.
And even if we do, we wake up immediately.
Because the mind
doesn't accept that we're dead.
Instead, it draws a story for itself,
just like in dreams.
We don't have much time, Cem.
Cem, come on!
Come on, Pal! Come on, Cem!
Come on, Cem!
Am I dead?
Yes, Cem.
What happens now?
Nail?
- Nail?
- Al...
- Alara!
- What happened? Are you still on your way?
- Nail, what's happened?
Nail, tell me!
- Cem.
- Alara, I'm here!
I'm here.
- I'm here. Look at me.
- No.
Look at me.
- I'm here.
- You didn't go away.
Look at me.
- You didn't go.
- Look at me.
You didn't go away.
I'm here.
- I'm here.
- Cem.
Look at me, please. Look at me.
Cem.
I'm here.
- Cem!
- I'm here.
Look at me, please.
I told you not to go.
A new adventure awaits... you'll be a dad.
Please, look at me.
Ah...
I'm sorry.
Love your mother very much.
I love her so much.
Make her proud.
Make her laugh.
Love her very much, no matter what.
Don't go.
Subtitles: Monica Lobefaro