Lt. Carapax, tell me
that you found Carabusul.
Cut it now
This thrilling!
It's been working non-stop since I dug it up
two weeks ago.
Good. Let's keep it a secret
until we present it to the board.
Miss Kord. Miss Kord! Sorry.
- Dr. Sanchez, hello!
- Hi! That's not my name.
- How long will it last?
- We reach the core before sunrise.
Work harder!
Am căutat 15 ani.
Nu vreau să mai aștept nicio secundă.
I searched for 15 years.
I don't want to wait another second.
Is there.
I feel it.
ARCHEOLOGIST DAN GARRETT
MAKE A NEW DISCOVERY
GARRETT RECEIVES FUNDS
FROM TED KORD FOR RESEARCH
NEW HERO IN PALMERA
Justice "Blue Beetle"
save the city from Firefist
TED KORD FOR CLEAN TECHNOLOGY
TED KORD MISSING
VICTORIA KORD:
THE NEW EXECUTIVE DIRECTOR
OMAC (One Man as an Army)
LOCALIZED BLIND
Excavation location_10
KORD RESUMES THE MILITARY PROJECT
I LOVE PALMERA CITY
Welcome to PALMERA CITY
Okay, let's do this!
VOTED #1 FOR LOWEST FEES
FOR CORPORATE AMERICA
Excuse me, sir! How do I look?
Like you're 6 figures in debt.
Good.
(in italian)
You know. We're not saying anything for now.
Let's enjoy this moment!
Before he found out.
I tell him.
(in italian)
What the hell? Why not?
And that's bad news.
I can be happy.
Your job is the balloon.
I hope I can handle it.
What?
Hey, the graduate is here!
- How was the flight?
- Good.
- Are you hungry?
- Sure.
Here you go! That was all they had.
A LITTLE BOY
- Welcome back, brother!
- Thank you.
(in italian)
Now we hug!
Where's Uncle Rudy?
That's it! Welcome, damned student!
- Come down to hug me!
- Not. They're following us.
- There are rooms. Facial recognition.
- I knew you were going to say something.
Body scans.
Yes, and they are all happy
that I finally catch you
See? This style of speaking
it's going to screw us all up.
- Where did you get this?
- I got it for Jaime.
A boy? We know it's a boy.
It probably has a microphone in it.
Come on! What are you doing?
God! How I missed it!
It's good to know that some things
does not change.
Mom and Dad have something to tell you.
- Miraculous.
- What the?
He ate his taco,
now tell him the truth!
The truth? What is it?
- We...
We are losing our house.
Ce?
- Do you see? He didn't take it that badly.
- No, are we losing the house? What do you mean?
- The owner tripled the rent.
- We give him the money in three months or we leave.
I'm so sorry, flaquito.
No. But don't worry!
It's not your fault.
It just means you will have to
let's work hard at the service.
The service is no more.
- How?
- Thank Kord.
- Brother.
- I couldn't handle it.
Especially since your father...
He had...
- A...
- Dad had a heart attack.
Ce?
I'm fine!
(in italian)
At least the food is the same.
No, cabezón?
Wait, why didn't you tell me?
You worked so hard, my love.
We didn't want to disturb you from school.
Mom, I could have done something.
I could have turned back.
I could have been here. I could have...
Cheer up, Jaime!
We managed. We always do.
We have a lot to be for
grateful. Mira...
(in italian)
Yes. And the last one!
Yes, because you didn't sign up.
To be in debt for life?
No thanks.
Ce? 25%?
Mi amor, these people
he doesn't earn anything anymore.
We are broke.
Let's do it tomorrow
worry about money.
Welcome to EDGE KEYS
OUT THE CORD
You remember how my mother used to teach us
salsa right here on the porch?
- You were always better than me.
- Know. You still don't know how to dance.
- Yes, I am hindered. I have nothing to do.
- Yes.
Do you remember your 21st birthday?
I remember the first part.
I can't believe we're losing this place.
It was hard.
Yes, I won't go again.
And college?
It won't help the family.
I can't accumulate more debt.
Cheer up, brother!
You always fall on your feet.
You are Jaime.
Thanks, but...
It wasn't meant to be, Mili.
What was supposed to happen?
I had to leave.
Get us all out of here.
Thanks bro, but I like it in the Keys.
- You know what i mean.
- Yes.
Don't mind me talking
about progress and they take everything,
while we impoverish here?
You're Mexican in the Edge Keys, carnal.
That progress is not for us.
Good? The poor stay here, the rich stay here,
until the rich come here and drive us out.
I had the area behind the rails
and now they want that one too.
I have a degree, right?
It must matter.
I'm going to get a job.
Not just any, but a good one.
Yes, I will make money
to save this place.
Don't look at me like that!
Look, Mili...
In five years, we'll be bathed in money.
This will be just one of our houses.
We will have a villa on the water,
with marble throughout, infinity pool.
Yes, you will see, Mili.
You'll see.
Excuse me, Mr. Reyes?
Finished scraping the gum off the chaise longue?
What crap!
Wow! "Thank you, Milagro,
for finding me this job! "
It's not my fault that your future
it didn't turn out the way you wanted.
How to experience
when no one gives me work?
That sounds like your problem.
Really?
What the? They give us work, newbie!
Yes, I finally found it.
Dr. Sanchez is doing tests now.
With the code in hand,
we can pass the prototype phase.
Pay attention!
Yes Yes.
Look at Victoria Kord.
Look at that walk!
She's sexy like Cruella,
Kardashian's.
- I will greet her.
- Not...
Hello ma'am!
If you want, we could.
It's the discovery
which I was waiting for, general.
We are invisible
for people like them, Jaime.
It's our superpower.
Good. Back to work!
Agree. It's a waste of time
but, general, I tell you,
what I'm going to show you tomorrow night
it will leave you alone.
Yes. I can't wait too.
Pa!
Aunt Vicki.
Jennifer, what are you doing here?
I didn't know you were coming.
Carapax, she's Ted's daughter.
My favorite niece, Jennifer.
So how do I get this unexpected pleasure?
The world has changed.
Kord Industries faces off
an unprecedented challenge,
to secure our goods
from here and abroad
from our promethium mines
from Guatemala
to development projects
from Palmera City.
ntroducing the future of private policing,
OMAC, a man as much as an army.
where are we going
Gotta lighten up, bro.
I want you to hold six.
The staff bathroom is there.
Yes, I deserve to relieve myself in luxury now too.
(in italian)
Eu...
Using Kord symbiotechnology
revolutionary,
OMAC connects directly to the human brain
to create
an autonomous warfare unit,
allowing a single soldier
to have the power of legions.
OMAC ensures safety
that Kord can count on.
A future we can control.
OMAC-ul.
It goes well, don't you think?
This project has been stopped
years ago.
Why did you relaunch it?
Jennifer, the OMAC
is the future of this company.
You should be excited.
No no no. I really want to know
What's on Pago Island?
This is top secret.
It's a secret.
But I'll tell you what's not a secret:
what happens at this party
It's going to be an amazing evening,
with very interesting people.
If you want to come, bring someone
and it's going to be fun.
Okay, see you later.
I know what you're doing, Vicki.
We don't make weapons anymore.
We?
Us, who?
You are nothing in this company.
You are an expense.
A treat on the spot
from her father's counsel,
who travels for pleasure through the world
on company money...
- doing "charity works".
- Dad wouldn't be...
Your father got a company
built by me, my company,
which he then buried
with his stupid inventions
and reckless administration,
and after that you know what he did?
He disappeared and left me
to gather the remains
Your father abandoned this company.
And he abandoned you.
I won't let you do that.
Don't get in my way, Jennifer!
Back off!
I'm not afraid of you.
Maybe you should be.
He said back off ma'am.
It was divine!
Oh damn!
And who are you, handsome?
Jaime Reyes.
I think it's time to find out
a new job, jaime reyes.
- I...
- And you, toilet. Go away!
Thanks.
where is the car
47 minutes.
Are you ok? That was...
I appreciate the cavalry,
but I can take care of myself.
Absolute. But what a pain, right?
It's a Kord. They are all impatient.
Jenny Kord.
We are not all insufferable.
Clar. From the.
Look... I'm so sorry about that.
It's fine.
- Give me the phone, I'll give you my number.
- Good. Yes.
- Yes. Come to Kord Tower tomorrow.
- Good.
I might be able to give it to you
a job in the company.
Yes. God, that would be great!
I'll do anything. Wow.
Anything?
You know he has a degree, right?
- Right.
- I do.
- Do you need lawyers?
- Good.
- Message me!
I thought it was good, Jaime Reyes.
Me too...
Jenny Kord.
I think he likes you.
What the? Not.
Pa!
- Believe?
- Yes. Yes.
He took a look
at your young mexican ass
hero of the moment and he liked it.
You know what?
Maybe it will get you out of poverty
as in María la del Barrio.
Except she's rich white
and you are María!
Yes. Good.
Posts JennyKord1 HELP AFRICA
Hey Jenny! This is Jaime Reyes.
I will accept your offer.
See you tomorrow.
At?
- Only one.
- Good.
Don't tell mom!
You can not sleep?
Not.
(in italian)
I planted those nopales with nana,
when you were a baby
Check them out now!
Like you and Mili, big and beautiful.
Are you ok?
And.
I'm sorry, apá, it's just that everything now
seems unachievable and…
I feel like I've disappointed you.
We're on a journey, Jaime.
Casa asta, nopales, the auto shop.
Everything.
I'm just a stop on that journey.
But that is not the destination.
But which one is it?
I do not know.
The important thing is that we go
traveling together.
Things don't last.
It's in the family forever.
That remains.
(in italian)
Everyone has a purpose.
You just haven't found yours.
So what is your goal?
I'm still looking too.
But right now, this is it.
Let me talk to you. Here.
(in italian)
Good.
Hey, this is Jaime Reyes.
I will accept your offer.
See you tomorrow.
Okay, Jaime, you can do this.
God!
Thank you, papa.
Ya, pues, you can go, okay?
It's gonna be fine, flaquito.
Your place is here.
Yes, cabezón. you look like a jerk
like everyone here.
(in italian)
Good.
- Give it your all, brother!
- Yes.
Bring a Molotov cocktail and set it on fire!
Good! Yes!
And get me a job too!
Jaime, Jaime, Jaime!
I don't go out into the world often.
Hi, I'm Victoria Kord
and here is Kord Industries,
a company concerned with health
planet and with the future in mind.
We take our technology
latest...
Hi! Nice to meet you.
Deliveries are down.
No no no. My name is Jaime.
Jaime Reyes.
I came to Jenny Kord.
Do you have a date, Jamie?
- It's Jaime, but...
- Here you go?
Yes, I have a date.
- He said to pass, so I'm sure I'm...
- You can stay there.
Why don't you take a seat, Jamie?
Good. Thank you.
RESTRICTED AREA
REQUIRES AUTHORIZATION
ACCESS ALLOWED
He found it.
Jenny?
Good...
Good.
Just you and I.
Not.
No no no!
Not!
An intrusion has occurred.
Lock down the building!
Jenny! Jenny.
What the?
Jenny!
Sorry.
Jenny Kord! I am. Jaime from yesterday.
- I'm sorry, I'm in a hurry.
- No, it's okay.
But yesterday you said you were thinking
give me a job
and I can't live without one,
although it sounds too...
- Can you stop for a moment? Please...
- Jaime, this is really a bad time.
Good. Let's talk while you eat.
Please...
Keep in touch!
- You said you'd do anything, right?
- Yes.
- Basically, anything.
- Here you go!
- Guard it with your life!
- Good.
But don't open it! Don't touch it!
Don't even look at him!
- Okay, I'll just defend him with my life.
- Yes, you learn quickly.
- Yes.
- Good. Now go!
- Good. Good!
- Go, go!
Lock the southern entrances!
You two, with me!
Ok, let's go!
Guard the outer gate!
​
So you went to get us a job
and you only came back with a hamburger?
I don't think it's a burger.
Didn't you look?
He said not to open it. I...
- It's not here.
- What the?
(in italian)
Okay, okay, a look.
You are so childish!
what the hell is that
(in italian)
Why was he hiding it?
I do not know.
It's kind of disappointing.
The biggest tick in the world.
Okay, you guys wanted to see.
Miraculous. Okay, look...
Very mature, but he said not to open it.
- Please no...
- He said not to open it.
Finish!
- It's tough.
- Good.
I will use a motor.
- I'm taking my drill.
- Stay!
Leave the drill! What are you doing?
God, I hate it when you do that.
Is that the new Tamagotchi?
How did you get him to do that?
I do not know.
I think he likes me.
What the hell?
Do not like me!
Jaime, it's on your face! It's on your face!
Take it from me!
Alberto!
What the hell?
Where did he go? Where did he go?
God! I'm trying to help you, cabezón!
I think it's in me.
God! It's in me!
In you? How?
(in italian)
He's possessed!
Dear good!
James!
Miracle!
Rudy, what's going on?
Moves.
- Jaime?
- Moves.
No no no! Not!
Damn it! Hell!
It scared me because I did it myself.
are you ok mijo
Jaime.
What the hell'...?
Host acquired.
Who said that?
System configuration initialization.
Wait! Don't you hear that?
Don't look him in the eye!
Host analysis.
I hear a voice in my mind.
- Hi Jaime!
- What happens?
- Checking systems in three...
- Checking systems?
Two, one.
Thrusters activated.
It's fine. It will be okay!
What are you doing?
- What happens?
- Escape velocity activated.
Where are you taking me?
We cross atmospheric layers.
- Stop!
- Pressure adjustment for host.
Ay, virgencita, I'm in space.
I'm in space.
God, I'm in space!
What the heck is happening?
- Wait, is that my house?
- Testing re-entry systems.
Wait, wait! No no no!
No no no!
God! Oh God! I caught fire!
Stop it! Oh God!
Fly! Fly!
- Not. No no no.
- We are approaching contact.
- God, I'm going to die!
- 300 m.
200 m.
100 m.
Full brake system check.
Thank God it's over!
Okay, you can take me home now.
Flight systems activated.
Wait, wait, wait... Don't activate them!
Stop, stop!
Hear me out!
You got the wrong person!
I swear! I'm nobody!
Oh come on!
Testing acceleration systems.
Too fast! Too fast!
Careful! Careful!
What was that?
I don't know what I'm doing!
I'm sorry about that.
Flight control adjustment.
Take care! Take care!
Pick up! Pick up!
Why are you doing this?
- The host overreacts.
- Exaggerated? You kidnapped me!
(in italian)
20 minutes ago, I think.
- Does it work for you?
- Not.
- Because I don't have it.
- Does it work for you?
- No, man.
My back!
Full landing systems check.
- Are you OK?
- What did you do to my car?
Do you have insurance, man?
I was sick of the trouble.
A threat is approaching.
What the hell?
Oh no! What you did?
Successful host protection.
Look, did anyone get hurt?
Oh no! Calm down! I can explain.
Do not worry!
Oh my God, look a child!
It wasn't me, I swear.
It will seem crazy,
but i'm not in control...
Full systems check.
Oh no, not again!
I think it worked.
Let me explain myself one more time.
Basically, she's not a missing person,
but it disappeared.
- But it's also...
- Possessed!
It shot through the roof.
With rockets behind.
Shouldn't we be looking for him?
And I'm waiting.
Successful return landing.
Leave it! I found him.
(in italian)
Come on, hide those huevos!
It's Jamie, not Jaime.
Oh no!
What are you doing?
(in italian)
Jaime. Are you feeling good, mijo?
Not. No way.
Jaime, listen!
- Do you have something on...
- Not now, Milagro.
- I'm serious.
- Not now!
- Have something...
Jaime, hold that blanket now
that chorizo touched you.
What happens?
You can't fly.
You can't fly. Superman flies.
Those on the bus were fine.
Good. That probably
that happens all the time.
Yeah, they shouldn't do this to me.
Yes. Good.
I tried to tell him.
I need to find Jenny Kord.
She'll know how to get this out of me.
where are my shoes
Come on, where are my... shoes?
Not basketball!
They were my favorites.
Good good.
- Jaime, what happened? Where did you go?
- Well, I don't know.
I think I cut a bus in half and...
- What the?
- I flew into orbit.
- Cómo que flew into orbit?
- Well, I don't know.
- That's why I have to find Jenny Kord.
- I'll call the police.
No no. Don't call the police!
He works for Kord.
What do you think Kord will do
when will he realize it
that a Mexican kid is like that
of military technology in it?
They will close it.
And they're going to wipe our brains,
not to tell anyone.
And it's not like when the government
he's not used to locking up mexicans.
We are talking about sci-fi. We're talking about the CIA.
- From Area 51!
- Rudy, focus! What do you want to say?
I say that the government and Kord
she'll be riding us
and after that they will ask for documents.
And you, nana. And to you, Alberto.
Okay, then I'll go alone.
- Don't leave this house!
- Well, I'm 22 years old!
- And if he's in danger?
- In danger?
- Jaime, you flew through the roof.
- You do not understand.
- She likes it.
- Absolutely.
I do not like it.
- Followed his Instagram account.
- Where is...?
She's Brazilian.
Lives at Regent Tower.
And she's single, by the way.
A bit lonely, in my opinion.
is she alone
You didn't seem to like it.
- What are you doing with my phone?
- You left it unlocked.
(in italian)
Yes, he is Maria.
Yes, I said the same thing.
But María la del Barrio.
(in italian)
- Do you hear that, dude?
- Rudy!
Not. No no.
Not. Not. Not!
James!
Not! Not! Not!
(in italian)
Don't be silly! Rudy!
What a scratch!
Good.
You can not!
What the...?
Wait, what...?
Jenny?
Oh God!
What are you doing here?
- Let it go, I'm coming!
- Who?
They!
- Oh God! Good!
- Come on! Come on!
Good good. Oh God!
- I told you to go!
- You should have said they have guns.
Take care!
Rudy is going to kill me!
My headlights!
Not! My mirrors!
what the hell man
What's up with you? Cabezón!
do you want some water
- My tailgate!
- No thanks.
Good.
What did you do with Taco?
- He's Rudy too.
- My name is César, okay?
And only my friends call me Rudy.
- I'm Jenny.
- “I'm Jenny. ” Hi Jenny!
We know who you are. What are you doing here?
You are thinking of making this house
a nuclear plant?
I went swimming near the waves
does your family have company
My testicles are seven times bigger.
You shouldn't loot cobalt
from a developing country Jenny?
- Where is it?
- Yes.
Let me!
Rudy! What the?
- What are you doing?
- Rudy!
I thought chingaderas was going to come out.
- To leave?
- God!
- What is he talking about?
- About it.
I forgot how bad it looks.
(in italian)
I've seen worse.
- Where?
- You do not want to know.
Okay, what the hell is this thing?
It's called Carabus.
Dad got it when I was little.
It's a kind of weapon
destroyer of worlds.
How pretty!
- Weapon?
- What did he say?
What the?
And you knew what was going to happen
with my brother
when you gave him this gun
destroyer of worlds?
No, I swear I had no idea.
It's like this...
Dad said it can't be activated
by anyone.
They have to choose you.
- I guess he chose you.
- No more meetings with strangers.
- Good. And how do we make them stop choosing me?
- I do not know.
But we'd better get moving
because my aunt
he's going to kill us just to get him.
Will it kill us?
I am not sorry.
I didn't mean that.
She sent the assassins.
(in italian)
I'm sorry I put you in this situation.
I didn't know it would activate.
Even. I did not know.
- How convenient!
- He already said he didn't know.
It's a Kord! Do you really trust her?
We will find a solution.
We always do.
Come on, we're the Reyes family.
We have faced harder things.
Yes?
Cheer up! We can do this.
Yes. Yes, father.
Is right.
Okay, so how are we going to get this out of me?
Before they give us another hole in the house.
Exact.
There is a place
where we could find answers.
- But we need the key.
- Okay, and where's the key?
In the Kord building. And they probably are
on alert since I took Carabus.
So what are we talking about?
Laser based security systems?
Moving image detection
on large areas, maybe?
Photonic emitters?
- Not really...
- Because I worked on something...
what I think would help us
and it's almost done.
If I get the mechanical structure.
I love you mom.
Give me a few hours!
Are you aware that
if you do the OMAC,
you will be the strongest
arms manufacturers in the world.
Invest and you can tell me what you want.
That I was talking about the wolf...
General, he is Lt. Carapax.
It was crucial
for prototype development,
and I personally chose it
for his courage
during anti-terrorist operations,
anti-communists from Guatemala.
It's the perfect container for OMAC,
and a product of the School of the Americas.
Nice to meet you, lieutenant.
I can't wait to see him in action.
When it will be done?
It's ready, right?
We just have a few more details to finish.
We have a problem.
Excuse us!
Smoke a cigar!
They are made by real Cubans.
have you lost it How?
- Someone helped her.
- I want to know who he is working with now.
Because, without Carabus,
we cannot complete the OMAC.
I take care I'm going to bring the Carabus back.
- This time, I will do it personally.
- I hope so, Carapax.
Otherwise, all your sacrifices
they will have been in vain.
Think about how much suffering
your body passed.
I am aware of what you did to them.
God! What we did to him.
Ignacio, I'm on your side.
You don't remember what it was like
when did i find you
How stupid were you?
How broken?
I'm trying to fix you.
Good?
Good.
I have to get back to the party.
Bring me that Carabusa!
That's it?
I call him El Chapulín.
Why?
You know, when you do something cool,
you can call it whatever you want.
Please make yourself useful! Hold this!
Are you sure it works?
Thank you. Yes.
Unlike the crap made
by Kord, my technology works.
- You could just say yes.
- Good. Sweetie, do you hit the switch?
- The yellow one.
- I did it.
Good. At least I don't have to open it
that annoying tailgate.
Enter at your own expense.
Make some room!
I have to give it a…
- That's sexy!
- That's great!
That's great! So it goes.
Yes, it works.
I'll keep the engine running.
Come on!
Mira nomás. "So it works"?
guys...
Something is happening.
what the hell is this
Join me and my little friends,
and Kord branches...
The key is here.
Worldwide,
to build a better future.
A future Kord.
She looked so different then!
Vicki and my grandfather founded
Kord Industries together
and they transformed it
in a military power.
Then when my grandfather died,
Victoria thought she would get the company.
But he left everything to my father.
- It seems somewhat...
- Sexist?
Yes.
But dad wanted a different direction
for the company.
So Victoria became obsessed
to erase my father's legacy.
can you help me here
Yes, sorry. what do you need
- Hold this!
- Good.
A signal is jamming our transmission.
We are jammed.
Lt. Carapax, we have a problem.
- Is that the key?
- Yes.
- Ok, let's go!
- Let's go!
TED CLOCK
PROTOTYPE DESIGNED BY TED KORD
That's why I don't let anyone drive Taco!
Honestly, I didn't think Chapulín would go.
Yes, that's right Rudy.
It's like a Mexican Doc Brown.
Really?
- Good.
- Is that all you need?
- Yes.
- Dear good!
I don't know why I thought so
that it will be much harder.
Oh damn!
The car, now!
what is he doing here
Let's run away? Don't slow down.
Take care!
God! how did you do that
I have no idea.
He got angry.
What the hell is that thing?
the OMAC.
You will regret this.
Host defense.
God! Quick! Go to Rudy's!
- Attacking the threat.
- Attack? Not!
Oh damn!
Okay, wait, wait! No, no, wait! Not!
What did you do that for?
I told you not to attack.
I have an arsenal at my disposal.
Not! No weapons.
It's my song too!
- Caesar!
- What the?
- What the hell, where is the cabezón?
- There!
Hey! Calm down!
- Damn it! Go! Go! Go!
- C'mon C'mon!
I will talk to him.
Verbal communication is not recommended
in a combat scenario.
Man, I think this is just a misunderstanding...
I didn't mean to hit you.
I swear I wouldn't...
I don't control this thing.
No, let me explain!
Leave! Do not listen.
Permission to take over the host.
Yes! Anything!
Watch and learn, Jaime!
Where are you going?
Come on!
What the hell?
Oh God! My hands are weapons.
Threat neutralized.
What's with the swords?
Elimination of the threat.
No no no. Put down the swords!
Would you like to use another weapon?
Not. No need to kill him.
- Elimination of the threat.
- You are listening to me?
Elimination of the threat.
Stop it! I'm not a killer.
Order accepted.
Cabezón!
James!
Uncle Rudy.
Not!
God!
Rudy!
Where do you think you're going?
You have to get out of here!
What's with this guy?
What the?
Stupid boy!
Do you think you could beat me?
I recommend lethal measures.
I told you, I'm not...
Warning: Concussion detected.
You should have liquidated me
when you had the chance.
It's going to kill him.
Not. He won't do it.
Hold on!
Please don't hurt my family.
Love to your family
makes you weak
Caesar! What are you doing?
Okay, Kord girl,
when i tell you
pull hard on the handbrake!
- Are you ready?
- God, this is crazy!
Three, two, one.
Now!
Cabezón, let's get out of here!
It's good? James! James!
Jenny! Snap out!
- Good.
- Do not look!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm fine, Rudy. Thank you.
Good. All right.
God...
That psychopath was going to kill me.
Did you get the key?
- All right.
- Yes.
Good. Now let's take it out
The nerd in you.
Khaji- Yes.
The Carabao's name is Khaji-Da.
How do you know?
Something happened there.
I can feel it in my mind. Is it crazy?
Become symbiotic.
- What the?
- Okay, where now?
- Take that exit!
- What the? Stay!
No no no!
Does anyone know how to drive in this town?
Won't he look for you here?
There was no one here
since I was eight years old.
Yes I understand. Makes sense.
So your dad was obsessed with ghosts?
Where we are?
You can not!
Stay!
Was Ted Kord Blue Beetle?
What the hell is Blue Beetle?
You were a child. He's Palmera's superhero.
Like Superman in Metropolis
and Flash in Central City.
But...
I don't know, maybe not as good.
I can't believe it was Blue Beetle.
But I understand.
Eccentric billionaire, a genius.
Your father was a great man.
I did not know.
You can call me César or Rudy.
As you wish, I don't care.
How about all this...?
- Are you ok?
- Yes.
What were you saying?
- How come these don't look anymore...?
- Beautiful? Less ridiculous?
No, but I mean...
Look at this!
It's like Batman's...
if he had ADHD.
Batman is a fascist.
Blue Beetle had a sense of humor.
Dad never could
to unlock Carabus.
Instead, he made his own equipment
to fight like Blue Beetle.
If there's a way to get it out, it's there.
Let's crack this one!
- Damn you!
- This is your shirt.
Come on, I think I am
some of dad's clothes upstairs.
It is a good idea.
This is going to take a while.
God!
When will this day end?
Everything is okay?
Yes. Yes. I'm going out right away.
Yeah, I think... I think I'm coming.
And they're comfortable too, so…
Good.
It must have been really cool
to grow up here, right?
Honestly, it was...
I was quite alone most of the time.
- Was it just the three of you here?
- Yes.
That was my mother's last painting.
Why did it stop?
My mother died when I was six years old.
We do not...
- I am sorry that...
- No, it's okay.
what was it like
She was great.
It changed my dad's life.
She taught him that the world is a place
what needs to be protected.
Beautiful!
But when my mother died,
it really got lost.
He was obsessed with Carabusul
and disappeared for days on end.
Sometimes weeks.
And one day...
he left and...
he never came back.
I'm so sorry, Jenny.
You are very lucky.
This house... is full of stuff.
Your house is full of love.
A family.
Yes.
That's a dorm.
I am sorry. I am so sorry.
For what?
I didn't talk about it anymore
for a very long time.
Sounds like fun to do, doesn't it?
Thank you.
Yes.
You know how to listen.
Mom says it is
because of the big ears.
Look, I found something...
- Nothing happened.
- Her mother died.
I found something you need to see.
Perfect! That's great! Come on!
Nice pajamas, güey.
Good.
I looked through the files.
So, Ted had a teacher,
a guy named Dan Garrett.
The bastard chose this Garrett
before they choose you.
And pinche Ted was testing it
to see
how Carabus reacted to the human body.
When the Carabus sticks in someone's ass...
It didn't bother me.
Okay, it connects through the brain
and that's what he's trying to do to you, Jaime.
Try to be one with you.
Why?
Ask him yourself! It has its own will.
He is aware.
That's why it chooses a host.
That's why sometimes it does what you want
and sometimes not.
Who made it? can i help us
It wasn't made on Earth, cabezón.
- You can not!
- Sure.
- It's alien.
- I don't really like the term.
- You can use it, but...
- It doesn't matter, Rudy.
What happened to Ted's teacher?
How did he get it out?
You might want to sit down.
Or not. Good...
- Rudy, please! Concentrate!
- I have good and bad news.
The good news is that I figured it out
how to remove it.
Good.
And the bad news
it's that you must be dead.
- What the?
- Dead.
What do you mean "dead"?
Look, Jaime, now merge
with every cell in your body.
It's completely wrapped around your brain.
And nothing on Earth
he could not remove it.
It is made to defend its host.
To keep her alive.
- So this is in me forever?
- No, it's not forever.
Only until you... die.
Sounds cool to me, right?
You're basically a superhero, cabrón.
- I am so sorry! I had no way...
- You did not know.
So what options do I have now?
Option one is to become an android
for the rest of the life.
Or option two is to volunteer
a psychopathic billionaire criminal?
I just wanted a job.
- Pérate, güey. Maybe it's a...
- Maybe what, Rudy?
It's all bad news.
That does not improve our situation.
I don't understand why you can't...
God!
Finally. I'm going to take two steps.
Jaime, just...
I talk to him.
I think I know where this is going.
Cabezón, wait!
God!
Look at him! I knew I would find you here.
Like a cat, Jaime.
Forgive me for yelling at you, Rudy.
I shouldn't have, but...
It doesn't escape me that your situation
it's a bit unusual.
Yes we are...
We are resilient people.
Life will keep hitting us
and the difference is that it makes us
stronger.
Look at your father!
He brought me here from Sonora.
I was ten years old. He was 19 I think.
And people think that crossing the border is difficult.
Yes, it's hard, but you know what's even harder?
The next 20 years, on the leash.
But your viejo worked 16 hours a day,
he was scolding himself.
Any grief caught.
Jornalero, waiter, waiter.
He was a mechanic, he was a todo,
dishwasher.
And it brought us all here
and held us all together.
And not that he wanted to, but that he had to.
We go from there.
The universe sent you a gift, Jaime.
And you'll have to see what you're going to do with it.
Maybe it happened for a reason.
Maybe it's time we had our own hero.
Not just kicks in the ass.
But what do I know?
I'm just a broken promise
who sleeps in his brother's living room.
Don't say that, man!
You are not a broken promise.
Come on, you're the best! You know this.
- I am the best.
- Yes.
And I love you.
I love you too, cabezón.
OK.
- Yes.
- Guys?
Do you hear that?
It's Victoria.
Where are they going?
The home.
You are wasting too much water.
It's always my fault.
(in italian)
Hear...
I think there's someone at the window.
Jaime Reyes, come out with your hands up!
Surrender! We are authorized
to use lethal force.
(in italian)
Good. Good.
I will fly. I will fly.
Let's do this!
Yes!
Yeah, no chance.
Now!
Man, don't worry! Do not rush.
Thank you, Jenny.
- You have to force him out.
- What the...?
- You are a genius.
- Know. What I said?
You said you were going to protect me, right?
He won't let me die?
No no. When you die...
- Let's see if it works.
- I wouldn't test this.
- No, no, no, Jaime!
- Wait, Jaime!
- We're going back to Tacoma, I guess.
- Yes.
We surrounded the Reyes' house.
The family is inside.
You know what you have to do.
Take them!
Penetration team, go!
With me!
I entered.
Spread yourself out! The light!
Free!
- The light!
- I'm defending your left.
Back room, free!
Free!
Hands on head. Don't move!
- Good good.
- Don't move!
- Don't touch my family!
- Get up!
Come on! Up, up!
Hands up! Watch out on the right!
Miss Kord, we found the family.
- I'm going out now.
- Take them out! Come on!
Force them out!
Come on! Move!
Move!
C'mon C'mon!
Do not oppose!
Down! Down!
Down now! Come now!
The kid isn't there.
Find him!
Is he in?
(in italian)
Where is it?
- I could use the arsenal now.
- I didn't think you would ask again.
Hell yes!
Well done Khaji!
Are you OK?
- Jaime?
- Sorry I'm late, mom.
Magnificent!
wait what?
Don't shoot! I don't want to hurt you.
Fire!
Damn it!
I said don't shoot!
God, I'm bulletproof.
Let's see what you can do!
Target the family!
- Attack!
- Liquidate them!
I'll protect you, no worries!
It will be okay.
Okay, let's see what you can do.
Threat removal.
What the? No, Khaji, we don't kill them!
Yes, that's how it goes!
Leave here!
Run away!
- Threat level analysis.
- Okay, let's do this!
Hell yes!
Down to earth!
- Daddy!
- Honey!
I caught one.
(in italian)
Down! Do not move!
Stay where you are!
- Not!
- I caught another one.
Father!
Come to my father!
Carapax, prepare the claw!
Daddy, I'm scared.
Everything will be alright.
- Jaime, your family.
- Sit down!
Get up!
Okay, come on, papi!
Mili, get dad out of here! Go!
- Go!
- Good. Let's go!
Prepare her!
They have a gun. I suggest we retreat.
No way! attack my family
we're going to finish this.
And...
Father...
Dad, no! Dad, what is it?
Father! Father!
No no no! Father!
Not!
No no no!
- Father!
- Not!
Now!
What happens?
- Symbiotic systems... critical.
- Khaji, do something!
Dad, no!
Father! The water!
Not. No no no.
Not.
No, Jaime.
Jaime, watch out!
You! You!
What do you want from us?
What are you doing?
Take that away from me, psycho!
Mother!
- Mommy!
- Honey!
Alberto!
Let me go!
- Khaji, do something!
- I caught him. Let's go!
- Rudy. Rudy, Rudy.
- Hermano, wake up!
The water!
I'll come... I'll come get you.
Call an ambulance!
Free!
Free! Free!
(in italian)
But not now.
Nana is right, Mili.
We have to save Jaime.
How?
We don't even know where they took him.
I might know where it is.
Please!
Come with me!
I can help.
Be careful!
Good.
Let's do this!
Miraculous, hurry up. Come on!
Good good.
Enough enough.
Good.
Let's hope the Kord technology works.
Stay like that!
Man!
- Done.
- Welcome back to the Beetle Ship, Teddy!
- That's sexy!
- Look at you!
- It's crazy!
- Thrusters!
- Let's get our boy!
- Let's do this!
Jenny.
Good.
Good, good, good. Good.
And what's the plan when we get there?
- We burn that bridge when we get there.
- That's not how they say it...
Amá, fly!
After 15 years, everything I've done,
all the sacrifices
they drove at this point.
Finally, the power of Carabus
it will be ours.
Almost ready.
We're going to change the world, Carapax.
Are you ready?
I'm ready.
(in italian)
Is that bulletproof?
Do you want to see daddy's toys?
Wait, is that Kabloom gum?
No no. It's not what you think.
Kabloom CHEWING GUM!
It's just a special prototype
designed by dad.
Do these work?
Some. Sometimes.
That's the Beetle Shield.
Try pressing another button.
Yeah, you know what?
I think I'll keep this one.
Okay, so how do we learn to use these?
Nanny?
How do you know how to hold that perfectly?
(in italian)
This is where they took Jaime.
Pago is an island in the Caribbean,
near the Cuban coast,
which Kord bought
from Batista in the 50s.
It's a fortress.
How the hell are we going to get in there?
(in italian)
What the hell?
Mili, one day we will have to talk
about grandma's revolutionary past.
Here you go?
(in italian)
That's where we enter!
directly to the basement.
Yes, the generators are here.
We can burn them, leave them without electricity.
(in italian)
Damn it, nana!
Who are you?
What are you doing?
Get me out of this please!
Is there a problem, Sanchez?
I am sorry.
You're sorry! What this means?
Tell him to snap me out of it!
It's fine.
Yes. Listen, kid!
The bastard chose you.
This is true.
But it doesn't belong to you.
It belongs to me.
But now that you've activated it,
we can transfer his code
directly in OMAC.
What are you talking about?
No, no, Miss Kord. It could kill him.
Nasty!
But sacrifices must be made
for the greater good.
And this is yours, Jaime Reyes.
Do it, Sanchez!
With all due respect,
my name is not Sanchez
Hey, hey!
Get me out of this!
Damn it!
Beetle.
- Rudy.
- Yes, I see him.
You're going too fast!
There is no death attempt!
AIR BRAKES
Hold on!
Good. Good.
It's coming!
Prepare for impact!
Come on, come on!
At the wall! Attack! Attack!
Rudy, do something!
Rudy, we have to move.
BEAST MODE
Let's go!
Good good.
To one side!
I am sorry!
- It's like I can't miss!
- There!
(in italian)
Twenty points!
I activate the camouflage system.
Activate cockroach.
Not from here!
- Yes, this way!
- Good.
Hey, come on!
I know you hear me.
Let me go!
I'll keep him safe.
Start the transfer!
And when it's done, kill the kid!
Get me out of here!
But we could learn a lot
from his connection with Carabus.
We can learn a lot more
from his corpse.
Let me go! Not! Not!
Miracle! Hide!
God!
Okay, I guess that's okay.
What the...?
Victoria, you damn fool!
what the hell is this
Fully functional OMAC systems.
Enough to make an army.
Miss Kord, this doesn't look good.
What happens?
Oh, no. Downloading Carabus
generates too much energy.
Systems are at full capacity.
What this means?
The transfer is killing him.
He can't die
before the transfer is complete.
His pulse drops.
Straighten it up!
Hey, flaco.
Father.
What happens?
What are you doing here?
Know...
Not. The water.
(in italian)
Miracle, here.
Help me with these!
Jaime.
It's not your time yet.
You have to go back.
(in italian)
Please!
I understand everything now.
I was meant to be here with you.
At this point.
To help you pass.
(in italian)
That's your goal.
Time to accept your destiny, Jaime.
How am I going to do this without you?
(in italian)
How will I know what to do?
I love you too, papi.
Something is happening.
What the?
His brainwaves are synchronizing
with the Carăbușului frequency.
There. It's connecting.
I need you, Khaji!
I become one.
Did I get the code?
The transfer is complete. The code is ours.
It works!
Oh no!
Go! Go! Go!
Good. We let it go!
- OK, come on!
- Yes.
Not. No no no!
Sanchez, stop him!
Oh damn!
What the?
Take your family and run off the island!
Stay! The family?
- Quick!
- What do you mean "family"?
Go!
Sanchez, you idiot! What are you doing?
My name is not Sanchez, pendeja!
It's Jose Francisco Morales
Rivera de la Cruz!
What are you doing?
Stop him, Carapax!
Go! I will be fine.
Okay, Khaji, come on!
Good. All right, Khaji, activate!
Reboot.
Reboot? You're kidding?
Oh God! Oh no! Oh no!
- Go, go!
- Good good.
Milagros, wait!
- Oh, no, no!
- What? What?
No, no, be careful!
Jenny.
Jenny?
Jenny!
I can finally feel it.
This image really suits you.
Good.
Okay, Khaji. All right, Khaji-Da.
You can do this. You can do this.
Come on! Let's go! Come on!
Still rebooting.
Come on!
Do not move!
Stand there!
Come on!
Do not move!
Knock him down!
Nanny?
(in italian)
Good.
Where did you learn to shoot like that?
(in italian)
Open your eyes!
Miracle!
Jennifer, Jennifer, Jennifer.
What a disaster you have created!
Come on! Standing! Get up!
(in italian)
Miraculous.
Where is it?
- Milagro and Jenny are there.
- You can not!
Okay, I have to go back.
Yes. And the suit?
It doesn't work now.
I can't deal with him.
- Jaime.
- Yes?
Good.
What is the name of that chongo?
Khaji- Yes.
Yes.
I know you hear me, Khaji-Da.
I want you both to come to your senses!
Find your strength, mijito!
Use the pain we feel
and turn it into power!
I want you back there...
(in italian)
I found one of them.
Trouble!
- Drop the gun!
- Damn it!
Full reboot.
Get the hell away from my sister!
I'm out of ammo.
Are you ready, Khaji?
(in italian)
Come on them!
who's first
Want more?
Wait, watch out!
Attack the target!
Come on!
God, there are more!
Catch him!
What the hell? Get them off me!
With pleasure.
- Thank you, Khaji.
- No way.
Stay!
One more.
Get over here!
Come on!
Nice slap!
(in italian)
Okay, I deserved that.
I thought I would never see you again.
I told you I'm not going anywhere.
- But you left...
- I wasn't there...
Rudy! Rudy!
Dear God! You are safe.
I thought I lost you.
No no. Look!
Stay! where is jenny
We were separated. I do not know.
Okay, we have to find her.
We will find her
before others, because...
Careful!
What the hell was that?
- OMAC is coming, Jaime.
- Damn it!
Give it up!
Okay, let's do this, Khaji!
Give me rockets or something!
Detach blasters.
Okay, now give me the swords!
Okay, now give me...
Watch out, he's stronger than before.
Okay I understand.
- Okay, where are we going?
- At Ship-Bug! It's beyond.
- But where are you going?
- To take Cabezón. Go!
Critical wing damage.
You will help me? I'll help you too.
Okay, strongman!
You don't deserve this power!
I thought you hit harder than that!
Okay, we need something else, Khaji!
Power reactor access.
Like this!
Okay, do you want to dance?
Now give me a sword.
So I can make whatever weapons I want?
Anything you can imagine I can create.
Let's party!
Good choice!
Come on!
On time!
Yes!
Come on! Is that all you can do?
Let's not rush, Jaime!
Khaj, don't worry! We can do this.
Okay, it's a little harder than I thought.
Critical regenerative systems.
- What the hell?
- There can only be one of us.
Khaji, do something!
What? Can't you breathe?
Jaime, I can't protect you anymore.
I am sorry.
Khaji, Khaji, stay with me!
You're still a scared little boy!
I told,
the love you feel
for your family it makes you weak.
Hey!
(in italian)
Come on! Come get me!
Aquí te lo tengo, man Come on!
Rudy.
Damn it!
Not!
Rudy!
Khaji-Yes!
Your OMAC has failed.
Jennifer, you don't know what OMAC is.
Carapax is just a prototype.
That's the only important thing.
The Code of Carabus.
With this, I can make a thousand Carapaxi.
It's the culmination of my life's work.
It's Kord's legacy. It is our heritage.
Not mine. I'll make sure of that.
You will coalesce
with that junk in Edge Key
instead of your family?
That trash from Edge Key
knows more about a family
than you will ever know.
I know. I know about family.
I know about my family,
who overlooked me
just like you are doing now
because you are just like your pitiful father.
Which he didn't have the courage to do
what was needed for the greater good.
I wish Ted was here now,
to see this.
(in italian)
Not! I'm not finished!
Jaime, the disarmed threat.
You lose control.
Do you think you could beat me?
You should have finished me
when you had the chance.
OMAC neutralized.
I recommend ceasing the attack.
What are you doing?
We are not murderers, Jaime. Let her go!
And dad?
And Rudy?
During transfer,
I unlocked his memories.
Let me show you.
What if he doesn't survive the operation?
Then we'll get another one.
It could kill him.
Sacrifices must be made
for the greater good.
This country is facing
with a brutal challenge,
from armed guerilla troops,
supported by others outside Guatemala.
The United States is determined
to restore democracy
and solve basic problems
of violent insurgency.
We know the problems in Guatemala.
Perfect! Collect them!
Mother!
Ignacio!
Now understand?
Hey! Cabezón!
You're wrong.
That love that I have
for my family...
that makes me strong.
Okay, give it to me! Come on!
- To stay?
- Yes, that one.
Not!
What you did?
Not! No no!
Jenny!
It's fine.
Carapax, kill them!
Kill them both!
(in italian)
Good.
What are you doing? We don't...
Not.
Wait, Jenny, wait!
Return to the Beetle Ship.
I'll come right away too.
- What the?
- I promise.
We can be partners.
I'll fix it. I'm going to direct you.
We can find another Sanchez.
Do you remember everything I did for you?
(in italian)
Khaji, what is he doing?
It maximizes its
the power reactor in the suit.
I advise you to move away.
Ignacio.
(in italian)
What the? What the?
What not! What are you doing?
Stop it! Not!
(in italian)
Sacrifices must be made
for the greater good.
Not! Please! Not!
Ignacio, no!
I suggest we run.
Good. Damn it!
Milagros, shoot!
Rocío!
Are you ok?
Miles
Cabezón.
Rudy?
- How?
- Yes. Know...
(in italian)
It's a delicate moment
for Kord Industries.
And of course we mourn
the loss of Victoria Kord.
But I look ahead.
As I said, we will no longer make weapons.
What I want to do
it's to honor my father's legacy.
It's not about destruction,
but of building a better future.
It's not about taking from the community,
but to give back to the community.
What are we going to do now?
Come on, Rudy, okay?
We'll get through this.
As always.
Hey! Reyes are here.
Hear...
(in italian)
Nana
Where? We don't have a house.
Rudy, one half of the Edge Keys
they are in our yard now.
They will certainly be happy to help us.
Yes, of course. Of course they will help.
- Yes, until when? Until Kord kicks us out?
- I wouldn't worry about that.
Jenny, Jenny.
(in italian)
I think it's time to bring back Edge Keys
to those who made it great.
Apparently the Reyes family is influencing her
a little Jenny Kord huh?
Kord has a lot to learn from Edge Keys.
Starting with you, Rudy.
- Wait, you told him to say that?
- Rudy, I didn't say anything.
Sounds like something you would tell him to tell me.
And don't worry! Kord Industries
he will fix it up and give you your house back.
Excuse me!
- Here you go!
- Thank you.
- Welcome, Rudy!
- What is this?
I felt very stupid,
so i bought you a new hatchback.
Do you like it sweetie?
Wow, it's blue. A bit obvious, right?
- Rudy.
- Rudy. "Thank you".
- I will think about it.
- Yes, look!
- Come on, help me like it.
- Okay, I inherit it.
OK I have to go.
Yes.
How about driving you?
- Yeah sure.
- Good.
And... when will I see you again?
Soon. I hope
Where are you going?
Dad's home.
I want to look at my mother's paintings again.
I forgot how beautiful they are.
Good. Good.
What if I took you?
How?
I can feel your blood rushing
in the middle part.
Finish!
No no no. Not you.
What does it say?
Nothing.
Good.
Hold on!
Hello? Hello?
God, it works! Good.
Whoever turned on my computer
to give a message to my daughter Jenny.
Jenny Kord.
Please tell her I love her
and that I'm sorry
and that her father is alive.
Ted Kord is alive.
TRANSLATION AND ADAPTATION
ANDREA PUTICIU
Oh, that's sexy!