In here.
Hey!
Hey! Hey! What about him?
What about him?
Hey. Someone.
Help. Assistance.
This man needs help.
This man pays my salary.
Forty point two three pounds.
Are they back yet?
Have you heard from anyone?
If Pinkman is gone...
...I'm done. Do you understand?
I quit.
I just told you, 40.23 pounds.
Forty point two one.
My brother-in-law, he keeps talking
about driving out to the factory farm.
And I have- I have stalled him
as long as I possibly can.
It's really at the point now...
...where he's gonna find someone else
to take him there.
So I don't know
if it's been made presentable yet.
But I should be the one
to take him out there, right?
Can you just run it up
the chain of command then?
Anything suspicious?
Still no, Walt.
Well, then should we go?
Got some place to be? Because it's,
like, the third time you asked me that.
No, I'm just curious
what the next move is.
Our next three moves
is sitting here and waiting.
This here's the job, buddy.
Ain't all supermodels and speedboats,
you know.
Any cartel news these days?
Seems like I'm always reading
something or other in the paper.
Yeah, well,
not a lot happening stateside.
Hearing rumblings
about some big play down south.
Lots of bodies, apparently.
You know, even by cartel standards.
We'll know more
when the buzzards leave the bones.
So when we gonna talk
about your face?
- I don't wanna get into it, okay?
- No, it's not okay.
My brother-in-law shows up
looking like Macho Camacho...
...and he thinks
we're not gonna discuss it?
If you're in over your head
on something...
...don't you think I might be the guy
to come to?
You know, one of my old buddies
from Glynco had a gambling problem...
...except his thing was scratch cards
instead of blackjack.
Dumb Okie bastard had his car repo'd
playing scratch-and-wins.
He's fine now, you know.
He got help and all.
But I know he got on a ride
that was rough to get off of.
I'm just saying I'm here, you know.
If you want to talk about it.
I don't want to talk about it,
to you or to anyone else.
I'm done explaining myself.
Hey, you think he needs more blood?
It's in the refrigerator.
What, you- You want me to...?
A- negative, yes?
Your blood type?
I don't know, maybe.
A- negative, 25 years old...
...seventy kilo, 180 centimetres.
You smoke, you drink,
you puff, puff, puff.
But no disease, no condition.
No complication
other than an allergy to...
Oh, wait, don't say.
Erythromycin.
But I have cefazolin here,
so no problem.
How do you know all that?
Jesus.
He thought of everything.
O- negative.
That's what he needs.
It's time to go.
What about Mike?
With this injury? No travel.
At least a week.
I'll send for him.
You need protection, Gustavo?
I wouldn't have guessed.
Water and rest.
What happened to the plane?
There are many good ways south.
But, unfortunately, only one way north.
Six miles to Texas.
I've got a man there
who'll drive us the rest of the way.
I kind of liked the plane.
So you gonna make it?
Six miles is pretty far.
I'll make it.
You did well down here.
And you also proved a point.
I think you can run the lab
by yourself now.
Don't you?
Let Mr. White go.
Pay him off or fire him.
Don't kill him.
- You know that won't work.
- Then you got a problem.
Hi. We're home.
Are you doing your homework?
Yeah.
Well, dinner is in about 30.
Hey, sorry to call you at home...
...but I think maybe
you're not getting my messages.
That or you just
don't feel like talking to me.
Anyway, why I've been calling
is because that thing we discussed?
Well, I've been thinking...
...and I decided I can't do it. That's
probably not what you wanted to hear.
But hopefully you'll understand...
...and if you want to talk more about it,
that's fine.
So call me. I'm around.
- Hey. Come on in.
- Hi.
First, I wanna tell you that I get it.
From what you've told me, this situation
with Walt's gambling sounds...
...intense.
Yeah, it definitely was.
And continues to be.
So I would greatly appreciate it
if you would just help me out here.
Well, I've thought long and hard
about this...
...and here's what I want to do.
So is Walt gonna be okay?
Are you in contact with him?
He's fine.
Good. That's good.
- He doesn't know about you offering -
- No. Absolutely not.
And I mean to keep it that way, so...
Six hundred and seventeen
thousand dollars written out to me.
- What is this?
- I can't take your money.
- And why is that?
- Because, at the end of the day...
...paying my debt
with illicit gambling winnings...
I don't know, it feels wrong.
"It feels wrong"?
To me it does.
I'm not judging you or Walt. I'm
just saying I feel uncomfortable with it.
Well, Ted, the whole reason
we're in this mess...
...is because you had me
cooking your books.
So when did wrong
suddenly become a problem for you?
Now, hold on,
that was a one-time measure...
...in an honest attempt
to protect my employees...
...and save my dad's company.
It might've been a big mistake, but
that's no reason to go out make another.
No, Ted, this is the big mistake,
right here.
You owe the federal government
$617,000. If you do not pay them...
...they will come after you
and then they will come after me.
And if they audit my business
find out that Walt and I paid for it...
...with close to a million dollars
in untaxed gambling winnings...
...we will go to prison. Where you will
already be. Do you understand?
I understand you're upset, but I think
you're overstating things too.
No one's going to prison.
Oh, my God.
How are you not following me here?
Okay, fine,
let's say I take your advice.
I pay the IRS. Then what?
Then you don't owe them.
Okay, but I still owe the bank, Skyler.
I'm still going to go bankrupt
and lose my business and my home.
I still have to pull my girls
out of school.
Just because I pay some stupid fine
doesn't make my life any less ruined.
So if I'm understanding you
correctly...
...you're saying you can't take
the money I gave you...
...but you can take a larger amount.
No. I'm just saying...
...as much as I appreciate the gesture...
...the money you gave me
doesn't really change anything.
- Because it's not enough?
- No, no, don't twist my words.
This isn't about amounts,
this is about me doing the right thing.
- Ted, are you blackmailing me?
- What? No. Blackmailing?
God.
- I feel I'm not explaining things right.
- I think you're explaining it fine.
I notice that this is for less
than what I gave you, by the way.
That's the Mercedes. I leased it before
I knew where the money came from.
Now that you know,
you will be returning it.
The leases are ironclad,
so I have to see what's possible...
...but, yeah, I'm gonna do my best.
And I will pay you back
as soon as I can.
I don't want you to pay me, Ted.
I want you to pay them.
Try it again.
Write a new cheque.
- Skyler.
- Same amount.
- This time, made payable -
- What happened to us?
Make it payable
to the Internal Revenue Service.
- I can't.
- You have to.
- Actually, no I don't.
- Write it.
Saul Goodman, please.
Tell him it's important.
Yeah.
What have I done?
Hello, Hector.
All of them, Hector.
Don Eladio.
Don Paco. Cesar.
Renaldo. Artuno.
Cisco and Luis.
Escalada.
All dead.
As is your grandson, Joaquin.
Do you know who killed Joaquin?
Would you like to see?
This young man.
Do you remember him?
That young man
shot Joaquin to death.
While I made my escape.
I believe you have met him before.
It was just you and Joaquin.
He was the only family you had left.
Now the Salamanca name
dies with you.
Will you look at me now?
Look at me, Hector.
Look at me.
I really appreciate you doing this.
You guys must have your hands filled
with the car wash and all.
No, no. No worries.
Happy to do it.
Besides, it gives me a chance
to see how you work a case.
- It's interesting.
- Yeah.
Like watching weeds grow.
This job can be boring as hell.
Until it's not.
So...
- Any more news on that thing in Mexico?
- No, same old, same old.
Bunch of animals
clawing each other's eyes out over turf.
So you think all the victims
were cartel members?
Not in the loop enough to know.
Take a right on this street, will you?
Right?
But we're going to the chicken farm,
that's straight ahead.
No, we're taking a little detour.
All right.
Yeah, there's this industrial laundry
I wanna check out.
It's not far.
Just, yeah, turn right here.
What-?
What laundry? What about it?
It's owned by this company,
this Madrigal Electromotive.
It's this big German conglomerate
right into everything.
It turns out it's the same company
that owns Fring's chicken joints.
Sounds like a real shot
in the dark there.
I mean, you said it yourself.
If this Madrigal, is it?
If this is such a big conglomerate...
...then, you know, they must own
all kinds of businesses.
No, it just -
It just sounds kind of thin.
Well, look at you. You lose your hair,
go on a couple stakeouts...
...all of a sudden you're, what, Kojak?
I'm just saying.
Now, the chicken farm, however,
boy, that place seems ripe...
...for some kind
of clandestine activities.
I just don't want us to miss anything,
you know?
You wanna talk
about clandestine activities?
Madrigal Electromotive
also owns a subsidiary...
...that manufactures this
state-of-the-art air filtration system.
And none other than Gale Boetticher
took delivery of one of these systems.
A chemist who was in possession
of hand-drawn plans...
...for a meth super-lab and was visited
by none other than Gus Fring...
...just days before he was capped
in the face, okay?
This shit is starting to feel like -
Like Three Days Of The Condor,
you know?
Anyway, an industrial laundry would be
one hell of a place to hide a meth lab.
There it is right up there.
Just turn in there.
Well, slow down.
You gotta turn in there, Walt.
- What are you doing? You missed it.
- Sorry.
It looked like a dirt road.
I thought you meant further up.
Just- Just bang a U-ie over here.
Hits the spot. Thanks, guys.
I said to Mom "ice cream,"
but she was like:
"It tastes the same and it's healthier."
So sorry.
I tried.
Frozen yogurt does taste the same.
Tastes exactly the same.
I feel, like, sorry for your taste buds.
- Weigh in here, Uncle Hank.
- Hey, it's free food.
Free food always tastes good.
Free drinks even better.
Hey, hon.
Can you handle another visitor?
Mr. Magoo. Yeah, sure.
Hey, watch out.
- Don't run into any walls or anything.
- Okay.
Hey, Dad.
Hey, son.
So how you feeling, Hank?
It feels like one of those cones
they put on dogs...
- ...so they don't lick their own balls.
- Nice. Thank you. Stay classy.
Anyway, hanging in there.
Glad you stopped by.
Listen, I'm sorry about all this.
I mean,
that guy just came out of nowhere.
Yeah, actually, he didn't.
I saw him coming a mile away.
Hey, just mark it down
as a brain fart...
...and be thankful no one got killed.
Well, I'll tell you one thing.
Your Hardy Boys routine is over.
No more asking him
to drive you on stakeouts.
It's too dangerous. You hear me?
- I'll do it.
- No, you won't.
No, Marie's right.
It was a bit short-sighted of me.
- That's why I caved.
- Caved?
Yeah, I broke down.
I ordered me a gimp-mobile.
I wish you would stop calling it that.
What do you mean?
Like a handi-van with a lift?
No, no, it's a regular Tahoe.
It's got hand controls. I ordered it.
Should be here in about a week.
I don't expect to be in it long...
...but gotta get around on my own. Stop
being such a damn burden to everyone.
Sorry. Car wash business.
Hey, it's me. Can you talk?
- I can listen.
- Fair enough.
He doesn't own a gun,
at least not one that he bought legally.
Nor does his home security system
have any panic button arrangement.
So way I see it, we're good to go.
If this is still how you want to handle it.
Like I said, I don't want anyone hurt.
All I want
is for him to write a cheque.
Yeah. It's gonna be fine.
I've got my A-team on it.
- Can I help you?
- Yeah, thanks.
What-? You just can't -
- What's this about?
- I'll tell you what this is about.
This is about you and me
doing our best to keep Huell happy.
- Huell? Who's Huell?
- This is Huell.
- Huell, you happy?
- Reasonably.
What would make you unhappy?
This motherfucker
not doing what he's told.
If you were unhappy,
Mr. Beneke wouldn't care for that?
I'm gonna say no.
Well, there you have it.
Let's go find your chequebook. Ready?
Here we go. All right?
We're walking, we're swinging our feet.
There you go. Very nice.
Beautiful place you have here.
This way. So the amount's
gonna be for $617,226 -
- I don't have that kind of money.
- Hold that thought.
Forgot to mention we know exactly how
much money is in your account, okay?
Understand? You still want to say
that stuff from before? Maybe not.
So $617,226 and 31 cents...
...made payable
to the Internal Revenue Service.
What?
Wait, this is...?
- Skyler? Skyler White sent you?
- It doesn't matter.
For now, all you have to do
is worry about that.
My God, this is a misunderstanding.
Skyler is a dear friend of mine,
all right?
Let me call her. We'll...
No, you're misunderstanding,
Mr. Beneke. Phone call time is over.
- Cheque writing time.
- Skyler would never do this to me.
Sit down and write!
There you go.
Six hundred-seventeen thousand,
two-hundred-twenty-six dollars...
...and thirty-one...
Yeah, right.
You got it.
Huell, you happy?
Huell's happy.
All right. Everything else
has been filled out for you.
All's we need...
...is a signature...
...right there.
Great.
Hard part is over.
Here's what happens next.
Huell is gonna hang here with you.
I'm gonna make sure I get this down
to UPS before 5:00.
Way back,
I'm gonna grab some sandwiches.
The three of us can hang out
and play cards or watch TV...
...for the next couple
of days until the cheque clears.
Painless, right?
Unless you don't have cable...
...in which case it's gonna suck, so...
Does the laundry have to be dirty?
Nope.
Someone cooked here.
You've been out of commission
four days.
You think we're gonna shut down
the whole operation just for you?
Who cooked? Who was here?
I don't know how you're doing the flips.
Tell me.
Keep cool.
Oh, I'm gonna get you.
Jump.
You're pressing buttons,
and it makes you do magical stuff.
- No.
- Yes. Cheater.
- Hey.
- Who's winning?
- I am.
- Go on. Got you. Look at you.
- Look at -
- Yeah.
- A hundred and one back flips, I did.
- Oh, you. Hey, keep it going.
- Hey, hey, hey.
- Relax.
- You're in trouble.
- Good luck.
Mama is in the house.
Jesse.
- What do you want? I'm busy.
- We need to talk.
I got nothing to say to you, man.
Jesse, please. I'm sorry.
Just one minute. That's all I ask.
Get the hell out of my house.
Come on. Come on.
Hey. Just give me one minute.
Let me just explain. Okay. Okay.
Let me -
All right. All right.
Okay, okay. All right, I'm sorry.
I know that you have been cooking
without me.
That's right. So what?
So what?
Isn't it obvious to you
what Gus is planning?
He's going to use you to replace me.
He doesn't think
you need me anymore.
Jesse. Jesse, if you agree...
...to replace me...
...he will kill me.
You brought your brother-in-law to our
lab. What the hell is wrong with you?
- That's not my fault, Jesse.
- Get off.
You've got to help me. Please.
The last time I asked for your help,
you said:
"I hope you end up buried in a barrel
in the Mexican desert."
You are done.
Fired.
Do not show your face
at the laundry again.
Stay away from Pinkman.
Do not go near him.
Ever.
Are you listening to me?
Or else you'll do what?
What did you say?
Stay away from Pinkman...
...or else you'll do...
...what?
Kill me?
If you could kill me...
...I'd already be dead.
But you can't.
You can't kill me...
...because Jesse wouldn't cook for you
if you did.
That's it, isn't it?
No matter how hard you try...
...to turn him against me...
...to screw with his head...
...so that he would hate my guts...
...and he still won't let you do it.
For now.
But he'll come around.
In the meantime, there's the matter
of your brother-in-law.
He is a problem you promised
to resolve.
You have failed.
Now it's left to me to deal with him.
You can't -
If you try to interfere...
...this becomes
a much simpler matter.
I will kill your wife.
I will kill your son.
I will kill your infant daughter.
Great. Perfect. You know, this is just...
I told her you were my A-team.
It was an act of God.
Ain't no accounting
for no act of God.
Cheque is in the mail, at least.
"Hello, Mrs. White.
The good news is the IRS
has been paid off. The bad news is..."
Jesus!
Well, here goes nothing.
- Hey! Hey!
- Slow down.
- What the-?
- Saul.
- How did you hear?
- What? Hear what?
Guys, go, go, go. Scram.
- What the hell happened to you?
- Saul. Saul.
This man that we spoke of before.
This person that you said
could disappear me.
- Give me a new life.
- Yeah.
- Make sure I'm never found.
Yeah, I need him, Saul.
Gus is gonna murder
my whole family.
Christ.
I need this man now.
- Saul. Now, Saul!
- Yeah, yeah.
There's no coming back. You're gonna
get new Socials, new identities.
You can't contact your friends
or relatives ever again.
- All right. I understand.
- How are you gonna sell this...
- ...to that wife of yours and your son?
- I have got no choice.
You're wanted by scary individuals,
not to mention the law.
You're high-risk. You'll need
the deluxe service. It'll cost you.
How much?
Last quote I got on the deluxe
was 125 grand.
But you got four people.
It'll be at least half a million.
- He accepts cash only.
- I've got the money.
- Please!
- Here.
Okay.
This is a vacuum cleaner
repair company.
Did you expect Haji's Quick-Vanish?
I don't even know his name.
You just call and leave a message.
You tell them
that you need a new dust filter...
...for a Hoover MaxExtract
Pressure Pro, Model 60.
I wrote it right on there.
He'll call you back.
Okay, fine. How long does it take
for him to arrange?
The guy works fast. That's the game.
You gotta have your family packed
and ready before you make the call.
He'll tell you where to meet,
he'll put you up in a safe house.
You gotta bring money. He doesn't
lift a finger unless he's paid.
Okay.
- Saul.
- Can't say it's been a pleasure -
I need you to do one more thing
for me.
You need you to call the DEA.
You need to tell them Gus
has a hit out on Hank.
- You have to do it for me.
- I gotta go on living here.
- I'm way too comfortable in my -
- Just call anonymously.
- You call anonymously!
- I can't!
I'm practically in the DEA family.
I go to their Christmas parties.
They know me. They know my voice.
They'll know me.
Please, you gotta do it for me.
- Please. Please.
- No.
My brother-in-law doesn't deserve
to die because of this.
There's no way I'm mentioning Gus.
- Okay.
- The most I'll go -
I'll say it's the cartel.
They're back to finish the job.
You say whatever you have to say.
You just give me an hour to...
I need to collect my wife and kids.
Okay?
Give me an hour and then you make
the phone call. Don't forget. Please.
Yeah.
Thank you, Saul.
No, no, no.
Where's the rest?
That's not enough.
- Walt?
- Down here!
Walt, what did that phone call mean?
Where is it?
Where's the rest?
The money, Skyler.
Where is the rest?
Skyler, where is the money?!
I gave it to Ted.
What?
- You did what?
- Walt, I had to.
For us, for the family.
I swear, Walt -
You gave our money to Beneke?
Walt, please.
Please just hear me out. Please.
Walt.
Hi, you've reached the White family.
Please leave a message.
Skyler.
It's happening again.
The DEA called, they got some tip
from an informant.
The cartel, they want to kill Hank.
Oh, God.
They're sending agents
to our house right now to guard us.
Oh, God.
When is this going to end?
Marie, I'm here.
I'm here.
Tell me exactly what happened.