Subs collected, corrected and if necessary re-synced by Tronar for
"Breaking Bad Season 1, 2, 3, 4 & 5 + Extras BDRip DVDRip HDTV TSV"
Are you okay?
- You are a lifesaver.
- Yeah, man.
- We can't thank you enough.
- No, hey, mad props.
I could have sworn the guy said south.
But then all of a sudden
we're off the main road.
I'm trying to read the map while
driving, a bonehead maneuver.
And then all of a sudden, bam,
we're in that ditch.
Yeah, bam. I'm like,
"What the hell?" You know?
Yes. Oh, yes, and my coffee mug.
Of coffee? My mug of coffee.
It spills all over my pants, I mean...
Just a nightmare.
There's your Sony GPS,
I mean, for real.
Let's just...
Like I said,
we couldn't be more grateful.
Can't we just dump them here?
What, and somebody finds them?
Then what?
People have seen us.
Hey, you're gonna flood it, man.
I'm not gonna flood it.
She's not gonna flood, all right?
We're just gonna stay positive, right?
We're gonna clean up this mess.
And you, start.
Goddamn it. See, you flooded it.
All right.
All right. You know what?
The RV is going to start now.
The RV is going to start right now.
It's gonna start.
We're gonna drive it to your house.
- My house?
- Your house.
We're gonna drive it over there
and park it overnight.
- And then tomorrow...
- Man, not my house.
Shut up. Shut up.
After we finish
cleaning up this mess...
...we will go our separate ways.
Our paths will never cross.
And we will tell this to no one.
Understood?
Oh, what, I can talk now?
Fine. That goes double for me.
Okay. Okay.
Be good to me.
Yes!
Yes. Okay. Okay.
Thank you.
Oh, shit.
Walt?
You coming out?
Yeah, absolutely.
We've got looky-loos
in both directions, Dan.
Better plan on being late
if you're going to work.
This is Lisa in the Skycopter, we'll have
more Albuquerque traffic on the hour.
Hey, you wanna hear
something funny?
We had a faculty meeting
last Thursday...
...and the topic was
senior-class photos...
...and how we had instituted
a new rule last year...
...that seniors are allowed
to have photos taken...
...by a photographer of their choice.
You know, not necessarily
the photographer...
...that the school hires, right? So...
So anyway,
some of the senior girls...
...were going to that Glamor Shots
place to have their photos taken.
And now they're bringing us
all these photos...
...and Joan Everman...
You know Joan.
- Suddenly has to go through
all the photos...
...and turn them down
because they show cleavage.
Did you get enough
pancakes, sweetie?
Yeah. I'm good.
Okay.
You know, even the
small-busted girls have cleavage.
Apparently there's some new type of
brassiere or something.
The Wonderbra.
It's the Wonderbra.
Yeah?
Okay.
Hey there. You've reached Walt,
Skyler and Walter Jr.
We can't come to the phone right now,
so please leave us a message.
Hello, Mr. White.
This is AT& T calling.
Are you happy with your current
long-distance service?
Because if you're not,
I would definitely really, really love...
...to talk to you
as soon as possible about...
Hello, this is Walter White speaking.
You said he was
practically dead, okay?
You said he would die any minute.
Listen, I am having breakfast
with my family right now...
...and I really don't appreciate
these sales calls.
Well, too bad, man,
because guess what.
He's still not dead.
I went and put my ear to the RV.
I can hear him, like,
rolling around in there, all right?
I think he's awake, man.
I think he's trying to get loose.
Where the hell are you?
I'm freaking out here.
- Calm down, damn it.
- You gonna help me clean this up?
- We got loose ends here.
- Calm down.
I will be there after school.
After school. Are you shitting me?
Ditch it, man. Call in sick.
Listen, that is just
not gonna work for me.
I'm not interested in that at all.
And I would appreciate it
if you don't call here anymore.
Damn. They're so annoying,
those people.
- You have a good day, sweetie.
- Okay, Mom. You too.
Bye, honey.
- Drive safe.
- Okay.
Yo, yo, yo, 1, 4, 8, 3 to the 3
to the 6 to the 9, representing the ABQ.
What up, beyotch?
Leave it at the tone.
So the term "chiral"...
...derives from the
Greek word "hand."
Now, the concept here being that just
as your left hand and your right hand...
...are mirror images of one another,
right, identical and yet opposite...
...well, so, too,
organic compounds can exist...
...as mirror-image forms
of one another...
...all the way down
at the molecular level.
But although they may
look the same...
...they don't always behave the same.
For instance...
For instance.
I'm sorry. For instance...
Thalidomide.
The right-handed isomer
of the drug thalidomide...
...is a perfectly fine, good medicine...
...to give to a pregnant woman
to prevent morning sickness.
But make the mistake of giving
that same pregnant woman...
...the left-handed isomer
of the drug thalidomide...
...and her child will be born
with horrible birth defects.
Which is precisely what happened
in the 1950s.
So chiral, chirality,
mirrored images, right?
Active, inactive, good, bad.
So.
- Yes, Ben.
- Is this gonna be on the murder?
What?
Is this gonna be on the midterm?
Chirality on the midterm?
No, no. Well, maybe.
Maybe. Yes, you know...
But prepare for it to be on the midterm.
Can't hurt to know it, right? So...
Knowledge is power.
Oh, no. Oh, no, no. No.
Not good. Not good, not good.
What the...?
Hey. Hey. Hey, you.
Hey, listen, you.
No, no, no!
Oh, God.
Okay.
MILFs?
The hell is a MILF?
Now what?
Lock the other one out in the RV.
He's:
- You're sure?
- Yes.
- You're positive?
- You know what?
- Feel free to go check.
- Good idea. Maybe I should...
...before he, too, wanders off
down the street.
- Okay, you know what? I am sick...
- All right.
Just...
The one downstairs,
tell me about him.
Oh, come on. Anything. Something.
Start with his name, at least.
Krazy-8.
What the hell does that even mean?
I don't know, man, okay? It means,
like, Krazy-8, okay? I don't know.
So you work with him regularly.
No, not him so much.
- His cousin, mainly.
- Who's his cousin?
- The guy out in the RV.
- All right, all right, all right.
Krazy-8's one level higher.
One level higher.
Yeah, you know.
Not, like, street level. Higher.
You know how there's, like,
a Starbucks on every corner?
Krazy-8 is like the dude that sells
Starbucks' beans.
Okay, so he's a distributor.
Okay, so is he? I mean, is?
In other words,
what is his reputation for violence?
Well, he did try to kill us both
yesterday, so there's that.
Look, what I'm trying to say
is that he's a distributor, right?
He's a businessman.
He's a man of business.
It would therefore
seem to follow that he is...
...capable of acting out of
mutual self-interest, yes?
What?
Do you think he is capable
of listening to reason?
What kind of reason? You mean,
"Dear Krazy-8, hey, listen...
...if I let you go, you promise not to
come back and waste my entire family?
No Colombian neckties?"
That kind of reason?
No, man, I can't say as I have high
fucking hopes where that's concerned.
What was that?
What was what?
We didn't tie him up.
- Why the hell didn't we tie him up?
- Oh, God.
- Because he was out cold.
- Yeah, but what if he's faking it?
You know, like, if it was me,
I'd be all faking being knocked out, yo.
And then, when the coast is clear,
I'd be up looking for weapons and shit.
Ready to pounce.
No, see. Now, if it was me...
...and I couldn't find
a decent enough weapon...
...I would just lie back down
and bide my time.
So now what do we do?
You keep asking me that
like you think I have some answer.
- Well, you gotta do something.
- We.
We have got to do something,
and I am open to suggestions.
Man, okay,
this whole thing was your deal.
Don't you dare put that on me.
You brought those guys out there.
This is your responsibility.
Like I came to you,
begging to cook meth.
"Oh, hey, nerdiest old dude I know,
you wanna come cook crystal?" Please.
I'd ask my diaper-wearing granny...
...but her wheelchair wouldn't fit
in the RV.
What about the phosphate gas?
Phosphine gas. What about it?
I mean, do you think
it still might kill him?
You know, with, like,
a delayed reaction or something?
I don't know.
- You're supposed to be a scientist.
- Look.
This isn't even the issue
that demands immediate attention.
We have got a body in that RV.
And it's getting warmer outside.
Understand?
And we have got to
do something about that soon.
And in a way that
no one will ever find it.
Now, that last part
is very, very important.
Therefore, it seems to me...
...that our best course of action
would be chemical disincorporation.
Dissolving in strong acid.
Oh, man, that's messed up.
I mean, you're not serious.
You serious?
Well, who's gonna do that?
And don't look at me.
I guess we'll both do it together.
No, Mr. White, okay,
I'm not good with dead bodies.
Look, we are in this fifty-fifty. Okay?
I guess the only other fair way
to go about this would be...
...that one of us deals with
the body situation...
...while the other one of us deals with
the Krazy-8 situation.
In a scenario like this,
I don't suppose it is bad form...
...to just flip a coin.
- Heads or tails?
- No, I'll do the body in the acid, okay?
Heads or tails?
Heads. Heads.
Best two out of three?
Yo, yo, yo, 1, 4, 8, 3 to the 3
to the 6 to the 9, representing the ABQ.
What up, beyotch?
Leave it at the tone.
Hey, Mr. White, it's me. Pick up.
I got a container question.
Hello, Mr. White.
Pick up the phone, man.
- Yes.
- Yo, what kind of plastic, man?
Polyethylene.
How the hell am I
supposed to know that?
Because I told you.
Look, just look at the bottom
for a triangle...
...stamped LDPE.
It should be molded into the plastic.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, LDPE.
Right on, got it.
I don't know, man.
This feels kind of flimsy.
Any decent acid's
gonna eat right through this.
- Not hydrofluoric.
- Why not?
Look, you skipped, clowned around...
...or otherwise jerked off
through every lecture I ever gave.
As far as I'm concerned,
your chemistry education is over.
Oh, okay, be a dick about it. Jesus.
So, hey, have you done the thing?
Yeah, I'm working up to it.
You know what?
I bet he doesn't even wake up.
You know, not even if you took him
to the hospital right now.
Now, if it was me,
I would just try and think of it...
...like I was doing him a favour.
I need a check approval
on checkstand eight.
Approval on checkstand eight, please.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Who's there?
What, you fucking break in?
Show me who's there.
Yeah. I see you.
What you gonna do?
Hey.
Hey...!
I need water.
Hey, hello.
Bring me some water, would you?
Please.
You don't like the crust?
Where's my cousin Emilio?
He dead?
Oh, I'm a coward.
Hey, Mr. White. Hey, Mr. White?
Oh, fuck.
Are you smoking weed? Oh, my God.
Wait a minute, is that my weed?
What the hell, man? Make yourself
at home, why don't you?
- So, what'd you end up buying?
- Nothing.
No store in town sells a plastic bin
big enough for a body.
I don't suppose
you could buy two bins?
And just:
Legs in one, torso in the other?
Oh, God.
I don't suppose
you could kiss my ass?
So...
...how'd it go?
- You didn't do it?
- Not yet.
Oh, God.
- Oh, damn. I gotta go.
- Hey, hey.
What? No, no, no. Come back here.
- Sorry. I'll do it tomorrow, I promise.
- Tomorrow.
I've got a doctor's appointment.
I gotta go.
Look, stay away from him.
He's awake.
Hey, man, we flipped a coin.
We flipped a coin.
We're good?
We're very good.
We're excellent, I'd say.
Oh, would you look at that face?
Smile, peanut.
So who's up for knowing?
It's...
Yeah.
- Girl.
- Girl?
- You sure?
- Pretty sure.
Oh, God. Can I tell you,
that's exactly what I was hoping.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
You remember you said that
when she's 16 and starts dating.
Looking fabulous. Let me see
if they're done with the blood sugar...
...then we'll get you out of here.
I'll be right back.
Who's Jesse Pinkman?
- Jesse?
- Jesse Pinkman.
He called just this morning.
- Walt, please don't deny it.
- Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It says on his MyShout page
he attended Wynne.
- Was he one of your students?
- Yeah.
He was nobody.
Who is he to you? Why is he calling?
What is this big secret...
...you seem to be discussing
with some druggie burnout?
You don't come home last night until 2
in the morning. You don't tell me...
...where you've been. You spent
the entire night in the bathroom, Walt.
Tell me what's going on with you.
Don't you think you owe me that?
Who is this Jesse Pinkman to you?
He sells me pot.
- He sells you pot?
- Marijuana, yeah.
Not a lot. I mean, I don't know.
I kind of like it.
Are you out of your mind?
What are you, like, 16 years old?
Your brother-in-law is a DEA agent.
What is wrong with you?
Look, Skyler...
...I just haven't
quite been myself lately.
- Yeah. No shit. Thanks for noticing.
- I haven't been myself lately...
...but I love you.
Nothing about that has changed.
Nothing ever will.
So right now, what I need...
...is for you to climb down
out of my ass.
Can you do that?
Will you do that for me, honey?
Will you please, just once,
get off my ass?
You know.
I'd appreciate it. I really would.
Stop.
Stop in 15 minutes.
Your face is too sharp.
Powder. Powder!
Take a powder, go on.
Nice. Beautiful talcum powder.
Lucky you, number eight.
Just meat,
it's all just a bunch of meat.
Oh, Jesus.
You're cool, you're cool.
You're all good, you're all...
You're all good. You know it.
It's fine. It's just a bunch of meat.
Come on. You're good.
Excuse me.
Excuse me. You. Yes, you.
May I talk to you?
Hey, hey, hey.
This is private property.
- Just a minute. I wanna talk to you.
- No, not interested.
- Come on.
- Hey, don't touch me. Do not touch me.
All right. Look, not touching.
Not touching.
Look, lady, whatever you're selling,
I ain't buying, yo.
Well, my name is Skyler White, yo.
My husband is Walter White, yo.
He told me everything.
- Seriously?
- That's right.
And just so you know,
my brother-in-law is a DEA agent...
...and I will not hesitate to call him.
Not if I have to. Understood?
This is your one and only warning.
Do not sell marijuana to my husband.
- Okay.
- I mean it. Don't call our house again.
You stay away from him,
or you will be one sorry individual.
- You get me?
- I think so, yeah.
No more marijuana. I can dig it.
You can dig it. Wonderful.
Not that it's any of my business,
but you might wanna consider...
...a different line of work.
Okay.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Let's go to your house, you know.
Makes perfect sense. Let's
completely screw up your house...
...so you never wanna spend another
night in it. Sure. You know, why not?
Yeah, and how's about
I send over my psycho-bitch wife...
...to, you know, break your balls
and threaten you?
God, that would be hilarious,
you know.
And then, you know,
the killer in the basement...
...the one who's completely
my responsibility...
...hell, let's just
let him live down there.
Just, I don't know, make sure
to feed him, like, three times a day.
Sure, why not? It's been really amazing.
Thank you so much for the opportunity.
I always dreamt about, I don't know,
melting bodies.
You got a brother
in the goddamn DEA?
- What?
- You said you were...
...just doing some ride-along. Yes or
no, do you have a brother in the DEA?
- He's a brother-in-law.
- Well, there's a load off my mind.
Where did you hear that?
Your freaking wife told me
when she was here all up in my shit.
Yeah, that's right.
She almost caught me moving Emilio.
Good job on
wearing the pants in the family.
And why'd you go and tell her
I was selling you weed?
Because somehow
it seemed preferable...
...to admitting that I cook crystal meth
and killed a man.
Is that what I think it is?
Yeah. Yeah, it is. I smoked a bowl.
So what? My house, my rules.
Hey, no, no.
Don't give me that, okay?
I held up my end. I already took care of
Emilio. You're still diddling around...
- ...trying to get your nut up.
- Yeah, well, boo-hoo.
I have the truly awful job here.
You wanna talk awful?
You wanna go there?
Try dragging 200 pounds of stink
up a flight of stairs.
I barely got him in the bathtub.
Bathtub, what?
What do you mean, bathtub?
Another thing. Why you got me
running around town...
...trying to find
some stupid piece of plastic...
...when I have a perfectly good tub
I can use?
Oh, God.
Hey. Hey.
I'm sorry, what were you asking me?
Oh, yes.
That stupid plastic container
I asked you to buy.
You see, hydrofluoric acid
won't eat through plastic.
It will, however, dissolve metal,
rock, glass, ceramic.
So there's that.
Okay, here we go.
Okay.
Here I go.
Subs collected, corrected and if necessary re-synced by Tronar for
"Breaking Bad Season 1, 2, 3, 4 & 5 + Extras BDRip DVDRip HDTV TSV"