Subs collected, corrected and if necessary re-synced by Tronar for
"Breaking Bad Season 1, 2, 3, 4 & 5 + Extras BDRip DVDRip HDTV TSV"
All right, everybody. Listen up.
Tuco Salamanca.
For those of you who were
not with us this morning
we raided his headquarters.
Also his last-known address.
Even the little den of iniquity
he keeps for his meth-hag girlfriend.
We netted a bunch
of his lieutenants.
The big man himself
smelled us coming.
So study the face.
Study the file.
Get a big old raging hard-on
at the idea of catching
this piece of shit.
My apologies
to the H.R. department.
Grow tumescent with anticipation.
All right.
On the hit parade, 1998.
Reputed to have whacked
one "Dog" Paulson
back when our homegrown bandidos
were wresting the crank trade
away from the So Cal biker gangs.
Also, we're pretty sure
he knifed a Mexican national in '03.
And for my money, seeing how
he customarily deals with rivals,
I'd say he is a prime suspect
in the disappearance
of our dearly missed Krazy-8.
Hats over your heart
for that dirtball.
We hauled Tuco in
for questioning on that
but as usual,
we couldn't make it stick.
Yeah, he runs a tight ship.
Smug bastard.
And even worse, El Paso says he's
got some kind of cartel connection.
Yeah, yeah. I know it's... We all
know what's going on down there.
We sure as hell don't want it
going on up here,
which brings us to the good news.
We finally got some actual,
honest-to-God evidence.
- This is one of Tuco's henchmen.
- No-Doze.
Found him tucked in the junkyard
along with Tuco's own brother-in-law,
a.k.a. Gonzo.
Gonzo, this rocket scientist,
was moving No-Doze's body...
Either hiding it there or pulling it out.
We're still not sure.
...when he got his arm crushed clean off.
Heh, heh.
Anyone wanna see the photos, they'
re on my website. Hilarious.
Anyway. The upshot is
we got us a nice, big, juicy,
bloody fingerprint
which belongs to Señor Tuco.
Christmas came early
to the Schrader household.
That is,
provided we find this guy.
So to all present, I ask you,
you wanna find this guy?
- Yes.
What the hell was that? Jesus.
Wanna try that again?
- Do you wanna find this guy?
- Yes!
- Are we going to find this guy?
- Louder, damn it!
- Yes!
Give me a "hell, yeah!"
Hell, yeah!
- Hell, yeah!
Hell, yeah. Hell, yeah, Hell, yeah.
They ain't gonna find him.
Guy is in México by now.
Appearances, Gomey. Tsk, tsk.
It's all about appearances.
Listen, I gotta take
some personal time.
Now, in the middle of a manhunt?
Skyler called last night.
It's Walt. He's missing.
Just disappeared from the house,
and no one's heard from him since.
Damn. You don't think he...?
Holler if you need me.
All right. Thanks a lot, man.
Appreciate that.
- This is the most recent photo.
- We haven't taken many lately, so...
But that's what
he looks like now.
Without the hair.
Hey, it's me.
Hey, Tim. Really appreciate
you sparing us your day off.
No worries.
Happy to help.
Yeah, this is helpful.
Good.
What about height and weight?
Five eleven,
most recently, about 170.
One sixty-five.
That's what I weigh.
I guess he weighs a little less.
That's fine. That's close enough.
Good.
What about other
distinguishing features?
Tattoos or moles or scars?
Anything that might help us.
Tattoos? No. Not really. No.
That's fine.
Is that the list of medications?
Yes.
I wrote them all down.
And there's no drug interactions.
None that are listed.
I called his doctor, so, no.
Has he been depressed?
He's, um, been withdrawn lately.
A little withdrawn.
Yeah.
Last night, he was, uh, agitated.
Agitated?
Yeah. When he came home last
night, he was agitated, upset.
Upset in general?
Or upset because
of something particular?
Um...
When I asked him what
was wrong, he said:
"I don't know where to begin."
Then he just walked out of the
room... Out of the bathroom.
I was in the tub,
I was taking a bath.
...and when I came out about
10 minutes later, he was gone.
Nothing else missing?
His keys, wallet, cell phone.
Just what was on him.
But... What about the phone call?
Uh... I'm looking into it.
What phone call?
Walt's cell phone rang.
He pulled it out, looked at
it, and didn't answer it.
But then, a short time after,
he wandered out of the bathroom.
I mean,
couldn't that be, uh,
important, right?
Anything else you can think of?
Anything else. Um...
No. I called
the credit card providers,
and there's no report
of any recent activity.
I... Let's see. I checked with
every hospital within 50 miles.
Every police station.
Every morgue.
So, no, I really don't...
I don't have anything else.
I was actually hoping
that you had something else,
being that you're the expert.
I'm sorry.
No worries.
I think this is
good enough to start.
Gives us plenty to work on.
Mrs. White.
Thank you.
Walter.
So that cell-phone call she's
talking about? I ran it.
And?
Never happened.
No record of it.
Second cell phone.
Yeah. I'm thinking.
I understand.
Out.
Get away from me!
Settle down, bitch.
- You gonna shoot me, huh?
- Shoot me in here!
I hope I bleed like a mother too!
That way, you have to clean it up!
It's your ride, retard.
I ain't gotta clean jack.
Now get out.
Get up.
Oh, my God.
Don't do this, Tuco.
No more posters?
Walter Jr.'s making more.
Thank you, Marie.
I don't think he'll hurt himself.
I mean, he just doesn't
strike me as the type.
He'll turn up.
Okay, the whole tiara thing,
- I just find it bewildering that...
- Marie.
- You didn't believe that...
Not now.
Empty your pockets.
Thought your name was Heisenberg,
"Walter Hartwell White."
Heisenberg is kind of
a pseudonym.
You know, a business name.
Yeah.
I like doing business
with a family man.
There's always
a lot of collateral.
Answer me one thing.
Can I trust you?
Yes. Yes, absolutely.
Sit down.
DEA...
hit my place of business
this morning.
About a hundred cops
looking for me.
You two haven't
been talking, right?
No.
Picked up my whole crew,
top to bottom.
Everybody except Gonzo.
That's weird, right?
I mean, don't you think
that that's weird?
It's weird. Yes.
Unusual.
Last two days, I couldn't
get Gonzo on the phone.
He's been acting all pouty
on account of No-Doze.
Explain to me.
How is it my fault that that little
bitch did not know his place?
I saw this coming.
I can see the future, you know?
It's this gift that I have
deep inside my head.
I knew last night they were
gonna come try and bust me.
Gonzo.
He went and snitched to the cops!
That lousy son of a bitch!
I trusted him like a brother!
I was good to him! I was good!
I see Gonzo, I'm gonna gut
him, I'm gonna skin him,
and I'm gonna stuff his hide
for a heavy bag,
and every time I hit him, it's going
to be like a lesson to myself!
You never, never trust the
people that you love!
So you plan to ice Gonzo,
like, future tense?
What?
You're saying, Tuco...
You're saying that Gonzo
is currently operating
as a police informant
as far as you know?
I'm very sorry to hear that.
That's disappointing.
Yeah.
- I'd waste him too, yo.
- Shut up.
Okay.
They're out there
looking for me right now.
They got ghetto birds
and black ops.
I need to get high. Oh, fu...
I need to get good and high.
What's with this gak?
It smells like headcheese.
No, it's, uh... it's killer.
Yeah, seriously.
So I was thinking last night.
I came up with this great idea.
México.
Mexico?
Ha, ha. We'll disappear
way out in the jungle.
We'll set you up in a superlab.
We'll do nothing but cook 24/7.
And no Federales
are gonna mess with us
because I got my people there.
Connections.
We're going to make beaucoup
bucks, Heisenberg, huh?
Tuco, I...
I have a wife and family.
So what?
You'll get another one.
I don't want you to take this
the wrong way, but I can't just
uproot my life like that.
Yeah, man.
I mean, me neither.
Who's talking to you?
You need me, man,
because I cooked that scante
in your hands.
Yeah.
I'll tell you something, yo.
You never tried nothing like it.
Stink or no stink,
one bump,
you'll be flying high for days.
It's a new product him
and I've been working up.
Careful when you hit it.
It kicks like a 12 gauge
when it comes on.
It's got a secret ingredient.
What secret ingredient?
Chili powder.
I hate chili powder.
This blue magic, this is money.
You keep cooking this,
Heisenberg.
We're gonna rewrite
history with this.
All right. Time to clean the
menudo out from between your ears.
No, no, no. No,
I need him, Tuco.
I need him very, very badly.
He's my partner.
And if he doesn't go,
I don't go.
I'll tell you this. My cousins
are driving up here right now
to smuggle us back down, and
they're gonna be here by sunset
and you're gonna be
on that truck,
or you're gonna be dead!
And you...
You better hope they got room
in the trunk.
Where are you going?
Louis is taking me
to the train station.
We'll put these up.
No, no, honey. No, I'll do it.
He wants to help, let him help.
I mean, how long has it
been since you've slept?
Yeah, she's right, Sky. Why
don't you lay down a while?
For Christ sake,
you got a bun in the oven.
I got my cell if you need me.
- Okay?
- Okay.
- Bye, sweetie. I'll see you later.
- All right. Bye.
Actually, I think the very fact
they haven't found him yet
bodes well.
Well, I mean, if he...
You know.
Somebody would've
smelled something by now.
There's got to be something.
Some detail that
we haven't picked up on.
What about the second cell phone?
Ah, Jesus.
What? We can't just ignore
a potential clue, Hank.
Okay.
What are you talking about?
Uh, the call you said Walt got
before he disappeared?
There's no record of it
with the phone company.
No incoming, no dropped
calls, nothing.
But his phone rang.
I heard it.
Um, all right. Well, then if that's the
case, he must have a second phone.
Wh... Why? What sense
would there be in that?
Yeah. All right. Okay.
I'm not here to argue with you.
No, Hank. You can't just bring up
secret cell phone and then drop it.
What does it mean?
I don't know, Sky.
What do you want me to say?
It means Walt has a secret.
Everyone's got one from somebody,
big or little.
Okay. Oh, wow. Everyone. Okay.
Skyler, come on.
He kept cancer
from you for weeks.
Okay, then, let's assume
there's a second cell phone.
So what?
What, is he having an affair?
Walt? Please.
What about the marijuana?
He's not on pot anymore.
Says who? Him?
Chemotherapy and
marijuana go together
like apple pie and Chevrolet.
Maybe he's addicted to the pot
and he owes his drug
dealer a lot of money.
Marie, you don't get
hooked on pot like that.
How do you know? You didn't even
know he had a second cell phone.
Hank, you have to question
this drug-dealer person.
He may know something.
Well, I'm telling you,
we're grasping at straws here.
Then grasp.
Excuse me, ma'am.
Hi, I'm looking for Jesse.
He around?
No. I'm afraid not.
Why?
I'm sorry. Hank Schrader.
I'm actually hoping to talk to Jesse
about my brother-in-law, Walter White.
He taught your son
chemistry in high school.
Oh, Mr. White.
Yes, I remember him.
That was a long time ago.
Yes, ma'am.
It's my understanding that he and
Jesse, they've stayed in touch.
Really?
Yeah.
Huh.
Mr. White must've seen
some potential in Jesse.
He really tried to motivate him.
He was one of the
few teachers who cared.
Yeah, Walt's that way.
He's a good man.
I'm so sorry to hear
about his illness.
Please pass along
our best wishes.
I certainly will,
as soon as he turns up.
He's missing, actually.
Just kind of walked off, or...
Anyway, which is why
I'm going around,
trying to think of anyone
who knows him, even slightly.
That's terrible.
Anything we can do to help.
Well, if you could put me
in touch with your son...
Like I said,
we're kind of desperate for leads.
Jesse's not answering either
phone number I have for him,
and no one seems to be home
at his house.
And why do you think my son
and Mr. White would be in touch?
I don't necessarily.
I just, um...
Are you with the police?
No, ma'am. Not at all.
I'm with the
Drug Enforcement Administration.
Oh, my God.
Is my son in trouble?
I have absolutely no reason
to think that, no.
Do I need to get a lawyer?
You know, you don't seem
very forthright about this,
coming here and asking
questions about my son and...
Mrs. Pinkman, I swear to you,
I'm not here on official capacity.
I do not care what your son may
or may not have done wrong.
I just wanna find
my brother-in-law.
His wife is worried sick, and
she's got a baby on the way.
I'm sorry.
I would like to help you,
but I have not seen my son
in over a month.
I don't expect to see him
anytime soon.
Well, thanks for your time.
Oh, uh...
If you could tell me
one more thing.
Is Jesse still driving the '89 Chevy
Monte Carlo, as far as you know?
If he had spent half as much
time and money on his education
as he has on that
ridiculous bouncing car...
Low rider, huh?
Gomey, hey.
No, nothing yet. Hey, listen,
do me a solid and check out
a '89 Chevy Monte Carlo
registered to a one
Jesse Pinkman.
Specifically, I wanna know
if the car's got a LoJack.
It's one of those jack-off low riders, so I'm
betting it's got a good shot that there is.
If so, can you go ahead and get
me a fix on it? Thanks, buddy.
Chili powder.
Did I not already tell you
how moronic that was?
Whatever, man.
At least I tried something.
Hey, it almost worked too.
How's about
you leaving my gun, huh?
First you boost it, then
you leave it in your house.
My gun.
How was I supposed to know you were
chauffeuring Tuco to my doorstep?
Well, at least
he wants you alive.
Hey, I don't get it.
If Tuco didn't kill Gonzo,
then who did?
I don't know.
Does it really matter?
If he finds out that Gonzo is
dead and not a police informant,
who does he automatically blame?
Us.
We need a plan.
- Think, think.
- Let's just bum-rush him, man.
You know, you crack him over
the head with something,
and I'll go for his gun.
Crack him over the head
with something?
Hey, you got the C-bomb,
man, all right?
You're as good
as checked out already.
Okay? You should be, like, all
sacrificial, jumping on a grenade, yo.
Just...
Oh, so my life is not
the priority here,
because I'm gonna be
dead soon anyway.
That's your point?
Uh, yeah.
We gotta get him to take this.
Well, he don't much like
the taste of chili P.
That much has been established.
So unless you can convince
him to booty bump...
Eat!
We got a long ride ahead of us.
Oye, tio.
La comida esta
preparada, señor.
Go on, sit. You're looking
a little weak, Heisenberg.
I don't want you to go belly up
before we get there.
Take it easy, Tio.
I will feed you.
I eat first. That's the deal.
What?
I get it, I get it, I get it.
Oh, you greedy old bastard.
I tell you, Heisenberg.
Old people.
You feed them, huh?
You put them in a really
nice crib in the country,
and yet they gotta steal
the food off your plate.
You better eat every bite of that.
What did you do that for?
God!
Ha, ha, ha. Shh.
Hey, look. Look.
There's nothing left.
What?
What do you want?
No.
Don't even tell me
that you're hungry.
Don't go there.
Are you mad-dogging them, Tio?
What, you don't like them?
One ding.
That means yes.
Tio don't like you.
Why don't you like them, Tio?
You don't trust them?
Why don't you trust them, Tio?
Tuco, come on. He's...
There clearly some dementia.
He's not lucid.
Shh.
Did they do something
to you, Tio?
Something that you don't like?
What did they do to you?
What did you do to my tio?
Nothing. Nothing.
Bullshit! My tio does not lie!
I don't know. I swear.
I don't know. I...
No, I... Maybe it was... I did change
the channel on his TV, but...
Yeah, that's it.
While you were cooking,
he was watching one of
those, um... Those telenovels
with all those ripe honeys on it.
He was really into it.
I told you not to
change the channel, man.
You know, dude needs his eye candy.
That's it.
Is that it, Tio?
Did they change your mamitas?
What are you telling me, Tio?
Huh?
Are they punking me?
Hey. No.
No, man. No.
Come here! Aah!
No.
No, no, Tuco.
Tuco, no. Tuco.
- Tuco.
- Shut up!
No. Please, no. God.
Please, no.
No, God.
I don't wanna die.
Tell me what you did, Walter!
Jesus, I don't wanna die.
No!
Tell me what you did!
We tried to poison you.
We tried to poison you,
because you're an insane,
degenerate piece of filth,
and you deserve to die.
Who's the bitch now?
Let him bleed.
The keys.
Tuco.
Oh, my God.
The cousins?
What the hell is going on?
Jesse Pinkman.
You're a hard man to find.
Oh, shit.
Easy.
Oh, my God.
Oh, God. Hank.
Who?
Hank.
What?
Oh, my God.
Stay. What are you doing?
Subs collected, corrected and if necessary re-synced by Tronar for
"Breaking Bad Season 1, 2, 3, 4 & 5 + Extras BDRip DVDRip HDTV TSV"