Son of a...
I'm not leaving.
Walt, I'm not leaving.
Oh, my God.
I can hear your cell phone ringing.
This is ridiculous. I can't...
What is going on with you?
I've left you, like, 23 messages.
- And?
We need to talk about the car wash.
Skyler,
now is not a good time for me, okay?
- Can we talk about this later?
- No, okay? We can't.
Why are you doing-?
Oh, Jesus.
- What happened?
- Nothing. I just bumped it. That's all.
Okay, I'm- I'm coming in.
Okay.
Exactly what happened?
It's complicated
and I don't wish to discuss it.
- It's none of your concern.
- Are you in danger?
Walt.
Walt, I need you to look me in the eye
and tell me right now.
- Are you in danger?
- You know what?
Let's just say that I have a hell
of a lot more on my mind right now...
...than thinking about buying
a damn car wash.
Okay?
So if you could you just -
Please.
Okay.
Okay. Then we go to the police.
- What?
- We tell them everything.
That you're a drug dealer
afraid for your safety...
...and the safety of your family
and you need help.
- What choice is there?
- What choice?
If you're in danger then it would be -
Wait, wait, stop, stop. Stop.
You keep saying that word.
"Danger. " "Danger."
- But you said -
- No, I have never used that word.
I said "complicated"
and then you flew off the handle.
Yeah, I flew off the handle
when I saw that.
Okay? Where'd that come from?
A fall in the shower?
This is just so passive-aggressive,
you know.
Passive-aggressive?
I go two days without returning
your phone calls, two days...
...and I have one minor little incident,
and now you're telling me...
...that I should turn myself
in to the police!
- A minor incident?
- Yes.
What minor little incident?
I had an argument with a coworker,
okay?
And?
I had an argument.
We were in this bar...
...and we were discussing
a particular business strategy.
And it got heated and out of control,
and he hit me. Once.
And I didn't retaliate
because he's a much older man.
And that's it.
You were in a bar fight?
Yes, Skyler. I was in a bar fight.
So you're okay?
Really?
Yes.
I'm okay.
And I think, in the end,
that it may have been a good thing...
...because we were able to clear the air
and, you know...
Mutual respect, and...
So...
Frozen peas.
- What?
- It's the best thing for the swelling.
Oh, it's not really swollen, it's just -
No peas.
You don't even have ice.
I will get peas, I will get ice.
Peas and ice, I'm writing it down.
I...
I need you to promise me...
...that if things do get dangerous -
- Skyler -
- Promise me.
Absolutely.
So...
Car wash.
Honey. Charles.
Take a look at this kitchen.
Hi there.
Can I answer any questions?
Yes. Any chance of a top off?
Oh, I think we can
help you out there.
So, what do you think?
Oh, very nice. Very open.
Oh, I agree. It flows.
Whole lot of natural light.
Michael Kilbourne.
- Tori Costner.
- It's nice to meet you.
Well, three bedrooms, one and a half
baths on just under half an acre.
There's a non-attached casita
out in back.
Permit useable as office
or guest suite.
Plank wood floors.
Central heat and air.
I see you're married.
No, divorced.
Very recent.
- Old habits.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
- But any children?
- Yes, as a matter of fact. A little boy.
Oh, how old?
He turned 4 in May. He's a Gemini.
Would love this yard.
Oh, plenty of space for a jungle gym.
And the neighbourhood preschool
is fantastic.
I think Eli is going to be
homeschooled.
- Well, great.
- Not for religious reasons.
I wanna make sure
he's getting attention.
He'll still go to summer camp
and whatnot, playdates.
- Don't want him to be socially awkward.
- Makes sense.
He tests very highly, 96 percentile.
But that whole right brain, left brain.
You want those in balance.
Oh, yeah.
You said the casita has plumbing?
I work a lot with clay,
so I need access to running water.
Well, it's pipe fitted
for a quarter bath so...
Make a perfect studio.
This could work.
Hell, that's the doctor's plan
to get her patients at ease.
If you know what I mean.
But, nurse -
Hello? I'm back.
That's okay.
- Hank?
- Yeah.
I had to go to three places
to get the moisturizer that you like.
But I got that.
And I got your Shiner Bock
and your chips.
And I couldn't resist.
The complete encyclopaedia
to fantasy football.
- Look, it has all the latest rankings.
- Marie, I said Cheetos, not Fritos.
Wait, I...
I said Cheetos, like, 10 times.
You need me to write it down?
No, and I don't need you to be mean
about it either.
Well, I'm just saying, you know,
I said Cheetos... sound.
Virtually impossible to confuse
Cheetos with Fritos, seems to me.
- Where are you going?
- I- Back to the store, I guess.
Here.
And the draft's not for two months,
so this is useless.
Can you believe it?
What?
What? This.
Well, you always said this place
could be bugged.
- Now we know.
- Yeah, well.
I don't like it.
It's a violation of the work space.
Yeah, I guess.
You wanna do something?
Do something?
Like what?
Go-karts?
Go-karts. What-?
Yeah, there's a track
down by the Coliseum.
It's pretty fun.
No, actually I have
some kind of a meeting, so...
All right, whatever.
Rain check?
Yeah. Sure.
How you doing?
- Good.
- Yeah?
You okay?
Is there anything
we should talk about?
How's your eye?
Yeah, it's fine.
Anything we should talk about?
For what it's worth...
...getting the shit kicked out of you...
...not to say you get used to it...
...but you do kind of get used to it.
Two words: nail salon.
Perfect for money laundering.
It's a high-volume business
with a discreet work force.
I mean, nobody does,
"Mister, me know nothing"...
...better than Mrs. Mookjaiaporn
and her gals.
Mr. Goodman -
"Saul," please.
Now, for the lady of the house.
Drum roll.
How about a lifetime supply...
...of French manicures
and enzyme peels?
Oh, yeah, go ahead. Pinch yourself.
We're not buying a nail salon,
Mr. Goodman.
- We're getting the car wash.
- I'm sorry.
Am I missing something here?
Didn't you already try that?
Yeah. I mean, Walt told me that you
took a run at this Bogdan character...
...and he wrestled you into submission
with his eyebrows.
Ten million,
that was the asking price, right?
Apparently, he upped it to 20.
Nice negotiating. Yeah, I mean,
hey, you bombed. It happens.
You were smart to call me. Now -
You just sit back, relax
and let a professional take over.
That's for me. Excuse me.
What do you want? I'm in a meeting.
Why didn't you think of that before?
It's not my...
I'm in a meeting.
Can Huell use your bathroom?
Huell?
Sure. The top of the stairs.
He'll be quick.
It's a stomach thing. It's...
So where were we?
- Professionalism.
- Yeah.
So if the guy won't sell, he won't sell.
I don't accept that.
I don't accept that he won't sell.
I think he just lacks the proper...
...motivation.
Motivation.
As in, "motivation" motivation? I mean,
just so we're on the same page here...
...are you saying we make him an offer
he can't refuse?
Nothing so dramatic as that, no.
Motivation.
Attitude adjustment.
This one, she's a keeper.
Well,
an audit can be highly motivating.
I know a gal at Tax and Revenue.
You give her 10 minutes,
she'll have his sky raining frogs.
No, we don't want to draw
any unwanted tax attention.
We don't want them looking at us
after Bogdan sells.
All right, how about an ICE raid?
He's got illegals working over there.
He has to.
We are not getting a bunch
of poor innocent people in trouble, no.
Yeah, and also you're gonna need them
after you take over.
Hey, how about terrorism?
"Oh, Agent Hoover, I gotta tell you...
...I've seen some real Islamic comings
and goings over there at the car wash.
Yeah, I mean, guys in turbans
pulling up in vans and stuff like that."
Saul, Bogdan is Romanian.
Okay, well,
we're just spitballing here, so...
Okay, there's always:
"You got a real nice place here.
Be a shame if something
happened to it. " That angle.
What are you talking about?
Violence?
Attitude adjustment.
Oh, no. That, no.
That is not at all what I meant.
I- We do not do that.
That's not who we are, right?
Yeah, no, no, no. She's right.
Look, do I need to state the obvious?
I mean, there's gotta be dozens
of car washes in this area.
Who says it has to be this one?
I do.
I say it has to.
Why?
I just do.
God.
Well, that clears things up.
I don't like him. Bogdan.
He was condescending to me,
rude about you, and I do not like him.
Simple as that.
Hey, nobody appreciates
a passionate woman more than I do.
But in this business -
And Walt can back me up on this.
- The number one rule
is don't take things personally.
What do you mean, rude about me?
Something along the lines
of you weren't man enough...
...to face him yourself.
- What?
- That you had to send your woman...
...to do your business for you.
Speaking as your lawyer, I'm gonna
go on record and say this is a bad idea.
- Now, I advise against -
- It's this one. It's this one.
Okay, so...
All we have to do is think
of a non-violent, unsuspicious way...
...to purchase the car wash,
that protects the innocents...
...and doesn't cost $20 million.
Don't everybody speak at once.
I like it.
Yeah.
Hi.
Can I answer any questions?
- Spoons.
- Yes, the owner is quite the collector.
Aren't they something?
One for each of the 50 states.
Puerto Rico is technically a territory.
You know, maybe they were thinking,
"Someday."
So no basement?
- No basement. Sorry.
- That's a problem.
My brother's in the Peace Corps
and won't be back for 18 months...
...and I said I'd hang on
to his furniture.
Well, if you're looking
for storage space, there's an attic area.
Well, an attic might be even better,
as long as it's dry.
- Let's take a tour.
- Okay.
Actually, I have a handout for you.
It has all the information.
- I'm Stephanie Doswell, by the way.
- Charlotte Blattner.
- So nice to meet you, Charlotte.
- You too.
So I told him point-blank.
You're my husband and I love you,
but you're 53 years old.
This job has just gotten too stressful
and difficult, and it's time to quit.
And, miracle of miracles,
he listened.
What a fascinating career
that must have been for him.
It was.
I mean,
NASA was like a second family to us...
...but, you know,
it was time for a new adventure.
So between his pension and the income
I bring in from hand modelling...
...we're, you know, comfortable.
When were these floors redone?
Two years ago.
The counters are brand-new.
I can tell. Travertine.
Nice.
- Any children?
- No.
I don't really want kids.
- Is that horrible for me to say?
- Not at all.
Not everyone has to have children.
You should talk to my husband.
Garbage disposal?
Check it out. Score, yo.
- Come on. Come on. What you got?
- You're going down!
I really love your home.
Oh, well, thank you, Mimi.
It has a very European feel.
- You think?
- Oh, I lived in London for years...
...so, yeah, this feels familiar.
Where in London?
I was stationed at Upwood in the '60s.
Downtown,
but we were almost never there.
My husband is an illustrator. We
travelled a lot. Paris, Italy, Denmark.
It was before the kids were in school,
so it was easy to pick up and go.
That was before my youngest, Lucy,
was diagnosed with endocarditis.
- Oh, my.
- Gosh, is that-?
It's a bacterial infection
of the heart valves. It's...
Yeah, it can be...
That's terrible.
Is she all right?
Your daughter?
Is she okay?
Yes. Thank you.
The doctors put in a prosthetic valve
so she's- Lucy's fine.
Running and walking, riding horses.
- Thank goodness.
- Yeah.
We're very lucky.
- Excuse me, miss.
- Very nice, thank you.
- I just called the police.
- Okay, then.
I know you stole that spoon.
What are you talking about?
You're a thief.
- Excuse me?
- And a liar.
Making stories up.
What's wrong with you?
No, what's the matter with you?
You better just back off, okay?
- My husband is a DEA agent.
- Oh, I thought he was an astronaut.
Or an illustrator.
Get your crazy lies straight.
You know what, fatty?
You are so lucky...
- ...that I am late for an appointment.
- You're not going anywhere.
- Let go of my purse!
- Not until the police get here.
Let it go!
Let it go! Let it go!
You are in big trouble.
Yeah.
Just slow- Hey, just -
Slow down. Start from the- You're -
You're where?
Why the f-?
Why are you-?
Are you seriously doing this
to me again?
Jesus, just -
Would you stop crying?
I'll make a phone call. Just sit tight.
Where they got you?
So good news.
The officer spoke to the homeowners.
They're not gonna press charges.
Good. I won't either.
Okay, then. So we're good to go.
You ready?
Marie, you wanna go home?
Marie?
Yes, it's Skyler White
calling for Saul Goodman, please.
Yes, it is important.
Thank you.
Sorry. Same as before.
But this is not right.
You cannot shut me down.
You cannot do this.
I've checked your wastewater
inside and out.
I've checked your runoff gutters,
and now out here, more contaminants.
Ammonia, acetone, benzene,
nitrobenzene.
No, no, no, this is a mistake.
Where is Gary? He'll tell you
my soap is very good, very green.
Your soap is not the issue,
it's your filtration system.
The very least,
you'll need to retrofit.
But if you're leeching
into the groundwater...
...which is a real possibility here...
...you're gonna need
to replace your system.
Replace?
Do you know what cost that is?
Two hundred thousand dollars.
It's a hardship.
If you like, we can give you
a list of approved vendors.
If you get going, your downtime
shouldn't be any more than five weeks.
Okay. So sorry, you are right.
From now on,
we will be extra careful and clean.
- No more pollution, okay? Yes?
- No, I'm sorry.
The state requires you to suspend
all activity...
...until these levels
reach the mandated minimums.
- Where is usual man? Where is Gary?
- Got transferred to Las Cruces.
- If you'd like to file an appeal -
- I have done nothing wrong.
Tell me why you shut me down.
- What laws did I break?
- What laws? Several.
Tell me exact specific laws or I refuse.
Right now.
- Tell me what laws I broke.
- The specific laws...
Hold on, okay, hold on, hold on.
Wait, wait, wait. Okay.
Okay. The New Mexico
Hazardous Waste Act of 1978...
...section 74, chapter four,
part 13 states:
"Whenever the disposal
of solid or hazardous waste presents-"
- An imminent
or substantial endangerment...
...the offender may be fined...
...not more than $5000 each day
in which the violation occurs.
All right, okay.
Now the...
Okay, baby.
All right. The EPA can cite him
under the Toxic Substances -
- Control Act of 1976.
U.S. code, title 15, chapter 53 -
"- subchapter 1-"
- Section 2606.
Satisfied?
Was that specific -
- Specific enough for you?
Threw one in the channel
in the 10th.
- I guess they're even now.
- Yep.
And they're even in this match.
Both have -
All done with lunch?
You hardly touched this.
I'm not hungry.
Well...
I'm leaving the rice pudding.
I'm not hungry, Marie.
So don't eat it.
Speaking of babies, he has a new one,
Joseph, and a son, Anthony.
Hey, Marie. How you doing?
- I'm okay. Is there a problem?
- No, no.
Everything's fine.
I'm here for Hank, actually.
Oh, you're so sweet.
Hank'll be thrilled.
Hard and straight.
- And makes it the wrong way.
- Sweetie.
You have a visitor.
Oh, Jesus.
What now? She rob a bank?
Hey, buddy. How you doing?
Oh, well...
Can't complain.
You know, every day a little better.
- That's good. You're looking good.
- Yeah, well...
...handsome was never the hard part.
Come on in, grab a seat.
Yeah, just throw that stuff anywhere.
Listen...
...thanks again for the other day.
You know, this whole thing, it's...
It's been hard on her.
Forget it. Glad to help.
So rock collecting?
They're minerals, but, yeah.
It's cataloguing.
You know, sort them, label them.
- It's actually a lot of work.
- Yeah.
No, it looks like it.
- So, what's up?
- Well...
Actually,
I could use your help on something.
Homicide. Possibly drug-related.
You want my help on a case?
What am I, Ironside?
No, you're a drug cop
who knows the local talent.
And a pal I just did a favour for,
so let me pick your brain a sec.
You ever come across a guy
by the name of Gale Boetticher?
No.
Someone came along
and shot him in the face.
- Okay.
- No signs of forced entry...
...no signs of robbery.
Okay, so it's a crime of passion.
Where's the drug angle?
We found a notebook at his place.
I made a copy for you,
in case you're interested.
Looks like it pertains to some kind
of methamphetamine superlab.
Yeah.
It's filled with scientific formulas
and chemical purchase lists...
...drawings,
pages and pages of this stuff.
It looks big-time, but I'm no authority,
so I wonder if you might take a look?
Come on, Tim, seriously?
What is this,
some sort of a charity thing?
Your expertise could be useful here.
I'm lying here like third base...
...living from bowel movement
to bowel movement.
I'm not even useful to myself.
Want my advice?
You take this to Steve Gomez.
- He'll help you out.
- I give this to Steve Gomez...
...and all of a sudden it becomes a
DEA case, what good does that do me?
If you could just take a look,
tell me what I got here.
I'd really appreciate it.
Yeah.
Whatever.
Thanks, man.
Take it easy.
That's what I do.
- No, no.
- The three, seven, nine. He says, "No."
Well, it was a good try.
Here we go. Time for your nap. Yeah.
Okay.
So...
Nail salon sounded promising.
What do you think?
I think we wait.
Wait?
Skyler, it has been five hours.
He'll call.
- Just wait.
Look...
It was a good idea.
It was a great idea, but it didn't work.
So why don't we simply chalk it up
as a learning -
White residence.
Oh, hello, Mr. Wolynetz.
Am I still interested?
Well, I think that depends.
Yes, 879 was the original offer,
but that seems high to me now.
- Now I'm offering 800.
- No, no, no.
- No, don't do that.
- Why?
Well, because you're
an unpleasant person, Mr. Wolynetz.
You were rude,
disrespectful towards my husband.
Furthermore, I've met
with quite a number of sellers...
...and the market seems much softer
than I thought, so 800.
Well, I understand that you're
disappointed, but that is my final offer.
I'm sorry we couldn't make it work.
Goodbye.
What are you doing?
I'm negotiating.
Why?
Because I want to pay less.
Oh, no.
Seventy-nine thousand dollars less?
Who cares?
Do you know how much I make?
Yeah, but that's the very reason
we need to negotiate.
We don't wanna arouse suspicion
by not trying to get a good deal.
Look, I get the logic, I do,
but you just went too far with it.
You're calling him names?
I didn't call him names.
I said he was unpleasant.
Well, he's not calling you back.
I mean,
you didn't honestly think that worked?
Yeah, I do.
No way. Sorry. No.
So look, it's time to move on.
Okay? I'm gonna call Saul.
Where's my phone?
- No.
- What?
- No, just -
- What for?
Wait. Wait.
Oh, my God.
Hello.
Hello, Mr. Wolynetz.
No one's paying attention
to where these things are.
There's gotta be thousands of them
all over the world coming right for us.
And put one inside an ice cream truck,
drive it into San Francisco.
I'm not even that scared
of burning up and cannibalism.
To me, the thing that worries me
is getting trampled...
...or shoved up
against a chain-link fence.
If you think about it,
if you're against a chain-link fence...
...and you've got a lot, I mean,
a lot of people trying to escape...
...pushing hard enough forward...
...you are gonna get squeezed
right through the chain-links.
Like Play-Doh
or some kind of soft meat.
And this is inevitable, okay?
And there's nothing you or me
or anyone can do about it.
And if the fence posts are stuck deep,
really deep with the cement...
...way down inside the ground...
...it's definitely happening to you.
- Oh, yeah.
- Yeah, bitch.
Somebody got shot.
Somebody probably got shot.
Like soft meat, man.
Right through.
Squeezed through there like soft meat.
Like soft meat.
Right through the chain-links,
right through the chain-links.
Hey. Hey.
Money!
That one was mine.
- Take it easy!
- Hey, you took mine, man!
Yeah!
- Nice.
- Yeah.
To clean cars and clean money.
Hear, hear.
You see?
I told you we'd get it.
Did you?
Seriously.
It was really great work.
It's impressive.
Thank you.
And Saul finally came through.
Well, I mean,
he found the guy, right?
Well, yes, he found the guy, but
I told him what to do and what to say.
You're right. That's the hard part.
But, yes, Saul was finally useful.
Throw him a bone.
Oh, my God.
- This is truly amazing.
- Yes, well, it better be.
Three hundred twenty dollars
a bottle.
What?
"Cuvée Pol Roger
Sir Winston Churchill."
Apparently,
it was his favourite champagne...
...so they just named it after him.
- How did you pay for it?
- What do you mean?
No. Cash, I paid cash.
No, I'm asking how did you,
Walter White...
...an unemployed school teacher,
pay for it?
- How do you explain it?
- Skyler.
No one saw me.
Whoever sold it to you did.
And that's not the point.
The point is we're broke, remember?
I'm waiting for your unemployment
cheque so I can pay the phone bill.
I asked for an extension
from the power company. Why?
- Because on paper, we have no money.
- You are completely overreacting.
I'm not apologising for wanting
to celebrate in some small way.
I'm not asking you to apologise,
Walt.
I'm asking you to be smart.
I bought one bottle of champagne.
One single bottle, Skyler.
I paid cash. That's it.
That's all it takes, okay?
I mean, look at Watergate.
One piece of duct tape on a door...
...brought down
the president of the United States.
- What? I'm Nixon now?
- No.
What I'm saying is
the devil is in the details.
One little mistake,
one slipup in our story...
...that could ruin us.
Fine.
Gotta destroy the evidence.
And when I look at this image
that is part of the record...
...I am very concerned about
what sort of distraction that could be...
...whether it's from
any sort of signage...
...but especially signage that's
changing every five seconds.
Thank you.
Any other questions?
We have a motion and a second
on the floor to grant the appeal.
All those in favour, raise your hand
and say yes. Yes.
There's four in the affirmative.
Those opposed?
There's five no's and the -
That motion fails.
I would like to make a motion
to uphold the decision...
And the motion, then, is seconded
by Councillor Cook. Any questions?
I see none. All those in favour, signify
by saying "yes" to deny the appeal.
All those in favour,
signify by saying "yes."
There's five in the affirmative
All those opposed, say "no."
There's four in the negative.
Now, that passes.