In closing, I can tell you
we take this very seriously.
APD as well as the DEA.
Stopping the sale of methamphetamines
remains one of our highest priorities.
The theft of lab equipment from your
school is also receiving our attention.
Rest assured, no stone will go unturned
in our search for the person
or persons responsible for this.
If you have any questions,
now would be the time. Sir.
You're talking like
you haven't caught anybody yet.
What about the janitor
dealing drugs at school?
There is no indication
that this individual was selling drugs.
He was arrested for having
a small amount of marijuana
in his car, not in the school.
And he's since been fired.
He had a record. I'd like to know
how he got a job here in the first place.
Why wasn't there a background check?
There was one. We're currently
reviewing our hiring policies.
You better be doing more. This guy
was arrested in front of my daughter.
This guy was stealing
lab equipment, right?
That's not our thinking at this time.
We're looking at others, but not
limited to the maintenance staff.
Are you saying there was a break-in?
Do we know when this happened?
I mean, could it have been
during school hours?
We haven't been able to establish
a date or time. There is no sign
of breaking or entering.
So whoever took it had a key.
We're talking inside job?
Someone who's still at the school?
Sir, at this time I'm not able to discuss
details with you. What I can tell you
is we have good people
working hard on this case.
I'm sorry, officer,
but that just sounds like double talk.
We're trying to protect our children.
Level with us.
Really, we're giving you
all the information we have.
You know what I'd like to see
in school? Drug-sniffing dogs.
Yeah. Dogs and metal detectors and
locker searches and strip-searches.
- Our district has strict policies...
- I heard about this school in Canada
they arrested one
of the groundskeepers with drugs,
and the next day they found out over
half the students were high on LSD.
LSD? When were you gonna tell us
about the LSD?
No, please.
No one said anything about LSD.
What about the equipment that's stolen?
The equipment was taken
from our chemistry-department locker.
And tonight we're lucky
to have someone here
to give us some specifics.
Walt?
Yeah.
Mr. White
is currently on medical leave.
But as he's chair
of the science department
he's made a very special effort
to be with us here.
And I'd like to take a moment
to thank him for that.
Could you please tell us more
about the equipment that was taken?
- Please.
- Yes.
Sorry.
And thank you.
The inventory list
for the missing labware is as follows:
One 5000 milliliter
round-bottom boiling flask.
One Kjeldahl-style recovery flask,
800 milliliters.
Two full-face respirators.
Some CEP funnels, some head
with a thermometer holder.
- Okay.
- Okay. Okay.
Where did that come from?
And why was it so damn good?
Because it was illegal.
The basement.
Unfinished, of course.
But just look at all this space.
You gotta think rec room, media room.
Just imagine all the things
you could do down here.
Now remember, you're buying
for this fantastic neighborhood.
Big lawns and shade trees,
walking distance to the country club.
What happened there?
Bit of a fixer,
but this house has great bones.
Know what? We're zeroing in. I've got
another listing, new, around the corner.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Hi.
- It's by appointment only.
- Oh, well, I'm here to see the owner.
He's in the recreational vehicle.
Yo, it's appointment only.
How are you feeling?
About as good as you look.
Jeez, you look like Lex Luthor.
Listen, I visited you in the hospital,
but you were asleep.
Yeah, Skinny Pete
said you wanted Tuco's address.
Acting like you're all out for blood.
But you are alive.
Obviously you wised up.
- No, I did go see him.
- Bullshit.
- So, what, are you selling your house?
- I got two dudes
that turned into raspberry slushy
and flushed down my toilet.
I can't even take a proper dump in there.
I mean, the whole damn house
has gotta be haunted by now.
You didn't actually go see Tuco.
Here.
That is 17,500.
Your half of the 35,000.
Plus, there's an extra 15 in there.
It's all yours. You've earned it.
- You got this money from Tuco?
- Yeah.
So Tuco gave you this,
is what you're saying.
Well, we made a deal.
- You made a deal?
- That's right.
How...? Why would you
make a deal with that scumbag?
- You see what he did to me?
- Because I think
that we can do business together.
We came to an understanding.
No way, man.
Okay? No understanding.
Take a look at the money in your hand.
Now, just imagine making that every week.
That's right.
Two pounds a week, 35,000 a pound.
Without even talking to me
you told this insane ass-clown
dead-eyed killer that...
That we would give him 2 pounds a week.
We'll just scale up our operation,
add a few more hours.
No, don't talk to me about hours.
What about pseudo, man?
How are we gonna get that?
You think the meth fairy's
just gonna bring it to us?
God, it takes me a week
to get this stuff.
I'm driving all the way to Las Cruces
200 miles each way
to meet up with my smurfs.
- Smurfs?
- The dudes who go to the drugstores,
and get a couple boxes at a time
and then sell them to me.
That's maybe only good for,
like, maybe a half-pound worth.
See, that's the bottleneck
in your brilliant business plan.
All right.
Of course, you would've known
that if you would've just asked me.
- Well, here we are again.
- Here we are.
- Skyler, you look great.
- Thank you.
You must be, what, six, seven months?
- How goes it?
- It's great.
Other than waddling
to the bathroom every five minutes.
The baby shower is next week.
And it'll be good to...
It'll be good to have a day
that's just about Skyler.
Very nice.
- Thank you.
- Walt, I see you committed to hair loss.
- Yeah.
- How do you feel?
- Okay.
I... You know, pretty decent, actually.
His color is better.
You know, his energy.
And he's even more physical.
More physical?
Well, sexual.
Frisky, actually. I mean,
that's gotta be a good sign, right?
- Sure, I'll take that. Right, Walt?
- Right.
Couldn't that mean
that the chemo is working?
Well, realistically, it may just mean that
we've got the antiemetics tuned right.
Truth is, until Walt's finished
this round of chemo,
and we look at a new PET scan,
we just can't say for sure.
Well, isn't there anything else
we could be doing?
I've been wondering
about alternative medicine.
I mean, Eastern healing.
- You know, holistic.
- Well, I can't speak to its efficacy,
but as long as it doesn't
interfere with our treatment
anything that helps my patient
have a better outlook
a better comfort, is fine by me.
So you're saying it's all psychological.
It doesn't make any real difference.
Having a better outlook
can make a tremendous difference.
But it's also important
that we manage our expectations.
What?
A junkyard?
Let me guess, you picked this place?
What's wrong with it? It's private.
This is like a non-criminal's
idea of a drug meet.
This is, "Oh, I saw this in a movie.
Look at me."
Yes. So where do you transact
your business? Enlighten me.
I don't know, how about Taco Cabeza?
Half the deals I've ever done
went down at Taco Cabeza.
Nice and public. Open 24 hours.
Nobody ever gets shot at Taco Cabeza.
Hell, why not the mall?
You know, wait at the Gap.
Hey, it's time for the meet.
You know, I'll put down
the flat-front khakis
head on over, grab an Orange Julius.
Skip the part where
psycho-lunatic Tuco, you know
comes and steals my drugs
and leaves me bleeding to death.
Look, you don't have to be here for this.
Okay? I mean, seriously.
I'm okay.
No. I'm no pussy.
I'm good.
Mr. Clean and his boy.
Now, I'm sorry that I had to tune you up.
Respect, ése,
you gotta give it to get it.
Hey, what are we doing
way the hell out here?
What, they close the mall or something?
Heisenberg, come on, break it out.
- That's it? That's all you got?
- We had some production problems.
0.53.
I thought you was a player.
You told me 2 pounds,
and now you waste my time
with these Chiclets?
Seventeen and a half.
Minus the half for wasting my time.
- Hey, come on.
- What, you gonna argue?
You got something to say?
You're doing business
like a couple little bitches.
I want all of it.
Seventy grand.
- What did you say?
- You like this product.
And you want more.
Consider it a capital investment.
Look, old, bald motherfucker.
Fifty-two and a half, 25 points vig.
Vig?
Interest, weekly.
Okay.
That's $65,625 with interest.
- 1.875 pounds.
- No, 2 pounds.
Next Friday, and no production problems.
Can you handle 4 pounds?
Listen, old man, talk is talk.
But owing me money, that's bad.
What did you just do?
Four pounds. Four pounds.
Two pounds wasn't bad enough.
We're talking 2, 300 boxes
of sinus pills.
There ain't that many smurfs
in the world.
We're not gonna need pseudoephedrine.
We're gonna make phenylacetone
in a tube furnace.
We're gonna use reductive amination
to yield methamphetamine, 4 pounds.
- So no pseudo?
- No pseudo.
So you do have a plan.
Yeah, Mr. White.
Yeah, science.
Okay.
- What's this?
- That is a shopping list.
Getting some of those items
may be challenging.
One autotransformer
6 liters anhydrous methenamine.
- Two 35 M and M tube furnaces.
- It's mm, millimeter.
One 70 millimeter would be fine,
but they're hard to come by.
Forty grams thorium nitrate.
Yo, Mr. White,
I can't even pronounce half this shit.
No. Count me out. All right?
I'm leaving town.
I'm moving to Oregon or something.
- This is just...
- Jesse, Jesse, Jesse. Listen to me.
Today is the first day
of the rest of your life.
- What are you doing?
- The first day of the rest of your life.
But what kind of life will it be?
Will it be a life of fear,
of "Oh, no, no, no. I can't do this."
Of never once believing in yourself?
- I don't know.
- Listen.
These things?
We need them, all right?
And only you can get them for us.
Okay, it's ready. Here you go.
Hi, baby. I'm your Aunt Marie.
Of course you already know that
because when you watch this
20 years from now, I will look
exactly the same as I do now.
I know, it is amazing.
I have aged shockingly well. Haven't I?
Anyway, welcome to your baby shower,
Esmeralda.
- Esmeralda?
- Esmeralda.
That's your name
and you heard it here first.
Now, that is your wonderful,
handsome older brother.
Show her, older brother, your face.
Okay, not right up the nose. Don't...
Okay, not up it. Back. Back to me.
Here's your mommy. Hello, Mom.
- And look, there you are, Esmeralda.
- Yeah.
- Wake up, baby. Time to party.
- Easy, easy. Believe it or not
Esmeralda, right after the party,
your name was changed to Holly.
And I believe, Hank,
that was around the time
we took Aunt Marie to the insane asylum.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I dropped her off at the curb.
Then I married Shania Twain
and lived happily ever after.
There's Daddy. Speak, Daddy.
Say hello to your daughter.
Holly, I am very proud of you.
And I...
I think about you all the time.
Wherever you go, whatever you do in life
always know that you have a family
who loves you very, very much.
- Cheers.
Oh, my God, it's so cute.
Oh, Carmen. It's...
Oh, look. Look at that. It's adorable.
- I love it, Carmen. Thank you.
- You're so welcome, honey.
Thank you.
Look at the little feet.
- Okay.
- From me. And Hank.
What nice wrapping paper.
Marie always finds
the best wrapping paper.
- I do.
- Okay.
Let's see. And...
Exciting.
Oh, boy, oh, boy, oh, boy.
- It's... It's a... A tiara.
- Yes.
Marie, is this...?
White gold and several carats
worth of zircons.
Oh, Marie.
You spent too much on this.
You shouldn't have.
You really, really shouldn't.
But it's so... It's really... It's...
It's sparkly.
- Sparkly.
- I know.
- Thank you.
- Hey, listen, Walt.
You got anything stronger than beer?
- It's... It's great. I love it.
- Yeah.
Thank you.
Thank you, sweetie, thank you.
Sorry, man. It's just, you know, after
200 presents, it just gets kind of old.
- It's nice stuff.
- It is, isn't it?
I got just the thing to go with that.
- I'm sorry, man, I wasn't thinking.
- No, no, no. It's okay.
You mind if I have one?
- You think that's a good idea?
- Hank, I've already got lung cancer.
Okay. You got me there.
Thanks.
Cuban.
I did a little favor for an FBI guy.
Now, I was under the impression
that these were illegal.
Yeah, well, sometimes forbidden fruit
tastes the sweetest, doesn't it?
It's funny, isn't it?
How we draw that line.
Yeah.
What line is that?
Well, what's legal, what's illegal.
You know, Cuban cigars, alcohol.
You know, if we were drinking this
in 1930, we'd be breaking the law.
Another year, we'd be okay.
Who knows what will be legal next year.
You mean like pot?
Yeah. Like pot. Or whatever.
Cocaine? Heroin?
I'm just saying it's arbitrary.
Well, you ought to visit lockup.
You hear a lot of guys talking like that.
"Hey, man, what, you busting me
with these 14 bales of ganja?
It's all going to be legal next year
when Willie Nelson's president."
Say it, buddy.
It don't only go one way either.
I mean, some other stuff is legal
that shouldn't be.
I mean, frigging meth used to be legal.
Used to sell it over every counter
at every pharmacy across America.
Thank God they came to their senses
on that one, huh?
Yeah.
Okay.
Nice party.
A tiara.
A white-gold tiara for a newborn baby.
Yeah. You know, I think she got that
at Gertrude Zachary's in Knob Hill.
I mean, that thing must've cost,
like, what, 5 or 600 dollars.
You know, I think I'm gonna return it.
Are you sure?
She's bound to find out.
Well, maybe I can explain to her
that we need a Diaper Genie
more than a white-gold baby tiara.
Hey. You know, I've been thinking
about what you said to Dr. Delcavoli
about alternative medicine.
No. Don't worry.
I'm not gonna mention that anymore.
No, no, no. What I mean is that
maybe there is something to it.
Look. They do this Navajo sweat lodge
up by Farmington.
Healing ceremony. It's supposed
to be good for your lungs.
I'm not saying that I believe in it...
but it might be an experience.
Really.
You?
In a sweat lodge.
I was thinking about driving up
on Friday, coming back Sunday.
- I mean, if you're okay with it.
- Well, of course I'm okay with that.
Okay.
- Sweat lodge?
- Yeah.
I'm already sweating. Help me out.
Okay.
Hey.
70 millimeter tube furnace. Excellent.
- This is excellent. Good work.
- Damn straight.
Okay, hydrogen.
Electrolytically produced, yes?
Yeah, like you asked. I mean, this...
This crap wasn't easy to get.
And it's expensive.
Methylamine.
Where's the methylamine?
I don't see the methylamine.
Yeah, well,
that's where I ran into some trouble.
What kind of trouble?
Well, half this crap
I could just buy, right?
But this methylamine...
Not so easy.
I mean, they got it locked down tight.
But I did find some pros
who will rip it off for us.
But they want 10 grand.
What's the problem?
You have the money.
No, had.
I spent almost the whole wad.
I mean, I got, like, 2 grand left.
I told you, all this crap was expensive.
So these thieves, did they say
where they would be stealing it from?
A chemical supply place, south of town.
They got guards and security cameras.
They got steel doors.
That's why these dudes
are charging so much.
What?
So why don't we just steal it ourselves?
Yeah?
How we gonna do that?
With this.
So, what's this stuff called again?
Thermite.
And that will cut through a lock?
Because this is supposed to be
one big-ass lock.
In World War II
the Germans had an artillery piece...
It's the biggest in the world.
...called the Gustav Gun.
And it weighed a thousand tons.
And the Gustav
was capable of firing a 7-ton shell,
and hitting a target,
accurately, 23 miles away.
I mean, you could drop bombs on it
every day for a month
without ever disabling it.
But
drop a commando
one man, with just a bag of this...
and he could melt right through
4 inches of solid steel,
and destroy that gun forever.
Jeez.
So yes
I think it will cut through
any lock we're likely to find.
- You'd like to return this.
- It's very nice, but yes.
Well, it... It is from this store,
isn't it?
Oh, yes, it's from this store.
Do you happen to have a receipt?
No, I don't. It was a gift.
A gift.
Mr. Wilson,
could you step over here, please?
Mr. Wilson, I'd like you to watch
this lady while I phone the police.
Whoa, excuse me?
Ma'am, this item is stolen,
as I'm sure you know.
- It...
- Come with me, please.
Oh, yes. I intend to press charges.
Please do.
We'll be here.
Look, I...
I've never stolen anything in my life.
All right?
I told you, that tiara was a gift...
- A baby-shower gift.
- So who gave it to you, then?
- I don't have to tell you that.
- You don't have to tell me anything.
You can talk to the police.
I can tell them
my daughter-in-law remembers
showing this particular item
to a tall blond woman
who, when her back was turned,
walked right out the door with it.
- So there.
- Oh, yeah?
Well, then, I can talk
to the Channel Three News.
Yeah, I can tell them
how you people, without a shred...
Without a modicum of evidence,
illegally detained
an innocent pregnant woman
in a dank storeroom.
- This is my office.
- I feel I'm being held hostage.
Furthermore, I'm not
getting enough air back here.
I don't think...
I don't think I can breathe.
Oh, my... Oh, my God. Oh, no.
I'm going into labor. Yes, I...
Hi, you've reached Marie.
Do the beep thing.
Marie, it's Skyler.
I just left Zachary's.
I need to talk to you immediately.
Where is the guard?
He's supposed to be coming by.
- Do you think he already passed?
- Look, I don't... I don't know.
Okay.
- Wait, there he is. There he is.
- Yeah, I see him.
Okay, wait till he passes.
Okay, it's clear.
Here.
- What the hell is this?
- It's all they had.
If this is all they had,
you're in the wrong place.
Just put it on.
Should've... Of course.
Okay, okay.
Okay. This is it.
Oh, God.
Okay.
- Get...
- What?
- Look.
Hey, Jimmy, I'm stopping...
He's not supposed to come back.
What's he doing?
Oh, my God.
Hope everything comes out all right.
- He's going to the crapper.
- Oh, God.
- Okay. You coming, man? Come on.
- What are you doing?
Okay, there it is.
Is this gonna be loud?
You'll find out in about 10 seconds.
Stand back.
Jesus.
Come on, come on.
Hey, what's going on?
- Where are the gallon jugs?
- I don't...
- God!
- What?
Let's just take this.
Come on, come on.
What the...?
Damn it.
What are you doing opening the door?
- How are we gonna take this thing out?
- Come on. Take that.
Lift.
- God.
- Jeez.
Hey. Somebody?
- Billy, you back from the crapper yet?
- Let me out of here.
- I'm gonna kick somebody's ass.
- The alarm's going off. Check it out.
Billy?
- Billy?
- Jimmy?
Help!
- Come on, let me try.
- How is it gonna be any different?
- Can I just try it?
- Fine, go ahead.
Jesus. Okay.
All right.
Yeah, baby. See?
Eat it. Okay, I'm the king.
- Yeah, okay.
- I'm the king.
No. No, no. That didn't sound good.
Oh, God.
Well, this thing's not going anywhere.
We're not cooking
in my damn driveway, I'll tell you that.
God.
What part of "slow it down"
did you not understand?
What are you talking...? I'm...
It's heavy, man. It got away from me.
Okay. All right.
Now, that's good, that's good.
Now just bring it up, bring it up.
Easy, easy, easy. Okay.
Your real estate agent,
when is she supposed to come back?
Oh, shit.
Yeah. I don't know.
I'll make damn sure she doesn't.
Good call, yo.
Keep the temperature steady
at 425 degrees.
We'll need to run it two more hours
to have enough to make
4.5 pounds.
Four and a half, not 4?
Two pounds pays Tuco back.
Four and a half pounds
puts us $44,000 ahead.
- Each.
- Right on, man.
Right on.
With the amount of methylamine
that we got last night
we can make
4.5 pounds a week for...
Well, for the foreseeable future.
How long is that gonna be?
I mean, in your situation.
How much cash do you need?
More.
Someone's in the yard.
Yeah, this is definitely the one.
It's pretty.
Actually, I like it.
We could pull that out
and put in a closet.
Just a little...
We'll have to bring that down.
I thought you didn't like
that type of thing.
Oh, no. No, I don't.
Right, right.
Was there, by any chance, scheduled
for this afternoon, an open house?
- I left her a message. It's not my fault.
- I don't care how you do it
just keep them out of here.
Do you understand?
- Yeah.
- All right, go.
Absolutely.
You know, you can't duck me forever.
What?
Come on, I left you, like, 15 messages.
When I went to your office,
you snuck out the back.
I didn't sneak. I was going to lunch.
Skyler, what are you,
the paranoid police?
You know what, Marie? Marie, I have
never been so humiliated in my life.
That...
That tiara.
They accused me, at Zachary's,
of shoplifting it.
What were you doing at Zachary's?
I was returning it.
You were returning it.
Why would you return it?
It just wasn't...
Marie, what is wrong with you?
Can you please tell me that?
Can you tell me
why you'd do such a thing?
What does that mean?
Does that mean you don't know?
That... means that I have no idea
what the hell you're even talking about.
You have no idea what I'm talking about.
The shop...
The shoplifting. No idea?
You're not going to admit this, are you?
I can't really admit to something
when I have no knowledge
of what it is that I'm admitting.
- Would you like that gift-wrapped?
- Yes, actually.
Don't forget to sign in.
- Thank you.
You're right.
Look at this wall here.
Excuse me,
I'd just like to see the basement.
- Yeah, well, it's occupied.
- It's not a bathroom.
I just want to see the basement.
What's the big deal?
You ain't seeing the basement, bitch.
You got that? Is that sinking in?
Now, beat it.
All you all, house is not for sale.
Get the hell out.
- Hey.
So how was it?
Was it an experience?
Yeah.
It was definitely an experience.
What's that smell?
Oh, yeah, it's
sacred Navajo herbs.
You know.
Hey, everything okay?
No.
Not really.
Actually, not at all.
You know that tiara that Marie gave us?
- Yeah.
- Well, she stole it. Yep.
I practically got arrested
trying to return it at the store.
Oh, my God.
I mean, she refuses to admit it.
She refuses to apologize.
I don't know what to do.
People sometimes
do things for their families.
do things for their families?
And what, that justifies stealing?
Well...
That must've been some sweat lodge.
Are you even listening to the words
coming out of your mouth?
What would you do if it were me?
What do you mean, if it were you?
If it were me, what would you do?
Would you divorce me?
Would you turn me in to the police?
You don't want to find out.
You want something to eat?
No, thanks.
What is this shit? This is blue.
We used a different chemical process,
but it is every bit as pure.
It may be blue, but it's the bomb.
Tight, tight, tight, yeah.
Blue, yellow, pink. Whatever, man.
Just keep bringing me that.
4.6.
Come on.
And what'd I say, man?
This guy can cook.
You're all right, man. You're all right.
We're gonna make a lot of money together.
Just remember who you're working for.
What did you say?
I'm just saying, they gotta know
that they're working for you.
Like they don't already know that?
Are you saying that they're stupid?
No, I'm just... I'm just saying.
Okay, so you're not saying
that they're stupid.
So I don't understand.
Are you saying that I'm stupid?
No, come on, Tuco. I'm just...
I'm just saying.
No, you're just speaking for me!
Like I ain't got the goddamn sense
to speak for myself!
Is that it? Is that what you're doing?
Tuco.
Hey, why don't we all just relax, huh?
Heisenberg says "relax."
I'm relaxed. I'm relaxed.
I'm relax...
Damn, man! Look at that! Look!
That is messed up.
Okay, Heisenberg.
Next week.