You can come on out.
It's an actual store.
I guess I figured "vacuum cleaner repair"
was a term of art.
If you would step right here
on this blue spot.
Leave your luggage
where it is for the moment.
That good?
- Sure.
- What about this?
I'll Photoshop that out.
Oh, Nebraska. What's in Nebraska?
You. From now on.
It's gonna take me some time
to get your new situation fixed.
Until then, you're gonna be staying here.
I got a place downstairs, out of sight.
It's not the Ritz-Carlton, but it's
comfortable enough for short-term.
How short-term?
Considering you got your face up
on buses and billboards all over town
I'm thinking two days.
Maybe three.
Only thing is,
and I don't like to do this,
but you'll have a bunk mate.
Oh, yeah? He's still here?
For the moment.
He's a special case.
Gonna take some doing.
How's he holding up?
You be the judge.
We will find Hank.
Steve too.
They're out there,
and we're gonna find them.
You have my word.
Sir.
Call it in, get her out of here. Move.
I get to his door,
and I could hear music inside.
Like squeaky voices.
And I thought, you know, maybe...
I knocked on his door.
The music stopped,
and then he was right there.
When he saw the gun, he thought...
Hey, Kenny.
Does this pussy cry
through the entire thing?
Just watch.
He kept saying that, you know,
"You don't have to do this."
His eyes were so big.
- They high-fived because it worked.
- Such a bitch. He won't quit.
Then, you know, we turn around,
and there is this kid on a dirt bike
looking at us.
Drew Sharp.
That kid that went missing
up in White Horse.
It's him.
And then out of nowhere
Todd, that Opie, dead-eyed piece of shit
pulls out a gun and shoots the kid.
This is Todd Alquist we're talking about?
He killed Drew Sharp?
Like it was nothing.
Hey, Uncle Jack. Hold up.
We should keep him for a while,
get a couple of cooks under our belt.
You seriously giving me
this turn-the-other-cheek crap?
- He ratted you out, personally.
- We still got 600 gallons of methylamine.
Meth? Who gives a shit about meth?
We won the lottery here.
We've got all the money in the world.
You're talking to me about selling crank?
I mean, this is millions, Uncle Jack.
No matter how much you got,
how do you turn your back on more?
You little
son of a bitch.
It's that Lydia woman.
You're sweet on her, you little bastard.
- Hey, Kenny, you believe this?
- Hey, it's all about this right here, huh?
Come on.
You can do better.
That one's so uptight, probably
got a wood chipper for a coochie.
Stick it in down there,
you're pulling back a stump.
Oh, what the hell?
Heart wants what the heart wants, right?
Let's go back and watch some more
of that crybaby rat, huh?
How thick is it?
This is mild steel?
No, this would be cash.
What?
Nothing.
Hey, you know what?
Make yourself useful.
Give me a list of hitters, mercenaries.
Yes, yes, I remember.
You've got "concerns."
Don't worry. We'll take the time
to vet them.
Make sure there are no
undercover cops on the team.
Five should do it, providing they're
the right men for the job.
I'm gonna hate myself for asking,
but who are we hitting?
Jack Welker and his men.
They murdered Hank.
They stole my life's work.
I don't know any hit men.
You know a guy who knows a guy.
Just get me the contacts.
Anybody in that world.
I'm paying top dollar. We'll find them.
You mind if I give you
a nickel's worth of advice?
Just for old time's sake?
You're worried about your wife and kids?
Don't leave.
The way things are now,
some people... Not me, mind you,
but some people might say
you're leaving her high and dry.
Some people would be
ignorant on the facts.
Some people wouldn't know
that as far as the police are concerned
Skyler is a blameless victim.
No, no, no. Go ahead.
Get it off your chest.
Go on.
The phone call was a smart move.
Kudos to you.
Odds are it was recorded.
It'll play great for a jury.
It might even buy her a mistrial.
In a year and a half. Until then,
if they don't have you, they go after her.
- There's no point. She knows nothing.
- Well, too bad. She's got nothing to trade.
I hate to be a downer here,
but there are two DEA agents missing,
presumed dead.
Think the feds will let that go
because you hit the ejector seat?
First thing they're gonna do, they will
RICO your wife and kids out of the house.
That condo is gone.
Your bank accounts, they're frozen.
Her picture's probably on TV right now,
next to yours. Who's gonna hire her?
- Money's no problem.
- Well, I don't mean to contradict you,
but getting it to her, impossible.
The feds are praying
that you'll make contact.
The Internet, the phone, it's all tapped.
Hey, Mike was no dummy.
But every time he tried to get
his nest egg to his granddaughter
it ended up in Uncle Sam's pockets.
So you propose what?
Stay. Face the music.
I mean, how much time have you got left?
You walk in with your head held high
be the John Dillinger of the Metropolitan
Detention Center. How bad is that?
And you bring a barrel
full of drug money.
Maybe that soothes some troubled waters.
Maybe they let your family stay
in the house.
After all, the house predates
the criminal enterprise.
God, you think I want to run?
This is the last thing that I want.
This... This changes nothing.
What I do, I do for my family.
My money goes to my children.
Not just this barrel. All of it!
I'm going to kill Jack
and his entire crew,
and I'm gonna take back what is mine
and give it to my children.
And then, and only then
am I through.
Do you understand?
Everything good?
Define "good."
You're set. Time to go.
You'll be a little longer.
I'm still working on transportation.
Change of plans.
He's coming with me.
- No. No, that's not...
- We're going together. I can use him.
I'll give you two a minute.
Hey, I'm a civilian.
I'm not your lawyer anymore.
I'm nobody's lawyer. The fun's over.
From here on out, I'm Mr. Low-Profile.
A douche bag with a job
and three pairs of Dockers.
If I'm lucky, month from now,
best-case scenario
- I'm managing a Cinnabon in Omaha.
- You're still part of this
- whether you like it or not.
- Sorry. I don't think so.
You remember what I told you?
It's not over until...
It's over.
Do you want us to cuff her now?
Would that make you feel better?
Your client admits to...
Her day of reckoning is now.
...by the time this goes to trial.
Is she even listening?
Mrs. White?
Are you following all this?
Do you understand what's happening here?
Yes.
I understand.
I understand I'm in terrible trouble.
I understand that you will use
everything in your power
against me and my children unless...
Unless I give you Walt.
But the truth is,
I can't give you what you want.
I don't know where he is.
All right, go and discuss this
with your lawyer here.
Rack your brain.
And hope you can come up
with something we can use.
Four-seventeen?
Four-seventeen. No activity.
Ma'am, is there anybody else
in the house?
What about your son?
If I go look in his room,
am I gonna see him?
He's not gonna pop out and surprise me?
If this guy takes his hand away,
are you gonna scream?
He's at his friend's house.
He's been there all week.
Please, please, don't hurt my baby.
- Please... Please.
- Ma'am.
We got a lot of respect for your husband.
There's just something
that we gotta straighten out.
Okay, we know that you've
been talking to the police,
and that's okay. You gotta do that.
But you've seen some people.
Like that lady
who came into the car wash.
The one with the black hair.
You said anything about her?
No.
You sure about that?
I didn't.
The police don't need
to know anything about her.
Okay, ma'am,
I'm gonna need you to say it.
I will not
say anything about her. Ever.
I swear.
Okay.
When we leave, you're not gonna go running
to those police officers out front?
No.
Okay.
Because you really
don't want us coming back.
Sure.
Don't. Stay where you are.
We'll talk like this.
Okay.
So that thing that we talked about
- I went to Mr. and Mrs. White's house...
- You don't have to say the name.
Sure. And it went really good.
I mean, the message was received
loud and clear.
The message? Yeah.
Look, I know you did your best.
I just think...
Hi. What can I get you?
Chamomile tea with soy milk, please.
- And I'll need more stevia.
- Sure.
The person we're discussing saw my face.
You're not Western Union.
We can't just settle
for you sending messages.
Really, if you'd been there,
I think you'd see it different.
We threw a real scare into her.
She seems like a nice lady
watching out for her kids.
So you're not going to have
a problem with her.
- I can pretty much guarantee it.
- I wish I had your certainty,
but I'm not like you and your uncle. I'm
just... I'm not used to this kind of risk.
We're gonna have to take a break.
I have 50 pounds vacuum-packed
and ready to go.
And I wish you all the luck
in the world with it.
It's 92 percent.
I'm sorry?
Ninety-two percent.
- Truly?
- Tested it twice.
And it's blue, just like before.
Ninety-two. That's Heisenberg level.
He's not with you?
Well, next best thing. Pinkman.
They're looking for Pinkman.
Well, they're not going to find him. He's
with us and he's not going anywhere.
Ms. Quayle, this is what your guys
in Europe have been begging for, right?
I just think we work together good.
We make a good team.
I think it's kind of
mutually good.
Ninety-two percent.
Mr. Lambert,
welcome to New Hampshire.
All right.
Let's have a look at this place.
You got about a month's worth
of food on hand.
Most of it's canned goods,
but there's steaks in the freezer.
You got a generator outside, works on LP.
Ought to be enough in the tank
to last the winter.
It's only 15 amps, but that ought to do
for the lights, the TV, and the freezer.
That's a wood-burner.
Ought to warm the place up pretty good.
Plus you can cook on it.
On the TV front,
the reception's pretty much nil.
You got some mountains in the way.
Weather's right, you might
be able to catch Montreal,
but mostly you'll be limited to DVDs.
Mr. Magorium's Wonder Emporium.
Two copies.
I'm not much of a movie guy.
I'll make a supply run next month.
You want something else to watch,
put it on the list.
Supply run.
Fifty thousand dollars
for a trip to Costco.
It's risk.
And risk is what you're paying me for,
not toilet paper.
Risk and a 4400-mile round trip.
Mr. Lambert
my clients and I don't usually have
an ongoing relationship.
Normally you and I would have already
gone our separate ways,
but you're you.
- Where's the phone?
- No phone.
Up here, ice storms equal service calls,
equal you in cuffs.
- Internet?
- Same deal.
Also satellite, cable TV,
drop phone, car.
You want news,
I'll bring the Albuquerque papers.
- Whatever you need, just put it on the list.
- Put it on the list. Yeah.
Look, I have business to conduct.
Your business is your business.
My business is keeping you
out of custody.
You are the target
of a nation-wide manhunt.
Your face is all over TV.
You are the hottest client
I have ever had, by far.
It stands to reason
you've got to keep out of sight.
And what's keeping me
from walking out that gate?
Nothing.
There's a little one-horse town
eight miles down the hill.
There's not a thing on God's green earth
that I can do to stop you
going down there.
All I'm saying is
if you leave this place,
you will get caught.
And I gotta tell you
if I find out that
you've left the reservation
I won't be coming back.
That is for my own safety.
You understand?
Sure.
Know how to work the stove?
- The flue can be tricky.
- Yeah, I got it.
You paid good money for this.
You got two acres up here,
lots of woods, nice, warm place.
Seems to me just the spot
for a man to rest up and think on things.
If you look around,
it's kind of beautiful.
You've been very helpful. Thank you.
See you in a month.
Tomorrow.
Come...
Oh, so you're just too good
to eat with the rest of us, huh?
- It's not for me.
- Damn, man, seriously.
That's not my chocolate chip, is it?
You're gonna spoil him.
Hey, you awake?
Yeah.
We had some Ben & Jerry's.
There's peanut butter cup
and AmeriCone Dream.
I didn't know what you liked,
so I got you some of each.
There you go.
So that batch that you just cooked
was 96 percent.
Kind of figured you deserved
a little something.
Thanks.
Well, better get some sleep.
Tomorrow's gonna be a big day.
Got a whole new batch.
- Hey, Todd.
- Yeah?
Would you mind
leaving the tarp off tonight?
Well, might get cold.
No, I don't mind. I just...
I just wanna see the stars.
Sure. Okay.
Thanks.
Well, good night, Jesse.
Night.
Okay. Okay. Okay.
Okay.
Come on, bitch.
Go ahead! Do it!
Just kill me now and get it over with,
because there's no way
I'm doing one more cook
for you psycho fucks!
- Yes?
- Hi, ma'am. How you doing tonight?
You're Andrea, right?
How can I help you?
You know Jesse Pinkman?
Right? Well, I'm a friend of his.
My name's Todd.
I'm sorry to bother you so late,
but it's nice to meet you.
How is Jesse? Is he okay?
Yeah, he's okay.
Actually, I brought him with me.
Jesse's here?
Yeah, he's right over there
in that truck.
Where?
No!
Just so you know, this isn't personal.
Whoa, hey, settle down.
Settle down.
Hey, remember.
There's still the kid.
I brought you a couple of cases of
Ensure. Maybe put a little weight on you.
Jesus.
I can barely read this.
Almost forgot.
Without a prescription, I had to take
an educated guess and shotgun it.
One of these ought to come close.
Did you check on them?
Is Skyler in a better place?
No, she's still at that place
off of Eubank.
Kids are both still with her
for the moment.
There's no court date yet.
The news was talking about a grand jury,
but they didn't say when.
I saw her public defender on TV.
Looks like a deer in the headlights.
Think I got socks older than him.
What are they doing for money?
She's doing taxi dispatch, part-time.
Leaves the baby with a neighbor
when she goes in.
I saw her shopping one time.
She looks pretty good.
And she's using her maiden name.
I wouldn't take that personally,
under the circumstances.
Those working for you?
Yeah, yeah.
I took a run by your old house.
The auction's still pending.
They put a fence up around it.
They put up a fence?
Seems like the place got to be kind of
a tourist attraction. Kids breaking in.
The neighbors complained,
so the bank put up a fence.
You ready?
Yeah.
Sorry about last time.
It should go better now.
I watched a couple of YouTube videos.
It's all about finding the vein.
Give it to me. I'll do it.
Here, you do it.
Make a fist. Tight. There we go.
All right, it's just...
Stick.
That's it. Okay. Hey.
Pretty good. There you go.
Think I had worse my last physical.
I will see you on...
Let's see.
Afternoon of the 15th.
Stay a little longer?
Yeah, I got a long trip ahead of me.
Two hours?
I'll give you another $10,000.
Please.
Ten thousand.
One hour.
Cards?
All right, well...
The game will be seven-card.
I'll deal, since you are encumbered.
One of these days, when you come up here
I'll be dead.
My money over there.
What happens to it then?
What if I ask you
to give it to my family?
Would you do it?
If I said yes
would you believe me?
You wanna cut the cards?
No.
A king.
Two kings.
Flynn White to the principal's
office, please.
I'm sorry to pull you out of class.
It's your aunt Marie.
It sounds very important.
- You can take it in here, okay?
- Okay.
Here he is.
Thank you.
Hey, Aunt Marie.
What's...? What's going on?
Hold on a sec, honey.
Look at those numbers for Denver.
Things haven't gone their way...
Son, it's me. Please, don't let on.
Carmen's nearby, right?
She cannot know.
Son, are you there?
Yes.
It's so good to hear your voice.
I...
Son, the things that they're saying
about me...
I did wrong.
I made some terrible mistakes.
But the reasons were always...
Things happened that I never intended.
I never intended...
Listen, son, we don't have much time.
Is Louis' family still at 4848 Newcombe?
Son, your friend, Louis Corbett
does his family still live
in that same place up on Newcombe?
- Yes.
- Okay, good.
Okay, he's a good kid.
He's like you. He'll understand.
I'm sending Louis a package.
Now, it's addressed to Louis,
but it's for you
your mother and your sister.
There's money inside.
About $100,000. Okay?
I think.
It was all that I could fit into the box.
It has to be a secret.
If anyone says a word,
the police will take it.
I wanted to give you so much more.
But this is all I could do.
Do you understand?
Son?
Can you hear me?
Do you understand?
You want to send money?
Yes. Good.
Good, good.
So you'll talk to Louis, right?
You killed Uncle Hank.
- You killed him!
- Listen. Wait. Wait, son.
- No. What you did to Mom... You asshole.
- Please...
You killed Uncle Hank.
- Listen to me. You've got to listen to me.
- Just shut up. Just stop it. Stop it.
I don't want anything from you.
I don't give a shit.
- You need this money.
- You killed Uncle Hank.
- You killed him!
- Your mother needs this money.
- It can't all be for nothing.
- What you did...
- Please. Please.
- Just shut up. Shut up.
Will you just...? Just leave us alone.
You asshole!
Why are you still alive?
- Why won't you just die already?
- Please...
Just... Just die.
Wagner hasn't had to be
really stellar tonight.
Made solid saves
back in the first period.
You know, Michael, that's probably...
Going back, look at Wagner's numbers
you know, it seems like he's one of
the last goalies in the league.
They don't wanna
put pressure on this guy.
Kevin Granato looks to make a move,
had the puck taken.
Denver comes back out the other way.
- -by Graham Melanson off Rycroft.
- Who else?
Boy, he's been all over the ice tonight.
DEA, Albuquerque District Office.
How may I direct your call?
I'd like to speak to the agent
in charge of the Walter White
investigation.
Who may I say is calling?
Walter White.
Hello? Hello?
Sir? Sir, are you still there?
...this is not just a goalie that's
out there, it's a whole team.
Two forty-nine remaining
in the third period.
You ready for that drink now?
Dimple Pinch. Neat.
You got it.
...and Melanson
with a good look makes the save.
That's why you need good, solid
breakout passes.
Matt Peterson... Win the draw, Englehart
wins the draw, back to Peterson
goes behind the net, makes a terrible
breakout pass, goes right to Hackard.
He just winds up, puts it on net here.
Turnovers, turnovers.
When you get turnovers
in the offensive zone, chances happen.
Hopefully it won't happen again.
Turnovers generally...
- I wasn't sure you'd come.
- I'm not staying...
- Madam, is this transfer good on the...?
- Darker than a normal rosé...
For us, it's always been
science first, and...
Wait, would you...? Would you...?
Would you go back, please?
- ShamWows...
- More of a by-product.
- There.
- Exactly.
- What, this?
- Yes.
But just yesterday, your charity
the Gretchen and Elliott Schwartz
Foundation
announced a $28 million grant,
for drug-abuse treatment centers
throughout the Southwest.
Charlie, the Southwest is our home,
and we couldn't just ignore
what's going on in our own backyard.
But I'm sure you're aware that there
are people who suggest other motives.
Andrew Ross Sorkin of The New York Times
wrote a column suggesting
that the grant was
a kind of publicity maneuver
to shore up the stock price
of Gray Matter Technologies
because of your association
with Walter White.
- Well, that's not exactly the way...
- To cleanse yourselves, so to speak
of having a methamphetamine kingpin
as cofounder of your company.
Charlie, I'm glad you brought that up.
I have to believe that
the investing public understands
we're talking about a person
who was there early on,
but who had nothing to do
with the creation of the company,
and still less to do with growing it.
So, what was Walter White's contribution?
You know, to be honest... Honey?
- The company name.
We came up with it
by combining our names.
"Schwartz" means "black."
- Black plus white makes gray.
- Hence Gray Matter Technologies.
Exactly. As far as I can recall,
his contribution begins and ends there.
There are continuing reports
of blue methamphetamine
considered his signature product
throughout the Southwest,
and some evidence
of reaching as far as Europe.
So my question is,
is Walter White still out there?
No, he's not.
You sound very sure.
I am.
I can't speak to this Heisenberg
that people refer to,
but whatever he became
the sweet, kind, brilliant man
that we once knew long ago, he's gone.
But to be absolutely clear...
Police! Hands! Show us your hands.
Show us your hands.
What's going on?
Let's see your hands!