How big's the batch?
Should be about 50 pounds, give or take.
Uncle Jack, that mask
I think you should...
Mr. White said the fumes
aren't good to breathe.
Let me worry about what I breathe, kid.
Just hurry this up so I can grab a smoke.
Seventy-six percent.
- Nice going, nephew.
- Thanks, Uncle Jack.
Where's the blue?
- Where's the what?
- The blue color.
Does it come later, when this hardens?
Where is it?
I am correct in assuming
this should be blue?
See, I'm thinking the headline here
should be "76 percent."
Yeah. Whole lot more than it was.
That dude who looked like Wolverine?
He couldn't crack 70.
Fine. Yes, percentage-wise,
it's marginally improved.
And congratulations, Todd.
But blue is our brand, all over Europe.
It's what our buyers pay top dollar for.
If we're down a bit in purity
from the Heisenberg days
maybe they'll let us slide on that,
but not if it's not blue.
I don't know. To my eye
- it's kind of blue.
- Yeah, a little.
It's bluish.
Todd, you're the chef.
What do you think?
Yeah, kind of.
If it catches the light just right
I could see how you'd think
there's a touch of blue
blue-green in there.
- Aquamarine.
- Hell, we'll put food coloring in it.
Make it any damn shade you want.
Yeah, like they do
farm-raised salmon. Yeah.
I mean, Jesus, you ever see how pink
they make that crap?
Like, flamingo pink.
It sure as hell don't come out
the ocean looking like that.
All right. Let's make some money.
- Here you go, Ms. Quayle.
- Lydia.
Thank you.
Is the tea okay?
I made it just like you asked.
You sure? If it's too weak or something,
I can go put another bag in it.
I'm sure.
Look, about the product
I'm really sorry about the color.
For a minute or two,
it just got a few degrees too hot
in the mixing kettle, I think.
I might've just
cooked the color right out of it.
You burned it, like a cake.
Yeah, sort of, I guess.
But the point is I think I can fix it,
and I think I can bring
the purity up too.
I mean, I'm doing everything
just like Mr. White taught me, so...
You know,
it's bound to get better, right?
I appreciate you making
every possible effort
because, as you know,
my buyers expect a certain threshold
a continuity.
Yeah. Yeah, totally.
About your buyers
I could ask my uncle
to smooth things over with them...
if you want.
I'll pass. Thanks.
I've put a lot of faith
in your abilities, Todd.
I believe in you.
Please do make the cook better.
It's very important to me.
I've got a flight to catch.
- Hello.
- Hey. It's Walt.
Hey, Mr. White. How you doing?
I'm okay.
I...
Todd, I think I might have
another job for your uncle.
Oh, okay.
You want me to set up a meeting?
I... Yes. Please. Let's do that.
Any heads-up I should give him, like
which jail, how many targets,
stuff like that?
- Mr. White?
- Just one target.
Not currently in jail.
Jesse Pinkman.
You got it.
I'm surprised you didn't strangle him.
So now what? Book him?
I'm sure the AUSA will have plenty to say
about how to play him against Walt.
Knowing what we know about
how Walt deals with rats behind bars?
Punk has to be safer with the marshals
than out here where it's open season.
What does that mean?
What are you thinking?
The kid's got an idea.
What kid? That kid?
Timmy Dipshit there?
The one that screwed up our sting?
I'm all ears.
Just hear him out, would you?
Okay, genius, what's the idea?
You guys need evidence to put him away.
Only he's too smart
to leave any out there, right?
So you say.
Well, I know some evidence
that greedy asshole would never destroy.
His money.
- You know where he keeps his money?
- No.
But I know someone who might.
Oh, hey. How'd it go?
Trailed him to the Dog House,
picked him up there.
Seemed to be looking for someone.
- Had a lot of questions.
- No calls though, right?
- You got his phone?
- Yeah.
- He's on ice?
- Safe house off Rio Bravo.
We've got Van Oster babysitting him.
Yeah. What about Van Oster?
Did he have any questions?
Probably, but he knows better
than to ask.
Good job.
I gotta tell you this up front, Hank.
If this guy decides he wants to lawyer up
I don't care if you are my boss,
I'm gonna put a stop to this.
He won't lawyer up.
What the hell, man?
You're up.
Hey there. You mind
taking it outside for a minute?
- No, sir. You got it.
- All right, thanks.
Huell Babineaux.
Know who I am?
I'll take that as a yes.
Thanks for your patience.
As Agent Gomez said,
you're not under arrest.
Why am I here?
Well, you're here
for your own protection, sir.
How you figure that?
Well, we both know how dangerous
my brother-in-law can be.
Nice poker face.
Look, relax.
There's not much new you can tell me
about Walter White.
Multiple murders
ties to a white-power prison gang
ran the largest meth racket
in the entire Southwest.
I'm not asking, you're not answering
whoop-de-do.
Let's cut to the chase.
We have a wire on Walt's phone.
We intercepted a call between him
and a certain Saul Goodman, Esq.
You know, your employer?
Anyway, in the call, Walt said
that he was going to, quote:
"Take care of one Jesse Pinkman,"
unquote,
and that you were next on the hit list.
That's why you're here.
Bullshit. That don't make no sense.
I got the recording.
I can... I can let you hear it.
Your associate, Goodman's fixer...
What's his name?
Some carrottop named Patrick Kuby.
Boston P.D. ran him out of Beantown
a few years back.
Came out here for the sunshine.
Walt said he was gonna do this Kuby guy
the same way he does you.
In fact, Kuby's already missing.
Sorry to say, things are looking grim
for your... Your redheaded buddy.
Believe us, don't believe us.
Suit yourself.
Whatever you do,
I would not call Goodman.
He sold you down the river bigtime.
- The hell you talking about?
- Don't take it personally.
Goodman's next on the chopping block
if he doesn't do what White says.
To be fair, your circus clown of a boss
did try to spare you for all of, what
about 15 seconds
before he decided
to help Walt track you down.
You see, Goodman's got
a trace on your phone,
and as soon as you call him
Walt will find out where you're hiding.
Then it's just a matter of time
before you end up like this.
Oh, man. Oh, man. I swear to God,
I didn't know he was gonna kill him, man.
- I didn't know he was gonna kill him.
- Relax.
If we thought you did,
you'd be in lockup,
for conspiracy to commit murder
instead of under our protection.
Tell us everything you know
so we can get him before he gets you.
Why would he wanna kill me?
- I ain't do nothing.
- Who knows with this guy?
From what he said, it may have to do
with him tying up loose ends regarding
poisoning some kid named Brock.
Or maybe it's because
you know where his money is.
I don't know where his money is.
That ain't what we heard.
You ain't listening
to the people in the know.
Me and Kuby rented a van for the dude
loaded his cash up in a self-storage unit
handed over the keys to him at Goodman's.
Who knows where he took it from there?
A van, huh?
How much money we talking?
Seven barrels' worth.
Seven barrels?
When you say "barrels,"
you mean "barrels" barrels?
Barrels, man. You know,
plastic, black, 55-gallon type.
I got them at Home Depot.
Filled up every last damn
one of them too.
And where did you rent the van?
Lariat. The one
on Candelaria and Monroe.
- Lariat on Candelaria?
- Yeah.
Kuby rented the van.
Mr. White dropped it off.
He had us wash it good
before Kuby took it back.
Wash the rental? Why?
It was filthy, man,
like he went off-road with it.
After we had hosed it down,
he grabbed a shovel out the back
handed over the key, and that was it.
That's all I know.
All right, Mr. Babineaux.
Agent Gomez and I are going
to do everything we can
to find this son of a bitch.
Like I said, you're free to go.
But if I were you,
I wouldn't take one step out that door.
And remember, no phone calls.
Oh, actually, I almost forgot.
I took the liberty
of removing the battery,
so Walt can't track you by GPS.
So don't put that back in.
Agent Van Oster will stay here with you.
You're in good hands.
He's our best man with a gun.
Don't discuss the case with him
because the less you distract him
the better he can protect you.
How long you gonna be?
As long as it takes to keep you safe.
So just one guy this time.
Not even in lockup.
Some former partner, Todd says?
Yeah.
So, what are we talking, rat patrol?
Rat p...?
No, no.
Rat patrol? No. No, he's not a rat.
He's just...
He just won't listen to reason.
- Okay.
- He's just angry.
He's not a rat.
All right.
Angry non-rat. Got it.
How angry we talking, by the way?
Like, Hulk angry?
Like, Rambo-James Bond badass individual?
Not something you'd do yourself, huh?
Jesse is like family to me.
Look, I want what you do
to be quick and painless.
No suffering, no fear.
Bullet to the back of the head.
Something he doesn't see coming.
I respect that.
- There's too many savages out there.
- Let's just talk about the money.
No, we don't want your money.
We want you to cook for us.
You know I'm out of the business.
Just a couple times
to tutor my nephew here, that's all.
Get him on track
to bringing the purity up.
Get the color right too.
Apparently that blue touch you put on it
it's all the craze
with those Slavic types.
- So I'm told.
- No. Absolutely not.
Look, what was the price per head
last time? I'll triple it.
A drop in the bucket compared to
what we aim to earn from the blue stuff.
Don't skimp on family,
that's what I always say.
You want us to do this job?
Do it right? That's the price.
One cook
after the job is done.
Time is of the essence.
Do you understand?
Do him tonight if you want.
Just tell me where he is.
I don't know where he is,
but I know how to flush him out.
You want string cheese
or yogurt squeezers with your PBJ?
Both.
- I didn't hear you.
- Both, please.
Hold on, honey.
Hi, Andrea.
I don't know if you remember me.
I'm Walter White, Jesse's friend.
- Oh, yeah. Yeah, of course. Hi.
- Yeah. Yeah.
Oh, hi. Hi.
I'm sorry to just barge in
on you like this,
but I was hoping that I could
have a moment to talk with you.
It's about Jesse.
Sure. I'm sort of rushing around
right now.
Wanna talk inside
while I get my boy ready?
Oh, well, yeah. If it's...
If it's okay, yeah, sure.
Thank you.
- You met Brock before, right?
- Yes. Yes, I have. At Jesse's.
How you doing, Brock?
Brock, he asked you a question.
- I'm good.
- Good.
Froot Loops.
That's good stuff.
So Jesse...
Yeah, I...
I don't wanna alarm you,
but I've been trying
to reach him for days.
I've stopped at his house
I've left all kinds of messages
on his voicemail,
and he won't return my calls.
I can't find him anywhere.
Have you heard from him?
No, not since the last time
he called to check on Brock.
That was, I don't know,
two weeks ago, maybe.
Andrea
Jesse's using again, and I...
I have a bad feeling about this.
Have you tried calling the police?
Or a better idea.
Jesse's lawyer's name is Saul Goodman.
I have his card somewhere.
I mean, he may have ways of finding
Jesse without getting him in trouble.
"Better call Saul." Yeah. I... I did that.
He was able to verify
that Jesse's not locked up,
but, otherwise, very little help.
You see, the thing is
is that Jesse and I
had this argument recently.
And I won't bore you
with the details, but he's...
He's... He's pretty upset with me and...
And I'm hoping that's the reason
he hasn't called me back
instead of him being...
Well...
Well, I'll try him right now.
I mean, if that's it, he's mad at you
- maybe I'll have better luck.
- That would be such a help. Yes.
What...? What...?
What number are you calling him on?
- His cell.
- You know, he recently got a new one.
And there. That...
That's his new number there,
the highlighted one.
Jesse, hey, it's Andrea.
Your friend Walter just dropped by.
He's here at the house right now.
We... We're thinking of you.
Call me back as soon
as you get this message.
I really need to hear from you.
It's important.
Thank you, Andrea.
I appreciate that.
Well, I better... I better be going.
You're welcome to stay a few minutes
to see if he calls back.
No, no, no. You're trying to get
your son off to school.
If he does happen to call back,
would you call me?
Better yet, I've got your number.
I'll call you back, okay?
And thank you.
See you, Brock.
We on?
Yes. It should be any time now.
Copy that.
Remember, fast and painless.
And take him away from here.
I don't want the mother
or the boy to know.
You got it.
Jesse, hey, it's Andrea.
Your friend Walter just dropped by.
He's here at the house right now.
We... We're thinking of you.
Call me back as soon
as you get this message.
I really need to hear from you.
It's important.
Nice try, asshole.
How'd it go at the rental place?
Van have GPS?
No GPS. Nope.
They used to have GPS
until about six months ago
when the ACLU or somebody sued them,
and they had to get rid of it.
Well, that's it. Game over.
Yo, man, you can't just give up on this.
- Who said we're giving up?
- What do you got?
Just thinking about what Babineaux said
about the van being dirty,
and the shovel that Walt had with him.
I'll bet you 10-to-1
he buried that money.
No kidding. So what?
There's a whole lot of desert out there.
How we gonna find the spot?
You said it yourself,
there's no GPS on the van.
Yeah. But Walt doesn't know that.
All right.
Here's your change.
- Oh, count it out, please.
- Here.
Three. That makes 15.
Plus 5, that is 20.
- Give this to your car wash professional.
- Thank you.
Say it.
- Have an A-1 day.
- Oh, you too.
- Good.
- Why...? Why do I...?
Why do I gotta say that?
Because it reinforces our brand.
So getting the hang of it?
It's... It's pretty basic.
Mom, it's Saturday.
Can...? Can I go?
- Go where?
- Home.
Pick up a few things,
maybe chill for a little bit.
I'm sure the smell is gone by now.
Why don't you just stick around here
for a while longer?
- I need you.
- Hi.
Who do I give this to?
You know what? I'll take care of it.
Excuse me, son.
That'll be 14.97, please.
Hey. How you doing?
You're on our billboard. You're...
- You're the lawyer guy, yeah.
- "Better call Saul!"
Okay.
So 3 makes 15, and 20, 25, 30
35, 40, and 10 makes 50. Thank you.
I like your commercial.
What...? What happened to your face?
Oh, this is a... I guess you'd call it
an occupational hazard.
Thank you, and please give that
to your car wash professional.
Very good. Thank you very much.
Good to meet you.
- Yeah.
- Don't drink and drive.
- Okay.
- But if you do, call me.
Have an A-1 day.
Mom, you forgot to say it.
Yeah. Yeah, I did. Okay.
Make sure you get in there
between the cushions, all right?
That's it. Way in there. Attaboy.
What the hell you doing here?
I swear to God, the kid left
so much booger powder in there
my Caddy is a K-9 unit's wet dream.
Is your phone broken? All 200 of them?
Huell's gone.
Huell's gone where?
No idea. AWOL. Nobody's seen him.
He's not answering his phone.
So, what about Jesse?
He hasn't shown up yet.
He will, Saul.
He's probably high as a kite,
and hasn't gotten our message yet.
Or he got it loud and clear,
figured out it's a setup.
The kid is not as dumb as you think.
Are you wearing a bulletproof vest?
Did you miss the part about
my bodyguard has gone missing?
Look, I had him watching the Dog House
figuring the kid might show up.
Next thing I know, radio silence.
You're the math whiz.
Add up two and two.
Jesse is not on some killing spree.
It's me he wants.
It's just me.
Well, then where the hell's Huell?
- Any news?
- Not yet, but soon. I promise.
Have an A-1 day.
Next, inventory lists.
These are the inventory lists.
Every day, after close of business
you tally the total of every item sold,
and you mark it
under the appropriate column.
So say we sold, I don't know,
10 pine-scented air fresheners.
You mark "10" under this column,
and then you subtract 10
from the stock column.
Okay? Why don't you try that?
Jesse?
Got my photo, bitch?
That barrel look familiar?
Because I just found six more
exactly like it.
That big bastard who works for Goodman
I pistol-whipped that melon
he calls a head
till he gave up what he knew,
which led me to your rental van
which, it turns out, had GPS.
How do you like that, genius?
Guess you didn't think of everything.
Look, Jesse, I don't know
what you plan on doing here, but...
Well, I'll give you a hint, Walt.
It involves a couple of five-gallon cans
of gasoline and a lighter.
No, no, no! Jesse, please, listen to me.
No, you listen to me, bitch.
You get your ass out here
as fast as you can.
Yes, I'm coming. Okay! Okay!
And don't even think about
calling anyone for help, all right?
You hang up on me, put me on hold
lose my call for any reason
as soon as you do, I'm burning all of it.
All right? One big bonfire.
You get the picture?
- I get it, I get it. Okay.
- All right. You better hurry
because I'm burning 10 grand a minute
till you get here, starting right now.
I said, I'm coming!
Don't you touch my money!
Fire in the hole, bitch.
There goes 10 G's.
- Oh, nice orange flames.
- No, no, no!
Jesse... Jesse, please.
I'm dying. My cancer is back.
You're not hurting anyone
but my family. Okay?
I can't spend this money.
It's not for me. I won't be around
long enough to use it.
It belongs to my children.
Oh, you're gonna talk about kids.
You're seriously gonna go there?
I am sorry about Brock.
No, you're not.
- I am.
- You're not, but you're gonna be.
Yes, I am sorry about Brock!
But he's alive, isn't he?
He's fine, just as I planned it!
Don't you think I knew
exactly how much to give him?
That I had it all measured out?
Come on!
- Don't you know me by now?
- I know you're a lying, evil scumbag
that's what I know.
Manipulating people
- messing with their heads.
- Open your eyes!
Can't you see that I needed you
on my side to kill Gus?
I ran over those gangbangers!
I killed Emilio and Krazy-8! Why?
I did all of those things
to try to save your life
as much as mine.
Only you're too stupid to know it!
Jesse.
Jesse!
Jesse, talk to me.
Jesse, I didn't hang up! Jesse!
Jesse?
Jesse, I'm here. Where are you?
Son of a bitch.
Son of a bitch!
No. No. No, no, no.
Come on, come on.
Yes.
Yeah?
It's me. I've got Jesse in sight,
and he's coming for me right now.
He knows I'm alone.
- Let's go, boy.
- I'm guessing he's got backup.
- How many guys?
- I do... I... I don't know.
- Where are you?
- To'hajiilee.
An Indian reservation west of town.
- Get a pen.
- Go.
Okay.
"Thirty-four, 59, 20
106, 36, 52."
Those are coordinates.
If you want me around to cook for you
- you get here now.
- You got it.
As fast as you can. Okay. Wait.
They're coming.
Looks like there could be
three men total.
Wait a minute.
What? What is it?
- Stay in the car.
- Oh, my God.
Walter, what is it?
Walter, you still there?
Walter?
Walter, you got eyes on him?
What do you see?
Walter, talk to me.
Forget it.
Don't come.
What do you mean, "don't come"?
It's off.
Do not come.
Walt!
Come on out!
I know you're out here!
It's over!
Walt!
Come on out, Walt!
Got him.
Drop it!
Hands up!
Walk towards me slowly!
Stop.
Turn around.
Lace your fingers behind your head.
Walk backwards to me.
Stop.
Get on your knees.
How'd you like my barrel photo, huh?
Took it in the backyard
by the barbecue grill.
You know, where we used
to cook out with the family.
Gomey thought the dirt
might not match. But me?
I bet your greedy ass
would be so worked up
about the prospect of losing your cash
that you wouldn't catch it.
Looks like I was right.
He's clean.
Yo, I remember this place.
It's the very first place
we cooked, like, ever.
It is, isn't it?
Hey, what say you save us
the busywork, Walt,
and point out the spot
where you buried your money?
No?
No matter.
I'll get a search team out here.
We'll find it.
Agent Gomez, should we flip a coin
for the honors?
No way, man. It's all yours.
Walter White
you have the right to remain silent.
Anything you say can
and will be used against you
in a court of law.
You have the right
to speak to an attorney,
and have an attorney present
during questioning.
If you cannot afford an attorney
one will be provided for you
at the government's expense.
Do you understand these rights
as I have just recited them to you?
Coward.
- Get... Get over here!
- Bring it!
- Get in the truck, will you?
- Bring it, bitch!
- Put him in the car!
- Come on!
Get in the car! Hurry up!
Get in the car, kid. Come on.
Gonna take him down for booking, okay?
You should stay here
till I come back with a search team.
- You got it.
- I'd take the kid with me,
but they'd probably
kill each other on the way.
- Congratulations, buddy.
- Hey.
I'll call the tribal police,
let them know we're here.
Gonna make a phone call.
Hank, why is there what looks like
brains in our garbage can?
Hey, baby. I got him.
Dead to rights.
- You got Walt?
- Yeah.
I got him in handcuffs as we speak.
Want me to wave to him for you?
Well, he's not...
He's not feeling too friendly.
Oh, my God.
You did it.
Thank God.
Things are gonna be a little rough
for the next couple weeks,
but they'll get better.
Baby, you okay?
I'm much better now.
I gotta go.
It may be a while before I get home.
I love you.
I love you too.
Who the hell is this?
Tribal police?
Hank! Hank! Hank!
No...
Police! Drop your weapons!
Jack, don't do it!
Jack!
Drop your weapons!
You heard the man! Put them down!
How do we know you're cops?
Show us some ID!
Damn straight! Let's see some badges!
Jack!
Jack, don't do it! Jack!
No, Jack, it's off! Jack!
We'll give ourselves up,
you show us some badges!
Simple as that!
How about it?
No!
Jack!
Jack, it's off! Forget it!