More.
Another.
Careful, Señor.
Hot day like today...
...too much oiI in the machine...
...can cause it to blow a gasket.
There are two kinds of men in this world.
Those who drink...
...and those who pour.
Shut up and fill my glass.
Hey, you two.
Yes, you.
I used to be just Iike you.
Worked dirt for the
man till my hands bled.
But no more.
Because I learned that
a man can never drink his fill...
...by waiting in line for the tap.
Listen to him.
He can teach you something!
Hey, how you doing, boss?
Good to see you, my friend.
You know, I never pegged
you for such a deep thinker.
I keep thinking I should write a book.
Maybe, maybe....
So, what brings you to
this burro's asshole of a town?
I knew l would find you here.
Don't you have something to deliver?
Cutting it close, aren't you?
Lots of time.
Tortuga may be slow out of the gate,
but he always...
Finishes first.
Yes, I know.
Just like your namesake.
I like the way you talk, Tortuga.
Yeah?
You've got such a way with words.
They flow like a waterfall.
I like that about you.
I'm so stupid.
I missed your birthday.
No, I feel terrible.
So bad I came aIl the way
here to this burro's asshole...
...to give you your present.
Present?
Come on, boss.
No need to go too the trouble.
Forget it, I wanted to.
I have it for you in the back.
Back there?
Yes. Come. Follow me.
It's perfect!
Do you really like it?
I love it!
What a great pet it will make.
Thank you, boss!
Excellent.
Let me sign it for you.
Let me sign it...
..."For the big talker."
Gentlemen. Welcome.
Thank you for coming.
Any difficulty at the border?
The day I can't get across
the border is the day I retire.
Please, come in.
I apologize that it's not wheeIchair accessible.
My apologies, Gustavo.
Of course, you shouId have been advised.
It's your territory,
you had a right to bless the order.
We had no reason to believe
the man was of concern to you.
Indeed, he is.
So you're in business with this Heisenberg.
I don't know him by that name,
but yes.
I've made no secret of the fact that...
...l have always done business
with certain local manufacturers.
You and I,
we still make money together.
It's never affected our relationship.
Don Salamanca had a nephew named Tuco.
Yes, I knew of him.
Then perhaps you know
Salamanca mentored him in the business.
Thought of Tuco as a son.
When Don Salamanca was no longer able,
Tuco took over for his uncle.
He was a key man in our
organization north of the border.
He was loyal.
This Heisenberg, WaIter White...
...he was one of Tuco's local suppliers.
Until he betrayed Tuco.
So now you see,
blood must be repaid by blood.
Tuco's cousins here...
...they have the right to exact vengeance.
The Salamanca family, the Cartel...
...everyone stands
shoulder to shoulder on this.
Don Salamanca.
Gentlemen.
I feel your loss deeply.
Please accept my condolences.
I have no issue with
your right to vengeance.
But l am presently
engaged in business with this man.
When our business is done...
...he wilI no longer be
of any concern to me.
Until then...
...l need him alive.
Excuse us.
I don't tell you how to
fry your chickens, Gustavo.
You shouId really leave matters
of my organization's politics to me.
Do I not run my own territory?
Of course you do.
And I will advise them to be patient.
But l recommend you finish
your business with the man quickly.
Or you risk Iosing
the good graces of the Cartel.
That would not be wise.
And those boys inside...
...l cannot guarantee that they will listen.
They are not like you and I.