Good morning, Ladies, good morning.
Do you speak English?
I, I...
Help.
Help, help. Thank you.
I need, need... help.
To clean, yes?
What?
Understand?
What do you want?
It's fine.
Please, please.
To the back, to the back. Yes.
Very good.
What do you think?
No, no, no. We can't.
I'm sorry.
No, no. There's no problem.
One moment, one moment.
Not there, not there.
Can we?
No.
We can't.
We must go back to work.
One moment, one moment.
I need... Help...
To clean. Two hours maximum.
No, we can't...
Very easy.
They'll fire us.
He wants to do the back.
Money.
For you.
Yes, yes, yes. For you.
Yes.
President Grant.
For you. Yes.
More money, more money...
They'll fire us from work...
It's only two hours.
But they'll fire us...
We'll be without a job...
Let's go.
Two hours maximum, yes.
Please, please.
Equal!
But what does one do for money, right?