♪♪ The city's called Duke. ♪♪
♪♪ The state's called New Mexico. ♪♪
♪♪ Among the gangsters the gringo's fame is inflated, ♪♪
♪♪ 'cause of the new drug they created. ♪♪
♪♪ They say the colour is blue and the quality pure. ♪♪
♪♪ This potent drug's runnin' through the city, ♪♪
♪♪ and no one could stop it even if they wanted to. ♪♪
♪♪ The Cartel's runnin' hot because they weren't getting respect. ♪♪
♪♪ Talkin' 'bout some "Heisenberg" who owns the market now. ♪♪
♪♪ No one knows the man since they've never seen his face. ♪♪
♪♪ The Cartel's 'bout respect and they ain't forgiving. ♪♪
♪♪ But that homey's dead. ♪♪
♪♪ He just doesn't know it yet. ♪♪
♪♪ Heisenberg's fame has got down to Michoacan. ♪♪
♪♪ From way far away they want to taste that meth, ♪♪
♪♪ the blue stuff that has crossed the border. ♪♪
♪♪ Now New Mexico's livin' up to it's name. ♪♪
♪♪ Looks just like Mexico in all the drugs it's hiding, ♪♪
♪♪ except there's a gringo boss and he's known as "Heisenberg". ♪♪
♪♪ The Cartel's runnin' hot because they weren't getting respect. ♪♪
♪♪ Talkin' 'bout some "Heisenberg" who owns the market now. ♪♪
♪♪ No one knows the man since they've never seen his face. ♪♪
♪♪ The fury of the Cartel ain't no one escaped it yet. ♪♪
♪♪ But that homey's dead. ♪♪
♪♪ He just doesn't know it yet. ♪♪
What the hell are they thinking?
Sending us some loudmouth
who doesn't speak the language?
Politics, man. Politics.
Supposed to be some hotshot hero.
I say it's a bunch of crap.
Hero for Albuquerque, maybe.
Maybe it don't take much up there.