Here you go.
What happened there?
- It's my birthday.
- Yeah? Well, happy birthday.
Birthday meals are free at Denny's.
All you gotta show is a valid ID.
I'm good. Thanks.
Really? Free meal. Free is good.
Even if I was, like, rich,
free is always good.
Thank you.
Okay.
New Hampshire.
You're a long way from home.
How long a drive is that?
About 30 hours,
if all you stop for is gas.
You headed to California?
No. Here.
Okay.
So, what's here?
Business.
You know, I was in Boston once. Boston
and a little town called Swampscott
which is right outside of Boston.
That's kind of near New Hampshire, right?
Yeah. More or less.
Yeah, I was maybe 6,
so I don't really remember it.
I want to say I liked it.
They got this really big aquarium.
Yeah. Great science museum there.
Excuse me.
- Hi.
My name's Lucy. I'll be your server.
I got your word this won't wind up
crossing the border?
It's never leaving town.
Is there a manual? Instruction manual?
I pulled something off the Internet.
It's in there.
Well
good luck, I guess.
Happy birthday, Mr. Lambert.
Jesus, Walt, the news here...
Gus Fring is dead.
He was blown up along with some person
from some Mexican cartel,
and the DEA has no idea
what to make of it.
Do you know about this?
Walt?
Walt, I need you to...
It's over. We're safe.
Was this you?
What happened?
I won.
Oh, God.
Dad.
- Dad.
- Hey.
Hey.
Serious... You don't have the TV on?
Seriously?
No, sorry, I...
You didn't tell him about Mr. Fring?
- He knows.
- Welcome home.
Jesus, Dad,
it's all they're talking about.
They haven't said it on TV yet,
but Uncle Hank says he was
this major, major drug dealer.
I mean, like, holy shit.
Your uncle is safe, right?
How do they know that?
Uncle Hank was after this guy all along.
He didn't tell us, but he was.
He even took me
to his restaurant one time
just, like, totally toying with the guy
just like, "I got my eye on you."
Like that.
They figure Mr. Fring was the one
who put the hit out on Uncle Hank.
Just somebody got to him first.
Yeah, wow.
Aunt Marie's still pretty freaked.
She didn't want us to leave,
but Mom figured it was time.
There's still some agents over there,
but they figure it's over.
Like, when this hits the news
Uncle Hank is gonna be a hero.
- Yeah.
- I mean, even more so than before.
Seriously.
See... See if it's on TV.
Yeah, yeah, I want to.
Just give me a couple minutes, huh?
- -around the 24-yard-line.
- They break huddle...
Hi.
Hi, sweet pea.
Oh, Daddy missed you so much.
Yes, he did.
I know.
I missed you too.
Well, don't you think
I rate a "hello," at least?
Hello.
Hello to you too.
So are you gonna talk to me here?
Are you gonna...
You gonna show some kind of...
I don't know, some kind of mild relief
that I'm alive?
I am relieved, Walt.
And scared.
Scared?
Scared of what?
You.
Hey.
Hi.
Oh, shit.
Jesus, just say it already.
Tell me "I told you so."
Get it out of your system
before you need, like,
dialysis or something.
It's exactly like Boetticher's drawings.
Where were the two bodies?
Over by the freight elevator.
Over there.
- No idea who they were?
- No, not much left.
Apparently the teeth do this popcorn
thing when they get too hot,
so they tell me.
Whoever torched it did it up right.
Fring, you magnificent bastard.
What do you figure that was?
I don't know, some kind of lab equipment?
Maybe a camera?
Come on. Come on, you, be nice.
Be nice.
Come on. Hey. Hey!
You be nice. Just be nice.
Let Wendell in there.
If Wendell doesn't eat, nobody eats.
Yeah.
It's Gustavo.
He's dead.
Son of a bitch.
- Hold up! Hold up!
- Get out of my way, kid.
- Wait a minute, all right? Let him talk.
- I am done listening to this asshole talk.
Now get out of my way.
He's got something you need to hear,
all right?
What'd you do, Jesse?
Do you even know?
Do you even know what you've done?
- Yeah, he saved his own life...
- One more word.
Mike. Mike.
If you kill him, you're gonna
have to kill me. Come on.
Oh, Jesse.
Jesus.
What is it with you guys?
Honest to God.
May I?
Look, whatever differences
you and I have, they'll keep.
Right now we've got bigger fish to fry.
- Bigger fish.
- The video cameras.
Gus kept cameras on us at the lab
at the laundry,
God only knows where else.
And of course, when I say "us,"
I'm including you.
Mike.
Mike, if he taped all that shit
us cooking, you picking up...
If Gus had a record of that
and the police get to it before we do...
You son of a bitch.
Mike, it's all on tape somewhere,
or a hard drive.
Where?
Where did he keep it?
He had a laptop in his office.
Kept it in the back of the restaurant.
It all fed straight to there.
What?
Keys, scumbag.
It's the universal symbol for keys.
Meter fraud.
And yes, yes, it's a big deal.
Guy rigs his meter so he's paying
2 cents less for first-class postage.
I'm here to tell you that the USPS
takes that very seriously.
It's money out of your pocket,
it's money out of my pocket.
I was hoping... Now, look, sarge.
Do you think we could work together on
this thing? You folks have it over there?
Could you tell me that, at least?
Yeah.
Well, thanks for your help.
Inspector Clark... Inspector Dave Clark,
like the Dave Clark Five?
Before your time.
Well, you feel free to call me
day or night at this number.
Yes, sir. No, you as well.
Thank you.
Oh, yeah.
We're boned.
Well...
You know how they say
"It's been a pleasure"?
It hasn't.
Are you gonna tell us about the laptop?
- Where you going?
- I'm getting the hell out of Dodge, kid.
And so should you.
It's just a matter of time.
Mike, where is the laptop?
What the hell difference does it make?
They got it. End of story.
A.P.D., Northwest Area Command
on Second.
They tagged it, they filed it
it's in the system,
and they locked it in their evidence room.
All right.
All right. So describe the building.
Describe the...
How about I describe Fort Knox?
And what are you gonna do?
Are you gonna put on your black leotard
and go dangling on a clothesline?
It's a building full of cops.
What else do you need to know?
And why in the hell am I talking to you?
Mike, we gotta do something.
I am doing something.
He's good with this stuff, okay?
Just give him a chance.
Now, you look.
That laptop might as well be on the moon.
They build these evidence rooms
like bank vaults because guess what
lunatics like you wanna break into them.
But unlike a bank vault, this is a place
that is guarded 24 hours a day
by the police.
There's no way you're getting it
out of there.
Who said that we have to
get it out of there?
We just need to destroy what's on it.
Oh, so now you wanna
blow up a police station?
I don't believe I said that, no.
Nursing home full of old folks
just whet your appetite.
Now you wanna kill a bunch of cops.
I never said anything
about killing anybody.
I am, however, considering
the possibility of a device.
- A device.
- Yes, a small device.
Say this device gets filed into evidence.
- Now it is inside that room.
- What about a magnet?
You wanna commit a whole other crime
just to get this bomb into evidence.
- Who said "bomb"? I said "a device."
- What about a magnet?
An incendiary device.
One quick fire is all it would take.
You don't think they have fire
suppression? I'm not talking sprinklers.
I'm talking about halon.
Because halon doesn't destroy evidence.
- A magnet, though, maybe like...
- A bomb then. We plant a bomb outside.
Oh, actually I knew a crew
out of Fort Worth
that tried to blow up an evidence room
from outside.
About all they did was take out
a couple of hedges.
You are probably talking about 2 feet
of reinforced concrete.
Or what about a magnet?
What magnet? What about it?
You know, just:
So, what do you think?
Expensive.
Leaving aside engineering
rigging some kind of
alternate power source
my primary sticking point is
I actually need the thing.
As you gentlemen can see,
it's paying the bills.
But I mean it's feasible, doable?
Hey, we're living in a time
of string theories and God particles.
Feasible, doable?
Yeah, sure, why not?
Expensive.
What would you put it in?
What about that? Does it run?
We can get it running.
What's the box made of?
Plywood and aluminum, just what you need.
All right, so you wanna talk money?
Step into my office.
Hey, listen.
I don't actually have
any money right now.
My wife... There's an IRS issue.
Anyway, I'd appreciate it if you could
spot me my share. I'll pay you back.
Yeah. Whatever.
Right.
You coming?
If you have any brains,
you'll take that money you saved,
and you'll skip town.
Today. Right now.
You don't think this can work?
Is that a serious question?
Mike, this is a three-man job.
The only way I know it won't work for sure
is if we don't have you.
Come in.
Get in. Close the door.
What did we say about you coming here?
Yeah, speaking of things
that tend to rile you up
the police, they may call.
Let me back up a little. Can I sit down?
I'm gonna sit down.
Okay, why are the police gonna call?
May call you.
Distant, outside possibility.
But on the off chance,
I want you thinking one thought:
Hogan's Heroes.
Sergeant Schultz.
You remember Sergeant Schultz?
"I know nothing. I see nothing."
You remember how he...
I want you like that.
- Okay, Saul, why are the police...
- There was an incident with Beneke...
Oh, God.
- And it's...
- Oh, Jesus.
- What incident?
- An act of God.
There's no right. There's no wrong.
I mean, it just... That's the best phrase.
It fits, but we got a problem.
Ted's dead.
Sorry?
Ted is dead?
No. No, no.
He just woke up.
Right-o, that should do her.
All right, watches off.
Necklaces, earrings, rings, bracelets...
Gold. These are nonferrous.
Better hope.
What about that stuff you young guys
wear on the end of your pricks?
Speak now or forever sing soprano.
What's up with that, by the way?
Why would anybody wanna put a metal
ring through the end of their prick?
What are you looking at me for?
All right, guns, knives
tools, keys, plates in your head
artificial hips.
Check your pockets for me
one more time, please.
Oh, credit cards.
You want that plastic working
come Miller time.
You know, I can foresee a lot of
possible outcomes to this thing,
and not a single one of them
involves Miller time.
P.M.A.
Positive mental attitude.
Okay, I think we're good to go.
All right, where do you
want me with this?
Start 40 feet out.
That's more than the length of the room.
- Who's doing the honors?
- Me.
Flip that switch, turns it on.
Twist this here.
That's your power control.
- All right.
- Everybody ready?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Fire in the hole!
All right, you ready?
Fingers crossed it don't yank
the drive shaft through the floor.
Anything?
Nope. It's still working.
All right, start walking forward slowly.
Wait, wait, wait.
Yeah. That did it.
Yes.
Yeah, bitch!
Magnets!
How many batteries is this?
That there's 21, wired in series,
so 21 times 12.
Two hundred fifty-two volts.
Can you add 21 more, wired in parallel?
Up the amperage?
Everything goes flying
in that evidence room
it's gonna make one hell of a noise,
and there goes your element of surprise.
Won't matter.
Sixty seconds, we'll be gone.
Excuse me.
Hi. Who are you looking for?
Ted Beneke. I'm a friend of his.
But if it's not a good time, I could...
No, no, no, this is fine.
I'm just finishing up. Come on in.
Hey, Ted.
I tell you, he's been a real champ.
His color's better
and his blood pressure's up.
We are gonna have you
eating solid food in a day or two
I bet you money.
That's wonderful.
All right, I'm just down the hall.
Ted.
Can you hear me?
Yes.
Ted, I just...
I don't even know...
Skyler.
I haven't said anything
to anyone.
I told them it was an accident.
I tripped,
and fell. That is all they know.
Just...
I've... I've got children.
Family.
I swear to you.
Please.
I just...
I...
...will never breathe
one word of this.
Good.
It should be about a quarter
of the way down on the left.
We'll do a loop and come around
the other side. Turn here.
Right up there.
That's the wall.
What the hell is this?
There's some big-ass hump in the way.
So? Just drive over it.
- All right.
- Come on, you can do it.
Take it easy. Take it easy.
You got it.
Cut it.
It's, like, 8 feet away. Is this cool?
Is this close enough?
It'll work.
- Mr. White, let's go.
- Hold on.
- Let's just go!
- Hang on.
Mr. White, let's get out of here.
Just one minute.
- Turn it off! Turn it off.
- I will.
Jacocks! Jacocks, you okay?
Outside! Outside!
Yeah, bitch!
- Shut up.
- Yeah.
And what exactly are you celebrating?
You left the truck behind.
- So what?
- "So what"?
So what if they find prints?
And what if they trace it back
to the wrecking yard?
They won't.
There's no prints, I made sure of that.
There's no paperwork on the truck,
the magnet or the batteries.
Untraceable salvage, all of it.
I made sure of that too.
Well, you got all the answers.
So you tell me, Answer Man,
did all that even work just now?
Yes. It worked.
And I'm supposed to take that on faith?
Yeah? And why?
How do we know?
Because I say so.
07-66-26432.
Gutierrez, Alvin B.
Roofing hammer.
Undamaged. Bag still sealed.
11-58-73321.
Fring, Gustavo.
Samsung laptop computer.
Damaged. Glass screen
is broken and in pieces.
Bag still sealed.
11-58-73317.
Fring, Gustavo.
Framed photograph of two men.
Damaged.
The glass is broken,
and photo has slipped out of its frame.
Bag appears to be slightly punctured
by broken glass.
Check it out.
That's not on the manifest.
All right, so first off,
I'm not a marriage counselor.
Nor do I take sides in this thing.
And, not taking sides, mind you,
but you did put her in charge
of your money
which I advised against, if you'll recall
all of which is not to be construed
as an "I told you so."
I'm just walking you through
my mental process, so to speak.
So she comes to me with a problem.
That she's been cooking Beneke's books,
he's in Dutch with the IRS,
and once they audit,
it's Rio de Caca for the both of them.
To which I say, "Hey, let's involve Walt
in this discussion."
To which she says,
"No, let's cut Beneke a check
so's he can pay off the IRS."
Again, not taking sides,
but she really was trying to protect you.
A little feedback here might be nice.
"Let's involve Walt in this discussion."
Yeah, that's what I told her.
She said no.
And you didn't argue the point.
You didn't think to contact me.
You were a tad preoccupied at the time,
if you'll recall.
Okay. So you took it upon yourself
to give away $622,000 of my money
to a man who had been
sleeping with my wife.
She's my client, same as you.
Does this arrangement
get a little tricky at times?
Absolutely.
But I try my best, you know,
ethically, in my duty...
Ethically?
I'm sorry. I must be hearing things.
Did you actually just use
the word "ethically" in a sentence?
You're not Clarence Darrow, Saul.
You're a two-bit bus-bench lawyer.
And you work for me.
Yeah, well, Clarence Darrow
never had a client like you ask him,
for something
like this.
Okay? Yeah, I put my ass
on the line for you.
Huell too.
He's got fingers like hot dogs.
He could've easily busted this in two,
and killed everyone in the office.
But do I complain?
No. Beg, borrow or steal,
I'm your huckleberry.
I go the extra mile.
Only you never told me
that kid would wind up in the hospital.
You know...
Take that thing
and get the hell out of here.
You and me, we're done.
What are you...?
Come on. Hey.
Hey.
We're done when I say we're done.
Yes, you are. Yes.
Hey.
I heard what happened to Ted.
He's not gonna talk.
Yeah.
I forgive you.