No, no, no!
Hey.
It's me.
I wanted to say that I was thinking
about you and the kids.
I love you.
It's me.
I just wanted to say that I was thinking
about you and the kids, and...
- Morning.
- Afternoon.
Oh, really? Jesus.
You shouldn't have let me sleep.
You needed it.
Skyler, I don't entirely remember
what happened last night.
I mean, I might have said
some things that...
Did you know this Gale Boetticher person?
- Skyler, I can't even focus on...
- Gale Boetticher.
Did you know him?
My God. What...?
What exactly did I say last night?
Just enough.
Did you work together?
Who killed him?
Was it the people you work for?
Definitely not.
Was it somebody who
at some point,
might wanna do the same to you?
I seriously doubt it. No.
God.
Oh, God.
I think I know what happened
last night, Walt.
I know exactly what happened
last night. I drank too much wine.
You told Hank
that the man he was looking for
might still be out there.
That it might not be this Boetticher
after all.
And I was up all night, wondering
why you would say that to him.
Because I was drunk, Skyler.
No, but then I was remembering
your black eye.
Your business disagreement
that you don't wanna talk about.
Look, I don't want to talk
about any of this. Ever.
The firewall, all right?
Church and state.
That's how we need to approach
this thing.
And then I remembered the message
you left me the other day
when you said you loved me.
When I heard that,
I thought that maybe you...
I don't know, that you were regretting
what's happened between us.
And I get that.
After last night, I...
Walt, I think you're scared.
I think that message
was some kind of goodbye.
No, Skyler.
- I think last night was a cry for help.
- Oh, Jesus.
A cry for help?
I think some part of you
wants Hank to catch you.
That is just...
That is it exactly. Yes.
You're like Dr. Joyce Brothers here.
God.
At least this would all be over.
Yeah, yeah, oh, there's a tremendous
weight just lifted off of me.
Now I understand myself.
Thank you. Thank you.
Walt, I've said it before.
If you are in danger,
we go to the police.
- I don't wanna hear about the police.
- I do not say that lightly.
I know what it could do to this family.
But if it's the only real choice we have,
if it's either that or you getting shot...
I don't wanna hear about the police.
You're not some hardened criminal,
Walt. You are in over your head.
That's what we tell them, the truth.
- That is not the truth.
- Of course it is.
A schoolteacher, cancer,
desperate for money...
- We're done here.
- Roped into working... Unable to quit.
You told me that yourself, Walt.
Jesus, what was I thinking?
Walt, please.
Let's both of us stop trying
to justify this whole thing,
and admit you're in danger.
Who are you talking to right now?
Who is it you think you see?
Do you know how much I make a year?
I mean, even if I told you,
you wouldn't believe it.
You know what would happen
if I decided to stop going in to work?
A business big enough that it could be
listed on the NASDAQ goes belly up.
Disappears. It ceases to exist
without me. No.
You clearly don't know who you're
talking to, so let me clue you in.
I am not in danger, Skyler.
I am the danger.
A guy opens his door and gets shot,
and you think that of me? No.
I am the one who knocks.
Look, I was...
Skyler?
Here we are. Just like you left it.
And where is your pretty wife?
She has other business to attend to.
Well, like I say to her,
place sells as is. Understand?
Yes, I understand.
Good, good.
I don't want her coming back
with more demands.
She gave me hard time
when we settled on price.
We're all on the same page, Bogdan.
So here is everything you need.
- I keep very good files.
- Thank you.
So you are the boss now, huh?
You think you're ready?
Yes, I think so.
Being boss is tough.
I know you think I was hard on you,
but you'll learn.
Being in charge is not easy.
It takes hard work.
- You've seen me work hard, Bogdan.
- Yeah?
I don't know.
Not so much, maybe.
But maybe when you are the boss
you will just keep your feet up
and relax.
The real important thing...
And not everyone knows this.
...is to be tough.
Boss has to be tough.
Has to say no to people.
Has to make cashiers wipe down cars
even if they don't want to.
Can you be tough, Walter?
I am sure you can handle.
And if not,
you can always call your wife, no?
- Always sticky.
- Yeah.
No problem.
As is.
Who'd have thought that someday
I would be handing these keys to you?
Many years. Almost forgot.
Bogdan.
As is.
Thank you.
You okay there?
I'm fine.
Just not using is...
Eat something.
Yeah?
That's right, both of them.
All right.
I'm on my way.
You need any help?
No.
You want me to call her back?
No. No.
What exactly did she say?
I mean, exactly.
Just, you know, she asked if
I was okay and not to worry.
Like that.
Any rough timetable on this thing,
as to when she's coming home?
It's about the gambling, right?
Well, it's kind of hard to...
Dad, she can't understand.
It's not like you're doing this
on purpose. You can't help it.
It's not that simple.
Look, you have a disease.
It's like you're an alcoholic, right?
- No, it's not. Not at all.
- Yes, it is. I read online.
She's not even allowed to be mad at you.
She can't be mad at you
about the cancer, can she?
Son, these are two very different things.
Not really.
Gambling addiction is a sickness.
- You can't...
- Listen, what is going on with me
is not about some disease.
It's about choices.
Choices that I have made.
Choices I stand by.
You're not moving back in, are you?
No.
Hey, you know what?
School can wait.
Why don't we take a little detour?
What kind of detour?
You'll see.
Charlie, pick up line three.
Line three, Charlie.
I think it's time we got you
your own car. What do you think?
What?
I think if you're gonna buy me off
buy me off.
Get an attendant over to the lot.
- Amazing. It's amazing.
- Yeah. It's good-looking.
That's good. I'm glad you like it.
- I do. Thank you, Dad.
- All right. You're welcome.
So you're here.
Yeah.
You're actually here? To work?
Yeah, man. Jesus.
Jesse.
Come here.
- All right, I need an update.
- Update on what?
An update on these little field trips
that you've been taking with Mike.
I told you already. We pick up money.
Check on things. Stuff like that.
And you're his bodyguard, right?
What? That's what you said.
I said I guarded him.
Like backup, like a second set of eyes.
Everybody needs backup, right?
And this has to be you?
It can't be, I don't know, Tyrus or any
of the couple dozen muscle-heads
that Gus has working for him?
It has to be Jesse Pinkman.
Why? What, is there something
about you that I don't know?
Are you a former Navy SEAL?
Your hands registered as lethal weapons?
Register this.
All I'm saying is that
do you not even question this?
Do you really believe that you mean
anything to these people?
Not trying to insult. Just trying to
make you see things.
I see they can't outright kill me,
but they don't want me getting high.
I see this thing probably started
as Gus getting Mike to babysit me.
But you know what?
I saved Mike from getting robbed,
even killed, maybe.
So maybe I'm not such a loser after all.
I mean, what if it...? Oh, God.
- All right. What if it's all just a setup?
- What?
What if this robbery that you stopped
wasn't even real?
I mean, think about it.
Your first day out guarding Mike.
He steps out for one second
and what happens?
- You immediately get robbed.
- You are such an asshole.
Keep your friends close,
your enemies closer. Like you said
Gus can't kill you because of me,
he knows I won't stand for it.
He hates the fact that he needs me.
What does he do? He goes to work
driving a wedge between you and me.
If you'd been there,
you'd know it wasn't a setup.
Wait a minute. How long
did those guys chase you, huh?
Because the way you describe it,
they gave up pretty damn easy.
No, no, this whole thing, all of this
it's all about me.
Hello?
Look, just hang on.
Yeah?
I'll be right up.
- What?
- I gotta go.
What? Am I supposed to clean all this
on my own?
Hey.
God...
Buenos dias, ladies, buenos dias.
Do you speak English?
- No.
- No, okay.
Help, help.
I need help to clean. Yes.
- Yes, muy bueno. It's just this...
- No.
No, no, no.
No, no, ladies.
Let me see, let me see. I tell you what.
I tell you what. Look, look.
Universal language.
This one for you. Yeah, sí.
Sí, Presidente Grant.
Very important man.
Mas dinero after the...
Are we good?
I think we're good. I think we listened
to you. Please, por favor, por favor.
Please, por favor, por favor.
Yes.
What's the deal?
Well, the deal is,
we're watching that house.
Couple down on the left
with the tree in the front.
Yeah? What for?
A little birdie told me there's some guys
that have 3 pounds of our product
which they're selling.
And which they sure as hell
didn't get from us.
So, what's the plan?
I just told you.
We sit here and watch that house
until one of our entrepreneurs
pops his head out.
Then we ask a few questions
and get our property back.
Why don't you just go break the door down
pistol-whip those bitches
and show them who's boss?
Because a little birdie also told me
these guys are into the product,
and most likely armed.
Now, what you may not know
about meth-heads...
Or maybe you do.
They're kind of unpredictable.
I don't care for unpredictable.
So we wait.
Sorry to burst your bubble, kid,
but that's 90 percent of the job.
Don't worry. I brought sandwiches.
Yes, sir.
Pimento cheese. How's that sound?
Where you going?
You said they're selling right?
Maybe I'm looking to buy.
Who the hell are you?
- Tucker! Tucker!
- I'm here to buy.
- Will you shut the damn door?
- Not my question.
Name's Diesel. Heard you
maybe had some of the blue.
- Tucker. Shut the door, Tucker! Tucker!
- I just...
- Just looking for a teenth, yo.
- Tucker!
- Come on, help a brother out.
- Will you shut the damn door?
- We don't sell to strangers.
- Tucker!
- Get off the porch, asshole.
- Will you shut the door?
- All right already!
Tucker!
Guess we'll go with Plan A, then.
- Pop the trunk, would you?
- Why?
- There's something in there I need.
- And what would that be?
I'm getting those pricks
out of that house.
Oh, your first attempt
being such a wild success?
You may know this whole
PI sit-in-the-car business,
but I know meth-heads.
What are you doing?
Digging.
Why?
You know why.
How deep are you going?
I don't know.
How deep do you think it is?
Pretty deep.
Hey, you mind taking over for a minute?
Yeah, sure.
- Hey, mind if I use your john?
- Yeah.
Tucker.
Tucker!
Who the hell are you?
- I just...
- Who the hell are you?
It's cool. Hey, I'm a friend of Tucker's.
- What do you want?
- I just wanna buy some of the blue.
It's not for sale.
I know you were selling it earlier...
- Oh, yeah? How do you know that?
- Tucker told me.
Yeah, Tucker needs to learn
to keep his damn mouth shut.
Tucker! Tucker!
So you gonna hook me up?
Don't have enough for all
of Tucker's asshole friends. Tucker!
You know, I think he's outside.
You wanna just go outside...
- Tucker! Tucker!
- Hey, hey. Let's go find Tucker.
Okay? Let's go outside.
I don't have enough for you, all right?
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I get it. Okay.
- I don't wanna start any trouble.
- Trouble? What's that mean? Trouble?
No, no, no.
I'm just saying we're cool, okay?
- We're good.
- What?
You can't know that.
What does that mean?
You don't put thoughts in my head.
- Absolutely. You're right. You're right.
- Tucker?
You...
Here you go, Maria.
Veronica.
Ilia, gracias.
I missed that one.
I'm sure it was good.
Wait, where you taking them?
- Come on, Tyrus, what are you doing?
- I'm putting them on a bus.
- Why? What bus?
- One that takes them back to Honduras.
Hey, wait a second. Wait a minute.
Wait, wait. This was my idea.
Don't punish them.
You tell Gus to blame me, not them.
He does.
Give us a minute, will you?
We won't be too long.
The crew that hit our truck
gave away the cargo
to a couple local nobodies.
Very disciplined of them,
not keeping anything for themselves.
It was all about sending a message.
Which they did, literally.
It was written on the bucket lid.
"Ready to talk?"
That, I believe,
is the English translation.
I know you're not really asking
for advice.
But let me hire 10, 15 more
good operators.
Then we hit them hard.
Hit them where they live.
No. This war stays cold for now.
What about their message?
What's the answer?
Set up a meeting.
Let's see what they have to say.
How did he do today?
I hear you can handle yourself.
I guess.
Good night.
Hey, excuse me?
Why me?
I like to think I see things in people.
Slow down.
The car is not going anywhere.
- Mom.
- Hey, sweetheart.
- Hi.
- Hey.
- So did you see what's in the driveway?
- There you go.
Yeah, I saw.
Hey.
So that's yours, huh?
Yeah. Dad got it for me.
Well, that was very nice of him.
Yeah.
I know it looks like
well, awesome, but it's super safe.
Dad made sure.
And I promise
to always go the speed limit. Or below.
Way below.
And it gets great gas mileage.
So Dad said I can take it around
the block a few times. That okay?
Just around the block.
Yeah. Just around the block.
- And be careful, okay?
- I will.
Bye.
It's really... It's really great
to have you home, Mom.
Hey, seriously, be careful. Okay?
- I will.
- Okay.
I guess we should talk.
Well, I think you said plenty
the other day.
Look, about that, it just...
Did you get the car wash keys?
Yes. Yes. Here.
Skyler, I may have
overstated things earlier,
and I'm sorry to be so forward.
But I just...
I want you to know something.
I want you to...
I need you to understand
that you are safe.
You, Junior, Holly.
You are completely safe.
Everything that I do, everything
I do it to protect this family.
So buying that car,
that was protecting your family?
Okay. I...
All right, maybe it's a little flashy,
but he needed a car,
and I'm his father, and I should
be able to get what he wants.
It goes back.
Tomorrow.
Skyler, it will crush him.
That car directly contradicts our story.
And if you're so invested
in protecting this family
it means protecting the story.
What do you think the neighbors
are gonna say, Walt?
What about Hank and Marie?
How about the IRS?
What were you thinking, Walt?
I was thinking that I wanted
to do something nice for my son.
Look.
I just worry that he'll blame you
for this.
Oh, he will.
Once again, he'll blame his bitch mother,
for taking away
what his loving father has given him,
so thanks for that.
But you know what, Walt?
Someone has to protect this family
from the man who protects this family.