And when does Don Eladio arrive?
Let's see how the cook goes first.
Who's the chemist?
ls this a joke?
Okay, we've all met.
Let's get to work.
Please show him the phenylacetic acid.
We synthesize it ourselves.
All the ingredients are here.
What's the problem?
Mr. Pinkman was under the
impression that the phenylacetic acid...
...would already be synthesized upon his arrival.
Any sophomore chemistry student can make it.
What kind of amateur have you brought us?
This is ridiculous.
l'm not letting some infant...
...who can't even synthesize phenylacetic acid...
...teach me my business.
Clean up!
l'm so happy...
...you finally came to your senses.
May l present the cook.
Hello, young man.
He doesn't speak a word of Spanish, does he?
And he's no chemist...
...l'll tell you that.
l don't care if he's a pig farmer.
He cooks better meth than you do...
...with all your fancy college degrees.
And this one will have
plenty of time to learn Spanish.
What's in there?
A gift?
Gustavo, you're so generous.
lt's a token of respect.
ln honor of our renewed friendship.
Let's see what's in here.
No, impossible!
Zafiro Añejo!
Look at this.
Even the bottle is a work of art.
lt's perfection!
Perhaps...
...it's too good to share.
What do you think, Gustavo?
lt's yours to do with as you choose.
l choose...
...to drink it!
Good!
Hurry up, boys.
Careful.
That's beautiful stuff.
lf you spill a drop...
...l'll cut off your hand.
Come on, hurry up.
This one's an addict.
To work, he must be sober.
None for you!
Enough business!
Bring the girls!
Cheer up, man.
...l'm not angry.
l had to spank you.
But what choice did l have?
Look, once every 20 years...
...you forget your place.
There's no place for emotion in this.
You of all people should understand.
Business is business.
lf you'll excuse me.
Where are you going?
To use your bathroom.
lf l may.
Show Gustavo the pisser.
And make sure he doesn't get lost.
Hurry up.
Don Eladio is dead!
His capos are dead!
You have no one left to fight for!
Fill your pockets...
...and leave in peace!
Or fight me...
...and die!