Why?
Why is this stilI under discussion?
I don't like him.
I don't care who he knows.
We're supposed to trust him with our products.
Big man.
Big Generalissimo!
Big fry cook is more like it.
The "Chicken Man."
You wiIl do what you want.
But you have my vote.
Never trust a South American.
Dirty, dirty people.
He broke my toy! He broke my toy!
He was just having fun.
You'll get over it.
No! I hate him! I wish he was dead!
Grab your oId uncle a beer, would you?
No, no. A cold one.
This is what you wanted.
Your brother dead. Right?
You're going to have to try harder than that...
...if you want to save him.
How much longer do you think he has down there?
One minute? Maybe more? Maybe less?
Family is all.
Finish him.
Too easy.