So cigarettes and gas is $79.70.
Crap.
There's an ATM right outside.
Yeah, I don't have a card.
Well, you can write a personal check
with ID.
Kind of in between banks right now.
You think I could just come back later?
I'm totally good for it.
I'd come back, I swear.
If it were me, I'd be totally,
you know, "No problem."
But my dad is this ginormous hard-ass.
He was in Fallujah for a year.
And he always checks the receipts.
I mean, like, always.
I gotta call him. I'm sorry.
Wait, wait, wait.
Hold on a second.
Maybe we could
trade.
Ever try it?
I mean, I smoke pot a lot sometimes.
I party.
But...
- But that stuff's really addictive, right?
- Not really.
It's just a media thing. You know?
What's it like?
It's awesome.
Everything's maximum interesting.
You get these really cold
and sharp-like action dagger feelings.
It's awesome.
Come on. What do you say?
Have a nice day.
So how does it feel?
Does it hurt?
Yeah, it's tight.
- Yeah, but is it painful?
- It's hard to breathe.
Well, you need your breathing.
Although let's not lose sight of the fact
that you were the victim
of a terrible accident, Antonio,
so some discomfort is to be expected.
Let's go with that one.
A cashier's check, por favor.
Oh, and spread the word.
I'm building a class-action, flight 515.
Victims' families would be great.
I'll take anyone on the ground
who suffered emotionally.
Anxiety, sleeplessness.
You get the picture.
Trouble?
Ted Beneke? You cannot be serious.
- That guy is a joke.
- You know what? You called my bluff.
What does that even mean?
You dared me to tell the police
and I couldn't do it, so you win.
If you want to stay in this house, fine,
but we are not married anymore.
I told you that
I was done cooking meth, Skyler.
- I promised you that.
- So what?
You know what?
At least I didn't run off to go...
Jesus! I mean, everything that I did,
I did for this family.
- Just keep telling yourself that.
- What is that supposed to mean?
You don't like it, then leave.
- And take your drug money with you.
- That's what you want.
- Jesus.
- Garbage disposal.
You think this will get me to move out?
You can screw Ted. You can screw
the butcher, the mailman.
- God, Walt.
- Whoever you want.
Screw them all.
I'm not going anywhere.
Suit yourself.
Is this a good or bad thing?
Suit myself.
You want me to suit myself?
I'll suit myself to his face!
It's a bad thing.
Hello.
Walter White to see Ted Beneke.
I'm sorry.
Mr. Beneke's on a conference call.
Okay. I will wait.
It could be a while.
I have all the time in the world.
Okay.
- Here we go. Okay.
- Excuse me.
- Mr. Beneke's not available.
- Ted? Come on.
Sir, excuse me.
Excuse me.
Ted, I can see you.
I can see you standing right there
in your office.
Now, come on.
Open the door. Come on, let's talk.
I just want to talk. That's all.
Come on, let's be men about this.
Okay? How about that?
Hey, Walt. I'm kind of in the middle
of something now.
Oh, yes, you are.
So open the door.
You're damn right.
You're right in the middle.
Just open the door
and let's talk about it, okay?
Open the door, Ted, right now.
You don't want to be a man about it?
Plan B. How do you like that? Plan B.
We have a situation.
Walt. Walt. Walt.
What are you doing?
I'm talking with Ted.
Next time, you'll open the door.
- Freeze! Come on.
- Oh, damn it.
No, I'm just here to talk.
- I just want to talk to him.
- Outside. Let's go.
God. Can I just talk?
I just want to talk to him.
- Calm down.
- I'm just... Okay, all right.
All right, all right, all right.
I'm calm. I'm calm.
Asshole.
What do you want?
Hey! Hey, come on.
What the hell is wrong with you?
You act like you're the first guy
this happened to.
I caught my second wife screwing
my stepdad, okay?
It's a cruel world, Walt. Grow up.
- I just wanted to talk to him.
- Yeah, well, now I'm talking to you.
Consider this an intervention.
You could have been arrested
back there. You understand.
Speaking as your lawyer,
I'm always looking for billable hours.
But speaking as your business associate
I'm strongly advising
that you get your shit together.
Just cool it with this Beneke guy,
at least for now. Okay?
Let's talk shop, because
I think this is a great opportunity
to channel some of that negative
energy into something positive.
- How did you know?
- Sorry?
About Skyler.
About where to find me just now.
How did you know?
That's just my meticulousness.
Don't bog down in detail, Walt.
- The lesson here should be...
- Did you bug my house?
Yeah, but I didn't know it was
your house, did I?
You'd moved out.
Besides, you basically told me to.
- I told you to?
- You strongly hinted that I should.
You were worried your wife might say
something to the police.
What? No, no, that's not true.
When the hell did I say that?
Let's not get lost in the who,
what and whens.
The point is we did our due diligence
and she didn't talk.
She kept quiet.
She stood by you, Walt
which, if you ask me,
is the ironical silver lining here.
I mean, on the one hand
sure, she snuck off the reservation
to get some dirty, damp and deep.
On the other hand...
Off me.
You're fired!
- You're done!
- Good!
"Oh, boohoo,
I won't cook meth anymore."
You're a crybaby. Who needs you?
I'm unplugging the website,
so no more money laundering.
How do you like that?
I want those bugs out of my house today.
I want them out now!
You just bought a $300 suit, psycho!
Go.
Great, drilled right into the stucco.
A little bit of putty, you'll be fine.
Just make sure
you get all of those things.
A, these things cost $800 apiece.
B, you're not that interesting.
So yeah, I'll get all of them, Walter.
Great line of work, by the way.
Real upstanding field.
Yeah, well
I enjoy it.
You're free to leave now. Anytime.
You know, Walter
sometimes it doesn't hurt
to have someone watching your back.
Mr. White?
Hi.
What's up?
I can't begin to understand
what you're going through, Walt
with all of your health concerns
and the stresses you've been under.
But still, as educators
there are certain responsibilities
we need to be meeting here
to the school
and to the students themselves.
Of course.
Is this a wheaten terrier?
Norfolk.
Norfolk?
That's surprising.
Walt, could you come back over here
and have a seat, please?
Sure.
You've been absent a lot recently.
And when you are here at school, there
have been some behavioral questions.
And frankly I'm concerned.
Thank you.
Are you feeling okay?
Do you think maybe I should call Skyler?
No.
Let's just keep this...
What...?
Hey!
Walt, what's wrong with you?
You know, look, you're the one
always talking about D.C., okay?
This is how you get there.
You answer the bell.
You pay your dues.
Besides, you know,
it's a big deal to get picked for this.
El Paso's like the Super Bowl.
I could get killed crossing the street,
okay?
Whatever. You know, I want to go.
What about last time?
Schrader.
Hey, sheriff. Yeah.
Blue, huh?
Yeah, yeah. Thing is...
Thing is I'm supposed to be getting
on a plane right now.
The stuff this guy had was blue.
You sure about that?
Yeah.
Yeah, I want to talk to him.
Taxi.
- Hi.
- Man, I'm sorry.
I needed to talk to you,
but you weren't at your apartment.
No, I moved back home.
That's good, right?
Yeah.
- Yo, did you just get fired?
- No.
No, no, no.
It's more like a sabbatical.
Indefinite. Yeah.
So, what's up?
Should we go somewhere?
No, this is fine.
So I want an intro to your guy.
What guy?
Your guy. Your distribution guy.
The guy Saul hooked you up with.
No, no, no. Come on, Jesse.
- I thought about it and I want to.
- God.
It's the one thing I'm good at.
No, that is just not true.
You're good at a lot of things, son.
Like what?
What about your sobriety?
I told you, I'm not using.
Ever.
I just want back into the business.
Well, I don't. I'm sorry.
I know, and that's cool.
I'm not asking you to cook.
What's this?
In the end, I just went with
two reflux condensers.
I didn't want to lose track
of my pH levels.
But I did everything else
just like you taught me.
Super careful in my amounts,
and watched the numbers
every step of the way.
So, what do you think?
It's good, right?
What in the hell is this?
- What?
This. This. This is my product.
This is my formula. This is mine.
It's our product,
but yeah, I was gonna cut you in.
Oh, you were gonna cut me in?
No, no, no. I cut you in.
What the hell is your problem?
All I'm asking is for you to set a meet.
- Absolutely not.
- Why?
Because I am not gonna lend my name
to an inferior product.
I mean, look at the diameters here.
What did you use for reduction?
Don't tell me. Platinum dioxide, right?
No. Mercury-aluminum amalgam.
The dioxide's too hard to keep wet.
All right, well,
you must've done it wrong, then.
Your color is all cloudy, so you were
struggling with distillation too.
Now, this is very shoddy work, Pinkman.
I'm actually embarrassed for you.
What?
No way. I gave out samples
and everyone said it was the bomb.
Oh, they said it was the bomb.
And who were they, I wonder?
A bunch of meth heads?
- Yeah.
- They should know, right?
- Yeah, well, sorry.
- I can't help you.
- Fine, ass-wad.
- I'll contact the guy myself.
- Oh, yeah? Well, good luck.
Because my guy is a pro
and he doesn't deal with junkies.
- You know what? Eat me.
- Anytime, loser.
Hey, hey, hey!
Wait. Hey!
I can't believe it's only 4:00.
This day is dragging.
Okay.
I wish I could stay.
So stay.
What's stopping you?
What, like everything, you mean?
How about my lunatic husband
refusing to leave the house?
So move in here.
And then my son hating me even more.
That'll pass.
I went through that with the girls.
They adapt.
And now everyone at work thinks
I'm an evil ladder-climbing whore.
They're all fired, effective immediately.
What else?
Oh, aren't you the answer man?
Where did it...?
Where did it go wrong, exactly,
with you and Walt?
I mean, I always saw him as kind of...
mild-mannered.
Something, I don't know,
change when he got sick or...?
I don't know what changed, Ted.
And I just don't feel really comfortable
talking about it.
Sorry.
Just asking out of self-interest.
Gotta make sure
I don't make the same mistake.
I would be amazed.
Just let me see if
I'm following you here, Russell.
You got this stuff from some guy
at Gasparza's
who was wearing tan pants,
and who you're 80 percent sure
had a mustache.
That's it, right?
That's your brain
working at maximum capacity?
Russell.
Everything all right in there?
Mel. The dude's name was Mel.
Well, there you go. See?
You served an actual earthly function.
I can't believe I remembered that.
Mel who?
Does he have a last name?
Yeah, Mel.
Wait.
Was it Mel,
or Mark?
It was definitely an M name.
Oh, man, I'm losing it.
Wait, wait.
Yeah.
It's gone.
- It was an M name though.
- Yeah.
I remember the... sound.
All right, well,
we'll go with the... sound.
- Thanks a lot. Appreciate it.
- Yeah.
He definitely had tan pants.
Remind me to get a vasectomy.
Okay, it's after 9,
so this bar that Girl George is at
probably wall-to-wall dirtbags by now.
Let's go have a little looky-loo,
see if we can't find this M-named clown.
What? It's a lead.
- Lead to what?
- To Heisenberg.
I told you it was only a matter of time
before this guy booted up again.
Here we go, my friend.
Don't hate me because I'm beautiful,
Gomey.
Just apologize and buy me a beer.
Man, you're reaching.
This stuff could be a knockoff
or left over from an older cook.
How do you know Heisenberg's
gearing up again?
How do I know?
Because I know.
I don't get it.
This is the reason why
you're blowing off the task force?
Chase down teeners?
I'm getting tired
of all the second-guessing.
If you're not sufficiently stimulated
by this investigation
do us both a favor
and ask for a transfer.
What is up with you lately?
Starting bar fights,
turning down El Paso,
and now this bullshit?
Do you need to talk to someone or what?
Talk to someone?
Talk to who?
I'm not trying to step on your toes,
bro. Okay?
I'm just worried about you.
That's all.
Appreciate that, bro.
Now take your hand off my shoulder.
Yeah, yeah, the one that was on TV.
Did any little piece
fall on your property?
I'm not looking for an entire wing here,
Mr. Linkas.
It could be a nut or a bolt.
It could be a bag of peanuts
just so long as it caused you
pain and suffering.
Oh, no, no, no. Closed.
Calling you back.
You had your chance.
I told you to get him cooking again.
You blew it off and now it's too late.
The guy's gone mass maniac on us!
All I wanted was to show you two
your potential.
And what do I get in return?
A bone contusion.
You wanna see the scar?
I wish you two had...
Hi, there.
- How in the hell did you get Walt to...?
- I made it.
You know the guy
who knows the guy, right?
Well, good news is,
for a stage-three cancer,
the guy's doing well physically.
Mentally, the guy's a disaster.
He's gone off the rails
over this thing with his wife.
My opinion, he's not coming back.
Not on his own.
Your friends were at his place again,
by the way.
They drew something on the street
outside his house.
- The scythe.
- Animals.
- Does the lawyer know?
- Should he?
No.
If you want this guy to produce again,
why not just tell him?
You stand between him
and an ax in the head.
I don't believe fear
to be an effective motivator.
I want investment.
For now, I'm simply interested
in time frame.
He will live for the foreseeable future,
yes?
Foreseeable. Couple years at least,
barring acts of God and men with axes.
From the lawyer,
I'm supposed to let you know
the Pinkman kid is looking to sell.
- I don't work with junkies.
- That's what I thought you'd say.
Probably for the best.
What I hear,
he and Walter are splitsville.
Really?
That's what Goodman says.
Cats and dogs.
Do the deal.
You have one unheard message.
Agent Schrader, you need
to be calling me back ASAP.
I've got Texas breathing down
my neck and I'm not about...
No, I haven't seen Matt since my dad
fired him, like, a while ago.
Where can I find him, you think?
- No idea. Haven't seen him.
- I know. You said that a few times.
Yeah, because I haven't seen him.
I don't know what else to say.
- What's your name, darling?
- Cara.
Where did this come from, Cara?
I don't know.
What is it? Drugs?
Look, I'm just gonna come right out
and say it.
You're a bad liar, Cara.
Don't get me wrong.
Not the worst I've ever seen.
Once had a guy try to explain the dope
balloon up his butt on bad Thai food.
Still, you're not a very good liar.
- I honestly don't know...
- Stop.
You look like a good kid.
I'm not here to get you in trouble.
But you need to tell me
where this came from right now!
I never do stuff like this.
I swear to God.
I tried it and I hated it,
so I just gave it to Matt.
- Okay, and who gave it to you?
- Some guy.
He came in a couple days ago
and wanted to trade it for gas.
Some guy? What's his name?
Okay, what...? What did he look like?
I don't know.
He looked pretty normal.
You know, white.
I think his hair was lightish brown.
He had really blue eyes.
They were really, really blue.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, dreamy.
Okay, what else?
Piercings, jewelry, distinctive
articles of clothing. Come on.
Come on.
Listen to me.
It's real important that I find the person
that had these drugs.
So if you can remember anything else...
Come on, think.
Come on, now. Come on.
He drove an RV.
Okay, good, good.
What can you remember?
What kind of RV?
What color?
Did you spot a license plate?
I don't know the kinds
and I didn't see the license.
But the color was,
I think, white, brownish color.
I'm sorry.
I know I'm not helping you...
but, please, don't tell my dad.
Cara.
Please, tell me that that camera works.
Damn it.
Bingo.
These eggs are good, Mom.
Thanks.
Hey, you know what's weird?
Dad's website.
It's been three days
since the last donation.
Yeah, well, people lose interest.
So how long are you off for?
A few weeks.
I'll play it by ear.
I probably pushed it, you know,
going back to work too soon.
Think I can get a ride today?
Louis has a doctor's appointment.
Yeah.
Hey, so, Dad can babysit now, right?
You won't have to take Holly
to work every day.
Sometime, maybe.
Yeah, we'll see.
What's up?
I think you'll seriously enjoy, yo.
Wait. No, no. No way.
Hey! Hey!
Hey. What the hell? This is only half.
That's right. It's your half.
Yo, where's the other half, bitch?
I mean, the whole thing was crazy.
Poor bastard. I felt sorry for him.
I think he actually thought
we were the cable guys, you know.
Anyway, sorry about
those missed calls, chief.
I'm changing providers.
It won't happen again.
Are you going to El Paso, Hank?
Hell, yes.
With pointy boots and bells on.
Got this break in the Heisenberg case.
The blue meth, you mean?
The teenth?
Yeah, well,
that teenth got things rolling.
I traced it to a gas station in Cibola.
That's where I got these.
The station's closed-circuit was down...
Surprise, surprise.
...but I was able to pull some of these
snapshots off an ATM security camera.
We always thought these guys
might be camper-cooking.
First off, your typical Class C
motor home
is gonna grunt at least 5000 pounds
of interior fixtures.
Appliances, furniture, built-ins,
5000 pounds at least, okay?
See how high that suspension's riding?
No way, no how, this thing's carrying
that kind of weight.
This thing has been cleared out and
stripped down to its tight-and-curlies.
For what? Blood bank?
Maybe a bookmobile?
There's no clear view of the plates.
Yeah, well, you can only get
so lucky, right?
But there's no front plate. Tells me
it's likely New Mexico registration.
I check with DMV.
There are only 29 of these early-'80s
Bounders registered in the state.
- Only 29?
- Yeah.
So I gotta go, you know,
knock on some doors.
They need you in El Paso, Hank.
You bet. I'm just gonna wrap up
this Heisenberg thing first.
- You're refusing the assignment.
- I'm not. I'll go.
It's just I need some more time.
You're not hearing me, Agent Schrader.
You're out of time.
Are you going to El Paso now, tonight?
It's a simple yes or no.
No. I can't.
But that's only because
I'm really close to something big here.
Better get to it, then.
This is KECA 480,
Albuquerque's news radio.
KECA news time, 10:13.
Our top story this hour, Donald Margolis
the air-traffic controller criticized
for his role in the recent air disaster
in which 167 persons died
was rushed to an area hospital
early this morning
apparently the victim of
a self-inflicted gunshot wound.
Police won't say whether or not...
Your half.
Okay, okay.