Hey, Mr. White. It's me.
I know you're probably
real busy with retirement,
but I got some news I think
you should maybe know about.
Me and Declan had some
differences of opinion,
and it got a little
messy.
It's all straightened out now,
but just a heads-up, there's been
a kind of change in management.
Anyway, just thought you should know.
Feel free to give me a call
if you want the details,
but, you know, it's cool, so whatever.
Okay, then. Thanks. Bye.
Right, so there I am,
I'm on top of the train
pumping the water in, he's watching
to make sure we put in
exactly what he'd calculated.
We gotta be real precise because
water and methylene weigh different,
and he figured it all out to,
like, milliliter.
I'm up there with my hose
we're going as fast as we can.
We only got a few minutes.
At the crossing, we got this guy
who's smooth-talking the engineer.
And it's all just going great
until this other dude shows up
in this monster truck,
so we're pretty much screwed,
because he can just push
the entire dump truck off the tracks,
which, you know, is what he does.
Wait. What's your guy doing?
- You can't stop him?
- Yeah, but what's he gonna say?
"Thanks anyway, sir, but my friends
are still stealing cargo back there."
So I'm looking all around,
because I know we're not done,
but the gallons are slowly ticking away.
And finally Mr. White
tells me to cut it.
So I fling the hose, I'm grabbing the cap,
I'm screwing in the bolts.
Just, like, busting ass, you know?
And then I feel the train start moving
and I'm...
- You're...
- I'm on top.
- Did you piss your pants?
- Yeah, right?
So the thing starts speeding up,
so I jump off the moving train.
Like, total stuntman stuff.
It's like Hooper. You ever see Hooper?
Oh, hey, man, Burt Reynolds.
Good movie.
He jumped out of a helicopter,
not a train.
Whatever, man. It's a good movie.
This guy Jesse, he's underneath,
and the train just drives right over him.
And luckily he's this skinny little guy.
Damn. That's a tight operation.
It was perfect.
No one even knew they got robbed,
just like we planned.
Mr. White told me it was, like,
the biggest train heist ever
like, potential money-wise.
So that's how that happened.
Can I get you anything else?
Nope. Thanks, darling.
I'm ready for the check.
You feeling good about cooking?
Yeah.
You'll be able to run your own lab?
- Do it up right?
- Yeah. For sure. I got this.
All right.
Let's make some money, then.
I gotta hit the head.
Ever been on a plane and find yourself
looking down at the armrest next to you
looking at the little plug
where the ashtray used to go?
I look at that and I say,
"What the hell happened to this country?"
Nanny state.
I see a kid with a bicycle helmet on
I wanna smack the shit out of him,
like, for his own good.
Mr. Pinkman.
How are you today?
Not so good, huh?
Of course, I might be able
to help you out.
I wanna talk to you about
your partner, Heisenberg.
See, I know he's my brother-in-law, Walt.
Oh, yeah. That's the look.
Lucky for you,
I'm more interested in him.
So I got an offer.
If you help me out here
tell me all about you and him
and your little meth business
maybe I talk to my friends
at the A.P.D,
and make all this go away.
I know he's the mastermind here.
Plus
I'm thinking,
based on your recent activities
that maybe there's a little trouble
in paradise?
Maybe you guys aren't
getting along so good?
I'm right, aren't I?
Eat me.
Sure that's how you want to play this?
Why don't you try and beat it out of me?
That's your thing, right?
He really did a number on you, didn't he?
I don't know,
but happy people usually don't go around
throwing millions of dollars away.
I don't think
Walt's gonna be patting you
on the back for that.
But maybe that's the point.
But, you see, I get that.
My own brother-in-law
lying to me for over a year.
Using me.
Maybe you understand that feeling.
Help me out here, Jesse,
and we can put him away.
I know you want that.
I think you wanna talk.
Not to you.
Agent Schrader,
beat any good suspects lately?
Tall and taller, ask him
about his history with my client.
He knocked the poor kid unconscious
last time they were alone.
So, what'll it be, a civil rights
lawsuit the size of Montana?
Because I'll oblige you.
So long, Rocky. Keep your left up.
Detectives, I'm inviting you to leave.
I'm gonna try to remain calm,
but will you do me a favor
and tell me what is up with you?
My guys are busting their asses
trying to hide Walt's money
from the feds,
and you're tossing yours out a window?
And I have to hear about your little act
of philanthropy on the news?
Did you hit your head or something?
Why didn't you call me
the second you got arrested?
What did you say to Schrader?
Nothing. Jesus. Just chill out.
Chill out? No.
No, I don't chill out right now
because things have gone nuclear.
I imagine Schrader shared
with you his recent discovery.
Okay, well, then you get
my complete lack of chill.
Just use the money that I gave you.
No, Saul. Saul, I...
Stop... Saul. Stop talking. I don't care.
Just... Just make it happen.
Work your magic.
And call me when he's out.
Hey, Dad, I'm home.
Oh, okay. I'll be right out.
Hey, you going to work today?
You were out late last night.
I... Well, I...
Yeah, I guess I just lost track of time.
Dad.
I'm gonna head out, okay?
- Where you going?
- Aunt Marie just called.
She wants me to help her
with some computer thing,
and asked me to stay for dinner.
That cool?
- I guess that...
- Cool. All right, see you later.
Wait, son?
- Junior. Hang on a second.
- Yeah?
- Oh, good. Come on back inside.
- What happened?
Oh, this? Nothing.
No, I'm fine. It's fine.
Really. I do wanna talk to you, though.
Okay. Are you okay?
Yeah. Here. Sit down a second.
I just don't wanna keep things
from you, okay?
I mean, you deserve to know
what's happening.
Yesterday, I passed out.
Briefly. Very, very briefly.
And I did this.
Why did you pass out?
Well, my latest scans
show a little shadow on my lung.
But my doctor put me right on
a new round of chemo
which is why I've been so tired lately.
But I was pushing myself too hard.
I know it.
I just don't want you to worry.
I learned my lesson.
Well, what's the...?
What now?
What now is that we go on,
like always. Right?
Hey, don't worry about this, okay?
I know that's hard, but I beat this once.
There's no reason to think I won't again.
And my doctor says I'm doing great.
I'm responding really well
to the treatment.
And I'm...
I'm feeling very...
Very good about this, all right?
And what would really help me out
is if we all stayed positive.
Can we do that?
Yeah?
Okay.
So why don't you go
and help your Aunt Marie,
- and we'll talk about this later.
- No. No. No way.
I'm staying. I'm not leaving.
- Flynn is not with you, is he?
- No.
No. Why would he be?
How'd it go?
That bad, huh?
How bad are we talking, Hank?
I didn't tell them.
Why not?
- It's just not time yet.
- No, it's past time.
Way past time. We talked about this.
You've got to tell them now.
It's gonna be worse
if they find out that
you've kept this from them.
Look, it's just I've got some things
I gotta chase down.
What? What things?
- Leads, you know.
- What leads? What? Something new?
I'm not keeping anything
from anybody, Marie, okay? Jesus.
Don't tell me how to do my job.
Walt.
Are you sure about this?
It's the only way.
Okay.
I'm ready.
My name is Walter Hartwell White.
I live at 308 Negra Arroyo Lane
Albuquerque, New Mexico, 87104.
This is my confession.
They're here.
Thank you for coming.
Okay, I'll start.
- Skyler and I...
- Welcome to Garduño's.
My name is Trent.
I'll be taking care of you.
Can I start anybody off
with some beverages?
Margarita? How about some
of our tableside guacamole?
I think we're fine.
We need some time with the menu.
No worries.
Be right back with some water.
So you here to confess?
There's nothing to confess.
We're here to talk about Walter, Jr.
Flynn and Holly should be living
with us. End of story.
And while we respect your opinion
we think that your concern is misplaced.
Skyler and I feel, due to Marie's attempt
- to lure him to your house...
- I wasn't trying to lure him.
Regardless of what you might call it
Skyler and I would like to ask you
to please leave our children out of this.
Junior has been through
a lot already this year.
You are just...
This investigation, Hank
do you realize what this will do to him?
Hearing these things?
He's gonna hear it when I kick in
your front door and arrest you.
If that day ever comes, so be it.
You have no evidence
to support your claims.
Why tear this family apart?
So how about that guacamole?
We make it right here at the table.
I'll just give you guys
a few more minutes.
How can you sit there and listen to this?
All we want is for those kids to be safe.
You're putting them in danger,
keeping them under the same roof...
They are safe, Marie.
- You yourself sent them out of the house.
- And I brought them back.
Look, whatever you think he did
this is not an ongoing situation.
- Skyler.
- No.
They need to understand.
It's in the past.
It's over.
There is nothing to go after here.
- There's nothing to accomplish.
- How can we believe anything you say?
There's no telling
where the lies begin and end.
That affair of yours,
did that even happen?
Please. Look, Junior just found out
that my cancer is back.
He's already facing the idea
of living without his father.
To put this on top of that?
It's just not right.
I swear to God, you start
throwing the word "right" at me...
- What I mean...
- Was it right to run a drug empire?
There is no drug empire.
Lying to your son,
to all of us, is that right?
What do I have to do
to make you believe me?
Why don't you kill yourself, Walt?
- What?
- Just kill yourself.
This whole thing dies with you.
That's what you're saying here?
Is that Hank should just let it go
and wait for you to die.
Well, maybe you should just
go ahead and die, then.
- That is not a solution.
- No, it's not a solution.
- He's not getting off that easy.
- Jesus, Hank.
And the same goes for you
if you stick with him.
Both of you think you're just gonna
walk away from this thing?
Never gonna happen.
- That is not what we're saying.
- Enough with the bullshit.
You're not gonna negotiate
your way out of this thing.
There's only one solution: Step up,
be a man and admit what you've done.
That's it. There is no other option.
Let's go.
My name is Walter Hartwell White.
I live at 308 Negra Arroyo Lane
Albuquerque, New Mexico, 87104.
This is my confession.
If you're watching this tape
I'm probably dead
murdered by my brother-in-law,
Hank Schrader.
Hank has been building a meth empire,
for over a year now
and using me as his chemist.
Shortly after my 50th birthday
he asked that I use
my chemistry knowledge
to cook methamphetamine,
which he would then sell
using connections that he made
through his career with the DEA.
I was astounded.
I... I always thought Hank
was a very moral man,
and I was particularly
vulnerable at the time
something he knew and took advantage of.
I was reeling from a cancer diagnosis
that was poised to bankrupt my family.
Hank took me on a ride-along
and showed me just how much money
even a small meth operation could make.
And I was weak.
I didn't want my family
to go into financial ruin,
so I agreed.
Hank had a partner, a businessman
named Gustavo Fring.
Hank sold me into servitude to this man,
and when I tried to quit,
Fring threatened my family.
I didn't know where to turn.
Eventually, Hank and Fring
had a falling out,
and things escalated.
Fring was able to arrange
I guess...
I guess you call it a hit on Hank.
It failed,
but Hank was seriously injured,
and I wound up paying his medical bills
which amounted to a little over $177,000.
Upon recovery, Hank was bent on revenge.
Working with a man named Hector Salamanca
he plotted to kill Fring.
The bomb that he used was built by me.
He gave me no option in that.
I have often contemplated suicide,
but I'm a coward.
I wanted to go to the police,
but I was frightened.
Hank had risen to become the head
of the Albuquerque DEA.
To keep me in line, he took my children.
For three months he kept them.
My wife had no idea
of my criminal activities
was horrified to learn what I had done.
I was in hell.
I hated myself for what
I had brought upon my family.
Recently, I tried once again to quit,
and in response, he gave me this.
I can't take this anymore.
I live in fear every day
that Hank will kill me,
or worse, hurt my family.
All I could think to do
was to make this video,
and hope that the world
will finally see this man,
for what he really is.
Who do you think he's shown this to?
No one. It's a threat.
It's what he will do if I don't back off.
I think you should show this to Ramey.
Just get ahead of it.
That video is a bunch of lies, Hank.
Anybody who knows you will know.
A hundred and seventy-seven
thousand dollars?
Hell is he talking about?
Marie?
They told me it was gambling money.
What was gambling money?
Oh, Jesus Christ, Marie.
- Oh, God, no.
- How was I supposed to know?
How was I to know where it came from?
Why were they paying for my bills?
What about my insurance?
Insurance wouldn't have covered
the treatment you needed, and I...
- I wanted the best for you.
- Why didn't you tell me?
Because I knew that you would refuse it,
and without it, you may never
have been able to walk again.
Oh, Christ, Marie.
You killed me here.
I mean, it's the... It's the last nail.
That's the last nail in the coffin.
What do we do?
If I were you, I'd be more nervous.
Jesus.
It's always the desert.
I already checked it.
It's clean. I wouldn't have
driven it here if it wasn't.
Get one of these, by the way.
Reads radio signals. Much easier.
What does he know?
I mean, he knows you're Heisenberg.
But I figure not much else
otherwise, you know, you'd be locked up.
What did he say exactly?
He wants me to inform on you for him.
Tell him everything we did.
Anything else?
I don't think he's told
the rest of the DEA.
Why do you say that?
Just him being there all by himself,
and, plus, he was acting kind of shady.
Seemed like he didn't want the other cops
hearing what he had to say.
Are we gonna talk about the rain of caca
the kid brought down upon us?
Want to hazard a guess
what his little charity drive cost you?
Why don't you go take a walk, Saul?
Jesse, will you let me help you?
I don't like to see you hurting like this.
Maybe it's time for a change.
What kind of change?
I don't know.
I don't know, maybe...
Maybe it's time for you to just
leave all of this behind.
Just get out of town.
Don't look back.
Saul knows a man.
He specializes in giving people
new identities.
He would move you someplace far away,
and set you up with a whole new life.
Yeah, I know, sounds a little extreme.
But maybe it's exactly what you need.
You know, I really think
that would be good for you.
A clean slate.
All right, just think about it.
You get a job, something legitimate,
something you like.
Meet a girl, start a family, even.
Hell, you're still so damn young.
And what's here for you now anyway?
I tell you, if I could, I'd trade places.
A whole lifetime ahead of you
with a chance to hit the reset button.
In a few years
this might all feel like nothing more
than a bad dream.
Would you just, for once
stop working me?
What are you talking about?
Can you just stop working me for, like,
10 seconds straight?
Stop jerking me around?
Jesse, I am not working you.
Yes. Yes, you are.
All right, just drop the whole
concerned-dad thing,
and tell me the truth.
I mean, you're acting like
me leaving town is all about me,
and turning over a new leaf,
but it's really... It's really about you.
I mean, you need me gone
because your dickhead brother-in-law
is never gonna let up.
Just say so.
Just ask me for a favor.
Just tell me you don't give a shit
about me,
and it's either this...
It's either this or you'll kill me
the same way you killed Mike.
I mean, isn't that
what this is all about?
Us meeting way the hell out here.
In case I say no.
Come on.
Just tell me you need this.
Your change.
If you'll hand this
to your car wash professional,
and have an A-1 day.
Skyler?
Skyler, I've got my chemo
in about 45 minutes.
Can you take over the register for me?
Skyler?
It worked,
and we're fine.
Okay?
We're fine.
So Palmer and Castanares
are sitting on that jerkoff
Saul Goodman's office
- keeping an eye on Jesse Pinkman.
- Yeah, I put them on it.
You wanna explain that to me?
Yeah. Right.
Why the hell should I know anything?
They're just my guys, after all.
You gotta tell me what's going on.
Pinkman is A.P.D.'s problem, not ours.
You got a history with this kid.
If he catches wind
that you're trailing him,
and this explodes, he could sue.
Look, if I can't explain this to Ramey,
I gotta pull my guys.
Fine. Take them off.
I said, take them off.
What else you want?
I'm going out for a while.
You have that 3:00.
Will you be back?
You know what, it's gonna have
to be another day. Reschedule it.
Last chance. You sure there's nobody
you wanna say bye to?
Nobody at all?
No.
This is it. Once I make the call,
there's no take-backs.
I need a new dust filter,
for my Hoover Max Extract
Pressure Pro, model 60.
Can you help me with that?
Yeah, pickup.
He's hot. Not "hot" hot,
just a little hot.
Currently out on bail.
Yeah, he knows the rules.
One hour. Okay, he'll be there.
And done.
Okay, this guy's fee is 125.
Your benefactor
asked me to send you out
with something extra.
Get you started, you know?
Keep you sitting pretty
until you get into the groove
of your new life.
Provided, of course, you don't
toss it out the window on the way.
Seriously, this is the last of it,
so you might wanna think
about making a budget.
Hey, what are you doing?
You can't fire up a doob in here.
Put that out.
I mean it. Put it out.
Look, Mr. Natural, I'm not
gonna let you sabotage this thing.
This guy is not gonna take you
if you show up high,
so stop screwing around,
or it's both our asses.
Right. Well, that's a start.
Now, give with the dope.
Christ.
Some people are immune to good advice.
I'm gonna get a bag for this cash.
Don't even think about lighting up again.
Francesca, we got any bags?
For money. Money-sized bags.
Huell will drop you at the pickup spot
then he's gonna get
the hell out of there.
You got that?
Guy won't pick up the kid
if he's got company.
You got a phone?
Cops took it.
All right, in case something goes wrong
guy doesn't show, whatever,
you give me a call.
Seriously? Hello Kitty?
Seriously, it's free.
We got a beggars-choosers situation here,
so stop busting my balls.
Corner of Juan Tabo and Osuna.
You, you're gonna sit and wait.
This guy's punctual with a capital P.
Okay? So don't move.
Don't get up and get an ice cream.
Just stay put like a good boy.
He'll pick you up, you pay him.
He'll take your ID,
he'll give you a new one.
Goodbye, Jesse Pinkman.
Hello, Mr. Credit to Society.
So do I get to pick where I go?
Well, it's your life.
I imagine you get a say.
Want a suggestion?
How about Florida?
You get a tan,
meet the Swedish bikini team
you know, swim with the dolphins.
What about Alaska?
Alaska. Okay, well,
that's a different vibe.
I never figured you for a moose lover,
- but whatever floats your boat.
- Alaska.
Alaska's good.
Anywhere you can get
a fresh start is gonna be good.
You ready?
Yeah.
Take care, Jesse.
All right.
Excuse me.
Hey, man, you can't go in there!
He a no-show? Why didn't you call?
Why didn't you...?
Stop!
Code red!
- Huell!
- No! Hey!
- Hey!
- Get in here!
Back off!
You, stay where you are.
What? I don't know what happened here.
What did I do?
You stole it off me.
You and him, you took it
out of my pocket, didn't you?
Calm down. Yes.
Okay. I had Huell lift your dope.
I told you I couldn't risk
the guy not taking you.
No! Before. The cigarette.
You stole the cigarette.
- What?
- The ricin cigarette!
You had him steal it off of me!
And all for that asshole Mr. White!
He poisoned Brock!
He poisoned Brock, and you...
You helped him!
- Okay, Jesse, calm down.
- Say it again!
Tell me one more time
to calm down! Come on!
I'm sorry. Yes. Okay.
I had Huell lift your cigarette,
but Walt made me.
He told me he was helping you,
he was saving you.
I never would've agreed to it
if I'd known what he was gonna do.
Jesse, you gotta believe me.
I didn't want any of this!
Back up!
Get off me!
What do I pay you for?
Hey, it's me. We got a big problem.
...eighteen, 19 and 20.
Actually, you gave me a 5, not a 1.
Oh, I... I did. I'm... I'm so sorry.
Here you go.
Thank you for your honesty.
Oh, and please give this
to your car wash professional.
Have an A-1 day.
God.
- Hey.
- Hi.
- What's going on?
- Not much.
- Yeah? Nothing?
- Nope. Things are fine.
- Good.
- Why?
Oh, no reason.
You know what I found the other day
is that the... The...
The latch on the soda machine wasn't...
latching.
It's... It's catching every time
that I stock that darn thing.
So I thought I'd check it out.
Great.
Thank you.
Exact change.
I like that. Thank you very much.
Okay.
And
please give this
to your car-care professional,
- and have an A-1 day. Thank you.
- Thank you.
I just remembered
they gave me a prescription
to go pick up, so...
I forgot.
I'm gonna go head on over
to the drugstore, okay?
- Yeah, okay.
- All right.