Gustavo, sit down.
You're making me nervous.
lt's a good plan. Trust yourself.
Everything is going to be okay.
Are you crazy?
The boss is gonna rip your balls off!
What, you gonna tell?
And you?
They ain't gonna say nothing.
They like what they see.
You're not going to offer our guests anything?
Who says they're guests?
lf the boss wants them to drink...
...they drink.
So...the Chicken Brothers.
l like your restaurant.
Dark meat and white meat?
Don't look like no brothers to me.
At last!
The master chefs!
You two....
That chicken you cook....
l swear, it has got to be the
tastiest chicken in all of Mexico.
Thank you, Don Eladio.
lt's a great honor.
Max is the chef.
The compliments are all his.
Gustavo is too modest.
There'd be no restaurant without him.
Well, however you two do it, keep it up.
Your chicken, it's so...zesty.
Piquant.
But it does not taste like a Mexican style.
lt's a recipe l learned in Chile...
...which l've modified a bit for the Mexican palate.
l bet we like a little
more chili than you Chileans.
We Mexicans like a good hard kick!
Sit down please.
So...if your partner is the chef...
...then who are you?
Don't tell me you are just the taster!
l handle the business operations.
Gustavo is a brilliant businessman.
Good, good.
But tell me something.
That chicken, so fabulous...
...so excellent....
Besides that, what else
do you have on your menu?
We have several side dishes.
Rice. Beans.
Sometimes we prepare a carnitas entrée...
...if we come across fresh beef in the market.
Anything else?
Come on, be honest.
There is nothing else you offer?
A little taste of something else?
Something on the side?
Because when l send my men to your restaurant...
...they come back with more than just chicken.
They come back with drugs.
You are selling them narcotics.
Methamphetamine.
With all due respect, Don Eladio.
l didn't sell it to them.
l gave them samples.
Samples.
Some businessman.
l gave them samples to give to you.
To introduce you to our product.
Don Eladio, Gustavo meant no offense.
But he...that is to say we...
...could think of no other
way to get your attention.
We want to work with you, Don Eladio.
l know all about methamphetamine.
That's poor man's cocaine.
Only bikers and hillbillies use it.
There's no money in it.
May l, Don Eladio....
l am a biochemist by training.
The methamphetamine
we make is much superior...
...to the so-called biker crank you know of.
lt is crystallized, like glass.
Purer.
And the chirality of the molecule...
...its very structure, is different.
The narcotic effect is far more potent.
This product is the drug of the future.
lt'll triple your profits.
Perhaps quadruple.
They're not only good cooks...
...they're great at shoveling manure.
Right now, you deal almost exclusively with cocaine.
But the coca plant can't grow in Mexico.
You are no more than middlemen...
...for the Colombians.
They cut you a percentage
for smuggling across the border.
But the lion's share
of the profits goes to them...
...despite your assumption of all the risk.
This new crystal methamphetamine....
lt's stronger, more addictive than cocaine...
...which means it will move in higher volume.
But most importantly, it's completely artificial.
We can show you how to manufacture it...
...right here in Mexico.
And you keep all the profits.
My men do like your product.
Hector, what is wrong with you?
Why did you not get glasses for our guests?
Go on.
You are quite the talent.
l bet you learned cooking
from your mama. lsn't that true?
But...what about the chemistry?
l studied at the University of Santiago.
Gustavo paid for my education.
Oh, really?
l have degrees in both
biochemistry and chemical engineering.
With minimal capital investment...
...we can set up a
factory-grade laboratory for you.
Train your own people
to manufacture large quantities...
...of highly pure methamphetamine.
Fantastic!
Tell me one thing, though.
lf you're the cook....
Why do l need him?
You.
Why should l negotiate with
someone who doesn't respect me?
Who insults me by dealing
under my nose without my permission?
Who manipulates me into a meeting...
...in front of my own men?
What do l need you for?
Don Eladio. Please.
l didn't sell anything.
l apologize if you are offended...
...by my method of obtaining this meeting.
l merely took the initiative.
l meant no insult.
Don Eladio, Gustavo didn't mean to offend.
l know Gustavo like a brother.
He's an honorable man.
The most loyal man l have ever known.
He rescued me from the Santiago slums.
He made me the man l am today!
Gustavo is a genius.
He will make you millions!
Just find it in your heart
to forgive him this one small mistake.
Please...
He's my partner.
l need him! l swear to God!
Look at him.
You did this to him.
Now, look at him.
Listen to me.
The only reason you are alive and he is not...
...is because l know who you are.
But understand....
You are not in Chile anymore.
My advice....
Stick to chicken.