jmg subs
They've broken through
the front lines!
I've lost contact
with the capital!
There's too many of them!
(EXPLOSIONS)
Stand fast! (GRUNTS)
DECEPTICON 1: Finish them!
(GRUNTS)
(OPTIMUS GRUNTS)
Where's B-127?
(DECEPTICON SCREAMS)
BUMBLEBEE: Sorry I'm late.
I hit a little traffic.
AUTOBOT 1: Get down!
Incoming!
BUMBLEBEE: Uh, Optimus.
DECEPTICON 2: Decepticons, attack!
Autobots, fall back!
Get to the tower!
DECEPTICON 3: Destroy the launch pad!
Let none escape!
OPTIMUS: Cybertron has fallen.
Get to the escape pods.
There are other Autobots
scattered across the galaxy.
We must reach them
if we hope to survive.
Optimus, this is our home.
We have to fight for it.
We will fight on. But we
must find refuge first.
I found a planet that's well hidden.
Earth.
You will travel there and
establish a base for us.
Once we've gathered the
others, we'll join you.
You must protect
the planet.
If the Decepticons find it, then
our people are truly finished.
Now go!
Good luck, soldier.
I'll buy you some time.
(GRUNTS)
(PANTING)
(SCREAMING)
(ALL GRUNTING)
No!
Ow! Ow! Ow!
Okay, okay!
I'm dead already,
man!
(SCOFFS)
Oh, not just you.
Being the overachiever
that you are,
you managed to get your
whole squad killed, Danny.
Bravo.
Come on, man.
Those things sting.
- What things? These things?
- Ow!
- You know, I wouldn't know. I haven't been hit yet.
- (GUN POPS)
- Ow! Okay, you know what? That's too close, man.
- (SOLDIERS LAUGHING)
You could've taken out an eye.
I got a date tonight, man.
This ain't sexy!
- You're right. I'm sorry.
- Ow!
- That one was on me.
- (YELPING)
That's a malfunctioning
trigger.
This weapon is just faulty. Someone
is going to get a talking to...
Man, would you stop?
All right, just stop.
(SIGHS) I should've
let you die in Grenada.
If you did, we wouldn't be
able to come to the forest,
run around and play
these awesome games.
DANNY: Exactly.
(GRUNTS)
(MUFFLED) Oh, I hate you.
Wow, man, that hurts.
'Cause I love you.
But you refuse to let it in
'cause you got intimacy issues.
A therapist will probably tell you
you weren't hugged enough as a kid.
- Look, man.
- Danny, I know I look stupid, but...
Hey, yo, take cover!
(GRUNTS)
(ALL GRUNT)
(GROANS)
(COUGHS)
- (GROANS) Danny.
- (COUGHS)
You okay?
Uh, yeah, man.
(GRUNTS)
This is Agent Jack Burns.
I need medical
up here now.
We have
a projectile strike
in the northwest corner
of the training course.
Multiple injuries.
And would someone please explain to me
why you dropped napalm on your own guys!
SOLDIER: (ON RADIO) Negative. There are no
live fire drills in the northwest sector.
What the hell hit us, then?
SOLDIER 1: Target on your right!
I need all of you to fan out
and track that thing down now!
Drive!
There!
What the hell?
Take it down!
Get down there now
and flush that thing out!
SOLDIER 2: There it is!
(SHOTS FIRING)
SOLDIER 2: (ON RADIO)
Target has been located, sir.
Light it up!
(BRAKES SCREECH)
Damn it!
(GRUNTS)
Oh, no.
It's going for the mine!
Cut it off!
(GRUNTS)
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
SOLDIER: Move, move!
(SOLDIERS
SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
(VISOR BEEPING)
BUMBLEBEE: Please.
This is a mistake.
Stay cool.
Hold your fire.
I don't want
to hurt anyone.
(AIRCRAFT APPROACHING)
Who called in the Air Force?
That's not the Air Force.
Run.
(SOLDIERS SCREAMING)
(GRUNTS)
(REVVING)
(BUMBLEBEE GRUNTS)
Did you think you could hide?
(GRUNTING)
Now you'll die screaming.
- Like your friends!
- (BOTH GRUNTING)
(GRUNTING)
(BUMBLEBEE GROANING)
(ENGINE SPUTTERS)
Tell me where
your friends are hiding.
I'll never talk.
Is that right?
Then let's
make it official.
(GAGGING)
(VISOR BEEPING)
(BLITZWING TAKES OFF, LANDS)
B-127...
As a member
of the Autobot resistance,
you are a traitor
to Cybertron
and are hereby sentenced
to death.
- (RAPID BEEPING)
- (GASPS)
No!
(GROANING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(HEAVY FOOTSTEPS THUDDING)
(METAL CREAKING)
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLES, BUZZES)
(VISOR BEEPING)
(CHILDREN CHATTERING
INDISTINCTLY)
(SYSTEM POWERS DOWN)
- (ALARM BLARING)
- (CHARLIE GROANING)
CHARLIE: Ugh.
Shut up.
(INDIE ROCK MUSIC
PLAYING ON WALKMAN)
Sweetness, sweetness
I was only joking
When I said by rights
You should be
Bludgeoned in your bed
And now I know
how Joan of Arc felt
Now I know
Morning, Dad.
As the flames rose
to her Roman nose
And her Walkman
started to melt
(AIR DRUMMING TO
DRUM ROLL ON TRACK)
(SNIFFING)
Bigmouth, la-da-da da-da
Bigmouth...
SALLY: No! Don't tickle.
Ow! (LAUGHING)
Uh-oh!
Caught.
- Gross, Ron.
- (SALLY LAUGHING)
Excuse me.
Are those
your diving trophies?
Taking up too much space
in my room.
You're gonna
regret doing that.
Where's breakfast?
Breakfast is conveniently located
in the cupboards and the fridge.
- Ah.
- SALLY: Try to help out...
- Yeah.
- ...a little.
Since I'm such a big kid now, making
my own breakfast and what have you,
you know how I could be an even
bigger help around here, Mom?
If I had a car.
Charlie.
What do you know,
it's my birthday tomorrow,
perfect timing
for a large cash gift.
You know, $500 is really all
I need to finish the Corvette.
I don't have $500. You
know how much nurses make.
"Half as much as doctors
for twice the work," right?
Tell you what, kiddo...
I got another
job interview tomorrow.
If all goes well, I'll have
you swimming in car parts.
- (CONAN WHINING)
- I prefer cash, Ron.
Don't be rude.
Feed the dog.
Conan is Otis's dog.
Make him do it.
OTIS: What?
SALLY: Aw! You look so grown
up in your karate suit.
My baby boy
is becoming a man.
Oh, shoot,
I'm gonna be late.
Can you drop your brother at
karate on your way to work, please?
Um, I could if I had a car.
Just let him follow you on your
bike so nobody abducts him.
Abducts him? You just
said he's a grown man now.
If anyone tries anything, I will
rupture their freaking spleen.
(RIDERS SCREAMING)
And do you feel scared?
I do
But I won't stop and falter
And if we threw it all away
(LAUGHTER)
Things can only
get better...
- That's two for you guys.
- MAN: Thanks, bro.
All right.
Have a good one.
Eat safe. (CHUCKLES)
(KIDS SCREAMING)
Excuse me. Hi.
We've never actually met...
Sorry, I can't right now.
- Yeah. Oh, okay.
- (GIRLS GIGGLING)
- GIRL: Whoo!
- BOY: Hey, hot dog girl!
CHARLIE: Oh, my God!
(GASPS)
I'm so sorry.
Oh, God.
(IN SING-SONG)
Someone's getting fired.
If I had to wear that,
I would pray to be fired.
Good one, Tina.
Let's go.
Oops.
Ooh.
On the street where you live
Girls talk
about their social lives
They're made of lipstick
Plastic and paint
A touch of sable
In their eyes
All your life
All you asked
When is your Daddy
Gonna talk to you
But we're living
In another world
Tryin' to get
Your message through...
(STATIC WARBLES)
Come on.
CHARLIE: Hey, Uncle Hank.
Are you still working
on that damn car?
You still working
on that damn personality?
- What have you got for me?
- Whatever you want.
Russians are gonna
blow us all to hell anyway.
That's the spirit.
BILL: Hey, kid.
Hand me the three-eighths,
would you?
- You working on the carburetor?
- BILL: Mmm-hmm.
- You need the half-inch.
- BILL: I said the three...
Huh.
- Thanks, kid.
- Yep.
You saw me standing
By the wall corner
Of a main street
Take a chance
Like all dreamers
Can't find another way
You don't have
To dream it all
Just live a day...
(GRUNTS)
(BEES BUZZING)
(ENGINE STARTS)
(RADIO WARBLING)
(OVERLAPPING RADIO CHATTER)
SHATTER: Where is Optimus Prime?
He survived the fall
of Cybertron.
And no rebellion
is truly dead
until the leader
is vanquished.
So where is he?
My name is Cliffjumper, lieutenant
in the Autobot resistance.
My safe return will be considered...
(GRUNTING)
(IN SING-SONG)
Wrong answer.
- (GROANING)
- SHATTER: We know he's planning to establish a base.
Tell us where it is
and we'll let you live.
My name is Cliffjumper,
lieutenant... (GRUNTS)
(MUSIC PLAYS ON RADIO)
Sometimes you wanna go...
(RADIO WARBLES)
CLIFFJUMPER: No.
SHATTER: That's B-127's signal.
- Can you trace it?
- Already did.
If you won't tell us where Prime
is, perhaps your young friend will.
Never.
You're a brave warrior.
You deserve a better death.
(SCOFFS)
But then again...
(DROPKICK GRUNTS)
(CHUCKLES)
Set course for Earth.
(RADIO WARBLES, STOPS)
(BEES BUZZING)
I'll give you thirty bucks
for all of it.
(CHUCKLES) I can get twice
that much for the coil alone.
From who? I'm the only one
that comes in here.
I don't even know
how you're still open.
Just take it. Go.
My show is on.
(STATIC CRACKLING)
Hey, where did you
get that Beetle?
I swear to God, ever since
they put up that dumbass tower,
I can't get a signal
to watch my shows.
I've got to see what happens
to Alf this week.
CHARLIE: Come on!
- (METAL CLATTERING)
- (CHARLIE SIGHS)
(CHARLIE GROANS)
(METAL CONTINUES CLATTERING)
(GROANS)
Are you kidding me?
(METAL SQUEAKING)
(GRUNTS IN FRUSTRATION)
Damn it.
(SIGHS)
I give up.
I can't do this without you.
(SOBBING)
- ALF: (ON TV) Nice to meet you. Interested in a new Buick?
- (ALL LAUGH)
- KATE: (ON TV) Nice try.
- ALF: All right, I touched. But I didn't eat.
KATE: And I'm supposed to
believe one of these steaks
just got up and walked away
on its own?
ALF: I've seen stranger.
KATE: No dinner
for you tonight.
ALF: But I'm starved!
I've been fasting since lunch!
(LAUGHTER)
ALF: Well,
I did eat that pumpkin.
(ALARM BLARING)
(GROANS)
(ALARM CONTINUES BLARING)
(ALARM STOPS)
(SOFTLY) Happy birthday.
I miss you, Dad.
I think it's too low, honey.
No.
No, I think it goes
to that button.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
I don't know about...
Fix it.
Hey.
- Good morning, birthday girl!
- Hi.
You look...
Nice.
Happy birthday, baby.
I love you. Come on, open your present.
I'm gonna be late for work.
Thanks, Mom.
Helmet. With...
Daffodils.
So, I keep hearing
about people on mopeds getting run
over and their brains smashed in.
You got to wear this
from now on.
I don't care if it's not
the law. It's our law.
Plus, look how cute it is.
Yeah.
SALLY: Happy birthday.
I actually got you
a little gift, too, Charlie.
I mean, it's small,
but, it's from the heart.
A smile is a powerful thing.
It releases endorphins.
It says to the world,
"I'm fun and approachable."
You know, there's a whole chapter in here
about how people who smile more often
actually have more friends.
That's unbelievable.
I really think it's gonna
change your whole outlook
if you smile more often.
I want the Beetle.
- What?
- The yellow Beetle, I want it.
I'll make you a deal. If I get
that thing started, it's mine.
That's no deal. That's
just you taking my car.
If I get it started, I keep it and
I work here every day for a year!
I'll scrub the grease
off the floors, okay?
I will pick up and organize every
scrap of paper in this place.
I'll even detail your
horrible, disgusting toilets.
Please.
It's my birthday.
Sorry, no deal.
'Cause we ain't hiring.
It's yours, kid.
Happy birthday.
(GASPS)
Thank you.
Thank you,
thank you, thank you!
And my toilets are gorgeous.
Think about it
There must be higher love
Down in the heart or hidden
In the stars above
Without it
Life is a wasted time...
CHARLIE: Oh, God, please.
(ENGINE STALLING)
Come on.
(ENGINE REVS)
Oh, my...
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God, thank you so much!
I love you!
(CAR ENGINE RUMBLING)
- That thing ain't even safe to drive.
- It's a deathtrap.
She's happy, though.
(HIGHER LOVE PLAYING)
Bring me a higher love
Where's that higher love
I keep thinking of?
Man.
Looks amazing.
(WHISPERS) What?
(GASPS)
(GASPING)
(WHISPERS)
Oh, my God.
(GASPING)
SALLY: Charlie,
what was that noise?
Nothing! I'm fine. Mom, you should
go back to bed. Everything's fine.
- What the hell is that?
- Um, it's...
What is that car doing
in our garage?
Car?
Oh, that, uh, car
is my car.
Uncle Hank gave it to me.
- It runs.
- (SOFTLY) Yeah.
Those aren't safe.
I wish you would've told me
before you brought it home.
Okay. Sorry.
Um, I'm in the middle
of some stuff, Mom.
Okay, I'll get out
of your hair, but...
Tell me things sometime.
- I'm your mother.
- Okay.
Okay.
Good night.
- It really runs?
- Yeah, it really runs.
Cool.
CHARLIE: You still in there?
(METAL CREAKS)
Okay.
A little jumpy. I'm sorry.
(GRUNTS)
Hi.
(BUMBLEBEE CHIRPS)
Oh, God, are you...
Do you speak?
(GROANS)
I won't hurt you.
(SOFT GASP)
Can you understand me?
What are you?
Where did you come from?
Okay. It's okay.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
You like my shirt?
You a metal fan?
No, wait...
Oh, who? Me?
Who am I?
Oh, I'm...
Charlie.
Charlie Watson.
I'm 18.
Today.
Actually, it's
my birthday today.
What's your name?
You don't know
or you don't have a name?
You sound like
a little bumblebee.
I'm gonna call you that
from now on.
Bumblebee.
Matches your outfit, too.
- (BUMBLEBEE HUMS)
- (CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
(COUNTRY MUSIC PLAYING)
All my exes live in Texas
(CLATTERING)
AMBER: I want a divorce, Roy!
Come on, Amber.
Give me one good reason.
You tried to sleep
with my sister!
Unsuccessfully!
Yeah, you're unsuccessful
at everything.
That down payment was for a house.
You bought a car.
How stupid are you, Roy?
We don't need a car. God!
Now, just settle down for
one second and hear me out.
- What the hell is that?
- What?
Oh, God, Roy, that thing
is coming right for us!
No, no, no, no, no...
Not my car. Not my car.
Please, God, no, not my car!
Oh, thank God, my car.
Yeah, I'm okay.
Oh, that's good, baby.
That's good.
BOTH: Run. Run!
(GLASS SHATTERING)
ROY: Oh...
- God!
- (ENGINE REVVING)
Is that my car?
Hello...
ROY: Jeez!
SHATTER: Earth.
- AMBER: Roy!
- ROY: Oh!
How underwhelming.
The indigenous life is even
more primitive than I expected.
Hey...
(SCREAMS)
(GASPING)
Hmm. I like
the way they pop.
Focus, comrade.
B-127's distress signal came from
the western coast of this continent.
For now, we head west.
(TIRES SQUEALING)
(ALARM BLARING)
RON: When do they start
letting you use nunchucks?
OTIS: I don't know,
but I hope soon.
- Morning! See you guys later.
- Where you off to so fast?
Nowhere. Have a nice day.
Morning...
Bee?
Bee, where are you?
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
- Oh, God. Oh, God. Oh, God. Oh, God.
- (CAR DOOR CLOSES)
- Bee!
- (ENGINE STARTS)
Where did you go?
Otis!
(PANTING)
Have you seen my car?
Unfortunately, yes.
No, have you seen
my car today?
It was in the garage.
Someone stole it!
No, idiot. Mom took it.
- (PANTING)
- She had to bring Conan to the vet
because he swallowed, like,
a rubber glove or something
and Ron needed
the station wagon.
Thank God.
Wait.
(CONTINUES PANTING)
Hi. Excuse me.
It's me again.
- We never officially met, but...
- I can't right now. Sorry.
Nope. Yep.
(STUTTERS) Okay.
(WHINING)
I know, buddy. Hang in there.
You can't eat
everything you see.
Just let this be
a good life lesson for you.
Oh, my God. Stop it!
Don't do that!
(BARKING)
Bee, no!
- Mom?
- Whoa!
Jesus! Charlie,
what are you doing?
Mom, you gotta pull over.
- What the hell is going on?
- Just pull the car over.
SALLY: Okay, okay. All right.
(CONAN WHINES)
Would you put that robot junk away?
What are you thinking?
SALLY: You almost gave me
a heart attack.
I thought
I was being carjacked.
I'm taking the dog to the vet.
I can't believe you would take him
without me. Mom, I'm so worried about him!
He's my dog, too, you know.
What happened to Conan
being Otis's dog?
(SIGHS) Mom, you're
being hysterical, okay?
You should not be driving
in such an emotional state.
I know how you get
during emergencies.
I'm a nurse.
Not of animals.
Oh, okay. I'm happy
for you to drive.
You weren't wearing
your helmet, by the way.
- I saw that.
- Oh, shoot.
(WHISPERS)
Keep it together, Bee.
(FAX MACHINE WHIRRING)
Sir?
Sir.
I thought you'd want
to see this immediately.
- They sure?
- SIMMONS: Yes, sir.
Two of them just
made contact in Texas.
Intel says they're heading
west fast.
Saddle up, Simmons.
We're going to Texas.
CHARLIE: Okay, Bee, we need
to go over a few things.
(SIGHS)
Okay. We're all clear.
All right. (SPITS)
I'm re-thinking the beach.
Ugh.
Oh, I'm good.
No, I'm good, thanks.
People can be terrible about
things they don't understand.
If they find you, they'll probably
lock you up in a lab somewhere
and cut you
into tiny little pieces.
It'll be bad, trust me.
The only person you can show
yourself around is me, okay?
So let's practice.
You ready?
If you see anyone besides me,
what do you do?
Great. Perfect.
(CHUCKLES) Come back now.
Okay, so let's say we're
driving and all of a sudden...
Oh, shoot! Somebody's here!
Hide, Bee, hide!
(BUMBLEBEE WHIRRING)
You serious?
Bee, it's too late.
You're already dead.
It's all right.
That's why we're practicing.
You'll get it.
PILOT: Fox-2 on approach.
Non-biologicals are inbound.
(VISOR CHIMING)
(INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER)
The goal, sir, should be
to communicate with them.
First contact
with an alien species.
I've spent my whole life
waiting for this moment.
If they make one wrong move,
we put 'em down.
The humans are multiplying.
Please let me kill them.
Not yet. B-127's
signal has gone silent.
I have an idea.
Listen up! I'm Agent Burns
and this is Dr. Powell.
We currently have 100 guns
pointed right at your head!
So state your business.
SHATTER: People of Earth,
we are Decepticon peacekeepers
patrolling the galaxy.
DROPKICK: What are you doing?
This is humiliating.
We believe a dangerous
criminal from our world
is hiding somewhere
on yours.
How is it you think
we can help?
We need your eyes.
Wait.
You want access
to our satellites?
SHATTER: Our scanners'
range is limited.
Your infrastructure
is primitive.
But combined, they
could be quite powerful.
No way!
Out of the question!
We have a common enemy,
Agent Burns.
There's a war raging
on our planet.
If B-127 isn't found, that
war may find its way here.
Perhaps...
We can find a way
to help one another.
We'll talk it over
with our superiors.
In the meantime,
if you could follow us.
Very well,
friend Powell.
Take us to your leader.
CHARLIE: Must suck being
cooped up in a VW all day, huh?
Is there anyone
that can help you?
Do you have a family?
You know, like a mom,
dad, siblings?
You all love each other?
Or drive each other crazy
and you can't wait to get away
and start a whole new life.
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLES)
Do you want me
to see if I can fix it?
I'll be gentle, I promise.
(SOFTLY) Whoa.
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLES)
You lay down, okay?
Hold still.
I think maybe
there's something...
OPTIMUS: (DISTORTED) B-127,
I pray this message finds you.
- Our war rages on.
- (TRANSMISSION BREAKING)
...planet Earth...
...survival...
(GRUNTS)
(GRUNTING)
DECEPTICON: Ravage, eject!
(GROWLING)
OPTIMUS: (DISTORTED)
...your mission...
...soldier...
I...
Are you okay?
(GROANS SOFTLY)
Who was that?
That voice said something
about a war.
Do you remember anything?
Is the VW Beetle
some kind of disguise?
Are you hiding
from something?
Are you scared?
(RADIO CRACKLING AND WARBLING)
CHARLIE: It's broken.
It's okay.
I think I can help.
(BUMBLEBEE CHIRPS)
Let's go home.
ALLISON: (ON TV)
...and a basket case,
CLAIRE: a princess...
- JOHN: And a criminal.
- CHARLIE: All right, I'm almost done.
BRIAN: (ON TV) Does that
answer your question?
CHARLIE: No way.
Are you actually
watching it?
Don't you forget about me
(CHUCKLES)
Don't, don't, don't...
You can pop in another one
if you want.
CHARLIE'S DAD: (ON TAPE)
Whoo! Come on, sweetie!
You got this, Charlie girl!
All right, Charlie girl!
(CROWD CHEERS AND APPLAUDS)
Hello, Brighton Falls.
This is Charlie Watson,
future Olympic gold medalist.
- (LAUGHS)
- That was so perfect.
- Thanks, Dad.
- CHARLIE'S DAD: How do you feel?
CHARLIE: No, no,
why would you play this?
Sorry. I just...
I finished.
Let's see
if we got something.
(CHARLIE CLEARS THROAT)
Okay.
All right.
(RADIO STATIC)
(SYNTHPOP MUSIC
PLAYING ON RADIO)
Oh, my God, yes!
It worked!
Look at you go.
You got some moves.
(MUSIC CONTINUES PLAYING)
Talking away
CHARLIE: You know, Bee, music can
help you say what you're feeling.
I'll say it anyway
You're gonna love this.
It's brand new.
Shying away...
(INDIE ROCK MUSIC
PLAYING ON STEREO)
Girlfriend in a coma,
I know
I know, it's serious
Not a Smiths fan.
Okay, um...
Here.
Try this.
(DANCE-POP MUSIC
PLAYS ON STEREO)
Never gonna give you up...
(CLANGS)
Fine.
Okay, where's my
Stevie Nicks?
Joan Jett and the Blackhearts.
Stones.
Hey, hey, please don't touch those.
Please.
They belonged to my dad.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
Do you want to hear it?
(SOULS MUSIC PLAYING
ON RECORD PLAYER)
We used to listen to this while
we'd work on the Corvette.
Oh, my love,
My darling...
It was his favorite.
I've hungered for your touch
A long lonely time
He used to say it would
make the car feel better.
(SONG CONTINUES PLAYING)
Time...
...goes by so slowly
(SIGHS)
We used to work on this car
every weekend together.
And time can do so much
It was our thing.
Are you still mine?
(SIGHS)
That tape...
(EXHALES)
That was the last time
I saw him.
He died of a heart attack.
I never got
to say goodbye.
You know, I always
thought if I could just
finish fixing this car...
If I could just get it
to start up again,
he would hear me.
He would hear me.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
(SNIFFLING)
I say this
with all due respect.
Have you lost your damn mind?
- That was with all due respect?
- GENERAL WHALEN: The man's got a point, Doctor.
Our satellite network is at the
forefront of our national defense.
Sir, please. It could be a
once in a lifetime opportunity.
Can you imagine the advances an alliance
with these creatures might bring?
I imagine the advances.
An advance on Washington.
- New York. An advance on Chicago!
- That's not gonna happen.
They literally call
themselves "Decepticons."
That doesn't set off
any red flags?
Enough! From both of you.
DR. POWELL: Sir,
we're talking about the most
advanced robotic system ever seen.
If we tell them no,
they'll just take their technology
to the Russians instead.
(ALL MURMURING)
Do you really want to go down in history
as the man who cost us the Cold War?
(SIGHS)
Fine.
We'll help them
find their fugitive.
And when it's done,
you can do all the
experiments you want. Hmm?
Yes, sir.
DR. POWELL: Gentle... Uh, Robots.
Welcome to Sector 7.
DROPKICK: How kind of you
to finally allow us in.
We're very happy
to have you here as friends.
Thank you, friend Powell.
My superior has agreed to grant you
limited access to our satellites.
In addition, you're welcome to
use all of our technology here.
It's the largest super-array
of Crays on Earth.
We thank you
for your hospitality.
Tell me, those vocal
communication devices you use,
do they function worldwide?
The telephones? Yes, why?
(RADIO TUNING)
You got to pick
a station, man.
I know there's
a lot of choices.
"You want to go
on a date with me, maybe?"
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
Okay, uh...
(RADIO STATIC)
What are you trying to do?
Here we go. Here we go.
You're not a nerd. You're not a nerd.
Okay, you're a nerd, but just don't
let her see that you're nerdy.
Excuse me. Sorry to barge in.
I just...
(GASPS)
CHARLIE: Um...
- Do you, just...
- (GASPING)
CHARLIE: No, no,
it's fine! Just...
Just sit down, please?
Shh, don't scream, okay?
- What is that?
- (CHARLIE SHUSHING)
It's okay, okay?
Just breathe. Breathe.
- First of all, hi.
- Hi.
I'm Charlie.
I'm Memo, hi.
Hi, Memo. Um...
It's nice to meet you.
Pleasure... Pleasure...
(GRUNTS)
Look, I know what you saw was
a little crazy. I can explain.
Yeah, I can't explain.
But here's the deal.
If you tell anyone
what you just saw,
I'm gonna have to
run you over with my car.
Jeez.
That was...
I don't mean that
in a mean way.
Okay? What I'm saying
is no one can know
what you just saw, okay?
You promise?
Yeah.
Okay.
(WHISPERS) Okay.
Bumblebee,
you can come out now.
(WHIRRING)
(MEMO WHIMPERING)
What?
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
It's, uh...
He.
Wow.
(RADIO TUNING)
He's been going up and down on that
dial all day today and I don't know why.
- Hey, check out his reflexes.
- What?
- Oh! Oh, God! (WHIMPERS)
- (CHARLIE CHUCKLES)
- Yo, give me your shirt.
- Huh?
Give me your shirt.
You mean the shirt
that I'm wearing?
Yes, yes! Come on.
I'll give it back to you.
Okay.
Come on!
Give me your shirt!
All right.
Wait, wait, wait! Hey, no, no!
You don't need to do this.
- Yes, I do.
- (STAMMERING) No, but...
- Come here. Come on!
- No, I get it. I get it!
- Whoo-hoo!
- (WHIMPERING)
Oh.
(LAUGHS)
Sorry.
I know I promised you, but, yeah,
you're not getting that back.
(BOTH WHOOPING)
So glad we've almost made it
So sad they had to fade it
Everybody wants
to rule the world...
DR. POWELL: It's incredible!
They're combining
our technology seamlessly.
Satellites, phones, computers.
They're creating an
interconnected web of information.
Volumes of data
at their fingertips.
It's revolutionary.
He's a weird guy. You ever
notice that about Powell?
DR. POWELL: They're tracking
fluctuations in Energon levels.
It's like a heat signature
specific to their species.
It's astonishing.
It's beautiful. It's...
Hello? Hello?
You've given them our satellites,
our comms, God knows what else.
Yet in the space of a day
they've given us a way
to not only hunt down B-127,
but all of them.
(SCOFFS)
Let them finish what they're doing.
Let them find B-127.
And then I'll give you
permission to destroy them all.
Use them for spare parts.
Sir, yes, sir.
MEMO: So you have no idea
where he came from?
CHARLIE: No idea.
You thought about
calling the cops?
(FAINT RADIO CHATTER)
What are they
gonna do, Memo?
They're just gonna send him away to a lab
and do weird science experiments on him.
(ON RADIO)
Weird Science!
Plastic tubes
and pots and pans...
- (CHUCKLES)
- You're getting pretty good with that radio dial, Bee.
Yeah, D.J. Bumble
in the house! (WHOOPS)
I can't live
without my radio
Is that why you're always
messing with the dial?
(GASPS) You're trying to teach
yourself how to talk, aren't you?
Walk like a man
Talk like a man...
- (LAUGHS)
- No way.
Oh, my God, Bee, you're a genius!
You're an actual genius!
Hit it!
(HIP-HOP MUSIC
PLAYING ON RADIO)
It takes two
to make a thing go right
- What is going on here?
- MEMO: That's Jim from sixth period.
(CHUCKLES) He said
he was busy this week.
You want
to check it out?
- This is pretty cool.
- Okay.
Bee, we'll be right back.
Don't do anything crazy.
MAN 1: Hey, everybody, come watch!
Tripp's gonna jump!
WOMAN 1: You're off your nut.
- What's going on over there?
- WOMAN 1: Don't do it, dude, you're crazy.
TRIPP: Come on,
it's not that big a jump.
CHARLIE: God,
is that Tripp Summers?
Oh, you know Tripp?
I mean, yeah. I spilled a
gallon of lemonade on him once.
Doesn't anyone have the balls
to jump off this thing with me?
Ah!
A brave volunteer.
(STAMMERING) Yeah, I... See, I didn't...
I didn't do that. I didn't actually...
(ON RADIO)
You got the touch
You got the power
Yeah
Hey, I know you.
Uh... No,
sorry about that. It...
You were on the dive team
with my little sister.
I saw you win state
a couple years ago.
(MEMO SCOFFS)
- Oh. Uh, yeah.
- Ladies and gentlemen.
This just got
a whole lot more interesting.
We have a championship
high-diver on our hands!
(ALL CHEERING)
Yeah, I actually,
I don't, I don't...
I don't do it anymore.
Oh, don't worry.
I won't make you go first.
MAN 2: Whoa-whoa-whoa!
Watch it!
(CHUCKLES)
Yeah, Tripp!
(TRIPP WHOOPING)
- WOMAN 2: Yeah!
- MAN 3: Yeah!
Dive Girl!
You better not back out on me.
(CROWD CHEERING
AND APPLAUDING)
(CHUCKLES)
TRIPP: You guys, she's gonna do it!
She's gonna do it!
ALL: (CHANTING)
Dive! Dive! Dive! Dive!
Come on!
- ALL: (CHANTING) Dive! Dive! Dive! Dive!
- (BREATHING DEEPLY)
CHARLIE'S DAD: You got this, Charlie girl!
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(ALL GROAN)
- MAN 1: Where you going?
- WOMAN 1: What, are you scared?
- You okay?
- CHARLIE: Let's just go.
WOMAN 1: What a loser!
MAN 1: Thought you said
you were on the diving team.
WOMAN 1: I think she's
gonna cry in her car.
Where you going,
sweetie?
(HANDLE SQUEAKING)
What happened out there?
- That was your big moment to look cool.
- (WOMEN LAUGH)
What's your damage, Tina?
Is that the churro guy?
Where's your hairnet, dude?
It's in the garbage, Einstein. You
throw them away after each use.
For sanitary purposes,
obviously, but...
TINA: This car
is an embarrassment.
You should have your dad
buy you a better one.
Oh, wait...
Sorry.
(LAUGHING)
You okay?
I'm fine.
They're idiots.
But I think I know something
that'll make you feel better.
What?
Revenge.
I don't want revenge.
I do.
What about you, Bee?
Want some revenge?
(ON RADIO)
I just want...
Revenge!
I'm mad
Come on. I got an idea.
CHARLIE: This is Tina's house.
(CHARLIE AND MEMO LAUGH)
CHARLIE: And this,
it's toilet paper.
You use it for when you...
Here, just take a roll.
- No, no, no, no. You've got...
- (LAUGHS)
You got to throw it.
Like this.
Not bad. (LAUGHS)
(CHIRPING)
- (CHUCKLES)
- Not... Yeah, um...
Okay, look, Bee,
you be our egg man.
- Right? Yeah. So...
- Love that.
- You see these right here?
- Mmm-hmm.
You grab one
of these, like so.
- And that right there, that's your target.
- That's right.
MEMO: All right? Just throw
it like this. (GRUNTS)
CHARLIE: I think we could
just hand it to him...
He could maybe,
yeah, and then...
CHARLIE: Uh...
- Bee, what are...
- What, um...
(BOTH LAUGHING)
(CHARLIE SHUSHING)
Don't hurt me.
(LAUGHING) Oh, my God...
- (GLASS SHATTERING)
- (METAL CREAKING)
(WHISPERS)
Oh, shit!
(CAR ALARM BLARING)
- Hide, hide, hide.
- Hide!
- Stay...
- MEMO: Oh, okay!
Okay. Okay.
Hide, Bee!
(CHARLIE GRUNTS)
CHARLIE: Go, go, go!
(TIRES SQUEAL)
(WHIMPERS)
Mom!
(BEEPING)
- (ENGINE ROARING)
- (SIGHS)
(SIREN BLARING)
- (MUSIC PLAYING ON RADIO)
- That was insane!
- (LAUGHS)
- My heart right now
is going crazy.
- (SIREN BLARING)
- Uh-oh!
- Oh, God.
- Stop the car, please.
(ENGINE REVVING)
Bee, what are you doing?
What are you doing?
-  I can't drive 55!
- (CHARLIE SCREAMING)
(CHARLIE AND MEMO SCREAMING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Bumblebee!
(BOTH SCREAMING)
I can't drive 55!
- (HORN HONKS)
- (BOTH SCREAMING)
I can't drive 55!
- (TIRES SQUEALING)
- (HORNS HONKING)
(MEMO EXCLAIMING)
-  I can't drive 55!
- (SCREAMING)
CHARLIE: Oh, my God!
(EXCLAIMING)
-  I can't drive 55!
- (BOTH WHIMPERING)
(SIRENS WAILING)
Oh, my God, we're
committing a felony!
(BOTH GASP)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
We got a yellow vehicle
driving its damn self
through the Pico Tunnel.
(CHARLIE AND MEMO SCREAMING)
(WHIMPERING)
Uh...
(TIRES SCREECH)
(BOTH GRUNT)
(EXHALES)
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Good night.
(SIGHS)
(WHISPERS) Good night, Bee.
Morning, buddy.
I got to go to work, okay?
Bee. Listen to me. You need
to stay in this garage, okay?
After what
happened last night,
I'm pretty sure the cops
are looking for you,
and, uh, you don't
exactly blend in.
I'll be back, all right?
(BUMBLEBEE WHINES)
Here.
You can have my Pop-Tart.
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
Take your baby by the hand
(SIZZLING)
I need you to go to the frozen
banana stand and steal some sticks.
We're out of sticks.
Can't we just sell the
hot dogs without the sticks?
No.
(MUSIC PLAYING ON TV)
Don't, don't, don't...
(BUMBLEBEE GRUNTING)
(CONAN WHINING)
(WHIMPERS)
(BIRD CHIRPING)
(GAS FIZZING)
(CLATTERING)
(CONAN BARKS)
(SOFA CREAKS)
(CLOCK TICKING)
(DINGS)
(MACHINE GURGLING)
(POWERING UP)
(BEEPING)
- What's happening here?
- We got a hit, I think. Where's that location?
Near San Francisco. A coastal
town named Brighton Falls.
- (EXPLOSION)
- (DOG BARKING)
(EXPLOSION)
You have a personal call.
- Hello?
- Charlie, hey, it's Memo.
You got to come home
right now.
(ENGINE REVVING)
(TIRES SCREECH)
It's bad.
It's really, really bad.
(CHARLIE GASPS)
Where's Bumblebee?
Bumblebee,
what have you done?
What were you thinking?
What...
I told you to hide
in the garage!
Great.
Helpful shame spiral, Bee.
(BUMBLEBEE WHINES)
I'm not mad, okay?
This is all my fault.
I never should
have left you.
MEMO: Hey, okay, maybe
don't transform all the way?
We've still got to get
you through the door.
(BUMBLEBEE GROANS)
Come on, buddy.
It's okay.
- (SIGHS)
- (OBJECTS CLATTERING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
I am so screwed.
(GRUNTING)
And now you're
crippled for life.
Honey, watch the hair.
- (DOOR CLOSES)
- (INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Go. Now. But be quiet.
Mom, wait!
(GASPS)
Oh, my God!
- Mom...
- SALLY: What happened?
CHARLIE: I'm sorry.
This is all my fault.
What'd you do to my TV?
Look, Mom, I can explain. We will
talk about this later, all right?
- Now, I have to go.
- Are you kidding me?
No. You're not
going anywhere.
- It's about my car. It's really important.
- About your car?
That you spend all day and night shut in
that garage, doing God-knows-what with?
Mom, I can't.
I really can't right now.
Oh, no, you really can,
Charlie.
You really can.
I have had it!
Your attitude,
your always sulking around.
You brought home that piece of
crap without even asking me!
Everyone in this family
is trying to be happy,
and all you want to do
is make things harder.
You know, Mom,
just because you've moved on
and you're happy with your
new life doesn't mean I have!
You've found a replacement
for my dad and I haven't,
okay, and I never will!
So I'm sorry if that
makes things harder,
but in ten months from now
you won't even have
to deal with me!
Charlie!
(SIGHS)
Hey, you okay?
Yeah.
I just feel like
ever since my dad died,
I've become this drain
on everyone, and I hate it.
It's like everybody expects me
to act like
nothing ever happened,
and it's impossible
to do that.
About your dad,
I'm really sorry.
Thanks.
You know, there's
this quote that I like.
"The darkest nights
produce the brightest stars."
That's nice.
My mom got it
from Weight Watchers.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
(BRAKES SQUEAL)
Get out and move
away from the vehicle.
(ENGINE REVS)
Stay cool, Bee.
(REVS AND STOPS)
What's going on?
(MEMO GRUNTS)
Hey!
- Come on!
- CHARLIE: Stop it!
Let go of me!
(SCREAMS)
- Weapons now! Take it down!
- Run!
No, don't run.
Do not run!
(CHARLIE GRUNTS)
She ran.
(CHARLIE SCREAMING)
(GRUNTS)
(HELICOPTER BLADES WHIRRING)
- (ENGINE REVS)
- (TIRES SCREECH)
Please tell me
they're on our side.
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
SHATTER: No more running.
No more hiding.
(VISOR TRILLING)
B-127, you're a traitor
and a coward.
Tell us where
Optimus Prime is hiding.
- Bee, look out!
- (DROPKICK GRUNTS)
DROPKICK: Why isn't he fighting back?
- (CHARLIE GRUNTS)
- DROPKICK: Why don't you fight?
Leave him alone!
Please!
Again.
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
Hit it again!
Stop! Stop it!
(GRUNTS AND GROANS)
(BREATHING STEADILY)
(MUFFLED CONVERSATIONS)
(GROANS)
AGENT BURNS: Your daughter stole
government property, Mrs. Watson.
SALLY: She's been
having trouble adjusting,
but we had no idea
it was this serious.
I...
Charlie. Honey.
I didn't steal anything,
and he doesn't belong to them.
- "He?"
- AGENT BURNS: Ma'am.
I can assure you
that it is an "it".
And "it" is a highly dangerous
war machine.
No, he isn't, okay, Mom?
He's not some "war machine."
I don't know
what he is, but...
He's my friend.
Ma'am, your daughter's had
a traumatic experience today.
Maybe doesn't understand
everything she's seen.
She's disoriented.
No, I'm fine, Mom.
I'm completely fine, okay?
You have to believe me, please.
I didn't steal anything!
Stop! Just go
to your room.
(SIGHS)
RON: When I was going
through puberty,
I stole things, too.
- Stole a box of Mallomars once.
- Yeah, we know.
(SIGHS)
(MOUTHING)
OTIS: Boom.
Caught you.
Oh, Mom's gonna love this.
Look, Otis, you need
to go home and...
Mom!
- No, Otis, stop it! Why would you do that?
- (GRUNTING)
- Let go of me! You're touching my buttocks!
- (SHUSHES)
I will tell you a secret
if you shut up.
Okay, so, um,
this is my room.
Just make yourself at home.
These are actually
my sister's stuff.
She likes playing pranks, like
putting her stuff over here.
- CHARLIE: Can I, uh, sit down?
- Yeah, yeah. Mmm-hmm.
REPORTER: (ON TV) Residents of
Brighton Falls have been witness
to an unusual sight
this evening.
Armed Forces pouring into town
as part of what we are told
is a routine military exercise
setting up camp
at our own McKinnon Air Base.
If Bumblebee's still alive,
that's where they're keeping him.
We have to go.
We have to try and save him.
Count me in. I'll take point.
- No, you won't.
- Come on.
No, Otis.
- But I can help. Master Larry says I...
- I need someone here.
I need someone reliable to make sure that
Mom and Ron don't know that I'm gone.
I'm someone reliable.
Hell, yeah, you are.
Good luck.
You, too.
Get over here.
(CHARLIE SIGHING)
Oh.
Let's do this.
SHATTER: Tell us where
Optimus Prime
and the rebels are hiding,
and we can end this war.
Talk!
DR. POWELL: Who is Optimus Prime?
SHATTER: This doesn't
concern you, human Powell.
Last chance.
(METAL CLANGS)
MEMO: Are you sure
this is a good idea?
CHARLIE: It's a terrible idea,
but I've got to try it.
MEMO: You can't get... Well, why
don't you... Stop, stop, wait...
- How'd you know the power was off?
- CHARLIE: I didn't. Let's go.
DROPKICK: Can I?
SHATTER: His memory cells are fried.
Finish him.
(DROPKICK GRUNTS)
OPTIMUS: We will fight on. Regroup,
rebuild, and retake our home.
But we must find refuge first.
You will travel to Earth.
Once we've gathered
the others, we'll join you.
You must protect the planet.
If the Decepticons find it, then
our people are truly finished.
Stay safe, soldier.
I am coming.
Prime is coming here?
They're all coming here.
This is our chance to wipe out
the Autobot resistance for good.
We'll burn the whole
planet to cinders.
SHATTER: We must get word
to Cybertron immediately.
(ON RADIO) This is Burns.
Tell them to bring an army.
(SOFTLY) Burns, we made
a terrible mistake.
Powell?
And thanks to
our human allies,
I know just how to get
the message home.
They're using our satellites.
They're calling an army.
They're gonna kill us all.
Thank you for your
hospitality, friend Powell.
He's all yours.
- No.
- AGENT BURNS: Powell?
- DR. POWELL: You have to stop them!
- Powell!
(RAY GUN POWERS UP)
(BOTH GASP)
RON: Where's the Krazy Glue?
What, did she cut
the wire to the TV?
Ron.
(GROANS) Charlie!
Charlie!
- (WHIRRING)
- Nice! Reel-to-reel still works.
Where is
your sister?
Charlie's fallen ill and must stay in
her bedroom for the rest of the evening.
She wishes not to be troubled.
Keep clear of her chambers.
What?
(SWALLOWS)
Charlie has fallen ill
and must stay in her bedroom
for the rest of the evening.
- She wishes not to...
- Otis!
Are you on drugs? Hmm?
No, no. Mom, Mom, Mom.
- Please stop. Stop!
- Charlie!
- Mom, there is no reason to go...
- Where is she?
- Mom, stop!
- Quit it, Otis.
(SIGHS)
Where is she?
Uh...
Otis?
SHATTER: I found a tower
to transmit our message.
- It's close.
- (ELECTRICAL HUMMING)
Oh. B-127.
I almost forgot.
I didn't.
(RAY GUN WHIRS)
No! Don't shoot!
(SOBS) No!
(CONTINUES SOBBING)
Bee!
Talk to me, Bee, talk to me.
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
I can fix this.
(SOBBING)
Charlie.
You got to wake up, Bee.
You got to wake up.
Please.
(SOBBING)
Charlie, we got to go.
- CHARLIE: The gun.
- What?
The electric gun. Get it.
I can fix you.
Come on, Bee.
Come back to me.
Come on, give me
the other one.
(SNIFFLES)
Bee, come on.
I can't lose you, too, Bee.
Please, Bee!
(SOBS)
(CHARLIE SIGHS)
I'm sorry.
Oh.
(SOBS)
Oh, my God.
Come on, Bee, we've got
to get you out of here.
- (VISOR WHIRRING)
- (GASPS)
MEMO: Charlie, there's like
a million guys out there!
- (CHARLIE GRUNTS)
- We got to move, now.
Come on, Bee, you've gotta get up.
Can you get up?
There's a door in my way.
They've got bombs!
- We got to go.
- CHARLIE: Bee, come on.
Charlie!
You've gotta get up, come on.
- Three.
- Charlie!
- Two.
- CHARLIE: Come on.
One.
- Charlie!
- Come on.
Memo?
Memo. Memo, wake up.
(MEMO COUGHS)
AGENT BURNS: Easy.
Easy.
Hold your fire!
Get the kid out of here.
- Memo! Wake up, Memo!
- (MEMO GRUNTS)
AGENT BURNS: Come on, kid.
Hey! No! (GRUNTS)
Bee!
Run!
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Bee! (GRUNTS)
Run!
- Let go of me!
- You need to get away from that thing.
- Take it down!
- CHARLIE: No, stop!
- Stop it!
- AGENT BURNS: Contain it and dismantle it!
Strip it down to parts!
CHARLIE: Leave him alone!
You don't understand.
(WHIMPERS)
Fight back, Bee!
- Bee!
- Kid, stop! It's a machine!
He's more human
than you'll ever be!
(GRUNTS)
That is enough!
(CHARLIE GRUNTS)
(VISOR WHIRRING)
(METAL CREAKING)
Oh, shit.
(GRUNTING)
AGENT: Open fire!
(AGENTS SCREAMING)
Fall back! Take cover!
- (SHOTS FIRING)
- (CRASHING)
Bee!
(SHOTS FIRING)
CHARLIE: Bee, stop!
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
You remember, don't you?
- (VEHICLE APPROACHING)
- (GASPS)
CHARLIE: They're coming back.
(SOFTLY) Oh, God.
Are you okay?
Yeah. Yeah, I'm fine.
We need to get out of here.
We've got to get you
someplace safe.
Bee, stop. They will kill you!
OPTIMUS: If the Decepticons find Earth,
then our people
are truly finished.
CHARLIE: Okay.
Then we fight.
Let's go, get in.
(VEHICLE APPROACHES)
Go on. I'll buy you
some time with these guys.
(CHUCKLES)
You just kiss me?
On the cheek.
- Still counts.
- (CAR DOOR CLOSES)
Still counts.
Halt!
(STAMMERS) Stop.
(HORNS HONKING)
(GASPS)
Well, that didn't work.
AGENT: Move, move!
(TIRES SCREECHING)
Faster, Bee, faster!
We should really look
into getting seatbelts.
Oh, my God, oh, my God.
It's okay. She's gonna steal the
robot back, fight off the police,
kill two bigger robots,
and come right back home.
Shut up, Otis.
REPORTER: (ON RADIO)
Folks, this just breaking.
There appears to be
a high-speed chase underway
just outside
McKinnon Air Base.
Go right! Go right!
- (TIRES SQUEAL)
- (GRUNTS)
(HORNS HONKING)
(PANTS)
(TIRES SQUEAL)
Closer. Closer.
You lose that car,
I will
personally rip your face off.
(TIRES SCREECHING)
Oh, God!
It's all under control.
(HORN HONKING)
- SALLY: Charlie!
- Mom?
You pull that car over
right this second.
This is very unsafe,
what you're doing.
Mom, you got to get
out of here, okay?
- Whoa! Whoa!
- (HORN HONKS)
CHARLIE: Mom...
You have to trust me, please!
Charlie!
- We got to help her, Ron!
- Hang on.
Oh, my God! Ron!
(AGENT BURNS GRUNTING)
Get out of the way!
Oh, my gosh!
What are you doing?
I saw this on Miami Vice.
God!
- Oh. Oh. I got it, I got it, I got it.
- Oh, my God!
- (TIRES SQUEAL)
- Whoa!
(HORN BLARING)
(HORN BEEPING)
- (GASPS)
- (BRAKES SCREECH)
Whoa!
(BRAKES SCREECH)
(ALL SCREAMING)
Nice driving, Ron.
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
Is everyone okay?
Ron! We have
a kid in the car!
I was trying to save
the other kid! What was I...
It was a lose-lose.
Otis? Otis,
are you all right?
That was radical.
(TRILLING)
(ENERGY PULSATING)
Preparing satellites
to transmit our message.
Okay. What's the plan?
This is the plan? I hate this plan.
Bee, I want to help.
(RADIO WARBLES)
I would hate anything
To happen to her
You're actually talking. And
you're listening to The Smiths.
Be careful.
(VISOR WHIRRING)
Handle him! And finish
the job this time!
(HELICOPTER BLADES WHIRRING)
(DROPKICK GRUNTING)
Oh, shit!
(GRUNTING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
How the hell am I
gonna get up there?
(CRASHING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(METAL CLATTERING)
(CHARLIE YELLS)
(GASPS)
(SCREAMING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(DROPKICK GROANING)
(CHARLIE GRUNTS)
(BEEPING)
(GASPS)
(HELICOPTER BLADES WHIRRING)
There. The one on the tower.
- (GROANS)
- (GASPS)
(SHOTS FIRING)
(CHARLIE WHIMPERING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
You think these little chains
can hold...
(HELICOPTER BLADES WHIRRING)
Okay.
(GRUNTS)
(GRUNTING)
Hold on!
(GRUNTS)
SHATTER: What are you doing?
(GRUNTING)
(CHUCKLES)
Come on.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(GASPS)
(POWERS DOWN)
No.
(WHIRRING)
(SHATTER GRUNTING)
(SHATTER YELLING)
After I kill you,
I kill her.
Bee, no!
(LAUGHS)
You missed.
(RUMBLING)
(GRUNTING)
You'll kill us both!
(SHATTER GRUNTING)
(SOBS)
(SHATTER GROANS)
Bumblebee!
(GRUNTS)
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
(BUMBLEBEE CHIMES)
(WATER SPLASHES)
(PANTING)
Oh, God.
AGENT BURNS: You.
You need to get outta here.
What do you mean?
I mean my friends are coming.
And they're gonna
be looking for him.
Thank you.
Hey, soldier!
(BUMBLEBEE CHIMES)
(ENGINE STARTS)
(PANTING)
I'm here. I made it.
What's going on?
World's already
been saved, kid.
Cool.
Hey, can you call my mom?
This is it, Bee.
(RADIO STATIC)
Let's go!
Bee, I can't go with you.
You've got people out there
that need you.
And so do I.
(SIGHS)
I gotta let you go.
(SOBBING)
MAN 1: (ON RADIO) Thank you...
WOMAN: (ON RADIO) So much...
MAN 2: (ON RADIO)
For giving me...
MAN 3: (ON RADIO) My voice.
Thank you for...
For making me feel
like me again.
I'll never forget you.
Goodbye, Bumblebee.
(VISOR WHIRRING)
No way.
You kidding me?
Are you telling me you could've
been a Camaro this whole time?
- Oh, my God!
- (ENGINE REVS)
Don't you forget about me
Don't, don't, don't
Will you stand above me
Look my way
Never love me?
Rain keeps falling,
rain keeps falling
Down, down, down
Will you recognize me
Call my name
or walk on by...
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
DEPUTY: Here you go, ma'am.
(SIGHS)
(GASPS)
Baby. (KISSES)
Thank God you're all right.
Thanks for coming, Mom.
That was some driving, Ron.
Well, I've taken a few notes.
Otis.
They forced me to tell.
I'm glad they did.
I couldn't have done it
without you guys.
MEMO: Hey, Charlie.
I'll be right back,
okay? (CHUCKLES)
Wow, um,
what happened to you today?
Oh, this?
Oh, you know, robot fights, high-speed
chases, international disasters.
The usual.
- Right.
- Yeah.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
Ooh, um...
Yeah, hmm...
- Not quite there yet.
- Nope.
- Yep. Okay, okay.
- No. Yeah.
(EXHALES)
(LAUGHS)
(CHUCKLES)
OPTIMUS: Old friend,
you kept this planet safe.
Because of you,
we have a future, B-127.
MAN 1: (ON RADIO) My name...
MAN 2: Is...
CHARLIE: Bumblebee.
(RUMBLING)
(TOOL CRANKING)
(TOOL CLATTERING)
CHARLIE: Let's see
if we got something.
- (ENGINE STARTS)
- (LAUGHS) Oh, my God, yes!