He's here!
- Professor Perlman!
- Welcome! Welcome!
- Thank you so much for having me.
- So nice to meet...
Oh, my goodness!
You're... you're bigger than your picture.
Well, I couldn't get all of my in the photo.
It's a problem.
- Mrs. Perlman.
- Anella.
Oliver. Very nice to meet you.
Thank you for having me in your home.
Elio!
You must be exhausted.
Ah... what gave me away?
Absolutely! Absolutely.
Every single one of these will...
Elio, Oliver.
Oliver, Elio!
- How you doing?
- Nice to meet you. Elio.
- You must be exhausted!
- A little bit.
Come! Come! Come!
May I bring your things up to your room?
- Err.... sure. Yeah.
- My room?
Follow him.
You're very welcome here.
Yes.
Our home is your home.
Hello.
Hi.
My room is now your room.
I'll be next door.
We have to share the bathroom.
It's my only way out.
We're being called for dinner.
Sorry.
Yeah. Um...
I'm probably gonna pass.
Would you make an excuse for me to your mother?
Thanks, man.
So this is your old room, huh?
Thanks.
Later.
- Wow!
- Ah...
- Look at this!
- Arrh.
Good morning, professor.
Good Morning!
Back from the dead.
- Was I out that long?
- It seemed like it, huh.
How are you?
Ah! Well, rested now.
Thank you.
I'm glad.
Would you like some er... espresso?
I would love some.
Thank you very much.
This looks amazing. But...
I didn't take your seat. Did I?
Oh, no, no, no.
It's okay. Please.
Did you... did you recover from your trip?
Er... I did, yeah. Big time. Thank you.
I could show you around.
That'd be great! Thank you.
Um... is there a... is there a bank in town?
I'd love to start an account while I'm here.
Let me do it.
I'm sorry.
- Ah... it happens to the best of us.
- No problem?
None of our residents has ever had
a local bank account.
- Really?
- Um.
Should I take him to Mount Dovie?
I think they're
closed for summer vacation.
You can try the.... Crema.
Crema?
Thank you.
Is this your orchard?
These are Annella's trees.
Oh wow.
Peaches, cherries and apricots.
- Pomegranate, melograno.
Have another egg.
How stupid.
No, no, no.
Now I know myself too well.
If I have a second I'm just going to have a third...
and then a fourth, and then you're just
going to have to roll me out of here.
Delicious.
Darling?
Thank you.
Should I get him on Kieser's bike?
What does one do around here?
Wait for the summer to end.
Yeah?
What do you do in the winter?
Wait for summer to come?
Well...
We only come here for Christmas
and some other vacations.
- Christmas? I thought you were...
- Easter as well.
I thought you were Jewish.
Well, we are Jewish. But also...
American, Italian and French, somewhat.
An atypical combination.
Besides my family, you're probably the only
other Jew to set foot in this town.
I'm from a small town in New England...
I know what it's like to be the odd Jew out.
So, what do you do around here?
I read books, transcribe music,
swim at the river.
Go out at night.
I don't know.
Sounds fun.
Alright, buddy.
Thanks for the help.
Oops... sorry!
Sorry about that.
That's alright.
Right. Later.
What do you have there?
That should all be...
What is this?
These are...
the continuation of these Archeology Department...
Yes. Yes. These are Archeology.
Yeah, those are Archeology.
And this... the rest of these should be History.
- Ah. Okay.
- Alright. Apricot juice.
Yeah.
- Take some.
- Thank you.
Aahh!
Help yourself to some more.
The word "apricot" comes from the Arabic,
it's like the words algebra, alchemy, alcoholic,
derives from an Arabic noun
combined with the Arabic article "al" before it.
The origin of our Italian
"albicocca" is "al-barquq".
It's amazing that today in Israel
and in many Arab countries,
the fruit's referred to by a totally different name...
mishmish.
I may have to disagree with you there, Professor.
Arrh?
I'm going to talk etymology,
so just bear with me a second. Umm...
You're right in the case of most of the Latin words
do find their origins in Greek words.
However, in the case of apricot,
is a little bit more of a complicated journey.
Ahh... How so?
Arr... well, here the Greek actually
takes over from the Latin.
The Latin word being "praecoquum" or "pre-coquere";
so it's "pre-coque" or "pre-reque" as you know...
to be precocious or premature.
And the Byzantines, to go on,
then borrowed "praecox",
which became "prekokkia",
which then became "berikokki",
which is how the Arabs
took "al-baquq".
It's courtesy of Philology 101.
Flying colors.
He does this every year.
It's about drink time.
Let's go here.
How do you know about this place?
Right on time!
- What's the matter? Are you alright?
- Cool.
- Pinch a nerve?
- I'm okay.
Here. Hold this!
Trust me. I'm about to be a doctor.
Hey! Hey? Come here.
See... that's the problem!
You're too stressed.
You just got to relax a little bit.
I am relaxed.
Marzia, come here for a minute.
Back me up here.
Feel that. Right there.
It's too tight, right?
- He needs to relax.
- Oliver!
Later.
You should relax more.
Okay, guys! Ready?
Red wine.
I don't think he's arrogant.
Just watch, this is how he'll say
goodbye to us when the time comes.
With his... "later!"
Meanwhile, we'll have to
put up with him for six long weeks.
Won't we, darling?
I think he's shy.
You'll grow to like him!
What if I grow to hate him?
Hey, Elio!
Play something.
You're spoiling everyone's fun.
Hey!
What are you doing?
Reading.
How come you're not with everyone else
down by the river?
- I have allergies.
- Yeah, me too. Maybe the same one.
Why don't you and I go swimming?
Right now?
Yeah... Come on! Let's go.
Do we have to go right now?
- I'll go get changed.
- Okay.
- Meet you downstairs.
- Um-hm.
See you downstairs.
- Elio, what are you doing?
- Reading my music.
No, you're not.
- Thinking, then.
- Yeah.
About what?
It's private.
- You're not going to tell me?
- I'm not gonna tell you.
He's not going to tell me
what he's thinking about.
Elio!
I guess I'll go hang out with your mom.
More apricot juice.
Sounds nice.
I thought you didn't like it.
Play it again, would you?
Follow me.
- That sounds different. Did you change it?
- I changed it a little bit.
Why?
I was playing it the way Liszt would have played it,
if he'd... altered Bach's version.
- Play that again!
- Play what again?
The thing you played outside.
Oh, you want me to play
that thing I played outside?
- Please.
- Arrh.
I can't believe you changed it again!
- Oh, I've changed it a little bit.
- Yeah! Why?
I just played it the way Busoni would have played it,
if I he'd... altered Liszt's version.
And what is wrong with Bach?
The way Bach would have played Bach?
Bach never wrote it for the guitar...
- In fact, we're not even sure if Bach wrote ..
- Forget I asked!
It's Young Bach. He dedicated it to his brother.
"I was too HARSH when I told him
I thought he hated Bach."
"I thought he didn't like ME."
"Oliver, Oliver."
- Hey, Professor.
- Hello!
Sit down here, please.
- Be honest. How bad is it?
- I think your insights here are persuasive, but...
Ciao.
- Elio!
- Hum...
Are you sleeping?
I was.
Listen to this drivel.
Tell me what you think.
- Wait.
- What?
I can't hear you.
For the early Greeks, Heidegger contends,
this underlying hidness is constitutive of the ways beings are...
not only in relation to themselves,
but also in relation to other entities general.
In other words, they do not construe hiddenness merely,
or primarily, in terms of entities relations to human beings.
Does that make ANY sense to you?
It doesn't make any sense to me.
And I don't think it makes any sense to your dad, either.
Maybe it did when you wrote it.
That might be the kindest thing
anybody's said to me in months.
Kind?
Yep. Kind.
- Elio!
- Hey.
- Hey! Marzia.
Come on.
We almost had sex last night.
Marzia and me.
Why didn't you?
I don't know.
Well... you know it's better
to have tried and failed, right?
All I had to do was find the courage to...
reach out and touch.
She would have said yes.
Well... try again later.
Try what later?
I just heard from the people in Sirmione.
They say they've come up with something.
Oh... fantastic!
I'm going there today.
Would you like to come along?
I would love to.
Thank you.
Can I come too?
Arrh... on the condition you remain silent.
Silent, as in he has too many opinions...
or silent as in, just not telling anybody
what amazing thing you've dug up?
Well... nothing has been dug up,
it's what has been brought up...
out of the water.
Dad always sits in front,
with Anchise to navigate.
She seems to like you a lot.
She's more beautiful than she was last year.
I saw her naked on a night swim once.
Great body.
You trying to to get me to like her?
What would be the harm in that?
No harm.
I just typically like to grow those things
on my own, if you don't mind.
Just don't play at being a good host.
What's going on, boys?
Oliver, come.
Sit up front.
Be my navigator.
What? ... What?
... and then another thousand...
then add five score.
The point of dissension is whether
it's named for a poem...
or... the man himself.
- Oh... Dr. Rosa!
- Welcome!
- Look who's here.
- Oh.
He's grown a bit, huh?
And this is Oliver.
Hey, boys!
The ship went down in 1827
on the way to Isola de Garda.
And gossip has it this statue was
a gift from Count Lecchi to his lover,
Contalto Adelaide Malanotte.
There were four known sets
after the Praxiteles originals.
This fellow is at number three.
The Emperor Hadrian had a pair,
dug up at Tivoli,
But um... one of the more philistine
of the Parmesia popes melted them down...
and had them recast
as a particularly voluptuous Venus.
Do you want to go for a swim
before we head back?
Elio!
Oliver!
- Hey! Hey!
- I have to go!
Goodness!
- Are you going too?
- No, no. I should stay and do some work on my book...
Oh, come on!
How about a drink to celebrate the day?
- Okay, maybe just one.
- Alright!
Marzia?
"The Cosmic Fragments"
by Heraclitus.
"The meaning of the river flowing
is not that all things are changing...
so that we cannot encounter them twice,
but that some things stay the same...
only by changing."
Darling, have you seen my Heptameron?
It's in German.
I don't remember where we left off, but...
I think you'll like this one.
So... I'll translate, heh.
"A handsome young knight is madly in love with a princess...
and she too, is in love with him...
although she seems not to be entirely aware of it.
Despite the friendship... Freundschaft...
that blossoms between them, or...
perhaps because of that very friendship...
the young knight finds himself so...
though humbled and speechless...
that he is totally unable
to bring up the subject of his love.
Then, one day, he asks
to the princess, point blank:
'Is it better to speak or to die?'
I'll never have the courage
to ask a question like that.
I doubt that.
Hey...
Eli-belli...
You do know that you can always talk to us?
My mom's been reading this 16th century French romance.
.
She read some it of to my dad and I
the day the lights went out.
Is it about the knight who doesn't know
whether to speak or die?
Right.
So does he or doesn't he?
"Better to speak," she said.
But she's on her guard.
She senses a trap somewhere.
So does he speak?
No.
He fudges.
It figures.
He's French.
- I gotta go to town in a litle bit to pick some things up.
- Oh, I can go. I'm not... doing anything today.
Then why don't we go together?
Right now?
Yeah.
Right now.
Unless, of course, you have
more important business going on.
(mumbles mockingly in reply)
Mind if I put this in your bag?
Yes, please.
I fell... just coming home the other day
and I... scraped myself pretty badly.
Anchise insisted on applying
some sort of witches' brew.
I think it helped.
Hold it for a second, would you?
- Want one?
- Sure.
Not bad, huh?
Not bad at all.
I thought you didn't smoke.
I don't.
It's World War II, huh?
Ah, no... this is World War I.
He has to be at least 80 years old
to have know any of them.
I've never even heard of the Battle of Piave.
The Battle of Piave was one of the most
lethal battles of World War I.
A hundred and seventy thousand people died.
Is there anything you don't know?
I know nothing, Oliver.
Well... you seem to know more
than everyone else around here.
If you only knew how little I know
about the things that really matter...
What things that matter?
You know what things.
Why are you telling me this?
Because I thought you should know.
Because you thought I should know?
Because I wanted you to know?
Because I wanted YOU to KNOW.
Because I wanted you to know.
Because there's no-one else
I can say this to but you.
Are you saying what
I think you're saying?
Don't go anywhere.
Stay right here.
You know I'm not going anywhere.
They mixed up all my pages.
I'm going to have to retype this whole thing.
I'm not going to have anything to work on this afternoon.
This is going to set me back a whole day.
Damn it.
I shouldn't have said anything.
Just pretend you never did.
Does that mean we're on speaking terms,
or not really?
It means we can't talk about those kinds of things.
Okay?
We just can't.
Hey!
- Ready?
- Let's go.
Pretty much.
- Thirsty?
- Yeah.
Il Duce.
That's Italy.
Come on!
This is my spot.
It's all mine.
I come here to read.
I can't tell you the number of books I've read here.
Oh my God, it's freezing!
The spring is in the mountains.
Two Alpi Orobie.
The water comes straight down from there.
I like the way you say things.
I don't know why you're always
putting yourself down, though.
So you won't... I guess.
Are you really that afraid of what I think?
You're making things very difficult for me.
I love this, Oliver.
What?
Everything.
Us you mean?
Ah... it's not bad.
It's not bad.
Better now?
Uh-uh.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
- We should go.
- Why?
I know myself, okay?
And we've been good.
We haven't done anything to be ashamed of.
And that's a good thing.
I want to be good.
Okay?
Am I offending you?
Just don't.
I think it's starting to get infected.
Stop at the pharmacist on the way back?
Excellent idea.
Elio?
Elio!
Are you alright?
Sit for a second.
If you insist.
- It was not my fault, right?
- No.
I am a mess.
Well... the kitchen table sure is.
Arrgh... where did you learn that?
My Bubba used to do this for us
when we were sick.
Trust me, it helps.
- I used to have one of these.
- Used to?
- Yeah.
- How come you never wear it?
My mother says we are
Jews of discretion.
- I guess that works for your mother.
- Funny witch.
- Arrgh! You'll fucking kill me if you do that.
- Well, I hope not.
- Oh hey, are you leaving?
- Where is Elio?
He's inside. He had a bit of a nose bleed
during lunch and he's just resting.
- Oh, right?
- Yeah.
Okay, I'll be right back in a minute.
Don't go anywhere.
Traitor.
Of course it is! Do not you see?
Because...
"Please don't avoid me. It kills me."
"I can't stand thinking you hate me."
"Your silence is killing me."
"I'd sooner die than know you hate me."
"I am such a pussy."
Way over the top!
"I can't stand the silence."
"Need to speak to you."
Did someone have a good night last night?
Well, you must be tired then.
- Or were you playing poker too?
- I don't play poker.
Several hundred color slides of our boxer and
the others like him arrived yesterday from Berlin.
- Oh.
- We should start cataloging them.
- That'll keep us busy till lunch, I imagine.
- Sure.
- Oh beautiful, aren't they?
- Mmm.
They're all so incredibly sensual.
Because these are more Hellenistic
than fifth century Athenian.
Most likely sculpted
under the influence of Praxiteles.
- Prax...iteles.
- Greatest sculptor in antiquity.
"Grow up.
I'll see you at midnight."
Muscles are firm.
Look at his stomach, for example.
Not a straight body in these statues,
they're all curved.
Sometimes impossibly curved, and so... nonchalant.
Hence their ageless ambiguity.
As if they're daring you to desire them.
... they have to be interpreted.
Don't forget Issac and Mounir are coming up for dinner.
Also known as "Sony and Cher".
Okay...
I'd like you to wear that shirt they gave you for your birthday.
No.
- Darling, they got it for you in Miami.
- I'm sorry, but it's too big. It's too big.
- Come on.
- It looks ridiculous on me.
- It would make them so happy.
I'll try it on for Oliver. If Oliver thinks I look
like a scarecrow in it, I'm not wearing it.
Oliver?
- Hey, what time have you got?
- It's two.
- Well, later.
- Later.
Mafalda.
- Hi.
Thanks.
- How are you?
- I'm good.
- Good to see you.
- It's great to see you.
- Ah, no, no. I have to go.
- Okay.
- Have a good night.
This right here...
is the brand new china
that you guys so kindly sent to us.
It looks wonderful.
- I can't put it on now, they've already met me.
- Yes, you can.
It will look like a put-up job.
Papa, it will look like a put-up job.
- No misbehaving tonight. No... no laughing.
When I tell you to play, you'll play.
You're too old not to accept people for who they are.
What's wrong with them?
You call them "Sony and Cher" behind your back.
That's what Mom calls them!
This only person that refects badly on is you.
Is it because they're gay
or because they're ridiculous?
If you know as much about economics at Mounir's age...
you'll be a very wise man indeed.
And a... and a... and a credit to me.
Now... now, just get into this! You...
Sorry, I have to go to bed.
Sorry, I am so tired.
Thank you.
- Elio?
- Uh... thank you.
Good night.
- Good night.
Do I know you?
Thank you again for everything.
I'm glad you came.
I'm nervous.
I like what you've done with the place.
It's nice.
Are you okay?
- Can I kiss you?
- Yes, please.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
Does it make you happy?
You're not going to get a nose bleed on me, are you?
I'm not getting...
Off, off, off, off, off!
Just pull it!
Or I'll pull it.
Oliver...
Call me by your name and I call you by mine.
Elio.
Oliver.
Did we make a noise?
Nothing to worry about.
I don't know, Mafalda always looks for signs.
We know she's not going to find any.
You wore that shirt the first day you were here.
Will you give it to me when you go?
Let's go swimming.
Are you going to hold what happened last night against me?
No.
Hey there.
Come here!
Take your trunks off!
Well, that's promising.
You're hard again.
Good!
Professor, I got your note.
Er... thank you for reminding me.
I'm gonna go into town
and pick up those typed pages today.
So maybe this afternoon
would be a good time to...
Later.
We'll look them over later, before you leave.
Okay.
So...  later!
Later!
Oliver!
You're not sick of me yet?
No, I just...
I just wanted to be with you.
I'll...   I'm gonna...   I'll go.
Do you know how happy I am
that we slept together?
I don't know.
Of course, you don't know.
I don't want you to regret anything.
And I hate the thought that maybe
I may have... messed you up.
- I don't want either of us to pay for this.
- No, I...
It's not like I'm gonna tell anyone... you...
You're not going to be in any trouble.
That's not what I'm talking about.
Are you happy I came here?
I would kiss you if I could.
What did you do?
Nothing!
I see...
You've moved onto the plant kingdom already.
What's next? Minerals?
I suppose you've already given up animals.
You know that's me.
I'm sick, aren't I?
I wish everybody was as sick as you.
Please don't do that.
- Do you want to see something sick?
- Please don't do that.
- Please don't do this.
Hey! Please don't do this.
Why are you doing this to me?
Why are you doing this?
You're fucking hurting me.
Then don't fight.
Sorry.
It's okay.
I don't want you to go?
God, we wasted so many days.
Why didn't you give me a sign?
- I did!
- You didn't give me a sign?
- When?
Remember when we were playing volleyball...
and I touched you?
Just to show you, that I liked you...
and the way you reacted
made me feel like I'd molested you.
I'm sorry.
No, that's fine.
I just decided I should keep my distance.
I don't know.
I come out here for
hours almost every night.
I didn't know that.
That's funny.  I didn't...
I felt that...
- Yeah, I know what you thought.
- Stop. Stop.
"For Oliver.
From Elio."
Elio!
I had to work.
Yeah... I do not know.
I just er...
I'm... I'm not your girl?
Oliver has to go
to Bergamo for a few days.
Oh?
Research at the university.
And he'll fly home from Linate.
What about Elio?
I mean maybe it could be nice for the two of them...
to get away for a couple of days, no?
What do you think?
You know you are our favorite student.
- You must come back.
- Are you sure you're not just saying that?
Oliver!
Thank you very much, Professor.
Ah, man.
Please. Please.
Come back soon!
Come back? I'm just going home to pack.
I'm moving here.
You're welcome.
Well...
- Thank, you guys, so much.
- Oh, of course.
Oliver, Oliver.
Come back!
Come here. Come here.
It's been amazing.
Thank you, guys.
Well...
Later, Perlmans.
Later.
Later, later, later.
- Ciao!
- Ciao.
- Arrivederci.
- Ciao!
Tell Elio to call when you get there.
Oh no!
What?
Nothing.
Oh, God!
Come on.
This
Did you hear that?
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
No, no.
It's this way, come on!
You're missing it.
Come on.
Hey guys. Don't stop.
This... this... you. You are...
Oh...
What did she say?
Did you get your passport?
Hello!
How are you?
Good.
You missed your dinner.
So...
Welcome home!
Thanks.
Did Oliver enjoy the trip?
Yeah...  I think he did.
You two had a nice friendship.
Yeah.
You're too smart not to
know how rare...
how special, what you two had was.
Oliver was Oliver...
- Oliver may be very intelligent, but...
- No, no, no.
He was more than intelligent.
What you two had...
had everything and nothing
to do with intelligence.
He was good.
You were both lucky
to have found each other, because...
you, too, are good.
- I think he was better than me.
- Arrrhh...
I think he was better than me.
- I'm sure he'd say the same thing about you.
- Yeah?!
He'd say the same thing?!
Which flatters you both.
You know, when you least expect it...
nature has cunning ways of finding our weakest spot.
Just... remember, I'm here.
Right now, you may not want to feel anything...
Maybe you never wanted to feel anything.
And ah...
maybe it's not to me
you want to speak about these things, but ah...
feel something, you obviously did.
Look, you had a beautiful friendship.
Maybe more than a friendship.
And I envy you.
In my place, most parents would hope
the whole thing goes away.
And pray their sons land on their feet. But...
I am not such a parent.
We rip out so much of ourselves
to be cured of things faster...
that we go bankrupt by the age of thirty.
And have less to offer each time
we start with someone new.
But to make yourself feel nothing...
so as not to feel anything...
What a waste!
Have I spoken out of turn?
Then I'll say one more thing.
It'll clear the air.
I may have come close...
but I never had
what you two have.
Something always...
held me back...
or stood in the way.
How you live your life
is your business. Just...
remember...
Our hearts and our bodies are given to us only once.
And...
before you know it,
your heart's worn out.
And... as for your body...
there comes a point when no-one looks at it...
much less wants to come near it.
Right now...
there's sorrow...
pain.
Don't kill it...
and with it, the joy you felt.
Does mom know?
I don't think she does.
Ooh... Latkes. (pancakes!
(telephone rings)
I'll get it.
Elio?
Are you there?
Hi.
It's me.
How are you?
- I'm good... good. How are you?
- I'm good.
- How are your parents?
- They're fine.
Good.
I miss you.
I miss you, too.
Very much.
I have some news.
You.... news?
Are you getting married?
I suppose...
I might be getting married next spring... yeah.
You never said anything.
It's been off and on for two years.
That's wonderful news.
Do you mind?
- Oliver!
Hey, hey.
When are you planning on coming back?
I wish I was.
You caught us in the process
of choosing the new you.
for next summer.
- And guess what...  he's a she!
- Oh, right.
Well,  speaking of news,
I'm calling to tell you guys I got engaged.
- Arrrh... wonderful!
- Ohh...
- Congratulations!
- Mazel tov!
- Congratulations, Oliver.
- Thank you. Thanks.
Listen, we'll leave you...
We'll... we'll let you speak to Elio.
- Happy Hanukkah!
Bye, sweetheat.
They know about us.
I figured.
How?
Well, from the way your dad spoke to me.
He made me feel
like I was a part of the family.
Almost like a son-in-law.
You're so lucky.
My father would have carted me off
to a correctional institution.
Elio?
Elio, Elio, Elio, Elio,
Elio, Elio, Elio, Elio...
Oliver!
I remember everything.
Elio?