The usurper.
He seems very confident.
Where's Elio?
I'll go down.
Darling, come help Oliver
take his things up to his room.
- He's already here?
- Yes!
You're leaving?
Nice to meet you.
I'll take care of the tart.
Let me do it.
Thank you.
Peaches, cherries, apricots...
Help yourself, darling.
Thanks.
- Ciao, Romano.
- Ciao, Oliver.
- How are you?
- All good.
Ciao, boys!
All good?
All good!
- Can you start please?
- Of course!
Good morning, gentlemen.
Go, Chiara!
He's better than the guy
who came last year.
Remember?
Get in there!
Much better!
See how cute he is.
Elio, water!
Sweetheart, Auntie Marcella and
the others are coming over for dinner.
Is Oliver staying with us or going out?
Don't know.
What a movie star!
Yes, those Americans...
Sparkling wine!
He's late.
Don't you think...
Don't you think he's impolite
when he says, "Later"?
Arrogant.
Oh, no, sweetheart.
- Take his plates away.
- Very well, madam.
I don't want to.
Why not?
Because I don't want to.
Why don't you go
to Moscazzano with others?
Because I don't want to.
Play well, darling.
Have you been to the river?
Mafalda!
Isn't she beautiful?
Come here.
What's going on?
Is he trying to get it on with her?
Elio, he already succeeded?
What do I know?
I'd love to be in his shoes.
Who wouldn't love to be in her shoes?
She wants him, no matter what!
Coming?
I'll come later.
Are you with me because
you're mad at Chiara?
Why would I be mad at Chiara?
Because of him.
Because of who?
Of Oliver.
Turn around.
Meet me here tomorrow night?
Wait for me!
Come on.
What are you doing?
Going to Lake Garda with my dad.
He wants to show Oliver
where he's dredging.
Can you tell him I came by?
He's inside with my dad, helping him.
You were amazing last night,
on the dance floor.
- He's a good dancer.
- A good dancer.
He's good-looking too.
- Want to get us together?
- No.
Come in.
I'll drive today!
Anchise, take the afternoon off.
Sammy! Come on!
Truce?
Sorry, Elio.
I brought some clean clothes.
Leave the door open.
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.
Come here, darling.
I straightened the wheels
and inflated the tires.
Perfect. Thanks.
Let's go, American!
Good morning, ma'am.
Excuse me.
Could I ask for a glass of water?
"People of Italy!"
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
So we got the government
of Bettino Craxi...
Because we don't do anything
but talk, talk, talk.
Let me speak.
We have five parties
that do nothing but fight.
Smoke and shut up!
Let them speak, him, her.
I'd like to know what they think too.
Annella, what do you think?
A five party government!
Darling, I think
it's the historic compromise...
Don't say that. Compromises are tragic.
You've changed
since you inherited this place.
What's that got to do with it?
What are you saying?
You're mad, darling.
You asshole!
- She's right.
- And you don't say anything to her.
Say something.
You're resigned.
Why don't we talk
about the death of Buñuel?
Buñuel was a genius.
- Know him?
- Cinema isn't the answer.
Cinema is a mirror of reality
and it's a filter.
They broadcast The Phantom of Liberty
with constant interr...
Everyone loves Buñuel!
Let's hear his opinion.
He doesn't know anything about Italy!
Say something. Give us your impression.
Do you have an impression?
Darling, he's American.
That doesn't mean stupid!
Just stop.
I don't give an easy ride
to some politicians.
She didn't say that.
I'm going to go mad.
What's the matter?
What's wrong?
It's nothing. It happens all the time.
- Mafalda, ice?
- It's in the fridge.
You get used to absolutely everything.
Don't you realise
you're mixing everything up?
What are you talking about?
There's no more politics, nothing.
He's left too.
You okay?
Are we going out?
I don't know if I can go out.
If my mom sees, she'll worry.
- She will?
- Yeah, she's a pain.
Where's Oliver?
Don't ask me.
- Didn't he go out?
- Would you like a smoothie?
No, thank you. We're having dinner soon.
All right.
I'm going out tonight.
- Don't make me worry.
- What are you talking about?
This is no good, madam.
- Let him do his own thing.
- Fine.
Why's she hassling me? I'm 17.
She's worried about you.
You like him, don't you? Oliver?
Everyone likes Oliver.
I think he likes you too.
More than you do.
Is that your impression?
- No, he told me.
- When did he say that?
A while ago.
Mafalda, do you know where Oliver is?
I have no idea.
This is Craxi.
I draw the center of Craxi...
- Hey.
-Hi!
It's me. Is that Marzia?
Sure it is! Can't you tell?
Sorry.
Is that for me?
Thanks.
Do you really read a lot?
I love reading too,
but I don't tell anyone.
Why not?
I don't know.
I think...
people who read are...
kind of secretive.
They hide who they really are.
Do you hide who you really are?
No, not with you.
Not with me?
Well, maybe a bit.
What do you mean?
You know exactly what I mean.
Why do you say that?
Why?
Because...
I think...
you're going to hurt me,
and I don't want to be hurt.
You're so hard.
Wait.
Kiss me.
- Is that good?
- Yes.
Are you lying?
- Oh, fuck, I'm sorry.
- It's all right.
Are you mad at me? Are you angry?
What's so funny? Why are you laughing?
Leave me alone.
Fuck, that felt good.
Not really.
I won't be here for dinner.
Okay, Mr Oliver.
Hello, Mafalda.
Marzia.
Where are we going?
You'll see.
Stop it!
- How are you, buddy?
- Hey!
- It's been ages.
- It has, yes.
- How are you?
- You've grown.
Remember Marzia from last year.
Hello.
Good to meet you.
Want to eat with us tonight?
- You're sure?
- Yes.
Goodbye.
Times change.
Thank God we had the partisans.
I know, but times have changed.
It's different.
What do you think of Bettino?
- I don't like him.
- I like him.
I'm happy, actually.
I don't know. We'll see.
Anyway, they make the rules.
Pasquina!
Hello.
Hello, ma'am.
- Tortelli cremaschi.
- Yes.
You disappeared for three days.
You completely disappeared.
I had a lot to do.
Come for dinner tonight.
Bring Marzia.
Bye, darling.
If you'll excuse me...
Just one second.
One second!
I saw them last year.
Richard Butler... fantastic!
Really? We saw them in concert too.
We hitchhiked to London.
Mafalda?
Mom?
Yeah, it's me.
Yeah, everything is fine.
I'm at the station...
in Clusone.
Listen, Mom, can you...
Can you come get me, Mom?
I read the book you bought me.
The poems...
They're really beautiful.
I love that... Antonia Pozzi.
I'm sorry, excuse me...
that you're sad.
I'm saying that because
I wanted to tell you
I'm not mad at you.
Not at all.
I love you, Elio.
Stay friends?
For life?
Because it was him.
Because it was me.
- Have you been to the Gaverine?
- Yes.
- May I?
- Happy Hanukkah!
To you too.
Hello?