check for ocr errors
Longing.
Rusted.
Seventeen.
Daybreak.
Furnace.
Nine.
Benign.
Homecoming.
One.
Freight car.
Good morning, Soldier.
Ready to comply.
I have a mission for you.
Sanction and extract.
No witnesses.
Well done, Soldier.
For a man who disapproves of diplomacy,
you're getting quite good at it.
I'm happy, Father.
Thank you.
Homecoming.
One.
Freight car.
I have your breakfast.
I could smell it before I opened the door.
Side of bacon and black coffee.
Again.
I can make you something different, if you like.
This is wonderful.
I will just put this on your...
It's okay, I can manage.
Suspect has broken containment.
He's headed down the east stairwell.
Longing.
Rusted.
Seventeen.
Daybreak.
Furnace.
Nine.
Benign.
Homecoming.
One.
Freight car.
Soldier?
Ready to comply.
James Barnes the suspect
in the UN Vienna bombing...
...escaped custody today.
...also missing Avenger
Captain Steve Rogers...
and Sam Wilson.
It hurts!
Good work.
Get me out of here.
This is room 201.
Bacon and black coffee again today?
You know me so well.
Hello? Your breakfast is here.
May I let myself in?