Captions synched to:
Captain America:First Avenger.TS.XVID.V2.IMAGiNE
Lovingly cooked by Bakemstr
You the guys from Washington?
You get many other visitors out here?
How long you been on site?
Since this morning.
A Russian oil team called it in about 18 hours ago.
How come nobody's spotted it before?
It's really not that surprising.
This landscapes changing all the time.
You got any idea what this thing is exactly?
I don't know, it's probably a weather balloon.
I don't think so.
You know we don't have the
equipment for a job like this.
How long before we can start craning it out?
I don't think you quite understand.
You guys are going to need one hell of a crane.
Base, we're aft.
What is this?
Careful.
Lieutenant.
- What is it?
- My god.
Mays, give me a line to the Colonel.
It's 3am, sir.
I don't care what time it is.
This one's waited long enough.
Tønsberg, Norway
March - 1942
They've come for it.
They have before.
Not like this.
Let them come.
They'll never find it.
Open it.
Why can't you find it?
It has taken me a long time to find this place.
You should be commended.
Help him up.
I think that you are a man of great vision.
And in this way we are much alike.
I am nothing like you.
Of course but what others see as superstition,
you and I know to be of science.
What you seek is just a legend.
Then why make such an effort to conceal it?
The tesseract was the jewel
of Odin's treasure room.
It's not something one buries.
But I think it is close, yes.
I cannot help you.
No.
But maybe you can help your, uh village?
You must have some friends out there.
Some little grandchildren, perhaps.
You have no need for them to die.
Yggdrasil.
The Tree of the world.
Guardian of wisdom.
And fate for some.
And the Führer digs for trinkets in the desert.
You have never seen this.
Have you?
It's not for the eyes of ordinary men.
Exactly.
Give the order to open fire.
Jawohl.
Fool.
You cannot control the power you hold.
You will burn.
I already have.
O'Connell, Michael.
Kaminski, Henry.
Boy a lot of guys getting killed over there.
Rogers, Stephen.
Kinda makes you think
twice about enlisting, huh?
Nope.
Rogers.
What did your father die of?
Mustard gas.
He was in the 107th infantry.
- I was hoping I could be assigned.
- Mother?
She was a nurse in a TB ward.
Got hit.
Couldn't shake it.
Sorry son.
Well just give me a chance.
You'll be ineligible on your asthma alone.
Is there anything you can do?
I'm doing it.
I'm saving your life.
War continues to ravage Europe.
But help is on the way.
Every able bodied young man is
lining up to serve his country.
Even little Timmy is doing his part.
Collecting scrap metal.
Nice work, Timmy.
Who cares!
Play the movie already.
Hey, want to show some respect.
Meanwhile, over seas...
..our brave boys are showing the axis powers...
..that the price of freedom is never to high.
Let's go, get on with it.
Hey, just start the cartoon.
Hey, you want to shut up.
Together with allied forces,
we'll face any threat, no matter the size.
You just don't know when to give up, do you.
I can do this all day.
Hey, pick on someone your own size.
Sometimes I think you like getting punched.
I had him on the ropes.
How many times is this?
Oh, your from Paramus now.
You know it's illegal to lie
on your enlistment form.
Seriously, Jersey?
You get your orders?
107th.
Sergeant James Barnes.
Shipping out for England first thing tomorrow.
I should be going.
Come on, man.
My last night.
Gotta get you cleaned off.
Why, where we going?
The future.
I don't see what the problem is.
You're about to be the last
eligible man in New York.
You know there's three and a half women here.
Yeah, I'd settle for just one.
Good thing I took care of that.
Hey, Bucky!
What'd you tell her about me?
Only the good stuff.
Welcome to the Modern Marvels Pavilion.
and the world of tomorrow.
A greater world.
A better world.
Oh my god.
It's starting.
Ladies and Gentlemen,
Mr. Howard Stark.
Ladies and Gentlemen.
What if I told you that in just a few short years,
Your automobile won't even
have to touch the ground, at all.
Yes.
Thanks, Mandy.
With Starks Gravitic reversion technology.
You'll be able to do just that.
Holy cow.
Well I did say a few years, didn't I?
Hey, Steve.
What do you say we treat these girls...
Come on, Soldier.
Come on, kinda missing
the point of a double date.
We're taking the girls dancing.
You go ahead, I'll catch up with you.
You really gonna do this again?
Well it's a fair, I'm going to try my luck.
As who, Steve from Ohio?
They'll catch you or worse they'll actually take you.
Look I know you don't think I can do this.
This isn't a back alley, Steve, it's war.
- I know it's a war.
- Then find kin to fight,
..start looking for a job.
- What am I going to do, collect scrap.
- Yes, I know that I'm
I'm not going to sit in a factory, Bucky.
Bucky come on, there are
men laying down their lives.
I got no right to do any less than them.
That's what you don't understand.
This isn't about me.
Right.
'Cause you got nothing to prove.
Hey Barnes. Are we going dancing?
Yes we are.
Don't do anything stupid until I get back.
How can I?
You're taking all the stupid with you.
You're a punk.
Jerk.
Careful.
Don't win the war 'til I get there.
Come on girls, playing our song.
Wait here.
Is there a problem?
Just wait here.
Thank you.
So.
You want to go overseas.
Kill some Nazis.
Excuse me.
Doctor Abraham Erskine.
I represent a Strategic scientific research.
Steve Rogers.
Where are you from?
Queens.
73rd street and Utopla parkway.
Before that, Germany.
This troubles you?
No.
Where are you from, Mr. Rogers?
Hmm?
Is it, New Haven?
Or, Paramus?
Five exams in five different...
It might not be the right file.
It's not the exams I'm interested in.
It's the five tries.
But you didn't answer my question.
Do you want to kill Nazis?
Is this a test?
Yes.
I don't want to kill anyone.
I don't like bullies.
I don't care where they're from.
Well, there are already so many
big men fighting this war.
Maybe what we need now is a little guy.
Huh?
I can offer you a chance.
Only a chance.
I'll take it.
Good.
So where is the little guy from?
Actually.
Brooklyn.
Congratulations.
Soldier.
Are you ready, Doctor Zola?
The machine requires the most delicate calibration.
Forgive me if I seem over cautious.
Are you certain that those combatants of yours
...can withstand the energy surge,
...long enough for a transference?
With this artifact.
I am certain of nothing.
I fear it may not work at all.
Twenty percent.
Forty.
Sixty.
Stabilizing at seventy percent.
I have not come all this way,
...for safety, Doctor.
What was that?
I must congratulate you, Arnim.
Your designs does not disappoint.
Though they may require
some slight reinforcement.
Nothing has changed, it's stable.
Amazing.
The energy patch, you called it,
equipped all my designs.
All my designs.
This will change the war.
Don't think so, Zola.
This will change the world.
Recruits, attention!
Gentlemen, I'm Agent Carter.
I supervise all operations for this division.
What's with the accent, Queen Victoria?
Thought I was signing up for the U.S. army.
What's your name, soldier?
Gilmore Hodge, your majesty.
Step forward, Hodge.
Put your right foot forward.
We gonna wrestle?
'Cause I gotta a few moves I know you'll like.
Agent Carter.
Colonel Phillips.
I can see that you are breaking
in the candidates, that's good.
Get your ass up out of that dirt,
..and stand up in that lineup at attention until,
- ...somebody comes and tells you what to do.
- Yes, Sir.
General Patton.
Has said.
"War's are fought with weapons
but they are won by men."
We are going to win this war, because...
...we have the best men.
And because they're gonna get better.
Much, better.
The Strategic Scientific Reserve.
Is an allied effort.
Made up with the best minds of the free world.
Our goal.
Is to create the best army in history.
But every army starts with one man.
Rogers! Get up from there.
At the end of this week, we will chose that man.
He'll be the first.
Of a new breed of super soldiers.
Rogers, get your ass out of that line.
And they, will personally escort Adolph Hitler
Through the gates of hell.
Pick up the pace, sweeties.
Let's go, let's go.
Double time.
Come on, faster, faster.
Move.
Squad halt.
That flag means you're only at the half way point.
First man to bring it to me,
gets to ride back with Agent Carter.
Move, move!
Come on, get up there.
That's what you got?
This army is in trouble.
Get up there, Hodge.
Come on, get up there.
Nobody's got that flag in seventeen years.
Come on, come on, fall in.
Let's go, get back in formation.
Rogers!
I said, fall in.
Thank you, Sir.
Faster ladies, come on.
My grandmother has more life in her, God rest her soul.
Move it!
You're not really thinking
of picking Rogers, are you?
I am more than just thinking about it.
It is a clear choice.
When you brought a modicum
asthmatic onto my army base.
I let it slide. I thought what the hell.
Maybe he could be useful to you, like a gerbil.
- Never thought you'd pick him.
- Up.
Stick a needle in that kids arm,
it's going to go right through him.
Come on, girls.
Look at that.
He's making me cry.
I am looking for qualities beyond the physical.
Do you know how long it
took to set up this project.
-Yes.
- All the groveling I had to do in front...
...of Senator whats-his-name committees.
Yes, I know. I am well aware of your efforts.
Then throw me a bone.
Hodge passed every test we gave him.
He's big, he's fast.
- He obeys orders, he's a soldier.
- He's a bully.
You don't win wars with niceness, Doctor.
You win wars, with guts.
Grenade!
Oh, no!
Stay away.
Get back.
Phony grenade.
Men, back in formation.
Is this a test?
He's still skinny.
- May I?
- Yeah.
Can't sleep?
Got the jitters I guess.
Oh, me too.
Can I ask you a question?
Just one?
Why me?
I suppose that is the one question that matters.
This is from Augsburg.
My City.
So many people forget that the first
country the Nazi's invaded was their own.
You know after the last war they,
My peoples struggled, they..they..
They felt weak, they felt..
...slow, then Hitler comes along.
With the marching and the big show,
and the flags and all that
And he, hears of me.
My work, and he finds me.
Then he says, you.
He says, you will make us strong.
Well.
I am not interested.
So he sends the head of Hydra.
East research division.
A brilliant Scientist by the name of, Johann Schmidt.
Now Schmidt is a member of the inner circle.
And he's ambitious.
Even Hitler shares his passion for,
occult power and tatanic myth.
Hitler uses his fantasies to inspire his followers.
But for Schmidt it is not fantasy.
For him, it is real.
He has become convinced
that there is a great power.
Hidden in the earth.
Left here by the gods.
Waiting to be seized by superior men.
So when he has found my
formula and what it can do.
He cannot resist.
Schmidt wants to become that superior man.
Did it make him stronger?
Ja.
But, it has other effects.
The serum wasn't ready.
But more important.
The man.
The serum amplifies everything
that is inside, so..
Good becomes great.
Bad becomes worse.
This is why you were chosen.
Because a strong man.
Who has known power all his life.
They lose respect for that power.
But a weak man.
Who values of strength.
And loves
Compassion.
Thanks.
I think.
Give this.
Whatever happens tomorrow,
you must promise me one thing.
That you must stay who you are.
Not a perfect soldier.
But.
A good man.
To the little guys.
No, wait, wait. What am I doing?
No, you have procedure tomorrow.
No fluids.
All right, we'll drink it after.
No, I don't have procedure tomorrow.
I can't after, I can now.
Is there something in particular you need?
I uh, understand you found  him.
See for yourself.
You disapprove.
I just don't see why you
need concern yourself.
I can't imagine he'll succeed.
Again.
The serum is the allies only defense.
against this power we now possess.
If we take it away from them,
then our victory is assured.
I shall give the order.
It has been given.
Good.
Doctor Zola.
What do you think?
Masterpiece.
I know this neighborhood.
I got beat up in that alley.
And that parking lot.
And behind that dinner.
Did you have something against running away?
You start running they'll never let you stop.
You stand up, push back.
You can't say no forever, right.
I know a little of what that's like.
To have every door shut in your face.
I guess I just don't know why you
would want to join the army.
You're a beautiful dame.
Beautifu..oh a woman. I mean...
An agent, not a Dame.
- You are beautiful.
- You have no idea how to talk to a woman, do you?
I think this is the longest
conversation I've had with a woman.
They're not exactly lining up to dance
with a guy that might step on them.
You must have danced.
Well, asking a woman to dance always seems so terrifying.
And the past few years just...
Didn't seem to matter that much.
Figured I'd wait.
For what?
Right partner.
This way.
What are we doing here?
Follow me.
Wonderful weather this morning.
- Isn't it.
- Yes, but I always carry an umbrella.
Good morning.
Please, not now.
You ready?
Good.
Take off your shirt your tie and your hat.
Senator Brandt, glad you could make it.
Why exactly am I in Brooklyn?
We needed access to the cities power grid.
Of course if you had given
me a generalized requisition.
A lot of people are asking for funds, ....
Oh, this is Clem uh...
Gregg Clemson, state department.
If this project of yours comes through.
We'd like to see that it doesn't get into the headlines.
Jesus.
Somebody get that kid a sandwich.
Comfortable?
It's a little big.
You save me any of that schnapps?
Not as much as I should have.
Sorry, next time.
Mr. Stark.
How are your levels?
- Levels at 100%.
- Good.
We may dim half the lights in Brooklyn.
But we are ready.
Good as we'll ever be.
Agent Carter, don't you think you would
be more comfortable in the booth?
Oh yes, ah, sorry.
Can you hear me, is this on?
Ladies and Gentlemen.
Today we take not another
step towards annihilation.
But the first step towards the path to peace.
We begin with a series of micro injections,
into the subjects major muscles.
The serum infusion will cause
immediate cellular change.
Then to stimulate growth.
The subject will be saturated,
...with Vita rays
That wasn't so bad.
That was penicillin.
Serum infusion.
Beginning in, five...
Four...
Three...
Two...
One.
Now, Mr. Stark.
Steven.
Can you hear me?
Probably to late to go to the bathroom, right?
We will proceed.
That's ten percent.
Twenty percent.
Thirty.
That's forty percent.
All signs are normal.
That's fifty percent.
Sixty.
Seventy.
Steven, Steven.
- Shut it down!
- Steven.
Shut it down.
Turn back, Mr. Stark. Turn it off kill it, turn back.
No!
Don't
I can do this.
Eighty...Ninety.
That's one hundred percent!
Mr. Stark.
Son of a bitch did it.
- I did it,
- Yes, yes.
I think we did it.
You actually did it.
How do you feel?
Taller.
You look taller.
How do we look now, Senator?
I guess the folks in Berlin
are about to get very nervous.
Congratulations.
Thank you, sir.
Stop him!
- They're coming, come on.
- Now.
You all right? Hey!
This guy's been shot.
I had him.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
Whoa, whoa.
No.
No, darling no.
Tommy no. Don't hurt him.
Go on.
Let me go.
No, don't hurt him.
Wait don't.
Don't.
No, don't.
Go get him, I can swim.
Who the hell are you?
The first of many.
I got off one hit.
Two more shall take it's place.
Heil Hydra.
The Führer is not accustomed to
being ignored, Herr Schmidt.
He funds your research because
you promised him weapons.
You serve at his pleasure.
He gave you this facility as
a reward for your injuries.
Reward, call it what it is, exile.
I no longer effect his image of Aryan perfection.
You think this is about appearances?
Your Hydra division has failed,
...to deliver so much as a rifle in over a year.
And we have learned through local intelligence.
You have mounted a full
scaled incursion into Norway.
The Führer fears, how does he put it?
The Red Skull has
been indulged long enough.
Gentlemen.
You have come to see the
results of our work, hmm?
Let me show you.
Hitler speaks of a thousand year Reich.
But he cannot feed his armies for a month.
His troops spill their blood
across every field in Europe.
But still he is no closer to achieving his goals.
And I suppose you still aim
to win this war through magic.
Science, but I understand your confusion.
Great power has always baffled primitive men.
Hydra is assembling an arsenal that will
destroy my enemies in one stroke.
Wherever they are, regardless
of how many forces they possess.
All in a matter of hours.
Your enemies?
My weapons contain enough destructive power,
...to decimate every hostile capital on Earth.
Quite simply, gentlemen.
I have harnessed the power of the gods.
Thank you, Schmidt.
For what?
For making it clear how obviously mad you are.
Berlin is on this map!
So it is.
You will be punished for your insolence.
You will be brought before the Führer and ....
My apologies, Doctor.
But we both knew Hydra could
grow no further in Hitler's shadow.
Heil Hydra.
Heil Hydra!
Think you got enough?
Any hope of reproducing the
program is locked in your genetic code
But without Erskine it would take years.
He deserved more than this.
If it could work only once.
He'd be proud of you.
Colonel Phillips, my committee is demanding answers.
Great, why don't we start with how a German spy,
..got a ride to my secret installation in your car?
What do we got here?
Speaking modestly I'm the best
mechanical engineer in this country.
But I don't know what's inside this thing.
Or how it works.
We're not even close to this technology.
Then who is?
Hydra, I'm sure you've been reading our briefings.
I'm on a number of committees, Colonel.
Hydra is a Nazi Deep science division.
It's led by Johann Schmidt.
But he has much bigger ambitions.
Hydra's practically a cult, they worship Schmidt,
they think he's invincible.
So what are you going to do about it?
I spoke to the President this morning.
As of today, the S.S.R. is being retasked.
- Colonel?
- We are taking the fight to Hydra.
Pack your bags, Agent Carter.
You too, sir.
We're flying to London tonight.
Sir.
If you're going after Schmidt, I want in.
Your an experiment, you're going to Alamogordo.
The serum worked.
I asked for an army, and all I got was you.
You.
You're not enough.
With all due respect to the Colonel.
I think we may be missing the point.
I've seen you in action, Steve.
More importantly.
The countries seen it.
Paper.
The enlistment lines have been around the block
since your picture hit the news stands.
You don't take a soldier, a symbol like that.
And hide him in a Lab.
Son.
You want to serve your country.
On the most important battlefield of the war.
Sir.
That's all I want.
Than congratulations.
You just got promoted.
I don't know if I can do this.
Nothing to it.
Sell a few bonds, bonds buy's bullets.
Bullets kill Nazi's, bing, bang, boom.
You're an American hero.
It's just I don't think I'm getting there.
The senator's got a lot of pull up on the hill.
You play ball, with us.
You'll be leading your own platoon in no time.
That's you.
Go!
*Who's strong and brave,
here to save the American way.*
Not all of us can storm a beach.
Or drive a tank.
But there's still a way all of us can fight.
*Who loves to fight like the
man for what’s right by day.*
Series E Defense bonds.
Each one you buy is a bullet in
the barrel of your best guys gun.
*Who built and came door to door for America?*
*Carries the flag shore to shore for America.*
*From Hoboken to Spokane.*
*The Star Spangled Man, with the plan.*
Cut.
All right, don't look at the camera.
*We can't ignore there's a
threat and the warning is big.*
Each one you buy is a bullet in
the barrel of your best guys gun.
*Who'll hang the noose on the
goose that we loosed from Berlin.*
*Who will redeem heed the call for America.*
*Who buys it all, gives his all for America.*
*Who stands to prove that task.*
*The Star Spangled Man, with the plan.*
We all know it's about trying to win the war.
We can't do that without bullets and bandages.
Tanks and casts.
And that's where you come in.
Every bond you buy will help
protect someone you love.
Look out there, he's there behind you.
The Germans will think twice
about trying to get the drop on us.
*Stalwart, and steady and true.*
*See how this guy can shoot!
We can tell that there's no substitute*
*Forceful and ready to defend
the Red, White and Blue!*
*Who'll give the Axis the sack
and is smart as a fox?*
*Far as an eagle we'll soar.*
*Who's making Adolph afraid
to step out of his bunk?*
*He knows what we're fighting for.*
*Who waked the giant that napped in America?*
*We know it's no one but, Captain America.*
*Who'll finish what they began?*
*Who'll kick the krauts to Japan?*
*The Star Spangled Man.*
*With the...*
*Plaaaaaaaaaan.*
How many of you are ready
to help me sock ol' Adolph on the jaw?
Okay.
I need a volunteer.
We already volunteered,
how do you think I got here?
Bring back the girls.
I think they only know the one song.
But, um...
Let me...I'll see what I can do.
You do that, sweetheart.
Nice boots, Tinkerbell.
Come on guys.
We're all on the same team here.
Hey, Captain.
Sign this.
Don't worry about it, they'll warm up to you.
Don't worry.
Hello Steve.
Hi.
- Hi
- What are you doing here?
Officially I'm not here at all.
That was quite a performance.
Yeah, uh...
I had to improvise a little bit.
The crowds I'm used to are usually more, uh...
- Proud.
- I understand you're America's new hope.
Bond sales take a ten percent
bump on every state I visit.
That's Senator Brandt's idea.
At least he's got me doing this.
Phillips would have had me stuck in a lab.
And these are you only two options?
A lab rat or a dancing monkey.
You were meant for more than this, you know.
What?
You know, for the longest time I dreamed about,
...coming over seas and...
..being on the front lines.
Serving my country.
Finally got everything I wanted.
And I'm wearing tights.
Look like they've been through hell.
These men move the most.
Schmidt sent out a force to a zone.
200 men went up against him.
Less than 50 returned.
Your audience contained
what was left of the 107th.
The rest were killed or captured.
The 107th?
What?
Come on.
- Colonel Phillips.
- Well if it isn't the Star Spangled Man with the plan.
What is your plan today?
I need the causality list from Bolzano.
You don't get to give me orders, son.
I just need one name.
Sergeant James Barnes from the 107th.
You and I are going to have a conversation
later that you won't enjoy.
Please tell me he's alive, sir.
B-A-R...
I can spell.
I've signed more of these condolence
letters today than I would care to count.
But...
The name does sound familiar.
I'm sorry.
What about the others?
Are you planning a rescue mission?
Yeah, it's called winning the war.
But if you know where they are, why not...
They're thirty miles behind the lines.
Through some of the most
heavily fortified territory in Europe.
We'd lose more men than we'd save.
I don't expect you to understand that,
because you're a chorus girl.
I think I understand just fine.
Well then understand it somewhere else.
If I read the posters correctly, you've got
someplace to be in thirty minutes.
Yes, sir.
I do.
If you have something to say, right now
is the perfect time to keep it to yourself.
What do plan to do, walk to Austria.
If that's what it takes.
You heard the Colonel,
your friend is most likely dead.
You don't know that.
Even so, he's devising a strategy, it takes time.
By the time he's done that, it could be to late.
Steve.
You told me you thought I
was meant for more than this.
Did you mean that?
Every word.
Then you gotta let me go.
I can do more than that.
On stage, girls.
Where's my helmet?
Anyone seen, Rogers?
The Hydra camp is in
Krossberg.
It's up between these two mountain ranges.
It's a factory of some kind.
We should be able to drop you
around the doorstep.
Just get me as close as you can.
You know you two are going
to be in a lot of trouble when you land.
- And you won't.
- Where I'm going if any anybody,
...yells at me I can just shoot them.
And they will undoubtedly shoot back.
Well lets hope this is good for something.
Agent Carter.
If you're not in too much of a hurry I thought
we could stop off in Usurea
for a late night Fondue.
Stark is the best civilian pilot I've ever seen.
He's mad enough to brave this air space.
We're lucky to have him.
So you two?
Do you?
Fondue?
This is your transponder,
active it when you're ready.
And the signal will lead us straight to you.
Are you sure this thing works?
It tested more than you, pal.
Get back here, we're taking you all the way there.
I'm jumping this plane, turn this thing
around and get the hell out of here.
You can't give me orders.
The hell I can't.
I'm a Captain.
As you can see.
Production and the work here is progressing on schedule.
Even with components of this size.
Increase the output by sixty percent.
And speak with our other facilities to do the same.
But these prisoners, I'm not
sure they have the strength.
Then use up what strength they have left, Doctor.
There are always more workers.
Not now.
You know, Fritz.
One of these days I'm going
to have a stick of my own.
Fellas.
Who are you suppose to be?
Um...
Captain America.
I, beg your pardon?
What are we taking, everybody?
I'm from Fresno, ace.
There anybody else?
I'm looking for a Sergeant James Barnes.
There's an isolation ward in the factory.
No one's ever come back from it.
All right.
The tree line is northwest,
it's eighty yards past the gate.
Get out fast, and give them hell.
I'll meet you guys in the
clearing with anybody else I find.
- Wait.
- You know what you're doing?
Yeah. I knocked out Adolph Hitler over 200 times.
You know how to use that thing?
Okay.
What is happening?
Hey.
Not exactly a Buick.
- That's Zündung. (Ignition)
- Zündung?
Get going, Dum Dum.
I didn't know you spoke German.
I recently mastered at Le Havre.
Plus the French girls much cuter.
Get after the Russian babes.
No, no, what are you doing?
Our forces are out matched.
Keep moving.
Grab a grenade.
Bucky.
Oh my God.
It's me, it's Steve.
Steve.
- Come on.
- Steve.
I thought you were dead.
I thought you were smaller?
Come on.
What happened to you?
I joined the army.
Did it hurt?
A little.
- Permanent?
- So far.
Captain America.
How exciting.
I am a great fan of your films.
So Doctor Erskine managed it after all.
Not exactly an improvement, but, still.
Impressive.
You've got no idea.
Haven't I.
No matter what lies Erskine told you.
You see I was his greatest success.
You don't have one of those, do you?
You are deluded, Captain.
You pretend to be a simple soldier.
But in reality you are just afraid to admit,
...that we have left humanity behind.
Men like you.
They embrace it proudly.
No fear.
Then how come you're running?
Come on, let's go.
Sir, we go to the roof?
What about me?
Where will I sit?
Not a scratch, Doctor.
Not a scratch.
Let's go.
One at a time.
Gotta get a rope or something.
Just go, get out of here.
No, not without you.
SENATOR BRANDT, I REGRET TO INFORM YOU,
...CAPTAIIN STEPHEN G. ROGERS
...WENT MISSING BEHIND ENEMY LINES,
...ON THE THIRD AREA.
RECONNASANCE HAS PROVEN
...UNFRUITFUL AS A RESULT,
...I MUST DECLARE CAPTAIN ROGERS,
...KILLED IN ACTION.
PERIOD.
The last surveillance flight is back.
No sign of activity.
- Go get a cup of coffee, corporal.
- Yes, sir.
We can't touch Stark, he's rich.
And he's the army's number
one weapons contractor.
- You are neither one.
- With respect, sir.
I don't regret my actions.
And I don't think Captain Rogers did, either.
What makes you think I give
a damn about your opinions.
I took a chance with you, Agent Carter.
And now America's golden boy,
and a lot of other good men are dead.
'Cause you had a crush.
It wasn't that.
I had faith.
Well I hope that's a big comfort to you,
...when they shut this division down.
There they are, I can't believe it.
What the hell's going on out there?
Some of these men need medical attention.
Medic, I got wounded.
I'd like to surrender myself for disciplinary action.
That won't be necessary.
Yes, Sir.
Faith, huh?
You're late.
Couldn't call my ride.
Hey!
Let's hear it for, Captain America.
I am honored to present,
...this medal for valor.
To my personal friend.
Captain America.
Captain America?
Captain, that's your cue.
I thought he'd be taller.
They one here in Poland, and the Baltic.
and the sixth one was...
About...
...here. 30, 40 miles west of the maginal line.
I just got a quick look.
Well nobody’s' perfect.
These are the weapon factories we about.
Sergeant Barnes said that Hydra
shipped all the parts to another facility,
...that isn't on this map.
Agent Carter co-ordinate with MI6.
I want every allied eyeball looking
for that main Hydra base.
What about us?
We are going to set a
fire under Johann Schmidt's ass.
What do say, Rogers?
It's your map. You think you
can wipe Hydra off of it?
Yes, Sir.
I'll need a team.
We're already putting together the best men.
With all due respect, Sir.
So am I.
So let's get this straight.
We barely got out of there alive,
and you want us to go back?
Pretty much.
Sounds rather, fun actually.
(Burp) I'm in.
(Speaking French)
We're in.
Hell, I'll always play.
But you gotta do one thing for me.
What's that?
Open a tab.
Well that was easy.
Another round.
Where are they putting all this stuff?
*There is a tavern in the town..*
- See, told  you.
They are all idiots.
What about you?
You ready to follow Captain America
into the jowls of death?
Hell, no.
That little guy from Brooklyn.
I was too.
I don't like to run away from a fight.
I'm following him.
Hey, you keeping your outfit, right?
You know what?
It's kinda growing on me.
*And remember that the best of
friends must part, must part*
*Adieu, adieu...*
- Captain.
- Agent Carter.
Ma'am.
Howard has some equipment for you to try.
- Tomorrow morning.
- Sounds good.
I see your top squad is prepping for duty.
You don't like music?
I do, actually.
I might even, when this is all over,
...go dancing.
Then what are we waiting for?
The right partner.
Pay attention, Captain.
Yes, Ma'am.
I'll be there.
I'm invisible.
I'm turning into you.
It's a horrible dream.
Don't take it so hard.
Maybe she's got a friend.
Initial signature is unusual.
Alpha beta remain neutral.
No doubt Rogers picked up on that.
Seems harmless enough.
Hard to see what all the fuss is about.
Write that down.
Excuse me.
I'm looking for a Mr. Stark.
He's in with Colonel Phillips.
Oh, of course you're welcome to wait.
I uh,
Read about what you did.
Oh, that...yeah.
Well that's, you know...
Just doing what needed to be done.
Sounded like more than that.
You saved nearly 400 men.
Really, it's not a big deal.
Tell that to their wives.
Uh, I don't think they were all married.
You're a hero.
Well, that...you know.
Tha..that depends on the definition of...
And the Women of America.
They owe you their thanks.
And um, seeing as they're  not here.
Captain!
We're ready for you.
If you're not otherwise occupied.
Agent Carter, wait.
Looks like finding a partner
wasn't that hard after all.
Hey, that's not what you thought it was.
I don't think anything, Captain.
Not one thing.
Always wanted to be a soldier, and now you are.
Just like all the rest.
Well what about you and Stark?
How do I know you two haven't been...
...fondueing.
You still don't know a
bloody thing about women.
Fondue's just cheese and bread, my friend.
Really?
- I didn't think...
- Or should you, pal.
The moment you think you know what's going on in...
a woman's head. Is the moment your
goose is well and truly cooked.
Me, I concentrate on work.
Which at the moment, is about making sure
you and your men do not get killed.
Carbon polymer.
Should withstand your average German bayonet.
Although, Hydra's not going to attack
you with a pocket knife.
I hear you're uh, kinda attached.
It's handier than you might think.
I took the liberty of coming up with some options.
This one's fun.
She's being fitted with electrical relays.
- That will allow you to..
- What about this one?
No, no that's just a prototype.
What's it made of?
Vibranium.
It's stronger than steel, and a third of the weight.
It's completely vibration absorbent.
How come it's not standard issue?
That's the rarest metal on Earth.
What you're holding there.
That's all we got.
Are you quite finished, Mr. Stark?
I'm sure the Captain has some unfinished business.
What do you think?
Yes, I think it works.
I had some ideas about the uniform.
Whatever you want, pal.
You are failing!
We are close to an offensive
that will shake the planet.
And we are continually delayed because,
...you cannot outwit a simpleton with a shield.
It's hardly my area of expertise.
I, I merely develop weapons.
I..I..I cannot fire them.
Finish your mission, Doctor.
Before the American finishes his.
Sir!
I'm sorry, Herr Schmidt.
We fought to the last man.
Evidently not.
Remember when I made you
ride the Cyclone on Coney Island?
Yeah, and I threw up.
This isn't pay back, is it?
Now why would I do that?
You were right, Doctor Zola is on the train.
Hydra dispatcher gave him permission
to open up the throttle.
Wherever he's going, they must need him bad.
Let's get going because
they're moving like the devil.
We only got about a ten second window.
You miss that, window.
We're bugs on a windshield.
Mind the gap.
Gotta get moving, buds.
Maintenant. (Now)
Now!
Stop him.
Fire again.
I had him on the ropes.
I know you did.
Get down!
Fire again.
Kill him, now.
Bucky!
Hang on.
Grab my hand.
No!
So.
What is this?
Steak.
What is in it?
Cow.
Doctor, do you realize,
...how difficult it is to get a hold,
...of a prime cut like that out here?
I don't eat meat.
- Why not?
- It disagrees with me.
How about Cyanide, does
that give you the rumbly tummy too?
Every Hydra agent that
we've tried to take alive,
..has crushed a little pill before we can stop them.
But not you.
So, here's my brilliant theory.
You want to live.
You're trying to intimidate me, Colonel.
I brought you dinner.
Given the valuable information that he has provided,
And in exchange for his full co-operation.
Doctor Zola is being remanded to Switzerland.
I sent that message to Washington this morning.
Of course it was encoded.
You guys haven't broken
those codes, have you?
That would be awkward.
Schmidt will know this is a lie.
He's going to kill you anyway, Doc.
You're a liability.
You know more about Schmidt than anyone.
And...
And the last guy you cost us
was Captain Rogers closest friend.
So I wouldn't count on the very best of protection.
It's you,
...or Schmidt.
It's just the hand you've been dealt.
Schmidt believes he walks
in the footsteps of the gods.
Hmm.
Only the world itself will satisfy him.
You do realize that's nuts, don't you.
Of course.
The certainty of the plan is of no consequence.
- And why is that?
- Because he can do it.
What's his target?
He's darkened.
He's everywhere.
Tomorrow...
Hydra will stand master of the world.
Born to victory on the wings of the Valkyrie.
Our enemies weapons will be powerless against us.
If they shoot down one plane.
Hundreds more will rain fire upon them.
Where they cut off one hand.
Two more shall take it's place.
Heil Hydra.
Heil Hydra!
HEIL HYDRA!
Heil Hydra...Heil Hydra!
Heil Hydra,
Heil Hydra!
Heil Hydra.
Doctor Erskine said that,
...the serum wouldn't just affect my muscles.
It would affect my cells.
Create a protective system,
..of regeneration and healing.
Which means, um...
I can't get drunk.
Did you know?
Your metabolism burns four times
faster than the average person.
He thought it could be one of the side effects.
It wasn't your fault.
Did you make the report?
Yes.
Well, then you know that's not true.
You did everything you could.
Did you believe in your friend?
Did you respect him?
Then stop blaming yourself.
And that was the dignity of his choice.
He damn well must have
thought you were worth it.
I'm going after Schmidt.
I'm not going to stop 'til all
of Hydra is dead, or captured.
You won't be alone.
Johann Schmidt belongs in a bug house.
He thinks he's a god and he's willing to
blow up half the world to prove it.
Starting with the U.S.A.
Schmidt's working with powers
beyond our capabilities.
He gets across the Atlantic.
He'll wipe out the entire
eastern seaboard in an hour.
How much time we got?
According to my new best friend,
in twenty four hours.
Where is he now?
Hydra's last base is here.
In the Alps.
500 feet below the surface.
So what are we suppose to do?
It's not like we can just knock on the front door.
Why not?
That's exactly what we're going to do.
Arrogance may not be a uniquely American trait.
But I must say you do it better than anyone.
But, there are limits, to what
even you can do, Captain.
Or did Erskine tell you otherwise?
He told me you were insane.
Ah.
He resented my genius,
and tried to deny me what was rightfully mine.
But he gave you everything.
So.
What made you so special?
Nothing.
I'm just a kid from Brooklyn.
I can do this all day.
Oh of course you can, of course.
But unfortunately I am on a tight schedule.
So am I.
Rogers.
You might need this.
Thanks.
We're in, assault Team now!
Fire!
I'm hit, full force.
Let's go find ten more.
Cease fire.
You're late.
Weren't you about to...
Right.
Get in.
Keep it steady.
Wait!
Go get him.
I'm not kissing you.
You don't give up, do you?
Nope.
You could have the power of the gods.
Yet you wear a flag on your chest and think
you fight a battle of nations.
I have seen the future, Captain.
- There are no flags.
- Not my future.
What have you done?
No!
Come in this is, Captain Rogers.
Do you read me?
Captain Rogers, what is your...
Steve is that you, are you all right?
Great, Schmidt's dead.
What about the plane?
That's a little bit tougher to explain.
Give me your coordinates I'll
find you a safe landing site.
There's not going to be a safe landing.
I'm going to try and force it down.
I'll get Howard on the line, he'll know what to do.
There's not enough time.
This thing's moving to fast and
it's heading for New York.
I gotta put her in the water.
Please, don't do this.
We have time, we can work it out.
Right now I'm in the middle of nowhere.
If I wait any longer a lot
of people are going to die.
Peggy.
This is my choice.
I'm here.
I'm going to need a rain check on that dance.
All right.
A week next Saturday at the Stork Club.
You got it.
Eight O’clock, on the dot.
Don't you dare be late.
Understood?
You know I still don't know how to dance.
I'll show you how.
Just be there.
We'll have the band play something slow.
I'd hate to step on your....
Steve?
Steve.
To the Captain.
Sir.
Take us to the next grid point.
But there's no trace of wreckage.
And the energy signal trace stops here.
Just keep looking.
There's a pitch, it's a ball high outside.
So, the dodges tied four to four.
At the count no doubt, one swing of his bat.
This fella is capable of making it
a brand new game again
Just an absolutely gorgeous day here at Ebbets field.
Philly's have managed to tie it up four to four.
But the Dodgers have three men on.
Pitch, it's a strike.
He leans in, here's the pitch,
swung on, it's a line drive.
It gets past Grissom.
Rizzo will score, Reiser heads to third.
Durocher is going to wave him in.
They look to relay but they hold steady.
- Pete Reiser with an inside the park...
- Good Morning.
Or should I say, afternoon.
Oh my god.
Where am I?
You're in a recovery room in New York city.
The Dodgers take the lead, it's eight to four
Oh ho, dodgers!
What a game we have here today, folks.
Fine game indeed.
Where am I really?
I'm afraid I don't understand.
The game.
It's from May, 1941
I know, 'cause I was there.
Now I'm going to ask you again.
Where am I?
- Captain Rogers
- Who are you?
Captain Rogers, wait.
All agents, code 13.
...13, all agents code 13.
At ease, soldier.
Look I'm sorry about that
little show back there, but.
We thought it best to break it to you slowly.
Break what?
You've been asleep, Cap.
For almost seventy years.
You gonna be okay?
Yeah.
Yeah, just...
I had a date.