Don't move.
I told Batroc...
If we want to make S.H.I.E.L.D. pay us...
...start sending them bodies now!
I have a bullet for someone...
Move that foot. You want
a bullet in the head...?
I don't like waiting.
Call Durand.
I want this ship ready to move
when the ransom comes.
Start the engines.
Shut up.
You want to be a hero? Is that it?
All right, I've waited long enough...
Find Batroc...
If I don't hear anything in two minutes...
...I start killing them!
I'll find him.
Two minutes.
Radio silence
from S.H.I.E.L.D., Batroc...
Time is up.
Who dies first...?
You!
Get that one.
The line just went dead.
I've lost contact with them...
I thought you were
more than just a shield...
Let's see.
I have her. Find him.