Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
Hey, what are you laughing about?
Your last hearing today.
Then, directly to Central Jail.
Sir, a man wants to file a report.
So what? Should I dance?
Write it down.
But he's livid.
Says he wants to file a... cheating case.
Shimmy-shimmy! I danced! Happy?
Now file his report. Lodge his case.
Sir, his case is against
the President of India.
Who?
President of India.
Yes, sir.
Why're you hesitating? Write my name.
Write...
Murlikant Rajaram Petkar.
I want to file a case of cheating
against the President of India.
Note all the Presidents' names.
Tell me.
V.V. Giri,
V.V. Giri...
Fakhruddin Ali Ahmed,
Ali Ahmed...
Neelam Sanjeeva Reddy,
Zail Singh, R. Venkatraman.
All of them cheated you?
Yes! They all cheated me.
Hello? Want to speak to him?
A puncture?
Hurry. We have to go to court.
Damn vehicle! Hang up.
How have the Presidents cheated you?
It's been 40 years...
I'm yet to receive the Arjuna Award.
That's it!
I'll fight for my right now.
Take Arjuna to court.
Why drag the Presidents?
Arjuna didn't give you the award...
Sir, players excelling in sports
receive the prestigious Arjuna Award.
Did sir ask you?
Knowledge...
- Doesn't he already know?
- Shut up, blabbermouth!
So many medals. Do you play a sport?
Not me... him...
- Who? This old man?
- Yes.
What does he play with? Marbles?
That must also be a challenge now!
Sir, please.
Fine.
What do you play?
I used to.
When?
40 years ago.
Damn!
What were you doing so long? Snoozing?
Let me finish my slumber,
and after 40 years...
claim my award.
Hey, what are you laughing about?
What else, mister?
Tell me this...
why do you want
an award after 40 years?
For my village.
What do you mean?
I mean...
Mr. Bhosle from Tujarpur,
got the Literary Award last year.
His village has progressed so much.
And my village...
has no road,
light or public toilet.
I want the Arjuna Award
for my village's development.
All that is fine.
But you're a bit late.
Who will give you the award now?
What do you mean?
Khashabha Jadhav got it.
Who's Jadhav?
That guy...
Mr. K.D. Jadhav.
Khashabha Dadasaheb Jhadav.
First Olympic winner of free India.
Isn't it, Mr. Petkar?
Correct.
- How do you know?
- What do you mean?
I was there!
My brother took me.
Where? The Olympics?
No.
Karad station.
Long live, Khashabha!
1952 Helsinki Olympics.
K.D. Jadhav was back
- after winning the Bronze in wrestling.
- Long live, Khashabha!
People from neighbouring
villages gathered at the station.
More than 10,000 people.
Long live, Khashabha!
Do folk show such respect
to anyone who wins a medal?
Not just village folk.
but the whole nation showers respect.
- The entire country?
- Yes.
- Hoist them on the shoulder?
- Yes!
No Indian has won
an Olympic medal before.
Not a single one?
- In all of India?
- Not a soul.
But it's only the 2nd Olympics
since India's independence.
We are all born as British citizens
before independence.
Me, too?
Yes, Murli.
Yes, you too are born a British citizen.
Don't tell father where we'd gone.
He looked like a king.
People were chanting...
Long live, Khashabha!
And Ma--
You got late today.
There were hordes on the city roads.
- God knows who had come.
- Khashabha, the wrestler.
He won India's first medal
at the Olympics in wrestling.
It was more crowded than the fair.
And more fanfare
than the Ganpati festival.
You're failing.
You'll make him a failure, too.
They know all the gossip.
But zero in academics.
They'll be empty vessels
when they grow up.
Eat.
Sir!
Yes, Kishan?
Sir, I'll grow up to become a doctor.
Why a doctor?
Doctors are God-like.
They save lives.
Well done!
Dagdu?
I'll join the army.
Why?
Soldiers protect us.
They save us from the enemy.
Very good!
- Murli?
- Yes, sir.
Sir, I'll go to the Olympics
and win a medal.
What?
The Olympics, sir.
I'll go to the Olympics,
become a champion
and win a medal.
Good. But which sport?
Kick the Stick.
Hey, what are you laughing about?
- You will win a medal?
- Yes!
You? A champion?
I am a champion.
You are not a champion.
You are "Chandu Champion, Loser Champion."
Let go!
- Loser! Loser!
- Hey!
Why're you picking up the stone?
Drop the stone.
Drop it!
I am a champion.
Why did you fight Dagdu?
Don't you know who he is?
He's Mr. Patil's son.
From Kandheri village.
So what?
I'm my father's son, too.
He was laughing at me.
He called me "Chandu Champion".
I'm not a loser.
I'm a champion.
Really? A champion?
Of what?
Words?
He was correct.
What have you achieved
to show you're a winner?
Want people to stop laughing at you?
Yes.
I'll show you how.
That's Ganpat sir.
Only he can make you a champion.
Got it?
Beg him to train you.
100 sit ups.
- Idiot, thrash him!
- Sir...
Wimp, haven't you eaten?
- Push him--
- Ganpat sir!
Sack of potatoes, pick him, pull...
well done!
- Make me your disciple.
- Let go.
- Please.
- Who's this?
- I want to be a wrestler like you.
- Leave me.
I'll do whatever you say.
Mentor me.
- Who's this?
- Train me.
- Please.
- Get up.
Move!
Are you crazy?
Come here.
What do you do?
I want to wrestle.
First learn to stand properly
and then you can wrestle.
Fly away, little peanut.
- Hey, what are you laughing about?
- Drop that stone.
Please forgive him, Ganpat sir.
Let me go!
Stop.
Come here.
He's pea-sized but spirited.
- Want to be a wrestler?
- And win an Olympic medal.
Really?
Why do you want to win a medal?
I want to be like Khashabha.
10,000-person welcome party,
chariots and a band.
A medal earns a lot of respect.
Which medal do you want to win?
I told you... the Olympics!
The Olympics has three medals.
Which do you want to win?
Which ones are there?
Bronze, Silver and Gold.
Which is the most coveted?
Gold.
Then I'll win the Gold.
Who is this?
- The world's biggest champion.
- Champion!
Indian champion Dara Singh!
Wrestlers, listen up!
My nephew Dagdu is wrestling
in the arena for the first time.
A new kid, a novice.
His father Patil wants
to show him off to the entire village.
One of you
will have to pretend-fight Dagdu.
And lose?
Yes!
How's that possible, sir?
If we lose against a novice,
no one will respect us.
- We have to protect our honor.
- Idiot,
Patil is my sister's husband.
He's very short-tempered.
Careful!
Sir, let him wrestle your nephew.
Bloody hell!
He's perfect. He's got strength.
But you haven't taught him technique.
He's the perfect choice... to lose.
Murli, come here.
Welcome wrestler Mandar Gaonkar!
Look out for the new catch,
and let's start the second match.
Where's Murli?
You want to wrestle?
Your results come today
and you want to wrestle?
No more wrestling.
Earn a single rupee,
then you can wrestle.
Papa, let me go today.
It's a big match.
For the first time... Ma...
My Olympic training starts--
Olympics!
The whole village ridicules you.
Do you know what people call you?
Please let me go today.
I'll prove to everyone.
I promise.
No one will laugh again.
Really?
Yes.
First, we'll go to school.
If you pass,
you can go to the arena.
If you fail, you will never
mention the word 'Olympics' again.
What are you doing?
Leave him.
Easy win for Kandheri's superstar.
Where's Murli?
Look... it's "Chandu Champion".
If you pass, it's the Olympics.
If you fail, it's the shop.
Failed, again!
The most coveted match of today...
This year, for the first time,
Patil sir's beloved son,
our adored Dagdu Patil,
will also wrestle today.
Applause!
Murli! Where's Murli?
Hey Sankya, where's Murli?
He took off after seeing the result.
What was it?
What else? He failed again!
Only he with true Maratha blood,
can fight Dagdu in the mud.
Anyone here has the guts?
To fight Dagdu, thus.
Speak now!
Is there anyone?
I'll wrestle him!
I'll wrestle him.
It's "Chandu champion".
The loser champion!
- Our wrestler will fight.
- Attaboy!
Only one wrestler here.
And from
Mr. Patil's brother-in-law's camp.
Let's test the strength of Islampur's soil.
Long live, Kandheri!
Will you keep going
around in circles?
Fantastic!
The winner gets this rupee
as prize money.
Let's see who's the winner.
Place your bets.
Get up, idiot.
As the duel gets intense,
both wrestlers face off.
Who will land the final blow?
Earn a single rupee first,
then talk about wrestling.
"Chandu Champion".
You loser champion!
I'm not a loser, I'm a champion!
Now we're in trouble!
Murli, know what you've done?
Brother, this money!
We'll give it to papa.
- I told you not to mess with Dagdu.
- Saw how I beat him?
Papa says wrestling has no money.
See how much I earned!
- You shouldn't have--
- This is wrong.
We've been cheated!
They'll kill you.
Won't let you stay here.
Clothes and shoes?
- Pakya, my clothes, quick!
- Move.
- Ganpat did this on purpose.
- No!
Dagdu is defeated and
we lose our village honor.
That's not true. What're you saying?
Murli's a novice.
Novice, my foot!
Have you ever seen
a newbie wrestle this way?
Run the fastest you can.
Thrashed Dagdu like a pro.
Promise... it's the first
I've seen him fight like this.
He's lying.
They've insulted us.
They've insulted Kandheri village.
- Beat them up.
- Control your people.
- There he is.
- Thrash him.
Run.
He's getting away.
Run, Murli.
Look there.
What's going on?
Get inside.
Why were they chasing you?
Have you stolen anything?
Will I get stuck helping you?
I'm not a thief.
Sure?
Give him a vest. He's lying naked.
Please dress before leaving home.
Want to reach the Olympics?
Join the army.
- Army?
- Yes.
Have you heard of Milkha Singh
and Dhyanchand?
No?
They're Olympians.
They've served in the army.
The army made them athletes.
I'm here too because of them.
Meaning?
I'm a player, too.
A boxer.
Actually, those goons
didn't drive you out of town
but pushed you closer to your dream.
Tomorrow is the army recruitment.
We're going there.
Why don't you try your luck?
Who knows you could be
the next Milkha Singh.
Olympics training at the army? Seriously?
100% true. Very much.
Sleep now.
We'll go early morning to enlist.
Let's sleep.
63 dead.
Airplane crashes into the Bombay seas.
Breaking news!
Give me one newspaper.
63 killed in airplane crash.
What happened?
Dead. All of them.
63 people dead.
How?
Incoming plane.
From where?
Japan to Bombay.
Then?
Torrential rains in Bombay!
As the plane turned to the airport
it stumbled and tumbled...
straight into the sea.
Dhoosh.
Dhoosh?
No one survived?
Have you ever seen an airplane?
No one survives a plane crash.
The plane swallows everyone.
Swallows everyone?
The train's here.
Gosh!
It's time. Hurry.
Karnail was right.
The goons pushed me towards my dream.
It was my life's biggest lesson.
I learned...
when faced with hurdles,
don't be scared.
Gather the courage and jump!
Jump and you shall gain.
I left my home
but a new life was waiting for me.
Pradeep Sharma, Shiv Kumar Rawat,
Anil Joshi,
Vilas Sawant, Mohan Doshi,
Karnail Singh, Murlikant Petkar.
You all have been selected.
You'll be sent to
EME Secunderabad tomorrow
where your military training begins.
Jokers!
The world's jokers were stuffed
in a train and presented to me.
You're all jokers.
- What are you?
- Jokers, sir.
Half won't even survive training.
Only he who has it in him
will make it from joker to soldier.
- Understood, jokers?
- Yes, sir!
A soldier's hair shouldn't
take long to comb.
And should be same for all soldiers.
Same to same.
- Got it, jokers?
- Yes, sir!
1, 2, 1...
Jokers!
A soldier's shoes should shine enough
to reflect your face.
Understood, jokers?
Yes, sir.
Up and down.
A soldier's teeth should be strong.
To chew iron, if needed.
Got it?
Yes, sir!
And Karnail gave his hand
and pulled me in the train
to the army.
And to the Olympic medal from here.
Olympics!
Hey, what are you laughing about?
Exactly, what are you laughing about?
Has any Indian won
an individual Olympic Gold medal?
That you will.
Does that mean no one ever can?
I'll win it.
You'll win it?
Olympic!
Hey, what are you laughing about?
Jokers!
Yes, sir!
There's no place in the army
for jokers like you.
Go back to your village.
- I don't want to go back, sir.
- You have to.
You're not fit to be a soldier.
I want to become a soldier, sir!
You can't.
Go back home.
I can't go back, sir.
I can't go back
until I've proved myself.
You should've thought about it
before fighting.
They were laughing at me, sir.
Mocking my dream.
Dream?
I want to play for India
and make my country proud.
I want to go to the Olympics
and win a medal.
It's been a childhood dream, sir.
What do you want to win?
Olympic Gold medal.
In which sport?
I'm a wrestler, sir.
The army doesn't train for wrestling.
But there's a sport
fit for wrestlers.
Meet me at 6 am.
At Tiger Ali's gym.
- Is this Tiger Ali sir?
- No.
That's Tiger sir.
Hurry up and make pairs.
- You're up, Jarnail.
- Sir, I'm Karnail.
Do I care?
- Naidu.
- Sir, Nadaswamy...
You and Gowda.
- Are you Manju?
- Yes, sir!
- Partner with Bhagpat.
- I'm Ganpat!
Why get touchy about your name?
Your parents chose it. You didn't.
- What is it?
- Ganpat!
Get in the ring, son.
Who to pair you with?
Sir, need a red carpet?
- Stop grinning! Where are your gloves?
- Gloves?
- Sir--
- I don't care about names.
Get ready.
Murli.
Tiger, what are you doing?
Put him in the ring already?
He's a boxer. Where else will I put him?
Not a boxer... he's a new recruit.
How dare you enter the ring?
- Sir, you asked me--
- Out!
- Take this joker out.
- Sir, one chance, please.
I'll learn.
One punch and you'll be crying for your mum.
Don't worry. I'm a wrestler.
Who do you think you are?
Dara Singh?
He's my role model.
Stop wasting my time. Leave.
One chance, sir.
One chance?
Boxing isn't a piece of cake.
You can't learn overnight.
Please make me your pupil.
I'll do whatever you say.
Fine.
You have a minute. Land one punch...
and you can start training.
Else, don't show me your face.
Come Kishan.
- I'm Karan, sir.
- Shut up and box!
Start.
Five.
10.
20.
25.
30...
35.
40...
You turned out to be a tiger.
What did your parents name you?
- What?
- Murlikant Rajaram Petkar.
Too long.
I'll call you Tiger.
Brother, forgot your own name?
Tiger is your name.
I'm Big Tiger, he's "Chhotu" Little Tiger.
Fire!
India's champion, Dara Singh!
Chhotu, sit!
He's my mentor, sir.
I'm your mentor.
- He's my first mentor, sir.
- Sit!
Well done.
These six soldiers from EME
will represent the Indian Army at the
International Military Games in Tokyo.
This tournament will pit
military players worldwide against each other.
And it is the gateway
to every sportsman's dream...
The Olympics.
Winning a Gold in Tokyo
means a chance in the Mexico Olympics.
Can anyone here make it to the Olympics?
Yes, sir!
Sir.
Have a good flight, sir.
Sir...
Thanks.
Have you seen a plane before?
No one survives a plane crash.
- The plane swallows everyone.
- Protect me, Lord Hanuman.
Protect me, Lord Hanuman.
Ali sir.
Look up. There's intense thundering.
Let's leave tomorrow.
- Tomorrow?
- Yes.
What time?
10 am.
Cool. We'll leave right after breakfast.
My father owns Air India.
- Perfect.
- Shut up! Stand in the line.
- Chhotu!
- Protect me Lord Hanuman.
Chhotu!
- Catch him.
- Hey! Murli.
The plane will swallow us!
Stop.
Murli. Where are you running?
- Very dangerous!
- Who?
The lightning.
It was lightening
the day of the plane crash.
- Which plane?
- I read the news...
The plane... coming from Japan.
It was pouring!
It stumbled and tumbled
straight into the sea... Dhoosh!
Dhoosh?
What nonsense. Catch him.
Come close to me
and I'll punch you.
- I'm a boxer.
- He's mad.
Mad?
- The plane swallows everyone.
- You're scaring everyone.
- Hold him.
- He's a boxer...
- Catch him.
- The plane will crash due to the rains.
I'm telling you.
You... and you...
Save me, Lord!
Cheers!
Have you ever had alcohol?
Yuck.
Not even a little?
Not a sip.
I'm a sportsman.
It's bad for health.
- It damages the liver.
- Yes.
You shouldn't even touch it.
Champagne, sir?
- Cheers!
Chhotu...
Karnail?
Yes, sir?
- Where were you? I've been looking...
- Nothing, sir.
Behave. I want you to meet someone.
This is Ms. Naintara.
She's a journalist.
On television.
TV?
They're calling you, sir.
Excuse me.
- Myself, Karnail.
- Hello.
His self, Murli.
- Shake hands.
- Hello.
I must say one thing...
Naintara is an Indian name.
- I'm Indian.
- Okay.
My father works in the Embassy.
That's why I stay in Tokyo.
- But, I studied journalism in London.
- Good.
Mr. Ali said,
you're both promising boxers.
Myself middle weight boxer.
Himself also... middle weight.
- Same.
- Yeah.
Ali sir was saying you're on TV...
Will we also come on TV?
Win and you'll be on TV, too.
I'll win the Gold.
- Straight to Gold?
- Actually...
he dreams big.
There are boxers from 55 countries.
So what?
I'll take on everyone tomorrow.
I like your confidence.
Best of luck.
Cheers.
- Cheers.
- Cheers!
Just a little.
Aleksander from Bulgaria.
Powerful left hook.
He lands the punch and you're done.
That's Manuel.
Mexicans don't believe in defense.
They only attack.
Nakamichi, a favorite here.
He'll tire you with his dancing.
Finish him off quickly.
And that's Sultan Mehmet.
4-year reigning champion.
He's the only one standing
between the Gold and you.
Welcome to the 1964 Military Games
in Tokyo, Japan.
In the red corner, boxing for Bulgaria,
Aleksander Dimitrov.
And in the blue corner,
boxing for India, Murlikant Petkar.
Watch the left hook.
Very good.
Careful.
Attack!
Get him!
1, 2... that's it.
Your photo is in the newspaper!
It says "Launda" does wonders!"
- They've written "launda"?
- No. They've written "boy".
It was in English.
I translated it for you.
You can read English?
Yes. I didn't fail in school like you.
My English is like the English.
Everyone in school called me
the English Colonel.
Divide and rule.
Didn't get it? You are fool!
Here's what they've written...
"Wonder boy from India
knocks out Japan's Nakamichi."
What does Wonder boy mean?
It means, an amazing lad!
Which you are.
- Wonder boy.
- What a lovely photo.
Wonder boy!
They're calling you
"Wonder boy from India".
Congratulations!
- Thank you.
- Thanks you.
Three knockouts! That's wonderful.
- Thank you.
- Thanks you.
All the best, Wonder boy.
Not "wondaer" boy.
- Wonder boy.
- Yes.
Karnail Singh from India is up against
the current champion, Sultan Mehmet.
Sultan Mehmet did not lose a single bout
on the way to his championship last year.
And this year he does not think that
anyone could be a challenge for him.
He is undefeated this year as well.
He knocked out the Indian boxer
Karnail Singh with ease--
We'll also sit there today.
You're being stubborn again.
That place is not for us.
We've been embarrassed enough today.
If he can sit there, so can I.
I've knocked out three players.
You'll get us killed!
Murli!
Hi.
Why take a fork and knife?
I want to eat like them.
If you want to become a champion
you have to learn all this.
Here...
Fork and knife.
Press and cut.
I'll show you how to cut it.
Broke the plate?
Champion, really?
Hey, what is he laughing about?
In the blue corner,
we have India's Murlikant Petkar!
And in the red corner,
Turkey's Sultan Mehmet.
Come on, Chhotu.
Get away from the ropes.
Careful, he's baiting you.
Chhotu!
Stop! 1, 2, 3,
4, 5, 6, 7, 8.
Get away from the rope.
Stop!
- What are you doing?
- What?
- What am I doing?
- This... anger.
- He was laughing at me.
- So?
- So what?
- Let him.
- I'll smash his face.
- Do it!
But not with anger.
With technique.
Calm your mind and observe him.
His right hand is moving slowly.
Clean him up.
Stay away from the rope.
Move ahead.
- Let's do an interview?
- What?
I want to interview you.
Sure!
Sorry, we don't have the time.
Please let me go, sir.
It's a TV interview!
Need to watch the other Semifinals
to study your competitor
and know what you'll be up against.
We have time, sir.
Yes, sir. I'll bring him back.
Promise sir. Karnail Singh promise.
Please, Mr. Ali?
Back by 6 pm sharp. Okay?
Okay!
But the interview will be in English.
It's fine. I'll manage.
And Karnail's there.
He was known
as English Colonel in school.
Sure, why not? Yes yes, of course.
- What's my problem?
- See?
Okay, let's go.
Yes.
Sit here. I'll be back.
Please look into this camera.
Please say something
for our audio check.
- Please say something.
- Speak.
Please say something.
- What do I say?
- Say your name.
Say something, please.
My name is Murlikant Rajaram Petkar.
- Village name--
- Louder.
Louder.
- Islampur--
- Louder.
Say, A, B, C, D, E.
A, B, C, D.
A - B - C...
No, no. Together, together.
He's asking to say them together.
E - F - H - J - L.
Louder, please.
I don't know beyond this.
You knocked out the champion Sultan
and now you're being called
the Wonder boy from India.
Do you think you can win
the Finals too?
Madam's asking
if you'll win the Finals.
Yes, yes. Win final.
Mr. Petkar, you're quite young.
What is your ambition...
your dream in boxing?
Dream... what's your dream.
Isn't it, madam?
Dream... Olympic Gold Medal.
Olympic Gold Medal.
Ali, sir.
The set up... and the English...
Lose focus from this Ugandan fighter
for even a second...
and it's over.
Goodbye, match.
Goodbye, boxing.
Goodbye, Olympics.
Go sleep, Wonder boy.
And the stage is set for the grand finale.
Come on!
Leave the rope.
Get away from the ropes.
Don't stop.
He's trapping you.
Get out, Chhotu.
Get away from the rope.
Goodbye, match.
Goodbye, boxing.
Goodbye, Olympics.
Knockout?
In front of Naintara?
Rascal!
I wasn't in my senses for a couple of days.
Couldn't even stand to accept this.
Let me see it.
Silver?
You don't get awarded the Arjuna
for a Silver.
- You could...
- Impossible! I know they don't.
Wasted my time.
He doesn't want the Award for the Silver.
What? There's more to the story?
Not now.
We're getting late for court.
- The judge fired me the last time.
- Wait a minute.
What happened after?
After Tokyo, I was posted at Kashmir.
- How did Kashmir come in the middle--
- Sit. Enough!
Exactly... enough.
- Sit down, Tambe.
- Sit.
You continue.
Tell us.
What about Ali sir and boxing?
Ali sir was also in Kashmir.
But after Tokyo,
he wouldn't speak to me.
You messed up there.
2-3 months passed.
Then one day, a letter arrived.
From the Olympics?
No.
Ali sir...
Sir.
Please see this.
Sir, I've been selected
for the Asian Games next year.
I've ranked number 1 in Asia.
The Ugandan who defeated me...
He ranks in Africa.
If I win the Asian Games,
I can still make it to the Olympics.
Sir, no mistakes this time.
Murli, we're done.
I won't train you anymore.
Sir, everyone's allowed one mistake.
Sir, he won't manage without you.
Sir, it was my first time
in the outside world.
I was blinded.
Just one more chance, sir...
One more chance? Why?
I dreamed of the Olympics, too.
To make my country proud.
It wasn't in my fate. I couldn't go.
Then you stepped into my ring
with passion in your eyes.
If I couldn't, you'd make it.
I'd help you.
But you turned out just like me.
Crashed before takeoff.
One more chance...
You were my 'one more chance', Murlikant.
And you stole that chance... from me.
Ali sir... Karnail...
Ali sir...
Ali sir, get out.
Murli, take Ali sir.
Take him to the bunker.
Keep your eyes open.
Ali, sir! Eyes open.
Karnail!
Ali sir.
Keep your eyes open.
Open your eyes, Ali sir.
Water... water...
I'll go to the Olympics, become a champion
and win a medal.
I want to play for India
and make my country proud, sir!
I want to go to the Olympics
and win a medal.
It's been a childhood dream, sir.
Nine shots.
From head to toe.
And yet you are...
Yes... I'm alive.
Sir, I haven't even had so many
shots at the doctor.
Sorry, sir. The puncture delayed--
- Let's go quickly.
- Shut up. Sit.
What happened after that?
A surprise visit by the Commandant.
Clean up quickly!
Who has kept the bed pan here?
Move it.
Clean the table.
Put it in the corner.
Wipe the dust.
Hurry, quick.
Why is Petkar's shirt so dirty?
Change the dirty bedsheets.
Hurry!
Who tied this knot?
Please... welcome sir.
- Welcome.
- Jai Hind, sir!
Move!
Soldier, are you okay?
Karnail!
Enemy!
What?
- Enemy!
- Leave him!
I want to go to my country.
No! Guns down.
- Let go.
- You're crazy. This is your country.
- He's your senior officer.
- I'm not crazy.
I know the Indian army uniform.
You've been unconscious for two years.
Know your name?
- How will you remember a uniform?
- Let go or--
- I'm not afraid of the enemy.
- We're not the enemy.
You're in India.
In the Udhampur Army Hospital.
In spite of being unconscious
for two years,
you still have strength in your hands.
- Get up, soldier.
- I'm sorry, sir.
It's okay.
What happened?
He took 9 bullets in the '65 war.
Two years, he's been in a coma...
conscious only 3-4 times.
One bullet is still lodged in his spine.
That's why, below the waist...
Removing this bullet
is a tough surgery.
No bladder control either.
Please move.
Don't lose hope, soldier.
You'll go to the best hospital
of the Armed Forces.
INHS Asvini, Bombay.
There the bullet will be removed.
You'll be fine.
Alright?
Murli, now that you're here,
everything will be fine.
You're in a wheelchair.
Some come on gurneys, half dead
and go back running!
Want anything... ask me.
I'll get it for you.
You help me in return.
A little help here and there.
Will your pension continue?
Murli, doctors view you as a patient
who they have to treat.
But man has other needs...
which I take care of.
Don't worry.
This is your new home
and your new neighbours.
Topaz, stop!
Stop right there.
I haven't moved, nurse.
What is this, Topaz?
What is it?
You know this is wrong.
Yes, it's very wrong.
Bombay has banned alcohol.
Hide it or the cops will arrest you.
Why will they arrest me?
I know you supply patients this stuff, Topaz.
Useless bugger, you are!
Major Gonzalves
takes a sleeping pill every night.
If the two mix...
he'll rest in eternal peace.
God bless you, nurse.
Where do you think you're going?
And...
What is this?
Nurse, why show me dirty pictures?
What will the new guy
think about you?
Chatterjee is on the pot for hours
looking at these photos.
He has had two heart operations.
Such photos will make his heart race
and ultimately flatline!
I am not done with you yet.
You... stay away from Topaz.
He's a gambler.
He loses his money in the lottery
along with everyone else's.
Stop now, I've never lost
anyone else's money.
Really?
- Enlighten us...
- Speak.
Whose money has he gambled away?
- Mine, nurse!
- Mine.
The lottery isn't gambling.
It's a game of luck.
Precisely!
Playing on luck is gambling, Topaz.
Murlikant Petkar's house?
Long live the soldier,
long live the farmer!
Ma...
Murli.
Brother!
Lie down.
Relax, lie down.
Doctor, the bullet...
You took it out properly?
No, Murli.
The bullet is lodged such that
if I try to remove it,
it could further damage you.
Your whole body could get paralysed.
How will I walk?
Murli, you took nine bullets.
You should be grateful to be alive.
I'm a sportsman, sir.
What use is such a life for me?
Murli!
Don't worry.
Look at me.
Once you're back home,
everything will be fine.
Okay?
Your mother will care for you.
Don't cry.
Don't worry.
Isn't this a lovely place?
Murli, I spoke to the doctor.
Do you know what he said?
He said, if you swim,
you'll gain strength.
Swim daily.
You'll recover faster.
I don't want to stay here.
I want to go home, brother.
Mother is old.
Dad and I run the shop the whole day.
The kids...
they need something or the other.
You haven't been to the village
since so long.
Coming back in this condition...
You don't even have bladder control.
There are doctors here.
Nurses, also. You have help.
You have everything here.
At home...
Plus the money issue...
Murli, I'm not saying you can't come home.
It's your home.
But think about it.
You'll be better off here.
Don't worry about mother.
I'll tell her the doctors said,
"Murli will recover faster here."
You're my champion.
Mother...
Sir, the court is calling.
It's time for the appearance.
I'll have to answer.
Hello? Yes... Kamble sir has left.
It's been a while.
Sir has left.
It's been 20 minutes.
He's on his way to court.
You can't get through to Kamble sir?
Can't get through to Kamble sir!
Network is sometimes a problem.
Sorry, sir. Bye.
Dad, you never mentioned
Jagannath uncle did that.
There's something graver
I've never told anyone.
What, Dad?
I hope you understand it now.
It was my birthday...
Happy birthday to you!
There was nothing in life
worth celebrating.
But Topaz saw my birthdate in the records.
So, I had to cut a cake.
Great, Murli!
You're a year older.
What do you want as a gift?
I'll get it for you.
A bottle of whiskey?
Whiskey.
What? Murli!
But you don't drink.
You just said, I'm older now.
No! It's very dangerous.
You saw how the nurse fired me.
I'll lose my job if I get caught.
If you get me whiskey...
If you get me whiskey,
I'll give you money for the lottery.
- The lottery?
- Yes.
No, it's very dangerous.
How much?
100 rupees!
Happy birthday, Murli brother!
Drink up. Easy.
Last evening, God spoke in my dream...
Topaz, bet on the numbers I tell you.
You'll hit the jackpot.
Want to try your luck on your birthday?
Bet all I've got.
Lately, God and I don't get along.
So, bet on a number above
what He said to you.
That'll be 1, 2, 3.
So?
That sequence hasn't come in decades.
And if someone does get it,
then you're God's favorite.
It's settled, then.
Let's see who's His favorite.
Is it?
I'm off.
Last five minutes.
No more bets after this.
Place your bets. Last five minutes.
I bet 100 rupees.
- 100?
- 100 rupees.
- What numbers?
- 2, 3, 4.
- Another 100.
- 100 more?
On 1, 2, 3.
- Whose pocket have you picked?
- Shut up!
I'm a reputable man.
Ratan Khatri is here.
Today's number will be revealed
to see who's the lucky winner.
Who'll pick the first number?
Me!
The first number is... two!
Two! My money has doubled.
Second number is, three.
Three.
I'm winning the jackpot.
Next number... four.
I told Murli to bet on 2, 3, 4.
Today's last number...
Today's last number is... one!
Ace.
1, 2, 3.
Who's the lucky person
who bet on 1, 2, 3?
Murli!
Brother!
Get up.
Murli, get up.
How much have you had to drink?
Murli, get up. You won the jackpot!
You've won 44,000 in the lottery.
44,000!
Let's collect the prize money.
He's throwing up something rotten.
Are you okay, brother?
Topaz, I need to pee.
- Pee?
- Yes.
But how do you know?
I don't know.
I'm feeling the pressure!
Pressure! What do you mean?
Sensation in your pelvis!
Money in and pee out.
All in one night!
Happy birthday!
Get up and let's get the money.
It's been 10 years since
anyone got a 1, 2, 3.
You're God's favorite.
No one has such luck.
Whatever you touch will turn to gold.
Ratan Khatri was right.
Whatever my business with God,
it wasn't in His plans
for me to die this way.
In Kandheri, Patil's people chased me.
I survived.
I took nine bullets. And survived.
I swallowed 30 sleeping pills,
with whiskey
and I puked it all out.
That day, I decided I would live.
And fight with everything
I've got, to live.
I tried my best.
I couldn't stand up and box,
so I started swimming.
Topaz said, everyone is equal in water.
Even fish don't have legs!
War is nasty, Chhotu.
The ones who start it, lose nothing.
The ones who fight it, lose everything.
Karnail was my first and only friend.
If he hadn't extended his hand
in the train...
I would've still been in that village.
Dead or alive, who knows.
And in front of my eyes...
I'll take you someplace tomorrow.
Where?
Dara!
Seeing this?
He's 40 but still fights.
Know why?
He saw a dream that hasn't come true.
To be a world champion.
Dara!
You consider him your first mentor,
don't you?
I always wanted to be like him.
What changed?
What?
Why did you stop trying?
What are you saying, Ali sir?
- You know...
- I don't.
If this man can fight at 40,
why did you stop trying?
My legs don't function.
- So!
- So?
You stopped living?
- No, but...
- Then why stop dreaming?
I don't get it.
I can't dream sitting
in this condition.
I can only exist.
Exist...
Heard of someone who doesn't have
both legs but can lift 310 kgs?
A man without a leg,
but can high jump five feet?
A woman crushed under a truck,
who lost her limbs
but wins the Gold in cycling?
Heard such stories?
I have.
These are Paralympic participants.
Paralympics?
A dream is over when we stop dreaming.
Your childhood dream isn't over yet.
If you strive,
you can still reach the Olympics.
Learn from your first mentor.
A champion may fall,
but they never stop.
Winning isn't defeating your opponent.
True winning is silencing that voice
that says you've lost... without trying.
Win over that voice.
Then you'll be a true champion
and win an Olympic medal.
That's who you have to become.
Will you?
Can you?
Will you become a champion?
I will!
I'll become a champion!
Again.
Did Mr. Petkar come back?
No, sir.
What's his village's name?
Islampur.
Sir...
Mr. Petkar was right.
If he's telling the truth,
you'll get all the credit.
He has won
an international Silver medal.
For the army! Not a joke.
Shut up, weasel!
Why instigate sir?
If Petkar's lying...
sir will lose his job. What then?
I've got a fantastic idea.
I can tell you--
Quiet! Want a beating?
- Quiet!
- Hear him?
I'm telling you! Quiet.
What's your idea? Get him down.
I'm coming, sir. Open it.
We'll sit and talk.
Tell me.
Sir, let's get a journalist.
- Okay...
- A journalist.
We'll ask them to write
an article about Mr. Petkar.
If it's true, you'll get credit.
If it's not,
the reporter will be at fault.
Very simple. Am I right?
Thank you.
Sir, think carefully. He's a swine.
Mind your tongue!
- What?
- Yes.
Hello, Mr. Petkar.
What are you doing here?
You never returned.
Kamble sir was remembering you.
He has sent a noted reporter.
Hello.
To hear your full story.
Tell sir, I don't want an award.
Don't want it?
Sir, a moment...
He didn't want the award for himself.
But, for our village.
For basic infrastructure.
Now, he's doing that too himself.
He doesn't want it.
And he was making the road?
Yes. Along with the villagers.
Okay.
Madam, he doesn't want the Arjuna Award.
Not anymore.
- He doesn't want the Arjuna Award?
- No, madam.
Will you do one thing?
Murlikant Petkar.
You've matched the best timing
of the Commonwealth Games.
Congratulations!
It's very impressive.
It also makes you eligible
for the Paralympics but...
I am sorry, Murli.
The Indian Olympic committee has decided
no one will represent India
in swimming this time.
But sir, if the timing matches, what's--
Matching the best timing
at the Commonwealth Games
and winning the Paralympics
are very different.
Know the Paralympic record
for 50m freestyle?
37.90 seconds.
And Commonwealth Games
is 39.85 seconds.
These two seconds mean
there are globally at least 15 swimmers
faster than Murlikant.
If you want to win at the Paralympics,
you have to beat
the world's best swimmers.
Which is impossible.
Murli, we fought a war
against Pakistan a year ago.
The country's treasury is empty.
With the little allocated to sport,
we've been asked to spend carefully
on regular Olympic athletes.
So, Paralympics aren't worthy for you.
It's neither the regular Olympics,
nor with regular athletes.
They can't even walk.
Why waste money on them?
Murli, it's not that...
It is!
We're here for society to pity on.
Isn't it?
If we perform spectacularly,
who will society pity?
No one considers a man fighting life
on his own accord.
No!
He must be constantly reminded
of what's being done for him
even though he's not regular.
We are regular people, sir.
With regular hope
and regular passion.
And regular strength.
Only your outlook isn't regular.
Murli...
You talk of war to this man? Him!
He lost both legs in the '65 war.
Now, you steal his dream
by making the '71 war an excuse?
Really?
Such a prestigious post
and such shallow thinking.
Comrade, how's your revolution?
It will happen one day.
All the best.
Tell me, how can I help?
Still posted at Secunderabad EME?
Yes, two more months. Need anything?
I wanted the details of an old soldier.
Please look into your old records.
A very interesting man...
if he's telling the truth.
When was he posted here?
Around 1964.
50 years ago?
They won't be in the computer records.
Oh!
Send me the details.
I'll go to the filing room.
Thanks. Right away.
I'll call back.
Yes, Major.
I found Murlikant Petkar's file.
It has so much more
than what you sent.
Even I'm shocked.
In fact, I'll take this file
to the Army headquarters.
Headquarters? What's in it?
Murli!
Where's Murli?
What happened?
Mr. Murlikant Rajaram Petkar,
the Indian Olympic Committee
has unanimously decided
for the 4th Paralympics being held
in Munich, West Germany in August 1972...
You will represent India in swimming!
Yay!
Chhotu,
- where are you going so late?
- I woke up, sir.
It's 8 am in Bombay.
Up for a walk?
It's 4:30 am here.
Why isn't this in our records?
Sir, all sports records before 1980
are in the old files.
These were archived, too.
Confirm Petkar's details with the
German Olympic Committee immediately.
Sir.
Murli!
Are you okay?
What's happening, sir?
A terrorist attack.
Some dead and some are held hostage.
Let's go.
They've now said,
there were 11 hostages.
Two were killed
in their rooms yesterday morning.
Nine were killed at the airport tonight.
The games of the 20th Olympiad
have now been officially suspended.
Tomorrow morning
in the huge Olympic stadium
there will be a memorial service--
What did he say?
The Olympics have been cancelled.
11 athletes are dead.
Yes?
The German Olympic committee said
the Olympics were paused
due to the terrorist attack
in Munich that year.
The Paralympics were shifted
to Heidelberg.
Whatever Petkar achieved at Heidelberg...
there's no record in India.
In lane 4, the world record holder
from Poland Andrzej Seremak.
In lane 5 is the Commonwealth champion,
Andrew Nicholls.
India's only swimming contestant,
Murlikant Petkar.
There are six contestants in this race
with better timing than yours.
You must be in the top 4
to move to the next round.
Got it?
Murli brother.
Take your marks.
First heat of the mens 50m freestyle.
Murlikant has a bad start.
He's in the last position.
Belgium's Jespers leads,
leaving Poland's Seremak behind.
Swimmers cross the half mark.
Murlikant in the 6th position.
He must catch up
to qualify for the next heat.
Make it to the top 4.
It seems India is set to lose
in swimming again.
Murlikant suddenly picks up speed
changing the board.
Petkar in 5th position,
leaving France's Bocquet behind.
Nearing the finish,
Murlikant in 4th, far from Roger Bates.
Murlikant gives it his all.
Murlikant catches up with Bates.
His every stroke bringing them closer.
Murlikant behind by one stroke.
Murlikant and Bates now neck and neck!
A photo finish!
Murlikant gave his best but
may have taken a bit longer.
Positions revealed...
Seremak is first, Nicholls second
and Jespers is third.
Awaiting the 4th position.
Who makes it to the next heat?
England's Bates
or India's Murlikant Petkar?
Hearts are racing.
Murlikant Petkar!
India's young swimmer
has qualified for the next heat.
An unbelievable story.
But one that must be told.
Murlikant Rajaram Petkar.
The story of a man
who was nameless
and went back into the shadows.
After 50 years,
it's important to tell this story.
For it to reach you.
Who is Murlikant Petkar?
And what is he made of?
The second heat starts.
Murlikant has a better start.
He is in 5th position.
Murlikant leaves
Belgium's Jespers behind
but New Zealand's Nicholls,
still ahead of both.
The first three swimmers
will go into the Finals.
Murlikant in 4th place.
Jespers giving him tough competition.
Murlikant picks up speed
leaving Nicholls behind.
Murlikant now in 3rd place.
Petkar faces a tough fight from
New Zealand and Belgium.
Can Petkar qualify for the Finals?
Poland's Seremak in first position.
West Germany in second
and India's Murlikant Petkar in 3rd position
confirming his place in the Finals.
Switch off the alarm.
Chhotu.
He's fast asleep.
Come on. It's race day.
Wake up.
Chhotu?
How much will you sleep?
Chhotu.
Chhotu?
Murli?
What happened, sir?
You were unconscious.
What's happened?
What happened?
I'm fine, sir.
Where did this blood come from?
What happened?
I fell the other day...
hurt myself a little.
Where?
On the head, sir.
Where on the head?
Ali sir, I'm fine.
Isn't it where you got hit by a bullet?
Your skull fracture.
Your injury has opened.
Get ready.
We have to go to the doctor.
Let it be, sir.
Why don't you get it, idiot?
If you hit the edge of the pool
even slightly,
know what will happen?
- Nothing will happen, sir.
- You'll die!
I won't die, sir!
If I enter the pool, I may die
but if I don't swim today
with all my might, I'll surely die.
Ali sir, every player here
has repeatedly heard,
"You can't do this and that."
But they turned a deaf ear.
That's why they're here.
And so am I.
Ever since my childhood I was told,
"You're no good."
You're not a champion.
You're a loser.
They made fun of me in my village.
Chandu Champion. Loser champion!
I want to fight today.
For every loser who wanted
to become a champion.
For every loser
who can become a champion.
You had said,
"Winning isn't defeating your opponent."
True winning is silencing that voice
that says you've lost... without trying.
I must win over that voice.
I also must.
Now, for the sports news.
In the 4th Paralympics in West Germany,
India's Murlikant Petkar will swim
in the Finals.
It is the first time in Olympic history,
an Indian swimmer has reached the Finals.
Murlikant Petkar is from Sangli,
Maharashtra.
Murli has been a part of the EME
and represented the Indian Army
in boxing.
In the 1965 war
he was posted in Kashmir.
Our Murli! Ma...
Move out of the way.
Ma!
What happened?
Why are you crying?
Murli...
What happened to Murli?
Mother...
What is it?
What happened to Murli?
Tell me. What happened to him?
Murli has reached...
Where?
- Murli has reached the Olympics.
- What?
Yes. Olympics!
Olympics!
Yes.
- The Olympics, Ma!
- Really?
Yes, I heard it on the radio.
At the shop with father...
Our Murli has reached the Olympics, Ma.
For the first time in Olympic history,
an Indian has reached the swimming Finals.
Murlikant Petkar is at the brink
of making history.
Sit!
He competes
with the world's best swimmers.
Take your marks.
The Final 50m freestyle race begins.
Murlikant has a poor start.
He's in 6th position.
Murlikant falling short
amongst the best swimmers.
Hey, loser champion!
The boxer from India has been defeated.
Murlikant Petkar picks up speed
leaving America's Robert behind.
Murlikant is in 4th position.
It's the day Murlikant's been waiting for.
He gives it his all.
Racing ahead of New Zealand's Nicholls,
Petkar's takes 3rd position.
Murlikant in 2nd position,
leaving Olbrich behind.
Who would've thought an Indian swimmer
would give world champion, Seremak,
a run for the Gold.
A few seconds for the race to end.
Murlikant picks up speed with every stroke.
Come on.
Murlikant neck and neck with Seremak.
And over!
History has been made!
India wins its first
individual Gold medal.
And the man's name is Murlikant Petkar.
A historic day for Indian sport.
It's a new world record!
Murlikant Petkar has broken the world record
in 50m freestyle.
Come on Murli brother.
With a new world record timing of 37.33 seconds.
The gold medal goes to Murlikant Petkar of India.
That day Murlikant Petkar's dream came true.
However, this unbelievable story
was lost in the sands of time.
But, it's important to take
the dust off the story
for Murli's story to get it's due in history.
Murlikant sir.
I'm Vishwas Patil.
Additional Secretary
in the Ministry of Home Affairs.
You wanted to apply for the Arjuna Award,
but the Government of India doesn't want
to give you that award.
You deserve a bigger award
for what you've done for this country...
The President of India wants to honor you
with the Padmashri.
- Padmashri?
- Yes.
Dad...
Murlikant Petkar's story
is the story of free India.
The year of liberation - 1947.
Circumstances were such
Could the country even survive?
The destination seemed unattainable,
but India fights with determination...
against all odds.
Similarly, Murlikant fights,
India wouldn't accept defeat,
nor would Murlikant.
Both had a dream
to achieve something
and prove themselves
remove all doubt, every question
and counter every ridicule
by turning around and saying,
"Hey, what are you laughing about?"