[♪♪♪]
Good morning, sir.
MAN:
Dicky Chow!
Just look at yourself.
You're covered in dirt.
I just--
Don't move!
And don't give me
the usual routine.
Why are you
always so untidy?
What's the matter,
Mr. Cao?
Explain yourself!
Let me talk to him.
MR. CAO:
Hmph.
Where did the dirt come from,
Dicky?
Well, on my way to school,
I slipped and fell over.
Don't your mom or dad
bring you to school?
Mom died a long time ago
and Dad's very busy.
What does your dad do?
He's a coolie.
I'd like to meet him one day.
Would that be possible?
I don't think
he has the time.
When he's available, then.
Will you let me know?
Go clean up
before class starts.
Thanks, Miss Yuen.
[♪♪♪]
I want to be a superstar.
Like who?
Nicole Kidman.
She gets $20 million
for a movie.
I wouldn't mind
being her either.
I want to be an entrepreneur.
What kind of business?
Any kind,
as long as it's really big.
Big business always pays out.
Why not?
[LAUGHING]
I want to be a poor person.
[ALL LAUGHING]
Stop!
My dad says
if you have integrity,
don't lie, don't fight
and study really hard,
then people will respect you
even if you're poor.
[CLAPPING]
Don't...
Don't come over here!
Put it down!
Go back to your seat!
[♪♪♪]
[CHATTERING IN MANDARIN]
[BELL RINGING IN DISTANCE]
[BELL RINGING]
[ALL YELLING]
BOY:
The name of this amazing dog
is CJ1.
It was developed jointly
by U.S., French
and German scientists.
Imagine!
Jointly developed!
Do you want a go?
Yes, please.
Back off, loser.
There are only two
in the world.
The U.S. president's daughter
has the other one.
What are you doing?
Eating noodles.
Stand up!
No matter how much
you eat,
you are doomed
to be a dwarf.
Now get lost!
The quality of the students
in this place
gets worse every day.
What have we here,
another alien?
What are you doing?
Eating rice.
You're just like
a huge tub of lard.
Maybe you should go
see the doctor.
You eat so much.
It's horrible!
Someone call the police
to shoot this monster!
ALL:
Eat to death! Giant monster!
What are you doing?!
[SOBBING]
Bullies! Heroes don't hit women.
Not you again.
Ignore him.
BOY:
Go away, poor boy.
We don't want you around.
[BOYS GIGGLING]
[♪♪♪]
[FOOTSTEPS
APPROACHING]
Hi.
You've been sent off
the field too?
Yes.
Did you forget your sneakers?
I brought them, but I didn't
wear them on purpose.
Why?
Because I wanted to be
with you.
[GULPS]
Are all your shoes
like that?
Yes, they are.
My dad gets them
from the dump.
Your dad's so nice.
He is, actually.
But I so much want a new pair
because I really love sports.
I'd like you
to keep the old ones.
Why?
Then we'd be punished together,
forever.
[GULPS]
[CHATTERING IN MANDARIN]
Get that panel up there.
Quickly!
You. Hurry up.
You're no longer needed.
Go home.
Hey, boss?
With it being so hot right now,
my son can't sleep.
I need to buy
an electric fan.
Can't you keep me on?
You should be
paying me back instead.
I paid all the bills when
your wife got sick and died.
Look at yourself. You'll die
before your debts are repaid.
You're starving yourself
so your son can go
to that fancy school.
If my son can go
to public school,
why can't yours?
Well, I want him
to have opportunities.
I don't want him
to end up like me.
But you have
to have capability.
He's highly capable.
I'm talking about you,
not him.
All you have is a casual job
with no prospects.
How are you going to cope?
I can manage.
You can't manage!
I can.
You can't!
I can manage.
Very well.
Block B. Foundations.
Thanks.
If you want to die,
I can't stop you. Shame on you.
[CONCRETE CRUMBLING]
[♪♪♪]
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
You're back.
Can we have dinner?
I'm starving.
Just step back a bit.
What's going on?
Turn round.
Come here.
What?
An electric fan!
That's so great! Is it real?
We finally have a fan!
Now sit down and let me turn it.
Quickly, Dad!
[FAN CLICKS]
[ZAPS]
[GRUNTS]
Dad, did you find this
in the garbage?
No, I bought it.
It cost a lot of money.
You were ripped off!
No, it was fine
when I bought it.
So how come
it's not working now?
Dumbass.
Use your head next time.
"Dumbass"?
Where did you get that from?
A guy in my class.
Oh, really?
Well, let me tell you,
we may be poor,
but we don't use bad language.
We don't steal.
We don't rob.
We don't take things
that don't belong to us.
You must concentrate
on your studies.
I didn't study at all
when I was young
and look where
it's gotten me.
[♪♪♪]
[INSECT BUZZING]
We're having
an apple today?
Yes, we are.
But put it down now.
Finish your dinner first.
Hey, Dad, my sneakers
are worn out again.
Will you buy me
some more?
I need you to get me
a better pair,
or I'll be sent off
the field again.
Got it. Don't worry.
Mm.
You're still eating!
Lay off the cockroach.
You can get it
after you've finished.
Hey.
Hey. Hey, hey, hey.
Hey. Hey. Hey.
Hey!
[♪♪♪]
Nice. You've improved.
Not bad.
[DOOR CLOSES]
[♪♪♪]
[LAUGHING]
[BEEPING]
There have been many sightings
lately of UFOs,
Unidentified Flying Objects.
What happened
to the cartoons?
They'll be back
in a minute.
Could you please tell us
what happened?
I saw a flying object.
It flew from here to there
with a "whew" sound.
Can you describe
the object in more detail?
That object
could really fly.
Though it wobbled a bit.
I suspect
it had crashed before.
Crashed?
Yes, like a car crash.
It might have been broken.
I took a picture of it.
Hmm.
What kind of camera
did you use?
It was expensive, but I can't
possibly tell you the make.
Did this particular
flying object make a sound?
It made some "whew" sounds
like I just told you.
"Whew." Do you hear me?
Ha-ha.
Unbelievable.
[HORNS HONKING]
[TRAIN CHUGGING]
[TOYS BEEPING]
Don't run off like that.
Dad,
this is called a CJ1.
Everyone at school has one.
They're great!
Really?
Let's go home. Put it back.
Oh.
[♪♪♪]
What's the matter?
Why can't I have it?
We'll buy it
after I get paid next month.
Now, put it down.
Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey.
Hey!
Let go!
Hey.
Didn't you hear me?
I have no money.
If you buy me this,
I'll never ask
for anything ever again.
I beg you.
[WOMAN SPEAKING
IN MANDARIN]
What about this one?
What features does it have?
Let go.
Let go!
[SMACK]
[SOBBING]
Let go!
[SMACK]
[WAILING]
Let go!
[SMACK]
Come back!
Sir? Do you wish to buy that?
[♪♪♪]
Come on, Dicky.
Don't cry.
Stop crying now.
Good boy, stop crying.
Dicky.
Are you Mr. Chow?
I'm Miss Yuen, Dicky's teacher.
Good to meet you.
Miss Yuen.
Good to meet you too.
Is Dicky well-behaved
at school?
Yes, he's quite good.
He's in a really bad mood
right now.
I know. Kids just want
every toy they see.
True.
Just happens I didn't bring
any money today, so...
Dicky, go to your dad.
Come here.
[LAUGHS]
I'm sorry, Mr. Chow.
Don't worry. He's like that.
In fact,
I'd like to do a home visit.
He did tell me,
but I'm very busy at work...
I believe
that a good education
doesn't just rely
on the teacher.
That's why I'd like
to involve you.
It'll be good for him.
Ah, yes. I see.
Dicky,
I need to go now.
Don't be so grumpy.
And listen to your dad, okay?
Okay?
I must go.
Okay.
Bye, now.
[♪♪♪]
[AIR HISSING]
[STATIC HISSING]
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLING]
[CHATTERING IN MANDARIN]
[CRASHING]
[ELECTRICITY ZAPS]
[DOOR OPENS]
Dicky.
Look at me.
I have something
way better than CJ1.
Do you want to see it?
Are you sure?
In that case,
I'll throw it away
and get back to work.
[DOOR CLOSES]
[♪♪♪]
[SQUEAKING]
Goodbye, sir.
Goodbye.
Fanny.
Where's this amazing toy,
then?
Look!
What's so great about that?
It's fun. Look!
It doesn't look
that fun to me.
What do you think?
Actually, I agree.
It's no fun.
Never mind.
See you tomorrow.
Hey.
What's that thing
you're holding?
Nothing.
It looks
like rubbish.
Says who?
This is way better than CJ1.
So, what's it called?
It's called CJ7.
Pathetic piece of crap.
Your dad found it
in the garbage.
Don't talk about my dad like
that! I'm going to beat you up.
Oh, yeah?
[BLOWS WHISTLE]
[THUD]
[♪♪♪]
Hello.
[CRUNCH]
[BOTH SCREAMING]
[THUNDER CRASHING]
MR. CHOW:
How many times
do I have to tell you?
We might be poor,
but we don't fight.
You really disappoint me.
Look at this.
Your uniform's all torn.
What was the fight about?
They were laughing at me.
What about?
[SQUEAKING]
Well?
[SQUEAKS]
[HISSES]
Fine.
If you're not going
to tell me...
[WOOD CLATTERS]
[WHIRRING]
...then I have no choice
in the matter.
[♪♪♪]
Last chance!
[THUNDER CRASHING]
It's moving!
[SHUTTERS BANGING]
[WHIRS]
[GASPS]
[SCREAMS]
There are ghosts.
Ghosts? Where?
There. In the ball.
Don't change
the subject!
You think you can
run rings around me,
but you're not as clever
as you think.
Your uniform's a mess. What will
you wear for school tomorrow?
Hm.
Do I have to go hunt
for another one?
MR. CHOW:
I'll deal with you later.
[♪♪♪]
[SCREAMING]
There's a ghost!
Hanging over there!
Help! Ghost!
It's horrible!
There's a red ghost
hanging there!
Hanging! Too horrible!
Calm down!
It's a broken lamp.
Can't you see?
[LAMP RATTLES]
[SCREAMING]
Not again!
You're a ghost too.
Stop shouting! I'll send you
outside if you don't stop!
Understand?
[DOOR CREAKING]
[♪♪♪]
[RUSTLING]
Mmm!
Are you on drugs
or something?
[SCREAMING]
What are you doing?
Please don't lock me in!
There's a ghost.
You have to believe me.
Let me out!
Please let me out!
[WHIMPERING]
Help me, Lord.
[♪♪♪]
[THUD]
[GRUNTS]
[THUDDING]
[SQUEAKING]
Learned your lesson now?
Yes, Dad.
Will you behave
yourself now?
I will. I really will.
I have to get back to work.
Okay! Off you go. Bye-bye!
[DOOR CLOSES]
[CREATURE COOING]
[SQUEAKS]
Are you from outer space?
[COOS]
Have you come to invade Earth?
[COOING]
[SQUEAKS]
[BARKS]
[COUGHING]
[GIGGLING]
[TRILLS]
[SQUEAKS]
[COOING]
I think you might be
an alien toy dog.
[COOING]
[SHRIEKS]
My name is Dicky.
Can I call you CJ7?
[SQUEAKS]
If you wag your tail,
it means you like it!
CJ7!
[SQUEAKS]
CJ7.
[GIGGLING]
[SQUEAKS]
[BONEY M'S "SUNNY" PLAYING
OVER SPEAKERS]
♪ Sunny ♪
♪ Yesterday my life was-- ♪
[MUSIC STOPS]
[RADIO TUNING]
♪ Sunny ♪
♪ You smiled at me ♪
♪ And really eased the pain ♪
♪ The dark days are gone ♪
♪ And the bright days
Are here ♪
♪ My Sunny one
Shines so sincere ♪
♪ Sunny one so true ♪
♪ I love you ♪
[HUMMING]
♪ Sunny ♪
[WHINES]
The apples in our house
are always rotten.
So how come
this one's not?
You know magic?
[SQUEAKS]
Wow! It's so sweet.
You really do know magic.
I'm going to be rich!
[♪♪♪]
[DOG GROWLING]
If you can beat
the most vicious dog on Earth,
then you really are
a superdog from space.
Go!
[SQUEAKS]
[BARKING]
[SHRIEKING]
[SHRIEKS]
[DOG WHINING]
[CJ7 SHRIEKS]
[DOG WHINES]
[SHRIEKS]
Oh, my God!
[♪♪♪]
I have a test today
and I've been playing with you
instead of studying.
But I really want to get 100.
Can you help me?
[SQUEAKS]
[GRUNTING]
[TOOLS CLATTERING]
What's that you're making?
Dicky Chow.
Why are you wearing
those glasses?
My eyes hurt.
Do you want to take a look?
No, I don't.
Sit down.
Oh.
Begin writing now!
[♪♪♪]
[BUZZING]
[BEEPING]
[GLASSES BEEPING]
[GLASSES BEEP]
[BOTH BUZZING]
[GLASS CRACKS]
Sorry, sir.
There was a fly.
A fly?
[GLASS CRACKS]
Sorry, sir.
There was a fly.
[GLASS TINKLES]
[GIGGLES]
I now have the results
of today's test.
And for the first time,
Dicky Chow got 100.
[ALL GASP]
[YELLING]
Thank you, sir!
Hold on a minute.
I want to see those glasses.
[♪♪♪]
Those super-glasses
were fantastic!
It's P.E. next,
so I'll need super-sneakers!
[CHUCKLES]
[SQUEAKS]
[GRUNTING]
[SPARKS CRACKLING]
[DRILL WHIRRING]
This is so exciting.
[SQUEAKS]
MAN:
Excellence at the high jump
requires talent, hard work,
training,
a good night's sleep,
and finally,
respect for your teacher.
This is
my personal record.
So far no one has
bettered it.
[WHIRRING]
I have new sneakers today, sir.
[♪♪♪]
Sir.
He just broke your record.
[LAUGHING]
Dicky,
it doesn't ring true
that a kid can jump
that high.
Be a good boy and do it again.
[SQUEAKING]
[CLATTERING]
[MAN SPEAKS
IN MANDARIN]
Dicky Chow. What are
those shoes you're wearing?
It's none of your business!
This is too much.
You drove me to this.
Come down!
[GASPS]
[GRUNTING]
[♪♪♪]
[CHUCKLES]
[YELLING]
Dicky! Are you out of your mind?
I...
Over here.
Catch him!
Come to your senses, Dicky.
Miss Yuen, bitterness,
like the sea, is boundless.
Dicky!
MAN:
Dicky Chow! How can you jump
so high? Come down this minute!
[ALL CLAMORING
IN MANDARIN]
[YELPS]
[CRACKLING,
SPUTTERING]
[SHRIEKS]
[ALL CLAMORING
IN MANDARIN]
MR. CHOW:
How on earth
can you sleep like that?
Wake up.
It's nearly time for school.
What do I have to do
to get you up in the morning?
It was all a dream?
[RUSTLING]
[SQUEAKS]
[GASPS]
You're real.
I'm getting ready right now!
[SQUEAKS]
[GROANS]
Dad, I'm going to get 100
on the exam today.
What?
I'm going to get 100!
Really?
Yes! All on my own!
One hundred!
That's great.
[DOG GROWLING]
If you can beat
the most vicious dog on Earth,
then you really are
a superdog from space.
Go!
[GROWLING]
[BARKING]
[CHITTERS]
[BARKS, GROWLS]
[CJ7 SHRIEKS]
[♪♪♪]
[GASPS]
[SCREAMING]
[GRUNTS]
[GROANING]
[DOG BARKING]
Run!
[♪♪♪]
[SIGHS]
So, what happened back there?
[COOING]
[ZAPS]
You're supposed to be
the superdog from space.
Don't tell me
you were just pretending.
[COOS]
Seriously.
I have to get 100
on the exam.
I need you to work
your magic for me.
[SQUEAKS]
Come on, now. Please!
I'm not joking.
[GRUNTING]
You have to give me
magic weapons.
[GRUNTING]
[♪♪♪]
[QUIVERING]
[LOUD POP]
[SQUEAKS]
[FLY BUZZES]
Time's up.
What? But I haven't
started yet.
Hey.
What's with the turd?
Turd? It's not that!
Shows how much you know!
[SCREAMING]
[ALL LAUGH]
[GURGLING]
[COUGHING]
You set me up!
[SNEEZES]
I'm going to kill you!
[GURGLING]
Give me the magic weapons now!
[QUIVERS]
[LOUD POPPING]
Why, you...
[MACHINE-GUNNING]
You...
Please, sir.
Can I say something?
MAN:
No, you can't.
You are a poor student.
You are always dirty,
and you are very wicked.
You discredit the school.
There's nothing more to say.
Now clean him up!
[KIDS LAUGHING]
DICKY:
CJ7?
Please come out.
Why would I be mad at you?
We're good friends.
The turd wasn't important.
I've seen it all before.
Let's just forget
it ever happened. Okay?
In fact,
I love you very much.
[SQUEAKS]
Do you know that?
[BARKS]
[TRILLING]
CJ7? Come here.
[SQUEAKS]
Closer!
[♪♪♪]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[CJ7 CHITTERING]
I'm going to stab you to death!
[GRUNTING]
[PANTING]
Rubbish dog from space.
You're low-tech and boring.
I got blamed and laughed at.
And all because of you.
If you're just an animal,
then say so!
Don't pretend
you have magic powers!
But did it ever say that?
Did I get it wrong?
Have I made a mistake?
I know I've made a mistake!
[♪♪♪]
[GASPS]
Wait!
Hey! Wait!
[CRYING]
Dicky! What's happened?
CJ7 has disappeared.
Shh.
Look.
[HOWLS, SQUEAKS]
CJ7?
[SQUEAKING]
I'm sorry.
I missed you so much.
I thought I'd never
see you again.
[LAUGHING]
And you're not angry with me.
You two already met?
[CJ7 TRILLING]
Is it a toy?
Yes, it is.
And it can walk
and move its eyes?
Where did you get it?
Someone at school
lent it to me.
[GRUNTING]
Where's the cover?
Where do the batteries go?
[SQUEALS]
It doesn't need them.
It's high-tech.
I've never seen
anything like it before.
[GRUNTING]
[THUD]
Did you see that?
Yes, I did.
It's all bendy.
[SQUEAKING]
Don't! I have
to give it back soon.
MR. CHOW:
It's fine.
What are you doing, Dad?
Nothing!
[SHRIEKS]
[QUIVERING]
[POP]
[SQUEAKS]
See, I told you it'd be fine.
It gets its shape back. Look!
[GASPS]
This is fun.
No more squeezing it!
That's enough!
Everything is high-tech
nowadays.
Basically there's no future
for uneducated people like us.
Dad, I don't want
to lie to you,
so CJ7 came out of the ball
you gave me.
It came from outer space.
How many times
do I have to tell you?
We might be poor,
but we don't lie,
we don't fight,
and we don't take things
that don't belong to us.
Study hard and be a useful
person in the future.
[♪♪♪]
[DICKY MOANS]
It's so hot.
[SQUEAKS]
[GRUNTING]
[GRUNTS]
[WHIRRING]
[♪♪♪]
[COOS]
[BEEPING]
Well, I'll be...
The hottest night and it starts
to work. Lucky, or what?
I'm off to school now.
Have you got
your lunch box?
Yes, I have.
Hey. How was the exam?
Mmm.
How come your head's gone red?
[YAWNING]
You don't look so good today.
Didn't you sleep last night?
[BUZZING]
[SQUEAKS]
Get inside and go to sleep.
You! Stop!
What's that thing
inside your bag?
Nothing.
I need to check your schoolbag!
What for?
I don't have
to tell you that.
Let go!
[ALL SHOUTING]
[SQUEAKS]
[GASPS]
Ah.
Oh.
What's that?
Let me see.
[SQUEAKING]
ALL:
Give it to me! Let me see first!
Give it to me! Don't pull!
[SHRIEKING]
[♪♪♪]
[SHRIEKS]
ALL:
Get it!
[BOYS CLAMORING]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[TRILLING]
[SQUEAKS]
[SHRIEKS]
[SCREAMS]
What is this weird thing?
Don't touch it!
Give it back to me!
Get the tool box!
[♪♪♪]
[SQUEAKING]
Open it up and look inside.
Here.
Let him go!
[CJ7 SQUEAKING]
Can't do it.
Try this.
No! Don't do that!
It's not working.
How is that possible?
[WHIRRING]
[SCREAMING]
[GASPS]
You won't do that
to my thing!
So what? Going to hit me?
You won't know what's hit you!
[♪♪♪]
Let him go!
You let him go.
You let me go first.
[GRUNTS]
[GRUNTING]
[GASPS]
[SCREAMING]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[BOY GASPS]
[PANTING]
[YELLS]
[WATER GURGLING]
I don't want a fight!
[GASPS]
[THUNDER CLAPS]
Don't force me to do this!
[CREAKING]
[GASPS]
[♪♪♪]
Are you okay?
I'm fine. Thank you.
You're welcome.
MR. CAO:
What's going on here?
Why were you fighting?
Tell me!
You're going to stand here
until you tell me!
[CHITTERING]
CJ7!
I knew you'd be okay!
Stop. Don't.
Good boy.
What is that thing?
Look! CJ7, sit!
That's cool.
What else does it do?
CJ7, happy face!
[BELL RINGS]
Angry face!
[GROWLING]
Sad face!
[WHIMPERS]
Saw a pretty lady!
[WOLF WHISTLES]
Your apartment's on fire.
[GASPS]
But you just won
the lottery!
[YELLS]
The whole family is dead.
[GASPS]
[GROANS]
You've got 100 on the exam!
[SHRIEKS]
Wicked.
Look!
[CRACKLING]
[CUCKOOING]
Wow, fireworks!
Hey. Where did you get it?
I want one too.
I can't tell you that.
But I want to thank you for
not telling Mr. Cao about this.
Of course not!
We don't discuss
our business with adults.
You have my word!
BOY:
Hey,
you're amazing.
Do you want to be
on our judo team?
They'd all make fun of me.
They wouldn't dare.
Would you make fun
of her?
[♪♪♪]
[CHORTLES]
[GIGGLES]
[ALL LAUGH]
Look at this.
My son got 100 on his exam.
That's a great kid!
Yes! Ha-ha-ha.
Look!
Get away!
He got 100.
[MAN SPEAKING
IN MANDARIN]
Boss.
My kid got 100 on his exam.
So he cheated.
What makes you say that?
My son's really smart, but even
he can't pass without cheating.
So how can your son get 100?
Hard to believe, dickhead.
You're not serious.
Look at the ink. He got zero
and changed it to 100.
He's a liar.
But he's not like that.
I know him better.
Your son cheated.
I can't let you say that.
He cheated!
I'll hit you
if you say that again.
Your son cheated.
You hit me? Just you try!
[GRUNTS]
Your son cheated!
You hit me?
You're fired!
Your son cheated!
Quick!
[TRILLS]
Get inside.
Tell the truth.
Did you cheat on your exam?
No, I didn't.
I think you got zero,
then altered it to 100.
Is that right?
Yes.
But that's not the same
as cheating.
I didn't want you
to be disappointed.
What's wrong with you?
It's so tough to send you
to that school.
I'm sorry, Dad.
I'll say it again.
Even though we're poor--
Okay! I know!
You're so annoying.
Can you stop going on about it?
I changed it. So what?
If there's nothing else,
I'm leaving.
What are you doing?
Why are you taking my things?
If you can't work hard,
then you don't get to play.
Give it back to me!
No.
Why are you taking my stuff?
Why? Because I'm your father!
And I can!
You're bullying me.
I don't have a dad like you!
You always get zeros.
I don't have a son like you.
Leave me alone!
Say it again!
Leave me alone forever!
Okay!
[CJ7 GRUNTS]
If you can use your own brains
to get over 60,
then I'll leave you alone
forever!
It's a deal!
I'm going to get that grade.
Just watch me!
We'll see about that,
Zero Hero!
That's not fair!
I'll show you!
Don't bother me anymore!
[WHIMPERS]
What are you looking at?
[SQUEAKS]
[CHATTERING IN MANDARIN]
Mr. Chow.
Miss Yuen.
Is something wrong? come in.
I won't, thanks.
But Dicky forgot
his lunch box today.
Could you see that he gets it?
Sure. Let me ask someone
to open the gate.
No, please don't.
If his classmates see me,
he'll never live it down.
How come?
I have to go.
Wait.
Dicky told me everything.
He was just being
temperamental.
If you'd allow it, he could
come to my house after school.
We can talk about
what happened.
And there's another exam
tomorrow,
so I can help him
to review.
What do you think?
Oh, thank you. Thank you!
You're welcome.
It's nothing at all.
I appreciate this so much.
It's just a small thing.
Nothing, really.
It's not nothing.
The thing is...
I can't give him
very much myself,
and that makes me feel
very guilty.
But if you were
to help him study,
I could never repay you.
Heh.
You really don't have to.
It's the least I can do.
Then I'll leave him
in your hands.
Sure. You just leave
Dicky to me.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
[♪♪♪]
[CHATTERING IN MANDARIN]
How's the boss feeling today?
You dare to come back?
I have to.
I need to eat.
I know
I have a big mouth,
but I think
we understand each other.
What?
I shouldn't have said that
about your son.
Let's forget it.
Here.
Well...
But he really did cheat.
Who doesn't, sometimes?
The kid is very smart.
I know he'll be successful.
I pray to God
that you're right.
So take it
and buy him some candy.
Hey! This is far too much.
Use it for books, then.
Or school fees.
But now get back to work.
Today must be my lucky day.
[♪♪♪]
[CREAKING]
[CLANGS]
[GRUNTING]
[CJ7 CHITTERING]
[♪♪♪]
I thought
you'd never pass.
Good.
Thanks, Mr. Cao.
What's happening?
Where's
your safety belt?
[GRUNTING]
[YELLS]
[GRUNTS]
[CLANGS]
What's going on here?
Help!
Give me your hand!
Reach out!
[ALL GASP]
Why haven't these been moved?
[LOUD BANG]
What was that?
Hey! Be careful!
[CROWD SHOUTING]
[♪♪♪]
I'm so sorry.
Dicky, you have to come
with me.
[INAUDIBLE DIALOGUE]
[SHOUTING
IN MANDARIN]
Is this your house, Dicky?
Are you hungry?
Do you want to eat?
Dicky, I'm going
to tell you something.
There was a terrible accident
and your dad passed away.
[SNIFFLING]
[CRYING]
There are some things we can't
control. Do you understand?
Don't talk any more, miss.
I want to sleep.
Please leave me.
[♪♪♪]
Dicky, open the door.
[CRYING]
[KNOCKING AT DOOR]
I'm sorry.
Miss Yuen,
I'm very tired.
I need to sleep.
[SOBBING]
Dicky.
[CRYING]
My dad won't leave me alone.
He'll be home
when I wake up.
I need to sleep now.
[SOBBING]
Dicky.
[WAILING]
Dad.
[CJ7 SQUEALING]
[SQUEAKS]
[WHIMPERING]
[SNIFFLING]
[VEHICLE PASSING]
[♪♪♪]
[BEEPING]
[HORN HONKING IN DISTANCE]
[SNORING]
[GRUNTS, GROANS]
Why aren't you
in your pajamas?
[♪♪♪]
Hey. What's up?
Dad, don't ever leave me.
[SNIFFLES]
I'll listen to you,
I'll study hard,
I won't lie,
I won't fight,
and one day I'll be
a really useful person.
[CHUCKLES]
That's good.
[FAINT BEEPING]
[COOING]
CJ7!
How are you?
[BEEPING QUICKENS]
DICKY:
What's that noise?
MR. CHOW:
Yeah, what is it?
Why are you so tired, CJ7?
[TRILLS]
[♪♪♪]
[SQUEAKS]
[BEEPING RAPIDLY]
[YELLS]
[SQUEAKS]
[BEEPING DIES]
[SIZZLING]
What's happened to him, Dad?
Maybe the batteries
have run out.
It wouldn't look like that!
But it's very high-tech.
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLES]
[WIND WHISTLING]
[♪♪♪]
DICKY:
The new term starts soon,
and we have a picnic
before going back.
Everybody's very happy.
Storm Dragon
doesn't fight anymore,
because he's fallen in love.
[♪♪♪]
Maggie likes me best.
[GULPS]
But my love is Fanny.
And she loves me
very much too!
Johnny always takes
what's mine.
Maybe he'll stop when I tell
the teacher about him.
Every pupil has
his own true love.
And so has my dad.
[INAUDIBLE DIALOGUE]
MISS YUEN:
It's just amazing.
When we saw you in the hospital,
you appeared to be quite--
Dead, yes.
But now I'm right as rain.
Not even the doctors
can explain it.
And how have you been
since then?
Well, I do have a bit
of a problem.
What kind of problem?
I'm far too handsome.
[LAUGHING]
Heh.
Very funny.
I mean it.
[LAUGHING]
DICKY:
It's not easy to win
a girl over,
especially if you're
not that funny.
But Dad won't give up.
He's my hero.
MR. CHOW:
You don't think I'm handsome,
Miss Yuen? You can't be serious.
I'm so lucky
that I still have you, CJ7.
Every day, while you sleep,
I close my eyes
and count to three,
hoping when I look again,
you'll wake.
I want you back so much.
Where are you, CJ7?
One, two, three...
[CHITTERING]
[SOFTLY WHOOSHING]
[BONEY M'S "SUNNY" PLAYING]
♪ Sunny ♪
♪ Yesterday my life
Was filled with rain ♪
♪ Sunny ♪
♪ You smile at me and really
Ease the pain... ♪
Whoa!
♪ The bright days are here ♪
♪ My sunny one shines
So sincere ♪
♪ Sunny one so true ♪
♪ I love you ♪
♪ Sunny, yeah ♪
♪ Thank you for the sunshine
Bouquet ♪
♪ Sunny ♪
♪ Thank you for the love
You brought my way ♪
♪ You gave to me
Your all and all ♪
♪ And now I feel
10-feet tall ♪
♪ Sunny one so true ♪
♪ I love you ♪
♪ Sunny ♪
♪ Thank you for the truth
You let me see ♪
♪ Sunny ♪
♪ Thank you for the facts
From A to Z ♪
♪ My life is torn
Like windblown sand ♪
♪ And the rock was formed
When you held my hand ♪
♪ Sunny one so true ♪
♪ I love you ♪
♪ Sunny ♪
♪ Thank you for the smile
Upon your face ♪
♪ Sunny ♪
♪ Thank you for the gleam
That flows with grace ♪
♪ You're my spark
Of nature's fire ♪
♪ You're my sweet
Complete desire ♪
♪ Sunny one so true ♪
♪ I love you ♪
♪ Sunny ♪
♪ Thank you for the smile
Upon your face ♪
♪ Sunny ♪
♪ Thank you for the gleam
That flows with grace ♪
♪ You're my spark
Of nature's fire ♪
♪ You're my sweet
Complete desire ♪
♪ Sunny one so true ♪
♪ I love you ♪
♪ Sunny, Sunny ♪
♪ Yesterday my life
Was filled with rain ♪
♪ Sunny, Sunny ♪
♪ You smile at me and really
Ease the pain ♪
♪ The dark days are gone
And the bright days are here ♪
♪ My sunny one shines
So sincere ♪
♪ Sunny, one so true ♪
♪ I love you ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Oh, my baby ♪
♪ I love you ♪
♪ Sunny ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ I love you ♪
♪ Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Sunny ♪