- Good morning, Teacher.
- Good morning.
Good morning.
Dicky Zhou.
Just look at you.
You're covered in dirt.
- I just...
- Stay where you are.
You're always giving excuses.
Why couldn't you just
keep yourself clean?
What's the matter, Mr Cao?
Explain yourself.
Let me talk to him.
How did you get so dirty, Dicky?
I fell down on my way to school.
Why couldn't your father or mother
send you to school?
My mum died a long time ago
and my dad's very busy.
What does your father do?
He's a labourer.
Can I make an appointment to see him?
I don't think he has the time.
All right then.
Let me know when he's available.
Take this and clean yourself up
before class starts.
Thank you, Miss Yuan.
I want to be a superstar.
- Who would you like to be?
- Nicole Kidman.
Nicole Kidman gets US$20 million
for filming a movie.
I wouldn't mind being her either.
I want to be an entrepreneur.
What kind of business
do you have in mind?
I'm fine with anything
as long as it's a big business.
The big boys can take over
the small players easily.
Why not?
I want to be a poor person.
My Ambition
Stop.
My dad says that
a humble, peace-loving
and studious person with integrity
will be respected even if he's poor.
Don't touch it.
Stay away from me.
Put it down.
Go back to your seat.
It's mealtime.
- It's mealtime.
- Let's go for our meal.
This amazing robotic dog
is called CJ1.
It was developed jointly by
US, French and German scientists.
Do you want to play with it?
Yes.
Not a chance.
There are only two of such dogs
in the world.
The other one is owned by
the US President's daughter.
- What are you doing?
- I'm eating my noodles.
Stand up.
No matter how much you eat,
you're doomed to be a dwarf.
Now, get lost.
Why is the calibre of our students
getting from bad to worse?
What do we have here? Another alien?
- What are you doing?
- I'm eating my rice.
Why are you so beefy for your age?
You should go see a doctor.
Stop gorging yourself on food.
You look horrible.
Guys, call the police and
get them to shoot this monster.
- I hope you die binging, freak.
- You're finishing all our food.
What are you guys doing?
Heroes don't bully girls.
Why are you still following us?
Ignore him.
Go away, poor boy.
We don't want to hang out with you.
- Shoo.
- Get lost, wretched poor boy.
Hello.
You've been sent off the field too?
Yes.
Did you forget your sneakers?
I brought them along,
but I chose not to wear them.
Why?
I wanted to be punished
together with you.
Are all your shoes torn and tattered?
Yes. My dad gets all my shoes
from the rubbish dump.
Your father is so nice to you.
Yes, he is.
But I really want
a new pair of sneakers
because I love
physical education lessons.
But I hope you can continue
wearing the old shoes.
Why?
We'll always be punished
together then.
Hurry.
Get that panel up there. Hurry.
You, step on it.
Since you're so weak,
you'd better go home.
You're no longer needed here.
Boss?
I need to buy an electric fan
for my son
as he hasn't been able to sleep well
in this hot weather.
Can you continue to hire me?
Buy a fan?
How about your wife's medical
and funeral bills which I settled?
If you've got the money,
you should pay me back first
or you'll be debt-ridden for life
given the sorry state you're in.
You're even starving yourself so that
your son can go to that fancy school.
If my son can attend public school,
why can't yours?
Well, I just want him to
have a better head start.
I don't want him to end up like me.
But you have to be capable.
I think he's highly capable.
I was referring to you, not him.
You're just an odd-job labourer.
How are you going to cope?
- I can cope.
- You can't.
- I can.
I can.
Go and lay the cement foundation
at Block B.
Thank you, Boss.
You've cheapened yourself
for your son.
So you must keep going
even if you're on your last legs.
Please
You're back.
Can we have dinner? I'm starving.
Just step back a little.
- What's going on?
- Turn around.
Come here.
What's the matter?
It's an electric fan.
Is this for real?
This is great.
We finally have a fan at home.
- Sit down and let me turn it on.
- Hurry, turn it on.
I want to feel the air from the fan.
Dad, did you find this
among the garbage?
No, I bought it.
This old fan cost me a bomb.
You must've been ripped off again.
No, it was fine when I bought it.
Good grief. Why isn't it working now?
Dumbass, you've got to be
smarter next time.
Dumbass? Where did you
learn that word from?
My classmate said that.
Really?
We might be poor,
but we don't use foul language.
We don't steal or rob
and we don't take things
that don't belong to us.
You must study hard and become
an asset to society in the future.
I didn't have an education
when I was young
and that's why
I'm lagging behind in society.
- We're having an apple today?
- Yes.
Wait.
Finish your dinner first.
By the way, Dad,
my sneakers are worn out again.
Can you mend them for me?
Get me a better pair next time
or I'll be sent off the field again.
I got it. I'll try my best.
Good grief.
Must you hit that cockroach?
We're having our meal now.
Cockroaches can wait.
Good. You've improved.
Not bad.
Lately, there have been
many sightings of UFOs.
What happened to the cartoon?
It'll be back soon.
Just wait a moment.
Can you please tell us what happened?
I saw a flying saucer.
It flew over there with a whoosh.
Can you describe
the flying saucer in detail?
It was a flying object,
but it wobbled during its flight.
I suspect it was involved in a crash.
- A crash?
- Yes, like a car crash.
It might've become faulty.
I even took a picture of it.
Sir, what kind of camera did you use?
It was an expensive one,
but I can't tell you the brand.
Did the flying saucer make any sound?
It made a whooshing sound
like I said.
Have you heard such sounds before?
They're unbelievable.
CJ1
Why did you run off?
Dad, this toy is called CJ1.
Everyone at school has one.
It's a fun toy.
Really?
Let's go home. Put it back.
What's the matter?
Why don't we buy one?
We'll buy it
after I get paid next month.
Now, put it down.
Let go.
Why are you so disobedient?
I can't afford this now.
If you buy me this toy, I'll never
ask for anything else again.
Please buy it for me.
You like this?
What kind of features does it have?
Let go.
Stop right there.
Sir, are you going to buy this toy?
Come on, Dicky. Stop crying.
Be a good boy, stop crying.
Dicky.
Are you Mr Zhou?
I'm Dicky's teacher, Miss Yuan.
Nice to meet you.
Miss Yuan, it's nice to meet you too.
Is Dicky well-behaved at school?
Yes, he's quite well-behaved
at school.
But he threw
a temper tantrum just now.
I know. Kids just want
every toy they see.
Yes. I didn't bring
enough money with me today, so...
- Dicky, go to your father.
- Come here.
- I'm sorry, Mr Zhou.
- That's the way he is.
Actually, I've always wanted to
pay you a visit at home.
He did tell me,
but I'm very busy at work.
I believe it takes more than teachers
to give children a good education.
That's why I'd like to
get you involved.
It'll be good for him too.
Yes, that's right.
Dicky, I need to go now.
Don't throw a tantrum again.
Listen to your father, okay?
Okay?
- I'm leaving then.
- Okay.
- Goodbye.
Dicky, turn around.
I have a toy which is
way better than CJ1.
Do you want to take a look?
Are you sure?
In that case, I'll throw it away
and get back to work.
- Goodbye, Teacher.
- Goodbye.
Fanny.
What's this amazing toy
which you mentioned, Dicky?
Check it out.
What's so fun about this?
It's super fun. Check it out.
It doesn't look that fun to me.
What do you think?
Actually, I agree.
It's not a fun toy.
It's okay. See you tomorrow.
What's that thing you're holding?
It's nothing.
It must be some kind of garbage.
That's not true.
This is way better than CJ1.
What is it called?
It's called CJ7.
Drop the act, poor loser.
Your father must've found it
among the rubbish.
Don't talk about my dad like that
or I'll beat you up.
Bring it on.
Hello.
How many times have I told you?
We might be poor,
but we don't get into fights.
You're such a disappointment.
Look at you.
Your uniform is all torn.
Why did you even get into a fight?
My classmates were laughing at me.
Why did they laugh at you?
Out with it!
Fine.
So you aren't going to tell me?
You're forcing my hand.
Come clean with me!
It's moving.
- There's a ghost.
- What ghost?
There's a ghost in the ball.
Don't change the subject. Sit down.
Do you think you can
run rings round me?
Don't mess with me
or I'll beat you to a pulp.
Look, your uniform is all torn.
What are you going to
wear to school tomorrow?
How am I supposed to
scavenge for another one?
I'll deal with you later.
There's a ghost hanging over there!
Help! There's a ghost!
It's so frightening.
There's a ghost in red
hanging over there.
This is so scary and frightening.
The ghost is hanging over there.
Stop screaming.
It's just a broken lamp.
There's no ghost.
What is it this time?
You look like a ghost too.
Zip it or I'll throw you out.
Do you hear me?
Are you on drugs?
Dad, what are you doing?
Please don't lock me inside here.
There's a ghost inside.
You've to believe me.
Dad, let me out.
Help!
Let me out.
Amitabha.
- Have you learnt your lesson?
- Yes.
- Will you behave yourself in future?
- I will. I really will.
I've to get back to work.
Be a good boy at home.
Hurry, get going then. Goodbye.
Are you from outer space?
Are you here to invade Earth?
I think you could be
an alien toy dog.
My name is Dicky. Can I call you CJ7?
Since you're wagging your tail,
that means you like the name.
CJ7.
The apples in our house
are always rotten.
Why is this one so fresh?
You know magic?
It tastes so sweet.
You really do know magic.
I'm going to be rich!
If you can defeat
the most vicious dog on Earth
then you really are a superdog
from outer space.
Go.
You're awesome!
There's a test today,
but I didn't prepare for it
because I was
playing with you yesterday.
Can you help me
score full marks nonetheless?
What are you making?
Dicky Zhou.
Why are you wearing those glasses?
I've got an eye injury.
Do you want to take a look?
Don't come near me. Sit down.
The test begins now.
Mark a tick if it's correct.
Mark a cross if it's wrong.
The start of the syllable,
the end of the syllable, the syllable
The end of the syllable
Sorry, Mr Cao. There was a fly.
A fly?
Chinese Language Test
I have the results for the test
which you took today.
For the first time,
Dicky Zhou scored full marks.
- Thank you, Mr Cao.
- Wait a minute.
I want to check your glasses.
Those super-glasses were fantastic.
It's physical education next,
so I'll need super-sneakers.
This is so exciting.
What does it take to
excel at high jump?
It boils down to talent, hard work,
lots of training, sufficient sleep
and respect for your coach.
So far, no one has been able to break
this personal record which I've set.
Coach, I'm wearing
new sneakers today.
Coach, he just broke your record.
Dicky, it would be unreasonable of me
to expect a kid to reach that height.
Be a good boy and do it again.
Dicky Zhou, what are those shoes
which you're wearing?
It's none of your business.
You've gone overboard.
That's because all of you
drove me into a corner.
Come down.
Dicky, are you out of your mind?
I...
He's over there. Catch him.
Come to your senses, Dicky.
Miss Yuan, the feeling of bitterness
can be as boundless as the sea.
Dicky.
Dicky Zhou, why did you jump
so high up into the air? Come down.
Mr Cao, you should calm down.
How on earth could you sleep
like that?
Wake up. It's time for school.
Didn't I tell you to be a good boy?
Why do you keep oversleeping?
Was it all a dream?
You're real.
I'm going to get ready for school.
Dad, I'm going to score full marks
for my exam today.
I'm going to score full marks.
Do you have what it takes?
Yes, I've got what it takes
to score full marks.
That's great.
If you can defeat
the most vicious dog on Earth
then you really are
a superdog from outer space.
Go.
Run!
What happened back there?
You're supposed to be
the superdog from outer space.
Are you playing dumb?
I'm being serious.
I have to score full marks
for the exam today.
I need you to work your magic for me.
Cut it out. Stop clowning around.
I'm not joking.
You have to give me a magic weapon.
Time's up.
But I haven't even started yet.
What's with the turd?
Turd? It's not turd.
Taste it if you don't believe me.
How dare you make a fool of me!
I'm going to kill you.
This is your last chance.
Give me the magic weapon now.
Why did you...
You...
Coach, I can explain.
Don't bother.
You're shallow, crass, wicked and
the most uncouth student I've seen.
Whatever you say
will be just full of crap.
Now, clean him up.
CJ7? Please come out.
Why would I be mad at you?
We're good friends.
The turd wasn't a big deal.
I've been through worse.
Let's just forget about this fiasco.
It's all water under the bridge now.
In fact, I love you very much.
Do you know that?
CJ7? Come here.
Good doggy.
I'm going to stab you to death.
You're a crappy dog from outer space.
You're low-tech and boring.
I got ridiculed by my classmates and
blamed by my teachers because of you.
So this is your karma.
You should've told me honestly
that you're lousy
and not as invincible as I thought.
But it never said it was invincible.
Perhaps I had
unrealistic expectations.
Have I made a mistake?
I know I've made a mistake.
Wait.
What happened?
CJ7 has disappeared.
Look.
CJ7?
I'm sorry. I missed you so much.
I thought I'd never see you again.
I'm glad you're not angry with me.
Both of you already met?
It's a toy?
Yes, it is.
It can walk, jump and blink?
Where did you get it?
My classmate lent it to me.
Where's the cover?
Where should we insert the batteries?
It doesn't need batteries.
It's very high-tech.
I've never seen
a high-tech toy like this.
- Did you see that?
- Yes, I did.
It's really bouncy.
Stop doing that.
I have to return it to my classmate.
Don't worry about it.
- What are you doing, Dad?
- It'll be fine.
Look, I told you it'd be fine.
It's restored now.
This is fun.
Stop squeezing it. That's enough.
Everything is so high-tech nowadays.
Uneducated people like me
won't be able to catch up.
Dad, I don't want to lie to you.
In fact, CJ7 came out of the ball
which you gave me.
It's an alien from outer space.
How many times have I told you?
We might be poor, but we don't lie.
We don't get into fights
and we don't take things
that don't belong to us.
You must study hard and become
an asset to society in the future.
It's so hot.
The fan started working again
when the weather is hottest.
- It seems every dog has its day.
- I'm off to school.
- Have you brought your lunch box?
- Yes, I have.
How did your exam go?
Why has your forehead gone red?
You look listless today.
Didn't you sleep well last night?
Get inside and go to sleep.
Stop.
What's that thing inside your bag?
Nothing.
Check his bag.
Why are you checking my bag?
I don't have to tell you the reason.
- Let go.
What's that?
Let me take a look.
- Give it to me. Let me see it first.
- Give it to me. Don't pull it.
- Catch it!
- Go after it!
- Come and help me.
- Here.
You're so useless. Stop running.
Catch it.
This is so frustrating.
Go over there now.
What's this weird thing?
Don't touch it. Give it back to me.
Get the toolbox.
- Let's open it up and take a look.
- Here you go.
Let it go.
It's not working.
Try this.
Please don't do that.
- It's not working either.
- How is that possible?
Why did you snatch my toy?
So what if I did?
Are you going to hit me?
Yes, I'm going to hit you.
Let him go!
- Let him go.
- You must let me go first.
I don't want to get into a fight.
Don't force me to do this.
Are you okay?
I'm fine. Thank you.
You're welcome.
What's going on here?
Why were all of you fighting?
Out with it.
You're going to stand here
until you tell me.
CJ7.
I knew you'd be okay.
Stop it. Be a good boy.
What's this thing?
Check it out. CJ7, sit.
It's so smart. What else can it do?
CJ7, show us a happy face.
Show us an angry face.
Show us a sad face.
You just saw a pretty lady.
Your apartment is on fire.
You won the lottery.
Your whole family is dead.
You've scored full marks
for the exam.
It's so smart.
Look.
It even displayed fireworks.
Where did you buy this toy?
Yes, I want one too.
I can't tell you that.
But I wish to thank you
for not telling Mr Cao about this.
Of course. We don't discuss
our business with adults.
- Is that a deal?
- It's a deal.
You're amazing.
Would you like to join our judo team?
No. They'll all make fun of me.
They wouldn't dare.
Will you guys still make fun of her?
Look at this. My son scored
full marks for his exam.
- Your son is so smart.
- Yes.
- Look.
- Go away.
He scored full marks.
Shift this over there.
Boss, my son really scored
full marks for his exam.
He must've cheated.
Why did you say that?
Even a smart boy like my son
only managed to score 60 marks
after he cheated.
Who would believe your son could
score full marks without cheating?
That's nonsense.
The ink is different.
That little liar must've changed
the number zero to a hundred.
But that's not the person he is.
I know him better.
Your son cheated.
- You can't say that.
- Your son cheated.
I'll hit you if you say that again.
Your son cheated.
So? You want to hit me?
How could you hit me
when it was your son who cheated?
You're fired.
Your son cheated.
Get inside now.
Get inside.
Tell me the truth.
Did you cheat in your exam?
- No, I didn't.
- You scored zero.
But you changed it to 100 marks.
Am I right?
Yes. But that's not
the same as cheating.
I just didn't want you
to be disappointed.
What's wrong with you?
I slogged my guts out
to send you to that school.
I'm sorry, Dad.
How many times have I told you?
- We might be poor...
- Sheesh, I know.
You're sounding like a broken record.
It's getting on my nerves.
What's done can't be undone.
What can you do about it?
If there's nothing else, I'm leaving.
What are you doing?
What are you trying to do?
If you don't study hard,
you don't get to play.
- Give it back to me.
- No.
You've no right to take my stuff.
No, I've every right to do that
because I'm your dad, okay?
You're just taking advantage of me.
I don't have a father like you.
And I don't have a son like you
who always does miserably in exams.
Get off my case.
I dare you to say it again.
Get off my case forever.
Fine.
If you can score 60 marks
with your own ability
I'll never bother you again.
- It's a deal.
I'm going to achieve that.
Don't go back on your word.
Stop bragging and
walk the talk, F student.
You should stop being so cocky.
I'll show you what I've got
so you'll get off my case for good.
What are you looking at?
- Mr Zhou.
- Miss Yuan.
What's the matter? Let's talk inside.
It's okay. Please pass this to Dicky.
He forgot to bring his lunch box.
Sure. Would you like to come in?
I'll get someone to open the gate.
Don't bother. He'll get ridiculed
if his classmates see me.
That won't happen.
- I have to go.
- Wait.
Dicky told me everything.
He was just being temperamental.
If you don't mind, you can let him
go home with me after school today.
I'll have a good talk with him.
I can also help him prepare for
another exam tomorrow.
What do you think?
- Thank you so much.
- You're welcome. Don't mention it.
- No, I really appreciate it.
- It's just a small gesture.
No, it's not.
I've always felt bad that
I wasn't able to give him the best.
So I can't thank you enough
for lending him a helping hand.
You really don't have to.
It's my duty.
I'll leave Dicky to you then.
Sure, I'll take good care of him.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
How is the boss feeling today?
I can't believe you've got
the cheek to come back.
I have to. I need to make a living.
I know I shouldn't have
shot my mouth off
but can we let that slide
since we're from the same village?
I shouldn't have said that
about your son in public.
I hope you can accept this red packet
as a peace offering.
But... But he really cheated.
Who doesn't? Your son is smart.
He'll be a successful man in future.
I certainly hope so.
All right, take the money
and buy him some food.
You don't have to give me
so much money.
Cut the crap. Just use it to
buy books or pay his school fees.
Now, get back to work.
Every dog has its day.
I'm surprised you passed the exam.
Good.
Thank you, Mr Cao.
What's happening?
Where's your safety harness?
Hurry.
What's going on here?
Help!
Come on, give me your hand.
- Stretch out. Give me your hand.
- Be careful.
Hurry, give me your hand.
I've got you.
Why haven't these been shifted?
Step on it.
What was that? Be careful.
Excuse me.
Dicky, you have to come with me.
What?
He's dead.
And it's all because of you.
I tried to save him.
Chinese Language Mid-term Exam
Is this your house, Dicky?
Are you hungry?
Do you want to eat something?
Dicky, I've got some news for you.
Your father met with an accident
and passed away.
Dicky, there are many things
beyond our control, okay?
That's enough, Miss Yuan.
I'm going to bed now.
- Please leave.
- Listen to me. Dicky.
- Dicky.
- I'm sorry, Miss Yuan.
I... I'm very tired.
I... I need to sleep.
Dicky.
My dad won't leave me behind.
He'll be home when I wake up.
I need to sleep now.
Dicky.
Dad.
Why aren't you in your pajamas?
What's wrong?
Dad, don't ever leave me.
I'll listen to you. I'll study hard.
I won't brag or get into fights
and I'll become
an asset to society one day.
That's my good boy.
CJ7.
How are you?
What's that sound?
Beats me.
Why are you so tired, CJ7?
What happened to him, Dad?
Maybe the batteries have run out.
It doesn't appear that way.
Well, it's very high-tech.
It's a delightful day at the picnic
organised by the school
before the start of the new semester.
Storm Dragon has fallen in love
and he no longer gets into fights.
But Maggie still
carries a torch for me.
However, Fanny is the one I love.
And she loves me very much too.
But Johnny always takes what's mine.
I'll rat on him to the teacher
and foil his plan.
Every student has a crush.
And so does my dad.
It's really a miracle.
When I saw you in the hospital,
you were already...
I was already dead.
But now, I'm as right as rain.
I couldn't figure out why.
Even the doctors were baffled.
And how are you feeling now?
I've been experiencing
a slight problem.
What kind of problem?
I think I'm far too handsome.
That's funny.
It wasn't a joke.
It's not easy to win a girl's heart,
but my dad won't give up.
He's my hero.
You don't think I'm handsome,
Miss Yuan?
Take a closer look.
And not forgetting you, CJ7.
Ever since you fell
into a deep slumber
I've developed the daily habit of
closing my eyes and counting to three
hoping that you'll wake up
when I open my eyes again.
Why don't you make my wish come true
since I'm so sincere about it?
One, two, three.