CRASH
ALL CHARACTERS, LOCATIONS,
ORGANIZATIONS, EVENTS,
GROUPS, AND BACKGROUNDS
IN THIS WORK ARE FICTIONAL
SEOUL NAMGANG POLICE STATION
RESTRICTED AREA
HIGH SCHOOLER REPORTED MISSING
FOR FOUR DAYS
POSSIBLE SUICIDE OR HIT-AND-RUN
CRASH
HWAPYEONG ISLAND LISTED AS TOP
100 ISLANDS TO VISIT IN KOREA
EPISODE 12
There are many tourists.
I know. Until a few years ago,
only fishers and herb gatherers visited.
What changed?
A few years ago,
the villagers had a meeting
and sold some land to out-of-towners.
Then out-of-towners opened
resorts and cafés on the island.
These days, there's also social media.
The tourists' social media posts
have made it a popular destination.
Honestly, the island has good scenery.
I agree. We should've come here
on vacation instead.
Those people are here again.
Who are they?
MCST will select five islands
to give ten billion won for developments.
It was called the K-Tourism Islands
or something.
Those people are
the selection committee members.
The entire island is making a fuss
to win the business rights.
What? Captain!
- Captain!
- Captain.
- My goodness.
It's been a while.
I'm sorry for making you travel so far.
It's nice to get fresh air.
Let's go.
LEE SEUNGA DISAPPEARANCE CASE
On the day she went missing,
Seunga headed out to attend
a friend's birthday party.
But…
Seunga went to a friend's birthday party?
But she doesn't have any friends.
It can't be a friend from school.
She doesn't talk to
other students at school.
She eats alone too.
I wouldn't call her an outcast,
but students tend to ignore her
since she's difficult.
Do you know if she had friends
outside of school?
I wouldn't know. Come to think of it…
I've seen her with a man.
- Really?
- No.
- They seemed pretty close.
- Did you see his face?
No. I saw them from behind.
A man.
On the day she went missing,
Seunga's shoes were discovered
on Bigu Peak Cliff
near the end of the island.
And traces of an accident
were found on the coastal road.
Seunga's house, Sunrise Resort,
is located near Namri Beach.
I think she got into an accident
on her way back home.
If that's true, someone intentionally put
Seunga's shoes at a different location.
The culprit probably wanted to
make it look like she jumped off a cliff.
Coast guards are searching the sea,
but they haven't found her yet.
They say there's a chance
the current washed her body away.
What about the traces at the scene?
A piece of a silver bumper.
- Hello.
- Inspector Cha, what brings you here?
Is it already time
to get your car checked?
I came to ask you something about a case.
Here you go.
This is the car model. Stallone.
A silver Stallone.
Let's find the silver Stallone cars
that passed the coastal road.
We checked with the Stallone cars
the out-of-towners brought.
Four out of seven were rentals.
According to the rental services,
none of them were damaged.
We checked the other three with the help
of the police, but they were fine.
That means it's one of the islanders.
We checked the islanders' cars too.
What are you looking for?
The cars are obviously fine.
I heard it happened at Bigu Peak.
Why are you harassing innocent islanders?
Seriously. I'm sure it was
an out-of-towner.
The islanders are like family.
- Who would cause such an accident?
- I know.
Chief. How much longer
will you keep us here?
- We need to get back to work too!
- Okay. For goodness' sake.
Stop it already.
You didn't find anything suspicious.
HWAPYEONG COMMUNITY CENTER
No signs of an accident?
The cars were clean.
We checked all three auto repair shops
on the island.
No one came in with a silver Stallone
to have a bumper exchanged or repaired.
Had they exchanged the bumper
or windshield, it would've shown.
But we didn't see any signs.
It was neither an out-of-towner's car
nor an islander's car.
At 11:20 p.m. on the night
Seunga went missing,
a camera caught
a silver Stallone at the entrance
of Buk 2-ri St. near Bigu Peak.
An hour later, it was filmed
as it came back out.
And the license plate number?
No, the image was too blurry.
But take a look at the right headlight.
It's broken.
It's the same location
as the bumper fragment we found.
Since the village is secluded,
they don't have surveillance cameras
for security.
The existing ones are all broken.
All the villagers are senior citizens,
so they have no intention of fixing it.
Hold on.
Over there.
And there.
They set up cameras
at farm tracks and greenhouses.
Why would they have one at farm tracks?
Crop theft.
Islands like this
should get surveillance cameras too.
There's nothing we can work with
for an investigation.
Had this happened in Seoul,
it would've closed in half a day.
The thing is,
this is a very peaceful island.
They say your name determines your fate.
It became peaceful after they changed
the name to Hwapyeong Island.
- What was the previous name?
- Sujeong Island.
- It's a pretty name. Why was it changed?
- Well, according to the seniors,
there were many ship accidents here
due to the weather.
In any case, there hasn't been
a single theft case,
let alone a murder case so far.
I also think that Seunga
may have taken her own life.
What? It seems like
Captain found something.
What?
No way.
With that angle,
it would've filmed the entire village.
If only it is working.
Hold on.
Excuse me, sir. Hello.
Do you know who owns this warehouse?
Thank you.
Ever since out-of-towners
began entering the island,
I found people going into the grape field.
I haven't checked it once
after installing it.
They told me to press the button,
but I didn't know which one.
Hold on. Over here.
I can't make out the place
since it's too dark.
Are you done?
- Give me a second.
- Okay.
- I'll send it now.
I got it.
I think I have a better idea now.
Let's reenact what happened
and figure out where this car went.
Okay.
Donggi, can you hear me?
Yes, I can.
- Okay. Set off slowly.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
- All right.
Too fast.
It was too fast. Go slowly.
Okay. Let's go slowly.
Slowly.
- Turn left.
Turning left. Can you make a left?
- Yes. It must be this path.
- Yes.
Go straight.
Okay. Going straight.
- Turn right.
Can you turn right?
Yes, we can turn right.
- I can see them.
- Yes.
Continue down that road slowly.
Okay.
Follow the road up the hill.
Follow the road straight up the hill.
Okay.
- Let's go up.
- Okay.
- Stop.
Stop.
Donggi, what is that place?
Can you see anything? Where are you?
Lieutenant,
I think we've come to the right place.
It says mountain cars can't enter.
All right.
Although it may look like a low mountain,
it's connected all the way to the dock.
It'll take a battalion at the very least
to search the mountain.
Do you know who owns it?
It should be a mountain
for the Gi family's gravesites.
Among the drivers
whose cars passed the coastal road,
there was a man whose surname was Gi.
You must be talking about Gi Hyungsoo.
He works at the oyster farm.
All right. Okay.
I checked with the dock.
Gi Hyungsoo's car never left the island
before or after the girl's disappearance.
- You checked their cars too.
- Right.
- The windshields and bumpers were clean.
- Yes.
Gi Hyungsoo has an alibi too.
- Have a safe drive.
- Please go back inside.
- Thank you.
- Take care.
- We'll get going.
- All right.
- Have a safe trip.
- Okay.
- We're in your care.
- Goodbye.
We're in your care!
You all did so well today!
Wait. How will you all go home?
My place is nearby, so it's fine.
I'll get going then.
On the night Seunga disappeared,
there was a gathering
at a sashimi place near the dock.
He left the restaurant around 10 p.m.
with Village Chief Shin Kyungja,
Kang Sanghoon, and Im Jisook.
He drove back to his place at Nam 2-ri St.
Get going.
Hey. You didn't drink, right?
There was a gathering,
but he didn't have a drop of alcohol.
Since this is an island,
we lack manpower.
It's impossible to set up DUI checkpoints.
He could've had a drink or two.
The accident occurred here.
Had it happened on his way home,
the three passengers would've known.
That's one thing,
but his car is also undamaged.
We need to verify Gi Hyungsoo's alibi.
Let's start with the president
of the women's society.
Mr. Shin, will you give them a ride?
Sure.
Where will you go?
I'll visit Gi Hyungsoo.
- I'll go with you.
- No.
I want to ask you for a favor.
Would you please check in
on Seunga's father?
Gosh, why are you outside?
Did you find Seunga?
Well, we haven't found her yet.
Could it be that she's still alive?
I feel like
Seunga left the island to see her mom.
We're considering all possibilities
while searching for her.
It must be difficult,
but please wait a bit longer.
We'll do our best
so that Seunga returns home safely.
- Okay. I understand.
- Yes.
In that case…
…please find Seunga.
Okay, sir.
He was waiting outside
in this cold weather.
That's how you feel
when you wait for someone.
For goodness' sake.
Why would I lie about this?
Mr. Gi drove me home.
And you didn't see Seunga
on your way home?
I didn't see her, okay?
I was drunk, so I was already home
when I opened my eyes.
What?
I already told you everything.
Hyungsoo drove me home.
Did anything happen on your way home?
That's enough.
- Pardon?
- She committed suicide.
Why do you keep suspecting the villagers?
We've lived in peace
without a single problem so far.
- Gosh, Village Chief. Why--
- Be quiet!
I knew that family was trouble
when he refused to pay for developments.
He had no intention to work with us.
He was just focusing on
making money off our island.
It's no wonder his wife ran away.
What are you doing?
I asked what you were doing
in front of my car.
- I came to ask you something.
- What?
When you returned home
after dropping people off that day,
did you stay home?
Why do you ask?
Didn't you drive someplace else?
Like where?
Bigu Peak?
It was too late to go anywhere.
I slept at home.
If you don't believe me,
go ask the islanders.
At this time--
That car wasn't Gi Hyungsoo's.
- What?
- Huh? What do you mean?
Detective Woo, please check
Gi Hyungsoo's VIN.
Okay.
VEHICLE IDENTIFICATION NUMBER
It seemed strange.
If Seunga got into an accident,
it had to be Gi Hyungsoo's car.
Why were there no traces?
Could it be
a twin car?
I have Mr. Gi Hyungsoo's VIN.
VEHICLE INFORMATION
The VIN is different.
He switched the cars.
It's a new car with the old license plate.
To hide his vehicle,
he bought a used car of the same model
and switched the license plates
so it'd look like nothing happened.
- Then the car from the accident…
- He must've hidden it
or discarded it in the sea.
- I think there's an accomplice.
- Who could it be?
What's certain is that
Gi Hyungsoo didn't buy the twin car.
There's only one vehicle registration
under his name.
The one who bought the car
is the accomplice.
Let's find the accomplice.
The twin car must've come
right after the accident.
When we checked for silver Stallone cars,
they were already switched.
So it must've entered the island
around that time.
Donggi and Hyunkyung,
check if the same car entered the island.
- Yes, sir.
Perhaps he still has the damaged car.
Inspector Cha and I will see
if he hid the car somewhere.
- The most likely location would be--
- Gi Hyungsoo's mountain.
It sure is an appropriate place
to hide something.
It's a secluded private property.
If he hid the car somewhere, it'd be here.
Yes.
Who could be the man Seunga was close to?
It can't be Gi Hyungsoo, right?
I'm not sure. Though I was close
to Seunga, I don't know much about her.
But every time I saw her,
she was always alone.
She always had earbuds in her ears.
She must've been lonely.
She was at the age
to hang out with friends.
Hold on, Inspector Cha.
Is this Seunga's earbud?
Yes, it's the same model
as Seunga's earbuds.
I remember it clearly since I bought them.
Did Seunga take them with her
on the day she went missing?
Probably. She always listened to music.
There are no earbuds in her room.
She must've taken them with her.
Then this could really be hers.
Yes, Hyunkyung.
You found it?
Here.
A silver Stallone entered the island
the day after Seunga went missing.
- It's the same model as Gi Hyungsoo's car.
- Did you check the VIN?
It's under Im Jisook's name.
How's the president of the women's society
related to Gi Hyungsoo?
They're cousins.
What about it?
I'm sure Ms. Im just got a new car.
That's entirely possible, but look here.
The bumper…
Her new car was destroyed
in a matter of days.
- When was this?
- Early this morning.
Ms. Im Jisook.
- You'll have to come with us.
- What?
It won't take long.
What's going on?
What's happening? My goodness.
Why are you doing this?
The car you took
out of the island this morning.
Where is it now?
What? Why do you ask about that car?
That car had a broken bumper.
Oh, that?
My goodness, I got into an accident
as soon as I bought the car.
It seemed like a bad omen
so I went to see a fortuneteller.
My goodness.
She said that I'd die early
if I continued to drive that car.
- Then what?
- Must you ask?
I had it scrapped.
Just because of a broken bumper?
Goodness, I couldn't sell
such an unlucky item to someone else.
I'm not that kind of a person.
This is your vehicle registration,
Ms. Im Jisook.
And this is Mr. Gi Hyungsoo's.
The two shared the same VIN.
Do you know what that means?
- I don't know.
- The two of you have the same car.
- What?
- The car you scrapped
belonged to Gi Hyungsoo, right?
After Gi Hyungsoo hit Seunga,
he scrapped his car.
Then you bought the same model
and switched it with his car, didn't you?
My goodness.
I have no idea what you're talking about.
Feigning ignorance won't get you anywhere.
I really don't know anything.
What on earth are you doing?
I told you, didn't I?
Don't cause trouble
over a girl who killed herself.
How dare you cause a ruckus
- at such a crucial moment?
- A ruckus?
It might be a murder case.
Murder, my foot.
- That will never happen on this island!
- You want to believe that.
You don't want to suspect
those you've known all your life.
But that's what the evidence suggests.
Otherwise, why would
the two cars be switched?
Hyungsoo, explain it yourself.
Okay, Director.
Well…
My goodness.
I switched the cars
without telling Jisook.
- What did you say?
- Listen.
Jisook said she got a new car,
but it was the same model as mine.
I switched the license plates
and car keys as a prank.
- But she didn't even realize it.
- What?
I was going to switch them back
after the prank ran its course.
Who knew that there'd be an accident?
- Do you expect us to believe that?
- I'm a witness.
I was with him when he switched the cars.
But that was after the girl went missing.
It has nothing to do with her.
Do you even know what you're all doing?
This is concealment of a crime.
It makes all of you accomplices.
Accomplices, my foot.
You're the one who's cornering
the innocent!
Hyungsoo already explained it.
He's the witness!
- Village Chief.
- What?
Chief, what are you doing?
Can't you see the islanders
getting hounded by the out-of-towners?
All right, everyone.
There must be a misunderstanding.
Let's call it a day.
Go back home now. Go.
- Go!
- For goodness' sake!
Chief, take responsibility!
Come on.
For goodness' sake!
- Chief, take responsibility!
- Get going!
I can't believe this!
Who are you branding as a criminal!
Don't be angry. It's standard procedure.
Let go! Are you siding with them
since you're an officer too?
Come on. Don't be like that to Mr. Shin.
We'd better not lose
ten billion won over this.
I won't stand still!
For goodness' sake. We got it, okay?
Im Jisook might not be
the only accomplice.
It's no wonder his wife ran away.
The accomplices might be everyone
involved in Gi Hyungsoo's alibi
on the day of the accident.
What should we do? The car was scrapped.
If they are all in collusion,
circumstantial evidence won't be enough.
How will we investigate?
Only one solution remains.
We must find Seunga.
I picked this up at the mountain.
Forensics will confirm it,
but we think it belongs to Seunga.
Shouldn't we search the mountain?
To search the mountain,
we'll need help from coast guards
and the military.
The community members
and islanders will be against it.
The islanders are sensitive
about the island's image.
If we fail to find something,
they'll resist even more.
Is there another way?
We must search the mountain.
Instead of making a move,
let's have them make a move first.
We apologize for causing inconvenience
during our search for Lee Seunga.
Thanks to all your help,
the investigation will be closed soon.
What? How will it be closed?
Has her body been found?
Yes. We'll find it soon.
What do you mean "soon"?
Did you find her body or not?
This is a wireless earbud.
It was something Seunga
always carried with her.
We recently caught signals
from the other earbud.
Tomorrow, an expert from Seoul
will come here.
Then we'll be able to figure out
the exact location.
If she jumped into the sea,
her body must be miles away.
- How will you find her body?
- Right.
Can't you tell us?
I'm sure there's a way, right?
Right.
Thank you for your cooperation.
You can go home now.
Aren't those earbuds very common?
The other one is sending out a signal.
All the kids use such earbuds.
Inspector Cha, doesn't this scenery
feel familiar?
During the Kanghee Junction case,
- a ghost at the mountain…
- Right.
Back then, you almost passed out
because I startled you.
I did?
"I did?" A witness is right here.
You fell to the ground.
I never did that.
Stop it. Why are you joking around?
- Gosh!
- My goodness. What?
I didn't know there were
camellia trees here.
Inspector Cha, you've changed.
- There.
- Stop it.
- No, I'm serious.
- Stop joking around.
You know where you're going?
- Over there.
- What?
I knew it'd be the four of them.
Where is it?
- Here.
- What?
No need to wait. Shall we get them?
- Wait.
- That isn't the place.
- What?
All right.
It's about here.
I'm not drunk. Ride my car.
You're moving like a butterfly.
You're swaying.
Don't be ridiculous.
Hurry up and get going. Go on now.
Hey. You didn't drink, right?
I drank.
I was talking to him, not you.
You didn't drink much, right?
- A little bit.
- A little bit?
Then you should drive.
You should drive.
Let's go. We'll get ten billion won.
Is it a coincidence
that Im Jisook scrapped the car today?
Do you think there's an accomplice
among the police?
It's suspicious.
It was right after Inspector Cha
found out about the twin car.
We can't jump to conclusions,
but we should be careful.
- Shine the flashlight here.
- Okay.
Captain's hunch was correct.
Inspector Cha, are you okay?
- Where? Here?
- Yes.
Start digging.
Goodness gracious.
How will they locate the buried body?
- Well, by using the Internet…
- Yeah?
There's a method.
Geez, this is ridiculous.
- I said we should throw it in the sea.
- For goodness' sake!
Shine the flashlight properly.
I can't see anything.
Okay.
What?
I found it.
All right. Here.
- Don't shine the flashlight on my face.
- It isn't me.
Goodness, so many of you are here.
- Is it just the two of you?
- Why? Do you want to bury us too?
Burying a few more people
won't be so hard.
- My goodness. Donggi, it's this way.
- Okay.
I didn't do anything wrong.
I only helped because they asked.
- Don't touch me. I'm a victim!
- Give me your hands.
I'm a victim too.
- You don't want to get hurt.
- I'll handcuff you.
You admit to your crimes, right?
- Let go.
- Give me your hands.
- It'll hurt if you pull.
- All right.
- Let's go.
- No, but…
- Gosh. Stay there.
Give me your hands.
All right. Give me your hands.
This is a wireless earbud.
It was something Seunga
always carried with her.
We recently caught signals
from the other earbud.
Tomorrow, an expert from Seoul
will come here.
Then we'll be able to figure out
the exact location.
RESTRICTED AREA
SOCIAL WELFARE FACILITY
SUJEONG CENTER
You must be Seunga.
Who are you?
I'm a police officer.
Let's go. Your father is waiting.
It was you.
The friend who saved Seunga.
Seunga!
Dad. Dad!
Seunga.
You brat.
Armin was a friend I made here.
THE DAY OF DISAPPEARANCE
That day, it was Armin's birthday.
Happy birthday, Armin.
You're a good friend, Seunga.
Thank you, Seunga.
It's your birthday.
Don't you miss your mom?
I miss my mom.
I miss my mom too.
I don't feel lonely.
Thanks to you.
Thank you, Seunga.
Call me when you feel lonely.
No matter what. Promise?
A nice song plays
whenever I call you.
It makes me feel better.
That song?
- Do you want to listen to it?
- Yes.
What was that?
What's this?
What? Go and check.
- My goodness!
- What?
- My goodness.
- Who's that?
What happened?
- Didn't you see him?
- What?
What? I know him.
He works on Mr. Park's fishing boat.
Is he alive or dead?
He's dead.
Over there.
I see another one over there. There!
Is she alive?
Help…
- She's alive! Call for help!
- Unbelievable!
Who will you call?
A police officer caused the accident.
But this--
This isn't entirely my fault.
Don't you remember who made me drive?
It was because of you, Aunt!
What should we do, Director?
Why did this happen
when we had important guests over?
It's a matter of ten billion won!
Let's bury them.
Don't you know what happens
if a police officer kills someone
in a drunk-driving accident?
Yes. That's a good idea.
We can't lose ten billion won.
If word gets out
about a death on the island,
who'll visit?
The decision is up to you.
No one saw it, right?
- Gosh.
- Be quiet.
Be quiet.
Let's bury the dead one
and look after the one that's still alive.
We need to get ten billion won!
- My goodness.
- Be quiet.
- Gosh.
- Goodness.
- I said be quiet.
This place used to be called
Sujeong Island.
Sujeong Center was
a facility for homeless children.
They were kidnapped for reformation
and suffered confinement and assault.
The group even buried bodies in secret.
Who knew that the heads of the group
remained and took over the island?
The thing is,
this is a very peaceful island.
They say your name determines your fate.
It became peaceful after they changed
the name to Hwapyeong Island.
What was the previous name?
Sujeong Island.
From Sujeong Island to Hwapyeong Island.
Hyungsoo, explain it yourself.
Okay, Director.
Only the titles changed
from "Director" to "Village Chief".
Everything else stayed the same.
We would have lived peacefully
if it weren't for them!
Do you still not get it?
You are the ones
who disturbed peace on this island,
both 20 years ago and now.
LEE SEUNGA, AGE 17
ARMIN, AGE 21 DECEASED
How did such a tragic event occur
on this beautiful island?
I know, right?
Even at a place like this,
cases come endlessly.
It really is tragic.
I wouldn't have been able
to solve it alone.
Thank you, everyone.
There wasn't a single case
we failed to solve together.
That's the very reason
why TCI must continue on.
Captain, if you return as the head of TCI,
will you call us back?
I forgot to tell you guys.
I turned in my resignation letter
before coming here.
- What?
- A resignation letter?
- Why so suddenly?
It wasn't sudden.
I've thought about it for a while.
I've done enough.
"Separation is inevitable,
but they will return."
I hope you won't be disappointed.
Thank you for everything.
CERTIFICATE OF APPOINTMENT
Seoul Metropolitan Police
has promoted Lieutenant Min Sohee
and three teammates
of the former TCI team
of Namgang Police Station
for solving the case of a missing girl
at Hwapyeong Island during their vacation.
I'll take the photo. One, two, three.
One, two, three.
One more time. One, two, three.
Please stand next to them.
- Please look forward.
- Okay.
I'll take the photo. One, two, three.
Wow! You guys are incredible.
You guys persevere
no matter the circumstance, like weeds.
How did you catch a murderer
on your vacation?
What's your secret? I really want to know.
Traffic Division solves all the cases,
so Criminal Division is idle.
Let us catch criminals too.
Congratulations.
- Thank you.
Chief.
It's a joyous day.
Shouldn't we go out and have dinner?
What? Does Lee Taeju want to
have a meal with you again?
Don't be ridiculous. It was just one time.
If it isn't Lee Taeju, who is it?
Gosh, it isn't like that.
I have my eyes on you. Get it together.
It's a good day.
Why don't we go out
and eat something fancy?
I'll spend up to one million won.
It's been a while since you were in Seoul.
Inspector Cha, you should decide
what you want to eat.
I'm sorry. I have a prior engagement.
A prior engagement. Okay.
That's important.
It came first, after all.
A prior engagement takes precedence.
That's important.
Well, that's too bad.
Why don't we lift our spirits ourselves?
Choose from mushroom chicken soup,
tuna sashimi, and beef.
I'm sorry, Chief.
We have a prior engagement too.
All right.
You guys are just mean. Goodness.
YESEUNG PORK BULGOGI
- Captain.
- You're here.
Yes.
Hello.
My goodness. Here.
All right.
I can't believe we're here
on the day of our promotion.
Inspector Cha wanted to eat here.
Inspector Cha, are you in a hurry?
Eat slowly.
It's been a while.
I missed this place
when I lived on the island.
Everyone, congratulations
on your promotion.
Although you contributed,
we got promoted without you.
I'm sorry.
No, don't be sorry. This is my choice.
Why don't we eat here from time to time?
Even if we aren't on the same team,
we could still eat together.
- I'm in.
- Same here.
Captain, hurry up and say yes.
You're the one
who crushed the revival of TCI.
- Okay. I'm for that idea.
- Okay.
Inspector Cha, I know you're in.
- Are you in?
- Yes.
You look happy.
I thought you were going to take a break.
Is your idea of a break
working on the road?
You have a point. Perhaps it's my fate.
I heard the news. Congratulations.
Next month, you'll be Director
of the National Office of Investigation.
I'm the one who wants to take a break,
but they keep giving me work.
Do you know what I want to do first
as Director of the National Office
of Investigation?
POLICE PERSONNEL RECORDS
The first person who suggested
the Traffic Crime Investigation team
was you.
Was there a special reason?
During my 30 years as a police officer,
there was a case I had buried in my heart.
A hit-and-run case that killed my wife.
I was inattentive to my family
with the excuse of being busy.
My wife visited the police station
day and night to look after me.
That day, she was bringing
a change of clothes to the station
when the accident occurred.
I investigated the case for a year.
In the end, I couldn't catch the culprit.
Perhaps the culprit is still driving
somewhere in Korea.
Perhaps the culprit caused
another accident.
Every year, close to 3,000 people
die on the road.
The number of deaths
from the five most common crimes combined
is far less than that.
People don't think
that a murder on the road is a murder.
"I didn't know. It was a mistake.
It wasn't intentional."
To them, a murder on the road
is simply an accident.
Every single day,
I see my wife on the road.
I see her crossing the street
at the green light.
I see her sitting behind the wheel
and changing lanes.
I see her riding a bicycle
on the shoulder of the road.
I hope there won't be an accident.
I hope there won't be any deaths.
I'm sorry.
That would be my reason.
Captain Jung Chaeman.
Let's do that together.
That's good. You're doing well.
Walk slowly.
Let's walk a bit more.
- That's good.
A bit more.
Dad, you've improved so much. Seriously.
- You're doing well. Right?
- He's doing very well.
- He improved a lot.
- Right?
- This is nothing.
- Good.
- I wonder…
- Yes?
…if I'll be able to drive again.
Why not?
Just because. I lack confidence.
I'm scared to.
Don't drive if you don't want to.
You've driven enough.
But you know,
I think you look the coolest
when you are driving.
When you turn the wheel,
your forearm muscles split.
When you back up the car,
you put your hand on the seat.
Not just anyone can do that.
Not just anyone.
When it comes to backing up the car,
you must be in the top three in Korea.
I sure am good at backing up the car.
My nickname used to be Min Back.
I know that.
Most of the time,
I don't even need to look.
That's right. How do you do that?
How do you do that?
NATIONAL OFFICE OF INVESTIGATION
TCI TEAM
This isn't a dream, is it?
We're really back, right?
It's more than that.
We're now under
the National Office of Investigation.
It's an upgrade!
National Office of Investigation, TCI.
It's seriously so cool.
Has the office been upgraded too?
- Has it?
- Has the office been upgraded too?
Gosh, it's snowing. Let's go inside.
- Let's go inside.
- All right.
An upgrade--
Why is our office the same?
If we're under
the National Office of Investigation,
- shouldn't our office get an upgrade?
- Exactly.
It really isn't easy to escape this place!
There's no space
at the Seoul Metropolitan Police.
They'll look into it, so let's wait.
It feels new and old.
I like it and hate it.
What's this emotion?
Being let down?
We should use our old desks then.
Why isn't Inspector Cha here yet?
I'm getting a call from Inspector Cha.
Why aren't you here?
Are you chasing a culprit or…
What?
I'm on my way.
I'm chasing an reckless driver.
It's your first day of work.
Where are you?
He's chasing a reckless driver.
Where?
He really is something.
Gosh, we just sat down.
It's our first case, so good--
Good luck.
Nothing has changed.
Inspector Cha.
Isn't this car really cool?
The exterior is so cool
and the interior is so clean.
It's totally my type.
You have good taste.
This is an electric car
with the aesthetics
as well as functional efficiency.
This model in particular
has eight speakers inside.
So you can enjoy the rich sounds.
- How do we apply for a test drive?
- You can apply for it
on the official website.
It has a safety function.
How nice.
Why do you want to buy a car?
I think I'll need it soon.
Do you want to listen to music?
Will you be okay? You were anxious
about listening to music while driving.
It's okay.
Go on in.
Congratulations on returning to TCI.
- What brings you here?
- There has been a case.
I'll see you often since you're under
the National Office of Investigation.
Look forward to it.
We're members
of the National Office of Investigation,
so we can carry out target investigations.
That means we can reopen
cold cases from the past.
My generosity ends here.
I won't go easy on you anymore.
I'll be prepared.
Let's have a proper face-off.
THE LATE LEE HYUNSOO
Did you hear about Minsung?
Yes. He received the final ruling.
I'm glad his sentence is lighter
than I expected.
When I visit him,
he seems like a different person.
He exercises diligently
and his thoughts have become clearer.
I'm relieved.
Yeonho.
You should live your life too.
You should date someone
and go on vacation.
You can laugh out loud.
You can do that now.
Let us
take one step forward.
From the place where we have stopped,
let's take one more step forward.
Inspector Cha.
You came to pick me up
for my dad's discharge.
Thank you. And you're driving too.
I wanted to pick up your father
with your car.
The road isn't our purpose
but it is progress.
The road takes us to special people
and also leads us to our destination.
But if someone breaks
the promises of the road,
ignores the rules of the road,
and discards the manners of the road,
the road can instantly become
an unfortunate place.
Everyone we meet on the road
is someone's family member
and a precious person.
Thus, we must all
stay safe.
If you're on the road right now,
we hope you'll safely return to those
who are waiting for you.
CRASH
SPECIAL APPEARANCE
BY SHIM SOYOUNG
Translated by Park Dong-joo
Ripped by WEISSACHsubs