CRASH
ALL CHARACTERS, LOCATIONS,
ORGANIZATIONS, EVENTS,
GROUPS, AND BACKGROUNDS
IN THIS WORK ARE FICTIONAL
When Jungwook was in LA…
Why can't I reach you?
I won't wait long.
Back then, you were always drunk
on alcohol and drugs.
What's wrong? What was the message about?
It's nothing.
Let's do ice today.
- You're good at injections, right?
- Yes.
Hey, tone it down.
You should think about your father--
This isn't murder.
Let me just blow off some steam.
Shall I have the guys bring it?
Tell them to bring something pure.
Okay.
Why are you so late?
Late? It took me less than five minutes.
Is it that punk again?
The police officer's son?
Goodness.
Don't use too much.
Your bones will weather.
Give me a break.
Wait here. He'll be out soon.
Yes, sir.
All right.
- It's going in.
- Take it out. Out!
Oh, Jungwook. My goodness.
Darn it.
Are you okay?
Please get in, sir.
- Look at that. A new car?
- Yes, it's a Mercedes-Benz 4MATIC.
It's perfect for speeding.
Jungwook!
You shouldn't drive.
I mean, it's a new car.
It isn't under your name, is it?
It's a burner car.
You little jerk. It's a violation
of the Motor Vehicle Management Act.
Do you want it to get confiscated?
So let me drive it once. I won't steal it.
Jungwook, let's get comfortable
in the back and have a drink.
I haven't been high in a while,
so I want to enjoy it, Mijin!
Hurry up and get in, you wench.
Damn it.
Thank you.
Have a good night.
Gosh! That bastard came out of nowhere!
Is he hurt?
- How could you drive that way?
- For goodness' sake.
Hey, don't get scared.
- Hey!
- Don't drive away!
That car is just driving off.
Hey!
Are you okay?
I'm at an alley
behind exit two of Sungoh Station.
A black sedan hit a motorcycle
and drove off.
- Jungwook!
- Whoa, whoa.
Darn it. What's going on?
What's up with that yellow bastard?
What do we do? He's following us.
Follow us all you want!
Stop the car!
- How could you hit someone and drive off?
- What the hell is he saying?
Jungwook.
That little…
Stop the car!
How could you youngsters be that way?
That yellow bastard is
getting on my nerves.
- I'll follow you until the end!
- He keeps following.
Let's just bribe him and make him leave.
- Don't turn this into a bigger problem.
- Damn it!
What are you doing?
Stop the car. It's dangerous.
That bastard!
Hey!
Goodbye!
CRASH
I'm at…
EPISODE 9
…an alley
behind exit two of Sungoh Station.
- Okay.
- A black sedan
hit a motorcycle and drove off.
A black sedan? Do you have
the license plate number?
I couldn't see it because it was dark.
But it went toward Sungoh Bridge.
The report to 112 was made at 1:34 a.m.
He got into an accident
while chasing a car
that hit a deliveryman and ran.
Have we confirmed
what happened at the scene?
Yes.
What's this? My goodness.
What's going on?
That's…
What a lunatic.
The driver was determined.
Is he trying to kill him?
Was it drunk driving?
- Did you identify the driver?
- We checked, but it's a burner car.
It's under a bankrupt company
with a ton of overdue bills.
So we don't know who the actual driver is.
No, but please watch the clip.
They're unlicensed taxi drivers
waiting near Gangnam.
If you look over there,
the black suspect vehicle was filmed.
I think it's an unlicensed taxi.
An unlicensed taxi in Gangnam?
Didn't Director General Lee Taeju
take on the case?
Why are they still roaming freely?
During our last investigation, we found
that each club had
a designated taxi company.
If we find the club,
we can identify the driver.
We put the car on the wanted list.
We have the dashcam video
from Lieutenant Min's father's taxi.
We'll identify the suspect soon.
We'll help too.
Tell us when you identify the driver.
We'll make the arrest.
That's right. Tell us if you need help.
We'll back you up.
Support the team with certainty.
Be genuine and fierce.
In any case, wrap up the case quickly,
with speed and precision.
This taxi is like her home.
Her mom passed away when she was young,
so I didn't want to leave her
at home alone.
That's why she always rode around
in my taxi.
She ate in here.
She studied in here.
She slept in here.
She practically grew up in here,
so I feel quite bad for her.
The visiting hours are over.
Okay.
Dad, hang in there.
I'll be waiting.
Okay?
I'll wait.
Ma'am.
Okay.
I'll get going now. I'll come again.
Sohee.
Why are you…
Why did you come here? You have no right.
Can I help you with anything?
The culprit is an unlicensed taxi driver.
You took the Gangnam taxi case
and promised to take care of it.
This wouldn't have happened
had you investigated properly. So what--
What can you help me with?
Just go. You won't hear
anything good from me.
Sohee.
You wrapped up the case
with a few arrests.
It's ridiculous. Give the case
back to me and I'll start over.
The taxi drivers won't talk anyway.
We won't have a way
to check the client list.
Is it because of Deputy Commissioner Pyo?
Because his son is involved in this case?
Has there been any external pressure?
- It isn't like that.
- Then what?
Is it the opposite?
Why are you looking for him?
Do you know him?
Tell Mijin to come here.
They're looking for your man.
You know him, right?
Yes. His name is Byungchan.
Did you meet him yesterday?
Are you here because of that?
He was driving a customer home
and got into a fight with a taxi driver.
Lee Byungchan, age 33.
He has six convictions for assault,
extortion, drug distribution,
and illegal taxi operation.
Since March, he has been working
at Quick Call, an unlicensed taxi company.
But he suddenly stopped
coming to work yesterday.
The last person who used the taxi
was an employee named Yoon Mijin.
While driving a customer,
there was a collision with the motorcycle.
The taxi driver who followed--
It was Lieutenant Min's father.
Yes.
According to Ms. Yoon Mijin,
she got off with the customer midway.
So she doesn't know what happened after.
The accident occurred after they got off?
What about the customer who was with her?
Well…
Pyo Jungwook.
He's Commissioner General Pyo's son.
He's well-known in the scene.
He spends generously and has good manners.
His father is in the police,
so there's no worry about a bust.
Gosh, Commissioner General Pyo's son?
Wasn't he on the list
during the unlicensed taxi and drug case?
Meet up with Lee Byungchan first.
If it was an unlicensed taxi,
Lee Byungchan was the driver.
Check and see
if his car was caught on any cameras.
- What should we do with Pyo Jungwook?
- Let's meet him as a witness.
See if his story checks out
with Yoon Mijin's.
Yes, sir.
Who are you?
Why are you doing this to me?
Tell me.
Excuse me. I don't know anything.
I really don't…
Jungwook!
Jungwook! Jungwook!
TRANSPORTATION
INFORMATION CENTER
Yes, Detective Woo.
The suspect car was caught on camera
on a highway near Homyeong Junction.
Okay.
Please show me the road
near Homyeong Junction.
On Local Highway 348 near Unho Bridge 1,
the suspect car was caught
on camera for speeding.
Local Highway 348 is connected
to Sinae Interchange.
Lee Byungchan's parents live in Haeju.
Perhaps he went there.
To go to Haeju, you need to pass
the North Haeju Interchange
and Mokgang Interchange.
He would've gotten caught
on traffic cameras.
So he's still between Mokgang-myeon
and Jeongdong-myeon.
This area has many mountains and lakes.
Did he hide the car there?
Rather than hiding the car,
getting rid of it would be better.
Will he scrap it?
Go through the junkyards in the area
and find the car.
Perhaps he ditched it in a lake.
See if there are any witnesses.
- Yes, sir.
SCRAPPED CAR LIST
There hasn't been a black sedan.
I'm from Namgang Police Station.
Have you seen this black car?
I haven't seen it.
Hold on.
Please wait. Just a second.
This one.
If we were a little late,
it would've vanished.
He already took the SD card
from the dashcam.
I'll ask NFS to run forensics on the car.
Okay. Well done.
Explain the situation thoroughly
to the forensic analysts.
Yes, sir.
Will we get anything from the car?
It's in a bad shape.
Who knows?
We might be able to restore the ECU data.
Judging by the way he scrapped it
in a hurry, he must be hiding something.
You're right.
NATIONAL FORENSIC SERVICE
About the car from Namgang Police Station…
Didn't they say only the driver
was in the car?
Yes, they did. What about it?
I'm going through the information
on the EDR.
Something seems off.
Come check this out.
RECORDS INFORMATION
DURING COLLISIONS
What's this?
Check this out.
Seat belts were fastened
in the passenger seat and the back seat.
What? There must've been a driver, so…
At the time of the accident,
three people were in the car.
ANALYSIS ON SUSPECTED VEHICLE
On the upper part of the window
by the driver's seat,
Pyo Jungwook's blood and DNA were found.
The driver was Pyo Jungwook.
But Yoon Mijin said
she got out of the car--
Pyo Jungwook must've made her say that
in order to hide his crime.
Captain, what are you doing?
This bastard hurt Lieutenant's father.
He's Commissioner General Pyo's son.
If we go into this unprepared,
we'll suffer from a counterattack.
But we can't wait around like this.
If we stall, he may destroy the evidence.
We must get an arrest warrant
as soon as possible.
What about it?
Over here.
"Belted." Seat belts were fastened.
"Not belted." Seat belts weren't fastened.
I know what that means!
So what does this mean?
The driver was Pyo Jungwook.
Commissioner General Pyo's son.
Commissioner General Pyo's son?
I thought the culprit was a taxi driver.
Pyo Jungwook's blood and DNA
were found in the driver's seat.
Commissioner General Pyo's son?
DNA. Hold on.
Why did Commissioner General Pyo's son
suddenly enter the picture?
Are you certain about all this?
Yes, sir.
Hold on. Let me think.
We need to be careful.
Otherwise, everyone here will die.
Everyone will get fired!
We'll get a confession from the suspect
and request a warrant.
Are we really going
to go through with this?
We need to do this, right?
Oh, gosh. My goodness.
My goodness.
Oh, dear.
As a suspect?
Okay then.
I'm hanging up now.
It appears Pyo Jungwook drove the car.
Commissioner General Pyo's son.
We have forensic analysis
and circumstantial evidence.
Pyo Jungwook, was it you?
Were you really the driver?
Answer me!
- What the heck?
- She startled me.
Who are you?
How could you have a drinking party
after running over a man? That's nonsense!
Oh, right. You're talking
about that accident.
I'm sorry. I heard from my lawyer.
I heard that you're a police officer.
I have a question.
Is a police officer's salary that low?
Seeing that your father drives a taxi.
I mean, let's look on the bright side.
It'd be nice for him
to get a good rest at the hospital.
Hey, don't laugh. Fill up your glasses.
- Cheers.
- The detective's father is quite ill.
For your father's complete recovery!
Cheers!
But if anything were to go wrong,
don't worry.
I'll give a hefty amount
at his funeral as condolatory money.
- Wow! You're so cool!
- I'll be conscientious.
You crazy bastard!
What did you just say?
Hey!
Let's leave.
Inspector Cha, hold on.
- You bastard!
- Are you okay?
- What a lunatic.
Is she insane?
How entertaining.
Has she lost her mind? Are you okay?
- For goodness' sake.
- Gosh, totally.
Be quiet.
- She ruined the mood.
- I said, be quiet!
Yes, Father.
Where are you?
Well, I'm working out right now.
Come outside.
He doesn't even know where I am.
How did you know I was here?
What happened to your forehead?
It's nothing.
Seriously, stop it.
Hey, I told you to stay in your lane
when you play around.
If you want to do drugs or meet women,
do so in secret.
How long must I clean up your mess? Huh?
That's why I didn't tell you.
I'll take care of it myself.
How? What can you do on your own?
You only know how to drink
and cause trouble.
Do you still take me for a child?
- What did you say?
- Father.
Be honest. Do you want me to go to prison?
- Will you be relieved then?
- You little…
I'm doing this because of you.
So that I don't harm your career!
Do you remember what you told me?
Ever since I was little, you told me
to get what I want using any means.
I learned that lesson by heart.
So now, please just trust your son…
and watch from outside.
Damn it.
Damn it!
Thank you.
Are you okay?
How did you know I was there?
Pyo Jungwook's interrogation is tomorrow.
I thought it'd be advantageous
to find Lee Byungchan first,
so I was on a stakeout.
Then I saw Pyo Jungwook.
What?
I know why you went there.
Tomorrow, I'll prove that Pyo Jungwook
is the real culprit.
Lieutenant.
Captain.
Welcome back. How's your father?
Well, he's getting a little better
day by day.
I want to observe
the interrogation with Pyo Jungwook.
Would that be okay?
Inspector Cha.
SEOUL NAMGANG POLICE STATION
WILL PROTECT
THE CITIZENS' DAILY LIVES
Gosh, I see you so often.
Are you a stalker or something?
Geez, is she the only detective here?
Before we begin,
I'd like to inform the suspect
that he can refuse to make statements.
You have a lawyer present
during the interrogation, right?
Yes, I am the suspect's lawyer.
According to Ms. Yoon Mijin,
who was in the car during the accident,
she sat behind the driver's seat
and Mr. Pyo Jungwook sat
behind the passenger seat.
- Is it true?
- Yes.
When you were in the car,
did you put on the seat belt?
No.
When you got in the car,
was the seat belt fastened?
Say that you don't remember.
I don't remember.
When you got out of the car,
- did you leave the seat belt fastened?
- Say that you don't remember.
I have no recollection.
This is the EDR information
of Lee Byungchan's car
from the moment of the accident.
As you can see,
the seat belts were fastened
in the passenger seat
and the seat behind it.
Do you know what this means?
My client got out of the car
before the accident occurred,
so he knows nothing about this.
According to Ms. Yoon Mijin,
the car took off right after
she and Mr. Pyo Jungwook got out.
Lee Byungchan was busy running away.
There's no way he went
to the empty passenger seat
and the seat behind it
to fasten the seat belts.
What do you think?
How would I know?
My client's claim is consistent.
He got out before the accident,
so he doesn't know
what happened afterward.
Mr. Pyo Jungwook.
When did you get the wound
on the left side of your forehead?
Oh, this?
I got it while exercising.
It's not from when you hit it
on the window of Lee Byungchan's car?
On top of the driver's seat window
of Lee Byungchan's car,
your blood and DNA have been found.
On the driver's side seat and floor,
the fiber of the clothes
you were wearing has been found.
Here is the forensic analysis.
Judging by the blood, DNA,
and fiber I had just mentioned,
the passengers' seats are as follows.
Pyo Jungwook in the driver's seat.
Lee Byungchan in the passenger seat
and Yoon Mijin in the back seat.
All the evidence
tells us that you were the driver
at the time of the accident.
Will you continue to play innocent?
Such simulations can only be used
as reference material in court.
Don't you know
these aren't direct evidence?
These are just circumstantial evidence.
Mr. Pyo Jungwook.
That night,
you drove the car, didn't you?
Let me repeat.
My client got out of the car
before the accident.
You drove the car, didn't you?
You were afraid of the truth getting out,
so you made up a lie
about getting out beforehand.
Thank you so much for your hard work.
My heart is beating so fast
because I feel like the culprit.
But you know,
such evidence is useless.
Bring me something cool.
Did you think that you could arrest me
with such lousy evidence?
How may I help you?
Oh, well.
I'm here to turn myself in.
Captain, Mr. Lee Byungchan
came to turn himself in.
What's this? Turn himself in?
I think he talked to Pyo Jungwook.
Otherwise, the timing is…
- I'll go in.
- Donggi, go in.
- Hey!
Don't you know the rules?
Donggi, go in.
Lieutenant.
The taxi driver followed me persistently.
I became angry
and did it without thinking.
Who was in the car
at the time of the accident?
I was alone.
I had a passenger, but he got out before.
Are you certain
he got out before the accident?
Why would I lie about that?
I was alone.
Seat belts were fastened
in the passenger seat
and the seat behind it.
Oh, that.
I fastened them. It's a habit of mine.
I do it so it's more convenient
for the passengers.
Do you expect me to believe that?
It's true.
Gosh, I'm getting hounded
because of my strange habit.
Why did you scrap the car right away,
if you were planning to turn yourself in?
I did that
because the car was badly damaged.
It would've happened sooner or later
since it was a burner car.
In any case…
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry about what happened
to the taxi driver.
Here.
- All of it.
- You were very natural.
I was so nervous.
- Really? You didn't look that way.
- I was extremely nervous.
Can we go now?
Yeah?
When can we go?
I heard the culprit turned himself in.
I told you I didn't do it.
A selfie.
I'll keep it a secret from my father.
You became an officer recently,
so it'd be bad to get fired already.
Can't you hear me?
Why are there so many frustrating people?
Hey, Pyo Jungwook.
What?
I heard that the culprit got caught.
Congratulations. Wow.
Well, work hard.
We have nothing else to talk about.
All right, then.
I meant it when I said that I'd give
a lot of condolatory money.
What did you just say?
So give me a call.
- Lieutenant, calm down.
- You bastard.
How dare you say that?
Lieutenant.
These police officers are running wild!
What do you think you're doing?
You should've worked harder.
Lieutenant.
He got Lee Byungchan and Yoon Mijin
to tell his version of the story.
He was at a disadvantage,
so he had Lee Byungchan turn himself in.
I'm certain he promised monetary rewards.
If that's the case,
we need evidence like bank transactions.
We'll find the evidence.
Let's use what we have now
to request an arrest warrant.
Hold on. That'd be a bit…
I talked to a judicial officer earlier.
Though he's suspicious,
there's no direct evidence.
If the prosecution releases him
due to the lack of evidence,
Namgang Police Station
will be put in a difficult position.
Are you asking because you don't know?
He's Commissioner General Pyo's son!
Why would the prosecution dismiss it
despite the clear evidence?
How frustrating.
That man named Lee something
turned himself in.
Am I wrong? He pleaded guilty.
That means it's over!
I'm sorry.
It's my fault Pyo Jungwook walked free.
I should've considered
Lee Byungchan turning himself in.
Why would you be sorry?
Why are you sorry?
The guilty ones are just fine.
I'm so angry it's driving me crazy.
I'm a police officer, but I'm powerless
before the culprit who hurt my family.
It makes me so furious.
I promise to catch the culprit.
Pyo Jungwook.
I also have a reason to do so.
What's all this?
They're related to my past accident.
Why would you…
We were blackmailed.
Everyone here, including myself.
Yang Jaeyoung, Han Kyungsoo, Pyo Jungwook…
They're the witnesses of the accident.
Hold on. Those three were
the witnesses of your accident?
How is this possible?
Among them, Yang Jaeyoung was killed.
Han Kyungsoo is currently missing.
Missing?
HAN KYUNGSOO
- Hello?
- Help me.
Help me. Pyo Jungwook…
Hello?
That day, I got a call from Han Kyungsoo.
He said Pyo Jungwook was after him.
Mr. Han Kyungsoo.
I visited his place the next day.
It looked like he had gone out,
but I couldn't reach him since then.
Could it be that Pyo Jungwook
killed Han Kyungsoo?
Yes. There's a possibility.
Or it could be the culprit
who killed Yang Jaeyoung.
At the scene of his accident,
there was a black car with tinted windows.
At Sangsan Rest Area
where I ran into Han Kyungsoo,
I saw a similar car.
Captain is investigating that car.
Hold on.
What exactly happened in the past?
Who is after the witnesses? Why?
I mean…
Why did Pyo Jungwook and Han Kyungsoo--
All I know is that three high schoolers
drove a car without a driver's license.
They witnessed my accident by chance
and reported it to 911.
Was Pyo Jungwook the driver back then?
No, they said Han Kyungsoo was the driver.
The car was Pyo Myunghak's.
Han Kyungsoo drove Pyo Myunghak's car?
It's a pattern we're familiar with.
They switched the driver.
Could it be why Pyo Jungwook
is after Han Kyungsoo?
Even if that's the case,
it's no reason to kill a man.
After all, the one who caused the accident
was me.
It can only mean that
something else happened back then.
Is there anything else you remember?
Was there anything suspicious?
I can't remember it clearly,
no matter how hard I try.
Oh, right.
It must be a difficult memory for you.
Although it isn't clear,
there's an image I see regularly.
Lights?
I can't be certain.
Hold on. If you saw lights,
it must've been from the headlights.
Perhaps Pyo Jungwook did something
at the scene of the accident.
He might be killing off his accomplices
in order to cover it up.
If that's the case,
why did Commissioner General Pyo
give Yang Jaeyoung's case to Captain?
- Why did he send the letters too?
- You're right.
Then who on earth…
Where's the letter?
It's here.
This is what I received.
That's what Han Kyungsoo received.
As you can see,
the printing pattern is the same.
They're from the same printer.
It means they came from the same person.
What's certain is that Pyo Jungwook
did something in the past.
And that's why someone hurt
Yang Jaeyoung and Han Kyungsoo.
Did you confirm Lee Jungsub's alibi?
He was at the hospital at the time
of Han Kyungsoo's disappearance.
But we can't be certain.
There's a chance
he left the hospital secretly.
I guess they took the initiative.
I don't know if this is a good thing.
Yang Jaeyoung and Han Kyungsoo.
The next one will be…
Leave Lee Jungsub to me.
I'll… take care of him.
Myunghak, if he's the one
who killed Jaeyoung,
we can't give him the easy way out.
We're in no situation to get rid of him.
I'm the Commissioner General of Seoul.
We need to do it by the law!
Cha Yeonho was the one
who reported Han Kyungsoo missing.
What?
Han Kyungsoo called Cha Yeonho
just before he went missing.
Does that mean Han Kyungsoo
told Cha Yeonho?
Damn it!
- Commissioner General.
- What?
Let's corner them.
What?
What? An evasive investigation?
You can give an explanation
to the disciplinary committee.
Let's go.
Is this the best
Commissioner General has got?
Cutting me off
and putting you in my position?
Captain.
Reflect on your mistakes
before you start writing a novel.
Why'd you hesitate to investigate
Yang Jaeyoung's case?
Is there a reason why
the culprit cannot be caught?
"He that touches pitch shall be defiled."
You are becoming more and more
like Commissioner General.
Escort Captain out.
- Yes, sir.
It's this way.
In the meantime,
I'll be the captain of TCI.
Report every development
in your investigation to me.
Why are you doing this?
What are you trying to hide?
I'm simply following
Commissioner General's order.
Do you even know what you're doing?
Why is the disciplinary committee
at Seoul Metropolitan Police?
Commissioner General called.
He asked me to send Captain
to Seoul Metropolitan Police
since he was the one
who assigned the case.
He should've been given time
to prepare for the disciplinary committee.
He wasn't even given a notice to attend--
You're right. That's how it should be.
But this is…
What do you want me to do?
It was Commissioner General Pyo's order.
Was I supposed to ask
for a private meeting and attack him?
Was I supposed to go all out without fear?
This is a very difficult position.
A very difficult position.
As for me,
I'm struggling a lot too.
It's already past 10 p.m.
He's late.
What's going on?
- Captain.
- Why didn't you go home?
What did the disciplinary committee say?
Well…
Three months of disciplinary action.
Neglect of duty, excessive investigation,
and undermining the police prestige.
I couldn't believe it.
Don't worry about it.
Why is Commissioner General Pyo
doing this to you?
Why did he assign
Yang Jaeyoung's case to you
and submit you
to a disciplinary action for it?
What's the relationship
between the two of you?
This is my investigation of your accident
at Eunseong Police Station.
I went over your case thoroughly
because Jungsub asked me to.
There was one strange thing.
The initial report to 911.
The first report was made
from Han Kyungsoo's phone.
He called and hung up without a word.
The emergency dispatcher found it strange
and called him back repeatedly.
Four minutes later,
the one who answered was
Han Kyungsoo.
Those four minutes.
I was suspicious about
what happened during that time.
During my interrogation,
Pyo Myunghak, who was Chief at the time,
suddenly entered the room.
I think you should be cool
and just admit it.
You need to be honest for me to help you.
I saw lights.
I can't be certain,
but I saw some lights
that crossed the center line.
Was there a car that crossed--
Hold on.
Mr. Cha Yeonho.
What are you talking about?
You killed a person by mistake.
Why are you coming up
with a strange excuse?
Is there evidence?
You'll only complicate the matter
if you behave this way
when there are witnesses.
Do you understand?
For goodness' sake.
If your memory is correct,
Pyo Myunghak intentionally left out
that part of the testimony.
Because the only car that could've crossed
the center line belonged to him.
If you and I
clung tenaciously
to what seemed trivial at the time,
things might've been different now.
I was planning to do so,
but I was transferred
to the countryside right after.
Transferred?
Gosh, it was only a transfer by name.
It was a demotion
for illegal investigation.
The Chief of Eunseong Police Station,
Pyo Myunghak, probably had a say.
On top of that,
my wife passed away from a hit-and-run.
I'm sorry.
Captain.
Where did you get these photos?
They aren't from the forensics.
Go meet
the reporter who wrote this article.
He was as invested as I was
in the accident.
I got these photos from him.
EUNSEONG DAILY
There were suspicions
regarding the accident at the time,
but they removed the follow-up articles.
They said the story wasn't newsworthy.
I didn't understand at the time.
I wondered
what outside pressure was at play.
Hold on. It occurred in 2014.
Here are the photos from the time.
All right.
Here.
DAEJEON EUNSEONG POLICE STATION
These are photos of the scene.
Did you notice anything strange
while covering the story?
The witnesses' testimonies
were suspicious.
Their testimonies didn't match.
They also didn't match
with the photos of the scene.
May we take these photos?
Sure.
By the way,
why are you digging up this case again?
Don't you know who their fathers are?
One is the current Commissioner General
and one is the chairman of YSC Group,
a former gangster.
You'd better be careful.
Okay. Thank you.
Hello.
Where are Lieutenant Min
and Inspector Cha?
There was a report of a staged crash,
so they went to the scene.
Where would that be?
She received the report herself,
so we're not so sure…
I guess the superiors take
such trivial cases in this team.
For goodness' sake.
It's Lee Taeju. Don't mind him.
Over here. It's a skid mark.
It was at the location of the accident.
I think it was from a car
on the opposite side.
Could it be the car that passed
the center line?
It makes sense if it was from that car.
And this.
The name of the tire is in the photo,
so I looked it up on the Internet.
The tread of the tire…
has this pattern.
Isn't it the same tire?
Like Captain said,
the car that crossed the center line was…
Look at this photo.
It's the tire mark
from Lee Hyunsoo's body.
I need to go back to the scene.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Shall we begin?
TRAFFIC ACCIDENT
EUNDONG JUNCTION, EUNSEONG-GU
Pyo Jungwook's car stopped
over there, across the road.
But according to their testimonies,
the witnesses' car should've been there,
across the road ahead of the accident.
Why was Pyo Jungwook's car
on the same side of the road?
Are you sure you're okay?
Yes.
Kyungsoo!
What's this?
Hey! Hey!
Hey! You bastard!
Hey!
What the hell!
You crazy bastard!
The witnesses were the culprits.
Then the tire mark on Lee Hyunsoo's body…
It's from Pyo Myunghak's car.
Pyo Jungwook and his friends ran over
and killed Lee Hyunsoo.
- I think the culprit knows the truth.
- Wouldn't it be Pyo Jungwook's doing?
Perhaps he got rid of Yang Jaeyoung
and Han Kyungsoo, witnesses to his crime.
- It isn't Pyo Jungwook.
- Why not?
There's something I haven't told you two.
The culprit who drives the black car…
has a crippled leg.
Could it be…
KIM HYUNMIN
Where's your son-in-law right now?
Mr. Kim Minsung.
Inspector Cha,
what brings you here at this hour?
Mr. Kim Minsung.
Perhaps,
I should call you Mr. Kim Hyunmin now.
CRASH
Kim Hyunmin, the forensic analyst,
is Kim Minsung.
He's getting revenge for his late wife.
Chairman Yang,
since when did you abide by the law?
I'll avenge Jaeyoung's death.
Putting those bastards in prison
won't change a thing.
I promise I'll catch them.
Why don't you mind your own business?
Don't meddle and risk losing your team.
The world is quite unfair.
Bring him to me.
I'll carry out the last blow.
Han Kyungsoo has testified.
The evidence is inadmissible.
This is just the beginning.
From now on,
I'll make you pay for all your sins.
PEOPLE OF THE POLICE STATION
I'm here today
because I had a feeling
that some may have heard
an unfamiliar term in today's episode.
DIRECTOR PYO JUNGWOOK
An unlicensed taxi. Not unicyclist.
Some might wonder exactly what it means.
If you don't know the term,
it means that you're leading
an upright life.
So you don't need to be embarrassed.
So what is an unlicensed taxi?
They're illegal taxis that usually operate
in entertainment districts
such as Gangnam.
Luxury foreign cars are used
to pick up and drop off customers
and entertainment business employees.
It's a mode of transportation
that's secretive and quite expensive.
Customers pay a hefty price
to ride illegal taxis
since they're secretive people
who wish to keep
their destinations and partners private.
But here's the problem.
Unlicensed taxis that guarantee privacy
are used for crimes
as you saw in this episode.
If they become involved in crimes,
it's hard to track down
the cars and culprits.
Thus, they hinder investigations.
Just like burner phones and burner cars,
illegal taxis are widespread
due to low public awareness
and their difficulty to track
in a crackdown.
Thus, unlicensed taxis
are being used in various crimes.
In Crash, Sohee wishes to eradicate
unlicensed taxis
because of such problems.
Until now, unlicensed taxis
were not a major concern
because they were seen
as a lesser-known practice.
Let's wait for the day
they become eradicated.
Jungwook, don't use unlicensed taxis.
THIS CAMPAIGN WAS BROUGHT TO YOU
BY SEOUL METROPOLITAN POLICE
Translated by Park Dong-joo
Ripped and synced by
WEISSACHsubs