CRASH
ALL CHARACTERS, LOCATIONS,
ORGANIZATIONS, EVENTS,
GROUPS, AND BACKGROUNDS
IN THIS WORK ARE FICTIONAL
What the hell?
Look at this bastard.
Hey, stop the car!
Are you insane? I said stop the car!
Look at you.
You jerk.
Please help me.
Help me.
Please.
I'm sorry.
Please help.
Jungwook.
Jungwook is here.
Sir.
I won't be able to forget Jaeyoung.
My goodness.
When he was alive, he would cause
so much trouble with his drinking problem.
I didn't think he would die before me.
As for the matter of drunk driving,
I made sure word didn't get out.
- Thank you.
- Don't mention it.
Jaeyoung was like a son to me.
The thing is,
there's something about Jaeyoung's car.
The brake fluid line was pulled out.
Was there a problem with the car?
I don't think it was a simple accident.
I checked the surveillance cameras.
Before the accident,
a black car was following him.
Are you saying
that bastard killed Jaeyoung?
Who is he?
Who dared to kill my son?
I'm looking into it.
It isn't certain yet, so wait.
If I get my hands on that bastard…
Why did he pass away so soon?
My poor Jaeyoung.
What are you doing here?
I had to come when I heard the news.
You came to check if he's really dead?
How could you say that?
What happened to him?
- How did you know about his death?
- The alumni group chat.
Jaeyoung was on his way to Daejeon.
So you have a social life, huh?
- What did you do yesterday?
- I drove, worked,
- and ate out.
- It wasn't an accident.
Someone killed him.
A bastard in a black car.
Does that mean Jaeyoung…
Are you suspecting me?
Why would I do that? Huh?
Who knows?
A jerk with a messed up life
can do anything.
How about you? You sure you didn't do it?
Perhaps you wanted to keep him
from babbling about--
Shut up, you bastard.
How dare you?
What are you doing at a friend's funeral?
Kyungsoo, it's been a while.
Have you been well?
Yes, sir.
Kyungsoo, I was inattentive
after the incident.
- I'll do better from now on.
- Uh. Yes, sir.
All right then.
Always drive carefully.
Yes, sir.
By the way,
if you see a black car lurking around,
make sure you give me a call.
Yes, sir.
All right.
CRASH
THE LATE LEE HYUNSOO
EPISODE 7
You're here.
Did you bring those flowers?
No, they were already here when I arrived.
How is your wife doing?
She's the same.
And you? How is being a police officer?
I'm learning a lot, sir.
About that letter…
Did you find out who sent it?
No, not yet.
By any chance…
Do you know something?
No.
I just asked.
I was curious, that's all.
Let's go eat.
There's a nice sundubu place nearby.
Come with me.
My poor Jaeyoung.
How am I going to live?
Jaeyoung.
This is 112 Emergency Center.
This is Route 78 to Seoul.
A car is parked on the road.
I think the driver fell asleep.
I'm worried an accident might happen.
Please do something.
ROUTE 78
Why does she always make me carry
such a big bundle?
Gosh. There's more stuff every time.
Hello.
Do you know me?
Aren't you Detective Woo Donggi's father?
Have we met before?
No, you just resemble him a lot.
How do you know Donggi?
Well, I'm Detective Woo's colleague,
Eo Hyunkyung.
Oh, I see.
It's nice to meet you.
It must be hard to work with Donggi.
You see, unlike his looks,
he's quite difficult.
He gets his looks from me,
but his personality is
just like his mother.
Don't be ridiculous.
My personality is the same as yours.
Why did you bring so much? Give it to me.
- Your mom always makes me deliver things.
- Give it.
Must I always carry duvets and this bag
in order for you to give us a call
once in a while, you punk?
Why does she keep buying duvets? Does
she think I can't sleep without duvets?
How did you know that he was my father?
I'm sorry, but it's written on your faces.
Father and son.
It's written on my face?
Hey, hold on.
- Isn't this my hat?
- It's mine. Give it here.
- Give it here. Give it.
- Take the shiny one.
I don't want an old man's hat. It smells.
Give it here. It's mine. Gosh,
you ruined my hair.
There's no hair to ruin, you punk.
- Geez, seriously.
- It's as shiny as a dime in the sun.
For goodness' sake.
Wear this instead of a kid's hat.
- Come on, you punk.
- No. You wear it.
An old man's hat smells.
- Gosh, my hair. I need to go back inside.
- Goodness.
You always make a fuss
when you have no hair.
Get going.
- Give it here.
- See you around, okay?
Have a safe trip home, sir.
You're so pretty.
Hold on. Father.
Here. Take this.
- What's this?
- Take it. It's money.
- Is it money?
- Yes.
- Why is it so thin?
- They're 50,000 won bills.
My goodness.
They're really 50,000 won bills.
He's like your doppelgänger
in his looks, expressions and speech.
I guess his genes were strong.
Like two peas in a pod.
That's why I still don't eat peas.
Whenever I see same-looking things,
my heart drops.
Is he still in the freight business?
He quit last year.
His stamina isn't the same.
He runs errands for my mom,
gardens, and does household chores.
He's such a family man.
Despite his looks,
my father is very feminine and delicate.
Even his name is feminine.
It's Woo Gilsoon.
I can see Detective Woo's future.
Hey, take that back. Words have power.
Hyunkyung, who do you take after?
Is your mom a beauty?
- No.
- Then is your dad handsome?
- I don't take after anyone.
- That makes no sense.
They didn't pick you up on the streets.
Let's see a photo.
I don't like taking photos.
You're suspicious in many ways.
She doesn't have to tell us
if she doesn't want to, right?
Did you hear? Crimes Division and
Women's Division will get more recruits.
Yes, I heard.
Can't our team get more recruits too?
Probably not.
Inspector Cha joined recently.
That's right.
We have Inspector Cha. Where is he?
Why isn't he coming?
Is he the only one with flexible hours?
Is that it? What?
Yes, Superintendent.
I'm on my way.
There's a stationary car
in the middle of the road.
I'll call Inspector Cha.
Go.
- Seriously?
- Yes.
I got this information
from a subordinate at HQ.
You fed me false information
about Cha Yeonho
and made a complete fool out of me.
Do you know how hard my life is
after giving up my parking space?
I suffered so many losses.
But I'm certain this time.
- You sure? Did you double-check?
- Double--
I triple-checked.
I see.
So someone in the Inspection Division
at HQ has a child at our station, huh?
That's right.
- Who is it?
- I don't know who it is.
Who is it? That's crucial information.
Who is it?
I don't know that yet, but it's true.
- For goodness' sake.
- All right.
But…
Trust me.
Here.
Sir.
Sir, wake up. Excuse me?
- Hyunkyung, open the door.
- Okay.
Did you call 911?
They're running late
due to morning traffic.
Okay.
- Ready?
- Yes.
I'll turn it. One, two.
It's working.
- A bit more. All right.
- One, two.
- It's working.
- Good. Open it.
- Oh, it worked.
Sir.
What should we do?
What do you think that is?
It looks like a machine part.
We'll need to send it to the NFS.
Oh, dear.
Hold on.
Yes, Inspector Cha.
Hey, Min Sohee. This is Superintendent Ha
of Gangsan Police Station.
Superintendent Ha,
why are you calling from this phone?
There's been
a car carrier trailer rollover,
so I'm at the scene.
A man keeps entering the scene,
claiming to be a police officer.
He doesn't have an ID.
Hey!
I told you not to enter!
Why won't you listen?
Get out!
This is driving me crazy.
Where are you?
STOP
- Oh, no.
- They're here.
My goodness.
Excuse me. Coming through.
Thank you.
Superintendent Ha.
- Hello.
Gosh, your skin is glowing.
Did you quit smoking?
Are you kidding me?
I just smoked one because of that punk.
Is he on your team?
Yes, he's Inspector Cha Yeonho.
He joined the team a few months ago.
Then why is he going around alone
without an ID?
Inspector Cha, didn't you bring your ID?
I told you to carry it with you.
In any case, take him with you.
What is he doing at our scene?
He keeps saying that something is missing.
I'm sorry.
Gosh, what happened here?
Isn't it obvious?
It's a rollover caused by an overload.
- Hey, hurry up and clean it up.
- Yes, sir.
We're blocking the road. Hurry up.
Inspector Cha.
It's rude to do this
at another team's scene.
It's a simple rollover.
What are you looking at?
Something doesn't seem right.
It needs to be here.
- Hey, Min Sohee.
- Yes?
- Hurry up and leave.
- Yes, sir.
Let's go. Hurry.
All right. Let's talk as we go.
Hurry up. Be careful.
Be careful. Watch out.
We're going. Thank you.
On Route 78, near Gunae Tollgate,
a car carrier trailer rollover
caused injuries
and tens of millions of won worth
of damage.
This year alone,
there have been three cases of rollovers
resulting in five deaths.
The causes are illegal modifications
and overload.
A five-ton car carrier trailer
can only carry up to three cars
according to relevant regulations.
But this car carrier trailer
was carrying five cars.
In order to carry more cars in one trip,
the trailer had been illegally modified.
- What's the reason for the overload?
- Otherwise, there are no profits.
If the drivers say that it's illegal,
the company owners cut off work.
- We can't help it.
- Gosh.
The driver who caused the accident
isn't at fault.
Seriously.
We have no power.
We must do as they say,
whether it be five or seven cars.
- Gosh.
- Everyone, be careful.
Insurance is of no use
in the case of a rollover.
Everyone knows that.
But we can't make any profits
if we follow regulations.
Seriously, it can't be helped.
…and is threatening the safety
of our citizens on the road.
Please come this way.
I did the basic inspection
as you requested
and changed the engine oil.
Would you like to take a look?
As you can see, nothing was amiss
from the engine and transmission.
Gosh, even a car checkup
uses data analysis these days.
The world changes
at an alarming speed, right?
Everything you requested is done.
- Please drive safely.
- Thank you. I'll take a look.
Yes, sir.
Inspector Cha, you're here.
- You have an appointment for 5 p.m.
- Yes.
- Hello.
- I didn't expect to see you here.
Do you two know each other?
I decided to start driving again.
I left my car here for maintenance.
I made a special effort
since it was your car, Inspector Cha.
You don't have to worry.
It's too bad that you won't need
a drive home from now on.
Right.
- Is that your car?
- Yes.
It's a nice car.
NATIONAL FORENSIC SERVICE
What is it?
It's a ratchet buckle.
It's used to secure the cargo
during transport.
If you look over here, it's a bit…
Someone cut it on purpose.
That's right.
If it broke on its own,
the cross section would've been smooth.
But it broke off in a pointed shape.
It means someone cut it on purpose
using a tool like a bolt cutter.
You already know this.
I heard you graduated from KAIST.
I'm also a fellow graduate.
I see.
What was the location of the accident?
Route 78, near Gunae Tollgate.
It isn't too far from the scene
of the car carrier rollover.
No way.
Excuse me.
So the metal piece stuck in
the deceased victim's neck
is from the trailer rollover
Inspector Cha witnessed.
We're certain it came
from the car carrier trailer.
It's a ratchet buckle, used to hold down--
- Let's talk at the station.
- Yes, sir.
So someone cut
the ratchet buckle on purpose.
Then it's a case, not an accident.
The dashcam had been formatted too.
The culprit erased it and turned it off
in case they were caught on camera.
The doors must've been locked.
How did he get in?
Maybe the driver did it.
There's a chance
he was after the insurance benefit.
A five-ton vehicle can only claim benefits
for the appropriate load.
Since the trailer was modified illegally
for overload,
insurance won't cover it.
Then who in the company
would benefit from this?
I know this since my father
was a freight driver.
An accident is bad news for the driver,
the freight owner and the company.
It's a loss for everyone.
It doesn't benefit anyone.
Then there's a high chance
that the cause is a personal grudge.
Let's interview people
the driver may know.
Okay.
What do you think you're doing?
Answer me.
Wipe this.
Do you have no morality?
How could you steal the case
without a word
in the middle of our investigation?
"Steal the case"?
We figured out
the possibility of a crime, so--
Forget about that crap.
Who has jurisdiction over this case?
We do.
If you wanted to investigate,
you should've consulted us first.
Why did you go through the dashcam
without telling us?
You thought it was an accident and
had the Investigation Section take over.
Wh-- What are you talking about?
We were running an investigation
thinking that it might be intentional.
- Isn't that right?
- Yes, sir.
In any case, we have jurisdiction over it.
Are you doing this because
what seemed to be a simple accident
became much bigger?
You just want to ride on our coattails.
What? How dare you say that?
- Hey, who's riding on whose coattails?
- Please sit. You sit down too.
Well…
Please calm down. How do we go about this?
According to page two, section nine
of the police's directives
on assigning jurisdiction over a case,
a case that has been reported
to two or more police stations
and is in need of a joint investigation
can be assigned by the chiefs
of the involved police stations
with the case's importance
and efficiency of investigation in mind.
That's the rule.
So it's up to the chiefs to decide
which police station
will take the case, right?
That's right.
Hold on.
Let's see.
Chief Seo of Gangsan Police Station.
Hello, Chief Seo.
It's been a while. Yes.
It's about the car carrier trailer case.
You heard, right?
Give us the case.
But… Wait, Chief.
Come on, why would you ask me that?
My guys have already made progress
with the investigation.
No, it isn't like that.
They were the ones who figured out
that it wasn't a simple accident.
Really? Okay. Let's do that.
Okay. All right.
Okay.
I'm going to use the restroom.
"My guys"?
Since when were we Chief's guys?
Rather than feeling touched,
I got the chills.
Why is Chief suddenly being like that?
He sided with his own subordinates.
Another station's good work
won't benefit him.
I get that, but his tone was strange.
He kept saying "my guys."
He was too affectionate. What an old fart.
I struggled with it too.
We have jurisdiction over it now,
so let's jump into the case.
Meet the car carrier trailer driver first.
- Yes, sir.
I was very smooth just now, right?
Yes, you were quite natural.
There was a term for it.
Hold on. Don't tell me.
Hold on.
Cold on the outside, warm on the inside.
Right, exactly.
I think that should be
my character from now on.
- It won't be obvious.
- That's a good idea.
How did I do?
- What? What do you mean?
- Well…
"Page two, section three
of the police's directives."
Who has jurisdiction over the case?
I kept them on their toes
and tossed it to you at a crucial moment.
It was natural.
It was as precise as Beckham's pass.
Nice.
Do you know what kids call it these days?
Dragon and tiger's match?
We have good chemistry.
Nice! Hurrah for the perfect chemistry!
NAM JAEHOON
Can I help you?
We're the police.
We're here to see Mr. Nam Jaehoon.
- He was here just now.
- Lieutenant.
Where is that?
It's the rooftop.
Show me the cameras of the rooftop. Hurry.
Mr. Nam Jaehoon.
I'm a police officer.
Do you know
how many people visited me today?
Everyone is making a fuss
and demanding that I pay for the damage.
They're the ones who ordered me
to overload the trailer.
Now that there's been an accident,
they're feigning ignorance.
I'll lose my savings
for my kids' college tuition
and the security deposit for my house.
That alone is enough
to make me feel victimized and angry.
But…
Apparently, someone died because of me.
He was hit by a buckle from my vehicle.
Please come down and talk.
I'm sorry.
I'm so very sorry.
But I can't bear
the outcome of my actions.
I have no courage to live. My goodness.
I just wanted to live diligently.
I don't know how this happened.
Dad!
What are you doing up here? I was worried.
Well,
I needed to have a conversation.
I came here to get some fresh air.
You should've put on a jacket.
What if you catch a cold?
Let's go.
See you around.
SEOUL METROPOLITAN POLICE
COMMISSIONER GENERAL
PYO MYUNGHAK
How nice.
I'm Commissioner General Kim Junghak.
The government has assigned
Deputy Commissioner Pyo Myunghak
as the new Commissioner General.
The new Commissioner General
has worked in the police force
for about 30 years
as Chief of Eunseong Police Station
in Daejeon
and Captain of the Investigation Unit
in Seoul.
He's an excellent expert
in police investigation.
Someone cut the belt?
Is there anyone you're suspicious of?
Someone who'd do that to you.
No, not at all. That means…
I didn't kill someone, right?
We're still investigating,
but there's a possibility of a crime.
Oh, my. Thank God.
Mr. Nam Jaehoon,
where was the trailer loaded?
A used car dealership in Incheon.
Did you stop anywhere?
Uh, I had to unload the trailer
the next day,
so I stopped by a rest area
and slept there.
I hit the road early morning.
Where was the rest area?
- Sangsan Rest Area.
Did anything happen there?
Nothing in particular…
Could it be that punk?
A man got in a car that was
on the trailer, so I was startled.
Hey! Hey, you!
Who are you? Get out, you punk!
Get out! What do you think you're doing?
Will you take responsibility
if the car gets damaged? Huh?
Don't be so dramatic.
I was just taking a look.
You crazy bastard! For goodness' sake.
Do you think you're
at a car dealership? Huh?
How dare you?
Did you just hit me?
- Yes, I did.
- Hit me more. Hit me!
We got into a little fight.
Mr. Cho Ikhwan?
Who are you?
Mr. Cho Ikhwan, where were you
around 11 p.m. on the 15th?
It really wasn't me.
Why would I do such a thing?
You got in a car that was on a trailer.
You had a go with the driver.
That only happened
because that punk ran his mouth.
Tell us where you were
around 11 p.m. that night.
I think I was in the dormitory.
At 11:40 p.m., this was caught
on the dormitory surveillance camera.
Mr. Cho Ikhwan, isn't that you?
You went out then
and returned around 4 a.m.
Mr. Cho, tell us honestly.
After you left the dormitory,
where did you go and what did you do?
Mr. Cho Ikhwan, tell us.
I…
He was with me!
We went out for a drive.
He said he'd take me to the sea
since he got a new car.
For goodness' sake, are you insane?
How could you date such a lunatic?
What was that?
A lunatic?
- Eunju.
- Yes?
Tell me whenever you feel frustrated.
Let's go see the sea again.
Really?
- Let's go to the East Sea next.
- Okay.
Hey, there's something
I wanted to ask you.
Do I like you?
Don't be ridiculous.
Eunju.
All right.
Okay. We verified your claim.
Thank you for your cooperation.
- By the way…
- Yes?
…while we were doing that--
Oh, sure. What happened?
I saw a suspicious man.
Suspicious?
- Eunju.
- Yes?
I can promise you this.
I'll help you cross all obstacles
with this car.
Ikhwan.
A cutter?
Yes. It looked like long scissors.
- A bolt cutter.
- A bolt-- Yes, that thing.
Were there any other characteristics?
He was a man of average height
wearing a black jacket and a green hat.
That's right. It was green.
Are you certain it was green?
Yes.
Did you see him again afterward?
A moment later,
he went that way.
What's that?
The Korea Transportation Safety Authority
built a rest area to prevent accidents.
- It's free for all truck drivers.
- I see.
Do all truck drivers fill out
this entry register here?
It isn't mandatory,
but we use it to get a count.
I ask them to fill it out,
but many drivers can't be bothered.
We'd like to check
the surveillance camera.
That one? It's broken.
No one checks it, so we never fixed it.
May we check inside?
I can't let you do that.
Some people walk around naked
since there's a bath.
I'll check the inside.
Okay then. I'll look over this.
Thank you.
Come on.
- For goodness' sake.
- Come on.
I told you to do that.
That's just wrong.
- Hey.
- Hurry up.
It's your turn.
Excuse me.
Are there no keys for these lockers?
There's no such thing.
What is there to steal?
The locker room had no keys.
It seems like the culprit took the keys
and committed the crime
while Nam Jaehoon was taking a shower.
He formatted the dashcam then.
- Then he put the keys back?
- Yes.
It must be a personal grudge,
but Mr. Nam doesn't know anyone
who wore a green hat.
He can't think of anyone either.
Since he used the truck lounge,
he must be a fellow truck driver.
We can't make a hasty conclusion
since anyone can enter the lounge.
Were there surveillance cameras?
The one near the entrance was broken.
Where will we find clues then?
If he used the lounge,
someone must remember him.
A black jacket and a green hat.
Some people filled out the entry register.
We'll meet them first.
We'll also check surveillance cameras
in the rest area for a green hat.
Tomorrow will be a busy day.
Jungwook has adjusted
to the company very quickly.
He takes after you,
so he has command over people too.
Gosh, I know my own son.
You don't need to sugarcoat things.
Just make sure he works quietly
without causing any trouble.
Of course. Don't worry.
- Excuse me, I need to use the restroom.
- Okay.
Young man, take good care of your pipe.
- Myunghak.
- Yes?
I found this
on Jaeyoung's desk.
LATE-NIGHT DRIVER HITS NEWLYWEDS
RESULTING IN THEIR DEATH
I know.
Jungwook and I received it too.
What kind of jerk sent this
to the Commissioner General?
What happened in Daejeon
should be smoothed over once again.
There was Jaeyoung's accident too.
I don't think this will be the end of it.
Do you mean
that the one who sent this…
This punk even entered
the Seoul Metropolitan Police.
There's a possibility
that he is in the police force.
Didn't the dead girl have family?
Her husband received surgery
and moved to the US.
He passed away not too long after.
Her father--
- That's right. Lee Jungsub.
- Yes.
He was a police officer too.
And he's close to Jung Chaeman.
What annoys me the most is…
that Cha Yeonho is
currently in Jung Chaeman's team.
Did the two of them find something out?
Otherwise, why would the two of them
be together?
I'll give Jaeyoung's case to Jung Chaeman.
Why would you do that?
Keeping the suspicious ones nearby
puts me at ease.
The investigation reports will
make it easy to find out where he went.
If he does anything suspicious,
I'll be able to sack him easily.
So you won't have to lift a finger.
You don't disappoint.
Myunghak, leave the cleanup to me.
You are now a man of prominence,
so you shouldn't get your hands dirty.
The final blow shall be carried out by me,
Jaeyoung's father.
That way.
Excuse me. You must be checking the tires.
Yes.
I moved the tires and put air into them.
I think the pressure is too high.
If the tires are overinflated,
they can burst due to road heat.
I see. You're very thorough.
If every driver is like you,
there won't be any traffic accidents.
You look quite young.
You must've started working early.
I followed my father's footsteps
and got into this business.
My father is a freight driver too.
I always followed him as a kid.
Same here.
- It's nice to meet you.
- Yes.
You make a good first impression.
You're so friendly,
like I've met you somewhere.
I get that a lot.
Did you have something to say to me?
You came to the lounge on the 15th.
Did you see anyone in a green hat?
Perhaps he was carrying a bolt cutter.
I'm not sure.
Both hats and bolt cutters
are common here.
Do you know Nam Jaehoon by any chance?
Well, I don't recognize the name.
Here's a photo.
- What? He…
- Do you know him?
I saw him at the lounge that day.
That's right. You have a good memory.
A fight broke out in the lounge that day.
A fight? Was Nam Jaehoon involved?
Yes. It wasn't anything serious.
Excuse me. You're splashing
shampoo. Please be careful.
Goodness gracious. These things happen.
That's no way for a youngster to talk.
You won't get treated
as an adult if you behave that way.
What? What did you say, you punk?
- What?
- "What"? For goodness' sake.
Don't splash shampoo, okay?
You're so petty
despite your rough looks.
Wash up quietly, okay?
Come to think of it,
he was wearing a green hat.
What? Did you see his face?
- Was it someone you know?
- No.
But I saw him at the lounge earlier today.
Today?
Do you remember the seolleongtang place
we often went to in Daejeon?
The owner always added
a piece of ox knee as a service.
But I ate yours since you didn't like it.
I heard about your promotion.
Congratulations.
I somehow ended up reaching this position.
Thank you.
I'm on duty.
You haven't changed.
I've always thought you were difficult.
How should I put it?
You're always very sharp like a knife.
It's a must for a police officer.
There are many things to cut.
Are you still mad at me?
I thought I cleared up
our misunderstanding.
Did you call me over
to talk about the past?
Okay then.
- What is it?
- Take over a case.
It's a traffic accident,
but it could be murder.
Why should I?
Why?
It's your job to investigate.
This is your specialty, isn't it?
Why? Is there a reason you can't do it?
ROUTE ONE TRAFFIC ACCIDENT
FROM SEOUL TO DAEJEON
YANG JAEYOUNG'S CAR
BEFORE AND AFTER THE ACCIDENT
Yes, I did visit the lounge that day.
But around 4 a.m.,
I was sleeping in the lounge.
I see.
Okay. Thank you for your cooperation.
By the way, is this about
the car carrier trailer accident?
I know Jaehoon.
Is that so?
Did someone cut the belt on purpose?
Nothing has been confirmed yet.
How strange.
What do you mean?
A few months ago, a friend of mine
caused a car carrier trailer accident.
He said the accident occurred
even though he had fastened the belt
and secured the parking brake.
He felt so victimized.
When he tried to check,
the dashcam was turned off.
Please excuse me.
Yes, Detective Woo.
When did it occur?
Let me think.
I'm checking the lounge
with Mr. Seo Dongwoo.
Okay.
I'll send Inspector Cha there.
He might've left the lounge,
so tell Hyunkyung to check the cameras.
- Okay.
- All right.
What happened?
You need to go to the lounge. Someone saw
the suspect in a green hat there.
Okay.
Nam Jaehoon.
That's right.
That did happen during the shower.
- What about it?
- Do you know him?
- Yes.
- Who is he? Do you have a photo?
That way.
Han Kyungsoo.
Mr. Han Kyungsoo.
It's you, right?
What are you doing here?
It's been a while.
You must remember me.
I don't think it has been a while.
I saw you at Jaeyoung's funeral.
You were there, right?
- How did Mr. Yang Jaeyoung--
- Did you come to see me?
Why?
No, it isn't like that--
Mr. Han Kyungsoo.
It wasn't an accident. Someone killed him.
A bastard in a black car.
Mister, what's wrong? Are you okay?
Lieutenant, I think
Inspector Cha found him.
He's at the parking lot.
Mr. Han Kyungsoo, are you okay?
Did you cause Jaeyoung's accident?
What do you mean?
Did you kill Jaeyoung?
- What do you mean by that?
- No, don't touch me.
Don't come near me.
Listen.
I'm different from Jaeyoung.
I won't become a victim so easily!
Han Kyungsoo!
Han Kyungsoo, stop!
Inspector Cha, he's the suspect
we were looking for.
The man who was with you. Get in!
For goodness' sake!
Gosh! Why did he appear? Why?
Is Han Kyungsoo a suspect?
Wasn't that why
the two of you were together?
No.
Uh-- Then why were you two…
Do you know him?
We're not close, but I know him.
Let's talk later.
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
Do you want to get out?
No, there's no time for that.
There it is.
License plate, 5428.5428.
Pull over, 5428.
- Hey, Hyunkyung.
- Lieutenant, where are you?
We're close to getting him.
- It's dangerous. Get out of there.
- What?
Someone cut the ratchet buckle
of the trailer.
That trailer is the next target!
What?
What? What's going on?
What's going on?
Why isn't the brake working?
Damn it!
Stop the car, 5428.
Stop, 5428. Pull over.
It isn't working.
What?
Damn it!
A wanted vehicle, 5428,
is passing Sangseon Interchange.
CRASH
What if there's another victim?
There's something that comes to mind.
Wasn't it your doing?
Do you think
the accident and the letter are connected?
Is the investigation difficult
or are personal feelings clouding
your judgments?
I need money.
It's either I get killed like Jaeyoung
or die hungry.
Nothing can stop me.
We'll teach them not to act up.
The two are in the same location.
Father, please pick up the phone!
PEOPLE OF THE POLICE STATION
Modern dramas and movies
often depict a used car dealer
who is involved in various crimes.
But in real life,
"illegal" used car dealers…
COMMISSIONER GENERAL
PYO MYUNGHAK
…are very few in number.
You know that, right?
There was a time when
scam deals and fraudulent reports
were pretty rampant
in used car dealerships.
However, tips on purchasing used cars
without getting scammed
have spread on social media.
Consumers are becoming smarter by the day,
and used car dealers
are actively revealing car records.
Such efforts continue to be made.
Perhaps that is the reason
that crimes involving used cars
are on the decline.
So, if you developed
prejudices regarding
the used car business by any chance,
please set aside your misunderstanding.
Recently, big companies in Korea
have entered the used car industry.
There's an expectation
for more transparency in the market.
Now, the breeding ground of crimes
you see in TV series
will be gone for good.
The police will be with you
along the journey.
Translated by Park Dong-joo
Ripped by WEISSACHsubs