CRASH
ALL CHARACTERS, LOCATIONS,
ORGANIZATIONS, EVENTS,
GROUPS, AND BACKGROUNDS
IN THIS WORK ARE FICTIONAL
Under the pretext
of ensuring safety for our citizens,
I failed to educate my son properly.
This is the result of my unrighteousness.
Please say a few more words.
Commissioner General.
- Please comment on this.
- How will you take responsibility?
Where are you going?
Why are you--
You are…
Pyo Myunghak.
If you try anything funny,
you'll end up
at the bottom of a river with me.
Lieutenant.
- Commissioner General Pyo was kidnapped.
- What? Kidnapped?
His vehicle is missing.
Stop the car right this instant.
Are you out of your mind?
- If we get into an accident--
- Your phone.
- Give me your phone.
- Hey! Okay.
- Did we identify the kidnapper?
- Not yet.
Attention. It's an emergency.
Put out an APB for the vehicle
and check all the traffic cameras.
Why are you doing this?
Why?
Do you really not know?
I explained myself
at the press conference.
I knew nothing of this.
So you didn't know?
While your son reached that state,
you had no idea, huh?
I wouldn't have left him in that state,
had I known.
How may I help you?
Well, the patient who was here…
She passed away two days ago.
Listen.
I have no idea why you're doing this,
but stop the car.
If you stop here,
I'll pretend this never happened.
You shouldn't do that.
Listen. Come on.
JUNG CHAEMAN
My goodness.
- Inspector Cha.
- Mr. Lee Jungsub abducted Pyo Myunghak.
He did it with Pyo Myunghak's car.
The police put out an APB.
His phone is still on,
so locate it and report to me.
- Yes, sir.
- Inspector Cha, keep calling him.
- He might answer your call.
- Yes, sir.
What exactly do you want from me?
This won't solve a thing.
It doesn't change anything.
It's all in the past, no?
Forget about the past
and focus on the future.
How much longer will you be
hung up on the past?
"Forget about the past"?
Sure. I wanted to forget about it too.
However,
you don't have the right to say that.
Even if everyone in the world
forgot about it,
you shouldn't.
Someone like you
shouldn't be in that position.
No. Someone like you shouldn't be alive.
Regarding your wrongdoings,
you have no hint of remorse or reflection.
You deserve to die!
Where on earth is he?
MIN SOHEE
Captain, they're passing Gahan Interchange
on the outer ring road.
Okay.
Jungsub…
CHA YEONHO
- Sir.
- Yeonho.
I'll take Pyo Myunghak with me.
We must get rid of him
so that his son
will get the punishment he deserves.
Sir, please don't do that.
Please leave it to me.
- I'll catch Pyo Myunghak.
- No.
I should've done it sooner
before Minsung made such a decision.
Yeonho.
You uncovered the truth
behind Hyunsoo's wrongful death.
- Thank you.
- Sir.
Listen, I have evidence.
I won't fall for such a trick.
I'm serious.
If I died, you'd never find the report.
- Sir?
- Let go!
Sir!
Damn it. Let go!
My goodness! Help! Please save me!
Jungsub, come to your senses!
Here!
Jungsub, stop the car!
Jungsub, come to your senses!
Stop the car!
Please!
Here! Over here!
Come on!
No!
Come on, stop!
- Jungsub.
- Let go of me!
Give me the evidence.
What evidence?
Evidence that your son killed my daughter.
Of course, there's no such thing.
- You little…
- Jungsub.
- Let go.
- Calm down.
- I'll kill this bastard with my own hands.
- Please.
Let go of me!
- Let go!
- Jungsub.
- How-- How could you!
- Please!
Here.
Geez, you sure took your time.
Get rid of him.
I'm fine, so get rid of him.
My goodness.
I survived thanks to you.
Thanks, Chaeman.
Hey, I need someone to drive.
- Hey, someone drive.
- Yes, sir.
CRASH
EPISODE 11
Why did you do that?
I wanted to fulfill my fatherly duty
one last time.
You may get mitigation of sentence,
but it'll be hard
to avoid a prison sentence.
I'm well aware.
Do you regret it?
Yes, I regret--
that I hesitated.
I believed him when he said
that he had evidence.
There's no way he'd leave such a thing.
As you probably learned
from the press conference,
Pyo Myunghak will use any means
to evade responsibility.
I won't let that happen.
I feel like I've left you alone
in this difficult fight.
I'm sorry, Yeonho.
Enter.
What brings you here?
You couldn't be reached.
I'm here to pick you up.
Mr. Lee, a man in his 60s,
who attempted to kidnap and murder
Commissioner General Pyo Myunghak,
turned out to be the father of the victim
who was killed by
Commissioner General Pyo's son
during the Eundong Junction accident.
It was a premeditated crime that was…
What's up with the wheelchair?
What's that on his arm?
He's wearing a mask too.
There wasn't even an accident.
- He pleaded for leniency on the culprit.
- Leniency? How dare he.
The kidnapper
is a colleague who worked
in the police force with me
in the past.
I understand how devastated he must be
about losing his child.
So I ask for leniency from the judiciary.
In addition,
for the impartial investigation
of the case my son was involved in
regarding Ms. Lee Hyunsoo's death,
I'll transfer the case…
I'LL UNCOVER THE TRUTH
BEHIND MY SON'S CASE
…to the prosecution.
Stop it already.
How far will you take this?
The public opinion has shifted favorably.
People are praising you
for the leniency towards the kidnapper
and for transferring the case
to prosecution.
They're as good as dogs and cows.
What did Chairman Yang
give the prosecutor?
Oh, well…
It's a photo that was taken
on the day of the accident.
Hey, let's take a photo.
Yang Jaeyoung, that sneaky bastard,
had a photo like this.
Had I known, I would've coaxed
Chairman Yang.
I cut him off too hastily.
It'll be hard to deny the fact
that Jungwook was behind the wheel.
Are you saying that there isn't a way?
Of course not.
SEOUL CENTRAL DISTRICT COURT
Mr. Han Kyungsoo.
WITNESS
Is the one who drove
and killed Ms. Lee Hyunsoo
by running her over
Mr. Pyo Jungwook over there?
Yes.
When the accident occurred,
why did you say that you drove?
Jungwook…
No, to be more precise,
Jungwook's father made me do it.
He said he'd cover up the accident.
He was Chief of Eunseong Police Station.
Then why did you change your mind?
Had you kept quiet,
this case would've remained buried.
That day,
my friend killed someone.
I'm both a bystander
and a sympathizer who stayed quiet.
It's belated
but I wanted to atone for my crime.
That is…
the best I can do
for the deceased's family.
No further comments.
Attorney, you may begin.
Mr. Han.
Didn't you ask the suspect
for 300 million won?
I…
300 million won?
I did ask for money, but that was--
You requested 300 million won
for switching the driver.
But when the suspect refused,
you held a grudge
and set out to frame him!
Objection! The defendant's attorney--
No further comments.
Han Kyungsoo's testimony won't be enough.
We need direct evidence.
There might be evidence.
Listen, I have evidence.
- I won't fall for such a trick.
- Evidence?
I'm serious.
If I died, you'd never find the report.
He definitely mentioned a report.
- A report on the tire mark?
- That must be it.
Only that report disappeared
from Mr. Kim Minsung's house.
But it doesn't directly prove
that Pyo Jungwook is the culprit.
It only proves that Inspector Cha isn't.
Despite that, he secretly stole it.
The existence of the report
was the problem.
Had it been revealed,
I would've been considered innocent.
Then it would've reopened
the investigation.
If he took it to keep his sins hidden,
would he still have it?
Even if he still has it, there's no way
Pyo Myunghak would hand it over.
Hold on.
Perhaps the person who wrote the report.
So who's on the list of witnesses?
Professor Jin Changwook of NFS
who made the report of the tire mark.
He currently lives in the US.
JIN CHANGWOOK
What's there?
It's a report on the tire mark
found on Lee Hyunsoo's body.
It doesn't seem like--
Retrieve it right away. Now!
Yes, sir.
TRAFFIC ACCIDENT ANALYSIS REPORT
TIRE MARK ON THE VICTIM'S BODY
AND TIRE MARK OF SUSPECT'S TIRE
Is there something I don't know?
- Professor Jin Changwook?
- That's me.
Hello. I'm Lieutenant Min Sohee of TCI.
Nice to meet you.
- We'll help with your suitcase first.
- Oh, yes.
Thank you.
By the way,
will my testimony be any help?
Of course. I'm certain it'll help.
Hey, get out.
Hey, can't you drive properly?
- Hurry up and get out.
- How can you stop the car that way?
Hey. I said get out.
- Come on out!
- Hurry up, okay?
You punks messed with the wrong woman!
- Excuse me?
- You guys won't get paid today.
- Shall we get started?
- Yeah, sure.
Hey.
- Did you just push me?
- What are you going to do?
- You want to die?
- For goodness' sake.
What's wrong?
I'm Detective Woo
who flew from the US to eat LA galbi.
What's going on here?
Gosh, I'm still jet-lagged.
- What do you want?
- No.
- There was a misunderstanding.
- That's right.
- What misunderstanding?
- Well…
- I'm sorry.
- Get going then.
The Korean subway is convenient, right?
- It's faster than a car.
- Right.
- It's this way.
- Okay.
COURT AND PROSECUTOR'S OFFICE
Your Honor.
I'd like to call Commissioner General
Pyo Myunghak as a witness.
He isn't on the list of witnesses.
Right.
But being the defendant's father,
he is deeply involved in this case.
Does the defendant's attorney agree?
Yes, Your Honor.
Okay then.
Witness, come forward.
Commissioner General.
If the report will be revealed anyway,
let's get a jump on them.
What do you mean?
Don't let them reveal it.
You should reveal it yourself.
Are you telling me
to reveal the report first?
The Seoul Commissioner General
who's merciless, even to his own son.
Isn't it the biggest virtue citizens seek
in a high-ranking official?
You asked to be a witness
because you had something to say
about the case.
That's right.
What is it?
A few days ago,
I received this anonymously.
It's a National Forensic Service report.
It's an analysis report of the tire mark
on the victim, Lee Hyunsoo's body.
According to the report,
the tire mark that was left
on the victim's body
doesn't match the tires
of the suspect, Cha Yeonho's car.
You said you received it
anonymously a few days ago.
Have you ever received this report before?
No.
Why wasn't this report revealed
at the time of the accident?
I'm curious about that too.
And there's one more thing.
In the report, the tires
that left marks on the victim's body
have been identified.
But they are…
the same kind as the ones of my car
which was driven by my son
at the time of the accident.
Do you know that this is evidence
against the defendant, your son?
Yes, I do.
However,
before I'm someone's father,
I'm an officer who is in charge
of citizens' safety.
That's the reason why
I submitted this report.
Please calm down.
- Defendant.
- Please.
You are at court!
Be respectful.
I'm sorry.
It's just that this trial is so touching.
It really moved my heart. Wow.
Your Honor
and prosecutor…
I'll just reveal everything.
Jungwook.
Hey.
What is he doing? Is he driving?
What are you doing? You bastard!
Please…
You crazy bastard!
Be quiet.
I said be quiet!
An accident? What accident?
I was driving your car
and ended up running someone over.
Damn it. Hey, listen to me carefully.
From this moment on,
you guys are just witnesses.
You guys saw her by chance.
You were driving out of curiosity.
But you saw an accident
so you made a report.
Don't say anything else.
I'll take care of the rest.
It was my father
who ordered us to act like witnesses.
It was my father who said
he'd take care of the rest.
It was my father who hid
the National Forensic Service report.
Your Honor,
my son is not in his right mind.
- Being a drug addict, he's currently--
- Sit down.
Gosh, seriously. Father, it's all over!
Someone like you shouldn't be
Commissioner General.
You deserted your own child
in order to save yourself!
- Be quiet!
- Shut your mouth.
No, I'll go on.
I wouldn't have come this far
if it weren't for my father.
I'm a victim too.
I was a minor at the time.
What does a child know?
Don't you agree? Huh?
I'll get a reduced sentence, right?
Here she comes.
She's here.
Today's trial ascertained
the fact that Commissioner General Pyo
tampered with evidence in the past.
That day, the person
who took the report on the tire mark
was Mr. Pyo Myunghak,
who's sitting behind me.
TEN YEARS AGO
The suspect's car
didn't run over the victim.
We should look into the car
that was at the scene.
We didn't check the tires of that car.
WITNESSES
Are you going somewhere?
The office is a bit of a mess, right?
I'll be moving to the US.
Is that so?
That's nice.
I learned later that he was the chief.
I wondered why the chief
of a police station came himself.
After further investigation
on the witness,
Mr. Pyo Jungwook,
Commissioner General Pyo's son,
and after securing evidence,
we'll indict Commissioner General Pyo
for tampering with evidence
and abuse of governmental power.
Was crucial evidence revealed today?
When will he resign?
No one knows what I had to do to get here.
No one knows.
I know fully well how you got there.
To cover up your wrongdoings,
you deserted your only son in cold blood.
Your son is right.
Someone like you
shouldn't be in that position.
You little bastard, you're all talk.
- Hey, nothing is over yet.
- No.
It's over for you.
To reduce his sentence,
Pyo Jungwook will put the blame on you.
I'm relieved
that your son takes after you.
I'm sorry. But I'm telling the truth.
A high schooler didn't know any better.
I just did what my father told me to do.
I switched the driver
because my father told me to do so.
That man is less than human!
That man ruined my life!
That man shouldn't be
Commissioner General!
Where did this letter come from?
SENIOR SUPERINTENDENT GENERAL
SHIN SOJUNG
Well, the sender seems to be an insider,
but we don't know who it is yet.
You shouldn't stir up a hornet's nest.
- What do you mean?
- I mean, I'm sure you understand.
If it reaches Commissioner General,
he'll complain about
not keeping people in check.
Inspection won't go smoothly.
Even without this,
Pyo Myunghak will be cut off anyway.
I see why every year
Seoul Metropolitan Police receives
the lowest score in integrity
among government offices.
Thoroughly check Commissioner General's
corruption specified in the letter.
If it turns out to be true,
we'll investigate.
COMMISSIONER GENERAL
PYO MYUNGHAK
Come in.
What's this?
We're from the inspection office.
We received a letter.
A letter? From whom?
Let's begin.
How dare you! Who do you think you are?
I apologize, sir.
Commissioner General approved of this.
No way.
Please excuse us for a second.
Let's step outside.
I never imagined
that you'd turn out like this.
So you want to cut off the tail
like a lizard, huh?
Don't be mistaken.
The inspection office
secured the information.
Do you think I'll go down alone?
Give it a go.
- What did you just say?
- Try all you want.
I'm not like you.
I'll show you how I turn a crisis
into an opportunity.
This morning,
Commissioner General Pyo
has been arrested and confined.
Nine hours after the request,
the court issued a warrant
due to the possibility
of evidence tampering.
Commissioner General
is suspected to have taken bribes
from Chairman Yang Seokchan
of YSC Constructions
for covering up bid rigging
and incidents of assault.
Commissioner General Pyo's misdeeds
were revealed from an anonymous letter
that came from someone
within the police force.
- According to the letter…
- Min Yonggun's guardian.
Yes.
Dad.
Dad. Dad.
Dad. It's me, Sohee.
- Sohee.
- Yes.
Dad, it's me. I'm here.
Dad, it's me.
- I'm sorry.
- What are you talking about?
I'm sorry.
Thank you, Dad.
Thank you.
I'm okay.
My goodness.
It's okay.
SEOUL CENTRAL DISTRICT COURT
Thank you.
Don't worry, sir.
The Department of Justice
wouldn't want to give a prison sentence
to the former commissioner general.
The law is made by people, after all.
Of course.
I will give my verdict.
The defendant, Pyo Jungwook,
murdered the victim, Lee Hyunsoo,
despite being aware that she was pregnant.
This is an aggravating factor
in the sentence.
In addition, the defendant, Pyo Jungwook,
was the culprit who hit Min Yonggun
and fled from an accident
on October 6, 2024.
After hitting Min Yonggun with his car
and causing serious injuries,
he fled the scene without attempting
to help the victim.
However, he admitted and confessed
to his crimes during the trial.
And as he was underage
at the time of the crime,
I give the following verdict.
You're working hard.
Let's take our time.
Wow.
You seem to be in a good mood.
You must be satisfied with the result.
Well, I guess you made
a big contribution, Jungwook.
You put your own father behind bars.
Let's have a meal together
when you get out.
Hold on. When will that be?
I sentence the defendant,
Pyo Jungwook, to 20 years of imprisonment.
I sentence the defendant, Pyo Myunghak,
to 12 years of imprisonment
and a fine of 1.5 billion won.
What do you think of the sentence?
- Do you plan to appeal?
- Please comment on this.
I sentence the defendant,
Yang Seokchan,
to ten years and six months
of imprisonment
for embezzlement, breach of trust,
bribery, and instigation of murder.
How is your health?
Is anything bothering you?
I'm okay.
Okay.
Please,
don't worry about me anymore.
I'll live well by any means.
I'll stand trial
and pay for my sins
so Hyunsoo wouldn't be ashamed of me.
Yes.
As you should.
You need to live.
Hyunsoo will be able to rest in peace now.
Director General Lee Taeju
has been promoted to Chief Superintendent.
Congratulations.
- Well done.
- Thank you, sir.
APPOINTMENT CEREMONY
Congratulations.
I thought you'd congratulate me.
Is it a cause for congratulations?
What brings you here?
I had some business
at the inspection office.
There's more to
the Commissioner General's corruption.
The unlicensed taxi case.
Why are you so surprised?
People might think you're to blame.
We should put an end
to the investigation into corruption.
Look forward to it.
CHIEF SUPERINTENDENT LEE TAEJU
This is Lee Taeju.
I have a report to make.
While working as an interim captain
of Namgang Police Station's TCI team,
I found a lot of things to report.
TCI WILL BE INTEGRATED INTO
OTHER INVESTIGATION DIVISIONS
The team got dissolved
instead of receiving an award.
This is utter nonsense.
Come on. They were let off lightly
since they made contributions.
In any case, they ended
Commissioner General's career.
What organization would welcome them?
Moreover, Captain Jung was on call.
Even so, this is wrong.
Captain Jung put so much effort into TCI.
What's this?
You used to hate them
for stealing manpower.
I did, but--
But still, this is wrong.
Why is Cha Yeonho
getting sent to an island?
What is this? Exile?
Exile is exactly what this is. Geez.
Gosh.
I want to turn it all
upside down.
Since there have been
many alarming crimes,
HQ wants to focus on investigations
that will bring public order.
It happened to be that way.
Captain Jung, you worked hard.
But reduced manpower in investigation
- may cause some cases to be abandoned.
- You know how it is.
An organization is like an organism,
so it adapts to new situations.
You know that.
I'll get going.
Everyone,
thank you for your hard work.
Gosh.
In any case,
Commissioner General Pyo is gone.
And the investigation officer--
Now, whom should I…
What?
CHIEF SUPERINTENDENT LEE TAEJU
What? Lee Taeju?
Yes. What? No.
He keeps saying
that we should have dinner sometime.
Is he your new connection?
No.
Lee Taeju?
I wondered when I'd leave this place.
Who knew it'd happen this way?
- Why? Are you relieved?
- Yes, I'm relieved.
I'm so relieved
that I feel disappointed.
- Lieutenant.
- Yes?
Why does this always happen to us?
We always work hard
and receive disciplinary action for it.
There's something wrong with the world.
Or maybe there's something wrong with us.
Try to look on the bright side.
It means we still have
a lot of work to do.
Captain, what will you do
with the plants on the rooftop?
I'll take the expensive ones.
As for the rest,
I'll leave them to you, Donggi.
Yes, sir.
I'll double their sizes
until you come back.
Captain, what will you do
during your three months off?
Who knows if it'll be three months
or go on indefinitely?
I'll think about it.
Inspector Cha must be troubled.
He's going to an island by himself.
TRAFFIC CRIME INVESTIGATION TEAM
What are you doing here alone?
I was just standing here.
Will you be okay?
It seemed like a very remote island.
I'm rather relieved.
I wanted to go away for a short while.
And I was feeling disappointed.
We'll continue to see each other around,
but only you…
Thank you for everything.
Thanks to you,
I was able to hold out until I got here.
Don't act like you'll never see me again.
Well,
I'd like to thank you too.
I wouldn't have gotten this far
without you.
I wouldn't have been able to catch
Pyo Jungwook, who hurt my dad.
Once a TCI member, always a TCI member.
Don't forget that.
Don't forget about my dad's kimchi either.
When your father is discharged,
I'll go pick him up.
Who knows when that'll be?
You'll come all the way here?
Whenever or wherever it may be,
I'll go and pick him up.
Really?
I'm seriously going to call you.
Yes. Please call me.
ONE YEAR LATER
HWAPYEONG ISLAND
I get that this is
a security center on an island,
but there are only four officers.
We alternate shifts as a team of two,
so we're always on call even after work.
It isn't like we get paid
for being on call.
Isn't this exploitation of labor?
- Stop the car for a second.
- What?
Why?
What about the cultivator?
I saw him drinking makgeolli earlier.
That old man's been drinking again.
Sir.
Sir, have you been drinking?
I just had a cup of makgeolli.
Why are you stopping me?
A farming machine isn't
subject to drunk-driving regulations.
While a farming machine isn't subject
to drunk-driving regulations,
you'll be punished by the traffic law
if you get into an accident.
I won't get into an accident!
I haven't been in one in 40 years.
Let me go.
No, sir.
- No, I'll get going.
- No, sir.
- No.
- Sir.
Leave this here and come get it later.
This never happened before.
What's up with the drunk-driving control?
- Please get off.
- I'll drive.
- You've been drinking.
A farming machine isn't subject
to the traffic law.
Come on.
What were you doing until this hour?
School ended hours ago.
Why do you care about what I do?
Why you little…
Hello.
Ever since we moved to this island
to open a resort, she doesn't listen.
- I see.
- All right.
What are you doing? How sentimental.
Come home early. Your dad gets worried.
Worried, my foot.
My dad doesn't have time for that.
It's about the resort.
After the divorce,
this resort is the only thing Dad has.
He's so busy
that he doesn't care about me.
If he wants to run it well,
he shouldn't fight with the locals.
He always shouts and fights with them.
He got a divorce
because of his quick temper.
Why does he fight with the locals?
Who knows? Something about paying money.
It's frustrating.
Mister, why don't we drink together?
I hid some alcohol the guests left behind.
I can't drink. I don't have
the enzyme that breaks down alcohol.
You don't have friends, do you?
I have friends.
Code Zero. Code Zero.
A traffic accident occurred
in front of Donggu Elementary School.
Requesting backup.
Sun 20, I received the report.
I'm on my way.
Come on out.
- Come on out, you crazy woman.
- Excuse me, sir.
- That won't break the window.
- Who are you?
Let's introduce each other at the station.
What is this crazy wench saying?
- Gosh, that hurts.
- Hey.
- It hurts!
- It hurts, right? That was my intention.
You admit to retaliatory driving, right?
You're under arrest.
You have the right to remain silent.
- You have the right to an attorney.
- I am one! Gosh, it hurts.
You must be proud.
I got a text message. Hold on.
Attention.
Cuff yourself.
Yes, ma'am.
We're meeting tomorrow, right?
No one is going to cancel, right?
It's tomorrow.
For goodness' sake.
See you tomorrow.
Starting first of next month,
we'll work with Korea Forest Service
to begin a crackdown on the illegal
harvest of greens and medicinal herbs.
So make sure you carry your permit.
And please spread the news
that the roots of the greens
shouldn't be pulled out.
- Village Chief.
- Yes?
- You had something to say.
- Yes.
The selection committee
members of the K-Tourism Islands
will come and look around the island.
So welcome them warmly
if you run into them.
Let me tell you this again.
If the island gets selected, we'll receive
ten billion won to develop the island.
Hello? Oh, you arrived.
I'll be right there.
Well,
I'll get going. Guests arrived.
We do all the work,
but someone else takes the profits.
Excuse me? Are you talking to me?
I mean, am I wrong?
You use all the water on the island.
Ever since resorts were built,
we don't have enough water
in the reservoir.
It isn't like you contribute money
for the development of the village.
I won't pay five million won, okay?
It's not only once or twice.
- Don't discriminate against the newcomers.
- What are you talking about?
It's thanks to us
that you're making a living on the island.
Before the resorts were built,
we cultivated and managed the island!
Did everyone else pay the fee?
- Yes!
- Did everyone pay?
All right.
Stop. That's enough.
Please calm down.
You can leave now.
- Geez.
- For goodness' sake.
- That little…
- Why is he so selfish?
Is he trying to pick a fight?
It looks tasty.
- Where are you going at this hour?
- A birthday party.
A birthday party? Whose birthday is it?
- A friend from school?
- Forget it.
- Sir, is it ready?
- Who?
- Almost ready. Okay.
- We're hungry.
- Please enjoy the food.
- Thank you.
- Did something happen?
- What?
Seunga hasn't come home.
She went out last night
to a friend's birthday party.
She isn't answering my calls.
- Goodness.
- Do you know her friend's name?
She said it was a friend from school,
but I didn't get the name.
- Where on earth is this brat?
- Did you check the ferry schedule?
- Perhaps she went to the land alone.
- I called the ferry terminal earlier.
They told me
that Seunga's name wasn't on the list.
Where is this brat?
Oh, right. You said
you were going to Seoul today.
Yes, but--
we should find your daughter first.
Excuse me.
- Do you know Seunga in 12th grade?
- No.
- Have you seen her around?
Did you see this student last night?
There aren't many places
kids can go to on this island.
Inspector Cha, there's poop. Watch out.
This is the place kids gather around
to drink and smoke.
The scenery is very nice.
It's the perfect place to drink.
What are those?
What are you doing? How sentimental.
Come home early. Your dad gets worried.
- Seunga's shoes.
- What?
Does that mean Seunga…
We don't know anything for sure yet.
Coast guards are looking for her too,
so let's just wait a little longer.
I thought everyone would be here,
but Inspector Cha is missing.
A high school girl went missing
on the island,
so it's an emergency.
A missing person case?
I thought it was a quiet village
without any crimes.
Investigation won't be easy
since they don't have many cameras.
He'll have to go everywhere.
It's manual labor.
Didn't the security center only have
- four officers?
- Four?
- Yes.
- It must be really hard to investigate.
- Donggi, eat up.
- Okay.
Four? Gosh, that's harsh.
- Inspector Cha!
Inspector Cha, you look good
in your uniform.
Thank you for coming a long way.
We can catch up later.
Let's find the girl first.
- Please come this way.
- Okay.
We checked with the ferry terminal.
She didn't leave the island.
We found Seunga's sneakers
on top of a cliff.
- And her cell phone?
- There's only one base station,
so it's useless to locate her cell phone.
What about CCTV?
There's a total
of six surveillance cameras.
Most of them are at the port and coast.
The cameras set up by residents themselves
need to be checked one by one.
Detective Woo will be able
to check the footage
by himself.
Bingo. I found her already.
It was taken around 9 p.m.
the day she disappeared.
Where is this?
It's near Jinmak Dock.
It's a path to Bigu Peak.
It's the route Seunga always takes.
- Lieutenant.
- Yes?
Remember those words?
The words the shaman said
at the time of the Kanghee Junction case.
- What did she say?
- Well,
she said that dark clouds
loomed over Inspector Cha,
and people who stayed by his side
would get struck by lightning.
Oh, right.
I think that shaman was right.
Everywhere Inspector Cha goes,
incidents and accidents occur.
Geez. Nonsense.
This island was known
to lack three things.
Thieves, crimes, and pollution.
But Inspector Cha arrived on the island
and broke the rules.
The dark clouds. It was his energy.
My goodness.
Look! Here come the dark clouds!
- Over here.
- That startled me.
What is it?
Inspector Cha, hold on.
Here.
What? Isn't this a piece of a car bumper?
Donggi, what do you think
the car model is?
I can't tell from this alone.
Worried, my foot.
My dad doesn't have time for that.
Inspector Cha, what is that?
It's from Seunga's phone.
Does that mean--
I think an accident occurred on this road.
CRASH
SPECIAL APPEARANCE
BY PARK JIYOUNG
She headed out to attend
a friend's birthday party.
I've seen her with a man.
It might be a murder case.
Murder, my foot.
That will never happen on this island!
Seunga's shoes were discovered
on Bigu Peak Cliff
near the end of the island.
Someone intentionally put
Seunga's shoes at a different location.
- What about the traces at the scene?
- A piece of a silver bumper.
I can't believe this!
Who are you branding as a criminal?
She committed suicide.
Why do you keep suspecting the villagers?
How dare you cause a ruckus
at such a crucial moment?
Only one solution remains.
We must find Seunga.
Translated by Park Dong-joo
Ripped by WEISSACHsuss