Son, have you studied
for your exams?
-You have to write well, okay?
-Okay mom!
If you write your exams well,
then I would get you a big cake.
We'll cut your cake along
with your friends in the evening.
-Okay?
-Happy birthday, dude.
-Give chocolates to your friends.
--Thank you!
-Happy birthday, dude.
-Thank you Harish.
-One more chocolate for me, dude.
-The bus is here.
Give chocolates to your friends
in the bus. Okay?
Okay, mom!
Get in carefully.
-Bye!
Mom, bye!
-Bye.
Bye.
-Bye!
"Happy birthday to you"
Pour some more Sambar.
Don’t stand there.
Come here.
Sir, please buy one doll.
My baby is crying in hunger.
Brother, please buy one doll.
How much is it?
-It is 10 rupees.
-Here, give it.
Hey!
The baby!
The baby is down there!
Hey!
Hey, run!
Hey kids, get down and run.
Run now!
Near Morampudi junction,
Near Rajahmundry,
there was an explosion due
to poisonous gases,
leaked from the sewage stagnant
in the manhole.
I strongly condemn this on behalf
of the opposition.
This is an unexpected accident.
Government has announced compensation,
to the families of those who have died.
I severely condemn the opposite
parties, who are trying to do
politics through this accident.
Hyderabad High Court has ordered this
case to be handed over to the CBI.
The convention of Muthamizh
Munnetram Party is a huge success.
Members of the party and public,
from all parts of area.
have extended their tremendous
support to this convention.
The Chief Minister, Ms. Dhatchayani
has said that, in spite of the many
sabotages around her, the support
of the people has made her happy.
Hail! CM!
CM’s convoy has started.
Stop all the public and tighten
the barricades.
Hail! CM Dhatchayani!
Get back!
Hey! Go back!
Move aside! Move aside!
Move away!
Hey!
It’s the CM!
Hail! CM Dhatchayani!
Hey! Move aside.
Move aside I say!
Come on! Come on!
Move away, it is the CM.
-Come on! one minute!
Sir? It is the ambulance.
-What are you doing?
Go on.
Go fast.
Did we block the road for
the ambulance?
Yes the ambulance can go only
if the traffic is blocked.
It is the CM.
-But that is a life.
Hey?
-Sir, it is a small girl.
She is covered in blood.
-So what?
How dare you stop CM’s vehicle?
Hail! CM Dhatchayani!
Tell me,
will you stop the CM’s
vehicle for that?
No ma’am. I am sorry.
You must stop like that.
CM is not important than people.
Will you not check for emergency
vehicles, before blocking the road?
Sorry madam.
Update me with the condition
of the girl in the ambulance.
Okay ma’am.
Shiva?
Yes ma’am, Constable Shiva.
Sakinetipalli Police Station.
Good job Shiva!
What you did is right.
You and I, we all are here for
the people.
If they are in trouble,
if there is benefit for everyone,
then don’t mind even the CM
or the PM.
Always stand bravely like this.
Good!
(RAP)
“Khaki is the symbol of safety
and security”
“Even when not in uniform,
you can feel its power”
“Police duty prevails round
the clock”
“If you disturb the public,
they will break your kneecaps”
“No matter who they are”
“Do not touch the police”
“Because you will not be spared”
“People everywhere praise
the Police”
“And that is the appeal of
this job”
“Even if the power and post
changes”
“Our happiness will never change”
“We are the hope of the people”
“We are the Supermen,
the Policemen”
“When someone calls for help”
“We will stand for them
all the time”
“The corrupt rowdies and thugs”
“They run when they see
the police coming”
“None of us have family time here”
“Because our first wife is always
thus uniform”
“This happens to every policeman”
“Even when we face troubles
we do our duty”
(RAP)
Oh my!
Oh God!
-Hey, leave my hand.
I shall get up myself.
It is paining.
Oh no! See if someone is coming.
Sorry! Sorry!
What sorry?
No, a lady driver and just now
she is learning to drive.
So sorry.
-Ladies can do anything is it?
Brother, do you know what I would
have done, if I was in your place?
What would you have done?
I would have said,
It's okay, it happens.
Hey!
If I say, there is scratch on my car,
you have to pay money, can you pay now?
You can’t right?
Then what?
Now get going.
What is there to stare here?
Go away.
Well said baby.
What is this baby?
How many times to tell you,
not to release the clutch suddenly?
There was too much of traffic,
so I was a little confused.
Do you expect to announce
a national holiday, when you drive?
Start the car.
-Yeah.
Oh god!
What now?
I was asked to stop.
Who said that?
-Ah…
Hmm.
Hi!
Thanks madam.
Don’t call me madam.
Then?
Just Julie.
That is very important now.
-Thanks, Julie!
You are sitting like you own
this car?
Get out of the car.
What did I do?
I lifted my hand.
She stopped and I got in.
That’s it.
Don’t act too smart.
I am just teaching her to
apply brakes.
Get down from the car, now.
Is it?
Also teach her how to give
a lift.
What do you say, Julie?
Come on let’s go.
Look to your right.
-Hmm.
Hey!
Lunch box.
What is the special?
-Tamarind rice.
-Stay away from that.
-Is this fresh or old?
-Keep it down.
-Please I want to eat it.
-Don’t touch it.
I am telling you right?
Can’t you understand?
I haven’t eaten anything
since night.
Hey give me that.
Please listen to me.
Why aren’t you listening?
What are you doing?
-Please!
No, she is teaching you to drive,
when there is an argument in the car.
You look ahead and drive.
You keep driving.
-Will you not call me?
Won’t you?
-Wait, what is your problem?
My problem?
When did you promise to come
back from your hometown?
They told it was going to be
for a day.
But CM commanded me to stay
over there.
Are you a big shot, if the CM
appreciated you?
Will you forget me?
-Hey! Take your hand off me.
-Should I apply brake or the clutch?
-You do know the work of a cop.
But I did call, someone else spoke.
I don’t know all that.
-Oh!
Are you both lovebirds?
We are not lovers Julie.
Oh!
-Just friends.
Okay.
-You look ahead and drive.
Careful and be steady.
-Today’s class is over.
Keep aside! Put the indicator!
-That’s it.
Okay, okay!
Be on left!
Yes, I am!
Yes, yes! Stop the car!
Your class is over, you can go.
There is still half an hour
left, baby.
No it is enough for now.
Will you teach me the rest,
tomorrow?
Tomorrow I am off.
-Why?
A prospective groom is coming
to see me tomorrow. -Hey!
You didn’t tell me.
-Baby!
Congratulations.
Who is that?
Yeah, it is me.
Prem?
Our school senior?
Driving school Prem?
Yeah.
Oh my!
My parents were pestering me
about marriage, so I went there.
And now he is torturing me
about love.
Oh my god!
Did you tell about our love?
So what?
I don’t have any problem
with that.
What is the problem for him?
It is a problem for us.
Why didn’t you slap him hard?
Like this…
Revathi was in love with Karthik.
But later she understood love of Mohan,
and didn’t they live happily ever after?
What?
Karthik will die in that film,
but this fellow is still alive.
It’s okay.
Hey! What is he talking?
He is talking about the movie,
Mouna Raagam.
He is planning to come
and talk with my parents.
My dad knows him well.
Please, you come and talk
before he does.
Hey, no way.
You are senseless and so is he.
The dates for my SI exams
have been announced.
I shall write that and then come.
You wait for me.
What?
I should wait for you?
What do you think about me?
First you asked me to wait,
till you got a job.
Then you asked me to wait
till you were posted.
Now till you become an SI.
I cannot wait till you become
the President of India.
Hey!
There is no problem in me
coming and talking.
But you do know about your father.
If I come and talk to him,
He will blabber about property,
status and caste. -Hey!
Are you going to marry my father?
It is me, right?
I am telling you now.
Tomorrow you come with your family to my
house, and ask for my hand in marriage.
Please!
Sir?
Hi Shiva! When did you come?
Just now.
You stopped the CM’s convoy is it?
Your name is in the newspapers.
You have become very famous.
That was nothing sir.
-Super.
I was just making way for an ambulance,
they blew everything out of proportion.
SI sir has asked you to come
and meet him.
Hmm. I thought so.
What is he going to say?
I sent you to escort the CM’s convoy,
And how dare you stop them?
Huh? I will hit you.
Hey!
I sent you to escort the CM’s
convoy,
And how dare you stop them?
The officers appreciated
you there,
but they have sent me a memo asking
about my inability to run a station.
Guys like this become police
through some quota,
without actually knowing
the nature of the job.
Then they cause too much trouble
for us.
Hey!
If I get any more complaints
like this,
I will suspend you.
Get lost!
Hey stop!
Is this the time to report to
the station?
I am going to write today as
an off for you.
Also I want an off tomorrow sir.
-Why?
My uncle is in a serious condition.
Serious?
It is pretty serious.
Yeah.
Not only just three days,
but we have to celebrate
this occasion every day.
Well said.
When our CM appreciated my son
do you know how happy I was?
That is why we are celebrating
for these three days.
Is that right or wrong?
Yes, thank you brother.
Mom, brother is here.
Everyone are jealous of you.
Every evil eye should be
warded off.
They should have published
your photo as well.
People all over are talking, you stopped
CM’s convoy, made way for an ambulance.
But that newspaper didn’t even
publish your photo.
Next time I will ask them to
do that, okay?
Before that,
I have an important thing to say.
Ah! Where is dad?
Shiva, I am giving you so many kisses,
can’t you give your father one?
Dad?
Hey Shiva!
Look everyone, he is here.
I love you, dear.
Shiva I love you.
Dad I have to tell something
important. Come inside.
Why should you speak
important things here?
Celebration is going on.
Dad, it is very important. Why do
you keep talking with this guy?
-Come on.
-Ok, coming!
Hey!
My son serious.
-I am go! You don’t drink, waiting!
-Go! Go!
Wait!
-Okay, okay waiting!
-Waiting.
-No drinking.
Hm?
Dad!
Dad I don’t know if you will become angry,
when you hear what I am about to say.
You are not sure yourself right?
Then we shall talk tomorrow.
Dad, Dad, no.
-Ah?
I shall tell you.
Please sit down.
Ah…
What is the matter?
Hey!
Why are you here?
We elders are talking right?
So get lost.
Okay son, you carry on!
-Dad!
No dad, not you.
You please sit down.
Sit down!
The matter is,
I studied in Baburaj School
when I was small, right?
Sorry Chinna!
Fees was very less and that is
why I joined you there.
Dad! It is not about the fees.
Dad!
-Huh?
Don’t interrupt me in-between.
I am losing my flow.
Please listen to me.
You too interrupted me
and brought me here.
Did I tell you anything?
Alright, fine.
I.
Yes, you?
In my childhood.
Your childhood?
There is a friend.
Oh, is this about Revathi?
-Huh?
Revathi?
Revathi.
Who is that?
Dad he is in love with a girl
since his childhood.
Love?
-She is a good girl.
She is very pretty too.
She is teaching driving in
Prem Driving School.
Is it?
Just a minute dad.
Hey! Where are you going?
All that is fine Chinna,
But you wanted to say
something important right?
What is that?
What?
This is that girl.
Why were you so hesitant
about this?
She looks like a goddess.
Yes, mom!
Not that song,
but this one.
This is my song.
-Let me sing it, please?
-Okay!
“Hey come, to cherish my
lovable heart”
“Shall I show a preview of
my past and future?”
“Shall I paint the moment when
I saw you the first time?”
“Shall I tell my entire life
in this one song?”
“Hey come,
to cherish my lovable heart”
“Shall I show a preview of
my past and future?”
“Will I ever forget the hickeys
of my cheek?”
“Will I ever forget when you
tied me in your white ribbon”
“And took me away as your captive?”
“You came to my school”
“You took my pencil away”
“And you rewrote my entire life”
“You became my companion
in my college days”
“You became my paper during
my exams”
“With the strength of mother”
“And the affection of father”
“You are going to rule over
my life”
“You are my better half,
my dear Revathi”
“Hey come, come let’s cherish
the love of our hearts”
“Let’s show on screen,
our love model that we saw
“The skies are showering flowers”
“The earth is celebrating”
“The marriage that is
happening here”
“Four grandsons”
“Five granddaughters”
“They join hands and dance
with us”
“Can you see that vision now?”
“Hey come, come let’s cherish
the love of our hearts”
“Let’s show on screen,
our love model that we saw”
Keep it there.
Should we have to go in this vehicle?
-Hey! That is not right.
Don’t talk like that.
This is Goddess Annapoorni
that feeds us.
Well said.
You have spoken such wise word.
My brother-in-law came to see
your mother, in this same vehicle.
Keep all this together.
-Even then I was in same position.
Look even he is doing same thing.
I am very delighted.
Where are you all off to?
I am asking, right?
Where are you going?
Dad! Brother told you already.
Ramamurthy’s daughter,
school, love, marriage…
You too said that the song
was superb.
Hey! Was that you in that song?
Dad!
I even took you to all
the locations.
How many times have I told you,
not to say anything to me
when I am drunk?
It is all because of you.
Fine, tell me
where you are going now?
I told you that we are going to
meet the bride for Shiva.
Okay, I shall get ready…
ready and come.
Alright dad, come soon.
It’s already late.
But I have one doubt.
Where did you meet this girl?
Hey! Dharmaraja!
I will lock you up in jail.
-Okay....okay.
Sorry, I will get ready now.
Shiva!
Hey Revathi!
-What is this?
We are being humiliated
and you are just watching.
Listen, if you want me,
come with me now with the sari
you are wearing.
We will take good care of you.
Or if you say, I want my father
and I will listen to him,
then you better marry him.
Forget me.
Come on dad.
Hey! If you are a police you
would do anything is it?
You have caused a ruckus with
the bride’s family at the temple.
You have beaten everyone there.
I didn’t cause any problem sir.
That girl and I are in love.
I went to ask her hand in
marriage and that’s it.
Then why has Ramamurthy come to
the station, to file case against you?
You do know what would happen,
if I take up his complaint, right?
Listen,
I assured him that you would
never interfere in her life.
So he went away without filing
a case.
You said that I wouldn’t interfere?
Sir that is my personal issue.
Why are you interfering?
Personal issue?
Then shall I file an FIR and lock
you and your parents in jail?
Sir,
I know why you are supporting them.
What do you know?
Tell me, what do you know?
-Sir, just a moment, please.
First you go out.
Don’t you know how to talk
to a senior officer?
You go inside sir.
I shall deal with him later.
You come here.
Why are you so arrogant?
Already that fellow has
a grudge on you.
Even after knowing this, how
could you back answer him, Shiva?
Sir, ask him to treat
every complaint equally.
He treats the rich differently
from the poor.
But now he preaches justice.
Shiva!
Don’t make him to come out again.
Look, there is a missed call.
For you only.
Speak now.
Go and speak.
Hey!
Why do you keep calling me
again and again?
Why are you shouting like this?
I want to talk with you.
I am waiting near the phone booth
outside. Come now.
What you spoke yesterday
was more than enough.
I have lot of work now.
I cannot come, you can leave.
-Hey!
I have to talk about
an important thing. Please come.
Listen, already I have
too many issues.
I cannot come out now.
Don’t act too smart.
If you don’t come out now,
then I will come inside.
Alright, I will come.
Sir, I am going out for tea.
-Huh!
Fine, fine…
you can even have breakfast
if you want.
Sir?
I have come out of my house.
Come, let’s get married.
Hey!
You only told me to come with
the sari that I am wearing.
Now I have come with a Chudidhar.
Come, let’s get married.
Great, now you are talking nicely.
But yesterday you were
keeping mum.
Fine, there were elders around
and I accept that.
But what did my parents do?
You told me and that is why
I brought them.
But when they were humiliated…
I don’t know Shiva.
-Yeah,
without knowing anything only,
You came all dressed up like
a doll, isn’t it?
I came dressed up because I thought
your parents would be there.
Yeah, yeah!
They said that we were going
to the temple.
That is why I asked you to
come there and talk.
I really didn’t know
that they would be there.
Now what?
Because of what happened yesterday,
They have planned to get me
secretly married at Thirupathi.
You tie the sacred thread on
my neck now.
Hey!
Stop this nonsense!
Your father has given a complaint
on me and my family.
This SI is torturing me with that.
So I cannot come with you now.
We have no time to think, Shiva.
I cannot live with anybody else.
I don’t know what you would do.
But please come
and take me with you.
Or else, I shall decide my end.
Hey!
Alright,
I will do something by evening.
Okay?
Where is sir, coming from now?
I went to have some tea.
Hmm. Mohanraj?
-Sir?
You asked for leave to attend
some wedding right?
You can leave now.
That wedding is tomorrow sir.
You can take two days off.
Go now.
-Okay sir, thank you sir.
Shiva, you start the vehicle.
I am talking to you,
start the vehicle.
Go and start now.
Even now she came and met him.
Oh, that’s the matter!
Okay, Rangappa, I will look
into it!
Hey! Don’t get drunk
and embarrass us here.
Where were you all this while?
I went to the driving class.
Why?
-How are you? -I am fine,
you go inside. Go inside.
Take me to IG’s office.
S.I. called just now!
He just spoke to me about, Shiva!
We should be careful,
they are planning something!
I will take care of everything,
Mangalam. Tomorrow…
-What is it, dear? Oh!
-No…nothing.
Hey Bharani, come here.
It’s Revathi’s marriage
tomorrow at Tirupathi!
Shiva?
-Yes sir.
What are you doing?
Go and get the vehicle.
-Yes, sir!
Revathi… here.
Mom, I shall come out and eat.
No need, you can eat here.
What is happening here?
I am telling you right?
I you want anything,
just call me.
Hey Shiva, you didn’t do
any work the entire day.
So go, do the night shift at
the station. -Sir?
What man?
Since morning you were just roaming
around here and there, right?
Go now!
I don’t know what you would do.
Come and take me with you somehow.
Otherwise, I will meet my
own fate.
Shiva, did he let you go,
just now?
Yes, sir!
Sir! Did Revathi call you?
No, what happened?
She told me that her parents are
going to take her to Thirupathi,
and get her secretly married
there tomorrow.
-Really?
-Yes sir!
Mani sir, I am leaving.
-Yeah.
Bye Shiva.
There will be problems if I
go there.
Will you come with me?
We shall go and see what happened.
What question is this?
Come, let’s go.
But…
SI asked me to do the night duty.
Let’s tell him that we went
for night rounds. Come on.
-Really?
-Yes!
Okay I shall change my dress
and come. -Yeah come soon.
What do you lack Shiva?
You would get promoted as
SI soon.
Her father doesn’t want SI,
He wants cash and caste.
Is that fool going to build
a family with money?
Times are changing now Shiva.
It is enough if the guy and
the girl like each other.
Hey!! Hey!!
Shiva!
Sir, are you alright?
I hope you are not hurt?
Nothing happened.
Give me the match box.
Hey Raju, don’t cause any problem.
Come let’s go.
Get lost!
Hey! Hey, stop!
Don’t cause any problem.
Hey, listen to me!
Hey no, let go!
Listen to what I say.
Leave it!
-What did you say?
How dare you touch a police?
This doesn’t concern you.
Let go!
Hey!
Hey! I am warning you, come on.
Will you shoot me?
No Raju.
-A gun!
Raju listen to me.
-Hey! Leave the gun.
Put the gun down.
Who are you guys?
I am telling you, right?
Put the gun down.
Go now!
-Hey! Mani sir!
Hey!
I am telling you.
Hey, don’t shoot.
Hey I am from CBI.
Don’t move.
Put the gun down. Listen to me.
-Stand there.
-Listen to me. Don’t shoot.
-Hey! Don’t talk here, come to
the station. -Listen to me.
I am telling you right? Stand there.
-He is an accused, man.
-Listen to what I say. I am from CBI.
-What are you doing?
You can explain everything at station.
- I am telling you right?
Don’t shoot him.
Put the gun down.
Get up, what are you doing?
What are you doing?
-Put the gun down.
Hey….
Sir, at least you tell him sir.
Sir, please tell him.
Tell me.
Do you have a matchbox?
Ma’am, a call for you.
-Who is that?
Raju’s brother Ravi is online.
Tell me.
Madam! CBI has arrested Raju madam.
When?
Ask them to bring the side dish.
Hello? Yeah tell me?
What are you saying?
Brother, the police are here.
Escape now!
I asked only for a side dish.
I have been searching for you
for the past 44 hours.
For side dish?
Central Bureau of Investigation.
Okay!
Do you have a matchbox?
-No, bro!
Why do you come to a party
without a matchbox?
A matchbox…
Hmm, sorry!
Hey!
Do you have a matchbox?
A matchbox?
No, no!
Go to the place that I tell you.
Hey leave me.
Hey leave me I say.
Just now, madam!
One hour ago!
Which area?
Hello sir!
We need to go to hospital!
Hello, listen to what I say.
Hello, excuse me!
Hey! Just shut up!
He is shouting like a beggar and
says he is a CBI officer.
I am talking to you.
Listen to me.
-You call to SI!
-Hello Mani, why don’t you tell him?
-Let’s go to the hospital.
-Mani, I am a CBI officer.
Brother, please take care.
I shall call the SI.
-Okay, sir!
-Please listen to me.
-Listen to what I say.
-Hey shut your mouth.
Listen to me guys, please!
At least make a call to the number,
then you will know who I am.
He is lying… He is lying.
You shut your mouth.
He is giving you the number of the hotel,
where he goes to do his shady business.
You call to the number I give you.
-Hey, don’t confuse them.
The CM will pick up the call.
Listen to me, hello!
-Hello excuse me.
-Yeah tell me, I can hear you.
Shut your mouth.
Hey, you shut up man.
-You shut up.
You shut up.
Hello?
Sir, this is Shiva from
the station.
Yeah, tell me Shiva.
Sir, when Writer Mani
and I were in night rounds,
two drunken guys
came and dashed on our vehicle.
Is anybody injured?
No sir,
all are fine except for Mani sir.
He has a mild bruise.
What are those guys doing?
Sir! They are in the lock-up.
One fellow claims to be a CBI,
while the other one says that
he knows the CM.
Directly CM is it?
No MLA and MP?
They are both drunk.
Shall I file an FIR?
No need, I shall come in
the morning and deal with this.
Till then let them stay in
the lock-up.
Okay sir.
Natraj! Raju is caught by the CBI.
When madam?
About 25 minutes ago.
Where?
-Near sakhinetipalli area.
I don’t know what you will do.
There should not be any problem,
when I wake up in the morning.
Okay madam,
I shall take care.
Revathi,
I asked you to stay in
the room, right?
Where are you going now?
-To the bathroom.
Do I need permission even
for that? -Hm?
Hey!
My wedding is in the morning, and
you are calling me to drink tonight?
What will Revathi think about me?
Won’t she think that I am a drunkard?
You guys are the bad influence
to the society.
Huh?
Sir?
-Tell me Shiva?
SI sir will come only in
the morning.
He said that both of them should
be locked up till then.
Okay Shiva.
-Hello!
Please listen to me.
-I have a small work.
Can you handle till I come?
-Okay Shiva.
-I shall take care.
-Please don’t go.
Please don’t go.
Listen to me.
I am a CBI officer.
Sir he is a big accused.
I got to surrender him in court tomorrow.
Please come back, sir! - Match box!
Listen to what I say sir.
Sir…Sir…
Sir listen to me.
Hey!
Tell your stories to SI sir in
the morning.
You blabbering drunkard!
Hey! I am telling you so much
and still you are leaving?
Hey! Are you a policeman?
Can’t you look into a man’s eyes,
and know that he is a criminal?
Hey! Do you know how many murders
he has committed?
He killed an SI in Kakinada station.
Check into old case files and
you will know who Raju is.
Hey!
It is not Raju.
It is Razu.
About 4 years ago,
in morampudi junction,
there was a blast due to
gas leakage in drainage, right?
40 people died in that incident.
He did that.
If you don’t believe me, then call
and enquire to the number I give you.
Hey,
-Sir!
don’t call to the number that
he gives you. -Listen to me!
-Instead, call the number I give you.
-He is an accused. Come here!
CM will come in that line.
-Listen to me! Come!
Then you will know about this Raju.
-Please!
Come here! LIsten to me!
Look here! This is the number
of my chief officer.
Call and inform him
that we are here.
We have to submit him in
Bangalore Court in two days.
We should not be here.
Government is behind him.
So it is not safe for us to
be here.
This is my chief’s number,
call him.
Go….Go…please, there is no time.
Please go. Go.
Be careful.
Go.
Wait, you can’t come in.
He is my son doctor.
He met with an accident.
-Sir, please wait.
He is our only son.
I can’t live without him.
-You don’t worry.
Nothing will happen to him.
Hello?
Hello
Mr. Varghese?
-Yes?
Do you know anyone called George?
George?
Who are you?
Is George with you?
I am calling from
sakhinetipalli Police Station.
George is here.
We have arrested him in drunk
and drive case.
Arrest?
No, No, No.
What is your name?
Shiva, Constable Shiva.
Look Shiva!
I am Varghese.
CBI Investigative Head.
It is not safe for George
to be in your station.
First give the phone to him.
Is Raju with him?
Yes, Raju is here.
-Shiva!
Hello?
Yeah, I will ask George to
call you.
Hello?
Hey Shiva?
-Sir?
Sir?
Shiva! Where are those guys, you
arrested for drinking and nuisance?
They are inside.
One person is CBI.
Just now I called and confirmed that.
-Alright…Alright.
Are they inside?
What SP you are here?
Two minutes!
Take your time.
Sir I am a CBI officer.
I have arrested him legally.
I have given my chief’s number.
Hello, did you speak with him?
Hello?
-Cool! Calm down!
Don’t shout!
Are you from CBI?
Yes!
-hmm.
Please go and do it.
Hey did you call and speak
with him?
Hey, Rangappa!
-Sir?
Send everyone out of here,
no one should stay.
Go!
-Okay sir.
Hey! All of you go home.
Take him along and go home.
-Sir!
Sir, one man is a CBI.
I spoke with his chief.
Hey, I know what to do.
-First you leave this place.
-Sir!
-First take him away.
-Raju, leave the gun here.
-Sir, I spoke with his chief.
Come on let’s go.
-Brother you go…
SI has told us,
so come let’s leave.
Come on.
Brother you go, I am telling
you, right? -Shiva…
This is high end business.
Don’t get involved in
these matters.
Do we need this?
Tell me?
Come on let’s go.
Gopal sir, just a minute.
Mukthar do you know the location?
Yes sir,
I am calling from the location.
Raju and the CBI officer,
both are here only.
What is this CBI guy
doing there?
He has to speak
with his senior officer.
You know what to do, right?
Yes sir, I know.
Call me once the work is done.
-Okay sir.
Don’t answer any phone calls.
-Rangappa, come here!
Sir, your medicnes!
What?
-Sir, sir!
Hey!
Shiva!
Why did you shoot me?
Hey, catch him!
Hey!
Shiva! Hey, Shiva!
Wait Shiva!
Shiva!!
You are making a very big
mistake, Shiva!
What you are doing is wrong, sir.
-Shiva! Shiva!
Shiva!
Hey, Shiva!
Stop there! Catch him!
Hey!
Shiva, come here!
-Hold him.
-Sir?
Come!
-Yes sir, I am coming.
Lift him up.
Come on.
We have to take him to
the hospital. Come on.
Let’s go!
You only shot me you fool!
I fired by mistake sir.
Hey Shiva, pick up the gun.
Come.
Shiva come quickly.
-Hey!
Lock it Shiva!
Come, come quickly.
We are running out of time.
Come on Shiva!
Dear!
Ask them plans for the honeymoon?
Marriage will be done.
Shall we send to Kashmir.
Son in law has the passport, right?
Yes brother, he has passport,
VISA and everything.
Hi!
-She’s my only sister.
I got to get her married.
I have to speak with you.
-Oh, I see!
Naughty!
No…No!
I want to speak with you.
Speak?
-Yes.
Now?
Yes now.
Okay.
Come over there.
Okay I will be there.
Okay, bye.
Revathi is my love.
Hey buddy, its time.
Where is the bottle?
Bottle is there only. Go drink
and become useless like Premji.
Okay, okay.
Dear, can you…
do me a small favour?
Can you take me to the place
where I want to?
[Whispering]
What?
Only air is coming out of
my mouth.
So cute!!
What happened?
Sir?
Did Raju’s men come here?
No, sir! One man!
One man?
A constable from this station, sir.
A constable of the station?
What were you all doing then?
Do you have his photo?
Look!
-Dad?
You need not give any money…
Hey Shiva,
what are you doing
here, at this time?
Hey!
Where have you brought me?
Dad, be careful.
Please come and take a look.
-Please come!
Hey!
Are you a doctor?
-No!
I am a mortuary van driver.
-Mortuary van?
What are you trying to do to me?
-You wait, man.
First aid must be done
to stop the bleeding.
You carry on sir.
-Okay.
Yo! Do you know how to do this?
Yo! You just turn to that side.
Sir, there will be
no bleeding, right?
For now, there will not be any issue.
But take him fast. -Okay!
-Okay dad, I shall leave then.
-Okay you take care.
Dad? Hey!
Is this your son?
He is taking a huge risk by
siding with the CBI.
They will kill him for sure.
Listen to me.
Tell him to let me go.
Tell him now.
Shiva, it is risky
to travel in this vehicle.
Can you find something else?
Shiva, you take our vehicle.
There will be problem if you go
in that vehicle.
No matter what, just hand him
over at the right place.
Hey, hey! What is happening here?
The policeman is very loyal.
CBI guy is very loyal.
Even a mortuary driver is
at most loyal. -Shiva…
There is a bad vibration
around me.
You cannot even cross
the district border.
They will kill the three of us.
Then you have to carry your
son’s body in your vehicle.
Hey!!
One smack and you’ll die
then and there.
I am used to seeing corpses
every day.
Sir, you please go.
Old man,
-Dad, come!
why are you becoming furious?
-Come!
I got scared.
Dad,
-Ah?
police will come to our
house, searching for me.
You take mom and sister
and go out of station.
I shall take care of that.
You go now…
and be careful.
Where are we going?
To meet Shiva.
-Huh?
Shiva?
Yes.
I have to meet him
and ask him a few questions.
That’s it?
Not only that.
You have to thrash him for good.
Really?
I swear.
It’s been many years.
Since you fought with someone?
Ah! Since I fought with
a single person.
Normally when I fight there
will be 40-50 fighters around.
I would punch and strike them.
But for you and only this
one time, I shall hit this one guy.
I’m so lucky.
Yes!
Come on baby,
let’s go on the bullet.
Did you compose this yourself?
This sounds very familiar.
-Yeah, I composed this just now.
-This is my own tune.
-It is very nice.
Even in the future, I can become
a great musician in some great movie.
Yeah, definitely.
Hey! CBI,
you work with Central Government,
whereas I work with the State Government.
You are legal and I am illegal.
But our jobs are almost similar.
Hey! I don’t work
for politicians like you do.
Ah?
Calculate well,
you too are working for politicians.
You aren’t aware of that.
That’s it.
Come on baby let’s go on
the bullet.
Hey Shiva!
Revathi!
Why has he stopped suddenly?
-What happened?
I think he understood what
I said.
-Sir! Just a minute.
-Why did you stop?
-Sir, please just one minute.
-What one minute?
Goodbye, brother.
-Shiva, where are you going?
-At least, release me and then go.
Shut up! Shiva?
Hey! Revathi! But where
are you going at this hour?
I asked you to come and take
me away. Why didn’t you?
Please, listen to what I say.
I have heard that a lot.
But where are you going at
this time? -Hey!
I should ask that to you?
Where are you going at this time?
That too with him. Huh?
-Oh! That?
I have eloped from my house.
Eloped?
-That’s fine…
Shiva, there is no time,
come fast.
Yes sir. I am coming.
-Hey!
Even we don’t have time.
He is a CBI officer.
Talk with some respect.
Sorry sir, even we don’t have time.
-CBI officer?
I have given him the due respect.
Is that enough?
There is a huge mess involving
CBI and police.
I am in an even greater mess.
They are asking me to get married to
this Idiot, tomorrow morning at Thirupathi.
Yes my marriage.
-Shall I marry him?
-You tell me. Shall I marry him?
-My marriage.
Tell me.
Alright, now…Sir!
-Shiva, time is running out, come fast.
Come now.
Tell me.
You come with me now.
Come on.
Hey…Shiva….Revathi…
Fight scene.
Shiva, who is this?
Who is this new addition?
My lover sir.
-Lover?
Yes, sir!
A small problem at her house.
So we eloped.
Hi sir.
Oh my…
Uncle?
-Son-in-law, where are you?
There has been a huge mistake.
Uncle… oh my!!
My girl is missing.
Girl is missing?
Yes son-in-law, my daughter Revathi.
-What are you saying?
I can’t believe this!
We have to somehow find her.
We will find her.
-Coming, uncle!
Revathi!
Hey!
A girl has come trusting you, but you
are trusting him and taking me along.
Let me go my way.
You both go and be happy somewhere.
Well said brother!
A criminal, you could
understand the situation.
But this policeman cannot.
Revathi, keep quiet.
Revathi!
How many years of love?
Brother, we are in love since
our school days.
Ah?
-Hmm.
Yes.
Since your school days?
Before we reach our destination,
they will kill you guys.
I am saddened
when I think about that.
Ah? Kill us?
Don’t you know?
Your guy has beaten DSP, SP,
vandalised police station, and taken me,
just because of what this guy said.
SP and DSP?
You don’t even know this guy.
How could you beat SP and DSP
for him?
We are in love since our childhood.
You could’ve beaten my father
once and taken me, right?
Sister you give me the address.
I shall deal with your father.
Don’t talk without knowing anything.
Will we die before our marriage?
Girl, can you keep quiet for
some time?
After we handover him,
I will get you both married.
-Really?
-Yes.
You? Let’s see!
Are you married in the first place,
you fool?
Listen,
in a little while, my men will come here.
They will kill you all and take me away.
Hey! You called me as brother
without even seeing my face.
I feel so sorry for you.
Anyway sister,
rest in peace.
What are you saying?
Hey he is just trying to scare you.
You keep quiet.
Tell me if you are scared.
I shall stop the vehicle and
you can go your way.
No, No, No
Instead of marrying him and
living with him,
I can very well die here with you.
Bad choice sister!
CBI is taking Raju to
the Bangalore court.
Ask them to check all
the vehicles in that route.
Definitely he will not go in
a police jeep.
Because he will know that we would
have informed all the police stations.
Arrange for check posts in
every district border.
Ask them to check every
public transportation areas.
Since Raju is injured, he will
definitely take him to the hospital.
Check all the hospitals.
Stop every suspicious vehicle
and inform to me at once.
Sir?
-Yes?
We enquired at his house.
They say that his parents have
escaped about 2 hours ago.
Won’t a policeman know that?
Enquire all his friends
and relatives.
He should not cross this district.
Sir, he has no relatives except
an uncle. He too has absconded.
We also enquired at the hospital where
his father works. But no information.
Why aren’t you allowing me inside?
I am an ex-councillor.
SI Rangappa is my relative.
Hey! Who is that?
-Let me in.
I have to meet the SI.
Tell him that Ramamurthy is here.
-Rangappa, come here.
What is happening here?
Why are you shouting here?
-Where is that Shiva?
-He is not here.
He has kidnapped my daughter.
File a case against him and
write an FIR.
Ramamurthy, this is another issue.
Revathi is not with him.
Son-in-law, come here.
Come here.
-Uncle?
-Come here! Tell him.
What should I tell him?
Tell him what happened.
Okay ready.
Constable Shiva, works in your
station has taken my Revathi.
What is your problem?
-Oh my, son-in-law!
It’s me sir.
It was me sir.
What are you saying?
Let me adjust my wig.
I am in love with Revathi
since my childhood.
Even after knowing that they both are
in love, I am still in love with her.
My love is so sincere.
My uncle fixed our wedding to be
conducted today morning at Thirupathi.
Yesterday night, she signalled
and called me.
Son-in-law?
I too thought the same thing.
And that is why I went with her.
But nothing happened.
Nothing happened sir.
Nothing happened at all.
She said that she wanted to give
him her peace of mind.
I believed her and we went in
my vehicle.
He came, while we were
crossing that Palem Bridge.
He came, stood, spoke
and they escaped.
My Revathi, who has to live as my bride,
went along with him like a corpse.
No, she got into that mortuary van,
and she eloped with him,
right in front of my eyes.
She left.
Sir, his father is a mortuary van
driver at the Government hospital.
Hey?
Who else was there in that van?
Sir, only wind is coming out of
my mouth. -Fool!
This wig is a nuisance.
Trace that mortuary van’s location.
They should not leave this town.
-Alert all the check posts.
-Okay sir.
What happened now?
-Sir, the radiator is all heated up.
We need to pour water.
I shall go and check.
Okay go and come fast.
Hey come slowly.
Hey! He is a big headache!
Go now.
Natraj sir! Please respond, over!
Tell me, which place?
Go the information that they are
going in a Mortury van that way.
Over!
Brother, I shall take some water.
The radiator has heated up.
-Okay, take it!
Hey! Shiva, long time no see?
Heard some criminal has escaped?
Have they sent you to catch him?
No sir,
the radiator of the vehicle has
heated up. I came to get some water.
Why are you using dad’s vehicle?
Jeep has broken down and that is
why I came in my dad’s vehicle.
Constable Shiva from Sakinetipalli Police
Station, has escaped along with an accused.
It is an order to inform about
their whereabouts if they are found.
I repeat!
Constable Shiva from Sakinetipalli Police
Station, has escaped along with an accused.
What’s this Shiva!
-Sir, Sir, no sir.
-Shiva, surrender!
-Sir! No, sir. Let go!
Don’t move, wait!
Shiva, come fast.
Is it over?
Sir the police have come.
Start the vehicle, fast.
Shiva!
I think he has poured the water
into the petrol tank.
They are closing in on us.
Go Shiva.
Shiva! Go…Go…
Shiva, there is a vehicle to
your left.
Shiva are you okay?
Go.
Block the bridge road.
Block them.
Hey, Shiva! Fast, fast!
Hey, Shiva!
Move it, move it!
Shiva!
What are you doing?
Leave it.
Brother, leave me.
Hey leave her.
Hey Shiva, you drive properly!
-Hey Raju, leave her.
Hey Raju leave her.
Hey, you look ahead.
-Hey Raju, leave her.
-Hey, Raju!
-Be careful.
Go that side.
Check if there is a way that side.
You go to this side.
Partner!
It is Razu, partner!
Razu!
Sorry my friend.
Sir, this way!
Sir, what are you doing?
Sir?
Sir…sir, what are you doing?
Please open the door.
I have been hit by a bullet. It is
useless for me to come all the way.
Sir, open the lock.
-Listen to what I say.
Listen to me, please!
-Listen!
Submit him at the Bangalore Court.
-What are you saying, sir?
Go Shiva.
How can we abandon you at
this condition?
Sir, please come with us.
-Hey!
If you were hit by a bullet,
I wouldn’t have thought like you.
Sir? Please open the door and come.
-I am a waste luggage Shiva.
There is no time, you go.
Listen to me sir.
Open the door and come inside.
-I cannot leave you here.
-Go…Go…Shiva!
Shiva, take him there. Don’t
talk and waste the time now.
They are coming here!
I shall take care.
-Go!
-Shiva! Come on.
Raju!!
My dear friend!
Can you hear me?
Raju, Raju!
Stay inside. Stay inside.
Hide inside
You were once a terror,
but now you are cowering
into a small lane.
How many times did I tell you?
Not to roam around and not to
go beyond jurisdiction limit?
What happened now?
You have been caught by the CBI.
How many murders
have we done together?
-But I am in a position to kill you.
-Hey, Raju! Stay here!
Wait, please!
What can I do?
It is the order from
the high command.
Raju!
-No! Raju, no!
What a great man you are!
You are frightened of me...
and hiding behind a meek constable.
How will your frightened face be?
I want to see your face.
Raju!
I’m here!
Come!
Raju…
It is not Raju…
Razu!!
Don’t I know that partner?
-Hey Raju!
Hey, no…no!
-It is Raju!!
Hey Raju, listen.
Don't go, stop.
Sir, leave! Listen to me.
Leave, sir!
Hey!
Hey, leave idiot!
-Hail! CM!
Greetings!
-Greetings!
Greetings! Please come!
Sir, is upstairs!
-Okay.
[clearing throat]
Good day uncle.
Ah! Come dear.
-Did you eat?
Yes.
Are your problems over?
It will be over soon.
You know everything.
Your father and I strived hard
to form this party.
When times were hard for a regional
party, to win over a national party,
We started this party for
the people.
The trust on your father…
and the sympathy wave due to
his death,
All these have made you
a CM today.
People have accepted you.
But owing to your past mistakes,
People in the centre are trying
to destroy this party, with the CBI.
Don’t you worry uncle.
I shall prove my innocence in
the court and come out.
What?
They have your entire history
in their hands.
It is the report that they have been
collecting for the past four years.
Uncle…
that will never help them.
The court needs evidence.
-Really?
What is that guy’s name?
Raju, is it?
He will not come.
In the next 24 hours, he will
be wiped off this face of earth.
Don’t mistake me,
We would have no qualms
if you ended up in some trouble.
But if it is going to threaten
the party…
I am aware of that.
Party is my priority too.
I shall meet you tomorrow
after the court.
Then…
Elections are approaching.
Don’t put us in a situation to
select another candidate for CM.
Greetings!
-Greetings!
-Hail! CM!
What is happening Natraj?
I have killed that CBI officer,
madam.
But Raju has escaped
with that constable Shiva.
Damn! Aren’t you ashamed to
say this?
We are running out of time Natraj.
If Raju gets captured,
then you and I,
we all would be in trouble.
You have till tonight.
Mobilize the entire Police
Department if you need.
Do anything you need to.
If you need more,
then make use of rowdies
and the party people.
I want Raju dead, today!
Please be cautious with the gun
otherwise it will fire!
Is it possible Shiva?
Can we go across all these people?
We can, come!
They will not spare you.
If you both want to live together,
Then let me go,
I shall take care of the rest.
I shall take care of that,
you come now.
Hey!
Are you trying to become a hero?
Very difficult.
Sister, why don’t you tell him?
Tell him to leave me.
Only that can you save you.
What are you looking at?
-No.
I am concerned about you.
You came with him, even though
you knew your life is at risk.
So I understood about you.
I want at least your love
to succeed.
Does that mean,
you too had a love?
Where is that girl now?
Oh my!
Tell me brother.
That is nothing dear.
It was just a one side love.
Didn’t you propose to her?
You should have.
I thought of telling it to her.
But I couldn’t.
You should profess your love.
-Hey Revathi!
Keep quiet!
Always talking nonsense!
Brother, who is that?
CM.
CM?
Oh my!
The same CM that sent
the henchmen to kill us.
Maybe I should have told her, then
all this could have been avoided.
Superb brother.
-Hey!
He is blabbering unnecessarily.
I am not blabbering,
I am telling the truth.
Yes Shiva,
when he was talking about her,
I could see a love spark in
his eyes.
-You could see?
-Yes!
Oh! Great, now come.
And please keep quiet for
some time.
Let’s focus on getting out of
this place safely.
That is impossible.
I bet that you cannot even go
beyond this limit.
You don’t know about this Natraj.
I thought…
he came to save me.
Just ask my brother to get here.
I shall go with him and finish
this once and for all.
You take her and leave.
I think that what he says
is right.
I have no hope that we could
go beyond all these men.
But I have hope.
I have hope that
I would submit him in the court.
Hey! Damn!
Why do you keep repeating
the same thing? Are you senseless?
Leave me!
Leave me I say.
Hey!
How many times to tell you?
Can’t you understand?
Brother!
Why are you hitting me in
the same spot?
Shiva!
-Hey, wait, wait!
Please, don’t fight.
Why are you fighting unnecessarily?
No one in your department
is bothered.
Is it only for you?
What he says is right.
Why don’t we leave?
You are important to me.
How can I leave and go?
Huh?
How can I leave him?
How can I leave even after knowing that
he is the one who killed my brother??
Damn!
What did my brother do to you?
“Every direction on the earth,”
“Shall proclaim our story.”
“Every nook and cranny,”
“Shall be filled with our song.”
“Just like conjoined twins,”
“Let’s hug and dwell in love.”
“This bond shall never
worn away,”
“Because this is the boon
of God.”
“Every direction on the earth,”
“Shall proclaim our story,”
“Shall proclaim our story.”
“Even if we are together
for seven births,”
“We will ask for some more.”
“We will do penance,”
“To be born together in
our mother’s womb.”
“We cannot live without
each other,”
“We will always stay united.”
“Holding hands together,”
“We will stay forever.”
“Who can be like us in
this world?”
“Really there is none anywhere.”
“Every direction on the earth,”
“Shall proclaim our story.”
“Every nook and cranny,”
“Shall be filled with our song.”
“Just like conjoined twins,”
“Let’s hug and dwell in love.”
“This bond shall never
worn away,”
“Because this is the boon
of God.”
“Every direction on the earth,”
“Shall proclaim our story,”
“Shall proclaim our story.”
Hey!
-Hmm.
What do you want to be?
Don’t you know?
I want to become a police, a SI.
I must do a lot of good to
the people.
That is my passion.
Hey Vishnu!
This serious demeanor doesn’t
suit you.
You be carefree as usual, okay?
I am happy for you man.
Thanks, man.
Hey hi!
-Hi, how are you?
Is that Srikanth here?
Everybody is here, only we are late.
-Shiva!
Go to the town and get
this medicine.
Mom! Dad is working
in the Government Hospital.
Won’t this be available there?
We have a match, mom.
This medicine is available
only in that shop.
You keep acquainting with these
useless fellows,
and keep roaming all the grounds,
playing cricket.
No way mom.
-Here take this.
You could have told about
this yesterday.
Today I have a match.
Mom!
As if you are the great
Sachin Tendulkar. Go now.
Hey are we going to the ground now?
You just go and start the match.
If you win the toss,
select batting.
-I’m coming!
-For that we have to win the toss.
-Hey Vishnu?
-Hah!
Go to the town and buy this
medicine for dad.
Okay bye.
-Hey, wait!
Your sister-in-law is waiting
for me.
We have to finalize
the invitation as well.
So?
Here take this.
Your invitation is important
that buying medicine for dad?
Hey! You fool! What are you saying?
-Hey!
You are not even married,
but there are a lot of changes
in your activities.
-Mom!
-Yeah?
He has changed
even before getting married.
Imagine what will happen
after marriage!
-Let him do anything, you go now.
-She is telling you only, so go now.
Hey, please listen to me. Your
sister-in-law is waiting for me.
Hey, Vishnu!
You are the man in the house,
after dad.
So you have to take care of all
these responsibilities.
Try to understand, okay!
Go now, there is no time.
-Hey!
Hey! You are very cunning!
You just take advantage of
my innocence.
I curse you now!
You guys will never win any of the game.
-Okay man, I shall take care of that.
You will lose every match you guys play.
-Okay man thank you so much.
You will become duck out. You will
not even get a chance to play.
Hello? Milk society?
Hey, it’s me.
Where are you?
Sorry, I have to get medicine
for my dad…
so I will be a little late.
What?
Okay, love you.
I shall come soon okay? Bye!
Give me a kiss now.
-Hmm?
I know that you will not give me.
Hang up.
Hey…there is baby!
Dear!
Move! Quick.
Hey!
Hey! Come out!
How?
Come fast!
Come on!
Come fast! Come….come…
Happy birthday, dear!
Get up! It’s okay!
Madam!! Come here.
Take this kid, fast.
-Okay, sir!
It is paining a lot.
-Don’t worry, come!
Hey!
Vishnu!
Vishnu….
-Hey, move!
Come, come! Move fast!
Come,come. Fast, faster!
Move, move! Fast, faster!
Vishnu….
-Come, fast!
Vishnu!
-Come, come!
Vishnu….Vishnu, look at me.
This is Shiva.
You are alright. Vishnu!
Nurse, please check him.
You escaped man.
-Vishnu!
Hey!
Vishnu!
Vishnu, don’t talk like that.
Don’t you cry.
I am sorry, man.
-I am just kidding…
I am kidding man.
Sorry!
Hey!
If I die, you should take care
of things.
Hey! No…
-You should take care of mom, dad!
Don’t talk like that Vishnu!
You have to get medicines for dad.
-Vishnu!
Don’t talk like that brother,
please!
I am there for you right?
Please.
Why do you suddenly
call me as brother?
You know that I will not
make it, right?
Hey….Hey…
Why do you talk like this?
Have you gone mad?
I am telling that nothing will
happen to you right?
Please stay strong.
Brother, please go fast.
Your sister-in-law!
She will be waiting for me there.
Everything is over before
the wedding.
What are you talking?
Nothing is wrong with you.
We will reach the hospital in five
minutes. Everything will be alright.
We shall go home soon. Okay?
Nothing is wrong with you.
Hey! Hey!
I had many desires.
-Don’t cry Vishnu!
Police…SI…
Don’t cry!
I wanted to do many good things
to people.
You will definitely help people.
You will help everyone.
Now you just listen to me.
All your desires shall come true.
Vishnu….Vishnu…
Nurse! Nurse!
Please check on him.
[Indistinct voices]
Hey what happened?
Clear the traffic!
Brother!
Vishnu! Hey, Vishnu!
Vishnu….Vishnu!
Nurse just now
he was speaking with me.
Nurse, please do something fast.
Vishnu….Vishnu!
Please wake up!
Brother please go fast.
Please go fast.
Hey! Vishnu get up, please.
Vishnu!!
Vishnu…hey!
Hey Vishnu!
Hey!
Since my brother died in
the blast, I got his police job.
Just for his sake,
I started to live the life of
a police that he desired so much.
Along with my brother, so many people
were killed for their political gain.
They convinced everyone that
it was an accident.
When I knew that he murdered
my brother,
I just wanted to kill him first.
But then,
no one would ever know the truth.
The family of the victims should
know the truth.
Only then their souls would
rest in peace.
Come, let’s go.
Get up.
There is excessive bleeding.
You also told that
the bullet is lodged inside.
We should check immediately.
Else it will become very worse.
Okay come.
[indistinct voices]
[humming song]
-Hi.
-What dear?
You want lift?
No!
I need the car itself.
Hey! Hey!
Thought to lift you and
you’ve lifted the car itself.
Damn!
He is here, speak now.
Hello?
Uncle?
Yeah tell me Pandu.
How are you all?
We are all fine.
But did you hear anything
about Shiva.
No, but he will be cautious
for sure.
Uncle, please be careful until
he comes back.
Yeah.
Bye uncle.
-Okay.
Give me the change.
Greetings!
Hello, Guntur, Sri Balaji Lodge?
Take a left here.
There is a hospital there.
Hey, Revathi! Wait, wait!
-What happened?
The police are here.
Take a reverse!
Go straight!
Hey, police!
Go into this house.
This house!
-Here?
Revathi be casual.
Just open the gate and park
the car in there.
Yeah I am coming.
Please wait.
-Who is that? Who are you guys?
-Madam please there is an emergency.
-Why are you coming in here? Who are you?
-We just need to make a phone call.
-Philip, look! Someone is here!
-One phone call, please help us, please!
Why are closing the gate?
-Madam please help us.
-Who are you guys, now tell me.
I am a police.
-Who are you guys?
-Madam, please!
Sir! Sir!
-Please go out.
-Who are you?
-Sir, my name is Shiva.
I am a constable at Sakinetipalli
Police Station, ID number 1302.
He is an accused in my custody.
What happened?
-Sir!
Sir he is hit by a bullet.
There is excessive blood loss.
Can I make a call to a doctor?
When did this happen?
Yesterday night.
We have just given some
first aid.
Okay bring him in.
-Thanks sir.
Please come, be careful.
Sir, do you know
what you are doing?
Relax! Relax!
How did this happen?
I was in night duty at the station.
-Oh!
Sir, is everything okay?
-Hmm.
Nothing to worry.
He must rest for two days and
he would be alright.
I have to hand him over to the CBI
court at Bangalore tomorrow morning.
Hey!
I have done first aid…
and there will not be
any problem for 6-8 hours.
Hello?
Hello sir, this is Shiva.
Shiva, where are you now?
They are saying that you locked up
George and escaped with Raju?
No sir,
they tried to kill George at
the station.
George and I saved Raju and
took him with us.
Huh!
Give the phone to George.
IG Natraj has killed George sir.
Now the entire police department
is searching for us.
I don’t know what to do.
Raju has a bullet injury.
Where are you now?
Sir…
I am at the home
of an ex-military officer.
You stay there,
I shall send my team.
An officer Ranjit will come and
take you from there.
Okay sir.
Sir!
I think there is some link
between that constable and Raju.
That is why he has destroyed
the entire station and saved him.
What’s this, sir?
He has taken an accused and
a CBI officer from your custody,
But you seem pretty casual
about that?
What caution have you taken
so far?
Sir! We are searching.
We shall find them soon.
Sir! We need all the details
about this case at once.
Sir! If you don’t co-operate,
then I have to report to Delhi.
Then you do one thing.
Get a letter from commissioner.
Huh?
Sir, one second.
Hello?
-Ranjit,
just now Shiva called me.
You told that you were meeting
with an officer Natraj,
who is handling this case right?
-Yes, sir!
That man has killed our George.
Yes sir,
I am now with him.
Shit!
Now don’t let him know that
we are aware of this.
Raju is now with Shiva.
He is safe in the house
of an ex-military officer house.
You meet them immediately there.
No one must know about this.
And one more thing.
Listen to me carefully.
That Natraj is a dangerous guy.
We are alone in this case.
Okay, sir!
Okay!
Sir, I shall meet the commissioner
and get the letter.
Okay sir.
This issue is getting serious.
Varghese sir called now.
We have to go there immediately.
Ah…here take this.
Your dress is torn
so change into these clothes.
There are clothes for your
friends as well.
Thanks aunty.
-That’s okay.
Did you eat anything dear?
No.
I am very hungry.
Since yesterday night they are
chasing us. We have been running.
Oh my!
You go and get refreshed.
I shall prepare some food for you.
Get ready and come.
Are you okay? Do you want something?
-Okay,
can I get a cigarette sir?
Hm?
It’s okay if you don’t have.
Are you a doctor?
No, an ex-army officer.
Then you must have rum, right?
Hey!
Usually they give that for pain.
How do you know all this
if you are not a doctor?
They taught all this in our
army training.
For emergency purposes in
the field.
It will be nice if the government
taught this to us.
We too face many emergencies.
How many men would you
have killed?
Why do you ask?
Just for some general knowledge.
What can you do with
that knowledge?
Sir!
You kill under government orders
and so do I.
But you are given medals while
I am branded as an accused.
What a comparison!
We kill enemies
for the safety of our country,
and you kill innocent people
for the corrupt politicians.
Don’t justify your murders.
Sir! A murder is a murder.
The person that I kill has a family
and so will the person that you kill.
You are one justifying murders.
Everyone has feelings.
Tomorrow the court will decide
which is right and which is wrong.
Why do you keep talking to
him sir?
What is wrong in what I say?
He is justifying everything…
Silence!
Who is that?
I am Ranjit
sent by CBI head Varghese.
Is anyone by the name Shiva here?
We are here.
I am Ranjit from CBI.
Shiva, main road is not that safe.
Five kilometres from here to the left,
you will find a path in the woods.
Take that. You will be safe.
Hey!
Hey, a vehicle is approaching.
Take a reverse!
Stay down! Stay down!
Hey! Suresh you go out.
Sundar you come with me.
Hey!
What are you staring at?
None of you want to
become the next Raju?
Oh!
You will proceed only if
I say action?
Go guys!
Shiva,
these guys cannot manage.
Just untie me, here!
Hey! Keep quiet,
they will take care.
Listen to me they will
kill everyone.
Untie me.
Shiva I will not escape.
Just untie me man!
Who wanted to become
the next Razu?
Come on!
Come!
Razu!
Sir no one is here.
They have escaped!
What??
Is evething okay?
Shiva, they are checking
for something.
There!
Come, let's go
Guys who grew under my tutelage
wants to kill me,
to become the next Razu.
The people who I knew
are trying to kill me.
But you are trying to keep
me alive.
Just wait and watch
what I do to these guys.
What can you do?
Are you going to kill them?
Yes!
How many can you kill?
They will keep coming.
Let them come.
They want you dead.
If you want to show them
who you are,
just tell everything
in the court tomorrow.
Huh! Court?
It is the CM.
They will be out of this case
in a second.
You don’t know anything.
Why? Has this never happened
before?
Do you know how many CMs and PMs
were locked up before?
Just tell in court for once.
Stand for justice.
It will be a penance
for every crime you did.
Everything depends on your
brought up right?
I too should have had a family
like you.
There was no one to tell me
what was right and what was wrong.
I grew up thinking that
what I did was right.
How was the food?
You did give the gift money right?
Reception was huge.
Raju, come!
I'm very happy that you came.
Hey Revathi!
I feel very happy.
Why are you here?
Mangalam Aunty.
Aunty?
-Yes.
Oh my!
Er…Is…Is this our wedding?
-Yes.
Yes! That is why I came here.
Your father said that you were
getting married in Thirupathi today?
That…
-Revathi where are you going?
-You come here even during your wedding.
-Come on, there is no time.
Aunty…
I’m so happy! Come, come!
-Why didn’t your father come?
-Ah…he’s angry on you.
Raju, come fast.
Hey stop kidding, come!
Look, saris and jewellery
are here.
There is everything. Get ready soon.
-I don’t want, aunty!
Ah…listen to me.
Listen to me.
Wear all these and come soon.
Why is your father angry with me?
I shall speak with him.
-Aunty it is not you but me…
Oh my!
Are you done serving the sambar?
Now drink.
Hello?
-Brother!
Why are you angry on me?
What did I do?
Why am I angry on you, Mangalam?
I know everything.
Revathi told me.
Revathi?
Did she talk to you??
When?
Just now she told me everything.
Where?
Here in our family’s wedding.
You lied to us
about Revathi’s wedding right?
I didn’t lie to you, dear.
She was the one who is lying
to you.
She eloped from her wedding.
Eloped?
Don't let her go anywhere.
I'm starting right away.
We have found Revathi.
Let’s go.
We can eat later, come on.
Yo! Son-in-law it’s getting late!
Bi-lingual.
Yeah I shall take care.
No matter what language you speak,
Please bring the girl to me sir.
-He's my brother, never gives me heroine.
Bring me the sambar.
What? Get me the sambar
What’s this?
Aunty, I will kill you.
Geetha! Had food?
What about you?
I’m done!
Hey, come, come!
“My dear Rukmani,”
“My sweet doe-eyed beauty”
“Are you the pure gold?”
“Forged by Lord Brahma himself?”
“You damsel with intoxicating eyes”
“I am giddy with your thoughts”
“Don’t you stick to my heart
and kill me.”
“What spell did you cast
over me?”
“I have come running behind you.”
“You are gambling with
your antics at me”
“You are my fortunate lover.”
“You are simply bundling up
my heart,”
“You are stealing the dream
in me”
“You are embracing my
little heart”
“With your smile you are
sowing dreams.”
Brother!
Mangala, where is Revathi?
Hey, have you gone mad?
Come!
-She's upstairs in the room.
-Hey, let's go.
What are you doing here?
Come fast!.
“Don’t stretch your arms and
legs over me”
“Don’t you play me like a game.”
“Even when my eyes are closed”
“My dreams shall only show you”
“So don’t you ask me to
leave hungry.”
“You can never be cheated
by others”
“Because they become a clown before you”
-Dad! Take your hand off me!
“You are my gold”
“I will take you away”
“And soften you secretly”
“You are simply bundling up
my heart,”
“You are stealing the dream
in me”
“You are embracing my
little heart”
“With your smile you are
sowing dreams.”
Come!
Look there, he is taking away
the girl again.
Superman!
-Oh no!
Is everything okay?
Be alert.
-Raju?
What happened?
Where is Raju?
I am wondering the same.
I trusted him!
Where did he go?
[indistinct voices]
What is happening here Varghese?
Ah…Sir, I spoke with that
military officer.
Constable Shiva is bringing
that Raju here.
Varghese! .
This is a very, very, very sensitive
case where CM is involved
If they don’t come to court tomorrow,
that will be huge disgrace to department.
Sir!
If we send some extra force there…
Where to send extra force, Varghese?
Already we have lost
a lot of people.
Ranjit is no more and
so is George.
I’m losing hoping.
We have to somehow find them.
Know their location as early
as possible.
Fast!
-Okay, sir!
Ah…Shiva!
It is all because of you.
If you hadn’t come with us, all these
problems would never have happened.
Damn!
Yes, there wouldn’t have been
these problems.
But I would’ve been married
to that Prem.
You could have married him.
Huh?
Instead you came here
and spoiled everything.
So if I had married him,
you would have had no issues.
Isn’t it?
-Hey?
-Stop the vehicle Shiva.
Revathi, keep quiet.
Stop the vehicle Shiva.
Hey Revathi, please keep quiet.
Stop the vehicle or else I’ll…
-Revathi, be quiet.
Are you mad?
Close the door.
I am telling you, close the door.
-Leave my hand.
Revathi close the door.
Take your hand off me!
Stop the vehicle!
Revathi!
Ah!!!
Sorry!
I shouldn’t have spoken like that.
Don’t you know?
This is my brother’s dream.
He wanted to become a police
and do service to people.
I became a police to fulfil
his dream.
Now look what happened?
I hit that inspector and many
others and brought Raju along.
But now he is missing.
Can I go back to our town?
Even if I go there,
will I get my job back?
Mom, dad…
and sister…
I even don’t know,
where are they?
I spoke out of tension.
Listen!
What I like the most in you is
your stubbornness.
If you set your mind to
finish something,
You will never stop till you
get it done.
That hope made me
to fall in love with you.
Not only in this issue,
no matter what,
I shall never leave you.
I love you so much.
Please forgive me.
The moment you came
and sat beside me,
I fell in love with you.
Shiva…
-Hmm.
I am a little hungry.
Okay!
I saw a hotel on the way.
Shall we have some Paratha there?
[indistinct voices]
Hello!
-Hey Ravi, it’s me.
-Yeah tell me!
Yeah tell me… tell me brother?
Where are you?
When will you reach here?
I am on the way, brother!
-Where are you?
-I…I am inside the exhibition.
There is a stage behind a ride.
I am standing there, come fast.
Ah! Okay brother,
I shall be there.
First keep aside your anger
and then think calmly.
You cannot understand anything
in rage.
He is injured,
so he could not go far.
There will be police everywhere.
Where would he have gone?
He definitely needs someone
to help him.
Then, where will he ask him
to come?
The exhibition that is happening at
Amar grounds will conclude tomorrow.
We request everybody to come
and enjoy the show.
Brother, one Kothu Parotta!
[indistinct voices]
Will he definitely be here?
I don’t know where he will
be here.
But we have no other option.
So we have to search
and he will be somewhere here.
Hey Raju!
-Where?
You go that side.
Shiva… there!
Raju, stop there.
Raju!
I trusted you and released your
handcuff. But you deceived us.
Hey!
-Shiva!
If we stay here together,
then they will kill us both.
How are we going to escape?
Leave me and go. -Shiva!
Hey! Where should I go?
Where do you want me to go?
Should I go to police who I hit?
Or should I go to my father to whom I
promised to avenge my brother’s death?
Hey! I will either submit you at
the court… Or I shall die trying.
Shiva!
I know both of you are here.
Enough…
enough of this cat
and mouse game.
He is here.
Don’t be here, go now.
One of your friends is here
to meet you.
I am leaving Shiva,
listen to me now.
Hand over Raju
and take him with you.
-Hey Shiva, listen to me.
-No Shiva.
Listen to what he says Shiva.
-Hey!
Dad! Dad!
-Shiva don’t go.
Ask Shiva to bring Raju here.
-Please don’t go!
I shall spare his life then.
Or else…
Ask him to come.
Dad… Dad.
He will not do anything,
listen to me. -He has a gun.
Trust me he will not do
anything to your father. -Call him!
No Shiva, don’t come out.
Truth alone should come out.
Why is he talking now?
All the victims who died along with your
brother, must get justice they deserve.
You leave now.
Hey…Hey Shiva!
You father has gone mad.
I have kept the gun at point
blank range.
-Dad!
-He will not do anything.
-Dad! Dad!
-If you want your Dad…
Leave him
and take your father with you.
Come on!
-Dad.
-He will not do anything.
-Dad!
You should not come Shiva!
You have taken an oath.
You have taken oath over
your uniform. -Hey!
I have taken many such oaths.
Shiva, what is important to you?
Your dad or taking Raju to
the court?
Just listen, he is trying to
kill us. -Dad! Dad!
You decide for yourself.
I will count till 10.
What can you do?
Are you going to kill me?
Go ahead!
I will kill you for sure.
Go ahead, kill me.
At such a young age,
my son is fighting against death,
then why an old man like me
should fear you?
He will not do anything to
your father. -Dad!
Shiva!
You should not fail because of me.
-Hey Shiva!!
-Wait, nothing will happen.
-Dad! Leave me.
If you don’t bring out Raju…
Dad!
“Did you leave to sojourn
the sky?”
“Dad, my Dad!”
-Leave me!
Dad!
Shiva!
“Did you end your life that
you lived?” -Hey!
“Dad, my Dad!”
“You found your end”
“But you abandoned me”
Brother, come on.
Get in.
“My heart is crying out”
-Brother!
Brother come in. Come!
-“My heart is burning”
“It cries out searching for you”
-Dad! Dad!
“I cannot bear this”
-Dad!
Leave me!
Dad!
“If someone does something wrong”
-Let’s go!
“We would complain him to the king”
“If someone does something wrong”
“If the king is a murderer”
“Then where can we go and complain?”
“My heart is crying out”
“My heart is burning”
“It cries out searching for you”
“I cannot bear this”
There is money in that bag.
Take that, go somewhere and live.
If you keep preaching
about justice and honesty,
they will first kill you and
then her.
What are you looking at?
I didn’t kill his father.
That is not my fault but yours.
I told you not to come with me.
You explain things to him.
Tell him to live along with people.
People!
Okay?
Take that money
and settle in some place.
Invite me for your wedding.
I shall come and feast on biryani.
They said that whoever kills Raju…
will become the next Raju.
I know you will be happy if I become
Raju, instead of some random guy.
Why did you stab me here?
Isn’t the liver on the right side?
Shiva!
You have to stab like this.
Right side, right side!
Shiva, please don’t go.
You don’t even know where to stab.
How can you become the next Razu?
-Revathi leave me.
-Shiva…
-I am telling you, right?
Let me go. -No Shiva.
Hey!
Shiva!
Raju, come!
Let’s go!
We need to go from here!
Revathi….Revathi…
Hey, Shiva!
Raju, Raju, come!
-Don’t let them go!
Come! Revathi, come!
Come, get in the train!
Revathi.. Come on!
Raju, don’t stop. Go!
You were saying that
your brother would come.
He came.
What happened now?
No one is loyal around you.
The life that you lived was
a lie.
What did you say? You said we
cannot even go beyond our town.
But now look where we are.
Truth will triumph.
It might take some time.
But it shall definitely triumph.
You said that my father’s death
will not come under your list.
It is right, it will not.
But do you know why he died?
He died so the truth could
come to light.
Try standing beside truth
for once.
Your life will change.
Shiva…Shiva listen to me.
Shiva even now I am telling you.
Just surrender.
Hey!
Revathi! Take the weapon!
Revathi, Revathi!
Revathi! Go to the engine.
This train shouldn’t stop anywhere.
Do you get it?
-How can I, Shiva?
Revathi! We have to do this
as we don’t have any options left!
You have a gun in your hand.
Use the gun if necessary.
But the train shouldn’t stop
at any station. Go, Revathi. Go!
We will get off
wherever the train slows down.
Double crossing over, next stage!
Put the walkie down.
-Ah?
If I shoot your head would explode.
Go fast….Go fast!
-Okay, okay!
Go fast!
Even faster, go fast.
I am doing it, madam.
Raju! Come, come…
Get in!
Hey!
Close it, close it!
Raju, get up!
Come, let’s go!
Raju! Come.
-I will not spare you.
Come. Let’s get to the engine.
Come, come!
Come fast!
Raju!
Raju! Listen to me!
Come, come
Raju! Raju…
Raju! Give me your hand.
Come, come.
Hey! Listen to me! Come!
Raju! Come.
Listen to me! Come!
Hey!
Hey, Raju! What are you doing?
Raju! What are you doing?
Raju…
Hey, hey!
Hey! Raju…
Raju, what are you up to?
Hey, hey! Stop the train!
Hey, hey!
Raju, what are you up to?
Raju, what are you up to??
Damn!
What Raju,
if you were in my place…
You too would have done
the same thing right?
Surely I wouldn’t have done
like this.
I wouldn’t have suffered so much.
I would have killed you
the very next minute.
Do you have a match box?
Hey…
Raju…Raju…
Raju!
-Hail to!
-Tamil warrior lady, Drakshayani!
-Brave lady, Drakshayani!
-Hail to!
-Jhansi Rani, Drakshayani!
-CM forever, Drakshayani!
-Hail to!
-Goddess of loyalty, Drakshayani!
-Golden star, Drakshayani!
You may proceed!
Your honour,
as CBI didn’t produce witnesses
even in this adjournment,
it is clear that CM's name was
intentionally induced into this case.
Thus, I request the Court
to dismiss this case.
You're honour, witness is here.
We are presenting now.
With your permission.
Permitted!
Shiva, Ma'am!
My lord!
My name is Shiva.
Sakhinetipalli Police Station
Constable.
ID number 1302.
On the way,
while I and CBI officer George…
were bringing this case witness
Raju to the court,
But while coming here,
IG Nataraj and some Police have
killed Raju and CBI officer George.
For that,
will you give the witness?
Who said I'm giving witness?
Raju himself will tell.
You said, they killed him right?
Will he come alive and
give witness?
He will.
Train shouldn't stop here.
Go, be courageous.
Go Revathi, go!
Hey listen, keep the camera inside.
Hey listen to me.
I think there is some problem.
Keep the camera inside.
Are you a big reporter?
Listen to me and keep it inside
What is this?
Sorry ma’am! Sorry!
One minute! Sorry ma’am!
Shiva, is this okay?
Yeah! Okay, ready.
Good day to you all.
My name is Rajashekar.
Razu.
If you’re seeing me in this video.
instead of directly saying, it
means CM already got me killed.
CM has killed me.
I wish to many facts with you.
-Do I say like this?
-Yes, go on!
Almost 40 died a few years ago, in
gas blast accident at Morampudi junction.
That was really an accident.
To make IAS officer Radhakrishna's
dead body disappear
IG Natraj and I planned this to hide
murder of IAS officer Radhakrishnan.
IAS officer finding out CM’s mistakes
and illegal activities, questioned her.
CM killed that man.
We laid his body in a vehicle at
Morampudi Junction and left there.
CM asked me to bring it.
I did by her orders.
I have done many such things
for CM.
I did many as such for CM.
This is my death statement.
Madam?
The money received from
the ruling party,
And I also have the recording
of our phone calls.
I have hidden it in a place.
Shiva will hand over that to you.
Okay. Wait!
-What?
What?
-There is one more thing.
-Ok, tell.
I fell in love with the CM right
at the first time I saw her.
She has nothing to do.
Just one side!
I didn’t want to say this.
But, Revathi asked me to say this.
No, not me!
That’s it.
Thanks!
Since Raju, the important witness of CBI
in this case, could not come to the court.
This court accepts his dying
declaration as important evidence.
I order the CBI to get all
the evidences mentioned by Raju,
From Shiva and proceed
with further investigations.
This court orders CBI to take
the accused,
The primary accused of this case,
A1, Dhatchayani,
A2 IG Natraj and other police officers,
who are involved in this case,
Must be taken into custody
for further investigation.
This court orders the CBI to produce
final report, within the next 21 days.
The court is adjourned!
Thank you Shiva,
you did a great job.
Thank you sir.
If you want you can join the CBI.
I can appoint you right away.
I want to be a police.
This is my brother’s dream.
Okay,
but you know that our doors
are always open for you.
Right!
All the best.
Good job, Shiva.
What you did is right.
You, me, and everyone else is
here to serve the public.
If it’s going to help the public,
don’t think twice to confront anyone.
Be it the CM or the PM.
Everything happened as you thought.
Shall we get married now?
She was requesting you throughout
the movie. Why don’t you marry her?
Audiences have to go home.
“Jagada Jagada Jagadam
we are ready for a battle”
Ragada Ragada Ragadam
We shall shake it all”
“Let a thousand lives come, we
shall swallow death again and again”
“With this seething, raging poison
Our call is a drum beat”
“I am the king of the jungle
Sky’s the limit but I always be humble”
“Lot of people talk about
this and that”
“ But…In the end they fumble”
“I go voice by the gate, paps follow
me as I am chilling on a break”
“Talk to me nice, this man don’t play man
if goes left, then it’s a little late”
“Talk to me nice cuz
I can boost some enterprise”
“Rooms flare up when I jump
on the mic”
“Walked on the yacht with a chica
on my right”
“The life I am living is
a hella pretty sight”
“Hey, I am so fly, you know”
“Life’s going so high,
how’d you know?”
“You never thought
I could spit fires you know”
“I am making the whole cry,
you know”
“Hey, I am so fly, you know”
“Life’s going so high,
how’d you know?”
“You never thought
I could spit fires you know”
“Now the whole world knows
I am style you know…”
“Let the sky fall
let the earth cave in”
“Our song still goes on, ho ho!”