Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
Yes?
Hello.
- I'm going down.
- Me too.
CUSTODY
I'll read Julien's statement.
This hearing was postponed to take it.
A word about his statement.
When we send children
to family mediation services
- I'll explain if you don't know -
we tell them that what they say
will be shared with their parents.
If they don't want something shared,
they mustn't say it.
It's a matter of due process.
Everyone must be fully informed.
Julien is 11. He's in 6th grade
at Monod Junior High in Saint-Dumont.
He said:
"My parents separated a year ago.
I live with Mom and my sister.
"There's a party
for my sister's 18th birthday.
"We live with Papy and Nana
except my father.
"Mom doesn't help with homework.
I'm a good student.
"I have lots of friends
and get by fine."
Where was I?
"...lots of friends and get by fine.
"I can't play outside.
We're scared that man will come.
"Papy screams. It's not good for him.
"When he comes, I worry about Mom.
All he wants
"is to harass her."
Listen to what I'm saying.
You can speak to your lawyer later.
"I worry about Mom.
He wants to hurt her.
"He's no father.
I'm glad they're divorcing.
"I can't leave my mom and sister alone."
Bad reason.
"Josephine dislikes him
but she's old enough to not see him.
"I won't see him either
"or be forced to
every other week
"or weekend.
"I won't see him again.
That's all."
Counselor, you may speak.
So...
Mrs. Besson receives...
an unemployment check
of 981 euros a month.
She's married to Antoine Besson,
who's in charge of fire safety
at Lecorney hospital.
He makes 2,200 euros a month.
They have two children.
Josephine will be 18,
so custody doesn't concern her.
But we have to establish
a new life for Julien.
It's why we took his statement.
We don't agree
with the other side's request.
Mr. Besson wants joint custody
once he moves to the area,
now that he was transferred here.
But as we can clearly observe,
the children don't want
to see their father again.
It's true that...
Julien expresses this desire
a bit forcefully.
He rejects his father.
His statement indicates tension
between the spouses,
but also extreme insecurity.
His own.
The case shows
why these children feel unsafe.
I provided
Josephine's medical certificate,
which shows the violence
she was subjected to
by her father.
So we ask that the children
reside permanently with their mother.
Josephine is almost an adult.
She can visit her father
as she wishes.
But we also ask
the same thing for Julien.
Until things calm down
and until he wants
to see his father again.
All this increases stress.
My client withdrew her complaint
to be conciliatory.
He threatened her
to make her withdraw it.
He'd call, go to her parents' house,
sleep in his car.
Do you have proof?
Her parents testified that he came...
I mean proof of threats.
No witnesses of course.
No messages saved.
She changed numbers repeatedly.
So, to be conciliatory yet again,
my client is not asking for alimony.
However, she is living with her parents.
She left everything she owned
personally and jointly
in their former home.
She must start from scratch.
She has no savings.
Yes, she's at her parents',
but she pays rent, helps out
and bears the cost of the children.
She has immediate
and essential expenses
to find a place to live.
So she requests an advance
of 5,000 euros
on her share of common property.
We request that you obligate
her husband to pay this.
Otherwise, we agree
to child support
totaling 110 per month, per child.
That's all I have on behalf of...
both the children and their mother.
Your turn, Counselor.
Thank you, Your Honor.
Julien said certain things
against his father,
but much has been read
into his statement.
I don't understand
the point of this hearing.
Nothing here is black and white.
Education is the responsibility
of both parents.
I'm shocked by what I just heard.
Mr. Besson was transferred
and requests joint custody
only to be accused of harassment,
of threats,
of violence against his daughter,
with a note from a school nurse
as proof?
I find it stupefying
and extremely inappropriate.
In my file,
you'll find several affidavits.
My client's parents,
also victims of her whims,
deprived of their grandkids
since the separation.
His colleagues, who describe him
as an excellent team leader,
well-balanced, calm, even-tempered.
Affidavits from members
of his hunting club,
describing him as generous, obliging,
a nature lover who doesn't drink.
A normal man,
who bears no resemblance
to the violent, threatening boor
portrayed here.
If Mrs. Besson has proof of threats,
let her show them
and the police can investigate.
But "harassment" and "threats"
don't describe
a hurt father reaching out
to his kids.
And I'm measuring my words.
Mrs. Besson severed all ties
with my client overnight.
And since then,
she's refused to let him
talk to his children.
Her parents' number is now unlisted.
Yes, it's true.
Mr. Besson did indeed sleep in his car
in front of her parents' house.
It's true.
Hoping to see his children,
not for the fun of sleeping in a car.
I can assure you that Mr. Besson is...
astounded to hear what Julien thinks.
His son's words don't reflect
their time together.
Given the context,
we can suspect they're someone else's.
This is what Mr. Besson says now:
"My daughter is an adult.
"She'll make up her mind
about seeing me.
"But I won't abandon my son.
"I love him. He loves me.
And he needs me.
"I'm leaving my job,
colleagues, friends.
"I'm selling my house to be near my son,
"to keep enjoying time together."
Mrs. Besson can't take that away.
It's a child's basic right.
She claims he wasn't a good husband
but it doesn't mean he's a bad father.
The law doesn't allow us
to break the father-son bond.
So we still request the same thing.
A standard visitation schedule.
Every other weekend,
from noon Saturday to Sunday at 6 pm.
And when my client lives in the area,
joint physical custody:
every other week and shared vacations.
So we need her future address.
Unless she leaves on a whim again.
This is all to make
Julien's new life easier.
Otherwise, we agree to their request
for child support.
But we ask that you rule, Your Honor,
on paragraph 7 of article 255:
"A spouse may receive an advance
on the liquidation of marriage property
if necessary."
I'd like to know
if it's necessary or not.
One spouse worked full-time
and is now unemployed,
but it was her choice
to leave and come here.
Each time my client asked
to see his children,
he was told
they left for the weekend.
She claims she's broke,
just 900 a month,
yet takes weekend trips
and plans a big birthday party.
The situation
doesn't justify this advance.
- Did you provide a balance sheet?
- Yes, Your Honor.
All right.
Let's begin
with Josephine's medical certificate.
What happened?
She was in 9th grade.
He kept an eye on her,
wouldn't let her date.
He saw her kissing Samuel
at the Conservatory.
She plays piano since she's 6.
Samuel is her boyfriend.
That day she skipped school
to go see him.
He caught them by surprise.
He waited till she got home that night
and he hit her.
I was at work and he called,
threatening to break her hands...
if I didn't go straight home.
And so...
she was in pain, and...
The next day she saw the nurse
to tell her about the problems at home.
All right.
Sir?
She sprained her wrist at the gym.
What can I say?
Which of you is the bigger liar?
Look at the certificate, Your Honor.
3 years later.
"I, Stephanie Bossel,
"examined Josephine Besson
on October 12, 2013.
"She had pain in the left wrist,
resulting in limited movement.
"Pressure on the scaphoid
and 5th metacarpal
"caused pain and a bruise
on the inside of the wrist.
"She mentioned problems
with her father.
"After discussion,
she decided not to use this note,
"written at her request
and sent by mail."
Mrs. Besson's former boss
also testified
that he often spied on her
at her workplace.
- Unbelievable!
- Please.
Your children have turned against you.
Can you explain?
No.
I'd like to understand.
I don't know what they're told.
We can see
Julien is not ready to see his father.
It's too stressful.
- You make things worse.
- Stop, Counselor.
You're the only person
losing your temper.
Mr. Besson bought Julien a phone
and yet he still has no contact.
Julien won't answer.
He tells Julien to put me on.
Julien stopped answering.
We just want peace.
I just want news of my kids.
Who just wants peace?
Excuse me?
"We just want peace."
Who's "we"?
Julien...
me, my daughter too.
Ask her, you'll see.
"Ask your daughter".
Your children seem to be on your side.
That's unfortunate.
Julien asked to give a statement
when he learned
his father was moving here.
I just want everything to go well.
I think of my kids' well-being.
May I speak?
Sir?
I think of his well-being too.
He needs supervision.
Taking away his father won't help.
Your lawyers will receive my decision
on May 29th.
Goodbye.
Thank you.
Hearings like this are always grueling.
I'll call you once I have her decision.
I'm confident.
She understands how the children feel...
Antoine!
- So?
- What a jerk.
I'll be contacting you.
Goodbye.
It went well.
Miriam!
For the kids.
It's up to the judge now.
- When will we know?
- A week.
- Go on. She'll kill you.
- I don't care.
- I'm at the Conservatory.
- I'm coming, Mom.
We got out early so I saw Samuel off.
Stop lying.
Your teacher said you never came.
Fifth time in 2 months.
Each time Samuel comes.
Why do I pay for your classes?
- I've had enough.
- I don't trust you anymore.
We'll have a serious discussion,
believe me.
It's over here.
Come in...
So, there are three bedrooms.
About 840 square feet.
This is the foyer.
A separate toilet there.
In the foyer, the intercom,
an electricity meter.
Separate toilet.
Wardrobe, closet... and the living room.
This is my room.
I'll have a double bed.
You sleep together?
What the hell do you care?
Is it him?
So?
- This is my room.
- Dream on!
Samuel can't come over,
so why a big bed?
Just like that man.
Don't start up.
Auntie?
- Who's he?
- Cyril, a colleague at City Hall.
He found this apartment for you.
- What is it?
- I won't make it.
You'll see him soon.
At your birthday.
- She's so unfair.
- You need to concentrate.
I promised I'd stop skipping class.
Come on.
I don't see myself here.
Come on, you'll fix up your room.
It'll be fine.
Come.
You can go have a look.
You're only 10 minutes from downtown.
There's a bus station below...
Excuse me.
- It's available?
- First of the month.
Hello, Counselor.
- Excuse me.
- No problem.
Yes, Counselor?
Really?
Why?
Miriam?
- What's going on?
- He doesn't feel well. He can't come.
Come out to talk.
- He has a stomach ache.
- I'll take him to the doctor.
- But...
- Come give me the address.
I don't want trouble.
No trouble.
The judge ruled, period.
Antoine, he's really sick.
Come out and we'll talk.
No, I won't come out.
I have him this weekend.
If he doesn't come...
I'll file a complaint.
Am I being clear?
What did he say?
Bye-bye, Juju.
Hello, sweetie.
Hello.
So I hear you're sick?
Your mom said you were sick.
Do you have any medicine?
Talk to me.
Put on your seatbelt.
- You're a growing boy!
- You barely ate.
We're going hunting early.
No, next time.
He's not feeling well.
Then there's no use insisting.
Bring us our coffee.
Blandine asked about her wedding again.
- When is it?
- Next Saturday.
I don't have Juju.
I can't drive another 600 miles.
Answer her.
So she can plan.
We can switch weekends.
You see?
She'd love to see you two.
I made a surprise for you.
Dad?
Let's switch weekends.
I'd like to go to Josephine's party
the weekend after.
You want to?
We have an hour.
Because I picked you up an hour late.
Who calls me "that man"?
Me.
Does your mother say it too?
No, just me.
And your sister?
Want to go to her party?
Why is your mother using you to ask me?
She can't ask me?
With a normal mom,
we can discuss things, don't you think?
She should ask.
Why doesn't she?
She has no cell phone.
Give me your notebook.
Give it to me.
Her number doesn't work.
Give me your notebook.
Julien, your notebook.
- Hello?
- It's that man.
- Is Julien with you?
- Yeah, he's here.
He asked to switch weekends
so he can go to the party
in two weeks.
- Where did you get my number?
- Answer me.
It would be nice if he could go.
Don't you think
you should ask me yourself?
- Listen...
- It's not that hard.
Can we switch weekends
so he can go?
Please.
I'm on my way. We'll discuss it.
Hey, Juju. How are you?
- He won't switch weekends.
- He said so?
- Because of his job.
- Fuck!
Asshole!
Why is he still there?
- Relax!
- Must I go outside?
I forgot my bag. I'll go get it.
She's not home.
You've reached 06 14 87...
Didn't I say she's not normal?
- She's not home.
- Where is she?
Can I get my bag?
I forgot it.
You won't go to the party thanks to her.
You'll be with me.
Tell me once you've done it.
Okay. I love you.
Erase contact "Mom"?
Hey sweetie, how are you?
Can you get your mother, please?
Julien?
I'll let you go to the party tonight.
She needs to tell me
when to drop you off.
She's not home.
Yes, she is.
She's not home!
Then where is she?
Where is she?
Up your ass!
- Can you help?
- I'm going to drop my bags.
Hello, my boy.
- How long are you leaving this?
- Until I get the keys.
Your mother made you rabbit.
So where is your apartment?
10 minutes from the new hospital.
It's nice.
A balcony, a room for Julien.
When does the hospital open?
I already told you. September.
And I'll start then.
Will you still come visit?
The Dutrieuxs say hi.
We saw them at the wedding.
Are they doing okay?
We saw Laetitia too. My God...
She won't find a guy like that.
Last time we saw her
was two years ago.
Regis' birthday party.
God knows how much she weighs.
She let herself go.
She doesn't have an easy life.
She lives all alone.
- No excuse.
- Works nights.
When she gets home,
it must be... 7am.
She said she saw you.
On her way home, with Josephine.
- Where does she live?
- The projects.
Why were you there?
Remember Laetitia?
It wasn't us.
You got in a bus.
Why were you there?
- What were you doing?
- No big deal.
Why where you there?
To see Josephine's friend.
But you got in a bus.
We were leaving her place.
To go where?
- Stop, Antoine.
- To go where?
School.
- Stop, Antoine.
- Shut up.
You saw her friend before school?
Answer me!
Stop it!
You always have to fuck things up!
Stupid idiot! You spoil everything!
It could have been nice.
You make it impossible!
Why must this happen each time?
It's no surprise
that your kids won't see you!
What'll you do now?
- What are you doing?
- Get your stuff.
Don't you ever set foot here again!
Julien!
Are you happy now?
Do you think I'm a fool?
You live in the projects?
No.
You're as big a liar as your mom.
You're no dumber than before, are you?
Look at me when I talk.
Is it her boyfriend's place?
She's holding a bomb
that'll blow up in her face.
She's not allowed to do any of this!
Understand?
She'll pay for it big-time
if she keeps playing me for a fool!
I'm your father!
I need to know where you live!
Look at me when I talk!
Look at me!
Where is it?
Straight ahead.
And now?
Straight.
Left.
What floor are you on?
Second.
Right.
Left.
It's her boyfriend's place?
She has no boyfriend.
Over there.
That one? There?
This one?
Give me your keys.
Come with me.
Leave your bags. Come.
Entrance refused.
Wait!
Stop!
Come on.
I'm driving you back.
Sweetie, I don't want trouble
every weekend.
Get in!
Come on, get in.
Where are we going?
Didn't you want to go
to your sister's party?
Can I have my keys?
I just called Laetitia.
She said she saw you here.
I don't want you to hit Mom.
I'll find it by myself.
What floor are you on?
Eighth.
Hello, ma'am.
I'm not interrupting?
What do you want?
To see where my kids live.
I have to go now.
- Where's my daughter?
- At the reception hall.
I've changed.
I have to go.
I'll pick him up tomorrow.
No problem.
What time should I come?
We're sleeping at my parents'.
11 o'clock?
All right.
Don't say he came.
Say I bumped into you in town.
- What's that?
- You don't make the law here.
Where's Julien?
At his mom's.
I'll pick him up tomorrow.
Staying for dinner?
It seems I'm not welcome.
Do as you please.
What did you and Josephine decide?
A song before or after the cake?
After.
Can we serve it now?
She wants to wait for Manon.
Where's Manon?
She'll call
when she gets off the highway.
You can't drive 300 miles tonight.
It's fine. I can drive.
You can stay at Nana's.
Don't worry. It's kind of you.
I prefer to drive. I planned on it.
You two can see each other,
but she can't skip classes.
She has to graduate.
You understand?
Yes, of course.
So we'll wait for Manon.
What are you doing, Miriam?
Have you seen Julien?
He must be inside.
Come on,
Josephine is going to sing!
Why are you here?
My dad mustn't see you.
I have a gift for Josephine.
I'll give it to her.
I left it in my car.
Give it to her tomorrow
when you get Julien?
Isn't it humiliating enough
for me to be here?
What am I?
What's that stare?
What am I to you?
I can't reach you.
You change numbers.
You run away from me.
Who am I for you?
I won't talk about the same old stuff...
You will, because we had two kids!
When you vanish, you hurt me.
You know it.
You need help.
The nerve of you!
You're the one who needs help!
Coming!
Who's he?
My sister's friend.
I'm coming.
Why is he at my daughter's party?
I'll deal with the cake.
Cyril... Nice to meet you.
I'm talking to my wife.
- Have a nice evening.
- I'm coming.
Give me Josephine's present.
You're such a tease.
Let go of me!
Who is he?
- Who is he?
- Stop it.
Have you fucked him?
- Stop.
- Tell me.
Let go of her!
We're just talking.
Leave her alone! Fuck off!
I'm very calm.
Beat it, prick.
Touch her again and I'll kill you!
- Kiss the kids for me.
- Fuck off!
I'm not talking to you.
Fuck off
or I'll call the cops, asshole!
What a loser.
- The prick left. He hit you.
- I'm fine.
- File a complaint.
- What for?
I'll come with you.
This has to end.
Come on...
- I'm sorry.
- Don't be.
Maybe I shouldn't come over tonight.
Hi, ma'am.
What a pain to find this place.
- Hey, Manon. Hungry?
- Starving.
There's plenty to eat.
It's up to you.
My granddaughter!
What is it now?
I just don't want to.
Let's say goodbye to your sister.
See you tomorrow.
- Can I drop you off?
- Cyril will.
Julien's staying with you?
Pick you up at 10.
You'll be okay?
Goodnight.
- He's not coming to Nana's?
- Not anymore.
Go to sleep. I'll clean up tomorrow.
I'll just straighten up the equipment,
the cables...
- Don't keep Papy up.
- We have a key.
Sleep well, kids.
Goodnight, Mom.
Goodnight.
See you tomorrow.
- Is it him?
- What do you think?
- Go to sleep.
- Can I sleep with you?
Come.
When he gets fed up, he'll leave.
Did he leave?
I think so.
Mom...
Our conversation isn't over.
Open up!
Open!
Open the door!
B-O-U-H-A-D-D-I.
- Bouhaddi.
- We're on the way.
TN-821 for 71...
Yes?
Saint-Dumont, 9 rue Winston Churchill.
I repeat: Saint-Dumont,
9 rue Winston Churchill.
Someone is forcing open a door.
The neighbor says he has a large weapon,
like a hunting rifle.
It's taking place on the 8th floor.
Use the intercom to enter the building.
The name is "Bouhaddi".
Bravo-Oscar-Uniform...
Dad, stop!
Antoine, please stop!
- Open up!
- Antoine, stop!
Mommy, I can't hear anything!
I can't hear anything, Mommy!
- What's the emergency?
- He fired!
What's the address?
He'll kill us!
Where are you?
He shot at the door!
I need your address. What address?
- Antoine, stop!
- Open up!
I need your address.
9 rue Winston Churchill.
A car is coming.
Do you know who fired?
My husband.
- You're not alone?
- With my son.
Antoine, stop!
Keep calm.
Do you have a room that locks?
Yes.
Go lock yourselves inside.
Open up!
Help is on the way.
Where are you?
In the bathroom.
Did you lock the door?
Can you block the door?
He's inside.
Listen to me, ma'am.
Do you have a bathtub?
Lie down in it with your son.
Take cover.
Get inside. Hurry up...
Get down.
More, more.
Stay on the phone.
You're not alone. I'm with you.
I'm with you. Don't worry.
A car is coming.
Just a few seconds. It's almost over.
Stay in the tub. Don't come out.
Open up.
Police! Drop your weapon!
Stay put. The police are there.
You're in a safe place.
Don't move, okay?
You're under arrest. Calm down!
Don't move!
It's over, ma'am.
Stay on the phone with me.
She's my wife!
Don't let them do this to me!
Get him out of here!
It's over, ma'am.
Hear me?
It's over.
I'll hang up.
The officer will take care of you.
All right?
Ma'am, can you hear me?
Can you please open the door?
It's over. You can come out.
Are you okay? Are you wounded?
Call an ambulance. Come...
We've secured the premises.
Two victims.
One is wounded.
Send us an ambulance. Thanks.
Copy that.
Subtitles: Andrew Litvack
Subtitling TITRAFILM