[THUNDERING CRASH]
[RUMBLING SOUND]
[JONAS, WHISPERING] I promise you.
I'll make this right.
[CRASHING SOUND]
[SOBBING]
- [THUNDERING CRASH]
- [GLASS SHATTERS]
- [CRASHING CONTINUES]
- [WIND HOWLS]
[CLATTERING]
[GASPS, PANTING]
[SUSTAINED, HIGH-PITCHED NOTE]
[MARTHA] Dear Jonas,
you promised
to make everything right again.
[GENTLE, MELANCHOLY MUSIC PLAYS]
I want you to know that you will do that.
You must never lose hope
that there is a way out of this maze.
A way to save me...
and you.
But we will have to make sacrifices...
do unimaginable things...
to untie the knot at the end.
Each fate in this knot
is linked to the next.
A thread,
blood-red,
that connects all our actions.
In light...
[BREATHING RAPIDLY]
And in shadow.
Why is Adam doing this?
[LOCK CLICKS]
Why are you locking me up?
[MARTHA] But the apocalypse...
must take place.
You must let me die,
so I can live.
We have to let some things go
before they find their way back to us.
You and I are perfect for each other.
Never believe anything else.
["GOODBYE" BY APPARAT PLAYS]
♪ Fold out your hands
Give me a sign ♪
♪ Put down your lies ♪
♪ Lay down next to me ♪
♪ Don't listen when I scream ♪
♪ Bury your doubts and fall asleep ♪
♪ For neither ever ♪
♪ Nor never ♪
♪ Goodbye ♪
♪ Neither ever ♪
♪ Nor never ♪
♪ Goodbye ♪
♪ Neither ever ♪
♪ Nor never ♪
♪ Goodbye ♪
LIGHT AND SHADOW
DAY OF THE APOCALYPSE
[DOOR OPENS]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[BREATHING RAPIDLY]
[DULL HAMMERING SOUND REPEATS]
[GASPING IN PANIC]
[GASPING]
[DOOR OPENS]
[GASPING RAPIDLY FOR AIR]
[MAGNUS] Martha.
Man, where were you?
Mom cried all night long.
Are you okay?
Hey.
What happened?
[MARTHA GASPING]
What's wrong?
Bartosz was right.
What he told us in the woods,
about the end of the world.
[GASPING]
The nuclear power plant. Today.
Bartosz' father is trying
to cover up an accident.
The containers.
I know this sounds insane, but...
The world is going to end today.
What? Have you gone crazy?
When did you last sleep?
[YELLING] Are you hearing
what I'm saying? The...
I haven't got time for your psycho crap.
I don't know what's going on with you.
But Mom doesn't deserve any of this.
None of it.
[DOOR CLOSES]
[GASPS]
[DARK, DISSONANT MUSIC PLAYS]
[CLICK]
[OLDER MARTHA] He had to die.
You're all wrong.
In this world.
And in ours.
I know what you're feeling.
But you'll learn to let the feeling go.
Everything will run its course.
Just as fate determined.
For our world.
And his.
[DOOR SLAMS SHUT]
[MARTHA PANTING LOUDLY]
[SCREAMS] Why did you lock me up?
You promised me there would be a way
to change everything.
[CRYING] So the apocalypse won't happen.
You lied to me,
just like my older self lied to me.
[GASPING]
[ADAM] Sic Mundus.
Old Tannhaus.
He firmly believed
he was creating a paradise
where we'd all be free of destiny,
and free of our pain.
A world outside your world and my world.
But I...
have finally realized
what this paradise really is.
Unending darkness,
in which nothing exists.
[SOBS]
[ADAM] But for that...
the apocalypse must happen.
In my world...
and in yours.
[YELLING] Jonas!
Jonas!
Let me out! Jonas!
[THUD]
6 HOURS UNTIL THE APOCALYPSE
[ALEKSANDER] Where are the containers?
I want you to wait.
I don't care.
You do what I say, Obendorf.
Understand?
Dad. Is everything okay?
I know I... I said I'd stay home today.
But something important came up.
I'm sorry.
That's all right.
I have to tell you something.
Someone is blackmailing me.
What?
Using this.
Something that happened long ago.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYS]
MURDER IN MARBURG
STILL UNSOLVED 33 YEARS LATER
Sometimes we make decisions
in our lives that we can never undo.
My name is not Aleksander.
It is Boris.
Boris Niewald.
But it was an accident.
You must believe me.
I'm not a murderer.
What about Mom?
Does Mom know about this?
Your mother is the best thing
that ever happened in my life.
She saved me from all that.
And I never told her the truth.
Bartosz.
I'm sorry.
[BARTOSZ WALKS AWAY]
[DOOR BELL RINGING]
[DOOR OPENS]
- [HANNAH] Charlotte?
- [CHARLOTTE] May I come in for a moment?
Thank you.
I came to see Ulrich real quick.
Is he here?
No, he's taking a shower.
Could I wait here? It's important.
How are you?
Okay.
At home?
Everything fine?
[QUIET, MENACING MUSIC PLAYS]
Listen, I should tell you,
Ulrich belongs to me.
And that will never change.
[FOOTFALLS ON STAIRS]
Charlotte.
- What brings you here?
- I wanted to show you this file.
Come by with Peter sometime.
We could all go out together.
While I still can. [CHUCKLES]
- Done in the bathroom?
- Of course.
- What are you doing here?
- Your cell was off.
Don't ever do that again.
Don't ever come here unannounced.
The forensic examination
of the two pennies is in.
And...
And?
And what?
WINDEN POLICE EVIDENCE
This is the penny I found in the bunker.
And this is the penny Helge had on him.
I believed it was a mistake at first.
That the photos were labeled wrong.
But this here,
this indentation here...
They're exactly identical.
I don't know how,
but it's one and the same penny.
But this one here,
Helge's had it as long as I've known him.
I know it doesn't make any sense... but...
But?
It's as if the penny...
As if it traveled through time.
- Where's Helge now?
- Still in pre-trial custody.
Ulrich!
[DOOR SHUTS]
[WIND WHISTLES]
[BREATHING RAPIDLY]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYS]
[MUSIC FADES]
[GASPS]
[WHISPERING] Gave me a scare.
Where were you?
Did you cut your hair?
What happened?
Do you believe in fate?
[SIGHS]
I don't know.
Um...
No.
I believe
that we take our lives into our own hands.
That we decide which road we take.
I know I...
I'm sure I'm the last person
you want to talk to, but...
If you do...
I'm here.
Your dad and I...
A lot of things might be different now.
But that's not necessarily all bad.
[SIGHS]
No, I'm sure it's not.
Are you going out?
I promised I'd do something.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC BUILDING]
[HISS, THUD]
[QUIET BREATHING]
WINDEN NUCLEAR POWER PLANT
GOD PARTICLE
FOLLOW THE SIGNAL
[WIND HOWLS]
- [DOOR SLAMS SHUT]
- [GEIGER COUNTER CLICKING]
[BEEPING, CLICKING]
[CLAUDIA PANTING LIGHTLY]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYS]
[GEIGER COUNTER CLICKING]
[QUIET BUBBLING SOUND]
[GEIGER COUNTER ACCELERATES]
[MAN] Stop!
Jonas.
You're alive.
[HISS, THUD]
I murdered him.
Why is he still alive in his world?
There's a switch point...
in the loop of time.
[THUNDER CRASHES]
[EVE] The moment...
that causes things
to run in one direction or the other.
You bring him to our world.
Or you don't.
A line that starts at one point,
then loops into itself once more.
Two possible ways.
On the outer edge of the line
or on the inner edge of the line.
And yet it is the same line.
Two overlapping realities.
On one of these roads, he dies.
On the other, he doesn't.
Both realities continue here,
repeating endlessly in the loop.
One triggers the other.
Quantum entanglement.
Adam has tried
to sever it for 33 years.
So that the thing growing inside you
will never be born.
But it's impossible.
Our worlds
can never be disconnected.
Every step Jonas takes is guided by us.
He cannot escape his fate.
[HISS, THUD]
[QUIET CLICKING]
[CLAUDIA] What is this?
This was left over.
After the catastrophe.
The God particle.
And this here?
What is this?
I've seen where all this goes.
In the future.
There's no way back now.
The cave was destroyed.
There's nothing anymore,
the passage is completely gone.
But this here...
If I find out how it works,
I'll be able to go back.
Then I can save them. Martha and Mikkel.
I can save them all.
How was it you found me?
How did you know I would be here?
The apparatus.
- The matter it needs.
- The apparatus. You have it still?
Where is it?
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
- [SWITCH CLICKING]
- [CLAUDIA] It doesn't work.
Maybe this is how it had to happen first.
For things to change next time.
The substance in the device.
You and I brought it
into the passage again.
The variables
in the equation were changed.
- There's a chance it might work next try.
- I can't wait 33 years to try!
I'm supposed to just hope
this won't happen again?
Maybe next time
I'm on the other side of the bunker door?
She didn't say anything.
Your older self.
She knew Martha would die.
How she would die.
Why should I trust you now?
The material at the plant.
I know what it is.
I can assist you.
I can help you to save Martha.
To save them all.
[HISS, THUD]
3 HOURS UNTIL THE APOCALYPSE
[MELANCHOLY MUSIC PLAYS]
Bartosz!
[BARTOSZ] Martha?
Can I come in?
Uh... Yeah.
[MARTHA, SHAKILY] 33 years ago
there was an accident at the plant.
Somehow...
the accident caused
some strange matter to form.
And your father helped
to cover everything up. [GASPING]
All the things we heard in the caves.
It's all the same.
The substance...
It starts the end.
Today.
We have to talk to him.
Starts what end?
The apocalypse.
POLICE
IDENTITY UNKNOWN
[PATHOLOGIST] Time of death must have been
immediately before the body was found.
Is it possible
that he'd been dead for a long time?
That his body had been preserved somehow?
Seriously?
What do you mean "preserved"?
[EERIE MUSIC PLAYS]
Everything okay?
[ULRICH] The scar on his chin...
Ulrich?
[MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
- [DOOR UNLOCKS]
- [KEYS JINGLE]
[HELGE GRUNTS]
The kid in the bunker.
You said it was you who killed him.
But you didn't mean him.
You meant Mads.
The boy in the bunker
looks just like Mads.
How can that be?
She... She said that I must do it.
Who?
Do what?
Send him to the future.
To fill the gaps.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYS]
[ULRICH] The pennies...
What does this mean?
- I must stop him.
- Stop who?
Who will you stop?
You.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYS]
You can go now.
[DOOR CLOSES]
[BARTOSZ] And this Jonas guy is dead now?
And you killed him there.
Well, not you. It was...
another you?
[QUIETLY] I was there.
In the future.
There's nothing left.
Nothing.
It all has to do with your father.
He can't be allowed
to open the containers.
Bartosz.
Please.
[PHONE VIBRATES]
INCOMING CALL BARTOSZ
CALL ENDED
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYS]
[TYPING ON PHONE]
Charlotte, Aleksander here.
I...
Can you get to the plant?
I want to show you something.
[BUBBLING, SWOOSHING SOUND]
[CRANKING SOUND]
[HISSING OF ELECTRICITY]
[CRASHING SOUNDS]
[NOISE SUBSIDES]
[TWO METALLIC BEATS SOUND]
- [BUBBLING, SWOOSHING SOUND]
- [BEATS REPEAT]
[METALLIC BEATS REPEAT]
[HISS, THUD]
- Come out.
- [MARTHA PANTING]
Adam's waiting for you.
Stop.
Take it off!
- What?
- Your clothes.
Get undressed.
[MENACING MUSIC PLAYS]
Why are you doing as he says?
We chosen few must fill the gaps.
So that you find your way here
and Adam his.
And we finally reach salvation.
[ADAM] We have waited
a long time for this moment.
You know what to do.
- [CLATTERING]
- [BUZZING]
[SIREN-LIKE BLARING]
[HISS, THUD]
[SOFT, SAD MUSIC PLAYS]
1 HOUR UNTIL THE APOCALYPSE
What do you think it means?
The birds? The light?
The boy in the bunker?
[MOUTHING] Martha is losing it.
She thinks
the apocalypse will happen today.
[MOUTHING] If we die today, then together.
Together.
[TWO METALLIC BEATS SOUND]
[BEATS REPEATING]
What's going on?
It's better if you see for yourself.
- [HELGE, WHISPERING] Tick... tock.
- [BEATS REPEATING]
Tick... tock.
- [METALLIC BEATS CONTINUE]
- Tick... tock.
- [BEATS CONTINUE]
- [SINISTER MUSIC PLAYS]
Charlotte, it's me.
Listen, the penny stuff...
I know it sounds crazy, but...
It's the same thing
with the kid in the bunker, I think.
Test a DNA sample.
I don't know how, but...
The kid in the bunker, he's my brother.
It's Mads.
Call me back ASAP please.
[BEATS CONTINUE]
Who are you?
[MAGNUS] Can't you guess?
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYS]
[MARTHA BREATHING HEAVILY]
Magnus?
[MARTHA GASPS]
You're from the future.
But not from yours.
What's going on?
[MAGNUS] They lied to you.
Your older selves.
They want the apocalypse to happen.
They're the ones who are responsible
for it happening in the first place.
But there is a way to change everything.
[FRANZISKA]
But you have to choose our world.
And trust in him.
Jonas.
Jonas is alive?
In our world.
And he knows where the origin is.
But before that, you must save Jonas
from the apocalypse in his world
and bring him into your world.
You're all crazy you know that!
[MAGNUS] You can't stop
what's happening now, but...
if you come with us,
you can prevent it.
Another time.
[BARTOSZ] What is that?
Martha, what's going on here?
Martha?
You've got to come with us.
- Come with you where?
- He's not one of us.
He's one of the others.
[DEVICE WHIRRING]
They will save him.
I'm sorry.
[BARTOSZ] Martha, wait!
[MUFFLED BANG]
[EVE] It's time.
Adam has moved
each of his tokens into position.
It's time
we do the same.
This knot has given us all life.
And we are its keepers.
In both worlds.
He'll never be able to untie this knot.
In all these years, he's never understood
how everything is connected.
- [BUBBLING, SWOOSHING SOUND]
- How it all ends and begins.
Not only in our world,
but also in his.
We are...
destiny.
We raise the walls
of this labyrinth.
Each of us shapes the paths
and extends their hand.
Bartosz, you must save yourself
to save our lives.
Claudia, you must guide yourself
to be our eyes in the other world.
Egon, you must create your past...
to preserve the family tree.
Noah,
you bring love...
to make everything new.
Every darkness is followed by light.
With every death comes a life.
[CRACKLING OF ELECTRICITY]
[HISS, THUD]
[MARTHA, CRYING]
You brought me into your world.
You promised me I could change it. [SOBS]
Why are you doing this?
[MARTHA SOBS]
Where are the others?
Where did you send them?
They are all fulfilling their destinies.
Magnus and Franziska.
Charlotte and Elisabeth.
Silja and Agnes.
They're sustaining the cycle's life.
So that you and I exist here, now.
What are you saying?
This is the end we've reached.
[QUIET, MENACING MUSIC PLAYS]
What's growing inside you,
the origin,
must die.
But it can't be killed by normal means.
It's born of both worlds.
And the energy of both worlds is necessary
to destroy it.
The apocalypse in my world...
and the apocalypse in your world.
This here is the end.
A machine that crosses not only time,
but space as well.
Which focuses
the energy of both apocalypses...
on this one point, concentrated.
Your son only exists...
because the matter exists.
Now, through it, he will die,
and all of us with him.
None of this...
will exist anymore.
Both worlds will erase one another.
Absolute annihilation.
You've gone insane!
There is no hope.
No salvation.
No paradise.
[SOBBING]
We're wrong.
You and I.
In your world...
and in mine.
Jonas.
Jonas!
[CRYING] Jonas, please don't do it.
[YELLING] Jonas!
[SOBBING] Don't. Jonas, please!
Jonas!
Jonas, please!
["THE PIONEERS (M83 REMIX)"
BY BLOC PARTY PLAYS]
[MARTHA WHIMPERING]
Jonas!
[PUSHES LEVER]
[THUNDERING CRASH OF ELECTRICITY]
No! No!
[EVE] The beginning is the end...
and the end is the beginning.
Every connection in one world...
must also be closed in the other world.
Everything is interconnected.
In light...
and in shadow.
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
[ROLL OF THUNDER]
POLICE
♪ Breathe in ♪
[BUZZING SOUND]
MACHINE FACTORY TANNHAUS
♪ Breathe in ♪
[GRUNTS]
[SIGHS]
[CRASHING SOUNDS]
[BEEPING]
[MARTHA SCREAMING]
VOLUME CONTROL ROOM
♪ It's under control ♪
♪ All you need is time ♪
♪ All you need is ♪
♪ Time ♪
[QUIET TICKING]
♪ It's all under control
It's all under control ♪
♪ Then it can be turned
All you need is time ♪
♪ All you need is time
♪ All you need is ♪
♪ We promised the world we'd tame it ♪
LET THERE BE LIGHT
♪ A sense of purpose
And a sense of skill ♪
♪ A sense of function but a disregard
We will not be the first ♪
♪ We will not be the first
[ALARM SOUNDS]
♪ We promised the world we'd tame it ♪
♪ What were we hoping for? ♪
[MARTHA] No!
♪ We promised the world we'd tame it ♪
♪ What were we hoping for? ♪
♪ Breathe in, breathe in ♪
[ALARM SOUNDS]
[CRACKING OF ELECTRICITY]
[ROARING SOUND]
♪ Breathe in, breathe in ♪
[SCREAMS]
[MARTHA GASPING]
[SCREAMING]
[ALARM SOUNDS]
[SOUNDS INTENSIFYING]
[SCREAMING]
[THUNDERING CRASH]
[RUMBLING SOUND]
[INTENSIFYING]
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYS]