THE ORIGIN
We are attracted
to the dark like moths to the light.
The dark is what we are born out of,
and so we return to it.
You've grown, Tronte.
Do I know you?
I knew your mother.
But that was long ago.
You take after her.
Your eyes.
Who are you?
I don't have a name.
I was never given one.
But back then it was me
who chose what to call you.
It belonged to your mother.
I think you should have it now.
I've got to go.
♪ Fold out your hands ♪
♪ Give me a sign ♪
♪ Put down your lies ♪
♪ Lay down next to me ♪
♪ Don't listen when I scream ♪
♪ Bury your doubts and fall asleep ♪
♪ For neither ever ♪
♪ Nor never ♪
♪ Goodbye ♪
♪ Neither ever ♪
♪ Nor never ♪
♪ Goodbye ♪
♪ Neither ever ♪
♪ Nor never ♪
♪ Goodbye ♪
♪ Dann ruft mein Herz dir leise zu ♪
♪ Mein Ideal bist du, nur du ♪
I love you.
♪ Nur dich allein ♪
♪ Wenn ich dich seh ♪
♪ Dann fange ich zu träumen an ♪
I don't know if you'll like it, but...
Can I put it on you?
You don't like it?
No, I...
I do. It's gorgeous.
I don't know.
I haven't felt like myself all week.
You look pale.
Maybe you should see a doctor.
Will you come back here?
I... I don't know yet. It's...
It might be best
for me to stay home tonight.
Katharina...
I'm glad you decided to stay here.
In Winden.
You're beautiful.
♪ Wenn ich dich seh ♪
♪ Dann fange ich zu träumen an ♪
♪ Es tut nur weh ♪
♪ Dass ich es dir nicht sagen kann ♪
♪ Ich weiß, dein Herz... ♪
SENSATIONAL NUDE PHOTOS
Look at her expression.
Where did you get it?
- It was in my father's things.
- Ines, Claudia. We're already late.
My father says
you don't learn anything at school.
You learn from life.
Why don't they have these
with men in them?
- That's not fair, is it?
- You're crazy.
Ever seen one?
- One that's not your father's?
- Ines!
Jana, come on.
What did it look like?
A little odd.
Like it wasn't a part of him.
Tronte?
I think he's kind of weird.
Has his mother returned?
It's strange, don't you think?
To just vanish like that.
POLICE
Doris.
What brings you here?
I wanted to talk.
And Kahnwald let me in here.
Where have you been?
I thought you left early to write reports.
It's, um...
Well...
There's something that came up.
Today...
I was washing clothes
and I found something.
Here. It was with her blouses.
I thought it could be important.
She said her husband was with the church.
And maybe it's just a coincidence,
but the minister who disappeared
at the same time...
his name is Hanno Tauber.
H.T.
WINDEN WELCOMES ITS NEW MINISTER
HANNO TAUBER FROM VECHTA
I...
I thought her husband was dead.
It's three months now.
You don't just leave your child alone
without saying a word.
You should go home. We'll take care of it.
Egon, I know something's going on here!
Why would she have left all this behind?
Who knows what goes on
inside a woman's head.
Doris!
MISSING SINCE JUNE 26, 1954
MRS. AGNES NIELSEN
Agnes, you have chosen the correct side.
Don't forget that.
UNIDENTIFIED WOMAN'S BODY
FOUND IN WOODS
You must give this to Claudia.
When it's time.
To live is a gift.
For those who know how to use it.
You'll tell Martha then?
What the origin really is?
After all these years I've wondered...
why you abandoned us in 1888.
Why you gave us
the material to create it...
and then just disappeared.
Who would've thought 33 years later
it would be us who gave you the order.
Magnus.
I'm so sorry.
It doesn't matter anymore.
Adam is waiting for us.
This is your future.
Thirty-three years from your yesterday.
That door in the cave...
What is that?
It is a path
that connects past and future.
Why are these names crossed out?
It means that they will die.
All of them.
- "All". What does that mean?
- In two days.
The apocalypse in his world.
It also happens in ours.
This is not real.
You're not real.
This is your future.
If you...
If you both fail to stop the apocalypse.
You came recently to Winden?
Three months ago. I like it here.
It's less complicated
than where I come from.
Well, that may be about to change.
You're pregnant.
At your age,
a pregnancy is not without its risks.
You should take care of yourself.
No strenuous activity.
That can't be right.
Listen.
Some gifts
come into our lives unexpectedly.
And yet they're still gifts.
Mrs. Doppler.
How can I help you?
I would like to know
if any news has come in.
Sadly...
Sadly, no.
Unless Helge decides
to tell us where he was...
That is...
who he was with,
we're not going to get anywhere with this.
This isn't about Helge.
This is about the missing minister.
If nobody looks after the church...
it leaves the door open for the devil.
You knew the man?
The minister?
Did he...
Have you ever seen him
in the company of a woman?
How dare you ask that.
I want you to find the man.
Hanno Tauber.
Sorry to disturb you.
Are you the new minister?
I used to be.
But that was long ago.
The thing is, I'm looking for someone.
Um... My husband and I are...
Our daughter is very talented.
Last winter, we sublet the guest room.
So we could save up money for Claudia,
for when she goes to college.
The lady who lived with us...
Well, she vanished, three months ago.
Her husband was a man of God.
She said her husband was dead,
but, I don't know why,
I just felt like that wasn't true.
And the man who worked here
vanished at the same time, so...
What if he was her husband,
and she went back to him?
I don't think she liked him very much.
Not all human bonds
are the result of fondness.
Well, it's about the child.
It's her boy, and...
I think a boy needs his mother.
Each lie we tell
comes at a cost to the human soul.
I don't understand.
You're not interested in the boy.
You're interested in the woman.
I don't think you understood what I...
The ways of the heart cannot be explained.
It wants what it wants.
Just ask your husband.
He'll tell you the same thing.
My husband?
Haven't you asked yourself
why he's been leaving the house so early?
And working so late?
What if there's another woman there?
It's difficult for us to let go...
of our deepest desires, inside.
Hello, Tronte.
Hello.
What's that?
It's wonderful.
Why weren't you at school today?
What are you doing here?
I like it here.
It's so...
desolate.
I like to write, you know?
Stories.
You have a nice smile.
POLICE
Why are you here?
You can't just show up here.
What if someone sees you?
Is everything all right?
I'm pregnant.
I thought you were taking precautions.
Is it mine?
Is it yours?
What do you think I do all day long?
Fuck around?
Do you think it was me
who chose all of this?
Living in this shithole forever? Huh?
I thought you were different,
but you're all the same.
You all think you own the world.
That you can take what you want.
You eat and fuck
and think that you're God.
Wherever you go,
always the same smug fucking assholes.
You don't know what you're saying.
It's best if I drive you home now.
The coal industry
has him around its finger.
I don't care how long it takes!
We'll submit
another building permit request.
Nuclear power is the future.
And the future cannot be stopped.
I don't care what the mayor says!
Oh, Claudia.
Look at you.
All grown up, aren't you?
A real lady now.
Pretty. Smart as a whip.
Helge will be pleased to see you.
And naturally,
you'll be rewarded for your services.
That's too much to offer.
I've some advice for you, Claudia.
A lesson.
If you really want something,
then you must take it.
Things will never happen on their own.
Thank you.
NUCLEAR POWER AND PEACE
TOWN HALL
Is Heinz sick, or...?
What's all this?
What exactly
is the coal industry paying you
to block the plans for the nuclear plant?
I have no idea what you're saying.
Did Doppler send you?
Do you know what gold cannot get you?
The future.
More precisely, your future.
We think we're all immortal,
but in reality
there's often only one heartbeat...
separating us from the hereafter.
What do you want from me?
WINDEN BUILDING AUTHORITY
BUILDING PERMIT
The building permit
for the nuclear plant. This is...
To the future.
You can change it.
You both can change it.
The barrels at the nuclear plant,
they start the apocalypse.
You must prevent them from being opened.
What do we do then?
Eve said there's a way to undo this knot.
That there's a way to let Martha live.
That's my Martha!
She lied to you.
There is no way to save both worlds.
You must choose one of them.
The apocalypse, in two days...
it can get stopped here.
You both have to stop it.
They can live. All of them.
Mikkel...
can live.
Isn't that what you wanted?
But you'll have to let her go.
Your Martha.
Your world.
You've seen what becomes of you there.
What you'll do there.
What Adam will do.
You've both lost it.
I'll go to the house and wake up in my bed
and realize this was just a shitty dream.
Jonas, this is exactly what you wanted.
You and Martha.
In this world the two of you can work.
Martha!
Wait!
Hey.
You believe all of this?
That they're all doomed?
That's crazy.
I'm crazy. That's...
Trust me,
I know exactly what it feels like.
It's all true?
All the things that she said are real?
But I know there's a way.
A way to make all of this right again.
And I want to continue
looking for that way.
I think she does too.
The Martha who brought me here.
It's time.
So you have no idea where your mom is?
And the man earlier today...
You think that could be your father?
My mother didn't talk much about him.
She had said...
he was just bad.
For a while I was in a home.
What's it like in a home?
Can you keep a secret?
That man, at the cave...
I don't even want to know
if he is my father.
And I'm glad that my mother is gone.
You can have it if you want.
Jana?
What are you doing here?
Didn't you go home hours ago?
We're already late.
Mom will be waiting with dinner.
See you around.
Maybe tomorrow.
What do we do now?
Don't worry.
I won't keep it.
Why do some people get to have it all?
And others get nothing?
Hm?
Why does destiny preordain
so much for some and not for others?
All my life, I've been trying
to hold onto things that I just can't.
But now I finally understand.
I need no one.
None of you.
I think you should go now.
Last year...
Daniel told me about it.
She does it properly.
I'm sorry.
So they're on their way?
The beginning is the end.
And the end is the beginning.
We are all born of him.
You gave him his life.
And now he will give us ours.
Him.
Agnes.
Tronte.
Jana.
Ulrich.
Katharina.
You.
A line with no start or end.
An unending circle.
Doris?
Are you okay?
I...
I'm sorry for what I said.
For this morning.
I know you just wanted to help out.
Lately, I've...
I'm not sure I've been myself.
This job and...
Well, I'm sorry.
I know what you've done.
With that girl.
What do you mean?
I want a divorce.
What... What are you saying right now?
We should have done it earlier, really,
but I...
I thought...
I don't know what I thought, I...
All the secrets we have, it's...
not how I want to live.
I...
I can explain it.
The ways of the heart cannot be explained.
It wants what it wants.
Hello.
I... I'm here to see Mrs. Obendorf.
You must wait.
My mother says...
they'll be in hell.
The ones...
that are gotten rid of.
I don't believe in hell.
Hell's what we make for ourselves here.
I'm Helene.
Helene Albers.
Katharina.
That's such a nice name.
Saint Christopher.
That's a good thought.
Someone carrying us on our journey.
Someone to watch over us.
All right, come.
Hello, Dad.
Where's Mom?
The ways of the heart cannot be explained.
It wants what it wants.
Come on.
Let him be.
WINDEN BUILDING AUTHORITY
BUILDING PERMIT
You made a promise.
I've kept up my end of the deal.
Now you have to keep up yours.
You want to know where the origin is
and how you might destroy it.
You will do it.
It was 66 years
before I finally understood...
how everything we know is bound together.
You're right.
It's time you understood, too.
At school...
At the door when you came in...
I got this feeling.
It was as if we knew each other.
From a dream.
Or...
I am sorry.
For everything.
In your world...
What was I like there?
Was I different?
THE BEGINNING IS THE END.
AND THE END IS THE BEGINNING.
♪ Evening rises
Darkness threatens to engulf us all ♪
♪ But there's a moon above
It's shining ♪
♪ And I think I hear a call ♪
♪ It's just a whisper through the trees ♪
♪ My ears can hardly make it out ♪
♪ But I can hear it in my heart ♪
♪ Vibrating strong as if she shouts ♪
♪ Oh, Ariadne, I'm coming ♪
♪ I just need to work
This maze inside my head ♪
♪ I came here like you asked
I killed the beast ♪
♪ That part of me is dead ♪
♪ Oh, Ariadne, I just need to work
This maze inside my head ♪
♪ If only I'd have listened to you ♪
♪ When you offered me that thread ♪
♪ Everything is quiet
And I'm not exactly sure ♪
♪ If it really was your voice I heard
Or maybe it's a door ♪
♪ That's closing up some hero's back
On his track to be a man ♪
♪ Can it be that all us heroes have a path
But not a plan? ♪
♪ Oh, Ariadne, I'm coming ♪
♪ I just need to work
This maze inside my mind ♪
♪ I wish I had that string ♪
♪ It's so damn dark
I think I'm going blind ♪
♪ Oh, Ariadne, I just need to work
This maze inside my heart ♪
♪ If I'd known that you could guide me ♪
♪ I'd have listened from the start ♪
♪ Somewhere up there midnight strikes ♪
♪ I think I hear the fall ♪
♪ Of little drops of water
Magnified against the barren wall ♪
♪ It's more a feeling than a substance ♪
♪ But there is nobody around ♪
♪ And when I'm in here all alone
It's just enough to let me drown ♪
♪ Oh, Ariadne, I was coming ♪
♪ But I failed you
In this labyrinth of my past ♪
♪ Oh, Ariadne, let me sing you
And we'll make each other last ♪
♪ Oh, Ariadne, I have failed you
In this labyrinth of my past ♪
♪ Oh, Ariadne, let me sing you ♪
♪ And we'll make each other last ♪
Why are we here?
Because this...
is where everything began.
In your world.
What are you saying?
Your older self,
she sent you and Jonas back
for a single purpose.
You were never supposed to stop
the apocalypse.
You were to create the seed.
This is the origin.
What's going on inside you
is the bridge between both worlds.
No, you're wrong.
It is the beginning of the knot.
And eventually also its end.
Your son.
He is the origin.