People are peculiar creatures.
All their actions are driven by desire,
their characters forged by pain.
As much as they might try
to suppress the pain,
to repress desire,
they cannot liberate themselves
from eternal servitude to their feelings.
As long as the storm rages within them
they can find no peace.
Not in life,
not in death.
And so, day after day,
they will do all that must be done.
Pain is their ship,
desire their compass.
All that humankind is capable of.
JUNE 26, 1954
ONE DAY UNTIL THE APOCALYPSE
The deceased woman is 5' 7".
Caucasian.
Probably 75
to 80 years old.
Cause of death, a shot to the chest.
The eyes are notable.
One blue, one brown.
It's known as heterochromia.
This woman, she...
She was at the police station.
The same day Helge reappeared.
And?
She was confused.
Not entirely there.
She apologized for something, I...
I didn't understand for what.
The same day Helge came back?
Maybe she's the madman's accomplice.
Could be his mother.
And she had Helge with her the whole time.
There's something else.
I only happened upon it by chance.
Her body
is heavily contaminated.
Here.
All over.
She must've been exposed
to heavy radiation for a prolonged period.
Peculiar.
Perhaps she worked as a radiographer.
A radiographer?
Visit the Doppler boy. Show him her photo.
Maybe he'll recognize her.
The data indicates
that the particle regularly decays
into two protons,
at a mass of 125 gigaelectronvolts.
In one case, however,
it decayed into four muons.
You're already here?
I must've lost track of time.
What day is it?
It's...
June 26.
Did you spend all night here?
FORMER WINDEN CHIEF INSPECTOR
FOUND DEAD ON JUNE 26, 1987
June 26...
Is something wrong?
I rescheduled the meeting with the French
for this morning.
Ms. Tiedemann?
Mom?
NUCLEAR POWER PLANT
WHAT'S BEHIND THE DOOR?
It all has to do with me.
Noah said the world will end tomorrow.
And that only the people
in the bunker will survive.
And he said she's alive.
My mother.
The documents
from the Marburg passport office are here.
As you suspected,
in that time frame there's only one entry
for an Aleksander Köhler.
And then the eyes saw, the ears heard
and nothing remained concealed.
Freud?
Tell Mr. Wöller.
We have to tell someone.
Who then? And what exactly?
Do you have anything to say?
I think he's here.
Who?
Jonas.
I think Bartosz is right. He's back.
We traveled through time
and that's all that interests you?
You said he's part of it.
Unlike you, he might know what this means.
Maybe he knows where Dad or Mikkel is,
or who knows what!
Magnus is right.
We have to tell someone.
Everyone has been up to
their own shit for months.
Everyone's silent.
What good has that done? None at all.
Okay.
Then we should do it.
We?
There is no "we."
There never has been.
- What does that mean?
- You knew what was going on for months.
You never told me or anyone else here.
Do whatever you want.
I hope it won't take too long.
Helge is still very exhausted.
Do you know this woman?
Answer the sergeant.
Were you with her maybe?
Did she lock you in?
He told me about her.
The White Devil.
Who?
Who told you about her?
The man who did that to you?
The White Devil.
Tell me about
the White Devil.
She wants to kill us.
All of us.
She's dead.
She can't hurt anyone anymore.
But she hasn't even started yet.
- Claudia?
- Hey, Dad.
Shouldn't you be at work?
I took the day off.
Is everything all right?
We discussed you moving in with us.
I...
Already forgotten?
You said I should think it over.
I just thought...
why waste time?
Then you'll be out of here.
I like it here.
I have to go.
To the hospital.
My first chemo.
Can I...
maybe join you?
That is, only if you'd like.
That'd be nice.
What do you want here?
I've already told you everything.
I'd like you to look at something.
Mr. Wöller?
What is it?
A copy of a document
from the Marburg Registry Office.
The info on your last ID
before you left Marburg.
I've no idea how this is relevant.
Nothing stands out?
No. What should stand out?
5' 6", I'd say. Tops.
That document says 5' 8".
So where are they?
Where are what?
The two inches.
This is ridiculous.
I'm arresting you.
On suspicion of identity theft.
You can't.
Hannah?
Anyone home?
Hello?
Hannah, if you're home,
please open the door.
Pardon me. I...
Who are you?
Please come in.
I...
I... I wanted to talk to Hannah.
She's not here.
Want a drink?
Do I scare you?
I don't want to.
I think
I'm just having déjà vu or something.
- I'm going.
- A glitch in the matrix.
What?
Or a message from beyond.
You read that somewhere.
How do you know that?
You found the pendant.
Jonas?
Do you think
that I was a good police officer?
Oh, Dad. No idea.
I'm sure you were good at what you did.
Actually, I don't think so.
You were always different.
You saw the world differently
from the very start.
Sometimes I think
that that's my problem.
That I can't see the world as it truly is.
I think I did something very, very stupid.
What do you mean?
Do you know that movie?
The one with the young man
who has this car
that can take him to the past?
I know this sounds crazy,
but...
the stuff in that movie
really exists.
Time travel.
And somehow...
it has all got to do with Mads and Helge.
And with things
that happened over 30 years ago.
Mr. Tiedemann!
Mr. Tiedemann.
A woman's waiting for you in your office.
Did she say what she wanted?
It's about the man in the asylum.
The one who killed the boys.
She says she knows him.
Thanks.
Hello.
How can I help you?
I...
I'm looking for my husband.
It was in the paper.
The dead children.
And there was a photo.
I think it's my husband.
Is that your husband?
There's a resemblance.
We looked for relatives.
No one came forward.
You know he was arrested last winter
for multiple murders?
Can I see him?
It's not that simple, he's...
currently in a psychiatric facility.
He won't talk.
I see.
But maybe he'll talk to me.
May I ask you what your name is?
Nielsen.
Katharina Nielsen.
Where were you all this time?
I promised you
I'd make it all right again.
I'm so sorry.
Suddenly it all makes sense.
Once you know, it's obvious.
Hannah?
Hannah, open the door!
Hannah!
Martha, don't.
Please.
Martha?
You know who this is? Hm?
Did he tell you where your brother is?
Who your brother is?
That man
is your brother's son.
My grandson, your nephew.
Mikkel is Michael Kahnwald.
You hear me, Martha?
And you are his aunt.
Martha.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
I... Believe me, I really wanted to...
Where's your machine?
The one you can travel through time with?
Hannah's got it.
She's vanished.
Hannah?
Tell me how I can get Mikkel back!
Mom...
Magnus has the device.
What?
We traveled with it.
You were there?
Did you see Mikkel?
Mikkel?
Keep your filthy fingers off her.
You got me?
Come on.
What is this?
My brother
also vanished without a trace.
In 1986.
Much like
Mads Nielsen's disappearance here.
Not a trace.
Nothing.
His name was Aleksander too.
Aleksander Köhler.
Just like yours.
A common name.
To be precise, there are
over 700 Aleksander Köhlers in Germany.
It isn't all that easy to track down
every Aleksander Köhler.
Particularly when they've assumed
their wife's maiden name.
Believe me, I'm speaking from experience.
When my parents split,
I took my mother's last name.
I went from Köhler to Clausen.
For some people
I'm still untraceable to this day.
But,
a couple of months ago,
this happened.
Read it.
Out loud.
"He that has eyes to see
and ears to hear
may convince himself
that no mortal can keep a secret.
If his lips are silent...
- ...he chatters...
- ...he chatters with his fingertips.
- Betrayal oozes...
- ...out of him at every pore.
You'll find the answers
concerning your brother in Winden.
A friend."
I have no idea
what's going on in this town.
But I'm very certain of one thing.
You...
are definitely not my brother.
Your husband never confessed.
He kept insisting
he wanted to save the children.
You and your husband...
You have children, right?
No.
Strange.
He kept saying he was looking for his son.
This may sound a bit odd, but...
Have you ever heard of a "White Devil"?
No. What is that supposed to be?
If he talks to you...
That is, if he should talk to you,
persuade him to talk to the police.
Persuade him to confess.
And the man came from the future?
Back to 1953?
That's when you arrested him.
And yesterday
that man tried to kidnap the boy?
No.
Not that man.
I mean...
the same man,
but older.
Because he's allegedly his son?
I know.
It all sounds completely insane.
The man,
the old man.
Where is he now?
Back in psychiatric care.
That's enough. You're moving in with us.
We'll get your things now.
So you believe me.
So you...
traveled with it?
To what year?
So that's what's going on.
You knew about this time travel shit?
Why didn't you say anything?
Martha.
Yes. At Franziska's.
Yes, I'll be right home.
You what?
Who?
Jonas is back.
Like Bartosz said.
But he's older.
You guys should stay out of this.
Unbelievable.
So you two knew it too.
That's exactly what ruins everything!
All your fucking secrets!
You couldn't even talk to us
when Dad screwed Benni!
What incompetent assholes you are!
Franziska.
K-53.
I'd like a moment alone with him.
I don't know if that's such a good idea.
Please.
Just five minutes.
As you wish.
Ulrich?
Ulrich.
Ulrich, it's me.
Hannah.
Is it really you?
Yes.
Or are you an angel?
Are you an angel?
- Is it you?
- Yes.
It's you.
Do you know where Mikkel is?
And Katharina? How is Katharina?
Martha? Magnus?
It's so different seeing you again.
What?
If you could choose today,
between Katharina and me?
What do you mean?
Why?
Back when we were together, you...
I...
I tried to remember if you...
if you ever said "I love you" to me.
I loved you.
I still love you.
Get me out and I'll leave Katharina.
I love you.
Okay?
He said I need no one.
But the truth is
you don't need me.
Yes, yes. I need you, Hannah.
I love you.
You've got to get me out.
I'll do anything you want.
Get me out of here, please.
Hannah, I love you.
You hear me?
I love you.
Hannah. Stay!
You fucking cunt!
Stay! Stay with me!
Stay with me!
I love you!
She's a liar!
There are similarities, but...
Hannah!
I love you!
That's not my husband.
Get me out of here!
Mom?
Everything will be fine.
Okay?
You got the machine?
Do you know how it works?
I...
don't.
Bartosz used it.
They're alive.
Mikkel.
And Dad.
What?
They're just not here.
They're in another time.
Just grab your pills quick.
We'll come back for everything else.
I just need a minute.
Come on. Let's go.
I wonder
why he wanted
to go into the caves with him.
Maybe there's something there,
in the caves.
Dad, stop.
But he wanted to go there in 1953 too.
And again now.
- Maybe there's something...
- There's nothing in the caves.
But there must be some reason
he wanted to go in there.
Can we go now?
Why are you really here?
What do you mean by that?
You know.
What do I know?
You know about the time travel.
- It's related to the nuclear power plant.
- I'd like to go now!
You're involved in all of this.
Don't be ridiculous.
We have to have the caves searched.
There's nothing in the caves!
There is no time travel!
- What are you doing?
- Calling the station.
To have them search the caves.
You're clueless.
What's in the caves eclipses
all scientific discovery.
That substance turns all we know
about the universe on its head.
And you want to risk all of that?
For nothing?
You haven't changed.
It's still all about you.
You have no heart.
Let go.
Let go!
Oh God, Dad!
Stay right there.
Don't move.
I...
I'll call an ambulance.
Come on.
Come on!
Winden Emergency Services,
how can I help?
Hello?
Hell...
"You'll have to make sacrifices."
"Everything will happen as it always has."
"But if everything goes right,
she'll live."
Regina.
I'm so sorry.
You are the White Devil.
You're sure he wasn't your husband?
I...
should've reacted quicker.
- I'm sorry.
- Don't blame yourself.
Nielsen...
That's an...
uncommon name.
Do you know an Agnes Nielsen?
No.
You're traveling back today?
I lost everything where I came from.
All I want is a fresh start.
SLEEPING OVER AT A FRIEND'S, R.
Who are you?
Why do you have a key to my house?
You gave it to me before you left.
Nonsense.
I don't even know you.
She gave it to you.
My older self.
We've got to go.
We don't have much time.
I don't understand.
I know what you did.
She told me.
But she also said
it didn't have to happen that way again.
Next time.
Where are we going?
To the future.
Subtitle translation by Nathan Fritz