MAN CAN DO WHAT HE WILLS,
BUT HE CANNOT WILL WHAT HE WILLS.
If we knew
how things would end...
where our journey would take us...
would we still make the same decisions?
Or would we choose a different path?
Could we even escape our fate?
Or would what is deep within us
lead us to the same end,
like an invisible hand?
Does it matter which path we choose
if we end up
facing ourselves again and again?
Wait. Martha, that's not possible, I...
- I don't understand.
- We don't have time.
What time are you from?
The question isn't from what time,
but from what world.
How did we get here?
I asked how we got here!
You're not Martha.
Who are you?
Today's the day it all began.
The day we first met.
What's that supposed to mean?
That you and I...
your world and my world...
form a knot that is
inextricably intertwined.
Your world?
What do you mean, your world?
I'll make it right.
- I promise.
- Wait! Where are you going?
Why am I here?
4 NOVEMBER 2019
Mikkel, put that away.
- Morning.
- No wonder you can't sleep at night.
What's up with him?
The same nightmare he always has.
Mikkel, that's enough.
Maybe it wasn't a dream.
But the here and now is one.
And none of us are real.
Ever thought about that?
Ha-ha! Very funny.
Oh, the damn electricity!
Pass the butter.
Come on, Mikkel. Go get ready now.
The bowl!
Is Magnus up yet?
- Martha, is Magnus up yet?
- No idea.
- Are you nuts?
- I just wanted to see if you were real.
Magnus!
You're going to be late!
Hello!
Magnus, either you get
down here or I'm coming up!
I'll be down in a sec.
- Arsehole!
- Race you to school. Morning, Mum.
- Idiot.
- Morning.
Shall I give you a ride?
It's supposed to rain later.
No, I'll be home late
today. Play rehearsal.
Don't forget, starting tomorrow
you guys are at your father's place.
Man, Mum, that sucks.
Good morning, sleepy head.
I was awake half the night again.
Why did it take so long?
First day back at school.
Long line at the baker's.
The apocalypse is coming.
Stay awhile.
I'm running late.
I'll see you this evening, okay?
Ulrich?
I love you.
You're beautiful.
MISSING
ERIK OBENDORF
SCHOOL THEATRE WEEK
I win.
Welcome back to hell.
Just because you're too pea-brained
to see education is the
only way out of this dump
doesn't mean we all share
your retarded opinion.
- Don't forget to breathe.
- Don't forget to think.
- Hey.
- Have you seen Kilian?
- Nope.
Why all the effort?
We all die in the end.
Are you sure you're not adopted?
Are you sure you don't
have a stick up your arse
that needs surgical removal?
- Dumbarse!
- Dumbarse yourself!
- Hey, Martha.
- Kilian.
Is there any news about Erik?
No.
It's all pretty creepy.
Good morning.
We request all grades to gather in
the gym for first-period assembly.
It'll be about your brother.
It's been two weeks already.
He's never been away this long.
He'd always send me a message
whenever he couldn't
stand it at home anymore.
But this time, nothing.
Let's go. Otherwise Mum will be angry.
MISSING
ERIK OBENDORF
It will happen again.
CONTACT THE WINDEN
POLICE WITH INFORMATION
It will happen again.
He hasn't said anything
else all morning.
- It will happen again.
- How'd it go at the doctor's?
It will happen again.
Fine. Just a check-up.
I have to go. I'm running
late. I just forgot something.
It will happen again.
Tick, tock.
POLICE
Erik Obendorf has been
missing since 22 October.
That's almost two weeks
now. No traces, no witnesses.
Questioning the neighbours
didn't bring any new
evidence to light either.
So, do you have any ideas?
We still haven't got the shift
schedules from the nuclear power plant.
All right, then follow up
on that. Go see Tiedemann.
- Wöller, look into the tyre treads.
- Yes.
- Jankowski, talk to the Obendorfs again.
- Okay.
Maybe he just took off.
It wouldn't be the first time.
Well, a black hole...
forms when a central region
collapses in upon itself.
And it contains neutrons.
WORMHOLE
Well, more like neutron matter.
But not enough of it.
So when the light of a star three
times the mass of the sun goes out,
then it explodes.
No, it implodes.
And that is a black hole.
And...
Can I help you?
Hello?
Are you new?
I'm Jonas.
Are you sure this is your class?
I wasn't notified of any new students.
A signature was missing.
Okay.
Bartosz, please continue.
Mm-hm.
So then we have a black hole.
And it has a huge gravitational pull.
Everything flying around the hole
is drawn to it and
somehow dragged inside.
Other stars, planets, and even light.
The gravitational force is so strong,
that even light is pulled into it.
Nothing can escape once it's inside.
Basically, no one
knows what's behind it.
Maybe nothing. Or maybe a new world.
A world in which nothing
is as it is in ours.
All I'm asking is to review
your employees' shift schedules.
Erik was last seen on the forest road.
The schedules
will allow us to check employee
vehicles with the tyre treads we found.
Do you have a court order?
This is a request.
Not an order.
I'll have someone search them out.
How are you?
Holding up.
Okay, then.
I was wondering...
do you think Erik could have
made his way onto the grounds?
The caves are partly located
under the nuclear power plant.
That's impossible.
The access points were
sealed up years ago.
No one can get in that way.
Okay, then.
A quick reminder that
all afternoon activities
after four o'clock are cancelled
due to the parents' meeting.
Except theatre, which
will go on as planned
but vacate the auditorium
an hour earlier.
The school newspaper will
meet in the youth café today
under the supervision of Mr. Hopf.
Katharina.
What are you doing here?
- I wanted to see you.
- Uh-huh.
I don't know...
I know you and Ulrich...
Ulrich and the kids...
I know they're part of him.
And I want you to know I
won't stand in the way of that.
That's very generous of you.
Did Ulrich stop at
your place this morning?
He wanted to bring something by.
Bring what by?
I don't know.
Something for school. For the kids.
No.
Then maybe he forgot.
Please don't forget to turn in
your presentations next week.
No exceptions!
Something up?
You didn't tell me why I'm here.
Do we know each other?
You have no idea who I am.
You coming?
ARIADNE
A PLAY
Jonas, right?
Everything okay?
What day is it today?
4 November.
What year?
2019.
I don't understand...
Mum?
Pardon?
Are you okay?
Can I help you?
POLICE
Charlotte?
We have to stop this.
That's not what you
were saying this morning.
Ulrich, not here.
Oh... I'm sorry.
What is it?
Um... the...
the tyre treads.
47 cars and 2 trucks.
In Winden alone there are
21,000 registered vehicles.
Yes. What do you want
me to do with that?
I...
No idea.
I got the power plant shift
schedules. We can run a check.
Wöller.
From then on, I knew
that nothing changes.
That all things remain.
The spinning wheel turns.
Round and round, in a circle.
One fate tied to the next.
A thread,
red like blood,
that connects all our deeds.
One cannot unravel the knots.
But they can be severed.
He severed ours
with the sharpest blade.
And yet, something remains
behind that cannot be severed.
An invisible bond.
On many a night, he tugs at it.
And then I wake with a start,
knowing that nothing ceases to be.
That all remains.
And because their eyes
and hearts were blind,
they were punished for
their sins. Here and now.
And what flew plummeted to Earth.
And what was on Earth changed its shape.
Revealed its grotesque face,
which was nothing but
blasphemy made flesh.
Great. We'll stop here.
Unfortunately, we have
to finish early today.
Please put everything away for the
parents' meeting tonight. Thanks.
9 o'clock tonight by
the bridge. Don't forget.
Martha.
I have no idea
what you want from me,
but I want nothing from you, okay?
So get lost.
Please listen to me. Maybe
you don't know who I am.
- But today is 4 November and Mikkel...
- What? Mikkel?
Michael Kahnwald, Hannah's
husband. He's not who you think...
Hannah's husband? Are you joking?
I don't know any Michael Kahnwald.
Hannah's husband is my
dad and his name is Ulrich.
I don't know what your deal is,
but just fuck off already, okay?
Wait. Not so fast.
I...
love you.
I love you.
It will happen again.
It will...
happen again.
It will happen again.
Mum?
Dad?
It will happen again.
It will...
happen again.
Tick, tock.
- Grandpa, is everything okay?
- Tick, tock.
Tick, tock.
The beginning is the end.
And the end is the beginning.
Tick, tock.
TIEDEMANN, REGINA
1.8.1971 - 2.9.2019
Can I help you?
Are you looking for
something in particular?
I wanted to know if
someone was buried here.
Who?
Kahnwald,
Michael Kahnwald.
No, we have a Daniel Kahnwald,
died in '64,
but no Michael Kahnwald.
Maybe that's why I'm here.
So that it doesn't happen.
What happens?
Do I know you?
I feel like I've seen you
somewhere before.
Hey, wait!
What's your name?
21 SEPTEMBER 1987
Hello?
Can I help you? You must be lost.
The master key.
For the nuclear power plant.
Is this a joke?
You kept it.
Do you think this is funny?
If you don't leave,
I'll call the police.
Police...
What do you want from me?
Nothing is in vain.
No breath.
No step.
No word.
No pain.
An everlasting miracle...
of the One.
Who the hell are you?
The police were here today.
You know what you've got to do.
Kilian?
Stop screwing around, okay?
What is this?
What do you want here?
I don't want to scare you.
- Why did you say we know each other?
- We do know each other.
Not now, but in another time.
What does that mean?
You've seen all this before.
The light.
The forest. Me.
It's déjà vu.
Or a glitch in the matrix.
What?
I think I know why I'm here now.
Why you came to get me.
So that I change it.
Change what?
Who is he?
- Where's Mikkel?
- Mikkel?
Mikkel isn't with you?
Are you blind or what?
What's he doing here?
Did you bring him along?
What is this?
- How do you know my brother?
- This can't be.
You took him with you.
Heide, the babysitter, is sick.
And he didn't want to stay
home alone, so he came along.
No idea what the fuck this is,
but Mikkel is old enough
to look after himself.
Now, you'd better fuck off.
Get lost, freak.
Come on.
Martha.
POLICE
Charlotte? I'm going
to the parents' meeting.
I can give you a ride if you like.
All right.
- Will you carry on with this?
- Mm-mm.
Why did he act like he knew you?
- Do you know him?
- No.
Who knows.
Did you know Nostradamus predicted
the world would end this year?
What a load of crap.
No. Really.
The apocalypse is
practically around the corner.
Glad I got myself a girlfriend
with her own bunker.
What?
Nothing.
Ow!
What?
And you think you'll
find something here?
Erik sometimes spent
nights here in summer.
Maybe the police overlooked something.
Have you heard the story
of the cave monster?
- Spare us the bullshit, man.
- It's not bullshit.
Some 100 years ago,
just after World War I, they
did experiments in there.
What kind of experiments?
- What was that?
- What?
Shit.
What's in the cave?
- What is it?
- Oh, shit!
- Fuck!
- What is that?
- Fuck! What's going on?
- Go! Run!
- What's with the flashlights?
- Go!
- Out of here! Out of here!
- Martha!
- Martha, come on.
- Out of here!
Run! Run!
Kilian?
Martha.
- Is it over?
- I think so.
What...
What... what is that?
Oh, God!
Fuck!
Shit!
Oh, shit. Shit!
Fuck.
- Is he dead?
- Fuck.
Yes, I think so.
Who... who is that?
STUDENT CARD
MADS NIELSEN, 4 DECEMBER 1973
Mads Nielsen.
I've waited for this moment
for so long.
For you to come back.
Who are you?
Mikkel.
He didn't travel back.
He won't become your father.
And you...
will never be born in this world.
A world without you.
Isn't that what you wanted?
Yet, despite that,
this world is doomed
to the same fate as yours.
Everything will fall apart.
In this world, just as it will in yours.
Again.
And again.
Because of you.
And because of me.
Martha.
21 SEPTEMBER 1888
Jonas?
You're alive.
You're alive!
I'm not Martha.
Not your Martha.
What does that mean?
I'm here to help you find the origin.
The one thing...
that's the beginning of everything.
In your world...
and in mine.