What is reality?
And is there only one of them?
Or do several realities coexist?
To help explain, Erwin Schroedinger
devised an extremely
interesting thought experiment.
Schroedinger's cat.
A cat is locked in a steel chamber
with a tiny amount of
radioactive substance,
a Geiger counter, a vial
of poison, and a hammer.
As soon as a radioactive atom
decays inside the steel chamber,
the Geiger counter releases the hammer,
which smashes the vial of poison.
The cat is dead.
However,
due to the wave characteristics
in the quantum world,
the atom has both
decayed and not decayed,
until our own observation forces
it into a definitive state.
until the instant we look
and see, we don't know
if the cat is dead or alive.
It exists in two superposed states.
The properties "dead"
and "alive"
therefore exist simultaneously
in the microcosm.
But what if the simultaneous
existence of life and death
also applied to the macrocosmic world?
I'll make this right.
Could two different realities
potentially exist side by side?
Could we manage to split time
and allow it to run in two
opposing directions?
And by doing so, allow the cat
to simultaneously exist in
both states, dead and alive?
And, if so,
how many different realities...
could exist side by side?
Martha!
Wait!
You can't go in there.
Bartosz?
- What are you doing here?
- Adam and the others lied to you.
He doesn't want to help
you. He's going to kill you.
In the future. He doesn't
want to stop the apocalypse.
Everyone will die.
Not because of you,
but because of him.
I know what the origin is.
And how it's all connected.
Please.
I can show you.
You've got to trust me.
IN BETWEEN TIME
It's hard for people to accept death.
TANNHAUS FAMILY: 8.11.1971
MAREK, SONJA, CHARLOTTE
We hold on tightly to
things that are long gone.
CHARLOTTE
30.5.1971
We long in vain for a
way to turn back time.
A way to reverse death.
But if time is relative
and nothing is really ever in the past,
and the simultaneous overlapping
of different realities is possible,
shouldn't it then be possible
to bring back something that
was believed to be dead long ago
and to create a new reality in
which what is dead lives again?
If our life is defined as that
which lies between birth and death,
then it exists there
in infinite versions.
Could we succeed in cheating death
by finding a way
to bring back life?
There, between time.
FOR CHARLOTTE
Tell me about paradise.
Paradise...
is free
of pain and suffering.
Everything we've ever done...
is forgotten there.
Any pain...
we've ever felt...
is erased.
And...
all the dead...
live.
Adam will keep his promise.
The passage will open.
What do you want?
You've been promising us there's
a way out of here for ages.
That we can stop the apocalypse.
But you still don't know
how the portal works.
It will work.
I saw it work.
In the future.
And then what?
When are you finally
going to tell us the truth?
You don't want to go back.
You don't want to stop
the apocalypse at all.
This is bigger than us.
Bigger than the apocalypse.
If the portal works, we can
use it to find the origin.
The one moment that started all this.
And when we've found it,
we'll destroy it.
And everything that arises from it.
That is paradise.
Paradise?
We've been stuck here for 2 years.
2 fucking years!
I don't want your fucking paradise.
I just want out of here.
Hello?
I... didn't mean to startle you.
Sometimes I think it'll
never stop raining.
I'm...
Silja.
Bartosz.
We can start a new series
of experiments tomorrow.
I know we've been
trying for a long time,
but it will work.
Jonas.
You can't lose hope.
I can't do this anymore.
What are you doing here?
Are you following me?
You promised me something.
Adam promised me something.
You said the apocalypse must happen.
So that we can be saved.
So that all of us will be saved.
You can't die.
You can't take your own life.
Because your older self already exists.
Time won't allow it.
No matter what you try...
something...
or someone...
will always stop you from doing it.
Elisabeth and I,
we found the passage.
You must keep your promise.
It will open again.
And then you will...
then Adam will...
lead us to paradise.
He said we will become friends.
Before you betray me.
Yes! Good.
Once more.
Yes! Yes!
It's a boy.
What will you name him?
Hanno.
Fate is playing a cruel game with us.
Yet we will always believe
there is a way to turn
the tide in our favour.
If only we want it badly enough.
A person is able to pursue a goal,
no matter how unattainable it may seem,
over the course of an entire lifetime.
No resistance, no
obstacle is great enough
to stop one from pursuing one's will.
Is this stubbornness in our striving
not that which distinguishes
us from animals,
which know only short-lived desire?
And isn't all progress,
through all ages,
not the product of this
unquenchable act of will?
No matter what motivates our will,
it will guide us on our path.
We will only be able to let go
when we have finally attained
our goal once and for all.
Why do you think it's not working?
Maybe Claudia doesn't want it to work.
Why do you even trust her?
Why did you trust him?
Adam?
He lied to you.
There is no paradise.
There's no world other than this one.
I know you think I will become him.
But I won't.
The portal will work, I've seen it.
In the future.
Everything repeats itself.
But if I can travel back,
I can change everything.
My older self tried it before,
but this time, everything's different.
I've changed the
components in the passage.
This time, it'll work.
She told you that?
Claudia?
What do you really know about her?
She sometimes disappears for days.
How does she know all
the things she knows?
She said not everything
that's here belongs here.
What did she mean by that?
Come inside.
Claudia's hiding something from us.
We can't trust her.
I hope you know that.
He still doesn't suspect anything?
No.
He has no idea you or
the other world exists.
You must continue to
guide him on his path.
The matter, it must not work yet.
You uphold the knot in your
world, and I'll uphold it in mine.
Wait.
All these past few years, the
things Eva said I had to do...
Does she know everything
that happens?
I was wondering.
Have you ever met her?
Who?
My older self.
No.
I still remember
exactly what she said.
"If everything goes right...
Regina will live".
I've thought about that all these years.
I just can't believe
that by that she meant
her suffering was to repeat
over and over forever.
There must be a way to untie the knot...
without destroying all life in it.
A way for Regina to live.
Really live.
I think neither Eva
nor Adam know that path.
But I'll find it.
In my world or yours.
Don't...
You didn't bring Claudia with you?
Noah is watching her.
We have to be careful.
You must give this to Claudia.
And she must give it to Tannhaus.
She understands
why it's necessary?
Why everything has to happen again?
You have to be strong now, Hanno.
For your father too.
Silja...
Bartosz, we tried everything.
She wanted to name her Agnes.
Tell me about paradise.
Paradise...
is free
of pain and suffering.
Everything we've ever done...
is forgotten there.
The passage will open.
And then...
we will be there.
You,
me...
and Charlotte.
Where is she?
Charlotte?
Where is Charlotte?
All these years, I wondered
what he meant by that.
That we'd be friends
before you betray me.
Where's Claudia? Does she have
Charlotte? Did you help her?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Where is she?
Where's Charlotte?
I don't know.
I wish you all the
suffering in the world.
I will find her.
I will bring her back.
I promise I will.
A man can do what he wills,
but he cannot will what he wills.
All the paths we take in our lives,
every decision that we make,
is guided by that which we
desire deep inside ourselves.
We cannot fight that desire.
It determines every one of our deeds,
no matter how grave and
unimaginable they seem.
Hannah?
Silja?
I...
I'm looking for Jonas.
Yes.
He has changed.
Travelling has left its mark on him.
Jonas?
This is my daughter.
Silja.
She's your sister.
How did you find us?
A few days ago...
there was this old woman.
She just showed up on our doorstep.
Eva.
She said...
she knew where you were.
And that you were looking for me.
You're right.
It's all my fault.
I ruined everything.
But now I'm here.
I'm here, Jonas.
Bartosz.
Prepare the chamber for them.
What are you doing?
Silja.
She doesn't belong here.
What's that supposed to mean?
"She doesn't belong here"?
All the pieces have to be in position.
She's in the wrong place.
So are you.
Mum.
I want to show you a secret.
But we'll let your mum sleep, okay?
Come on.
I...
I have travelled far.
I need a place to sleep.
Hanno?
Prepare the chamber for this gentleman.
I was wondering when you'd come.
I know you think I lied to you.
That I took Charlotte away from you.
But I didn't.
You were right.
Claudia...
she lied to all of us.
The book...
do you have it with you?
Are the last pages missing?
You must find the last pages.
They will lead you to Charlotte
and to your final destination.
You will find your paradise.
And Helge...
will help you do so.
Everything in life happens in cycles.
Sunset
is followed by sunrise,
over and over.
But this time...
it will be the last cycle.
Are you ready, Noah?
The matter,
it can finally be stabilised.
Everything must happen again
in exactly the same way.
You have to lead your younger
self down the same path.
He must not act differently.
MISSING
MIKKEL NIELSEN
You have to set the course, no
matter how hard that may seem.
But you'll finally be
able to change everything.
WINDEN WELCOMES ITS NEW MINISTER
The device...
He'll repair it.
A JOURNEY THROUGH TIME
You must destroy the passage,
and the knot with it.
You'll succeed this time.
Jonas...
You must never lose hope.
POLICE
Weeks ago, in the small town of Winden,
a 15-year-old boy
disappeared mysteriously.
Residents are now alarmed after
a second child has gone missing.
Eleven-year-old Mikkel has
been missing for two days.
Report any information you
may have to the Winden police.
Hello, Claudia.
Don't you want to get in?
You have to stop Adam.
FOLLOW THE SIGNAL
Have we met?
I'm sorry.
You are the white devil.
27 JUNE 2020
BEGINNING OF THE LAST CYCLE
Charlotte?
No, this can't be true.
Mum.
Jonas.
I've looked for you all these years.
You are not my father.
Regina?
I'm so sorry.
You used me.
There is no man without guilt.
None of them deserve a
place in your paradise.
Jonas?
And so the circle closes.
What about Martha?
Why did you bring me here?
They're the only ones who'll save us.
Save us?
Everything that's
happened is their fault.
No.
They are the light.
What do you want from me?
Isn't it peculiar...
that one feels the greatest aversion
towards the people who are
most similar to oneself?
I'm not like you.
You and I have nothing in common.
My whole life, I believed
that this moment could
never repeat itself.
That I could never do
what my older self had done.
Because I couldn't understand
how I could ever want what she wanted.
But now...
66 years later, I understand.
Some pain is never forgotten.
It brands us for our entire life.
You and I...
we share that pain.
We bear the same scars.
A memento.
So you never forget which
side you really belong on.
You may not understand yet, but
choosing us is choosing life.
Choosing Adam is choosing death.
No!
This can't be.
Hello, Jonas.