And if you gaze long into an abyss,
the abyss also gazes into you.
21 June 1921
The beginning... and the end.
I think it seems a strange idea
that maybe there's no difference.
Sic mundus creatus est.
And thus the world is created.
Sic
mundus
creatus est!
You've stopped believing the prophecy?
I believe in the irony of fate.
Adam says that all things
must happen in the same
manner they always have.
We have to bear the cross, no
matter how hard it may seem.
In six days this will be paradise
and hell on earth will end.
Sometimes I ask myself
whether paradise and hell
are one and the same.
Adam was right.
You've lost your faith.
And is that why he sent you?
I've waited for this moment for ages.
Interesting that it should be you.
I hope eventually a day will come
where you won't believe
everything Adam tells you.
You should...
ask why he took you in.
And why he chose to call you Noah.
27 June 2020 beginning
of the last cycle
You and I are perfect for each other.
Never believe anything else.
DO NOT OPEN BEFORE
4 NOVEMBER 10:13 P.M.
JUNE 2020
My name is Claudia Tiedemann.
I am one of the few survivors of
the apocalypse on 27 June 2020.
Almost three months have
passed since the catastrophe.
It's unclear what exactly
caused the events in Winden.
But the God Particle...
If we can stabilise it, it
might provide a way back.
Back to the past.
Maybe we can save them.
All of them.
21 June 2020
6 days until the Apocalypse
Morning, sleepyheads!
It's the first week
of the summer holiday.
The weather couldn't be
nicer for a day at the beach.
In local news,
more than half a year after
the mysterious disappearance
of 4 teenagers, a senior
citizen and a local police officer
from the town of Winden
there are no clues as
to their whereabouts
or what might have happened.
A federal police task force will
now assist with the investigation.
How are you today?
Still having joint pain?
Nausea?
To be honest, your lab
results are worrying me a bit.
I think we should admit you again.
No.
Of course not.
I'm staying at home.
Fine. We'll wait for the
results of the last MRI.
We may have to stop the hormone
treatment and switch back to chemo.
COME TO THE BRIDGE.
"He that has eyes to see
and ears to hear
may convince himself
that no mortal can keep a secret.
If his lips are silent,
he chatters with his fingertips.
Betrayal oozes out
of him at every pore."
That was Freud,
and I'm Clausen, head of
the task force for Winden.
As of today I'm in charge of the
past year's unsolved missing cases.
This task force's aim is to
reinvestigate the case
from the beginning,
To assess all the
circumstantial evidence
and make sense of the
secrets that remain hidden,
undiscovered until we find them.
In the coming days some of
you will receive subpoenas
to appear for another
round of questions.
- Yes?
- You keep saying "we".
- What do you mean by that?
- Myself and Mrs. Doppler.
Who is still assigned to these cases.
6 people have been missing for months!
And this is what they send us?
This is what you call a task force?
One person? And the woman
who hasn't found anyone.
She hasn't done anything.
10 people
who see an elephant
from 10 different angles
will give you 10 different descriptions
of the size and shape of that elephant.
But a single person who
looks at that same elephant
from all 10 different
perspectives instead
will be able to piece together
all of his observations
and eventually arrive at the
only reasonable conclusion.
My son is still gone.
The next time I need to
find an elephant, though,
I'll be in touch!
That's right.
Does your mother talk at home?
About the investigation,
I mean.
Not to us.
So we just sit and wait.
And nothing happens.
We've been clueless for 8 months.
Sometimes I think it'd just
be better if they were dead.
Hey, don't say that.
I better go.
- Where are you going?
- Elisabeth's staying at her friend's.
I'll call you later, okay?
Aleksander Tiedmann
died 27.6.2020
Justyna Jankowski
Torben Wöller
died 27.6.2020
Michael Kahnwald
born 5.11.1975
died 21.6.2019
Martha Nielsen
died 27.6.2020
I tried calling you the last few days.
There's a lot going on.
I wanted to talk.
- I have for a while.
- Don't worry about it.
I think it's better this way.
I guess...
that's it, then.
It's because of him.
- Because of Jonas.
- What?
What does that have to do with it?
We hardly ever see each other.
I don't...
You've really changed.
I...
I've been thinking that
you're hiding something.
I...
- I have no idea what's going on with you.
- What do you mean?
For fuck's sake, my mum is dying.
That's what's going on. And...
- There are things I just can't tell you.
- And why the hell not?
I just can't!
Okay? If you had any idea of
the shit I've been dealing with.
- I mean...
- The shit you've been dealing with?
In case you forgot, my father
and brother are still missing.
My mother is crazy and
doesn't give a shit about me.
And you're telling me about how
much shit you've been dealing with?
It's better this way.
THIS EVENING.
Energy creates community.
Nuclear power was, is, and always
will be the only viable option.
Nothing is more reliable,
cheaper or as safe.
The outside world, however,
demands progress.
In 7 days our plant
will close for good.
This will be a life-altering
adjustment for all of us.
I would like to thank you
for your loyalty.
Without all of you the
Winden plant as we know it
could never have existed.
And so, for the last 6 days,
let us fill this place
with the spirit of our community,
as we always have.
Everything is ready
for transport on schedule.
And the decommissioning?
What is at ground
level will be untouched
and become part of the greenfield.
Any radiation will be traced back
to the previous use of the pools.
Hello?
Who are you?
Why are you here?
How did you have a key?
It's my key.
What are you saying, your key?
I know this is all going to
sound like it doesn't make sense.
But hear me out.
Do you remember the yellow bike?
The bike you and Dad gave
me for my 8th birthday.
I drove it into a ditch
on the very first day.
I got that cut on my arm, here.
Get out!
Here...
Dad was making pancakes.
He dropped the pan and
spilled hot oil right there.
I disappeared from your
life over half a year ago.
And you found me over 33 years ago.
I knew it was you right away.
It was raining that day.
You and Grandpa wanted to
drive me there in the car.
You said there was still acid rain
because of Chernobyl.
I was wearing my yellow jacket.
It's me.
It's me, Mum.
Jonas.
How can it be you?
There are no coincidences.
Every path is predetermined.
Everything happens
when it is supposed to.
At the right time.
At the right place.
As if the world was a carpet
made up of a network
of infinite threads.
Each in its place.
But only a handful of people know
where their journey will take them.
You've taken your first step.
Adam will be proud of you.
I had that same feeling.
It will pass.
Adam...
why did he take us in?
Certain things are
still hidden from you.
But they will come to light.
Little by little.
It's all a matter of timing.
How do we know what's
right and what's wrong?
What's good
and what's evil?
By listening to our inner voice.
And choosing not to follow anyone
but ourselves.
Our true character shows
not only in our deeds,
but also in their purpose.
I am you.
I am your inner voice.
Never forget.
Everything's connected.
You,
me,
the past
and the future.
"Any passage into the
dead zone is forbidden.
Any attempt will result
in the death penalty.
Those are the rules.
We are the future!
Sic mundus creatus est!"
Sic mundus creatus est!
"Where were you?"
"There is nothing out there."
"Our only hope is in the passage.
Those without faith are already dead.
The prophecy will be fulfilled.
The passage will open
and lead us to paradise."
Those without faith are already dead?
They are all dead,
my family, my friends.
Everybody dies! In my time, in 6 days.
I don't need your fucking paradise.
I just want to go home.
What's behind that wall?
Why did Mum keep it all?
Great-Grandpa died ages ago.
I think it's because it's the only thing
that reminds her of her family.
Some things it's
impossible to let go of.
It's a shame I never
met Grandpa and Grandma.
Does Mum remember them?
Your mother was still
little when they died.
Come.
Were you born here?
My grandfather was. He
was the one who raised me.
Is your grandfather still alive?
No.
Have you considered
it could've been him?
- Who? My grandfather?
- No.
Your colleague, Ulrich.
No.
Why?
He called you right
before he disappeared.
The call lasted exactly 12 seconds.
Most likely a voicemail recording.
What did he want?
Nothing. He had the wrong number.
Did you keep the recording?
No.
Of course not.
The parents' testimonies
are in this one.
Thank you, Wöller.
Sure thing.
I had them set up an office for you.
Just down the hall.
Expectations lead to disappointment.
"Have hope", my mother used
to say, "not expectations.
You might just be surprised,
but not disappointed."
You expected a different kind
of colleague and got me instead.
Coincidence?
I don't believe in them.
I believe things come together
as they're supposed to.
Shall we?
Mum?
INVESTGATION FILE
STEEL DOOR?
It's remarkable
that people don't go crazy
knowing the futility
of their own existence.
An endless cycle of life and death.
What is the origin
of all this suffering?
Did you show Bartosz?
And he doesn't suspect anything?
He was always naive by nature.
The apocalypse
must come to pass.
Do you have doubts?
What must one do with a dead
forest so that new trees may grow?
One burns it all down.
There's very little time.
You must find
the missing pages.
Adam, they're waiting for you.
6 days left.
I'm on my break.
Whatever. Blow job is
40 euros, anal is 85.
Kinky games are extra.
But first I need to eat.
Go on, take them off.
You could say that I exist infinitely.
I'm here now,
and I exist for every second
between my birth and my death.
But I am always Jonas.
I'm the same as I was,
and yet not the same.
Just as you're not the same person
who came through that door
an hour ago.
But where is Jonas?
Where is my Jonas?
In the future.
In the future?
Yeah.
But he can't get back.
I tried to destroy the passage,
but I only managed to close it.
That's why he's still there.
So why are you here?
To put an end to everything.
Once and for all.
- That's the man!
- Which man?
The man with the watch. That's Noah!
Noah?
POLICE
Look out for the tiniest
discrepancies when people talk.
Every detail counts.
I've found Noah. Come to the Bunker.
Something wrong?
I have to go.
I don't have a driver's license.
I assume it'd be all right
if I rode with you tomorrow?
Yes.
Mum left it open.
What's that?
Dad's stuff.
Police documents and maps of the cave.
That's why Mum
goes in there every day.
I think she's looking for this.
A door.
In the cave?
It leads to the plant.
Everyone out there knows
something we're not supposed to.
Mum, Bartosz,
the police, too.
They all have a secret they're keeping.
Are you prepared?
Thanks for the coffee.
I'm glad to get rid of that thing.
Get in touch with Mum, okay?
Bye.
Ciao.
That's Noah.
Elisabeth found it. In a book.
It was at the store.
She said that was the man
who gave her the watch.
"8 January, 1921.
Sic mundus creatus est."
These people,
who are they, Charlotte?
- Why does your grandfather have this?
- I don't know.
CALL REJECTED