[MAN] What is reality?
Is it singular in nature?
Or do several parallel realities exist
at the same time?
To address this,
Erwin Schroedinger constructed
an extremely interesting
thought experiment.
Schrödinger's cat.
A cat is locked inside a steel chamber
with a small amount
of a radioactive substance,
a Geiger counter,
a vial of poison and a hammer.
As soon as a radioactive atom
disintegrates inside the steel chamber,
the Geiger counter triggers the hammer,
which smashes the vial of poison.
The cat is dead.
However,
due to the wave characteristics
of the quantum world,
that atom
is indeed disintegrated and intact.
Both states are true until we view it
in a definitive state of existence.
Until the moment, we check and see,
we don't know
if the cat is dead or still alive.
It continues to exist
in two superposed states.
The attributes "dead"...
and "alive"
exist here, in the microcosm,
at identical instances.
[MAN] But what if
the simultaneity of life and death
also applied to the world
in the macrocosm?
[JONAS] I'll make this right.
[MAN] Could different realities
exist side by side?
Could we split time
and let it run
in two different directions?
And as with this cat,
induce a state of death and life
simultaneously?
And if so,
how many different realities
could exist side by side?
[BARTOSZ] Martha!
Wait!
You can't go in there.
Bartosz?
[THUNDERING BANG, CLINKING]
What are you doing here?
Adam and the others, they lied to you.
He's not on your side.
He's going to kill you.
In the future.
He doesn't want to stop the apocalypse.
We're all doomed.
But not because of you, because of him.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYS]
- I know what the origin is...
- [DEVICE CLICKING]
and how it's all connected.
Please.
I can show you. You've got to trust me.
- [WHIRRING INTENSIFIES]
- [MUFFLED BANG]
["GOODBYE" BY APPARAT PLAYS]
♪ Fold out your hands
Give me a sign ♪
♪ Put down your lies ♪
♪ Lay down next to me ♪
♪ Don't listen when I scream ♪
♪ Bury your doubts and fall asleep ♪
♪ For neither ever ♪
♪ Nor never ♪
♪ Goodbye ♪
♪ Neither ever ♪
♪ Nor never ♪
♪ Goodbye ♪
♪ Neither ever ♪
♪ Nor never ♪
♪ Goodbye ♪
[LOUD TICKING OF CLOCKS]
IN BETWEEN TIME
[OLD TANNHAUS] As humans,
we struggle to accept our own mortality.
TANNHAUS FAMILY
One holds on to events that are long gone.
[CHURCH BELLS RING]
We long in vain
for a way to turn back time...
to reverse death.
But when time is relative
and nothing really ever passes,
and the simultaneous overlapping
of different realities is possible,
shouldn't it then also be possible
to bring back something
that was believed to be dead long ago
and to create a new reality
in which the dead live again?
If our life is defined
as everything between birth and death,
it exists there ad infinitum.
Could we succeed in cheating death
by finding a way
to bring back life?
There, in between time.
- [RAIN PATTERS LOUDLY]
- [SIREN WAILS]
[GRUNTS]
[BOTH PANTING]
FOR CHARLOTTE
[TICKING]
Tell me about paradise.
[SPEAKING ALOUD] Paradise...
is free...
of pain and sorrow.
Everything we've ever done
is forgotten there.
Any pain...
that we've ever felt...
is erased.
And...
all the dead...
live.
Adam will keep his promise.
The passageway will open up.
- [MENACING MUSIC PLAYS]
- [TICKING]
[WHIRRING]
- [CRANKING SOUND]
- [BUZZING]
[CRACKLING OF ELECTRICITY]
[BUBBLING SOUND]
[GRUNTS]
[GASPING]
- [TEARING SOUND]
- [CRIES OUT IN PAIN]
[PANTING]
[LOW BUZZING SOUND]
[DOOR OPENS]
[THUNDER ROLLS]
What do you want?
[BARTOSZ] You've been promising us
there's a way out for ages.
That we can stop the apocalypse.
But you still don't know
how the portal functions.
It will work.
I've seen it function here.
In the future.
And then? Hm?
When are you going to tell us the truth?
You don't want to go back.
Ending the apocalypse
isn't your intention.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYS]
This is larger than we are.
Larger than the apocalypse.
If the portal works,
we can use it to find the origin.
The one moment that started all of this.
And when we have found it
we'll destroy it.
And all of its results are gone.
That is paradise.
That's paradise?
It's two years we've been stuck here.
Two fucking years.
I don't want your fucking paradise.
I just want out of here.
[EXHALES HEAVILY]
[GRUNTS]
[BRANCHES CRACK]
Hello?
[SOFT, MYSTERIOUS MUSIC PLAYS]
I... I didn't want to startle you.
Sometimes I think the rain'll never end.
I am...
Silja.
Bartosz.
[SUSPENSEFUL TICKING]
[WHIRRING]
[QUIET BUBBLING SOUND]
[THUNDERING SOUND]
[ELECTRICITY CRACKING]
[SIGHS]
[POWER CUTS]
[CLAUDIA] We can start
a new series of experiments tomorrow.
I know we've been trying for a long time,
but it's going to work.
Jonas.
You can't lose your faith right now.
[JONAS] I can't do this anymore.
[MELANCHOLY MUSIC PLAYS]
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYS]
[JONAS GRUNTS]
[GASPING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYS]
[JONAS GASPS LOUDLY]
[WHEEZING]
What are you doing here?
- Are you following me?
- [SIGHS]
You made me a promise.
Adam made me a promise.
You said that the apocalypse must happen.
So we can get saved.
So all of us can be saved.
You cannot die.
- [GUN CLICKS]
- [GASPS]
[CLICKING]
[CLICKS]
[GUN GOES OFF]
You cannot take your own life.
Because your older self already exists.
Time won't permit it.
No matter what you try,
a force,
or someone,
will always stop you.
Elisabeth and I,
we found the passage.
You must keep your promise.
[GRUNTING]
[PANTING]
[MYSTERIOUS MUSIC PLAYS]
It will open up again.
And then you take us...
Adam takes us...
to paradise, finally.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYS]
He said we will become friends.
Before you betray me.
[SUSPENSEFUL TICKING]
[WHIRRING]
- [DOGS BARK]
- [HORSE NEIGHS]
[PANTING, GRUNTS AND SCREAMS]
That's good!
[SILJA WHIMPERS]
One more.
- [SCREAMS]
- [MIDWIFE] Yes!
- [BABY CRYING]
- [SILJA GASPING]
It's a boy.
[BABY CONTINUES CRYING]
What will you name him?
Hanno.
[SINISTER MUSIC PLAYS]
[OLD TANNHAUS]
Fate is playing a cruel trick on us.
[WHIRRING]
And yet we will always believe
that there is a way
to turn the tide in our favor.
If we only want it hard enough.
Man is able to pursue any goal,
no matter how unattainable it may seem,
over the course of an entire lifetime.
No resistance, no obstacle is great enough
to stop the human will in its tracks.
Isn't this stubbornness in our striving
what distinguishes us from animals
that know only short-term desire?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYS]
And throughout the ages,
is not this unquenchable thirst
at the heart of any progress
that is ever made?
No matter what motivates our will,
it guides us on our path.
We will only be able to let go
once we've reached our goal.
[SUSPENSEFUL TICKING]
[WHIRRING]
[PULSING SOUND]
[CLICKING, SHORT BEEPS]
[WHIRRING]
[APPARATUS POWERS UP LOUDLY]
[THUNDERING OF ELECTRICITY]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[SWOOSHING SOUND]
[OLDER JONAS] Why do you think
it still isn't working?
[NOAH] Maybe Claudia
doesn't want it to work.
Why do you even trust her?
Why did you trust him?
Adam?
He lied to you.
There is no paradise.
There is no world besides this one.
I know you think I'm becoming him,
but I'm not.
I know the portal will work.
I've seen it. In the future.
Everything repeats itself.
If I travel back,
I know I can change everything.
My older self tried it before.
But this time it's different.
The components
in the passage have changed.
This time it'll work.
She told you all that?
Claudia?
What do you really know about her?
She sometimes disappears
for days.
How does she know
all the things she knows?
She said that not all that's here
should exist here.
What did she mean by that?
- [DOOR OPENS]
- [GASPS]
Come inside.
Claudia's hiding something from us.
We can't trust her.
I hope you know that.
[CLAUDIA FROM OTHER WORLD]
He still doesn't suspect anything?
[CLAUDIA] No.
He has no idea
that you or the other world exist.
[CLAUDIA FROM OTHER WORLD]
You must guide him on his path.
The matter, it must not function yet.
You keep the knot up in your world
and I'll keep it in mine
Wait.
All these years,
the things Eve said I had to do.
Does she know everything?
Have you ever met her?
Who?
My older self.
No.
I still remember what she said exactly.
"If all of this works..."
"Our Regina will live."
I've thought about it all these years.
I just can't believe
that what she meant by that
was her suffering would repeat endlessly.
There must be a way to untie the knot...
without destroying all life in it.
A way for Regina to live.
Really live.
And I think
neither Eve nor Adam know this path.
But I'll find it.
In my world or yours.
Don't.
[LOUD BANG]
[BREATHING RAPIDLY]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYS]
[HISS, THUD]
[QUIET, UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYS]
Is Claudia not coming?
Noah is watching her.
We have to take extra care.
Put this in Claudia's hands.
And she must give it to Tannhaus.
She understands
why this is necessary?
Why everything has to happen again?
[SUSPENSEFUL TICKING]
[WHIRRING]
[BABY FUSSES QUIETLY]
[WOMAN] You have to be strong now, Hanno.
For your father too.
[QUICK STEPS APPROACH]
[BABY CRIES]
[POIGNANT MUSIC PLAYS]
Silja...
[WOMAN] We tried everything, Bartosz.
She wanted to name her Agnes.
[SUSPENSEFUL TICKING]
[WHIRRING]
[MOUTHING] Tell me about paradise.
Paradise...
is free
of pain and sorrow.
Everything we've ever done...
is forgotten there.
[ELISABETH SOBS]
[BABY FUSSES QUIETLY]
[SOBBING QUIETLY]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYS]
The passage will open.
And then
we will be there.
You,
me...
and Charlotte.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYS]
[ELISABETH WHIMPERS]
Where is she?
Charlotte.
[SCREAMS] Where is Charlotte?
For all these years
I wondered what he meant by that.
That we'd be friends
before you finally betray me.
Where is Claudia?
Does she have Charlotte? Are you in on it?
I don't know what you're saying.
[JONAS STRUGGLES FOR AIR]
Where is she?
Where is Charlotte?
I don't know.
I wish you endless suffering.
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[NOAH] I'll find her.
I'll bring her to us.
That's a promise.
[VOCALIZES]
[OLD TANNHAUS] You can choose as you want,
but your wants are chosen for you.
[SUSPENSEFUL TICKING]
[WHIRRING]
[OLD TANNHAUS] All the paths
we take in our lives,
every choice we make
is guided by our deepest desires.
[MYSTERIOUS MUSIC PLAYS]
[BEEPING]
It's pointless to fight
this sense of want.
[BUZZING]
It determines every one of our actions,
no matter how difficult
and unimaginable they seem.
[ELECTRICITY BUZZES]
[WHIRRING]
[WIND WHISTLING]
[METALLIC CLATTER]
Hannah?
Silja?
[DISSONANT MUSIC PLAYS]
I...
I'm looking for Jonas.
Yes.
He's changed.
Traveling has taken its toll on him.
[DOOR OPENS]
Jonas?
This is my daughter.
Silja.
She's your sister.
How did you find us?
[OMINOUS MUSIC BUILDING]
A few days ago...
There was this old woman...
She just showed up at our doorstep.
Eve.
She said...
she knew where you were.
And that you needed me.
You're right.
It's all my fault.
I ruined everything.
But I'm here now.
I'm here, Jonas.
[OMINOUS MUSIC INTENSIFYING]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYS]
Bartosz.
Get the room ready for them.
[THUNDER ROLLS]
[DOOR OPENS]
[HANNAH] What are you doing?
[JONAS] Silja.
She's not right here.
What's that supposed to mean?
"She's not right here"?
All the pieces must be
in the correct position.
She's in the wrong place.
So are you.
Mom.
[MUSIC INTENSIFIES SUDDENLY]
[HANNAH GRUNTING]
[FALLS SILENT]
[THUNDER CRACKS]
[THUNDER ROLLS]
Shh.
I want to show you a secret.
But we'll let your mom rest, okay?
Come.
[SUSPENSEFUL TICKING]
[CLICKING]
- [CHATTER]
- [WOMAN LAUGHS]
[DOOR OPENS]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYS]
I...
I have traveled far.
I need a place to rest.
Hanno!
Fix up a room for the gentleman.
[SUSPENSEFUL TICKING]
[DOOR OPENS]
[APPROACHING FOOTFALLS]
[ADAM] I was wondering when you'd come.
I know you think I lied to you.
That I took Charlotte away from you.
But I didn't.
You were right.
Claudia.
She lied to all of us.
The book.
Do you have it with you?
The last entries, they're gone?
You must find those pages.
They will lead you to Charlotte
and to your ultimate destination.
- [SINISTER MUSIC PLAYS]
- You will find your paradise, finally.
And Helge...
will help you.
Everything in life happens in cycles.
The sunset...
follows the sunrise,
over and over.
But this trip...
will be your last cycle in time.
Are you ready, Noah?
- [DRONING]
- [SUSPENSEFUL TICKING]
[WHIRRING]
[OLD WOMAN] The matter,
it can finally be stabilized.
But everything must happen again,
exactly the same way.
You have to lead
your younger self down the same path.
He must not act differently.
MISSING - MIKKEL NIELSEN
You have to set the course,
no matter how hard it may seem.
But you'll finally be able
to change everything.
WINDEN WELCOMES ITS NEW MINISTER
The apparatus.
He will repair it.
A JOURNEY THROUGH TIME
You must destroy the passage,
and the knot with it.
This time you'll get it.
Jonas.
You must never give up hope.
[MELANCHOLY PIANO MUSIC BEGINS]
[MUFFLED THUNDER ROLLS]
["PNEUMOTHORAX" BY BLUENECK PLAYS]
[RADIO ANNOUNCER] Weeks ago,
in the small town of Winden,
a 15-year-old boy disappeared
under mysterious circumstances.
Residents are now alarmed
after a second child has gone missing.
11-year-old Mikkel
has been missing for two days.
Please report any information you may have
to the Winden police.
♪ You sit there ♪
Hello, Claudia.
♪ In sole house ♪
♪ You only hope you'll burn ♪
♪ You could tell ♪
Don't you want to get in?
♪ You muddle all ♪
You have to stop Adam.
♪ Only so you will ♪
FOLLOW THE SIGNAL
♪ 'Cause you will burn alone ♪
♪ You will burn alone ♪
♪ This time ♪
[EGON] Have we met?
I'm sorry.
[OLD EGON] You are the White Devil.
♪ 'Cause you will burn alone ♪
[SHOT FIRED]
[NOAH] Charlotte?
No, this can't be true.
Mom.
Jonas.
[NOAH] I've been looking
for you all these years.
You are not my father.
[CLAUDIA] Regina?
I am so sorry.
[NOAH] You used me.
[ADAM] There is no man without guilt.
None of them deserves
a place in your paradise.
[MARTHA] Jonas?
[ADAM] We've come full circle.
[BARTOSZ] What about Martha?
[JONAS] Everything will be okay.
[SONG CONTINUING]
- [JANGLING SOUND]
- [MUFFLED THUD]
[MUSIC FADES]
Why did you bring me here?
They're the only ones who'll save us.
Save us?
They're the ones
who made all of this happen.
No.
They are the light.
[DOOR OPENS]
What do you want from me?
Isn't it strange
that the ones who despise us most of all
are the people who are most like us?
I'm not like you.
You and I have nothing in common.
I lived my whole life believing
this moment here
could never repeat itself again.
That I could never do
what my older self did.
Because I couldn't understand
how I could ever want
what she wanted then.
Now,
66 years have passed and I understand.
Some pain is never forgotten.
It brands us for our entire life.
You and I,
we share that pain.
We bear the same scars.
[MARTHA CRIES OUT]
[GRUNTS]
[MARTHA GASPS]
A memento.
So you never forget
which side you truly belong on.
[GASPING]
You may not understand it yet,
but by choosing us, you're choosing life.
Choosing Adam is choosing death.
[DULL THUD]
[MARTHA GASPING BEHIND GLASS]
No!
[SCREAMING] No! No!
[PUSHES LEVER]
No!
[MARTHA SCREAMS]
No! No!
[MARTHA SCREAMING]
[URGENT BEEPING]
[DULL THUD]
[ADAM SIGHS]
This can't be.
[DOOR OPENS]
[APPROACHING FOOTSTEPS]
Hello, Jonas.
[OPPRESSIVE ELECTRONIC MUSIC PLAYS]