Somehow, sometime
The future starts somewhere
I won't wait much longer now
Love is created through bravery
So don't think about it twice
We ride on fiery wheels
Towards the future through the night
JUNE 20, 2019
THE DAY BEFORE
MICHAEL COMMITS SUICIDE
MURDER IN MARBURG UNSOLVED
33 YEARS LATER
SEARCH FOR TWO FUGITIVE PERPS
STILL ON
ARIADNE
A STAGE PLAY
MURDER IN MARBURG UNSOLVED
33 YEARS LATER
Give me your hand
I'll build a castle out of sand for you
Somehow, somewhere, somewhen
The time has come
For some tenderness tonight
Somehow, somewhere, somewhen
DO NOT OPEN BEFORE NOVEMBER 4,
10:13 P.M.
Subtitle translation by Nathan Fritz