- [RAIN PATTERS]
- [THUNDER ROLLS]
[GRUNTS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYS]
[SIRENS SOUND IN THE DISTANCE]
[GRUNTS]
[OLD WOMAN] Why do we die?
- [TWO METALLIC BEATS SOUND]
- What is death?
MOM AND SISTER CAVE
Could we escape it
if we knew when to expect it?
Is the time
of our departure predetermined?
Our dying, part of an endless clockwork?
[BEATS CONTINUING]
We all have one truth in common.
We are born and we die.
[METALLIC BEATS CONTINUE]
No matter what path we take to get there.
["GOODBYE" BY APPARAT PLAYS]
♪ Fold out your hands
Give me a sign ♪
♪ Put down your lies ♪
♪ Lay down next to me ♪
♪ Don't listen when I scream ♪
♪ Bury your doubts and fall asleep ♪
♪ For neither ever ♪
♪ Nor never ♪
♪ Goodbye ♪
♪ Neither ever ♪
♪ Nor never ♪
♪ Goodbye ♪
♪ Neither ever ♪
♪ Nor never ♪
♪ Goodbye ♪
[WIND HOWLS]
LIFE AND DEATH
[ADAM] Your path
will always lead you here.
To Elisabeth.
To me.
Time plays a cruel game.
Have you decided?
Just one more day
and we can unravel this knot
once and for all.
But you must... like us all,
play your part in it.
Will you do your part?
Eve will never achieve her goal.
Her world is
no more deserving of salvation
than ours is.
[HISS, THUD]
ONE DAY UNTIL THE APOCALYPSE
[CREAKING SOUND]
[PIERCING BUZZ]
[HEARTBEAT-LIKE THUDDING]
[RATTLING, GROANING SOUNDS]
[GASPS, PANTING]
[GENTLE, UNEASY MUSIC PLAYS]
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
Let's go, to the nuclear power plant.
We don't have much time.
Jonas?
Nothing.
[KATHARINA] My God, where were you?
We were looking for you all yesterday.
Kilian said you were with him
and then you just vanished into thin air.
And where did he come from?
[KATHARINA SIGHS IN RELIEF]
It's all okay.
[KATHARINA] What's wrong?
I have to go.
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[HISS, THUD]
[PATIENTS MURMURING]
You wait by the door.
I'll get you out of here tonight
at ten o'clock.
And if anyone asks what you're doing,
say you couldn't sleep.
My mother changes shifts at five p.m.
She has a key card.
It's the same routine every day.
We'll bring Mikkel too.
Back home.
I swear.
I apologize.
For everything.
[MAN ON RADIO] One year
after the horrific events in Chernobyl,
five members of upper management
at the reactor
have been sentenced to years in prison.
Meanwhile, German nuclear power plants
have seen...
- [DOOR OPENS]
- Increased safety inspections.
[TANNHAUS] Oh, Charlotte.
You're back already?
[MAN ON RADIO] ...plants are safe.
U.S.A.: Germany's Foreign Affairs Minister
Hans-Dietrich Genscher
spoke at a UN conference in New York,
and urged global superpowers to take
further steps towards demilitarization.
Bremerhaven.
The German exploratory shuttle
"Polarstern" has been sent on...
Rough day today?
[RADIO] The goal is to explore the hole
in the ozone layer...
- [RADIO IS TURNED OFF]
- [QUIET TICKING OF CLOCKS]
Have you ever wondered
if it's possible to rewind time?
[CHUCKLES]
Yes. Yes I have.
And?
Possible, you think?
To go back and try changing anything?
You're such an adult now.
Adult enough.
For quite a while now, I've wanted
to be able to turn back time.
But my place is not in the past.
Nor in the future.
It's here,
with you.
Are those my parents?
I thought you said there were no photos.
That photo's not you.
Those aren't your parents.
That's my son and his wife.
And my granddaughter.
They died in a car accident.
That night, when it happened,
I woke up.
There was a noise down in the store.
There were two women.
Strange looking.
They were carrying a bundle.
That bundle was you.
They said
that on that night
everything would be taken from me.
And then I'd be given everything.
Then I got the call.
On the bridge,
a truck... had forced my son's car
into the river.
They only ever found the bodies of my son
and his wife in there.
My granddaughter...
was never found.
[RUSTLING]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYS]
This is the only thing
you brought with you.
[TICKING]
FOR CHARLOTTE
I don't understand.
Who are my parents?
Charlotte.
Who am I?
I just don't know.
I don't know.
[BELLS ON DOOR JINGLE]
[DOOR SLAMS SHUT]
[RAPID TICKING]
[HISS, THUD]
- Charlotte?
- Your colleague let me in.
I've got some questions regarding the dead
boy in the bunker. I hope that's okay.
Is everything all right?
[SIGHS] Just planning
a meeting for the demolition.
Everyone's nervous now.
In a year this'll all be gone.
I never imagined it would end like this.
But that's how it is.
Everything has its time.
When exactly did you get to Winden again?
Fall of '86.
Why?
And when did you start
working at this place?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYS]
Also around that time.
Did you get the shift schedules?
Were previous shift schedules
at the plant being archived?
Going back a ways.
What month are we talking about?
Not month.
1986.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYS]
[THUNDER ROLLS]
POLICE
[SIRENS SOUND IN THE DISTANCE]
[DOOR SQUEAKS AND SHUTS]
[METALLIC BANG]
[FOOTFALLS]
[THUNDER ROLLS]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYS]
[BREATHING RAPIDLY]
Hello, Claudia.
[THUNDER ROLLS]
[SOLDIERS CHATTERING]
[HELICOPTER FLIES OVERHEAD]
[SOLDIER] Men!
[MELANCHOLY MUSIC PLAYS]
Come on.
We need to go.
[MOUTHING] I'm not going with you.
[MOUTHING] They're dead, Daddy.
We haven't...
found a thing yet.
[MOUTHING] If they're alive,
why haven't they come back?
Why aren't they looking for us?
They're dead.
Everyone here is dead.
I don't want to do this anymore.
POLICE
You're from another world?
What do you want?
I'm here to guide you into the light.
There are two groups out there
fighting for superiority in time travel.
Light and dark.
I want you to join our side.
Eve's side.
Eve?
I know you thought you could trust him,
but you can't do that.
- Who?
- Jonas.
He belongs to the dark.
Jonas?
He's dead.
No.
He's not.
He wants to destroy both worlds forever
and untie the knot.
He doesn't know
that death is what he'll want in the end.
But all his impulses on this journey
will lead to that end.
But Eve wants to save both worlds.
I don't understand.
Jonas said we could change it.
We change one component,
we change the entire world.
It was you who told him that.
Your older self.
[THUNDER ROLLS]
A positive feedback loop.
Jonas opened the passage in 2020.
The older Jonas
had previously shut it in 2019.
After it'd been opened
in the summer of 1986 for the first time.
In all three moments, they left behind
traces of cesium residue,
a component of the black matter.
Half-lives.
In every cycle,
at each of these three moments,
this cesium is carried through the tunnel
and back before it's completely decayed.
It exponentially expands endlessly.
So the passage is the result.
It must continue to exist forever.
Everything has to happen again.
Jonas has to bring the matter
to the passage.
And opening one of the nuclear plant
barrels has to trigger the apocalypse.
Everything in this loop repeats.
Life...
and death.
[HISS, THUD]
[WIND WHISTLES]
WARNING! SECURITY ZONE
NO TRESPASSING
[GRUNTING SOFTLY]
- What exactly is in these containers?
- I don't know.
But in the summer of '86
an accident happened here.
A disaster.
And what remained,
the substance in the containers,
that makes it possible
to travel through time.
They're bringing the truck
with the barrels in today.
We'll wait until nightfall.
Ah!
Uh.
[MARTHA] Oh, shit.
It's all right. Just a scratch.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYS]
What's wrong?
The scratch.
She had it.
The Martha who took me here.
Everything repeats itself.
They wanted to change it.
But if you turn into her
everything stays the same.
Why did Eve lie?
She said there was a way to save it.
My world.
I've got no idea about your world,
but this here is my world.
If I can keep those barrels closed,
if there's a way for all this to stop...
And if that's what she wants?
All of this to still happen?
Maybe she doesn't want us to stop it.
Maybe it's us...
who make it all start.
- But why would she want that?
- Because they're lying!
I've always done
what the others have asked me to.
And it just made everything worse.
I have to go back to Eve.
I finally want to know what the truth is.
Jonas.
[MENACING HUM]
Jonas, wait!
[HISS, THUD]
[BUS APPROACHES]
You need your own invitation?
In or out?
Sorry. If I walk from here,
how long before I get to Winden?
I'd reconsider if I were you.
Winden is like a black hole.
Once you're inside, you'll never get out.
Are you all right?
It's complicated.
Everything's complicated.
What brought you here?
It's complicated.
My mother recently died.
My father lives here.
Until a few days ago
I didn't even know who my father was.
She told me.
Right before she died.
You think it's possible
to bring someone back who's died?
How would that work?
You'd have to get them before they died.
I'm Peter.
Charlotte.
[HISS, THUD]
- [DOOR OPENS]
- [CHARLOTTE] Peter?
Did they let you out of school early?
- I'm not going.
- What do you mean you're not going?
What are you doing here?
I was with Aleksander.
The day Mads disappeared,
Helge was working at the plant.
His shift was over at 6:00 p.m.
and Mads vanished around 6:21.
You're not serious, are you?
I don't know why Helge said that.
He had nothing to do with Mads,
or with the boy you found.
He was with me.
Your father might be involved
in the murder of two boys.
- [PETER, WHISPERING] She's not deaf!
- Erik is still missing, Peter.
That penny, what does it mean?
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYS]
Ulrich is right.
It's all connected somehow.
Ulrich?
I'm going back to work.
[DOOR CLOSES]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYS]
[HISS, THUD]
[THUNDER ROLLS]
[ELISABETH GASPS]
[MAN] Hey, wait.
[BREATHING RAPIDLY]
Don't be scared.
[THUNDER ROLLS]
[DISHES RATTLE]
[FOOTFALLS]
[BREATHING RAPIDLY]
[MAN] You live here alone?
I asked if you live alone.
[SIGHS]
I have no idea when I last ate warm food.
[GULPING]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYS]
[ELISABETH BREATHING RAPIDLY]
[BOTH GRUNT]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[GRUNTING CONTINUES]
- [MAN GRUNTS]
- [PETER GROANS]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[BOTH GRUNT]
[MAN GRUNTING]
[MAN GROANS]
- [MAN YELLS]
- [PETER GASPS]
[MAN GASPS, ]
- [GRUNTS]
- [PETER WHEEZES]
[PANTING]
[GRUNTS]
[ELISABETH GRUNTING]
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYS]
[SOBBING]
[MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
[THUD]
[SWOOSHING SOUND]
It's time.
You have to let her go, Franziska.
[MELANCHOLY MUSIC PLAYS]
[DOOR RATTLES AS IT SHUTS]
- [CRACKLING, RATTLING]
- [WHIR OF ELECTRICITY]
[ELECTRICITY CRASHING]
[BEEPING]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYS]
[CLAUDIA] Adam must never untie the knot.
You need to lead them.
Jonas, Noah, Elisabeth.
I don't understand.
- Lead them where?
- Along the same path.
Again and again.
We have to maintain the knot.
In your world you must do all you can
to maintain it, as I must in mine.
Jonas. You have to guide him.
And then, later, defy him.
[METALLIC CLICKING]
- How will I know what I'm supposed to do?
- It's all in there.
We'll see each other again. Soon.
- [WHIRRING, DULL BOOM]
- Stop, wait!
[HISS, THUD]
Jonas.
What if it's the truth though?
And only one world can make it.
Either yours or mine.
You decided long ago.
You want to return.
To your world.
[MELANCHOLY STRING MUSIC PLAYS]
I didn't want any of this.
You have to believe it.
You didn't want any of this?
Last night...
You didn't want that?
This here is wrong.
I am wrong here.
[MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
So that's wrong then?
[HISS, THUD]
[BIRDS CAW]
Are you following me?
What do you want?
[MENACING MUSIC PLAYS]
The key card.
You're crazy.
I don't want to hurt you.
The key card.
I knew it immediately.
You came into the ward and I knew you.
How do I know you?
[BOTH GRUNTING]
Momma, let go!
What did you say?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYS]
[GRUNTS]
[MUSIC INTENSIFYING]
- [MUSIC STOPS]
- [KATHARINA GASPING]
[KATHARINA GROANS]
I'm not your mother. You're from hell.
It is the devil who sent you.
You're not real.
[BOTH GASPING]
- I made you go away.
- [THUD]
I made you go away.
[GRUNTS]
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYS]
[GRUNTING]
Here. Go inside, all right?
I'll grab everything else.
[DISTANT DOG BARKING]
[DOOR CREAKS OPEN]
[DOOR CLOSES]
So...
Here we are again.
Shall I make us some hot chocolate?
Or are you hungry?
Michael?
Are you hungry?
[DOOR OPENS, KEYS JINGLE]
[DOOR CLOSES]
Mom? Is everything all right?
You're bleeding.
[WASHING HANDS]
Mom, what happened?
Mom, say something.
What is that?
Is that from Ulrich?
- You shameful tramp!
- [KATHARINA CRIES OUT]
[SOBBING]
You are unworthy
of the name I gave to you!
[SOBBING]
I should have made you go away too.
["IN THE WOODS SOMEWHERE" BY HOZIER PLAYS]
♪ My head was warm ♪
♪ My skin was soaked ♪
♪ I called your name ♪
♪ Till the fever broke ♪
♪ When I awoke ♪
♪ The moon still hung ♪
♪ The night so black ♪
♪ That the darkness hummed ♪
♪ I raised myself ♪
♪ My legs were weak ♪
♪ I prayed my mind
Be good to me ♪
♪ An awful noise ♪
♪ Filled the air ♪
♪ I heard a scream ♪
♪ In the woods somewhere ♪
♪ I clutched my life ♪
♪ And wished it kept ♪
♪ My dearest love ♪
♪ I'm not done yet ♪
♪ How many years ♪
♪ I know I'll bear ♪
♪ I found something ♪
♪ In the woods somewhere ♪
[DOOR OPENS]
[MARTHA] What is this place?
[JONAS] It's what will become of you.
Adam and Eve.
And so it begins all anew.
You lied to us.
You said we could save both worlds
when it was only one.
Or is that a lie as well?
I want to return!
Now! To my world!
Naturally you'd want that.
But there's no way back for you at all.
What are you saying?
A human lives three lives.
The first one ends
with the loss of naiveté.
The second one
with the loss of innocence.
And the third
with the loss of life itself.
Yours ends here and now.
- What?
- [DOOR OPENS]
[APPROACHING STEPS]
[DISTORTED ORGAN MUSIC PLAYS]
You've accomplished what you were sent
to this world to accomplish.
[MARTHA] We've accomplished nothing.
She said we have to stop the apocalypse.
The containers in the plant...
You will understand everything.
When it's right for you to understand.
Who are you?
I'm sorry.
[MARTHA GASPS]
- [JONAS GRUNTS]
- [MARTHA] Jonas!
[SOBS]
[MARTHA CRYING]
Jonas, please.
Stay with me. I can't...
[DOOR SHUTS]
Jonas, please. [SOBBING]
Jonas, I'll make this right.
I... [SOBBING]
No!
[POIGNANT MUSIC PLAYS]
[MUSIC CONTINUES]