[Adam] Where did it all begin?
Where did this begin?
In the past?
In the future?
Who can say where anything begins?
[rumbling]
Welcome to the future.
I want all this sick shit
to stop happening!
[Adam] Will we ever be able to know
the origin of it all?
Or will there always be something...
something that came before?
And before that,
and before that.
Is there a beginning and an end?
Or is everything connected
in one endless loop?
Do the words "beginning" and "end"
describe the same exact moment?
[young Jonas] Mikkel?
Mikkel!
["Goodbye" by Apparat plays]
♪ Fold out your hands ♪
♪ Give me a sign ♪
♪ Put down your lies ♪
♪ Lay down next to me ♪
♪ Don't listen when I scream ♪
♪ Bury your doubts and fall asleep ♪
♪ For neither ever ♪
♪ Nor never ♪
♪ Goodbye ♪
♪ Neither ever ♪
♪ Nor never ♪
♪ Goodbye ♪
♪ Neither ever ♪
♪ Nor never ♪
♪ Goodbye ♪
["Irgendwie, Irgendwo, Irgendwann"
by Nena plays on clock radio]
[in German] ♪ Somehow, sometime ♪
♪ The future starts somewhere ♪
♪ I won't wait much longer now ♪
♪ Love is created through bravery
So don't think about it twice ♪
♪ We ride on fiery wheels
Towards the future through the night ♪
Boo!
[chuckles] Good morning.
Good morning, sleepyhead.
So?
- What are your plans today?
- Uh, I'm going to the lake.
You know
there's going to be a storm, right?
- Morning.
[Jonas mutters]
[Hannah] Today's Katharina
and Ulrich's party.
- Don't get back too late again, okay?
- Sure.
Are you sure you don't want to come with?
[Michael] Anyone want coffee?
Fuck.
[refrigerator opens and closes]
[quiet, tense music]
All right, got to go.
[dismal music]
Are you okay, Papa?
Yes, I'm good.
Everything's all right.
I just had déjà vu.
Okay. See you later.
[door opens]
[door closes]
[gasps softly]
Don't you think it'd be good
if you got out once in a while?
Couldn't you give it a try at least?
Hmm?
For me.
I still have to finish my painting.
[unsettling music]
JUNE 20, 2019
THE DAY BEFORE
MICHAEL COMMITS SUICIDE
[soft, melancholy music]
[church bell tolls]
[dismal music]
Mm.
[chuckles softly] Uh-huh.
What is it?
Hmm?
[Katharina] Hmm.
I've got so much to do today.
My period is starting
and I haven't shaved in ages.
- I'm sorry.
- You know I don't care.
- I'm sorry, I can't.
- Yeah.
- [door opens]
- Ulrich, I can't.
Couldn't you just knock for once?
I'm sick, I think.
I've got red spots all over.
Maybe it's dengue fever?
[Katharina] Come here.
Shit!
You've got rubella.
Of all the days for this,
you had to choose this one?
Grr!
Come on, let's go to the doctor.
MARBURG MURDER UNSOLVED
33 YEARS LATER
SEARCH FOR TWO FUGITIVE PERPS
STILL ON
[Regina] Are you coming later?
[footsteps approaching]
- Are you coming to the hotel for lunch?
- Yes, of course. Yeah. Mm-hmm.
Is everything all right?
Yes.
Are you sure?
Mm-hmm.
[Regina sighs]
See you later.
[breathing heavily]
[door opens]
[sighs] Hey.
Where are the kids?
I was at the nursing home.
Are we going to keep doing this?
Are you going to continue
to not believe a word I say?
Say something.
Maybe that's the reason
all this has happened.
I get nothing from you. Nothing.
It's like you're dead in there.
I think I might...
I think it's best if I go alone
to the Nielsens' tonight.
[oppressive music]
[Bartosz] Know about the woman
who drowned here?
Knock it off!
When the water is clear,
you can still see her dress down there.
And sometimes, you can feel her hands
on your feet when you swim by.
Oh, but that's not all there is.
When she's hungry, she'll even...
pull people down with her.
Ah!
[Bartosz laughs]
You're an asshole!
Ha-ha, very funny.
[Martha] Are you coming tonight?
I think so.
Sometimes I wonder if my parents
are actually happy together.
Or if parents just learn
to put up with each other.
Are yours happy?
I don't know.
[serious music]
What's that?
Looks pretty old.
[Martha] That's Saint Christopher.
The patron saint of travelers.
[both laugh]
- [Martha] Don't ask.
- [laughing]
[car horn honks]
[honking]
Hey, Jonas. Weren't you going to the lake?
Martha and Magnus left a while ago.
[Mikkel] Ultimate fist bump?
[Katharina] Don't touch that little pest.
He's got rubella.
Where's your bike?
Do you want a ride?
- See you tonight, then.
- Someone will be happy to see you.
And, I mean, it's not Magnus.
- Ulrich.
- [Mikkel] Why?
Everyone knows
that Martha has a huge crush on Jonas.
[Katharina] Stop it. Come on,
we'll give you a ride to the lake.
- No, that's all right. Really.
- [Ulrich] All right.
- Okay.
- Get back to it, Romeo.
[Katharina] Good Lord.
- Magnus.
- You... You weren't moving.
I... I thought you weren't breathing.
And he said he saw a dead body, and I...
Well, still breathing.
Cool.
[chuckles softly]
ARIADNE
A STAGE PLAY
What is it?
[chuckles softly] I...
I was just thinking...
Wouldn't you love to know
what was coming next?
You mean the future?
Yeah, or...
maybe just in the next five minutes.
I...
sometimes get this feeling...
like something's happening.
You know?
Attack!
Fuck.
What is it?
I have to go.
Where to?
We gave Grandma Ines
a tablet for her birthday.
- I'm supposed to teach her how to use it.
- Okay.
So...
I'll be there later.
Jonas.
Why do you have a raincoat with you?
Because it's supposed to rain later.
See you.
[oppressive music]
Weren't you leaving?
Are you okay?
I thought I had more time.
Why does everyone say that?
To "have time."
How can you say that
when it's time that has us?
Did something happen?
[mysterious music]
You seem different.
I want to tell you something.
I've wanted to for a while.
You and I are perfect for each other.
Never believe anything else.
[soft, melancholy music]
I have to go now.
[soft, sad music]
[vehicle approaching]
- [Ulrich] Hi.
- [Hannah] Hello.
[Ulrich] Did the long ride strain you?
[Hannah] I hope you guys have
a fantastic anniversary.
[Katharina] Crazy, isn't it?
It's already been 25 years.
Thank you for the glasses, Hannah.
[Hannah] Well, no problem at all.
[Ulrich] Yeah, who would've thought?
25 years.
- I have to pee.
- [Ulrich] Go against that tree over there.
[oppressive music]
[Katharina] Could he use your bathroom?
Hannah?
[dismal music]
[Katharina] Hello?
- Go into the woods, then.
- No, sure. Sorry.
It's... It's right next to the entrance.
I think I just had déjà vu or something.
- Mikkel has grown so much.
- He eats like an ogre.
- Takes after his mother.
- Really?
[chuckles softly]
[door closes]
[dismal music]
[urinating]
[toilet flushes]
[oppressive music]
[breathing heavily]
[door opens and closes]
- Another hit?
- Uh-uh.
- Later, then.
- See ya. Martha.
Um...
I'm sorry I can't come over later,
but we're doing dinner.
My mother and the hotel...
I couldn't find a way to get out of it.
I just wanted to let you know.
It's okay.
And... I...
I really like...
your hair that way.
I mean, you look good.
With your hair.
Oh, shit. You know what I mean.
Well, um...
see you tomorrow.
- Ciao.
[thunder rumbling]
MURDER IN MARBURG UNSOLVED
33 YEARS LATER
Wöller, it's me.
I want you to look into something
if you can.
Confidentially.
["Irgendwie, Irgendwo, Irgendwann"
by Nena plays]
[in German]
♪ Somehow, somewhere, some when ♪
♪ The time has come
For some tenderness tonight ♪
♪ Somehow, somewhere, some when ♪
Hello, Martha.
- Hey.
- Hi.
Glad you could be here.
- Do you want a drink?
- Yeah, thanks.
- [Katharina] Hey! Well?
- Hey.
It was going to be a garden party
but this seemed much cozier.
I have tiramisu for later.
Oh, this is my favorite song.
I have to dance.
- ["Heaven Is A Place On Earth" plays]
- [Katharina] Oh!
- The champagne?
- Under the table.
- Oh, that's great.
- Magnus, we're so proud of you.
I think a driver's license
is the only logical next step.
- No.
- Yeah.
- Really?
- Of course.
- Charlotte!
- Awesome!
- Here. But you have to dance.
- No.
- Yes! Come on.
- No, Katharina, please!
- Hey.
So...
You know where this goes?
There. Over there.
Where's Peter?
He's under the weather.
And Michael?
Something like that.
- I'll take this over.
- Okay.
Champagne!
Ah! Ooh!
Thank you.
Hannah.
Come on, live a little.
Glad you made it.
- Glad you're all here tonight. Cheers!
- [guests] Cheers!
- Hello.
To our health.
- Hey, you. Dance with me, you old man.
- Well, of course.
♪ They say in heaven love comes first ♪
♪ We'll make heaven a place on earth ♪
[thunder rolls]
[door opens]
[door closes]
[mournful music]
[Michael] Jonas?
I thought I heard you come in.
Aren't you supposed to be
at the Nielsens'?
Did anything happen?
Hey.
Are you all right?
What happened to your hair?
[quiet, unsettling music]
I know, Dad.
What do you know?
I know everything.
What?
"Ultimate fist bump."
[thunder rolls]
What?
- What made you just say that here?
- Because I know.
I know it all.
I know that your real name
is Mikkel Nielsen, Dad.
[gloomy music]
It's okay.
I'm so sorry.
["Never Gonna Give You Up"
by Rick Astley plays]
♪ Never gonna give you up
Never gonna let you down ♪
♪ Never gonna run around
And desert you ♪
♪ Never gonna make you cry... ♪
[Ulrich] Even younger and prettier here.
- The third one, I thought you'd burst.
- [Katharina] You're mean!
- [Ulrich] That sweet little girl.
- Sweet little girl? That's Magnus.
- What's wrong?
- I can't sleep.
- Oh, no.
- [Ulrich]... thought he was God's gift.
- Oh, my God. You're hot.
- [Ulrich] Place didn't serve tourists.
- [Ulrich] By the North Sea.
- Okay, I'll take you up. Come on.
- [Hannah] I used to love that dress.
- [Ulrich] Oh, '80s fashion. My God!
And...
- Sleep tight. Good night.
- Until I'm asleep, could you stay here?
[indistinct chatter downstairs]
[growls]
Scoot over.
[inhales deeply]
[Michael] So you're from the future, then?
[scoffs softly]
And why are you here now?
I need to ask you for something.
What?
Don't do it.
Don't do what?
It's Ulrich's and Katharina's anniversary.
Of course you didn't go.
I mean, you chose to stay home.
Something was different, though.
I should've known something was wrong.
Jonas, I have no idea
what you're talking about.
[loudly] Don't lie to me, okay?
I saw it. God damn it!
I know you're going to hang yourself
in your studio.
[thunder rolls]
Have you written the letter yet?
What letter?
The letter you wrote to me.
Not to me, my younger self.
The one marked "Do not open
before November 4, 22:13 p.m."
DO NOT OPEN BEFORE NOVEMBER 4,
10:13 P.M.
Exactly to the minute when you disappear.
I'm here so that you don't do it.
It's intertwined.
Like an endless loop.
But when you... when you kill yourself...
that's where it begins.
[quiet, ominous music]
Promise me you won't do it.
Papa, you have to promise that.
Please!
Promise!
[dismal music]
[quiet music playing downstairs]
[Martha] You forgot this at the lake.
I put it on a string.
Thank you.
I thought about
what you said at the lake today.
[stammering] About Grandma's
and the Internet?
[chuckles softly]
Well, I think you're right.
Okay.
[thunder cracks]
The night that you disappeared...
you were here and then you were just gone.
Did you return to the cave?
And was the passage still there?
I didn't find it.
Someone took me there.
Who?
You.
[gloomy music]
What do you mean?
- [Michael] We were at the caves.
- What'll you give me for it?
- [Bartosz] An ass-kicking.
- [Franziska] What's in here is worth 500.
But I'll let you have it for 200.
Your dad's loaded anyway.
[Bartosz] Cut the bullshit! Yeah.
Now it's mine. Jackpot!
- [Michael] Then there was a strange sound.
- [metallic vibrations echoing]
[Magnus] What was that?
[Michael] We were sure someone was there.
[Bartosz] Someone over there?
Shit.
What's this?
[rumbling]
[whirring]
[Magnus] Shit. What's going on?
[Bartosz] What's wrong with the lights?
Come on, run!
Now!
Let's go!
- [Michael] We ran. Then I lost you.
- [Jonas grunts]
[Michael] I turned around
and you were gone.
[panting]
[Michael] But suddenly,
you were back again.
Quick.
Let's go.
[Michael] You said
there was something out there, far off.
Something evil.
You said we had to go into the cave.
You took me all the way back to the door
and through the tunnel.
I was so scared.
But you held my hand.
And you said
we had to stay there all night.
But everything would be all right
in the morning.
And when I woke up you were gone.
All these years I've tried to understand
why you would do that.
But then, after a while,
it all started to fade away.
It became unreal, like a dream.
But that can't be right.
I never did that.
I saw myself today.
Mikkel.
It's coming back now, this jacket, you.
Like it's all fixed.
Maybe you're not here to stop me.
But rather to show me
what it is I have to do.
Maybe you only show me the letter
so I'm aware what's in it.
That I can go and you live on.
No, that's not it. That's not it!
Adam said
I could prevent it all from starting.
If you don't kill yourself
none of this will happen.
But if none of this happens,
you won't be born.
And maybe your role in all this
is much greater than you think.
And perhaps...
I'm just a tiny section of a huge tumor
that is much bigger
than any of us can imagine.
- Someone said that to me already.
- Who?
I did.
God doesn't err.
He has a plan.
For all of us.
[door opens and closes]
[thunder rolls]
I have waited for this moment
for a very long time.
Who are you?
Are you with Adam?
There are two sides out there.
He is the darkness.
I don't follow him, I follow the light.
He lied to you.
He led you back here to ensure
it all happens exactly as it always has.
No, that's not right.
Adam wants this too!
No, he does not.
He doesn't want to fix things,
he wants to destroy them forever.
Your role in all this
is much greater than you think.
You alone can finally stop all this.
What are you saying?
You have to fight yourself.
Fight Adam.
But if I don't exist,
if I'm never born, then...
then how could Adam ever come?
I have seen the world without you.
Trust me...
it's not what you're expecting.
There are moments
when we must understand
that the decisions we make influence
more than just our own fates.
It's not just about you and Mikkel.
It's about everyone.
Your mother,
your friends,
Martha.
You alone can save them.
What are you saying?
[thunder rumbling]
We all have to make sacrifices.
Your father has to make sacrifices too.
[oppressive music]
[Michael] It's okay.
[thunder rolls]
[thunder rumbling]
This the apocalypse, then?
[thunder cracks]
It's a bit disappointing.
I thought it would be louder than this.
- Gaudier.
- [laughs]
If the world ended tomorrow
and everything started over...
what would you wish for?
A world without Winden.
And you?
["The Twisted Olive Branch"
by Asaf Avidan plays]
♪ Love is deep ♪
[thunder rumbling]
[rain pattering]
♪ With the sound of a thousand waves ♪
♪ Hit the shore ♪
♪ Love is black ♪
♪ The darkest raven will crawl ♪
♪ With the pain
Of a thousand black feathers ♪
♪ And the hate for a dove ♪
♪ Fly, black raven! ♪
♪ My heart's an open hatch ♪
♪ Oh, fly, black raven! ♪
♪ Hope is small ♪
♪ The smallest light beam will come ♪
♪ With the dance
Of a thousand flakes of dust ♪
♪ Hope is wrong ♪
♪ A weary sailor will crawl ♪
♪ With the hate
Of a thousand black stones ♪
♪ And a prayer for more ♪
♪ Fly, black raven! ♪
♪ My heart an open hatch ♪
♪ Oh, fly, black raven! ♪
♪ Come back, raven! ♪
♪ Twist your twisted leg ♪
♪ Upon that twisted olive branch ♪
[melancholy instrumental]
♪ Fly, black raven! ♪
♪ My heart an open hatch ♪
♪ Oh, fly, black raven! ♪
♪ Twist your twisted leg ♪
♪ Upon that twisted olive branch ♪
[thunder rumbling]]
[melancholy music]
[Michael] "Dear Jonas,
by the time you read this, everything
will have already happened, irrevocably.
It can't be changed anymore.
I would have liked
to explain things to you sooner,
but I hope once you understand
how everything is connected,
you will understand my decision.
The truth is a strange thing.
You can try to suppress it,
but it will always find its way
to the surface.
We make a lie into our truth
in order to survive.
We try to forget,
until we can't anymore.
We don't even know half of the mysteries
of this world.
We're wanderers in the darkness."
[door opens]
[footsteps approaching]
[man] You could've told him.
Adam, you could've told him
what his function is in all this.
What journey you've really sent him on.
Not long before the last cycle.
[tense music]
[woman] Magnus,
we all have to make sacrifices.
[whirring]
[electronic bubbling]
[intense music playing]