The beginning is the end.
And the end is the beginning.
Everything is connected.
The future,
the past
and the present.
I couldn't tell her who her mother was.
Just as I can't tell you
what your provision is.
And what I have to do today.
I have thought about this
moment for many years.
My older self wanted
to tell me something.
But he couldn't.
If you knew what I know now,
you wouldn't do what you must,
which enables me to get to this moment.
I can't exist in the here and now
if you don't go exactly
the same way that I did.
We're never free
in what we do,
because our will isn't free either.
Everything is prepared.
You must go now.
27 June 2020
The day of the Apocalypse
FEDERAL REPUBLIC OF GERMANY
PASSPORT
My future self
tried to shut the hole.
To reverse it all.
The passage was closed,
but the cycle wasn't broken.
But you said that we could change one
factor of the equation so that he...
So I'd be successful the next time.
Then none of this sick
shit will ever happen.
Mikkel won't vanish.
Michael won't hang himself.
Your father won't die.
The big things and the little
things don't follow the same rules.
We won't be able to change
the grand scheme of things...
but the details.
We change a grain of sand,
and with that, the whole world.
What was Grandma like?
I mean, as a mother.
Why would that suddenly
be so interesting?
She isn't dead, you know?
Meaning what?
She was here.
Last autumn.
After Mikkel disappeared.
She...
she left this for you.
Here.
She said that she was sorry.
And that if she could turn back time...
she'd change the way things happened.
I'll come back.
I promise.
Where are you going now?
Do you know what this is?
It's a search warrant
for the nuclear plant.
The plant has special conditions.
The judge issued
the warrant immediately.
I believe,
given the situation,
he may be interested in
what there is to find there.
Because of the
investigation against you.
WARRANT
I might not be able to prove
that my brother was murdered,
but I will get you for
what's happening here.
You must get me out.
There's no way.
This is happening.
You cannot let him onto the site!
Maybe it's better this way.
Maybe it's good if
everything's out in the open.
Martha, I didn't want any
of this. Please believe me.
- But listen to me now.
- What are you doing here?
Come in.
Why are you here?
What do you want?
You have to come with me, please.
- It's my fault everyone here is doomed.
- What?
Everything here will
explode in a few hours.
Everything will start over again.
The future will start, a new cycle.
What are you saying?
Believe me, please.
You just have to trust me.
This isn't right.
We aren't right.
Please leave.
No.
- I can't let you go this time.
- You're hurting me.
I saw you die once. I
won't let that happen again.
- Let me go.
- I can't do that.
I promised you I'd make it right.
And I will.
6 hours until the Apocalypse
Where's the machine?
Where is the damn machine?
My mother has it.
That's not right.
That's not how it should happen.
This is all my fault.
Why didn't he tell me what to do?
Why did he tell me all this?
He tells me how it works, then
he doesn't tell me what to do?
It could be you did exactly
what he wanted you to.
To show us how it works. That
could've been your only job.
Fuck.
- Where are you going?
- To find the fucking machine!
Hello?
Jonas?
Follow the signal
What is this?
The passage.
- We are reopening it.
- But you said you wanted to shut it.
In the future.
Or the past, your future.
It took me a long time to accept
that I had to help start the
disaster I wanted to avert.
- How do you know all this?
- The past 12 months.
You taught me everything,
about the future and the past.
Everything that has happened.
Everything that will happen.
There are two parties.
Adam and Sic Mundus want a new world.
You and I want to save this one.
Who is Adam?
- What is this?
- This is the only area that's safe.
Please don't, Martha.
Please.
Why are you doing this?
Because I know what will happen today.
About Mikkel...
Did you mean it?
That means...
I didn't want any of this, Martha.
You kept me alive.
I'm still here because of you.
Jonas will come back. Everything
will happen as it always has.
But I can't stop hoping that
I can still change things.
I have to try.
Jonas comes back.
Promise me you won't leave
this bunker for anything.
No matter what.
I'm so sorry.
POLICE
MISSING
Charlotte. I thought
you were still sick.
- Is Clausen here?
- No.
Clausen had Aleksander arrested
and got a search warrant for the plant.
He's on his way there.
Charlotte.
I... have something to tell you.
At the... nuclear facility...
Aleksander buried
something in the concrete.
Radioactive waste.
And I helped him.
I'm sorry.
That's the cause.
- What?
- It's all connected.
He said it has to do with
something in that facility.
- Jonas knew that.
- Jonas was found?
No, he travelled here
from the future.
We have to go!
Wöller!
Come on!
For Charlotte
Damn it, Charlotte, where
are you? Is Franziska with you?
Call me when you get this.
We're leaving.
To go where?
I don't think I'm...
certain what to believe.
But he said
only those in the...
the bunker...
will survive.
What about Mum and Franziska?
It will all be okay.
4 hours until the Apocalypse
I don't quite understand
what you're hoping for.
The site is huge
and tomorrow there's
the controlled shut down.
My mother always said
just because a task is daunting
doesn't mean you can't deal with it.
What's behind this door?
The, um...
the cooking bank of the old reactor.
It hasn't been used since the '90s.
I'm going to have a look.
You can't open the door
to have a look. Radiation.
And, honestly, I don't think you'd
find anything in there anyway.
Photo album
Michael
Just after high school graduation
Katharina.
How do you work this machine?
Where did you get it?
How can Mikkel come back home?
Even if I told you, it can't happen.
You don't want him to come back.
Then you wouldn't have been born.
I wish it was that simple.
But things in the past
just can't be changed.
Mikkel can't come back
because I already exist.
Mikkel belongs here. You don't.
You shouldn't exist at all.
Yeah.
I'd give my life for his
if only I could.
But I can't, damn it! Because
my future already exists.
Just like you won't be
able to bring Mikkel back.
So why did you decide to come?
Well, I thought I could
prevent the origin.
It's beyond our control.
Adam is the endpoint.
I might not be able to prevent
myself from becoming what he is.
But what's become of me,
I can stop.
I know that I've been lied to.
You never saved anyone.
None of them.
We can't escape our fate,
none of us.
Neither you nor I.
You're not waging war against God.
You're waging it against humankind.
Here are the last pages.
You used me.
Had me do what you wanted.
But now I know what I have to do.
Claudia was right.
You still don't understand
how this game is played.
What are you waiting for?
It's time who plays this game with us.
You think it's your destiny to kill me,
but that's not your fate,
just as it isn't mine
to die here and now.
Only when we've freed ourselves
of emotion can we be truly free.
Only when you're willing to
sacrifice what you hold dearest.
Charlotte is your daughter.
She is Elisabeth's daughter
and her mother.
There is no man without guilt.
None of them have earned
a place in your paradise.
Agnes.
This knot
can only be undone
by destroying it completely.
We cannot
escape our fate.
- What's happening?
- This is time.
We connect past and future.
What is that?
It's Jonas. He's reopened the passage.
It's that thing that
Mikkel went through?
Yes.
Martha.
Is everything all right?
Who locked you in here?
Martha, wait, wait, wait! You
can't go out there! Martha!
- What was that?
- Fuck.
It was the same noise.
Like the cave.
Fuck. You got the device?
It's not up there now.
And Mum's gone too. Martha as well.
Do you think she's with him?
With Jonas?
Noah was right. He was
right about everything.
I'm telling you guys, Jonas
is the reason for this shit.
Where are we going?
Bring the machine to the bunker,
near Helge's cabin.
You don't have much time.
And you?
I have to find my mother.
And Martha.
Jonas!
2 hours until the Apocalypse
Hey, Martha, call me back.
They're both not answering.
My father. He's with
Elisabeth in the bunker.
- He wants me to go there.
- To the bunker?
Shit.
Something's going on.
I'm going.
If they're not home in half
an hour we'll go join your dad.
Where are Mum and Franziska?
I have no idea.
So this Noah guy says he's your father
and he's from the future...
or, no, the past.
And he says the apocalypse
starts in Winden today?
And you think this is all connected
to the containers in there?
- What is that?
- The cooling pool of the old reactor.
Apparently it's been sealed off
and become part of the greenfield.
When?
That, um...
I don't exactly know,
but that's nothing unusual.
Sealing off the old reactor is a...
It's the start of the dismantling.
I want you to break it open.
Really?
Yes.
You can't keep him another night.
He hasn't done anything.
This is all nonsense.
When can Aleksander be visited?
I understand.
Regina.
Please don't be scared.
It really is me.
I am so sorry.
I didn't mean to just leave like that.
I'll explain.
But now you have to come with me.
Regina.
I'm so sorry.
Noah.
You look different now.
You know, I mean, since last time.
He sent you, didn't he?
Adam.
I've always wondered
when you turn into him.
I won't.
I will never do the things he did.
He said you'd say that kind of thing.
He also said we'd be friends.
Before I'm betrayed.
Why do you follow him?
What made you follow her?
Claudia.
We both want to believe.
We fasten ourselves to the
salvation that's promised.
If you kill him...
you kill all hope of salvation.
He is the saviour.
You'll be the saviour.
What is that?
Read it.
It's from Martha.
This can't be real.
You must save her.
Bartosz, Magnus
and Franziska.
And later, me and Agnes.
This circuit has to be finished
for the next cycle to begin.
Just as the prophecy foretells.
And so that Martha can live.
No, this isn't right.
Martha.
Regina.
That's you.
You are Claudia.
Follow the signal
Your colleague's in the old reactor.
Mum?
Jonas?
You're back.
You're really back.
I was looking for you.
- I'm here to tell you...
- I know it... all.
When we were standing in the
rain, I know why you said that.
Mikkel...
I know everything.
At the lake, that was you.
You and I are perfect for each other.
Never believe anything else.
And so the circle is closed.
Jonas, who is that?
Tell her who I am.
I told you all the game's
pieces are in position already.
All that's needed is a little push.
You keep lying!
You wanted it all the exact same way.
You're the trigger!
The trigger is in us all.
Each and every one of us.
Why do you want this?
Why do you want the
awful future repeated?
What is created today
will begin the end.
The dark matter must be created
so that I can lead it to
its destiny in the future.
The end of this world.
And I am the trigger,
just not for what you think.
I am the trigger for...
only what will make you
what I am today.
You'll be all right. You'll
be all right. You'll be all right.
Some pain you can't forget.
Mar...
- You'll carry this pain all your life.
- Look at me! Look at me!
Until you are finally ready
to let go.
Of her.
You can stop me.
Or you can try to save her.
You'll know what you have to do.
Please don't leave.
Martha.
Please.
Please don't go.
Don't open that! Stop.
Don't open that!
This is a hazard.
No, Mrs. Doppler. This is our elephant.
You have no idea what
this all really is.
- What is all this, then?
- It's not about the missing people.
This is about the future,
how it's connected,
connected to all of our pasts.
- Open it.
- No!
- Open it!
- Please don't. No! It's a mistake.
Magnus, open up!
Magnus! Open up!
Hurry!
Magnus!
What the hell? Who are you? Hey!
That's him.
It's you.
You are Jonas.
- This is all your fault.
- Yeah, it's my fault. I know.
- But I'm here to save you all.
- From what?
- From the apocalypse.
- Apocalypse?
What about Martha?
I said what about Martha?
For Charlotte
Mum.
Elisabeth.
It's beginning.
Where are we going?
I promise.
I'll make it right.
I'm not who you think I am.
Wait. Martha, this isn't possible.
- I don't understand...
- We don't have time now.
I'll explain later, but
you have to come with me.
What time did you come from?
The question isn't what time,
the question is what world.