9 HOURS SINCE MIKKEL’S DISAPPEARANCE
Jonas!
LIES
The victim is male,
between 10 and 12.
Time of death... about 16 hours ago.
The burns around the eyes are strange.
Like they’re melted.
No signs of sexual abuse,
no sperm, no foreign DNA.
One thing is strange. Take a look.
Apart from the burns,
the ear canals are destroyed.
The inner ear was damaged too.
Both eardrums have burst.
From an
extremely loud sound?
Yes... Or pressure,
caused by a nosedive.
Or by intense rotation,
such as in a centrifuge.
Do you know what otoconia are?
Tiny grains in the ear canals
that help us differentiate
between up and down.
They can get confused.
When the body rotates, for example.
We lose our balance.
With this boy, none of the grains
are where they should be.
Mikkel!
- What were you doing up there?
- Ouch! Are you crazy?
What were you doing?
I heard you guys talking at school.
About the caves...
and Erik’s drugs...
so I thought...
I don’t know what I thought.
I’m sorry about Mikkel.
Monday night in Winden,
another boy vanished without a trace.
According to the police, the 11-year-old
was last seen
with his siblings in Winden Forest
near the nuclear power plant
and the Winden Caves.
The police are asking the public for tips
that may help solve the case.
Citizens’ groups are also coordinating
searches with local authorities.
For two weeks now, a 15-year-old boy
from the Winden area has been missing.
Police have declined to comment on whether
the two missing persons cases are related.
Hello.
It’s Mom.
You’re probably out.
About Mikkel...
I really don’t know what to say.
Are Martha and Magnus okay?
Should we...
Can we help?
Call me when you hear this.
We’re very worried.
Okay.
I...
I couldn’t get hold of Ulrich.
Shouldn’t we go see the kids?
They’ve organized various search parties.
I have to go.
Where were you last night?
I woke up around midnight.
You weren’t there.
Couldn’t sleep.
I went into the garden
to get the bushes ready for winter.
The car wasn’t there either.
We were out of cord.
I had to go to the gas station.
First Mads, now Mikkel.
It’s exactly like back then.
When Dad’s brother disappeared,
- how old was he?
- MOTHER’S DAY 1986
Your father was 15.
Mads was three years younger.
And he was never found?
We talked about Erik.
In the forest.
Mikkel thought that was the worst.
When someone isn’t found.
Mikkel’s coming back.
Definitely.
Hey, this is Martha.
Leave a message after the beep.
Hey, Martha.
It’s me.
I, um...
Just call me back, okay? Bye.
The dead boy is neither Mikkel nor Erik.
This kid is disfigured.
The eyes are completely burnt.
There was red soil
all over his clothes.
But none where he was found.
And it looks as if someone
dressed the boy in clothes from the ’80s.
The shoes, the Walkman...
From the ’80s as well.
We found this around his neck:
a one-pfennig coin from 1986
on a red cord.
The cassette contains this.
We fall through the time stream
Then awaken from a dream
- And Mikkel and Erik?
- Wöller will coordinate the search.
For now, we won’t make
the discovery of the body public.
We’ve got two missing kids
and a dead, unidentified boy.
Contact the central office
for missing persons.
Question everyone in the proximity.
Everyone!
In the cave... there’s a door!
I found a door.
Can I have a word?
There’s a door inside the cave,
leading to the nuclear plant.
We need a search warrant. Maybe Mikkel
accessed the grounds through that door.
That’s a high security area.
You can’t just enter.
- Maybe he climbed the fence.
- The barbed wire?
We checked the fence.
There was no damage to it.
You’re thinking the same thing, right?
That the cases are all connected.
The dead boy, Erik, Mikkel.
Maybe you were right.
It’s just like it was back then.
Mads disappeared at the same spot.
Close to the nuclear power plant.
Something is wrong up there...
I just know it.
Okay.
I’ll request the search warrant.
The police will be here soon.
We need to get rid of them tonight,
Jürgen.
Tonight.
They’ll be snooping all over here.
Maybe someone else should do it.
Because of Erik...
They’ll be watching.
Are you blackmailing me?
No, why?
Do you know the difference between
successful and unsuccessful people?
Exactly.
So do it tonight.
And you talk to no one.
Understood?
FOREST HOTEL WINDEN
Can I help you?
I need a room.
Must be horrible for you.
First, the thing with your son Mads...
and now your grandson.
But...
the whole town is mobilizing.
We’ll find him.
Maybe.
Maybe not.
A JOURNEY THROUGH TIME
Ulrich,
it’s me, Charlotte.
Aleksander blocked
the search warrant immediately.
But we’re talking to the judge now.
Please call me back once you hear this.
END CALL
WINDEN CAVES
And so, at least hypothetically,
because of these gravitational anomalies,
it is possible to bend time and space.
Will we ever be able to travel through
a black hole to see what lies beyond?
And what price would we pay?
How far would scientists go?
Aleksander, please open the gate.
Let me in.
There’s a door in the caves.
Maybe he got through it.
Let me search the slope.
Let me search your section of the caves!
Please.
I can’t just let anyone in there.
It’s a high security area.
My employees patrol it every day.
If Mikkel were here, we’d know it.
You fucking asshole!
Why are you doing this?
Are you trying to ruin me?
We’re talking about my son!
I’m coming back with a search warrant!
And then you’ll open this goddamn gate!
You asshole!
Open up!
I’m sorry, Ulrich.
- Honestly.
- Open up, man!
ENTER CODE
3 ATTEMPTS REMAINING
INVALID CODE
2 ATTEMPTS REMAINING
What are you doing here?
- I wanted to see you.
- Come on.
What is this?
Why are you here?
I’m so sorry.
Have you found out anything?
Stop it, please.
Please.
I can’t do this, not now.
I’ll call you, okay?
WHERE IS THE CROSSING?
Car unidentified, unidentified...
“Identification: Van”?
Obendorf has a van...
POLICE RECORDS
Jankowski!
Did you question Obendorf?
Yes. Why?
The files say he was on duty at the plant
when Erik disappeared.
He works in the storerooms
and as a driver sometimes.
- Did you confirm that?
- Of course.
So he has access
to the power plant grounds?
- I think so.
- Was he at the plant last night too?
No idea.
I haven’t spoken to him yet.
Drop it.
Drop it, I said!
Ulrich!
What is this?
Is this yours?
We did it together.
Erik and I.
We sold some at the school.
Were you at the plant yesterday?
Yesterday? No, why?
What’s this?
When people bring their junk here,
you always find something.
Erik was saving up for a scooter.
Where’s my boy?
I don’t know, Jürgen.
Do you think
they’ll find him?
I hope so.
Do you think he had a secret?
Mikkel?
No, Dad.
Do you think
he was keeping something from us?
Why do you say that?
Do you miss him?
I think I miss a notion of him.
I don’t know who he really was.
Maybe we never know that.
What a person is really like.
Did you love him?
Whatever happens,
you’ll tell me the truth.
Don’t lie to me.
Whatever it is.
WHERE IS MIKKEL?
WHEN IS MIKKEL?
Who are you?
Why? Who are you?
Mikkel.
I live here.
Ulrich. And I live here.
You going to grow roots?
- You’re at the wrong house, fool.
- Hey, Ulrich!
Come on, we need to go.
Yes, Katharina, I’m coming.
Are you dense? You don’t live here.
Who is that?
The Grim Reaper. Can’t you tell?
Ouch! Katharina.
CHERNOBYL - HALF A YEAR LATER