Get dressed.
- Martha?
- It can't be.
You... You're alive.
This is not Martha.
What's going on here?
He's right.
I'm not Martha.
Not your Martha.
I promised I would fix everything.
So none of this would happen.
So that you don't die in my world,
and I don't die in yours.
So that Ulrich, Dad, Mikkel...
so... so that you all come back.
So all this can really end.
♪ Fold out your hands ♪
♪ Give me a sign ♪
♪ Put down your lies ♪
♪ Lay down next to me ♪
♪ Don't listen when I scream ♪
♪ Bury your doubts and fall asleep ♪
♪ For neither ever ♪
♪ Nor never ♪
♪ Goodbye ♪
♪ Neither ever ♪
♪ Nor never ♪
♪ Goodbye ♪
♪ Neither ever ♪
♪ Nor never ♪
♪ Goodbye ♪
THE SURVIVORS
♪ Open up your lovin' arms
I want some, want some ♪
♪ I set my sights on you ♪
♪ And no one else will do ♪
♪ And I ♪
♪ I've got to have my way now, baby ♪
- This is Ines...
- and Michael Kahnwald.
We're not at home.
Leave a message after the beep.
Mrs. Kahnwald? This is
Mr. Dietmann from the postal service.
I've been trying to reach you
for three months now.
If you don't pay the overdue bill,
we'll disconnect your phone next month.
Please get back to me as soon as possible.
MISSING FOR THREE MONTHS
I think you did the right thing.
Even if the coffin is empty.
To... To get closure.
At least you have each other.
They're here for support.
At least we have each other.
Now we can get our closure together
looking at a coffin that's empty.
Tell everyone where you were
when Mads vanished.
Fucking your girlfriend!
He was screwing Claudia Tiedemann
when my son went missing.
If only you'd devoted as much energy
to finding your own son
as you devoted to your mistress,
then maybe Mads wouldn't have gone.
I'm not sure what you're saying.
WHERE IS CLAUDIA TIEDEMANN?
You're not sure what I'm saying?
NUCLEAR POWER PLANT HEAD
MISSING SINCE JUNE 26,
THE DAY HER FATHER
WAS FOUND DEAD AT HOME.
POLICE
Scientists are
still looking for an explanation
for the events of June 27, 2020.
The presumed origin for the catastrophe
is assumed to be
the small town of Winden.
A French team of scientists believes
it possible that our world stood still
for a fraction of a nanosecond
on June 27th,
possibly causing
the divergence of tidal forces.
This would explain the global tidal waves,
weather phenomena
and disturbances of electrical systems,
which in turn could explain
the countless number of airplane crashes
and the simultaneous electrical outages
at nuclear power plants worldwide.
There is currently
no sign of the situation stabilizing...
How are you?
Mom.
You're leaving already?
I'll return before the sun goes down.
In five days this'll all be closed off.
Men, over here!
This whole area's been evacuated.
We have orders
to seal off the restricted area.
What?
To wall it in.
Why do this to her?
- You're from a parallel world?
- Where Mikkel didn't disappear?
And I'm mute.
And Jonas doesn't exist?
Where we're all dead because your world
ends just like ours does?
That's all bullshit.
I'm not dead...
I'm here.
How were we found?
How did you know where we are?
Jonas told me that.
I thought
there was no Jonas in your world.
He traveled.
From your world to mine.
You're lying.
I never went to your world.
Did you write the letter?
What do you really want here?
Did Adam send you here?
What did you use to travel?
Tell me what you used to travel!
You're late today.
The machines aren't running yet.
You have a visitor.
So you're the reason
why his mood
is even worse than usual today.
You have no reason to fear me.
People may say
that I'm not quite right in the head,
but I assure you
that I see more than those of you who see.
- Do you know this child?
- No.
- No, sorry.
- Do you know this child?
- No.
Ulrich.
I know you?
Do you know where this child could be?
WHO HAS SEEN MICHAEL KAHNWALD?
12 YEARS OLD
Maybe that lunatic got him.
What lunatic?
Get your hands off me, lady.
Hey, Ulrich.
Ulrich?
I thought you weren't coming today.
Katharina?
We're going to be late for history.
Katharina Albers.
Hello?
Now I remember.
What's her deal?
The old lady ain't all there.
Come on.
Hey.
Hey! What lunatic?
What lunatic?
Someone escaped
from the asylum this summer.
He grabbed Michael
and took him to the cave.
It was in the paper.
You stay the hell away from Mikkel.
And from Ulrich.
VISITOR'S PASS - NIELSEN, TRONTE
I told all of this to the police already.
It won't take long.
I promise.
And... this is for the newspaper?
The week before Claudia vanished...
did you notice anything?
Her appearance always mattered to her.
She was always put together.
But that week...
twice she wore the same thing.
She forgot appointments. Her hair...
I thought...
it all had to do
with that dog and the old woman.
She showed up a few days
before Mrs. Tiedemann disappeared.
And she said that the dog was hers,
but then she didn't take it with her.
After that,
Mrs. Tiedemann was somehow just...
changed.
Excuse me.
We're looking for
a woman in her late forties,
blonde hair.
And a teenage girl, red hair.
If they're not on the wall,
then they're not here.
This is good.
If they're not here...
then...
Maybe they've traveled.
CALL FOR WITNESSES
WE ASK FOR YOUR ASSISTANCE
MISSING TIEDEMANN, CLAUDIA
Hey!
The man from the psych ward.
- Why didn't you tell me about that?
- I thought I'd already explained this.
You can run in here as often as you like
demanding information on the whereabouts
of Michael Kahnwald,
but you won't get any.
Someone tried to kidnap my son
this summer.
Your son?
You can't identify yourself,
nor do you have any proof
you're actually the boy's mother.
You're not registered anywhere.
You don't have a birth certificate.
And, astonishingly,
you don't even want to reveal your name.
In three months nobody's seen him.
He doesn't go to school.
He's not at the house.
This man from the psych ward...
I actually remember that.
My mother told me about that.
He could... He could have tried
to do it again, couldn't he?
Listen to me carefully.
The boy hasn't disappeared.
Child Protective Services know
where Ines and Michael Kahnwald are.
After what happened this summer,
they decided the boy needed some time off.
And the lunatic was returned to the ward.
Where he's been the past 34 years.
What was that you just said?
Let me be totally clear.
If you turn up here again,
I'm putting you in protective custody.
- What is his name?
- Afternoon.
What is his name?
Hello, Regina.
Is that your dog?
She was my mother's dog.
Would you like a ride?
Strange, you know.
Looks just like Gretchen.
I assume that's why she kept her.
Do you think...
that all these things with Mads
and my mother... could be connected?
I just don't know.
The week before she vanished, did she say
anything to you about an old lady?
And...
did she say anything about me?
I...
just thought
she might have said something.
I'll...
get out right here...
and walk the rest of the way.
Regina...
if there's anything you might need...
My name is Claudia Tiedemann.
I am one of the only survivors
of the apocalypse on June 27, 2020.
Almost three months have passed
since the catastrophe.
It is still unclear
exactly what triggered
the events in Winden that day.
But the God particle,
if we can stabilize it,
maybe it'll give us a way back,
to return to the past.
We could save them...
all.
I'll take a look around upstairs.
Looking for food.
Are you?
MOM AND SISTER
Where do you sleep?
CAVE
What's going on?
Why are you here?
Are you following us?
I told you before,
we want nothing to do with you.
You want to protect her, I get it.
So do I.
And I will.
After you get killed.
MACHINE FACTORY TANNHAUS
I'm sorry.
About Jonas.
Since we got here...
he's...
He's changed.
How did you get here?
We traveled.
At the exact moment
when everything was destroyed.
He didn't want to come here.
This is just what happened.
The device is empty.
Here, in 1888, nuclear material
is somewhat hard to come by.
And this here?
What is this? The workshop.
The blind guy.
Does he know who you are?
Where you come from?
Come with me.
I need to show you this.
The young woman.
Is she one of you?
A traveler?
When I found you, now, that was a sign.
A god-sent miracle.
Whatever this woman means to you,
don't forget what we are going to create.
Paradise!
Every calamity can be reversed.
Every pain,
destroyed before it even exists.
A perfect world.
Sic mundus
creatus est.
Excuse me.
Can I help you?
I... uh...
I'd like to visit someone.
He's lived here for 34 years.
The inspector?
Do I know you?
You look familiar somehow.
Are you related to him?
He's my husband.
I see.
So you're one of them.
Those women
who go for lunatics or prisoners
because they can't find anyone else.
I'm off duty. Come back tomorrow.
That's Saint Christopher.
Patron saint of travelers.
He renounced the devil
and carried the creator of the world.
My mother also had one.
I've traveled a very long way.
Let me see him.
Please.
He was just released
from solitary.
My colleague will let you out.
Ulrich.
Katharina.
I'll get you out of here.
I swear.
Excuse me.
Excuse me, what are you doing here?
What do you want?
I...
I'll call security.
No.
You won't.
Jasmin.
Right?
Hell is empty.
And all devils are here.
Shh.
At some point you have to decide.
For us.
Or against us.
I...
saw Regina today.
She's all grown up.
I've wondered all these years...
if she could...
Claudia never said who the father is.
You're right.
I have to decide.
Mom?
Tronte?
Regina.
What brings you here?
I'm so sorry.
But it has to happen.
I don't understand.
She said...
it's the only way to save you.
MOM AND SISTER CAVE
LENTIL SOUP
What did he say to you?
What do you mean?
The boy.
Forget it.
I'm not a little kid anymore.
Why do you carry that around
everywhere you go?
What's in there?
Where are Mom and Franziska?
We'll find them.
Everything will be okay.
♪ Is this love
That's been keeping me up all night ♪
♪ Is this love that I'm feeling ♪
Clear the table.
I said, clear the table.
Must I always repeat myself?
♪ Broken sleep ♪
♪ All too human ♪
♪ A malady ♪
♪ It's gazing through when I would ♪
♪ Dream me a dream
Soft as a pillow ♪
Dream me a dream ♪
♪ Dream me a dream ♪
♪ Shapes of smoke ♪
♪ All too human ♪
♪ They grow ♪
♪ Like titans ♪
♪ I would like to fall ♪
♪ Silence every call ♪
♪ If I could fall ♪
♪ Fall ♪
♪ I would like to fall asleep ♪
MOM AND SISTER CAVE
♪ Silence every call ♪
♪ If I could fall ♪
♪ I would like to fall ♪
♪ Take my word for it ♪
♪ In the dark ♪
♪ Words can follow ♪
What is this?
It's like a secret society.
Old Tannhaus is the only one of them left.
His father was convinced
he could supersede
the rules of time and space.
He dedicated his life to doing just that.
And so did his son.
They tried to build
a time machine back then?
Jonas is trying to rebuild things
the way he saw them.
He's been here already.
Not now.
In the future.
He asked you something earlier.
If Adam had sent you.
He said...
that Adam killed Martha.
Who is this Adam?
He didn't tell you that?
He is Adam.
Jonas.
We don't know our end.
But our end
knows us.
Salvation...
or there is damnation.
We can indulge
in the illusion of free will if we want.
But we cannot escape our ultimate destiny.
The choices we make
in each world may be different,
but still
they converge on the same moment.
Things may not happen in the same way,
or at the same time.
But they always happen.
You believed a world without you
would be a better one.
But they're all going to die.
Mikkel.
Mikkel will die.
Everyone will die.
The apocalypse occurs
in my world just as it does in yours.
In mine,
it will happen in three days' time.