Dark Season 2
English Signs Only (HI)
for English Audio (Web-DL)
AND IF YOU GAZE LONG INTO AN ABYSS,
THE ABYSS ALSO GAZES INTO YOU.
FRIEDRICH NIETZSCHE
JUNE 21, 1921
JUNE 27, 2020
BEGINNING OF THE LAST CYCLE
DO NOT OPEN BEFORE NOVEMBER 4,
10:13 P.M.
JUNE 2020
JUNE 21, 2020
SIX DAYS UNTIL THE APOCALYPSE
MARTHA: COME TO THE BRIDGE.
ALEKSANDER TIEDEMANN
DIED JUNE 27, 2020
JUSTYNA JANKOWSKI
TORBEN WÖLLER
DIED JUNE 27, 2020
MICHAEL KAHNWALD
DIED JUNE 21, 2019
MARTHA NIELSEN
DIED JUNE 27, 2020
FROM UNKNOWN SENDER:
THIS EVENING.
PASSPORT
CAVE ENTRANCE
No, no!
Stop!
Who are you?
You are hiding it!
There, behind the wall! We saw it!
We followed the signal.
Till the dead zone.
You're hiding God!
You mustn't hide God.
He's not yours alone!
No!
Why did Mom keep it all?
Great-Grandpa died ages ago.
It's a shame
I never met Grandpa and Grandma.
Does Mom remember them?
THE GREAT MIKKEL HOUDINI
INVESTIGATION FILE
STEEL DOOR?
THE KYBALION
HERMETIC PHILOSOPHY
That's the man!
The man with the watch. That's Noah!
POLICE
PETER: I'VE FOUND NOAH.
COME TO THE BUNKER.
CALL REJECTED
Subtitle translation by Nathan Fritz