Where did it all begin?
Where did this begin?
In the past?
In the future?
Who can say where anything begins?
Welcome to the future.
I want all this sick shit
to stop happening!
Will we ever be able to know
the origin of it all?
Or will there always be something...
something that came before?
And before that,
and before that.
Is there a beginning and an end?
Or is everything connected
in one endless loop?
Do the words "beginning" and "end"
describe the same exact moment?
Mikkel?
Mikkel!
♪ Somehow, sometime ♪
♪ The future starts somewhere ♪
♪ I won't wait much longer now ♪
♪ Love is created through bravery
so don't think about it twice ♪
♪ We ride on fiery wheels
towards the future through the night ♪
Boo!
Good morning.
Good morning, sleepyhead.
So?
- What are your plans today?
- Uh, I'm going to the lake.
You know there's
going to be a storm, right?
- Morning.
Today's Katharina and Ulrich's party.
- Don't get back too late again, okay?
- Sure.
Are you sure you don't
want to come with?
Anyone want coffee?
Fuck.
All right, got to go.
Are you okay, Papa?
Yes, I'm good.
Everything's all right.
I just had déjà vu.
Okay. See you later.
Don't you think it'd be good
if you got out once in a while?
Couldn't you give it a try at least?
Hm?
For me.
I still have to finish my painting.
20 June 2019
The day before Michael commits suicide
Mm.
Uh-huh.
What is it?
Hm?
Hm.
I've got so much to do today.
My period is starting
and I haven't shaved in ages.
- I'm sorry.
- You know I don't care.
- I'm sorry, I can't.
- Yeah.
Ulrich, I can't.
Couldn't you just knock for once?
I'm sick, I think.
I've got red spots all over.
Maybe it's dengue fever?
Come here.
Shit!
You've got rubella.
Of all the days for this,
you had to choose this one?
Grr!
Come on, let's go to the doctor.
Murder in Marburg
unsolved 33 years later
Search for 2 fugitive perps still on
Are you coming later?
Are you coming to the hotel for lunch?
Yes, of course. Yeah. Mm.
Is everything all right?
Yes.
Are you sure?
Mm.
See you later.
Hey.
Where are the kids?
I was at the nursing home.
Are we going to keep doing this?
Are you going to continue
to not believe a word I say?
Say something.
Maybe that's the reason
all this has happened.
I get nothing from you. Nothing.
It's like you're dead in there.
I think I might...
I think it's best if I go alone
to the Nielsens' tonight.
Know about the woman
who drowned here?
Knock it off!
When the water is clear,
you can still see her dress down there.
And sometimes,
you can feel her hands on
your feet when you swim by.
Oh, but that's not all there is.
When she's hungry, she'll even...
pull people down with her.
Ah!
You're an arsehole!
Ha-ha, very funny.
Are you coming tonight?
I think so.
Sometimes I wonder if my parents
are actually happy together.
Or if parents just learn
to put up with each other.
Are yours happy?
I don't know.
What's that?
Looks pretty old.
That's Saint Christopher.
The patron saint of travellers.
Don't ask.
Hey, Jonas. Weren't you
going to the lake?
Martha and Magnus left a while ago.
Ultimate fist bump?
Don't touch that little pest.
He's got rubella.
Where's your bike?
Do you want a ride?
- See you tonight, then.
- Someone will be happy to see you.
And, I mean, it's not Magnus.
- Ulrich.
- Why?
Everyone knows that Martha
has a huge crush on Jonas.
Stop it. Come on, we'll
give you a ride to the lake.
- No, that's all right. Really.
- All right.
- Okay.
- Get back to it, Romeo.
Good Lord.
- Magnus.
- You... you weren't moving.
I... I thought you weren't breathing.
And he said he saw a dead body, and I...
Well, still breathing.
Cool.
Ariadne
a stage play
What is it?
I...
I was just thinking...
wouldn't you love to know
what was coming next?
You mean the future?
Yeah, or...
maybe just in the next 5 minutes.
I...
sometimes get this feeling...
like something's happening.
You know?
Attack!
Fuck.
What is it?
I have to go.
Where to?
We gave Grandma Ines
a tablet for her birthday.
- I'm supposed to teach her how to use it.
- Okay.
So...
I'll be there later.
Jonas.
Why do you have a raincoat with you?
Because it's supposed to rain later.
See you.
Weren't you leaving?
Are you okay?
I thought I had more time.
Why does everyone say that?
To "have time".
How can we say that
when it's time that has us?
Did something happen?
You seem different.
I want to tell you something.
I've wanted to for a while.
You and I are perfect for each other.
Never believe anything else.
I have to go now.
- Hi.
- Hello.
Did the long ride strain you?
I hope you guys have
a fantastic anniversary.
Crazy, isn't it?
It's already been 25 years.
Thank you for the glasses,
Hannah.
Well, no problem at all.
Yeah, who would've thought?
25 years.
- I have to pee.
- Go against that tree over there.
Could he use your bathroom?
Hannah?
Hello?
- Go into the woods, then.
- No, sure. Sorry.
It's... it's right next to the entrance.
I think I just had déjà vu or something.
- Mikkel has grown so much.
- He eats like an ogre.
- Takes after his mother.
- Really?
- Another hit?
- Uh-uh.
- Later, then.
- See you. Martha.
Um...
I'm sorry I can't come over later,
but we're doing dinner.
My mother and the hotel...
I couldn't find a way to get out of it.
I just wanted to let you know.
It's okay.
And... I...
I really like...
your hair that way.
I mean, you look good.
With your hair.
Oh, shit. You know what I mean.
Well, um...
see you tomorrow.
- Ciao.
Murder in Marburg unsolved
33 years later
Wöller, it's me.
I want you to look into
something if you can.
Confidentially.
♪ Somehow, somewhere, somewhen ♪
♪ The time has come
for some tenderness tonight ♪
♪ Somehow, somewhere, somewhen ♪
Hello, Martha.
- Hey.
- Hi.
Glad you could be here.
- Do you want a drink?
- Yeah, thanks.
- Hey! Well?
- Hey.
It was going to be a garden party
but this seemed much cosier.
I have tiramisu for later.
Oh, this is my favourite song.
I have to dance.
Oh!
- The champagne?
- Under the table.
- Oh, that's great.
- Magnus, we're so proud of you.
I think a driver's license
is the only logical next step.
- No.
- Yeah.
- Really?
- Of course.
- Charlotte!
- Awesome!
- Here. But you have to dance.
- No.
- Yes! Come on.
- No, Katharina, please!
- Hey.
So...
you know where this goes?
There. Over there.
Where's Peter?
He's under the weather.
And Michael?
Something like that.
- I'll take this over.
- Okay.
Champagne!
Ah! Ooh!
Thank you.
Hannah.
Come on, live a little.
Glad you made it.
- Glad you're all here tonight. Cheers!
- Cheers!
- Hello.
To our health.
- Hey, you. Dance with me, you old man.
- Well, of course.
♪ They say in heaven love comes first ♪
♪ We'll make heaven a place on earth ♪
Jonas?
I thought I heard you come in.
Aren't you supposed to be
at the Nielsens'?
Did anything happen?
Hey.
Are you all right?
What happened to your hair?
I know, Dad.
What do you know?
I know everything.
What?
"Ultimate fist bump."
- What made you just say that here?
- Because I know.
I know it all.
I know that your real name
is Mikkel Nielsen, Dad.
It's okay.
I'm so sorry.
♪ Never gonna give you up
never gonna let you down ♪
♪ Never gonna run around
and desert you ♪
♪ Never gonna make you cry... ♪
Even younger and prettier here.
- The third one, I thought you'd burst.
- You're mean!
That sweet little girl.
Sweet little girl? That's Magnus.
- What's wrong?
- I can't sleep.
- Oh, no.
- ...thought he was God's gift.
- Oh, my God. You're hot.
- Place didn't serve tourists.
- By the North Sea.
- Okay, I'll take you up. Come on.
I used to love that dress.
Oh, '80s fashion. My God!
And...
- Sleep tight. Good night.
- Until I'm asleep, could you stay here?
Scoot over.
So you're from the future, then?
And why are you here now?
I need to ask you for something.
What?
Don't do it.
Don't do what?
It's Ulrich's and Katharina's
anniversary.
Of course you didn't go.
I mean, you chose to stay home.
Something was different, though.
I should've known
something was wrong.
Jonas, I have no idea
what you're talking about.
Don't lie to me, okay?
I saw it. God damn it!
I know you're going to hang
yourself in your studio.
Have you written the letter yet?
What letter?
The letter you wrote to me.
Not to me, my younger self.
The one marked "Do not open
before 4 November 10:13 p.m."
Do not open before
4 November, 10:13 P.M.
Exactly to the minute
when you disappear.
I'm here so that you don't do it.
It's intertwined.
Like an endless loop.
But when you...
when you kill yourself...
that's where it begins.
Promise me you won't do it.
Papa, you have to promise that.
Please!
Promise!
You forgot this at the lake.
I put it on a string.
Thank you.
I thought about what you
said at the lake today.
About Grandma's and the Internet?
Well, I think you're right.
Okay.
The night that you disappeared...
you were here and then
you were just gone.
Did you return to the cave?
And was the passage still there?
I didn't find it.
Someone took me there.
Who?
You.
What do you mean?
- We were at the caves.
- What'll you give me for it?
An arse-kicking.
What's in here is worth 500.
But I'll let you have it for 200.
Your dad's loaded anyway.
Cut the bullshit! Yeah.
Now it's mine. Jackpot!
Then there was a strange sound.
What was that?
We were sure someone was there.
Someone over there?
Shit.
What's this?
Shit. What's going on?
What's wrong with the lights?
Come on, run!
Now!
Let's go!
We ran. Then I lost you.
I turned around and you were gone.
But suddenly, you were back again.
Quick.
Let's go.
You said there was
something out there, far off.
Something evil.
You said we had to go into the cave.
You took me all the way back to the door
and through the tunnel.
I was so scared.
But you held my hand.
And you said we had to
stay there all night.
But everything would be
all right in the morning.
And when I woke up you were gone.
All these years I've tried to understand
why you would do that.
But then, after a while,
it all started to fade away.
It became unreal, like a dream.
But that can't be right.
I never did that.
I saw myself today.
Mikkel.
It's coming back now, this jacket, you.
Like it's all fixed.
Maybe you're not here to stop me.
But rather to show me
what it is I have to do.
Maybe you only show me the letter
so I'm aware what's in it.
That I can go and you live on.
No, that's not it. That's not it!
Adam said I could
prevent it all from starting.
If you don't kill yourself
none of this will happen.
But if none of this happens,
you won't be born.
And maybe your role in all this
is much greater than you think.
And perhaps...
I'm just a tiny section of a huge
tumour that is much bigger
than any of us can imagine.
- Someone said that to me already.
- Who?
I did.
God doesn't err.
He has a plan.
For all of us.
I have waited for this moment
for a very long time.
Who are you?
Are you with Adam?
There are two sides out there.
He is the darkness.
I don't follow him, I follow the light.
He lied to you.
He led you back here
to ensure it all happens
exactly as it always has.
No, that's not right.
Adam wants this too!
No, he does not.
He doesn't want to fix things,
he wants to destroy them forever.
Your role in all this
is much greater than you think.
You alone can finally stop all this.
What are you saying?
You have to fight yourself.
Fight Adam.
But if I don't exist,
if I'm never born, then...
then how could Adam ever come?
I've seen the world without you.
Trust me...
it's not what you're expecting.
There are moments
when we must understand
that the decisions we make influence
more than just our own fates.
It's not just about you and Mikkel.
It's about everyone.
Your mother,
your friends,
Martha.
You alone can save them.
What are you saying?
We all have to make sacrifices.
Your father has to make sacrifices too.
It's okay.
This the apocalypse, then?
It's a bit disappointing.
I thought it would be louder than this.
Gaudier.
If the world ended tomorrow
and everything started over...
what would you wish for?
A world without Winden.
And you?
"Dear Jonas,
by the time you read this,
everything will have already
happened, irrevocably.
It can't be changed anymore.
I would have liked to
explain things to you sooner,
but I hope once you understand
how everything is connected,
you will understand my decision.
The truth is a strange thing.
You can try to suppress it,
but it will always find its way
to the surface.
We make a lie into our truth
in order to survive.
We try to forget,
until we can't anymore.
We don't even know half
the mysteries of this world.
We're wanderers in the darkness."
You could've told him.
Adam, you could've told him
what his function is in all this.
What journey you've
really sent him on.
It's not long before the last cycle.
Magnus, we all have to make sacrifices.