"From then on,
I knew that nothing changes.
That all things remain.
The spinning wheel turns,
round and round, in a circle.
One fate tied to the next.
A thread, red like blood,
that connects all our deeds."
That was your mother's favorite play.
She surely would have liked
to come with us tonight,
in the company
of such a distinguished young man.
FOR CHARLOTTE
Why do we die?
The dead are never truly dead.
Maybe they're not here, now.
But everything that once lived,
lives on forever.
In the eternity of time.
You there, what are you doing on the road?
I asked what you're doing!
Who is there?
Who are you?
He who has eyes to see
and ears to hear
may convince himself
that no mortal can keep a secret,
because if his lips are silent,
he chatters with his fingertips.
Betrayal oozes out of him at every pore.
I...
I... I don't understand.
Oh, but you do.
You're going into town
to draft a telegram.
Because you want
to tell the world about us.
Are you not?
You're one of them.
A traveler.
All those years
they said my father was insane.
But now they are here.
The travelers from the future.
The world must know
that they exist.
What we know...
is a drop.
What we don't know...
is an ocean.
ADAM AND EVA
The mistake in all of our thinking is...
that we each believe ourselves
to be an independent entity.
One self...
beside countless other selves.
While in reality, we're all just fractions
of an infinite whole.
What is this place?
A copy of my world?
Do you remember what you said to me?
Under the bridge.
The light.
The forest.
You.
Me.
A glitch in the matrix.
Why am I here?
You and I.
Adam and Eva.
That's what we are.
A glitch in the matrix.
You want to know why you're here?
To save them.
Your world.
And mine.
POLICE
Last night at around 10:00 p.m.,
Kilian Obendorf,
Bartosz Tiedemann, and Franziska Doppler,
along with Magnus and Martha Nielsen,
found an as-yet-unidentified boy's body
on the Doppler property,
by the forest road.
His clothes
and the Walkman are from the 1980s.
We also found...
an ID card on the body.
Wöller, can you continue?
Can I talk to you for a second?
You don't have to do this.
Wöller can do the briefings.
I can go to forensics.
Go home.
I've spent 33 years
looking for my brother.
Those are his belongings.
Those are Mads' belongings.
Someone...
kept them all.
And then put them on the boy
in the bunker.
Thirty-three years later.
You think it was the same killer?
That it's all connected?
Mads, Erik, the boy in the bunker?
Do you know why I joined the police?
When my brother disappeared...
they made pretty much every mistake
you could imagine.
The detective was a drunken moron.
And me?
I swore I'd do it all differently.
That I'd do everything right.
That was 33 years ago.
And what do I do?
My marriage is ruined.
And now I'm cheating on the woman
I cheated on my wife with.
I can't do this anymore.
TANNHAUS
MACHINERY FACTORY
Where were you?
What did she tell you?
We've been stuck here for weeks.
The fucking device is empty.
You have no idea
how any of this shit works.
All you did was lie.
You knew what would happen,
and you told us nothing!
Don't you realize she's just using you?
That isn't Martha.
She's dead.
No one returns from the dead.
Whoever she is...
she may be our only chance
to get out of here.
Why don't you tell us the truth?
Tell them
who really killed Martha.
Bartosz! Wait!
Tell them!
Tell them who Adam really is!
I told you all along!
Jonas is to blame for everything.
It's him.
He's Adam!
In all of that, didn't you ever wonder
why you can't let go of her?
You know you two are impossible.
Yet still...
you can't let her go.
An invisible bond
that binds you for eternity.
Adam tried to sever it.
But that's impossible.
You gave this to me.
You and I.
Black and white.
Light and shadow.
We are bound together for eternity
in this eternally repeating
déjà vu.
What is all this?
What do you want?
Why don't you just tell me
why I'm really here?
You've seen what you'll do.
What Adam will do.
If you want to save your Martha,
you have to choose the side of light.
And you have to make me what I am today.
I have to?
I don't want to have
to do anything anymore.
I'm sick to death
of always having to do things!
Then ask yourself
what you want.
Do you want her to live?
Your Martha?
Dad?
Can I come in?
Is Magnus here too?
I think he's still sleeping.
You have to tell me the truth.
What really happened in the bunker?
What did you see?
I did tell the truth.
We went in and the bunker was empty.
There was nobody there.
Then there was a light.
And then this...
this body fell down.
Had you taken anything?
What?
Did that Kilian kid give you anything?
Come on, what did you take?
What is this shit?
Are you playing the worried father now?
You usually don't give a shit about us!
It's just as we told you.
There was this noise...
It came from the caves
or the ground, or... I don't know.
We went into the bunker.
At first there was nothing there, then...
he was lying there.
Is that all?
Mom will be back any moment.
You'd better go.
But it was nice of you to drop by
to see how we're doing.
-Hannah.
-Hello.
Is Ulrich here?
I was trying to reach him all morning.
I thought he went home.
You look so different.
Did you get a haircut?
No.
It's nice to see you.
I'll just put this in his office.
Can we talk?
Get lost.
Last night...
in the forest...
Did you see anything else?
No.
Like what?
Do you sometimes feel
like you're losing your mind?
That nothing makes sense anymore?
Maybe...
Dad is right.
Maybe he was already lying there.
And we...
I know what I saw.
Where are you going?
Don't tell Mom.
I'll be back for dinner.
Everything repeats itself,
again and again.
For all eternity.
Because none of us is prepared to let go.
It took me a long time
to understand that.
That you can't let go of your past.
That you will always choose her,
always choose your Martha.
And just as you can't let go of your past,
I've spent my life clinging to mine.
You trusted Adam.
But where did that lead you?
You have to show her
how everything is connected.
You don't have much time left.
She has to see her future
in order to understand
what must be done.
She will follow you.
She is bound to your fate,
just as you are to hers.
You said I was in your world.
With you.
Why can't I remember it?
I don't know.
That letter...
I didn't write it.
You have to believe me.
Sic Mundus...
What is it?
Old Tannhaus' father...
tried to bring someone back from the dead.
His wife.
He was convinced
that the ability to time-travel
would be the world's salvation.
Every mistake could be prevented
before it even occurs.
But it doesn't bring salvation.
Only damnation.
They're all dead.
In my world.
I can't help hoping I can change that.
I know you think you can't trust me.
I want to prove to you that you can.
You traveled with that?
This is the last one I have.
It's the only way I can go back again.
You could have told him
which path you're sending him down.
How it will end.
He will never stop trying
to break this cycle.
He'll never understand
that we must preserve the knot.
That his Martha must die.
So all the others can live.
The beginning...
and the end.
WINDEN NUCLEAR POWER PLANT
VOLUME CONTROL SYSTEM
Ulrich, it's Charlotte. I...
I just wanted to know how you're doing.
Call me, okay?
Tick...
tock.
I'm here to see Kilian.
Kilian.
Hey.
It's okay.
What are you doing here?
You weren't at the dorm. I was worried.
They kicked me out.
Your father called.
He wanted to know
if I slipped you guys something.
-Did you?
-Fuck no! No, I didn't.
But sure, none of you
can get it out of your system.
I haven't lived here for two years,
but I'm still the trailer park trash
everyone points the finger at.
I knew it.
What did you know?
That you were only with me
to rile up your parents.
You don't give a crap about me or Erik.
You'd better go.
Okay.
About Regina...
I'm sorry.
It must be difficult for you.
How are you?
Bartosz?
We're managing.
I...
I'd like to propose a deal.
A deal?
I have something that belongs to you.
I'd like to return it.
Do you recognize it?
Don't worry.
The contents are in a safe place.
What do you want? Do you want money?
I don't want money.
I want you to destroy Charlotte.
I want her to lose everything.
Everything.
Charlotte!
What are you doing here?
Thanks.
You've helped me very much.
I tried to get a hold of you.
I went to the bunker.
Why aren't you home with Franziska?
I...
Last night, where was Helge?
You said you ate dinner with him.
Where was he afterwards?
What is this?
In 1987, when you came to Winden,
did your father still live in the cabin?
-I don't understand.
-Did he or didn't he?
No. After the accident
he moved into the nursing home.
-And the summer before, in '86?
-I think so. Why do you want to know?
Did he use the bunker for anything?
Charlotte, what do you want from me?
This is Helge's.
I found it in the bunker.
That... That can't be.
He was with us all night.
Doppler here.
He did what?
Where?
Yes.
Yes, I'll be right there.
Helge.
He's at the police station.
He made a confession.
POLICE
Dad, why are you saying this?
It makes no sense at all.
He didn't leave the house.
I was with him all evening.
Elisabeth was there, too.
I killed the boy.
-Dad, cut it out!
-His things...
The Walkman. The clothes.
Those are Mads Nielsen's things,
the boy who disappeared in 1986.
Do you remember that?
I killed him.
Who? Mads?
Where did you get his stuff?
What did you do to Mads?
What did you do to him?
You're alive.
-What?
-It was you.
What was me?
It was him.
What? Get off me!
-What are you saying?
-It was him!
FEDERAL REPUBLIC OF GERMANY
What is this?
Are you following me?
Why won't you tell me
how we know each other?
Actually, we've always known each other.
When Magnus knocked your tooth out
in kindergarten...
I was there.
When Mikkel put spiders in your shoes
while camping in the yard...
On the third grade class trip...
when you were so homesick
that Katharina had to come get you.
Where I come from,
you and I have the same past.
You're nuts.
I know that you saw yourself.
Last night in the forest.
You told me about it.
Your future self did.
What?
I know how completely insane
this all sounds.
For the longest time
I too thought it was all totally crazy.
That I was crazy.
Who are you really?
I can show you.
How it's all connected.
Where's Martha?
LET THERE BE LIGHT
SEPTEMBER 23, 2053
So you gave it to him?
I always was too gullible.
You did the right thing.
What is this place?
Where are we?
How did you do that?
She told me to bring you here.
That she'd explain it to you.
Who?
Who is that?
Welcome to the future.
Subtitle translation by Nathan Fritz