Get changed.
Martha?
This can't be.
You...
You're alive.
That isn't Martha.
What's going on?
He's right.
I'm not Martha.
Not your Martha.
I promised to make
everything right again,
so none of it happens.
So you don't die in my world,
and I don't die in yours.
So that Ulrich... Dad...
Mikkel...
so they all come back.
So everything finally comes to an end.
THE SURVIVORS
22 SEPTEMBER 1987
- This is Ines...
- And Michael Kahnwald.
We're not at home right now.
Leave a message after the beep.
Mrs. Kahnwald, this is Mr. Dietmann
from the Federal Postal Service.
I've been trying to reach
you for three months.
We'll disconnect the line next month
if you don't pay the outstanding bills.
Please call me back as soon as you can.
MISSING FOR 3 MONTHS
I think you did the right thing.
Even if the coffin is empty.
To... to get closure.
At least you've got each other.
For support.
At least we've got each other.
Now we can stand hand in
hand by an empty coffin
and finally get closure.
Tell them where you were
when Mads disappeared.
He was fucking her!
When my son disappeared, he
was screwing Claudia Tiedemann.
If only you'd put as much
energy into finding your own son
as you're wasting on
finding your mistress...
Then maybe Mads would be back by now.
I have no idea what
you're talking about.
WHERE IS CLAUDIA TIEDEMANN?
"I have no idea what
you're talking about".
NUCLEAR POWER PLANT HEAD
MISSING SINCE 26 JUNE,
THE DAY HER FATHER
WAS FOUND DEAD AT HOME.
22 SEPTEMBER 2020
The world's scientists are
still seeking an explanation
for the events of 27 June 2020.
The epicentre of the global catastrophe
is still thought to be
the small town of Winden.
A French research team
believes it is possible
that our world stood still for a
fraction of a nanosecond on 27 June.
Tidal forces may have
diverged as a result.
This would explain the
global spring tides,
weather phenomena, and
disturbances of electrical systems,
which in turn could explain the
great number of aeroplane crashes
and the simultaneous
loss of power supply
to nuclear power plants worldwide.
There is no sign of the
situation stabilising...
How are you?
Mum...
You're leaving again already?
I'll be back before the sun sets.
In 5 days all this will be closed off.
We're evacuating the entire area.
We have orders to seal
off the restricted area.
Seal off?
Walled in.
Why are you doing this to her?
- You're from a parallel world?
- Where Mikkel doesn't disappear?
I'm mute?
And Jonas doesn't exist?
Where we're all already dead because
your world ends just as ours does?
That's bullshit.
I'm not dead.
I'm here.
How did you find us?
How did you know where we were?
Jonas told me.
I thought Jonas didn't
exist in your world.
He travelled there.
From your world to mine.
You're lying.
I was never in your world.
Did you write the letter?
What do you really want?
Did Adam send you?
What did you use to travel? I want
to know what you used to travel!
You're running late today.
The machines aren't running yet.
You have a visitor.
So you're the reason
for his mood being even
worse today than usual.
Don't let me scare you.
People may say
I'm not quite right in the head,
but I assure you...
that I see more
than those among us who can see.
- Do you know this boy?
- Nope.
- No. Sorry.
- Do you know this boy?
- No. I'm sorry.
- Nope.
Ulrich?
Do I know you?
Do you maybe know where this boy is?
WHO HAS SEEN MICHAEL
KAHNWALD? 12 YEARS OLD
Maybe the madman got him after all.
What madman?
Don't touch me, Typhoid Mary!
Hey, Ulrich.
Ulrich?
I thought you weren't coming today.
Katharina.
We'll be late for history class.
Katharina Albers?
Hello?
I remember.
What's with her?
The old bat's not all there.
Come on.
Hey!
What madman?
A guy escaped from the
nuthouse this summer.
He tried to drag Michael into the cave.
It was in the paper.
You keep your mitts off Mikkel!
And Ulrich!
VISITOR'S PASS
NIELSEN, TRONTE
I've already told all
this to the police.
It won't take long.
I promise.
And this is supposed
to be for the newspaper?
The week before Claudia disappeared...
did you notice anything?
Her appearance was always
very important to her.
So neat.
But that week...
she wore outfits twice.
She forgot appointments. Her hair...
I think...
it all had to do with
the old woman and the dog.
She showed up a few days before
Mrs. Tiedemann disappeared.
She said the dog belonged to her,
but didn't take it with her.
After that, Mrs. Tiedemann
was somehow...
different.
Excuse me.
We're looking for...
a woman, late 40s.
Blonde hair.
And a girl. 17 years old.
Red hair.
If they're not on the wall, then...
they're not here.
This is good.
If they're not here, then...
Maybe they travelled.
CALL FOR WITNESSES
WE ASK FOR YOUR ASSISTANCE
MISSING
TIEDEMANN, CLAUDIA
Hey!
The man from the asylum.
Why didn't you tell me?
I thought I'd already made that clear.
You can barge in here
as often as you want
demanding information on the
whereabouts of Michael Kahnwald.
You won't get any.
Someone tried to kidnap
my son this summer.
Your son?
You can neither identify yourself
nor do you have any proof
you're actually the boy's mother.
You're not registered anywhere.
You don't have a birth certificate.
And, astonishingly, you don't
even want to reveal your name.
No one has seen him for 3 months.
He doesn't go to school.
He's not at home.
The man from the psychiatric ward...
I remember that.
My mother told me about it.
Maybe...
maybe he tried to do it again.
Now listen very carefully.
The boy hasn't disappeared.
Child Protective Services know where
Ines and Michael Kahnwald are.
After this summer's
events it was decided
it was best to give
the boy some time out.
And the madman is back
in the closed ward,
as he has been for the past 34 years.
What did you just say?
Just to make it absolutely clear,
if I see you here again, I'm
putting you in protective custody.
- What's his name?
- Goodbye.
What's the man's name?
Hello, Regina.
Is that your dog?
It was my mother's.
Could I give you a ride?
Strange.
Looks like Gretchen.
I think that's why she kept her.
Do you think...
the disappearance of
Mads and my mother...
that they're connected?
I don't know.
The week before she
disappeared, did she...
say anything to you about an old woman?
And...
did she say anything to you about me?
I...
just thought maybe she'd said something.
I'll...
get out just up ahead...
and walk the rest of the way.
Well...
if you need anything...
My name is Claudia Tiedemann.
I am one of the few survivors of
the apocalypse of 27 June 2020.
Almost 3 months have
passed since the catastrophe.
It's still unclear what exactly
led to the events in Winden.
But the God Particle...
if we can stabilise it,
maybe it is a way back.
Back to the past.
Maybe we can save them.
All of them.
I'll take a look around upstairs.
I'm looking for food.
And you?
MUM AND SISTER
Where do you sleep?
CAVE
What's going on?
Why are you here?
Are you following us?
I told you, we want
nothing to do with you.
You want to protect her, I know.
So do I.
And I will.
After you were killed.
TANNHAUS MACHINERY FACTORY
I'm sorry.
About Jonas.
Since we've been here...
he's...
he's been different.
How did you get here?
We travelled.
Exactly at the moment
everything blew up.
He didn't want to come here.
It just happened.
The device is empty.
It's not that easy to get nuclear
fuel from the future in 1888.
And this?
What is this?
The workshop?
The blind man?
Does he know who you are?
Where you come from?
Come along.
I need to show you something.
The young woman.
Is she one of you?
A traveller?
When I found you, it was a sign.
A godsend.
Whatever that woman means to you,
don't forget what we
are going to create.
Paradise.
Every calamity can be reversed.
Every pain, destroyed
before it even comes to be.
A perfect world.
Sic mundus...
creatus est.
Excuse me.
Can I help you?
I...
I'd like to visit someone.
He's been here for 34 years.
The inspector?
Do I know you from somewhere?
Somehow you look familiar to me.
Are you related to him?
He's my husband.
I see.
You're one of them.
One of those women who
go for madmen or prisoners
because they can't find anyone else.
I'm off duty. Come back tomorrow.
That's St. Christopher.
The patron saint of travellers.
He renounced the devil and
carried the creator into the world.
My mum had one just like that.
I've travelled a very long way.
Let me see him.
Please.
He was just released from solitary.
My colleague will let you out.
Ulrich.
Katharina.
I'll get you out of here.
I promise.
Excuse me?
Excuse me,
what are you doing here?
What do you want?
I...
I'll call security.
No.
You won't do that.
Jasmin.
Right?
Hell is empty.
And all devils are here.
At some point you have to decide.
For us.
Or against us.
I...
saw Regina.
She's all grown up.
I've wondered all these years...
if she...
Claudia never said who the father was.
You're right.
I have to decide.
Mum?
Tronte.
Regina.
What are you doing here?
I'm so sorry.
But it has to happen.
I don't understand.
She said...
it's the only way to save you.
MUM AND SISTER
CAVE
What did he say to you?
What do you mean?
The boy.
Forget him.
I'm not a little kid anymore.
Why do you carry that
around everywhere you go?
What's in there?
Where are Mum and Franziska?
We'll find them.
22 SEPTEMBER 2053
Everything will be okay.
Clear the table.
I said, clear the table.
Must I always repeat myself?
What is this?
This is a kind of secret lodge.
Old Tannhaus is the only member left.
His father was convinced he could
override the rules of space and time.
He dedicated his entire life to this.
And so did his son.
They tried to build a time machine?
Jonas is trying to rebuild
things the way he saw them.
He's been here before.
Not now.
In the future.
He asked you something earlier.
Whether Adam had sent you.
He said...
that Adam killed Martha.
Who is this Adam?
He didn't tell you guys?
He is Adam.
Jonas.
We don't know our end.
But our end...
knows us.
Salvation...
or damnation.
We can indulge in the
illusion of free will,
but we cannot escape
our ultimate destiny.
The choices we make in this
world may be different...
but nevertheless,
they converge on the same moment.
Things may not happen in the same way,
or at the same time.
But they happen.
You believed a world without
you would be a better one.
But they will all die.
Mikkel.
Mikkel will die.
Everyone will die.
The apocalypse takes place in my world
just as it does in yours.
But in mine, that's in just 3 days.