THE ORIGIN
We're attracted to the
dark like moths to light.
We are born out of the darkness
and we return to it.
You've grown, Tronte.
Do we know each other?
I knew your mother.
But that was a long time ago.
You take after her.
Your eyes.
Who are you?
I don't have a name.
I was never given one.
But I chose your name back then.
It belonged to your mother.
I think it should belong to you now.
I have to go now.
I love you.
I don't know if you'll like it, but...
may I put it on you?
You don't like it?
No, I...
I do, it's very beautiful.
I don't know.
I haven't felt quite right all week.
You look pale.
Maybe you should see a doctor.
Will I see you later?
I... I don't know. It's...
I think it's best if
I stay home tonight.
Katharina...
I'm glad you decided to stay here.
In Winden.
You're beautiful.
24 SEPTEMBER 1954
SENSATIONAL NUDE PHOTOS
Her facial expression...
KESS
THE EXHILARATING MAGAZINE
Where did you get it?
I found it in my dad's stuff.
Ines, Claudia. We're already late.
My dad says you don't
learn anything in school.
You only learn from life.
Why don't they have these with men?
- I don't think it's fair at all.
- You're crazy.
Have you ever seen one?
- I mean, that's not your dad's?
- Ines!
Jana, don't be like that.
And what did it look like?
Peculiar.
As if it didn't belong
to the rest of him.
Tronte?
I think he's a strange boy.
Is his mother back?
It's odd. Don't you think?
To just disappear like that?
POLICE
Doris.
What are you doing here?
I want to talk to you.
Mr. Kahnwald let me in.
Where have you been? I thought
you left early to write reports.
It...
I...
Something came up.
This morning...
I did the laundry
and I found something.
Here.
It was between one of her blouses.
I thought it might help.
She said her husband
was a man of God.
And maybe it's just
a coincidence, but...
the minister who disappeared
at the same time...
His name is Hanno Tauber.
H.T.
WINDEN WELCOMES ITS NEW MINISTER
HANNO TAUBER (42) FROM VECHTA
I...
I thought her husband was dead.
It's been 3 months.
You don't just leave your
child behind without a word.
You should go home.
We're taking care of it.
Egon! I know something happened.
Why would she leave all this behind?
Who knows what goes on
inside the heads of you women?
Doris!
MISSING SINCE 26 JUNE 1954
MRS. AGNES NIELSEN
HAS ANYONE SEEN THIS WOMAN?
You chose the right side.
Don't forget that.
UNIDENTIFIED WOMAN'S BODY
FOUND IN WOODS
You have to give this to Claudia.
When it's time.
Life is a gift...
for those who know how to use it.
Are you going to tell Martha?
What the origin really is?
All of these years, I've wondered...
why you ditched us in 1888.
Why you helped us create the matter...
and then simply disappeared.
Who would've thought
that 33 years later
it would be us who gave you the order.
Magnus...
I'm sorry.
It doesn't matter anymore.
Adam is waiting for us.
6 NOVEMBER 2052
This is your future.
33 years away from your yesterday.
The door in the cave...
What is that?
It's a path that connects
past and future.
Why are these names crossed out?
It means they die.
All of them.
- What do you mean, they all die?
- In 2 days.
The apocalypse in his world
also happens in ours.
This isn't real.
You're not real.
This is your future.
If you...
if both of you fail
to stop the apocalypse.
So you haven't been in Winden long?
3 months.
I like it here.
It's much less complicated
than where I'm from.
Well, maybe that's about to change.
You're pregnant.
At your age, a pregnancy
is not without risks.
You should take care of yourself.
No hard work.
That's impossible.
Listen.
Some gifts come into
our lives unexpectedly.
Yet they're still gifts.
Mrs. Doppler.
How can I help you?
I'd like to know if there is any news.
I'm afraid...
I'm afraid not.
Unless Helge decides to
tell us where he was...
That is...
whom he was with...
I'm afraid we're stuck.
This isn't about Helge.
This is about the missing minister.
The congregation has been
without support for weeks.
It leaves the door open for the devil.
You knew the man?
The minister?
Did he...
did you ever see him in
the company of a woman?
What are you thinking?
I want you to find the man.
Hanno Tauber.
Sorry to disturb you.
Are you the new minister?
I once was.
But it's been a long time.
The thing is,
I'm looking for someone.
My husband and I,
our daughter is very talented,
and last winter we sublet
the guest room
so we could save up money for Claudia,
for when she goes to college.
The woman who moved in with us,
she disappeared, 3 months ago.
Her husband was a man of God.
She said he died.
I don't know why, but I got
the impression that wasn't true.
And the man who was the minister here
disappeared at the same time, so...
What if he was her husband?
And she went back to him?
I don't think she liked him very much.
Not all human connections
are formed out of fondness.
Well, it's about the boy.
He's still with us, and...
a boy needs his mother.
With every lie
the human soul dies just a little bit.
I don't understand.
You're not interested in the boy.
You're interested in the woman.
I think you've
misunderstood me.
The ways of the heart
cannot be explained.
It does what it wants.
Just ask your husband.
He'll tell you the same thing.
My husband?
Haven't you wondered why he's been
leaving the house so early lately?
Why he's been working so late?
Couldn't the reason be another woman?
It's difficult for us to let go...
of what we desire deep within ourselves.
Hello, Tronte.
Hello.
What's that?
It's so beautiful.
Why weren't you at school today?
What are you doing here?
I like it here.
It's so...
desolate.
I like to write, you know.
Stories.
You have a nice smile.
POLICE
What are you doing here?
You can't just show up here.
What if someone sees you?
Is everything okay?
I'm pregnant.
I thought you were being careful.
Is it mine?
Is it yours?
What do you think I do
all day long? Fuck around?
Do you think I chose this?
Living in this shithole?
I thought you were harmless,
but you're all the same.
You all think you own the world.
That you can take what you want.
You eat and fuck and think you're God.
Everywhere you go, always the
same fucking smug arseholes.
Katharina, you don't
know what you're saying.
It's best if I drive you home now.
The coal industry has him
wrapped around its little finger.
I don't care how long it takes!
We'll submit another
building permit request.
Nuclear power is the future.
And the future cannot be stopped.
I don't care what the mayor says!
Oh, Claudia.
Look at you.
You're all grown up.
A real lady.
Pretty and smart as a whip.
Helge will be pleased to see you.
And, of course, you'll be
rewarded for your services.
But that's far too much.
Let me give you some
advice. A life lesson.
If you really want something,
then take it.
Things don't just happen by themselves.
Thank you.
NUCLEAR POWER AND PEACE
TOWN HALL
Is Heinz sick, or...
What do you want?
How much money did the
coal industry pay you
to block the plans for
the nuclear power plant?
I have no idea what
you're talking about.
So Doppler sent you, right?
Do you know what money can't buy?
The future.
More precisely, your future.
We think we're immortal,
but, in truth, often only one breath...
separates the now from the hereafter.
What do you want from me?
WINDEN BUILDING AUTHORITY
BUILDING PERMIT
The building permit for the
nuclear power plant, it's...
To the future.
You can change it.
Both of you can change it.
The barrels at the nuclear plant,
they trigger the apocalypse.
You have to stop them
from being opened.
What do we do then?
Eva said there's a
way to undo this knot.
That there's a way Martha
can live. My Martha!
She lied to you.
There is no way to save both worlds.
You have to choose one of them.
The apocalypse, in 2 days...
it can be stopped.
You two can stop it.
They can live. All of them.
Mikkel...
can live.
Isn't that what you wanted?
But, in return,
you have to let her go.
Your Martha.
Your world.
You've seen what becomes of you there.
What you'll do.
What Adam will do.
You're both out of your minds.
I'm going home now, and
I'll wake up in my bed
and all this will have been
just a crappy dream.
Jonas, this is exactly what you wanted.
You and Martha.
In this world, the two
of you are not impossible.
Martha!
Wait!
Hey.
You believe all this?
That they're all going to die?
That's crazy.
I'm crazy. This is...
Believe me, I know exactly how it feels.
It's all true?
Everything she said is true?
But I know there's a way.
A way to straighten all this out again.
And I'm not going to
stop looking for that way.
I think that's what she's doing too.
The Martha who brought me here.
It's time.
So you have no idea where your mum is?
And the man this morning...
You think that may have been your dad?
My mother didn't talk about him much.
She said...
he's a bad person.
I was in a home for a long time.
What's it like in a home?
Can you keep a secret?
That man this morning...
I don't even want to
know if he's my dad.
And I'm glad that my mother's gone.
You can have it if you want.
Jana?
What are you doing here?
Didn't you go home hours ago?
We're already late. I'm sure
Mum is waiting with dinner.
See you around.
Maybe see you tomorrow.
What do we do now?
Don't worry. I don't want to keep it.
Why do some people have everything?
And others nothing?
Hm?
Why does destiny preordain all that's
good for some and not for others?
All my life I've been trying to
hold onto things you can't hold onto.
But now I finally understand.
I don't need anyone.
None of you.
It's best you go now.
Last year...
Daniel told me about it.
She does it properly.
MRS. OBENDORF
I'm sorry.
You sent them off?
The beginning is the end.
And the end is the beginning.
We are all born of him.
You gave him life.
And he will give us ours.
Him.
Agnes.
Tronte.
Jana.
Ulrich.
Katharina.
You.
A line without a beginning or an end.
An infinite circle.
Doris?
Is everything okay?
I...
I wanted to apologise.
For this morning.
I know you just wanted to help.
Lately, I...
I haven't really been myself.
Work and...
I'm sorry.
I know what you've been up to.
With that woman.
What do you mean?
I want a divorce.
What are you talking about?
We should have done it sooner,
but I... I thought...
I don't know what I thought.
All these secrets.
I don't want to live like this.
I...
I can explain it to you.
The ways of the heart
cannot be explained.
It does what it wants.
Hello.
I... I'm here to see Mrs. Obendorf.
You have to wait.
My mother says...
they go to hell.
The...
the ones that are gotten rid of.
I don't believe in hell.
Hell is what we make
for ourselves on Earth.
I'm Helene.
Helene Albers.
Katharina.
That's a very beautiful name.
St. Christopher!
A nice thought.
Someone carrying us on our journey.
Someone watching over us.
Come on now.
Hello, Dad.
Where's Mum?
The ways of the heart
cannot be explained.
It does what it wants.
Come on.
Leave him.
WINDEN BUILDING AUTHORITY
BUILDING PERMIT
You promised me something.
I kept my end of the agreement.
Now you have to keep yours.
You want to know where the origin is.
And how to destroy it.
You will.
It took me over 66 years
to finally understand how
everything is connected.
You're right.
It's time you understood, too.
At school...
when you came through the door, I...
I had this feeling.
As if we knew each other.
From a dream.
Or...
I'm sorry.
About it all.
Where you're from...
what was I like there?
Was I different?
I AM LEFT TO DIE ALONE,
AND I AM MY SOLE JUDGE. ME.
THE BEGINNING IS THE END.
AND THE END IS THE BEGINNING.
Why are we here?
Because this...
is where everything began.
In your world.
What does that mean?
Your older self.
She sent you and Jonas back
for a single purpose.
You were never meant
to stop the apocalypse.
You were to create the origin.
This is the origin.
What's growing inside you
is the bridge between both worlds.
It can't be.
It is the beginning of the knot
and it will be its end.
Your son.
He is the origin.