WWW.MY-SUBS.COM
Man is a strange creature.
All his actions are motivated by desire,
his character forged by pain.
As much as he may try
to suppress that pain,
to repress the desire,
he cannot free himself from the
eternal servitude to his feelings.
For as long as the
storm rages within him,
he cannot find peace.
Not in life,
not in death.
And so he will do what
he must, day in, day out.
The pain is his vessel,
desire his compass.
It is all that man is capable of.
June 26, 1954
One day until the Apocalypse
The deceased is female,
5' 7", Caucasian.
Around 75 to 80 years old.
Cause of death: gunshot wound.
The eyes are noteworthy.
One is blue, one is brown.
Known as heterochromia.
This woman, she...
She was at the police station.
The same day that
little Helge reappeared.
And?
She wasn't...
in her right mind.
She kept apologizing for...
something I didn't understand.
You mean on the same
day Helge came back?
Maybe she's the madman's accomplice.
She could even be his mother.
Had Helge with her this whole time.
There's something else.
It was only by chance that I noticed it.
The corpse
is heavily contaminated by radiation.
Here.
Everywhere.
She must have been exposed
to heavy radiation over
a long time period.
That's strange.
It's possible that
she was a radiographer.
Radiographer?
Go back to the Doppler kid
and show him a picture of her.
He might recognize her.
The data suggests
that this particle breaks down
into two protons regularly.
Mass: 125 gigaelectronvolts.
However, in one case
it decayed into four muons.
Oh, you're already here?
I must've lost track of time.
What day is this?
Um...
It's...
the 26th of June.
We're you here all night?
Ex-Winden Chief Inspector,
found dead, June 26, 1987
June 26th.
What is it?
You have the meeting with the French
this morning that I rescheduled.
Mrs. Tiedemann?
Mom?
Nuclear Power Plant
What's behind the door?
It's all related to me.
He said the world was
going to end tomorrow.
And only those in the bunker make it.
And he said that she's alive.
My mother.
The documents from the Marburg
passport authorities have arrived.
It's just as you expected, there
was only one Aleksander Köhler
during that period in
the entire registration.
And so the eyes saw and the ears heard
and nothing remained hidden.
Freud.
Let Mr. Wöller know.
We have to tell someone.
Who? And what do we say, exactly?
Don't you want to say something?
- I bet he's here..
- Who?
Jonas.
I think Bartosz is right. He's back.
We traveled through time and
that's all you're interested in?
You're the one who said
he's involved in this.
Maybe, unlike you, he
knows what this is about.
He might know where Dad is,
or Mikkel, or anything, man!
Magnus is right. We
have to tell someone.
Everyone's been trying to
figure this out for months.
No one's talking.
And what's the point? Nothing.
Okay.
We should do it.
We?
There is no "we".
- There never was.
- So what are you saying?
You knew for months what was going on
and you didn't tell me or anyone else!
Do whatever you want.
I hope it won't take too long.
Helge is still not doing well.
Do you know this woman?
Answer the police inspector.
Were you at her place?
Did she lock you in?
He told me about her.
The White Devil.
Who?
Who told you about her?
The man... The man who did this to you?
The White Devil.
So tell me about this...
White Devil.
She wants to kill us.
All of us.
She's dead. She can't
hurt anyone anymore.
But she hasn't even begun yet.
- Claudia.
- Hello, Dad.
Don't you have to be at work?
Um... I took the day off.
Is everything all right?
I thought you were moving in with us.
I...
Did you forget?
You said I should give it some thought.
I just figured...
why waste any time?
And you'd get out of here for once.
I prefer it here.
I have to go.
To the hospital.
Starting chemo.
Can I...
Can I come along?
Only... if you want me to.
I'd like that.
What do you want?
I've already told you everything.
I would like you to take a look at this.
Mr. Wöller.
What is it?
It's a copy of the documents
from the registration at Marburg.
The data from your last personal
ID before you moved out here.
I don't see how this is relevant at all.
Nothing catches your eye?
No. Should there be something?
You're 5' 6", I bet. Maximum.
But the document says 5' 8".
So... I'm wondering where it is.
Where is what?
The two inches missing.
This is ridiculous.
You're under arrest.
I'm charging you with
identity theft and obstruction.
You can't do that.
Hannah?
Hannah!
Anyone home?
Hello!
Hannah, if you're at home,
please open the door.
I'm sorry, I...
Who are you?
Come in.
I, um...
I... I wanted Hannah's opinion.
She isn't here.
You want a drink?
Are you scared of me?
I didn't want to scare you.
I think I'm having déjà vu or something.
- I should go.
- A glitch in the matrix.
What?
Or a message from the beyond.
You read this all somewhere.
How do you know that?
Did you find the pendant?
Jonas?
Do you think I was
a good police officer?
Oh, Dad. How would I know?
I'm sure you were good at
whatever you were doing.
I don't think so myself.
You... were always different.
You saw the world differently
right from the start.
Sometimes I think...
that's what my problem is.
I can't see the world
for what it actually is.
I think I did something
very, very stupid.
What do you mean?
You know that film,
where the kid and the old man
traveled back in time with his car?
I know it sounds crazy,
but...
the stuff in the film,
it really exists.
Time travel.
And somehow...
It has to do with
Mads and Helge, too.
Everything.
All the things that
happened so many years ago.
Mr. Tiedemann.
There's a woman waiting in your office.
- Did she say why she's here?
- It's about the man in the asylum.
The lunatic who murdered those
kids. She says she knows him.
Thank you.
Good day.
What can I do for you?
I'm...
looking for my husband.
It was in the papers.
The dead children.
There was a photo.
I think that's my husband.
Is this him?
It looks like him.
We searched for relatives.
No one came forward.
He was arrested last winter in
connection with multiple murders.
Can I see him?
It's not that straightforward.
Right at this moment he's
in a psychiatric institution.
He won't talk.
I understand.
But he could talk to me.
Could I ask what your name is?
Nielsen.
Katharina Nielsen.
Where were you all this time?
I promised I would try
to make it all right.
I am so sorry.
It makes sense all of a sudden.
It's obvious now that I understand.
Hannah!
Hannah, are you here?
Hannah?
Hannah!
Wait, don't. Please.
Martha?
Do you know who that is? Huh?
Did he tell you where your brother is?
Who your brother is?
This guy
is the son of your brother.
My grandson, your nephew!
Mikkel is Michael Kahnwald,
do you understand?
And you are his aunt!
Martha...
I am so sorry.
I'm sorry.
I...
Believe me, I wanted...
Where's your machine?
The machine that makes
it possible to go there.
Hannah has it.
She disappeared.
Hannah?
Tell me now how I can get Mikkel back!
Mom.
Magnus has a time machine.
What?
We used it. It works.
You were there?
Did you see him?
Mikkel?
Keep your dirty hands off her.
Do you hear me?
Come on.
What is this?
My brother.
He also disappeared.
In '86.
Quite similar to the
case with Mads Nielsen.
No trace.
Nothing.
His name was also Aleksander.
Aleksander Köhler.
Just like you.
Mm...
A regular name.
To be precise, there are over 700
Aleksander Köhlers in Germany.
So it wasn't easy to track down
each and every Aleksander Köhler.
Especially...
someone who chose to take
the last name of their wife.
Believe me, I'm speaking
from experience.
After my parents separated,
I took my mother's last name.
From Köhler
to Clausen.
For some people I'm still
untraceable to this very day.
But...
a couple of months ago...
this happened.
Read it.
Out loud.
"He that has eyes to see
and ears to hear
may convince himself that
no mortal can keep a secret.
If his lips are silent...
- ... he chatters...
- ... he chatters with his fingertips.
- Betrayal oozes out of him...
- ... oozes...
- ... out of him at every pore.
- ... at every pore.
Answers about your brother
can be found in Winden."
"A friend"
I have no idea
what's going on in this town.
But I know one thing for sure.
You...
... are definitely not my brother.
Your husband never confessed.
He kept insisting that he
wanted to save the children.
You and your husband...
You have children, yes?
No.
That's strange.
He kept saying he was
looking for his son.
This may sound a bit odd, but...
have you ever heard
mention of a "White Devil"?
No.
What is that?
When he talks to you...
I mean, if he talks to you,
get him to talk to the police.
See if you can convince
him to make a confession.
And that man came from the future?
To 1953?
That's when you arrested him.
And yesterday that man tried to
run away with that little child?
No.
Not that man.
Not quite.
The same man, but...
much older.
And you say the boy is his son?
I know.
It all sounds ridiculous.
The man, the old one...
where is he now?
They sent him back.
That does it. You're living with us.
We're getting your things.
So you believe me.
You traveled... with this?
To what year?
What year?
That's what's going on.
You knew about this time travel shit.
Why didn't you say anything?
Martha.
Hey.
At Franziska's.
Yes, I'll be home right away.
You what?
Who?
Jonas is back.
Just like Bartosz predicted.
But he's older.
It's better if you stay out of this.
This is ridiculous.
You both knew that too?
This is what ruins everything!
All of your secret fucking bullshit!
You didn't even try to talk to us
when Papa and Benni slept together!
You incompetent asshole!
Franziska...
Open K-53!
I'd like a moment
with him alone, please.
Uh... I'm not sure if
that's such a good idea.
Please. For just five minutes.
As you wish.
Come.
Ulrich?
Ulrich.
Ulrich, it's me.
Hannah.
Hannah?
Ulrich, it's me.
Is it really you?
Yes.
Or are you an angel?
Are you an angel?
- Is it you?
- Yes.
It is you.
Do you know where Mikkel is?
Katharina. How is Katharina?
Martha, Magnus?
It feels so different
now, seeing you again.
What?
If you could choose today
between Katharina and me...
What are you...
What are you asking?
In all the time you and
I were together, you...
I...
I can't really remember if you
ever once said to me, "I love you."
I loved you.
I still do, love you.
Get me out of here and
I'll leave Katharina.
I love you.
Okay?
He said I wouldn't need anyone.
But the truth is...
you don't need me now.
I do. I need you, Hannah.
I love you.
Get me out of here.
I'll do anything you want.
Get me out of here, please!
Hannah, I love you.
You hear me?
I love you.
Hannah. Please!
I love you!
You lying fucker!
Please! Stay with me!
Stay with me!
I love you!
She's a liar!
She's a liar. Liar!
There is a resemblance, but...
Hannah! I love you!
That's not my husband.
Hannah!
I love you!
Get me out of here!
Mom.
It'll work out.
Okay?
You've got the machine?
Do you know how to use it?
I...
I don't know.
Bartosz used it.
It's them.
Mikkel...
Dad, they're alive.
What?
They're just not here.
They're in another time.
Just grab your pills.
We'll get everything else later.
I'll be needing a minute.
Come on, let's go.
I've been...
wondering why he returned to the cave.
- Maybe there's something in the caves.
- Papa, give it a rest.
He tried it in '53 as well.
And now again.
- Maybe there is something...
- That isn't true.
But don't you think
there has to be a reason that
he wanted to go in there?
Can we leave?
Why are you really here?
What are you saying?
You knew this!
I knew what?
You know about time travel!
The nuclear plant is connected to it.
How about we go now?
I know you're a part of this.
Don't be ridiculous.
We must have the caves searched, then.
There's nothing in the caves!
There is no time travel!
- What are you doing?
- Calling the station.
We have to go search the caves.
You have no idea.
The thing inside the caves is beyond
any other scientific discovery.
It turns everything we know
about the universe upside down.
And you're willing to
jeopardize that? For nothing?
You know, you haven't changed at all.
You are all you've ever cared about.
You have no heart!
Let go.
Let go!
Oh, God. Dad.
Stay right there.
Don't move.
I...
I'll call an ambulance.
Come on!
Winden Emergency
Services, how can I help you?
Hello?
Hello...
"There will be sacrifices.
Everything will happen as it always has.
But if everything goes
right, she will live."
Regina.
I'm so sorry.
You are the White Devil.
You're sure that's not your husband?
I, um...
should've reacted sooner.
- I'm sorry.
- That's all right. Really.
Nielsen...
That is an...
unusual name.
Do you know an Agnes Nielsen?
No.
Are you traveling back today?
I lost everything I had at home.
I'm just looking for a fresh start.
Sleeping over at a friend's, R.
Who are you?
Why do you have a key to my house?
You made me take it before you left me.
No, I didn't.
I've never seen you before.
I know who you got it from.
My older self.
We need to go. We don't have much time.
I don't understand.
I know what you've done.
She told me.
But she also said it
didn't have to happen again.
Next time.
Where are we going?
To the future.