Why do we die?
What is death?
TIEDEMANN, REGINA
1.8.1971 - 2.9.2019
MUM AND SISTER CAVE
Could we escape it if we
knew when to expect it?
Is the time of our
departure predetermined?
Our dying, part of
an endless clockwork?
We all have one truth in common.
We are born.
And we die.
No matter what path we take in between.
LIFE AND DEATH
Your path will always lead you here.
To Elisabeth.
To me.
Time plays a cruel game.
Have you made your decision?
Just one more day
and we can untie this
knot once and for all.
But you must,
as all of us,
do your part.
Will you see it through?
Eva will never achieve her goal.
Her world doesn't deserve to be saved
any more than ours does.
ONE DAY UNTIL THE APOCALYPSE
We have to go.
To the nuclear power plant.
We don't have much time.
Jonas?
Never mind.
My God, where were you?
We were looking for
you all day yesterday.
Kilian said you were with him
and then you just
vanished into thin air.
And who are you?
Everything will be okay.
What's wrong?
I have to go now.
Wait at the entrance.
I'll get you out of here tonight at 10.
And if anyone asks what you're
doing, say you couldn't sleep.
My mother changes shifts at 5:00 p.m.
She has a keycard.
She always takes the same route.
We'll bring Mikkel back.
I promise.
I'm sorry.
For everything.
One year after the horrific
events in Chernobyl,
five high-ranking
employees at the reactor
have been given long prison sentences.
Meanwhile, German nuclear power plants
have seen increased safety inspections.
Oh, Charlotte. You're back already?
...that German nuclear
power plants are safe.
USA.
German Foreign Affairs
Minister Hans-Dietrich Genscher
addressed the UN General
Assembly in New York
and urged global superpowers
to take further steps
towards disarmament.
Bremerhaven.
The German research vessel Polarstern
has set out to explore the Antarctic...
Bad day?
The expedition's aim is to
research the hole in the ozone.
Have you ever thought whether
it's possible to turn back time?
Yes.
Yes, I have.
And?
Do you think it's possible?
That you can go back and change things?
You're so grown up now.
Grown up enough.
For a long time now I've wanted
to be able to turn back time.
But my place isn't in the past
nor in the future.
But here,
with you.
Are these my parents?
You said there were no photos.
That's not you.
Those aren't your parents.
That's my son and his wife.
And my granddaughter.
They died in a car accident.
In the night,
when it happened, I woke up.
There was a noise
downstairs in the shop.
And 2 women were there.
They looked peculiar.
They were carrying a bundle.
That bundle was you.
They said
that everything would be
taken from me that very night.
And that at the same time,
I would be given everything.
And then I got the call.
On the bridge,
a truck had forced my
son's car into the river.
They only ever found the
bodies of my son and his wife.
My granddaughter...
was never found.
This is the only thing
that you had with you.
FOR CHARLOTTE
I don't understand this.
Who are my parents?
Charlotte...
Who am I?
I don't know.
- Charlotte?
- One of your colleagues let me in.
I have questions about
the dead boy in the bunker.
I hope that's okay.
Are you all right?
The planning meeting for
dismantling the facility.
Everyone's getting nervous.
In a year this is all meant to be over.
I never would have thought
it would end like this.
But that's how it is.
There's a time for everything.
When exactly did you come to Winden?
Autumn of 1986.
Why?
And when did you start working here?
Around the same time.
So you got the shift schedules?
I was wondering if you
archive the shift schedules.
Long term.
What month is this about?
Not month.
1986.
POLICE
Hello, Claudia.
We need more men!
Come on.
We need to go.
I'm not going with you.
They're dead, Daddy.
We haven't...
found them.
If they're alive, why
haven't they come back?
Why aren't they looking for us?
They're dead.
Everyone here is dead.
I don't want to do this anymore.
POLICE
You're from another world?
What do you want here?
I'm here to guide you into the light.
There are 2 groups out there
who are fighting for
supremacy in time travel.
Light and shadow.
I want you to join our side.
Eva's side.
Eva?
You thought you could
trust him, but you can't.
Who?
Jonas.
He belongs to the shadow.
Jonas?
He's dead.
No.
He's not.
He wants to obliterate both
worlds and destroy the knot.
He doesn't yet know that's
what he'll want in the end.
But all the impulses on his
journey will lead him there.
But Eva wants to save both worlds.
I don't understand.
Jonas said we could change it.
We change one component, which
will change the entire world.
That's what you told him.
Your older self.
A positive feedback loop.
Jonas opened the passage in 2020.
The older Jonas had shut
it prior to that, in 2019.
After it had been opened for the
first time in the summer of 1986.
All three times, cesium
residue was left behind.
A component of the black matter.
Radioactive half-lives.
In each cycle, at all 3 moments,
cesium is brought back into the
tunnel before it has fully decayed.
It expands exponentially ad infinitum.
So that's how the passage was created.
And that's how it must
continue to exist for eternity.
Everything has to happen again.
Jonas bringing the
matter into the passage,
the opening of one of the drums in
the plant triggering the apocalypse.
Everything in this loop repeats itself.
Life.
And death.
WARNING!
SECURITY ZONE NO TRESPASSING
What exactly is in these barrels?
I don't know.
But something happened
here in the summer of 1986.
An accident.
And what remained,
the substance in the barrels...
that makes it possible
to travel through time.
They're bringing the truck
with the barrels in today.
We'll wait until nightfall.
Oh, crap.
It's fine. Just a scratch.
What's wrong?
That scratch.
She had it.
The Martha who brought me here.
Everything repeats itself.
She wanted to change it.
But if you become her,
everything stays the same.
Why did Eva lie?
She said there was a way to save it.
My world.
I've got no idea about your
world, but this is my world.
If I can stop the barrels being opened,
if it's possible to stop it all...
And what if that's what she wants?
For it all to happen again?
Maybe she doesn't want us to stop it.
Maybe it's us
who trigger it in the first place.
- Why would she want that?
- Because they're all lying!
The entire time
I've done what the
others have told me to do.
And it just made everything worse.
I have to go back to Eva.
I finally want to
know what the truth is.
Jonas.
Jonas, wait!
You need a special invitation,
or what?
Coming or not?
Excuse me.
If I walk, how long does
it take to get to Winden?
If I were you, I'd reconsider.
Winden is like a black hole.
Once you're there, you never get out.
You all right?
It's complicated.
Almost everything is complicated.
What are you doing here?
It's complicated.
My mother died.
My father lives here.
Until a few days ago, I didn't
even know who my father was.
She told me.
Shortly before she died.
Do you believe it's possible to
bring someone back from the dead?
How's that supposed to work?
You have to get them before they die.
I'm Peter.
Charlotte.
Peter?
Back from school so early?
I didn't go.
What do you mean, you didn't go?
What are you doing here?
I saw Aleksander.
The day Mads disappeared,
Helge was working at the plant.
His shift ended at 6:00 p.m. Mads
disappeared at around 6:21 p.m.
You're not serious, are you?
I don't know why Helge said that.
But he had nothing to do with Mads
or with the boy you found.
He was with us all evening.
Your father may be involved
in the murders of two boys.
- She's not deaf!
- Erik is still missing.
This penny, what does it mean?
Ulrich is right.
It's all somehow connected.
Ulrich?
I have to go back to the office.
Hey, wait.
Don't be scared.
Do you live here alone?
I asked if you live alone.
I've no idea when I last ate warm food.
It's time.
You have to let her go, Franziska.
Adam can never be allowed
to untie that knot.
You have to lead them.
Jonas.
Noah.
Elisabeth.
I don't understand.
- Lead them where?
- Down the same path.
Again and again.
We have to preserve the knot.
In your world you must
do all you can to do that,
as I must in mine.
Jonas. You'll have to guide him.
And then later, defy him.
- How will I know what I must do?
- It's all in there.
We'll see each other again.
In your world.
Soon.
Hold on, wait!
Jonas?
What if it's the truth?
If there can only be one world.
Yours or mine.
You decided long ago.
You want to go back.
To your world.
I didn't want any of this.
You have to believe me.
You didn't want any of this?
Last night...
you didn't want that?
This is wrong.
I'm wrong here.
So this is wrong, hey?
Are you following me?
What do you want?
The keycard.
You're crazy.
I don't want to hurt you.
The keycard!
I know you. I knew it right away,
that first day in the hospital.
Where do I know you from?
Mum, stop it!
What did you say?
I'm not your mother.
You come from hell.
The devil sent you.
You're not real.
I got rid of you.
Here. You go inside.
I'll grab the rest.
Right...
here we are again.
Should I make us a hot chocolate?
Or are you hungry?
Michael?
Are you hungry?
Mum, is everything all right?
You're bleeding!
Mum, what happened?
Mum, say something.
What is that?
Is that from Ulrich?
You dirty little slut.
You're not worthy of
the name you were given!
I should've gotten rid of you too.
What is this place?
It is what will become of you.
Adam and Eva.
And thus everything starts over again.
You lied.
You said we could save both worlds,
but we can only save one.
Or is that a lie too?
I want to go back!
Now!
To my world!
Of course you do.
But there is no way back for you.
What do you mean?
A human being lives 3 lives.
The first one ends
with the loss of naiveté.
The second...
with the loss of innocence.
And the third...
with the loss of life itself.
Yours ends here and now.
What?
You have accomplished what you
were sent to this world for.
We've accomplished nothing.
She said we had to stop the apocalypse.
- The barrels in the power plant...
- You'll understand it all
when it's time for you to understand.
Who are you?
I'm sorry.
No. Jonas!
Jonas, stay with me.
Please, I can't...
Please, Jonas.
I'll make this right.
No, no.