THE SURVIVORS
SEPTEMBER 22, 1987
THE GOONIES
MISSING FOR THREE MONTHS
WHERE IS CLAUDIA TIEDEMANN?
NUCLEAR POWER PLANT HEAD
MISSING SINCE JUNE 26,
THE DAY HER FATHER
WAS FOUND DEAD AT HOME.
SEPTEMBER 22, 2020
WHO HAS SEEN MICHAEL KAHNWALD?
12 YEARS OLD
VISITOR'S PASS - NIELSEN, TRONTE
This is good.
If they're not here, then...
Maybe they traveled.
CALL FOR WITNESSES
WE ASK FOR YOUR ASSISTANCE
MISSING
TIEDEMANN, CLAUDIA
I'll take a look around upstairs.
MOM AND SISTER
Where do you sleep?
CAVE
MACHINE FACTORY TANNHAUS
MOM AND SISTER
CAVE
LENTIL SOUP
What did he say to you?
The boy.
I'm not a little kid anymore.
Why do you carry that around
everywhere you go?
What's in there?
Where are Mom and Franziska?
SEPTEMBER 22, 2053
Everything will be okay.
MOM AND SISTER
CAVE