[Claudia on recording] We've managed
to stabilize the God Particle
and consequently the resulting mass.
In a stable state
it seems to create a kind of portal,
which possibly allows for time travel.
Supplied with sufficient voltage
the matter can be kept
in a stable state in the long term.
Sending objects
through the stabilized matter
has proven possible.
[roaring, electronic bubbling]
[recording continues indistinctly]
A generator has to supply
sufficient AC current for that.
Despite lengthy observation,
we have yet to determine
the matter's energy source.
It would appear
to be running entirely on its own.
The readings indicate
that there is no loss of energy.
It seems to be a recursive,
self-sustainable system.
[roaring]
[mechanical whirring]
Radiation emanating from the matter
is above control values.
Yet there are no signs of deterioration.
This is consistent with the principle
of conservation of energy,
yet contradicts
the second law of thermodynamics.
The matter seems to exist
independent of external temperatures...
in solid, liquid
and gaseous states simultaneously.
Its molecules are continually rearranged
in a cyclical process.
[droning and whirring]
[beeping and whirring]
[loud whirring]
[quiet, tense music]
[breathing heavily]
[bubbling and electronic whirring]
["Goodbye" by Apparat plays]
♪ Fold out your hands ♪
♪ Give me a sign ♪
♪ Put down your lies ♪
♪ Lay down next to me ♪
♪ Don't listen when I scream ♪
♪ Bury your doubts and fall asleep ♪
♪ For neither ever ♪
♪ Nor never ♪
♪ Goodbye ♪
♪ Neither ever ♪
♪ Nor never ♪
♪ Goodbye ♪
♪ Neither ever ♪
♪ Nor never ♪
♪ Goodbye ♪
JUNE 22, 1987
FIVE DAYS UNTIL THE APOCALYPSE
[breathing heavily]
[gloomy music]
Hey, sleepyhead.
We're running a little late today.
[sighs] Don't worry, it'll be fine.
Just one week, then you're on vacation.
But it's my mom's birthday.
You know what we said, hmm?
The past is the past, you know.
And now is now.
Shall we?
Let's go.
[Claudia] Regina, you'll be late!
The French delegation
is visiting the plant.
- I can't make it today.
- No problem.
I'm not doing anything at all.
- Regina!
- I can do this more often.
- [Claudia] Regina!
- [dog barks]
["Never Gonna Give You Up"
by Rick Astley plays on the radio]
Where did you find this little one?
- She looks like Gretchen.
- For God's sake.
Regina, where are you?
[Egon] Listen.
I want to talk while I'm here.
There's something
I really need to tell you about.
Hi, Grandpa. We going?
- Don't say goodbye, no problem!
- [door closes]
Tell me what?
It's nothing.
All right. Goodbye, then.
[door opens and closes]
[dog whimpers]
POLICE
[quiet, ominous music]
JANUARY 8, 1921
SIC MUNDUS CREATUS EST
[quietly] "Sic mundus creatus est.
Thus the world was created."
[door opens]
[Clausen] The Tiedemann interview.
You forget?
No. I thought you wanted to do it alone.
What's wrong? Have something better to do?
No. It's just, I'm wondering
why Mrs. Tiedemann is first.
There's no link to the missing persons.
The missing all disappeared
near the caves or the nuclear power plant.
It's also true
of your colleague Ulrich Nielsen's brother
in 1986.
And then...
there's also that door we found
to the nuclear plant, underground.
How long have Aleksander Tiedemann
and his wife been married?
I really don't know.
Regina was...
mid-20s.
How come?
It's not unusual?
What?
That Aleksander Tiedemann
took the name of his wife when he married?
No.
We going?
- Coming?
- Yup.
[doorbell rings]
[doorbell rings repeatedly]
[door opens]
[Franziska] Hey, where have you been?
Why didn't you call back?
I've been trying to reach you all day.
Last year.
I know where you got the cash.
Blow job 40 euros, anal 45?
Kinky games extra?
Who'd you do it with?
Who've you been sucking off
in this fucking town?
Nothing's changed!
All the lying, everybody.
- I have no idea what you're saying.
- I followed you.
I know where you got the cash.
- Your first thought is I'm a prostitute?
- What else could I think?
I don't sell my tits or my ass.
I fucking sell
hormone therapy prescriptions.
My father used to pay
for his visits with them.
Since he hasn't been able to,
I'm the new source.
Why do you do it?
I help her, she helps me.
That's all it is.
The secrets are never the problem,
it's what everyone in this town projects.
Besides, I said it doesn't concern you
and it doesn't.
I can't believe you've been spying on me.
How fucked up is that?
[door opens and closes]
What is that?
A time machine.
[unlocking machine]
You can travel 33 years into the past
or 33 years into the future.
You're serious, huh?
I did it all wrong.
I meant to keep it secret.
But you see,
that's exactly what's behind this.
The secrets.
Mom, I know it seems insane.
I want you to see for yourself,
with your own eyes.
Meaning?
[quietly] Dad's secret, I mean.
["Being Boiled" by The Human League plays]
♪ Listen to the voice of Buddha ♪
♪ Saying stop your sericulture ♪
[song stops]
Out of my way, douchebag!
[Katharina] Hey, Hannah, come on.
What are you staring at?
[school bell sounding]
Thank God you're here.
There's someone's waiting in your office.
[dog barks]
I didn't know...
It... It's the dog.
She says it belongs to her.
[sighs softly]
[dog whining softly]
Is she yours?
I'm so sorry.
She ran to me.
The animal shelter said
no one had reported her missing.
And she looks like the dog I had
as a little girl.
Gretchen.
How did you know that?
Because it's my dog.
Just like it is yours.
[mysterious music]
Excuse me?
[Egon Tiedemann] And the blood levels?
So it's already spread.
The hospital?
Friday already?
Oh, no.
Yeah, okay. That'll work.
Don't worry. I have someone.
Yeah.
[sighs heavily]
[breathes shakily]
NO TRACE OF MADS NIELSEN
ALMOST A YEAR AFTER HIS DISAPPEARANCE
POLICE DIARY 1986
10:30 A.M. INTERVIEW: HELGE DOPPLER
WHY NOT THROUGH THE FOREST?
[quietly] Why not through the forest?
[old Claudia]
I know it's hard to believe.
But I remember.
What?
This exact moment.
Go to the window.
Trust me.
There are two people at their desks,
Hermann und Kowaltschik.
Our secretary will approach the desk.
She'll fan her face on the way.
Watch Kowaltschik.
He's about to drop his pen.
You should be more careful.
Someone could trip.
What's this all about?
It happened to me.
All you have experienced,
all you've ever been.
I am you.
And I was told by me
that you and I are the same person.
This can't be real.
This is Gretchen.
The day she ran into the caves
I was there waiting for her.
Knew me as if I hadn't aged a day.
I made sure she would find you
on the other side.
Some things have to happen
exactly the way they always have.
The cave.
Everything last summer.
There was something else!
[suspenseful music]
["Suspicious Minds"
by Elvis Presley plays]
♪ We're caught in a trap ♪
♪ I can't walk out ♪
♪ Because I love you too much, baby ♪
♪ Why can't you see ♪
♪ What you're doing to me ♪
♪ When you don't believe a word I say? ♪
♪ We can't go on together ♪
♪ With suspicious minds ♪
[tank noise drowns out music]
♪ On suspicious minds ♪
♪ So, if an old friend I know ♪
♪ Stops by to say hello ♪
♪ Would I still see suspicion
In your eyes? ♪
♪ Here we go again ♪
♪ Asking where I've been ♪
[faded] ♪ You can't see
These tears are real I'm crying ♪
[tense music]
♪ Why can't you see ♪
♪ What you're doing to me ♪
♪ When you don't believe a word I say? ♪
- [Regina] Do you believe in ghosts?
- [Aleksander] What do you mean?
[Regina] This book we're reading
in school right now.
It's about the ghosts and demons
we inherit from our parents.
And the ones we pass on.
Dark stuff.
From generation to generation.
I guess.
But you only got your mom's best features,
if you ask me.
[Regina scoffs]
- I didn't even know she had any.
- No?
You have no idea.
She's never there.
And when she is,
all she does is complain about me.
She's never said, "I love you, Regina."
Let me, then.
[Clausen] How would you describe
your relationship with Ulrich Nielsen?
We don't have a relationship
with any of the Nielsens at all.
Mm-hmm. The day before he disappeared
he was at your hotel.
What did he want?
[Regina] He wanted to know
what really happened in 1986.
Because I was the last person
to see his brother before he died.
Your husband.
He came to Winden...
Since 1986.
- Why do you ask?
- Why did he take your last name?
I don't understand.
What does my name have to do with this?
- I think we're done here.
- Sh! Sh, sh, sh, sh, sh, sh.
There's still something else.
No?
Last year a man came to the hotel.
Those are his things.
He wanted a room.
He looked like a homeless person.
He paid cash.
He left after a few days.
He wanted to keep the room, though.
He never came back.
These were covering the walls.
When he left, he asked me
to deliver a package for him.
To whom?
Jonas Kahnwald.
You kept this secret?
I have to go.
Elisabeth has swim class.
I totally forgot.
I'm sorry.
You can take a taxi home.
Well...
[door closes]
This strange man...
What did he look like?
[Hannah] What is this?
Why are we here?
[Jonas] It's safer to travel from here.
[unlocking machine]
[whirring]
I meant it when I said it'd be easier
once you've seen it.
[suspenseful music]
Don't be scared.
[quiet clattering]
[muffled roar]
[roaring]
[Mikkel panting]
[Noah] Shouldn't you be at school?
I know you.
You were at the hospital.
I come here a lot.
It's special here.
So...
Why aren't you at school?
Mm!
I get it. Sometimes we don't really know
where we should be.
I wouldn't be going in there.
It's like a maze in there.
Some don't come back out.
At the hospital,
something you said...
about God
and how he has a plan for everyone.
What if God doesn't know
what he's doing?
If the plan is wrong?
If God is wrong?
God is never wrong.
Sometimes we need faith
that things will get better for us again.
[eerie music]
[ominous music]
[Egon Tiedemann]
I've been meaning to for a long time.
To come by here.
Now that I'm retired,
I mean, it's easy to do.
I...
Mads' disappearance.
It still haunts me.
That day...
You were working at the plant that day.
You said you took the country lane home,
but that's the long way.
Tell me why you wouldn't take
the forest road?
[faltering] He said...
he could change it.
That he could change everything,
the future and past.
Who told you that?
[shuddering] The man with the stone.
But that was 30 years ago.
What's this to do with Mads at all?
Nobody can change it. Nobody!
Not even the white devil!
The white devil?
You've talked about all this before.
You were just a child.
[weeping] Tick, tock.
Tick, tock.
[old Claudia] I want you to believe
in an idea that is bigger than you,
bigger than any of us.
What is that?
This is mankind's greatest discovery,
and also its doom.
It lets you travel through time.
Thirty-three years backwards.
Thirty-three years forwards.
And it will take exactly 33 years
till the cycle is complete again.
You will stand here
where I am standing.
And you will accept your part
in all of this,
and what it means you'll be losing.
In five days everything starts over.
You must stop Adam.
Who is Adam?
You don't understand it yet.
But you will soon.
But until then everything will happen
the way it always has.
[whirring]
The way it has to.
[high-pitched whir]
In the end, life is just
a collection of missed opportunities.
You don't have much time with Regina.
[clattering]
But if everything works out...
she will live.
[eerie music]
[roaring]
[guns cocking]
[Jonas breathes heavily]
[threatening music]
A JOURNEY THROUGH TIME
[phone line ringing]
[Peter] Charlotte?
Charlotte?
Are you okay?
Last year, when the kids went missing...
a man was at Regina's hotel.
He had some drawing with him, copies.
What kind of drawings?
They're from the book.
The book my grandfather wrote, Peter.
A Journey through Time.
- They all said he was crazy.
- Where are you now?
But he knew that it was all true.
Why did he have that photo?
And why didn't he ever say
who my parents really were?
"You... You know the rules."
[girl] "Do you think
they don't apply to you?"
Why are you lying?
- About what's really in the dead zone!
- [gunshot]
Ah! Ah!
[groaning] Ah!
In five days, in my time,
everybody is going to die.
I have to stop that!
There is no prophecy!
The passage will never open!
Your paradise is nothing but lies!
But behind the wall...
[gagging]
[choking]
[gunshot]
[wheezing, gasping]
WINDEN BOY MISSING
[Egon Tiedemann] Hello. This is Egon.
MISSING PERSON REPORT:
MADS NIELSEN
Listen, back in 1953, we arrested a man.
MADS NIELSEN CASE:
POLICE IN DARK
WHAT HAPPENED TO HIM AFTER 1953?
He killed two children
and kidnapped Helge Doppler.
NO RESULT
Yes.
I was wondering,
what ever happened to the guy?
Yes, I'll wait.
IS THIS MAN A CHILD KILLER?
Yes?
Okay, you have the file.
But he can't still be here!
Where?
[door buzzer sounding]
Yes?
Chief Inspector Tiedemann.
I'm here to speak with a patient.
Was anyone told I was coming?
Not that I know of.
Well, well.
File number...
K-5-3.
Must've been here for 34 years.
The Inspector?
That's what we call him here.
Nice guy. I wasn't even born when he came.
He's like a permanent fixture.
- He'll be happy to finally have a visitor.
- Does he...
- get day release?
- No.
That ward is closed.
That one, with the long gray hair.
Thank you.
Excuse me, please.
I don't know
if you recognize me, but, uh...
my name is Egon Tiedemann.
I arrested you 34 years ago.
[dismal music]
Egon Tiedemann.
Of course I remember you.
I...
I wanted...
some of your time.
[Ulrich sniffs]
"My only aim is to take many lives.
The more, the better I feel."
I've heard that.
You've said those words before.
What the hell does it mean?
It means you're still an idiot
who doesn't understand.
You have to hurry now.
You don't have much time.
Until you're dead and buried.
It was in the papers.
- I'm not following you.
- No, of course you aren't.
Maybe that's your fate.
To die as clueless as you were born,
you know?
[laughs]
Everybody gets what they deserve.
[thunder rumbling]
[door unlocks]
Where were you?
I've been so worried, Mikkel.
I called the school.
They said you weren't there.
Something happen?
You know what? [clears throat]
There are some days
you just have to forget about.
But...
there's no better comfort food I know
than "Toast Hawaii."
Way back when I was little we'd have this,
with two cherries on top.
And my dad used to dance, like Elvis.
PINEAPPLES
[Mikkel] Do you believe in God?
Mm-hmm.
Do you think he has a plan?
[thunder rolls]
I believe that.
Yeah.
I believe, for example, that God made sure
you came to me.
And that his plan for me is to...
to take care of you.
[breathes deeply]
So, let's make this "Toast Hawaii," yeah?
[sniffles] Give me a hand?
[melancholy music]
[thunder rolls]
[gasping]
[gate opening]
[gun cocking]
[breathes shakily]
Why didn't she kill you?
Who are you, really?
[yells] Tell me now!
So show me, then.
What's really in the dead zone?
[soft guitar music]
["Thunder" by Ry X plays]
♪ Lover, lover ♪
♪ What have we done? ♪
♪ Let our heart leap ♪
♪ Then it gave up ♪
♪ Lover, lover ♪
♪ Let me in ♪
♪ Make my heart leap ♪
♪ Under your skin ♪
♪ Couldn't we both ♪
♪ Try to say no? ♪
♪ Try to not reach ♪
♪ For heaven ♪
♪ Tied to a post ♪
♪ Tight like a rope ♪
♪ Try to not reach ♪
♪ For memories ♪
♪ Lover, lover ♪
♪ What have we done? ♪
♪ We made our heart leap ♪
♪ Then it gave up ♪
♪ Lover, lover ♪
♪ Let me in ♪
♪ Make my heart leap ♪
♪ Under your skin ♪
♪ You came in the door like thunder ♪
♪ Then hit the floor like thunder ♪
♪ Laying me down you wonder ♪
♪ Shaking the walls like thunder ♪
♪ You came in the door like thunder ♪
♪ Then hit the floor like thunder ♪
♪ Laying me down you wonder ♪
♪ Shaking the walls like thunder ♪
♪ You came in the door like thunder ♪
[panting]
[dog whimpers softly]
[electronic music]
[grunting]
[panting]
BUILDING YOUR FAMILY'S HAPPINESS
[whirring, bubbling]
[generator drones]
[girl] What is that?
She said that it's a portal.
Who?
Tapes of a woman talking.
Her name is Claudia Tiedemann.
I know it sounds crazy.
But that could very well
be our way to get home.
I don't know if it works.
[whizzing and whirring]
[bubbling]
[bubbling abates]
You're going in?
Whether I die out here
or in there doesn't matter.
[whirring and bubbling]
[suspenseful music]
Jonas!
[roaring]
[threatening music]
[intense music playing]