We have managed to stabilize
the God Particle and the resulting mass.
In a stable state,
it seems to create a kind of portal
which possibly allows for time travel.
If the matter is supplied
with sufficient voltage,
it can be kept in a stable state
in the long term.
Sending objects through the stabilized
matter has already proved possible.
A generator has to supply
sufficient AC current for that.
Even after lengthy observation,
we are not sure what the energy source
of the instable matter is.
Measurements indicate
there is no form of energy loss.
It appears to be a type
of self-sustaining recursive system.
The matter's radiation levels
exceed control values.
Still, no signs of decay
have been observed.
This is consistent
with the law of conservation of energy,
yet contradicts
the second law of thermodynamics.
Moreover, the matter seems to exist,
independent of external temperature,
in solid, liquid
and gaseous states at once.
And the molecules seem to be
in a constant cycle...
JUNE 22, 1987
FIVE DAYS UNTIL THE APOCALYPSE
THE GOONIES
CAPTAIN FUTURE
NUCLEAR NAVIGATORS
Hey, sleepyhead.
We're running a bit late today.
Come on, everything will be fine.
Just one more week
and it's summer vacation.
It's my mother's birthday today.
You know what we said about that.
The past is the past...
...and now is now.
Shall we?
Come on.
Regina, you'll be late!
The French delegation
is visiting the plant. I just can't do it.
No problem.
I don't have anything else to do.
- Regina!
- I really can do this more often.
Regina!
Where did you find this little one?
- Looks like Gretchen.
- Nonsense.
Regina, where are you?
Listen.
I actually wanted to talk to you.
There's something I have to tell you.
Hi, Grandpa. Can we go?
No need to say bye. No problem!
You wanted to tell me something?
Never mind.
All right. See you later.
POLICE
JANUARY 8, 1921
SIC MUNDUS CREATUS EST
Sic mundus creatus est.
Thus the world was created.
The interview with Mrs. Tiedemann.
- Already forgotten?
- No.
I thought you might do it alone after all.
Why? Do you have something better to do?
No. I just wonder
why we're starting with Mrs. Tiedemann.
She has no link
to any of the missing people.
Everyone disappeared near the caves
and the nuclear power plant grounds.
Your colleague Ulrich Nielsen's brother
disappeared in that area in 1986 as well.
And then...
there's also the door in the caves
leading right to the nuclear power plant.
How long have Aleksander Tiedemann
and his wife been married?
I don't exactly know.
Regina was... in her mid-twenties.
Why?
Don't you find it unusual?
What?
That Aleksander Tiedemann
took his wife's name?
No.
Shall we go?
- Are you coming?
- Yes.
Hey, where have you been?
Why didn't you call me back?
I was trying to reach you the whole time.
Last year,
I know where you got the money.
Blow job 40 euros, anal 85.
Kinky stuff costs extra?
Who did you do it with, huh?
Who did you blow in this damn shithole?
Nothing has changed.
Everyone lies. Everyone cheats.
- I have no idea what you're talking about.
- I followed you.
I know who you get your money from.
Your first thought
is that I prostitute myself?
What else?
I don't sell my tits or my ass!
I sell hormone therapy prescriptions,
you idiot!
My father used to use them
to pay for his visits.
He stopped going,
and now I'm the new supplier.
Why do you do it?
I help her, she helps me.
It's that simple.
The secrets aren't the problem,
it's the shit we all project onto others.
I said it's none of your fucking business,
and it isn't!
I can't believe you spied on me.
How messed up are you?
What's that?
A time machine.
This machine takes you 33 years
into the past
and 33 years into the future.
You're serious?
I did it all wrong.
I tried to keep a secret.
The truth is,
that is exactly what's destroying us.
The secrets.
Mom, I know that sounds insane.
That's why I want you to see for yourself.
With your own eyes.
What do you mean?
Dad's secret.
Out of the way, dork!
Hannah, come on!
What are you staring at?
Thank God you're here.
Someone's waiting for you in your office.
I didn't know.
About the dog.
She says it's hers.
Is that your dog?
I'm so sorry.
She ran up to me.
We called the shelter,
but no one had reported her missing.
- And she resembles the dog I had as a kid.
- Gretchen.
How do you know that?
Because it's my dog.
Just like it's yours.
Excuse me?
And the blood test results?
So it has already spread.
To the hospital?
This Friday?
No.
Yes, that should work.
Don't worry. I have someone.
Yes.
NO TRACE OF MADS NIELSEN
POLICE DIARY 1986
10:30 A.M. INTERROGATION: HELGE DOPPLER
WHY NOT THROUGH THE FOREST?
Why not through the forest?
I know it's hard to believe.
But I remember.
What?
This precise moment.
Go to the blinds.
Trust me.
Two people are sitting at their desks,
Hermann and Kowaltschik.
Our secretary will approach
the desk on the right in a moment.
She'll fan her face on the way.
Watch Kowaltschik.
He's about to drop his pen.
How did you do that?
I experienced it all.
Everything you've ever experienced
and everything you ever will.
I am you.
And I was told by me
that you and I are the same person.
That's impossible.
This is Gretchen.
The day she ran into the cave
I was there waiting for her.
She recognized me at once,
as if I hadn't aged a second.
I brought her to the other side
so you would find her.
Some things have to happen
as they always have.
The cave.
The incident last summer.
Something else happened afterall!
Do you believe in ghosts?
What do you mean?
The book we're reading at school.
It's about the ghosts and demons
that we inherit from our parents.
And...
that you pass them on.
Dark stuff.
From generation to generation.
Maybe.
But you sure inherited
your mother's best features.
I didn't even know she had any.
No?
You have no idea.
She... She's never around.
And when she is,
all she does is gripe about me.
She has never once said
"I love you" to me.
I love you.
How would you describe
your relationship with Ulrich Nielsen?
I think it's known that we have
no relationship with the Nielsens.
Yet he showed up at your hotel
the day before he disappeared.
What did he want?
He wanted to know
what really happened in 1986.
Because I was the last one...
to see his brother alive.
Your husband.
How long has he lived in Winden?
Since 1986. Why do you ask?
Why did he take your last name?
What does one have to do with the other?
If we're done...
There's still something.
Isn't there?
Last year, a stranger came to the hotel.
Those are his things.
He wanted a room.
He looked like a homeless person.
He paid cash.
WHERE IS MIKKEL?
He left after a few days,
but he wanted to keep the room.
He never came back.
These were all over his walls.
As he was leaving, he asked me
to mail a package for him.
To whom?
Jonas Kahnwald.
Why did you not report this?
I have to go. Elisabeth has a swim class.
I totally forgot.
Sorry. You can take a taxi.
Well...
This stranger,
what did he look like?
What is this?
What are we doing here?
It's safer to travel from here.
I told you it would be easier
to understand once you've seen it.
Don't be scared.
Shouldn't you be at school?
I know you.
You were in the hospital.
I like coming here.
Special place.
So...
Why aren't you at school?
I see.
Sometimes we don't really know
where we're supposed to be.
But I wouldn't go in there.
It's like a maze in there.
Some have never returned.
In the hospital,
you said something.
The thing about God,
and that he has a plan for everyone.
But what if God
has no idea what he's doing?
If the plan is wrong? If God is mistaken?
God doesn't make mistakes.
Sometimes we have to have more faith
that everything will be okay again.
I've wanted to do this for a long time.
To come by.
Now that I'm retired, I have time.
I...
Mads' disappearance.
I can't stop thinking about it.
On that day...
you had a shift
at the nuclear power plant.
You said you took the country road home,
but that's a detour.
Why didn't you take the forest road?
He... He said...
he can change everything.
He can change the past, and the future.
Who said that?
The man with the stone.
But that was 30 years ago.
What does that have to do with Mads?
But no one can change it. No one.
Not even the White Devil.
The White Devil?
You've said that before.
Back then, as a child.
Tick, tock.
Tick, tock...
I'd like you to trust in an idea
that's bigger than you.
Bigger than any of us.
What's that?
This is humankind's greatest discovery.
And also its doom.
It allows you to travel through time.
Thirty three years back.
Thirty three years forward.
And it will take exactly 33 years
for the cycle to be completed again.
Until you are standing
where I am standing now
and accept your role
in this never-ending dance,
and every sacrifice it requires.
In five days, everything will start over.
You must stop Adam.
Who is Adam?
You don't understand it yet.
But you soon will.
Until then, everything will happen
as it always has.
As it must.
In the end, life is just a collection
of missed opportunities.
You don't have much more time with Regina.
But if everything works out...
she will live.
A JOURNEY THROUGH TIME
H.G. TANNHAUS
Charlotte?
- Is everything okay?
- Last year when the children disappeared,
a man was in Regina's hotel.
He had drawings with him.
Copies.
What kind of drawings?
They're from the book!
The book my grandfather wrote.
A Journey Through Time.
- Everyone always said he was nuts.
- Where are you?
But he knew that it was all true!
Why did he have that photo?
Why did he never tell me
who my parents really were?
You know the rules.
Do you think they don't apply to you?
Why are you lying to them?
Why don't you tell them
what's really in the dead zone?
In five days, in my time,
everybody is going to die.
I have to stop that.
There is no prophecy!
The passage will never open.
Your paradise does not exist!
But behind that wall...
WINDEN BOY MISSING
Hello? Egon here.
Yes.
MISSING PERSON REPORT:
MADS NIELSEN
Listen, in 1953 we arrested a man.
MADS NIELSEN CASE:
POLICE IN DARK
WHAT HAPPENED TO HIM
AFTER 1953?
He killed two kids back then.
Then he abducted Helge Doppler.
NO RESULT
I wanted to know what became of him.
Yes, I'll hold.
IS THIS MAN A CHILD MURDERER?
Yes.
Okay, that's the case.
What? He's still here?
Where?
- Yes?
- Chief Inspector Tiedemann.
I'd like to speak to a patient.
Weren't you notified I was coming?
Not that I know of.
Well...
File number...
K53.
He must have been here for 34 years now.
The Inspector?
We call him that here.
Nice guy. He's been here longer
than most of the staff.
Practically part of the furniture.
- He'll be glad to have a visitor.
- Does he...
Does he get day-release?
No, he's in the closed ward.
The guy over there,
with the long gray hair.
Thanks.
Excuse me, please.
You may not remember me anymore.
My name is Egon Tiedemann.
I arrested you 34 years ago.
Egon Tiedemann.
How could I ever forget you?
I...
I wanted...
I have a few questions.
My only aim is to take many lives.
The more the better I feel.
I know that.
You've said that before.
What does it mean?
It means that you, you moron,
still haven't understood a thing.
But now you have to hurry.
You don't have much time left.
I know when you die.
It was in the paper.
I don't understand.
No, of course you don't.
But maybe that is also your fate.
To die as clueless as you were
when you were born.
Everyone gets what they deserve.
Where have you been?
I was so worried.
I called the school.
They said you never showed up there.
Did something happen?
You know what?
There are days it's best to just forget.
But...
there's no better comfort food
than "Toast Hawaii."
We always had it at home
when I was little,
with two maraschino cherries.
And my dad used to dance,
like Elvis.
PINEAPPLES
Do you believe in God?
Do you believe he has a plan for us?
I believe... he does.
I believe, for example, that God saw to it
that you came to me.
And that his plan for me is
to be there for you.
Right, let's make "Toast Hawaii," okay?
Will you help me?
Why didn't she kill you?
Who are you really?
Who are you?
I want you to show me.
What's really in the dead zone.
IS THIS MAN A CHILD MURDERER?
BUILDING YOUR FAMILY'S HAPPINESS
What is that?
She said it's a portal.
Who?
I have tapes
with a woman speaking on them.
Her name is Claudia Tiedemann.
I know none of this makes sense,
but that may be the only way back home.
No clue if it works.
You want to go in?
It doesn't matter
if I die inside it or out here.
Jonas!
Subtitle translation by: