Is it not peculiar
that one feels the greatest aversion
towards the very people
who are most similar to oneself?
I want to know how to get back home.
Get dressed.
JUNE 25, 2020
TWO DAYS UNTIL THE APOCALYPSE
Wait.
I have to show you something.
We've got an appointment.
Maybe you'd better sit down.
Can we do this some other time?
We really have to go.
It's... I...
I have to tell you something.
It sounds totally crazy, but I have
to know what you think about it.
Are you nuts?
You've hardly spoken to us in months
and now you want to know what we think?
Look around you.
We're the kids, but you've been acting
like one for months.
Mom,
you act as if you're alone with this shit.
But we lost them too.
No.
So you want to talk,
that doesn't mean we do!
Why is he so interested
in the nuclear power plant?
Find someone at Criminal Investigation
who knows this Clausen guy.
What does he really want here?
Call me as soon as you know something.
Bartosz isn't here.
His bed hasn't been slept in.
He wasn't here all night.
- Maybe he's with Martha.
- They're not together anymore.
They must've made up. Have you called?
No one's answering.
I'm sure it's nothing.
Tell me it'll all be fine.
It'll all be fine.
You good, Inspector?
FORMER WINDEN CHIEF INSPECTOR
EGON TIEDEMANN
FOUND DEAD ON JUNE 26, 1987
CIRCUMSTANCES
SURROUNDING HIS DEATH STILL UNCLEAR
Ms. Tiedemann?
The French delegation.
They're all waiting.
I think you'd better get going.
Reschedule.
What?
But I can't just...
Why am I here?
A person lives three lives.
The first ends with the loss of naïveté,
the second with the loss of innocence,
and the third
with the loss of life itself.
It is inevitable
that we go through all three stages.
You will turn into your older self,
and your older self
into what you see before you.
I don't have time for this shit.
I have to go back home. To my time!
I've seen what will happen.
I've seen their graves.
You still have lots of time.
This is the year 1921.
Strictly speaking,
you still have 99 years.
Here. A fresh snack.
People can say what they like,
but Reagan is a first-rate guy.
The Olympic Games in East and West Berlin.
I call that visionary.
I have the whole speech on VHS.
You haven't been here in a long time.
I just wanted
to quickly check how you are.
It's fine.
Claudia.
You do know that I'm proud.
Of all you've accomplished.
And your mother would be, too.
I've got to go.
The real reason I came...
I want you to move in with us.
You wouldn't be so alone.
And Regina would be happy
to see more of you.
Tomorrow would be best.
Tomorrow?
You're acting
like I'm almost on my deathbed.
Think it over.
All right?
Katharina?
What do you want?
Is he here?
Jonas?
He has vanished.
I have no idea where he is.
You said you saw Mikkel.
You were there. How do I get to him?
He has this kind of...
device.
I guess it's like a...
time machine.
A time machine.
And do you know how it works?
Even if I did, it wouldn't help.
He took it.
He was always here.
Right in front of me.
I just can't believe you slept
with my husband and my son.
But you always did want
what belonged to me.
You're like a parasite.
Did Ulrich ever actually tell you
he loved you?
In the end, he would always choose us.
Hello.
You missed your appointment yesterday.
Oh, I'm sorry, I...
must have forgotten.
Hard to believe you'd forget it
when your own child is missing.
Mrs. Nielsen.
You were the last person
I expected to see here.
But since you're here...
Do you know who this is?
No, I don't.
And you?
Do you know this person?
No.
Do you know everything that will happen?
I know when wars begin and end,
what discoveries will be made
in the years ahead,
what shares I should invest in.
But I don't know
what my counterpart will do
as long as I haven't seen his future.
But you know my future.
You know what I'll do.
I am your future.
There must be a way to change it all.
So things happen differently.
A loophole.
It took me 66 years to find out how,
to find a way to escape this hell.
I've been here almost a week.
And I get the impression
no one is telling the truth.
Everyone's trying to hide something.
Although I'm not sure
if you're all hiding the same thing
or if everyone is trying
to keep their own skeleton in the closet.
Does he pay you?
Aleksander Tiedemann.
I don't quite follow you.
You worked as his physiotherapist.
You no longer do so, right?
Yet he still transfers you
the same amount every month.
One would normally expect
a service in return, so what is it?
What you don't get is
we stick together here.
We support each other.
My son disappeared.
Aleksander helps me with the money.
That's it.
Nothing beats a good neighborhood.
It's remarkable that Mrs. Nielsen
feels the same way about that.
Oh, well,
maybe that's how small towns are.
People share not only secrets,
but also money and beds.
- I want to know what you know.
- Fine.
Who is Noah?
He's one of them.
A traveler.
He's Adam's puppet.
He killed the children.
Mads, Erik, Yasin.
I think
all of this has to do with me.
Do you know who my parents are?
No.
But I knew your grandfather.
He's not my real grandfather.
I just grew up with him.
Did he know all this?
Is he one of them?
A traveler?
He's just a pawn, like most of us.
Claudia.
She used him.
Just like she used me, Peter
and the others.
She had him build this.
You know what will happen.
In the future.
Yes.
What is this?
Want to spend another night here?
Man, Bartosz, look at us.
What are we doing here?
Why won't you tell us what's going on?
I would if I could.
I'm not allowed to.
Even if I did tell you,
you wouldn't believe me.
Why not?
The human body
can go three days without liquid.
You're nuts. You can't do this!
You want to leave me here to die or what?
Hey, Martha.
Martha, wait. Please.
Martha, you can't do this!
Martha!
Okay.
It's a time machine.
What?
Are you screwing with me?
I said you wouldn't believe me.
Come on. We're leaving.
No. Wait.
Then show us how it works.
I need a phone.
- There's no reception here.
- That's irrelevant.
It just needs
to search for a signal, that's it.
ARIADNE
You need to come closer.
The incident last summer.
You told me it was from a reaction
in the volume control system.
I checked the data.
Everything was normal.
So...
What really happened?
I knew you wouldn't be able
to let it rest.
After the incident
I had a sample taken and analyzed.
What you see there are the results.
These values, they aren't possible.
I initially thought that too.
So I had the tests repeated.
The results were identical.
If this data is correct, then...
- Is this what I think it is?
- Possibly.
In many respects it corresponds
to Englert, Brout
and Higgs' calculations in 1964.
But not entirely.
The God Particle.
The particle
that gives all things its mass.
This is a sensation.
If this data is correct,
we have to go public with it.
I already told you
some sleeping dogs should be left to lie.
If we go public with it
people will want to know how we found it.
The nuclear power plant
is my legacy.
Do what you like with the data,
but leave my name
and the power plant out of it.
At least as long as I'm alive.
Can I help you?
Are you not well?
- Hello, Ines.
- Ina!
Hello.
We're out of iodine again.
Have you heard?
A guy escaped from the loony bin.
They say he killed two kids in the 1950s,
and beat another half to death.
He's on his last legs himself now,
but they say to be vigilant.
Thanks.
You seem familiar somehow.
I've waited over 33 years for this moment.
The question is not how,
but when.
You said that.
Remember?
Dad.
In the future
there's a prophecy about a new world.
That Sic Mundus
will lead people into paradise.
Is this that?
A religion?
We're the exact opposite of that.
We've declared war on time.
Declared war on God.
We're creating a new world,
without time,
without God.
What does that mean?
It means that what people
have worshipped for millennia,
the God who holds everything together,
that God is nothing more than time itself.
Not a thinking, acting entity.
A physical law
with which one can negotiate
as little as one can with one's own fate.
God
is time.
And time is not merciful.
We are born,
and our life is already trickling away
like the sand in this hourglass.
Death is forever inevitably before us.
Our fate
is nothing
but a concatenation of cause and effect.
In light
and in shadow.
Charlotte.
What do you want?
- I'm Noah.
- I know who you are.
You killed the children.
I can no longer change
what you think of me.
But...
maybe one day you'll understand
that I only did this
so that it will one day no longer happen.
So you're not taken from me again.
And neither is your mother.
When you were born
they didn't give you much of a chance.
You were premature. You were tiny.
But you wanted to live.
You were so strong.
Your little hand grasped my finger
and wouldn't let go.
Stop.
That's impossible.
Your mother took that picture.
I promised her I'd bring you back.
I've looked for you all these years.
But you were here the entire time.
Adam knew it was you.
He knew it all the time.
He's preparing for what comes afterwards.
I read the last pages.
The nuclear power plant, Jonas.
It'll all happen again. The apocalypse.
In two days.
But I now know
what I must do.
I have to end Adam.
So everyone lives.
Not just those in the bunker.
Who is my mother?
She loved you very much.
She still does.
What happened here?
The armchair is gone.
- What's going on?
- I didn't believe it at first either.
But then he told me things
that would happen.
And they did, just as he said.
That...
you and Jonas kissed.
He told me that before you did it.
That my mother would get cancer.
That Jonas would vanish.
Who told you that?
Noah.
Noah?
The priest with the big blue eyes?
- You know him?
- I don't.
But Elisabeth does.
Okay, what's going on?
Noah said it was about a war.
And about ruling over time.
That my grandma is involved in it
and that Jonas will return and...
Jonas?
Jonas is coming back?
Yes.
He's part of the war.
I'm going home.
You have to believe me.
Michael?
Egon, it's Ines.
I know it sounds strange, but...
I just got home
and Michael isn't here and...
The man who broke out
of the psychiatric ward...
Which man from the psychiatric ward?
It was on the radio today.
Do you remember
the children
on the construction site in 1953?
That man, he escaped.
I'll call the police station at once.
I might know where they're heading.
I'll come pick you up.
Stop! Freeze!
- Michael!
- Let the boy go!
- No!
- Get on the ground!
Michael!
- You don't get it!
- Get down!
- He's my son.
- I said get down now!
- Mikkel.
- Michael! Michael.
Mikkel, I'll be back. I'll take you home.
I promise.
It's all your fault. It always has been.
I swear, next time I'll kill you.
Come on!
Mikkel!
Mikkel.
Michael.
Our father
is just a small part of a knot
that is infinitely larger
and more convoluted.
The entire universe
is nothing but a gigantic knot
from which there is no escape.
If that's so,
if everything is perpetually in that knot,
if nothing can be changed,
then you've already had this conversation?
And posed that very question.
My whole life, I was convinced
that this moment
could never be repeated in this way.
I could never speak the words
that my older self said to me back then.
Because I could not understand
how I could ever in my life want
what he wanted.
Now,
66 years later, I understand it.
Some moments change us forever.
Some pain you never forget.
But there is a way
that leads us out
of all of this cruel futility.
But if that's true, if there is a way,
why does it all happen as it always has,
why have you changed nothing?
Every development
builds on the previous one.
First you have the wheel, then the car.
I can't be me
without previously having been you.
You saw the passage, in the bunker.
The chair, the device.
The thing in the future.
But that is not the end of the chain.
Thanks for taking the time.
I'd like...
you to analyze this for me.
And not a word,
to anyone.
What is it?
If it's what I think it is,
it'll revolutionize
our understanding of the world.
MODERN TALKING
ALBUM TOUR, 1987
PRESERVE CREATION
GAIN THE FUTURE
Stop! Wait, stop! Pull over!
Those are my children!
Magnus! Martha!
Do you believe me now?
You're back!
Where have you been?
Did this ever mean anything to you?
Did you ever actually love Dad?
I know you had an affair with Ulrich.
If you could choose
between Dad and Ulrich now...
With all this shit, I thought you were
the only person I can trust.
I ruined everything,
I know.
Maybe you always have.
Jonas.
You need no one.
Just yourself.
It's not the same
as what lies in the future.
It is, in a manner of speaking, it's twin.
It is a part of the infinite.
It pervades everything.
People have given it a myriad of names
over the centuries,
ether, dark matter, the Higgs field.
How did it come to be?
The one in the future, via the disaster
in two days you so dearly want to prevent.
This one here we produced ourselves.
It is the end
of a technological evolution.
And...
it will be the end of the knot.
This right here
will take you to the exact day
that you want to travel to.
It breaks the 33-year cycle.
That's why I'm here.
That's what you want from me.
There is a way to stop it all
if I stop the beginning.
That there is.
The question is only,
when is the beginning?
And what sacrifice must we make?
June 20, 2019.
The day before it all happened.
Before Dad took his own life.
Before it all fell apart.
If you can prevent him
from taking his life,
then everything that follows
will not occur.
Mikkel will not travel back.
You...
I...
We won't be born.
But everyone else will live.
Martha will live.
If you succeed
we will reorder the world.