[birds chirp]
[ominous music plays]
[sinister string music plays]
[old Claudia]
Every journey has a beginning.
-[gasping]
-[gasps]
[panting]
[old Claudia] But yours has no end.
It goes on forever and ever.
I'm here to finally make
your journey come to an end.
This is impossible.
You should be dead.
I had you killed.
You still have no idea
just how this game is played.
You want to destroy the knot,
but every action you take
continues its existence.
This can't be.
I have killed it.
I have killed the origin,
and the origin within her.
Your world and Eve's world,
they both should have never existed.
You thought that the origin
lies in the bindings of both worlds.
But in reality,
it's outside of both worlds.
Our thinking is shaped by dualities.
Black, white.
Light and shadow.
Your world and Eve's world.
But this is false.
You need a third dimension
to fulfill it all.
The triqueta.
[takes deep breath and sighs]
That means...
a third world?
[old Claudia] The world
that gave birth to this knot.
Where everything originates.
[cracking and hissing]
Where a single mistake was made.
Tannhaus, in the origin world,
like you, he lost someone.
And like you, he tried to bring
that person back from the dead.
[machine hisses and rattles]
But instead
he divided and destroyed his world...
[hissing and buzzing]
...and created our two worlds.
[bolts of electricity crackle]
[hissing intensifying]
But there is a way to destroy the knot.
Through preventing, in the origin world...
the invention of travel
through space and time in the first place.
["Goodbye" by Apparat plays]
♪ Fold out your hands
Give me a sign ♪
♪ Put down your lies ♪
♪ Lay down next to me ♪
♪ Don't listen when I scream ♪
♪ Bury your doubts and fall asleep ♪
♪ For neither ever ♪
♪ Nor never ♪
♪ Goodbye ♪
♪ Neither ever ♪
♪ Nor never ♪
♪ Goodbye ♪
♪ Neither ever ♪
♪ Nor never ♪
♪ Goodbye ♪
PARADISE
I'd have liked
to have spared you all that.
But your path has to remain unchanged.
Every step has to be taken as before.
Up until this very moment.
This here...
Has this happened before?
Your trying to destroy the origin
has happened an infinite number of times.
But this here, you and I...
this is the first time.
It's time for you to understand
how everything is really connected.
Everything you have done,
everything Eve has done,
has maintained the knot for eternity,
in both worlds.
You create yourself ever anew.
And she creates herself.
They must die.
They all must die,
so they can be reborn correctly.
[menacing music plays]
You carry both worlds inside you.
[Martha] What?
Your son.
He is the origin.
He gives everyone their lives,
alternately in the two worlds.
[door opens]
[serene string music plays]
He's waited a long time for you.
And he will do so time and again.
[old Claudia]
You want to destroy your son,
and the knot along with him.
Eve wants him to live.
Therefore, she must maintain the knot.
She can't help it.
She'll do anything she can
to keep her son alive, time and again.
Everything you and Eve
have done in this knot,
and will do again and again,
you have done out of love.
And yet you have brought nothing
but pain and suffering.
[door opens]
[two metallic beats sound]
[dissonant organ music plays]
[Eve] If you want Jonas to live,
for them all to ever live,
then we must do what's been done always.
Even you.
[old Claudia] Both of you have done
unimaginable things on your journey.
Because you can't let go
of your deepest desire.
[door creaks as it opens]
[Eve, muffled] Yours ends here and now.
[Martha] What?
[Eve] You accomplished what you were sent
to this world to accomplish.
[Martha] We've accomplished nothing.
She said we have to stop the apocalypse.
The containers in the plant--
[older Martha] You will understand
everything when it's right for you to.
[old Claudia] You have been trying
to escape what you will become.
But that's impossible.
You will end up facing yourselves
again and again.
[suspenseful music intensifying]
[Martha] Who are you?
I'm sorry.
[old Claudia] Your two worlds
should have never existed.
You and Eve should never have existed.
How do you know all this?
How do you know about the origin world?
I've spent 33 years looking for answers,
in your world and hers.
I tried to put the pieces
of the puzzle together.
To understand how everything
can continually be reborn
from the same family tree.
Until I realized
that we're not all part of the knot.
Both worlds are an ulcer
that must have grown from something else.
If you remove it, you destroy
everything that was born of it,
but you keep everything alive
that already existed in the origin world.
All these years I believed
that she was my daughter.
For a long time,
I wished you were the father.
But it's better this way.
She isn't tied to the knot.
She will live.
[old Claudia] But just like you and Eve,
I had to preserve everything,
in order to become what I am today.
You know what has to be done.
Do it quickly.
Don't let her suffer.
What she's living is hardly a life.
It must happen...
so I'll move heaven and earth to avert it.
[old Claudia] Just like you,
I've brought pain and suffering to others.
Again and again.
So that my path could lead me
here to you today.
Everything I did
was for Regina.
[bunker door squeaks]
[old Claudia] All these years,
I've searched in both worlds for a way
for her to live.
A way to break
the chain of cause and effect.
[melancholy string music plays]
Both in your world and in Eve's
I've tried to understand
how everything is connected.
Truly connected.
Until I understood
that our two worlds
were created from another.
That Regina will always die
in both of our worlds.
That she can only live in the world
which everything was created from.
The origin world.
I lied to you.
And to Eve.
But the knot had to stay tied.
I had to make sure
you were both in the dark.
To keep everyone in this knot in the dark.
Everything had to happen
the way it always has.
In your world and in hers.
Every step in this labyrinth
had to be taken as it was before.
An infinite chain of cause and effect
that repeatedly leads us
to our same fate in both worlds.
[out of breath] Excuse me.
You see someone come by here?
An old man?
[old Claudia] We do not have
the free will to act in either world.
We will forever do
what we have always done before.
[Ulrich] Hey!
You're Helge Doppler, aren't you?
[Ulrich] Helge.
[old Claudia] No fate in one world
is better than the other.
What's today's date?
[suspenseful music building]
November 8.
What year?
1986.
1986...
[Ulrich] I can change that, you know.
I can change the past, and what's to come.
[Helge] Help!
If you don't exist,
none of this will happen.
-[Helge screams]
-[Ulrich] Ah!
No!
[grunts]
What's in there? Is he in there?
[Ulrich] What did you do to him?
[Helge gasps]
[panting]
[old Claudia] As long as the knot exists
we are condemned in both worlds
to feel and incite
every act of suffering anew.
[Ulrich grunts]
There is no difference
between the two worlds.
Things may not happen in the same way,
or at the same time,
but they always happen.
No one in this knot can escape their fate.
[metallic clatter]
[old Helge] It was you.
[grunts]
[old Claudia] Every piece of the puzzle
always finds its place.
[approaching footfalls]
Just like you,
I moved the pieces around the chessboard,
and had to look on as everything happened
over and over again.
[wheezing]
But I finally know how to untie the knot.
I know where the loophole
you've searched for all these years is.
Time.
During the apocalypse it stood still
for a fraction of a second at that point
and that threw everything out of balance.
But when time stands still,
it also momentarily breaks
the chain of cause and effect.
One can...
change things?
Eve knows that.
She uses the loophole in your world
to send her younger self off
in one direction or another,
and in doing so maintains the cycle.
I used it to make myself run
in a different direction too,
to be here today.
You must use it
to send Jonas on a different path.
To break this cycle once and for all.
Jonas and Martha
are to blame for everything happening
over and over again.
You must send them to the origin world,
so they can finally put an end to this.
[ominous music builds]
[thunder rolls]
[rumbling sound]
-[dishes clatter]
-[glass shatters]
[whispering] I promise.
I'll make it right.
[door opens]
[Jonas] What are you doing here?
She'd dead!
What do you want from me?
I'll tell you everything. All of it.
But we have to get out of here first.
[mechanical ticking]
What are you doing?
What is that?
[rattling and buzzing]
[yelling] What is that?
That is our last hope.
[muffled bang]
[hiss, thud]
How did you do that?
What time is this?
The question isn't what time...
but what world.
What are you saying?
There is a way
that you can avoid becoming me.
A way where all of this
never needs to happen.
But you, Jonas, you must trust me.
You don't have much time left.
The other Martha, you must save her.
The other Martha?
All these years I had thought that...
that I, alone, had to change things.
But it's just as much her fault.
You are two parts of the same whole.
Only together can you return
to the origin world.
What we know is a drop.
What we do not know...
is an ocean.
What are you saying?
[branches crack]
[ominous music plays]
[Helge] Tick... tock.
Ticktock.
[Adam] Today is the day of the apocalypse,
in her world.
The loophole,
it also exists here.
For a moment time will stand still.
You must get Martha...
before Magnus and Franziska get her.
And before everything happens again.
[melancholy string music plays]
You two are our last hope.
[hiss, thud]
[old Claudia]
Adam will send Jonas on his way.
He and Martha,
they will stop
all this from ever happening.
Dad.
Tell him that I'm sorry.
[sniffs]
If all this works,
then Regina will live.
[melancholy string music plays]
[Claudia sobs]
[hiss, thud]
[suspenseful electronic music plays]
[music intensifies]
[Bartosz] Martha?
What's going on here?
Martha?
[ticking and buzzing]
-[Martha] You have to come with us.
-[Bartosz] Come where?
[muffled thud]
[hiss, thud]
[panting]
What's going on?
[Martha sobs]
You're alive.
[Martha sobbing]
You look exactly like her.
[rhythmic a cappella singing]
You don't know who I am.
What time are we in?
When are we?
Why are we here?
[sobbing]
Today's the 21st of June 1986.
The day our worlds were created.
Not here, just in his world.
Tannhaus, the clockmaker,
will open the passage
for the first time today.
What?
Our time's running out.
We have to prevent it from ever happening.
Wait!
What does that mean? [sobs]
[hiss, thud]
[breathy a cappella singing continues]
[swooshing, bubbling sound]
[cranking sound]
[loud static buzzing and crackling]
[power subsides]
[hiss, thud]
Where are we going?
We're returning someone from the dead.
What are you saying?
It's difficult to explain.
We have to get them before they die.
What are you trying to do?
You and I...
we're the reason that all of this happens.
Time and time again.
Because you can't let go of what you want.
And I can't let go of what I want.
But we are the glitch.
The glitch in the matrix.
You want them to never exist.
Your world and mine.
That we never exist.
[somber music plays]
[somber electronic music plays]
[tension building in music]
[sighs]
[door opens]
I've been expecting you.
I know why you're here.
[Eve] But in the end
every death is just a new beginning.
You cannot win.
My demise
is only another step in the cycle.
You're going to kill me today.
Martha finds my body.
Just as I once found myself.
It turns her against you once and for all.
What are you waiting for?
[gun rattles quietly]
[trigger clicks]
This isn't right.
It didn't happen like this.
It... It never happened like this.
You have me killed.
Every time.
You will die.
I will die.
And everything that has grown out of us.
What have you done?
[Adam] Life is a labyrinth.
Some wander around until their death
in search of a way out of it.
But there is only one path,
and it leads ever deeper inside.
Only when one reaches the center
will one understand.
Death is incomprehensible.
But one can reconcile oneself with it.
All that we've done...
is ultimately forgotten.
We are responsible...
for this never-ending déjà vu.
And we're the ones
who have to end it.
We...
-are the mistake.
-[sobbing softly]
You and I.
[Eve gasping]
[handle creaks]
[door creaks]
[Adam] Both of our fates
are bound together in eternal damnation.
Across both worlds.
All is cause and effect.
Every pain tempts us to act,
forms our will.
Tannhaus lost everything
that ever meant anything to him
in the origin world.
His son, his daughter-in-law
and his granddaughter
died in a car accident.
They were forced off a bridge
and drowned in the river.
He could never let go of his pain.
Jonas and Martha...
must take his pain away.
So that he never looks for a way
to undo everything.
They must go to the origin world...
and prevent our two worlds...
from ever being created.
[both panting]
This is the moment
the passage was first opened in any world.
He wanted to travel back to a world
in which his family was still alive.
But instead, his own world was split.
And the knot was created.
We were created.
[Jonas sighs]
It'll be any time now
when a bridge will come.
Connecting all three worlds.
You're going to his world.
To get to the moment his suffering began,
we'll have to travel back.
Jonas...
The one in your world...
Was he different?
[hissing]
[machine ticking]
[loud hissing]
[crackling]
-[bolts of electricity crackle]
-[buzzing]
[rhythmic a cappella singing]
[tinkling sound]
It's beginning.
-[crackling and buzzing intensifies]
-[atmospheric female vocalizing]
[atmospheric vocalizing continues]
[Eve sobs]
-[crackling]
-[whirring]
[music intensifies]
[whirring loudens]
[music and sounds fade out]
[echoing] Martha?
[yells] Martha!
[echoing]
[silence]
[echoing] Jonas?
[yells] Jonas!
[echoing]
[silence]
Martha! [echoes]
[muffled footfalls echo]
[yells] Jonas!
[distorted sounds in the distance]
[crackling]
[door opens]
[Katharina] Martha?
Oh, there you are!
He looks so sad.
-Who looks so sad?
-The boy standing there.
[Katharina] There's no one there.
It's only the back of your closet.
[melancholy string music plays]
[key turns in lock]
Jonas.
Is everything okay?
What do you want in the basement?
What is it?
[Jonas] There's a girl standing there.
[Michael laughs] There's no girl there.
Come on,
let's go back to the others, okay?
[chuckles] Come on.
[both gasp
[serene string music plays]
[quiet rattling]
[ticking]
[quiet whirring]
[whirring intensifies]
[thunder rolls]
[clocks tick]
Why do you always have to bring it up?
Can't you just let it go for once?
I just thought you wanted the store.
-Not now, but eventually.
-You never listen.
No wonder Mom couldn't stand it here.
Your endless lecturing,
Big Bang, Big Crunch...
Has Sonja ever been asked
if she's interested?
In all these years
have you ever asked if I'm interested?
Or what I want?
[thunder rolls]
[rain patters]
It's raining outside.
Is that all you have to say to us?
Marek, come on.
You told me the world outside
is full of secrets.
And what we know is a drop
in an unending ocean, yeah?
At least you were right about that.
You may know everything about
Einstein-Rosen bridges and black holes,
but about me...
You know absolutely nothing about me.
[bells on door ring]
[door closes]
I... I thought you'd be here a bit longer.
He's going to cool off.
[ominous music plays]
-[thunder rolls]
-[bells on door ring]
[door closes]
[rock music plays on car radio]
Was that really necessary?
We could just as well have left tomorrow.
You're ashamed of him.
You have no idea who he is.
To have to grow up with that...
He lives in his head, in his big ideas.
Have you ever seen the shit he makes?
I can't understand
why people even watch stuff like that.
Moons, theories, stars,
galaxies, stupid universes...
But me? He never saw me.
[thunder rolls]
You can't choose your family.
Yeah.
But I chose you.
You chose me.
[buzzing]
[Sonja screams]
Look out!
[brakes screech]
-[baby cries]
-Shh.
Are you okay? Yeah?
[baby cries]
[Sonja] What are they doing there?
[Marek] Wait a second.
Are you both insane?
You can't just hang out here!
I almost ran you over!
[thunder rolls]
[baby cries]
Are you guys okay?
Do you need help?
The bridge isn't open.
What?
There's been an accident.
You think this is funny?
Go home, get inside.
[Jonas] What we know is a drop.
What we do not know is an ocean.
[Martha] Your father loves you.
He would do anything for you.
[baby crying]
What did you just say?
[Sonja] Marek?
Are they okay?
The bridge isn't open.
Come on. Let's go.
Marek!
What was that?
You were right.
We'll drive back tomorrow.
[bells jingle]
[door closes]
You returned?
The bridge isn't open.
Your son thinks he saw a pair of angels.
Don't make fun of me.
I don't know why, I...
I suddenly had this...
this feeling.
[tender music plays]
I'm glad that you're here.
I haven't even stripped the beds.
[both chuckle]
I'll bring the bags upstairs.
Thanks.
Would you like to hold her?
Take good care of Charlotte.
I'll help Marek.
Do you think it worked?
[thunder rolls]
In the light...
I saw you.
As a child.
You were looking in my direction,
as if we could see each other.
The closet?
That was you?
It wasn't a dream.
I wonder if anything of us will remain.
Or is that what we are?
A dream?
And we never really existed?
I don't know.
[melancholy music plays]
You and I are perfect for each other.
Never believe anything else.
["What a Wonderful World"
by Soap&amp;Skin plays]
♪ I see trees of green
Red roses too ♪
♪ I see them bloom
For me and you ♪
♪ And I think to myself ♪
♪ What a wonderful world ♪
♪ I see skies of blue ♪
♪ And clouds of white ♪
♪ The bright blessed day
Dark sacred night ♪
♪ And I think to myself ♪
♪ What a wonderful world ♪
♪ The colors of the rainbow ♪
♪ So pretty in the sky ♪
♪ Are also on the faces ♪
♪ Of people going by ♪
♪ I see friends shaking hands ♪
♪ Saying "How do you do" ♪
♪ They're really saying ♪
♪ "I love you" ♪
♪ I hear babies cry ♪
♪ I watch them grow ♪
♪ They'll learn much more ♪
♪ Than I'll ever know ♪
♪ And I think to myself ♪
♪ What a wonderful world ♪
[song fades out]
[thunder rolls]
[pop music plays]
-[Hannah] Should we reheat the lasagna?
-[Regina] Yeah.
[Benni] Let me help you.
-[Peter] Shall I open another bottle?
-[Hannah] Absolutely!
[Wöller] Hey, do I get some?
-[Katharina] And now, a toast to Regina.
-[Wöller] Yes.
-To you.
-[Wöller] To you.
And thank you for the invitation.
-Of course.
-[Hannah] Here's to you.
Your eye. It looks way better.
[Katharina] You never actually told us
what happened.
-[Benni] You never told me either.
-Tell us.
-But promise not to tell anyone.
-[Peter] Tell us!
[hesitantly] Last summer...
[thunder rolls suddenly]
Shit. That scared me.
[everyone laughs]
-[Wöller] Everything okay?
-Yeah.
-[Benni] Is this the apocalypse?
-[laughter]
-I'll light some candles.
-Does anyone have a lighter?
[Regina] Yeah, here.
[Katharina] Hannah?
Are you okay?
[Wöller] Hey? Everything okay?
I'm not sure.
I think I just had déjà vu or something.
This is going to sound
utterly absurd, but...
What happened now, last night...
that's what I dreamed about.
The light was flickering,
loud thunder outside,
and then the place was totally dark.
And somehow...
the world had ended.
The world had ended?
[Hannah] Yeah, I don't know.
It was just dark
and it was never light again.
And the weird thing is...
that it felt really good.
For everything to be over.
Like suddenly being free of everything.
No wants.
No needs.
Unending darkness.
No yesterday.
No today.
No tomorrow.
Nothing.
You really need to get that analyzed.
[chuckling softly]
I'm sure it's just the hormones.
If the world were to end today
and you only had one wish,
what would you wish for?
[thunder rolls]
A world without Winden.
-Let's drink to that.
-Yes.
-A world without Winden.
-[everyone] A world without Winden.
[Hannah] Ah.
[Peter] Looks like Winden doesn't want
to just disappear.
[Wöller] Maybe it's for the best.
[Katharina]
Have you chosen a name?
I don't know.
I always thought "Jonas" was a good name.
["Irgendwie, irgendwo, irgendwann"
by Nena plays]
♪ Im Sturz durch Raum und Zeit ♪
♪ Richtung Unendlichkeit ♪
♪ Fliegen Motten in das Licht ♪
♪ Genau wie du und ich ♪
♪ Irgendwie fängt irgendwann ♪
♪ Irgendwo die Zukunft an ♪
♪ Ich warte nicht mehr lang ♪
♪ Liebe wird aus Mut gemacht ♪
♪ Denk nicht lange nach ♪
♪ Wir fahren auf Feuerrädern
Richtung Zukunft durch die Nacht ♪
♪ Gib mir die Hand
Ich bau dir ein Schloss aus Sand ♪
♪ Irgendwie, irgendwo, irgendwann ♪
♪ Die Zeit ist reif
Für ein bisschen Zärtlichkeit ♪
♪ Irgendwie, irgendwo, irgendwann ♪
♪ Im Sturz durch Zeit und Raum ♪
♪ Erwacht aus einem Traum ♪
♪ Nur ein kurzer Augenblick ♪
♪ Dann kehrt die Nacht zurück ♪
♪ Irgendwie fängt irgendwann
Irgendwo die Zukunft an ♪
♪ Ich warte nicht mehr lang ♪
♪ Liebe wird aus Mut gemacht ♪
♪ Denk nicht lange nach ♪
♪ Wir fahren auf Feuerrädern
Richtung Zukunft durch die Nacht ♪
♪ Gib mir die Hand
Ich bau dir ein Schloss aus Sand ♪
♪ Irgendwie, irgendwo, irgendwann ♪
♪ Die Zeit ist reif
Für ein bisschen Zärtlichkeit ♪
♪ Irgendwie, irgendwo, irgendwann ♪
♪ Gib mir die Hand
Ich bau dir ein Schloss aus Sand ♪
♪ Irgendwie, irgendwo, irgendwann ♪
♪ Die Zeit ist reif
Für ein bisschen Zärtlichkeit ♪
♪ Irgendwie, irgendwo, irgendwann ♪
♪ Gib mir die Hand
Ich bau dir ein Schloss aus Sand ♪
♪ Irgendwie, irgendwo, irgendwann ♪
♪ Die Zeit ist reif
Für ein bisschen Zärtlichkeit ♪
♪ Irgendwie, irgendwo, irgendwann ♪