[insects buzzing]
[gasping, panting]
[dissonant violin music]
[groans]
[coughing]
[man 1] Hey!
[man 2] What happened to him?
Where did you get that?
What are you doing here?
I just want to return.
Think he's a refugee?
Well, you look like you've been
through some real shit to me.
- You could probably use some food.
- [man 2] Mm-hmm.
- I'm all right.
- [man 2] Nonsense.
Erna loves stray dogs. Come on.
[children chattering]
[horse neighs]
[bell tolling]
Agnes, go get Erna.
Now.
[man 1] Where were you stationed?
Eastern front.
- Labor camp.
- [man 2] They aren't human over there.
That's a war we should've won.
[Erna] Do you have a place to sleep?
Tell your brother
to get the small room ready.
But only for a few days.
Till you're back on your feet.
This is going to sound strange.
But what year is it, please?
They really worked you hard out there,
didn't they?
It's 1921.
[oppressive music]
[quietly] 1921...
["Goodbye" by Apparat plays]
♪ Fold out your hands ♪
♪ Give me a sign ♪
♪ Put down your lies ♪
♪ Lay down next to me ♪
♪ Don't listen when I scream ♪
♪ Bury your doubts and fall asleep ♪
♪ For neither ever ♪
♪ Nor never ♪
♪ Goodbye ♪
♪ Neither ever ♪
♪ Nor never ♪
♪ Goodbye ♪
♪ Neither ever ♪
♪ Nor never ♪
♪ Goodbye ♪
JUNE 24, 2020
THREE DAYS UNTIL THE APOCALYPSE
[heavy breathing]
You and I are perfect for each other.
Never believe anything else.
[gasps, panting]
[crying]
- [knocking at door]
- Yeah.
[door opens]
Mrs. Doppler called in sick.
She's not coming in.
What's wrong with her?
Don't think she said.
Just a minute.
You're Mr. Wöller, right?
Yeah.
Then we're in for a fun time.
- Do you have a car?
- Mm-hmm.
Wonderful.
[quiet, dismal music]
[cell phone rings]
CALL FROM
HANNAH KAHNWALD
Where did you get this?
- Who is that?
- It's complicated.
Mom, why do you have that?
Do you want me to make some breakfast?
What do we do with Mom?
I have no idea.
[doorbell rings]
[extended ringing]
[door opens]
[Magnus] What are you doing here?
- Martha.
- Franziska.
- [Magnus] What do you want!
- [Franziska] We need to talk.
What?
If you think I'll say sorry,
you can forget it.
You fucked up,
but I shouldn't have said what I said.
We're even.
Am I the babysitter
while you make out in here?
Why did you bring her along?
Because our parents
haven't been home for two days.
I can't just leave her there alone.
Why is everyone acting so weird?
[quiet, suspenseful music]
- I want to know what's going on.
- You're going to go into the caves?
You don't have to come.
[gasps, panting]
[man] You slept for almost 24 hours.
[breathing heavily]
Who are you?
Everyone says
that Erna can't turn away a stray dog.
I'm not right here.
This isn't right here.
[young Noah] Hmm.
- At first I pictured you differently.
- [spooky music]
What's that supposed to mean?
Why did you say that?
[quietly] "Sic mundus creatus est."
[suspenseful music]
[guard] Can I help you?
Hi. I'm here looking for someone.
She used to work here,
a while back.
Tiedemann. Claudia Tiedemann.
She used to run the facility.
You know where I can find her?
Here there's only one Tiedemann.
Aleksander Tiedemann, the guy in charge.
Aleksander Tiedemann?
[Clausen] So that was why you wouldn't let
Ulrich Nielsen onto the property?
After Fukushima,
safety standards were raised.
I can't just let people walk in here.
His assumption that his son could be here
somewhere was completely unfounded.
Do you know about the door in the cave?
Installed in the '80s.
It was already welded shut back then
as a security measure.
- It's still shut to this day.
- You know what I find a bit strange?
Everyone who was born here stays.
That's quite unusual
for a town of this size.
Why is that?
What do you think?
The nuclear plant has always provided.
There's work.
Prosperity, security.
Although that's likely to change now.
When we close the facility.
- [Clausen] You're not from around here.
- [Aleksander] No. Why?
In 1986 you came to Winden.
That's the same time the kid disappeared.
Mads Nielsen.
Ulrich Nielsen's brother.
No. I came later.
A few weeks.
How's that relevant?
I guess it isn't.
One more thing.
What made you take your wife's last name?
Why do you ask?
Pretty unusual, especially back then.
The Tiedemanns
shaped this city, Inspector.
Especially Regina's mother.
Regina has no siblings.
- We wanted to keep the name alive.
- What is your real name?
Köhler.
Aleksander Köhler.
Who's next on the list?
Wöller.
[clears throat]
[Wöller] Hannah Kahnwald.
[older Jonas] Why do you have
a gun and someone else's passport?
They're for insurance.
Insurance?
There's someone very interested
in keeping those things hidden.
So it's blackmail?
Who are you?
Who am I?
[exhales]
Who are you?
[knocking at door]
[Charlotte] Hannah?
[knocking]
I'm sorry,
but we have to tell someone.
[door opens]
- Thanks for getting here so soon.
- [door closes]
I know none of this
makes any sense, but...
this is Jonas. He...
He's much older, but he knows
where my Jonas is and where Ulrich is.
[Charlotte] You're the man Regina
was talking about, from the hotel.
Who are these people?
This man here, the priest.
Do you know who he is?
That is Noah.
Are you sure?
What do you know about him?
- He's one of them.
- What is this?
[Charlotte] One of whom?
Of Sic Mundus.
The travelers.
The travelers?
Sic mundus creatus est?
What are you talking about?
You knew all this?
The time travel.
There's something
I think you both should see.
[oppressive music]
Okay.
[quiet, suspenseful music]
You want to go in there?
After four children disappeared?
[sighs]
You stay by me.
I'll make sure we're safe. Okay?
WINDEN MUNICIPAL LIBRARY
[clears throat] Excuse me.
I'd like to learn about...
the town's history.
Where can I find articles and documents
of the last 30 years or so?
That's all digital now.
And where's that?
Excuse me.
Where is the keyboard?
There isn't one.
SEARCH
CLAUDIA TIEDEMANN FIRST WOMAN
TO HEAD A NUCLEAR POWER PLANT
[gloomy music]
NUCLEAR POWER PLANT BOSS
DISAPPEARS WITHOUT A TRACE
[Clausen] Did you inform her
about the appointment?
[Wöller] Yes.
APPOINTMENTS
What do you know about Hannah Kahnwald?
Her husband committed suicide.
Hanged himself.
No one here understood
why she married him.
She was so pretty.
She could've had any man she wanted.
There were rumors that she had an affair
with Ulrich Nielsen.
Did Mrs. Nielsen know about that?
Can I ask you something?
Ask away.
How'd you get this position?
Special task force.
Did you volunteer for this?
Oh, yes.
I did.
[sad piano music]
IS THIS MAN A CHILD MURDERER?
She told me and Tronte what we have to do.
Claudia Tiedemann.
She knew exactly at what time
things would happen.
It didn't make any sense, yet it was
the only way anything made sense.
You knew about all of this?
Michael, Mikkel, Ulrich?
About everything?
This here... She gave us this book.
It's all in there, about all the children.
Who disappeared when.
Things about time travel.
Symbols and tables
we can't quite understand.
- The last few pages were ripped out.
- Does Katharina know this?
Well, you have to tell her.
Okay.
But let me do it.
REGINA AND ALEKSANDER TIEDEMANN
TO WED
WE'RE GETTING MARRIED
REGINA TIEDEMANN - ALEKSANDER TIEDEMANN
WALDHOTEL WINDEN OPENS
WALDHOTEL WINDEN CLOSES
NO TRACE OF MADS NIELSEN
CHIEF INSPECTOR EGON TIEDEMANN...
FORMER WINDEN CHIEF INSPECTOR
FOUND DEAD IN HIS APARTMENT
ON JUNE 26, 1987
Excuse me.
Can I print off these things?
[quiet rumbling]
[breathing heavily]
[Martha] Sometimes I dream about him.
Jonas.
It all feels so real.
As if he was still alive.
How could it feel that way
if he's really dead?
It's possible he knew something,
before he disappeared.
What are you saying?
What if he saw something
that he shouldn't have seen?
[Magnus] The door has to be
in this direction.
[blows]
[Katharina] Where are we going, Charlotte?
Tell me where we're going.
Damn it, Charlotte!
Where are you taking me?
It's easier to understand
if you just see it.
What have you found?
You found them.
We found them.
Both.
And they're not dead. They're still alive.
But they're not here.
They're not here?
But they're alive... What does that mean?
It's better if you see it
with your own eyes.
[suspenseful music]
[metal door creaks]
Why is she here?
What's all this about, Charlotte?
You said you thought Mikkel
went into the cave. You were right.
Mikkel was in the cave
and Ulrich was looking for him in there.
But they found something in the tunnels.
A kind of tear... in the fabric of time.
You can't be serious.
What is all this shit?
- Where are Mikkel and Ulrich?
- [Hannah] It's true.
Stay out of this!
Nobody asked you for your opinion.
Charlotte is right.
Uh-huh. Another one?
And who are you? Her new boy toy?
I'm Jonas.
Her son.
And your grandson.
[scoffs, laughs]
[mysterious music]
[low rumbling]
She says it's shaking.
[rock crumbles]
- What is it?
- We're not alone.
Go. Go, go!
[quietly] turn off the lights.
[footsteps approaching]
[tension-filled music]
- Bartosz?
- [groans]
What are you doing here?
- [Bartosz] What the fuck?
- [Magnus grunting]
[Martha] Why are you here?
[Katharina] My husband is trapped
in the '50s, and my son in the '80s.
You chose to leave him there
because Mikkel is your father. That right?
Yes.
I can't take this seriously.
You're buying into all this bullshit?
What's in it for you? Huh?
Do you want money?
Can you speak with the dead? Yeah?
Katharina.
I was there.
I saw him there.
Mikkel.
[tense music]
You've all lost your minds.
[metal door creaks]
[dismal music]
[suspenseful music]
No.
[grunting angrily]
[strained shouting]
[muffled, distorted chatter]
- [high-pitched ringing]
- [indiscernible muffled shouts]
[muffled audio]
[muffled audio] Fuck you, Magnus! [grunts]
[Magnus] I swear to God, if you have
anything to do with this shit...
[Bartosz] Fuck you.
- Stop it.
- Tell us what the fuck you're doing here.
[Bartosz groans]
Come here.
[low rumbling]
What is this thing?
- What is that?
- Don't touch it. It doesn't concern you.
[Magnus] If you have anything to do
with Mikkel or my dad...
I'm going to kill you.
What should we do now?
[Martha] We're taking it.
And him?
We leave him here.
Maybe that'll change his mind.
[Bartosz] Fuck.
You can't do this.
Martha! You can't do this!
Hey. Shit. Hey!
Magnus! Stop!
Magnus!
Magnus! [whimpers]
[groans softly]
[Clausen] What's your take on all of this?
We have a man-eating cave.
A nuclear plant
run by a man obviously hiding something.
An inspector
who seems to be hiding herself.
And we have a town full of people
who cheat and betray each other.
And they're obviously very invested
in hiding what's happening here.
So, Mr. Wöller...
what do you make of all this?
Uh... I'm not sure.
Tell me, what happened to your eye?
Okay.
But...
you can't tell anyone else.
Uh, so...
- last summer...
- Watch it!
[tires squeal]
- [car alert beeping]
- [panting]
Interesting.
[grave music]
TEACHER'S LOUNGE
PLEASE KNOCK
[mysterious music]
Okay.
Eighty-six.
Six-b.
Six-b, 6b, 6b.
Six-b, 6b.
CLASS REGISTER
[dismal music]
[gasps and weeps]
[young Noah] It's not open yet.
It'll be another 32 years before it opens.
So you know about this?
They're waiting for you.
Who's waiting for me?
Sic Mundus.
You want to get home, don't you?
That's what they say, anyway.
Who are "they"?
[quietly] The travelers.
What now?
It doesn't matter.
Everything is going to happen
the way it always has.
Then why are you here?
- He said there'd be a loophole.
- [Charlotte] Who?
- Adam.
- Who's Adam?
The leader of Sic Mundus.
[Charlotte] The people in the photo?
The travelers?
Yeah.
He wants the last cycle to begin.
In three days.
I have to stop it.
That's why I'm here.
She tried to do it.
But in the end,
she became exactly what she was fighting.
[metal door closes]
[dismal music]
[bird squawks, flaps]
[ominous music]
[door creaks]
[door closes]
Why did you bring me here?
You're one of them.
A traveler.
Not yet.
- But soon I will be.
- [door opens]
[threatening music]
It must feel strange
to see me here as well.
Especially after our last encounter.
But you've already made my acquaintance.
You'll get answers in time.
[eerie music]
[rumbling]
["The World Retreats" by David O'Dowda]
♪ Hold by confide among the stars ♪
♪ We could be the lucky ones ♪
♪ If we could only levitate ♪
♪ Fly low, dear ♪
♪ Dance beneath the trees ♪
♪ If only we had oxygen ♪
♪ Then we'd begin to breathe ♪
[soft piano music]
♪ And we can watch ♪
♪ While the beauty takes its toll ♪
♪ And we can stop ♪
♪ While the world retreats ♪
♪ Fly low, dear ♪
♪ Fix yourself a life ♪
♪ We could be the wealthy ones ♪
♪ If we could only emigrate ♪
♪ These walls get closer by the night ♪
♪ Everything is delicate ♪
♪ And everything in flight ♪
[sedate piano music, synthesizers]
[song fades]
[bubbling and whirring]
[gun cocking]
What are you doing here?
What's in there?
You knew it was in there!
You...
have lied to us the whole time.
What is that?
[yells] What is that?
They say it is a part of God.
But in reality it's a part of the devil.
[electronic bubbling]
The prophecy.
How did it arise?
The book, who wrote it?
Whoever it was who wrote it...
had already seen the past and future.
What will happen to him next?
Adam will send him on his way,
the path that's been determined.
So that the last cycle may begin.
[ominous music]
[Adam] You must have a lot of questions.
Traveling leaves its marks on all of us.
The human body isn't equipped for it
in perpetuity.
What is this here?
Shall we begin?
I'm not here to begin anything.
I want this to end, finally. All of it!
Don't worry, it will come to an end.
That can't be avoided.
Your end,
my end.
On closer inspection, it's everyone's end.
Who are you?
Can't you see it already?
[ominous music]
This isn't real.
I am you.
Every stone is back where it belongs,
everyone at their destination.
All that's needed now is a push.
[intense music playing]