Every journey has a beginning.
But yours has no end.
It goes on forever and ever.
I'm here to finally make your journey
come to an end.
This is impossible.
You're dead.
I had you killed.
You still have no idea
how this game is played.
You want to destroy the knot,
but every step you take keeps it intact.
This can't be.
I killed it.
I killed Martha
and I killed the origin.
Your world and Eva's world.
They both should never have existed.
You thought the origin
lies in the connection
between both worlds.
But in reality it lies
outside both of those worlds.
Our thinking is shaped by dualities.
Black, white.
Light and shadow.
Your world and Eva's world.
But that's wrong.
Nothing is complete
without a third dimension.
The triquetra.
There is...
a third world?
The world that gave birth to the knot.
Where everything originates.
Where a single mistake was made.
Tannhaus... in the origin world...
like you, he lost someone.
And like you, he tried
to bring someone back from the dead.
But instead
he split and destroyed his world.
Thus creating both our worlds.
But there's a way to destroy the knot.
By preventing the invention of travel
through space and time
in the origin world in the first place.
PARADISE
I'd have liked to have spared you
all of that.
But your path had to remain unchanged.
Every step had to be taken
exactly as before.
Up until this moment.
This...
Has it happened before?
You trying to destroy the origin,
that has happened
an infinite number of times.
But this here,
you and I,
is happening for the first time.
It's time you understand
how everything is really connected.
Everything you have done,
everything Eva has done,
has upheld the knot for eternity,
in both worlds.
You create yourself forever anew.
And so does she.
They have to die.
They must all die,
so that they can be reborn.
You carry both worlds inside you.
What?
Your son.
He's the origin.
He gives everyone their lives
alternately in each of the two worlds.
He's waited a long time for you.
And he'll do so time and time again.
You want to destroy your son,
and the knot along with him.
Eva wants him to live,
and must therefore uphold the knot.
She can't help it.
Time and again she'll do all she can do
to ensure he lives.
Everything you and Eva have done
in this knot,
and will do over and over again,
you did out of love.
And yet you have brought nothing
but pain and suffering.
If you want Jonas to live,
if you want all of them to live,
then we must do what has always been done.
You too.
Both of you have done
unimaginable things on your journey.
Because you can't let go
of your deepest desires.
Yours ends here and now.
What's that mean?
You have accomplished
what you were sent to this world for.
We've accomplished nothing.
She said we had to stop the apocalypse.
- The barrels in the power plant...
- You'll understand it all
when it's time for you to understand.
You have been trying to escape
what you'll become.
But that's impossible.
In the end, you will always stand
face to face with yourselves.
Who are you?
I'm sorry.
Your two worlds should have never existed.
You and Eva,
the two of you should have never existed.
How do you know all this?
How do you know about the origin world?
I've spent 33 years looking for answers
in your world and in hers.
I've tried to put together
the pieces of the puzzle.
To understand how everything can be reborn
from the same family tree
over and over again.
Until I realized
that we're not all part of the knot.
Both worlds are a cancer
that must have grown from something else.
If you remove it,
you destroy all that was born of it,
but you keep everything alive
that already existed in the origin world.
All these years, I thought
that she was my daughter.
For a long time,
I wished you were the father.
But it's better this way.
She isn't part of the knot.
She will live.
But just like you and Eva,
I had to preserve everything
in order to become what I am today.
You know what you have to do.
Do it quickly.
Don't let her suffer.
It's no life that's she's living.
It has to happen,
so I can move heaven and earth
to prevent it.
Just like you,
I've brought pain and suffering to others,
again and again...
so that my path
could lead me here to you today.
Everything I did
I did for Regina.
All these years, I've been searching
in both worlds for a way for her to live.
A way to break the chain
of cause and effect.
Both in your world
and in Eva's world,
I've tried to understand
how everything is connected.
Really connected.
Until I finally understood
that our two worlds were borne of another.
That Regina will always die
in both worlds.
That she can only live in the world
from which everything was created;
the origin world.
I lied to you...
and to Eva.
But the knot had to be upheld.
I had to ensure
that you both stayed in the dark.
That everyone in this knot
stayed in the dark.
First, everything had to happen
the way it always has...
in your world and in her world.
Every step in this labyrinth
had to be taken as it had been before.
An infinite chain of cause and effect
that leads us all, in both worlds,
to our same fate over and over again.
Excuse me.
Did someone just pass by here?
An old man?
We have no free will to act
in either world.
We will forever do
what we have always done before.
Hey.
You're Helge Doppler, aren't you?
Helge.
No fate in one world
is better than the other.
What's today's date?
November 8.
Which year?
1986.
1986...
I can change it, you know?
I can change the past.
And the future.
Help!
If you don't exist,
none of this will happen.
No!
What's in there? Is he in there?
- What did you do to him?
- Let go!
As long as the knot exists,
in both worlds we are damned
to feel and cause
every bit of suffering anew.
There is no difference
between the two worlds.
Things may not happen in the same way,
or at the same time.
But they do happen.
No one in this knot
can escape their fate.
It was you.
Every piece of the puzzle
repeatedly finds its place.
Just like you, I moved the pieces
around the chessboard,
and had to look on as everything happened
over and over again.
But I finally know how to untie the knot.
I know where the loophole is
that you've searched for all this time.
Time.
During the apocalypse,
it stood still for a fraction of a second.
And that threw everything out of balance.
But when time stands still,
the chain of cause and effect
is also momentarily broken.
One can...
change things.
Eva knows that.
She uses the loophole in your world
to send her younger self off
in one direction or another,
in order to preserve the cycle.
And I used it to send myself
in another direction, too.
To be here today.
You must use it
to send Jonas on a different path...
in order to break the cycle
once and for all.
Jonas and Martha are to blame
for everything happening again and again.
You must send them to the origin world,
so they can finally end all this.
I promise you.
I'll make this right.
Why are you still here?
She's dead!
What more do you want from me?
I can explain it. Everything.
But first we have to get out of here.
What's going on?
What is that?
That is our last hope.
How did you do that?
What time is this?
The question isn't "what time?"
But "which world?"
What's that supposed to mean?
There is a way
that you can avoid becoming me,
a way all of this never needs to happen.
But for it to work, you have to trust me.
You don't have much time left.
The other Martha,
you must save her.
The other Martha?
All these years I thought
that I alone have to change it.
But it is just as much her fault.
You are two parts of a whole.
Only together can you return
to the origin world.
What we know is a drop.
What we don't know...
is an ocean.
What does that mean?
Tick, tock.
Today is the day of the apocalypse...
in her world.
The loophole...
it also exists here.
For one moment, time will stand still.
You must get Martha...
before Magnus and Franziska get her.
And before everything happens again.
The two of you are our last hope.
Adam will send Jonas on his way.
He and Martha, they will stop
all this from ever happening.
Dad.
Tell him I'm sorry.
If everything goes right...
then Regina will live.
Martha?
What's going on?
You have to come with us.
Come where?
This can't be.
You're alive.
You look like her.
You don't know who I am.
What time are we in?
When are we?
Why are we here?
Today is June 21, 1986.
The day our two worlds were created.
Not here, but in his world.
Tannhaus, the clockmaker, will open
the passage for the first time today.
What?
We don't have much time.
We have to stop it from ever happening.
Wait!
What does that mean?
Where are we going?
We're bringing someone back from the dead.
What's that supposed to mean?
It's a bit complicated to explain.
We have to get them before they die.
What are you trying to do?
You and I.
We're the reason
everything happens the way it does.
Why it happens again and again.
Because you can't let go of what you want.
And I can't let go of what I want.
But we are the mistake.
The glitch in the matrix.
You want them to never exist.
Your world and mine.
That we never exist.
I was expecting you.
I know why you're here.
But in the end...
every death
is just a new beginning.
You can't win.
My dying
is only another step in the cycle.
You're going to kill me today.
Martha will find me.
Just as I once found myself.
It will turn her against you
once and for all.
What are you waiting for?
This isn't right.
It didn't happen like this.
It...
it never happened this way.
You killed me.
Every time.
You will die.
I will die.
And everything that has grown out of us.
What have you done?
Life is a labyrinth.
Some wander around inside it
until their death,
in search of a way out.
But there is only one path,
and it leads ever deeper inside.
Only when one reaches the center
will one understand.
Death is incomprehensible.
But one can reconcile oneself with it.
All that we have done
will ultimately be forgotten.
We are responsible
for this never-ending déjà vu.
And we're the ones
who have to end it.
We...
are the mistake.
You and I.
Both our fates are bound together
in eternal damnation.
Across both worlds.
Everything is cause and effect.
Every pain entices us to act,
shapes our will.
Tannhaus lost all that ever meant
anything to him in the origin world.
His son, daughter-in-law,
and granddaughter died in a car accident.
They were forced off a bridge,
and drowned in the river.
He never forgot that pain.
Jonas and Martha,
they have to take his pain away from him,
so that he never looks
for a way to undo everything.
They must go to the origin world
and prevent our two worlds
from ever being created.
This is the moment
the passage was first opened.
Tannhaus tried to travel back to a world
in which his family was still alive.
But instead, he split his own world.
He created the knot.
Created us.
For a brief moment,
there will be a bridge...
between all three worlds.
You want to go to his world?
We have to travel back to the moment
when his pain began.
Jonas...
the one in your world...
was he different?
It's starting.
Martha?
Jonas?
Jonas!
Martha?
Oh, there you are.
He looks sad.
Who looks sad?
The boy standing there.
But there's no one there.
It's only the back of your closet.
Jonas?
Is everything okay?
What do you want in the basement?
What is it?
There's a girl standing there.
There's no girl there.
Come on.
Let's go back to the others, okay?
Do you always have to bring that up?
Can't you let it be for once?
I thought you wanted the store.
- Maybe not now, but sometime later.
- You never listen!
No wonder Mom couldn't take it anymore.
Your endless lecturing,
Big Bang, Big Crunch...
Have you ever asked Sonja
if she's interested?
In all these years,
have you ever asked if I'm interested?
Or what I really want?
It's raining outside.
Is that all you have to say?
Marek, come on.
You told me
the world outside was full of secrets,
and what we know
is a drop in an infinite ocean.
At least you were right about that.
You may know everything about
Einstein-Rosen bridges and black holes,
but about me...
You know absolutely nothing about me.
I... I thought you'd stay a few more days.
He'll cool off.
Was that really necessary?
We could just as well have left tomorrow.
You're ashamed of him.
You have no idea what he's like.
Growing up that way.
He lives in his head, in his big ideas.
Have you ever seen what he does?
I don't get why anyone watches that stuff.
He only ever looked up.
Stars, galaxies, stupid universes,
but me...
He never saw me.
You can't choose your family.
Yeah.
I chose you.
Yes.
You chose me.
Look out!
Are you okay?
Yeah?
- What are they doing there?
- I'll go and see.
What the hell is this?
You can't just stand around here!
I almost ran you over!
Is everything okay?
Do you need help?
The bridge is closed.
What?
There was an accident.
Do you think this is funny?
Go on, go home.
What we know is a drop.
What we don't know is an ocean.
Your father loves you.
He would do anything for you.
What did you just say?
Marek?
Is everything okay?
The bridge is closed.
Come on. Let's go.
Marek!
What was that?
You were right.
We should leave tomorrow.
You're back?
The bridge is closed.
- Your son thinks he met a pair of angels.
- Don't mock me.
I don't know why...
but I suddenly just got this...
this feeling.
It's nice that you're back.
I haven't even stripped the beds yet.
I'll take the bags upstairs.
Thanks.
Want to hold her?
Charlotte already missed you too.
I'll help Marek.
Do you think it worked?
Inside the light...
I saw you.
As a child.
You were looking towards me...
as if you could see me too.
In the closet?
That was you?
It wasn't a dream.
Do you think anything of us will remain?
Or is that what we are?
A dream?
And we never really existed?
I don't know.
We're a perfect match.
Never believe anything else.
- Shall we reheat the lasagna?
- Yes.
- Let me help you.
- I'll open another bottle, okay?
- Definitely.
- Yes.
Can I get a sip too?
- And now we'll toast to Regina.
- Yes.
- Here's to you.
And thanks for the invite.
- You're welcome.
- To you.
Your eye.
- It looks much better.
- You never actually told us what happened.
- You never told me either.
- Come on, tell us.
But you have to promise
not to tell anyone else.
Last summer...
Shit. That scared me.
- Everything all right?
- Yes.
Is this the apocalypse?
- I'll light some candles.
- I'll help you.
Got a light?
Right, then.
- Here.
- Hannah?
Is everything okay?
Hey, everything okay?
I'm not sure.
I think I had déjà vu or something.
This is going to sound
completely absurd, but...
this is exactly
what I dreamt last night.
The light was flickering.
There was a loud bang.
And then suddenly everything was dark.
And somehow...
the world had ended.
The world had ended?
Yeah, I don't know.
It was just dark,
and it never became light again.
I had this peculiar feeling...
that it was a good thing...
for everything to be over.
Like suddenly being free of everything.
No wanting.
No having to.
Infinite darkness.
No yesterday.
No today.
No tomorrow.
Nothing.
You really need to get that looked into.
Maybe it's the hormones.
If the world were to end today,
and you had one wish,
what would you wish for?
A world without Winden.
Let's drink to that.
Yes.
- A world without Winden.
Looks like Winden doesn't want
to just disappear.
Maybe that's for the best.
Do you already have a name?
I don't know.
I think Jonas is a beautiful name.
Subtitle translation by Nathan Fritz