Where did it all begin?
Where did things begin?
In the past?
In the future?
Who can say where it began?
Welcome to the future.
I want all this sick shit to stop!
Will we ever be capable of knowing
the origin of all things?
Or is there still an origin before that?
And before that?
Do beginning and end even exist?
Or is it
all connected in an endless loop,
and are "beginning" and "end"
just different words
for one and the same moment?
Mikkel?
Mikkel!
Somehow, sometime
The future starts somewhere
I won't wait much longer now
Love is created through bravery
So don't think about it twice
We ride on fiery wheels
Towards the future through the night
Boo!
Good morning.
Good morning, sleepyhead.
So?
- What are your plans?
- I'm off to the lake with the others.
It's supposed to storm later, you know?
- Morning.
Don't forget
Katharina and Ulrich's party today.
- Don't be back so late again, okay?
- Yeah.
Sure you don't want to come?
Anyone want coffee?
Fuck.
Right. I've got to go.
You okay, Dad?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Everything's all right.
I just had déjà vu...
Okay. See you later.
Don't you think it'd be good
if you got out?
Won't you at least try?
For me.
I still have to finish my picture.
JUNE 20, 2019
THE DAY BEFORE
MICHAEL COMMITS SUICIDE
What's up?
I've got so much to do today.
I'm getting my period
and haven't shaved in ages.
- I'm sorry.
- I don't care.
- Sorry. I can't.
- You can.
- Ulrich, I can't.
- Couldn't you guys knock for once?
I think I'm sick.
I'm covered in red spots.
Maybe I have dengue fever?
Come here.
Shit!
You've got rubella.
You had to pick
today of all days for this?
Come on, we're going to the doctor's.
MURDER IN MARBURG UNSOLVED
33 YEARS LATER
SEARCH FOR TWO FUGITIVE PERPS
STILL ON
Will you come by later?
- This afternoon, to the hotel for lunch.
- Yes, of course.
Is everything all right?
Yes.
Are you sure?
Till later then.
Hey!
Where are the kids?
I was at the nursing home.
Shall we just go on like this?
That you won't believe anything I say?
Say something!
Maybe this is why all this happened.
Because I get nothing from you. Nothing.
It's as if you're dead inside.
About tonight...
I think it's best
if I go to the Nielsens' alone.
Do you know
about the lady who drowned here?
Stop it!
When the water is clear
you can see her dress down there.
And sometimes you feel her hands
on your feet while swimming.
But that's not the worst thing.
The worst thing is, when she's hungry.
Then she drags people down to her.
Asshole!
Ha-ha, real funny.
You coming tonight?
I think so.
I sometimes wonder
if my parents are really happy together.
Or if people just make do
with what they have.
Are your parents happy?
No idea.
What's that?
Looks pretty old.
That's Saint Christopher.
The patron saint of travelers.
Don't ask.
Hey, Jonas.
Weren't you guys going to the lake?
Martha and Magnus left long ago.
Ultimate fist bump?
Don't touch that pestilent boy.
He has rubella.
Where's your bike?
Should we give you a ride?
See you tonight then.
I know one person who'd be really glad
if you came, and it's not Magnus.
- Ulrich!
- Why?
It's no secret Martha's nuts about him.
Stop it!
Come on, get in.
We'll drop you off at the lake.
No, it's okay. Really.
- All right.
- Okay.
Then see you later, Romeo.
Gosh.
Magnus?
You weren't moving and I...
I... I thought you were dead.
He said there was a dead body there.
Still plenty alive.
Cool.
ARIADNE
A STAGE PLAY
Something up?
I was...
I was just thinking...
Wouldn't you sometimes like to know
what happens next?
You mean in the future?
Yes, or...
maybe just in the next five minutes.
I...
sometimes get this feeling
that something is about to happen.
You know?
Attack!
Fuck!
What's up?
I've got to go.
Where?
We gave Grandma Ines
a tablet for her birthday.
- I'm supposed to show her how it works.
- Okay.
Then...
see you later.
Jonas?
Why do you have a raincoat?
Because it's supposed to rain later.
Well, then...
Weren't you leaving?
Everything okay?
I thought I still had time.
Why do people say that anyway?
"To have time."
How can you have time
when it clearly has you?
Has something happened?
You're different somehow.
I wanted to tell you something.
I've wanted to for a long time.
I think we're a perfect match.
Never think anything else.
I've got to go now.
- Hi.
- Hello.
Hey.
Did Captain Nielsen make you work too?
All the best on your wedding anniversary.
Crazy, isn't it? It's been 25 years.
Thanks for the glasses, Hannah.
No problem at all.
Well, who would have thought that?
25 years.
- I need to pee.
- Just go on the tree there.
Can he use your bathroom?
Hannah?
Hello?
- Right, then go in the woods.
- No, sure. Nonsense.
It's just across from the front door.
I just had déjà vu or something.
- Mikkel has gotten big.
- He eats like an ogre.
- He got that from his mother.
- Hey, now!
Want more?
- See you.
- Till tomorrow.
Martha...
Sorry I can't come over later, but...
we've got a party,
for my mother and the hotel...
I just couldn't get out of it.
I just wanted to tell you that.
No biggie.
And I...
I really like...
your hair that way.
I mean, you look good.
With that hair.
Shit. You know what I mean.
Well...
See you tomorrow.
Bye.
MURDER IN MARBURG UNSOLVED
33 YEARS LATER
Wöller, it's me.
I need you to find something out for me.
Confidentially.
Give me your hand
I'll build a castle out of sand for you
Somehow, somewhere, somewhen
The time has come
For some tenderness tonight
Somehow, somewhere, somewhen
- Hello, Martha.
- Hi.
Hi.
Glad you made it.
Want a drink?
Yeah, sure.
Hey!
- Well?
- Hey.
It was meant to be a garden party,
but this is much cozier.
I brought tiramisu.
This is my favorite song. I have to dance.
- Where's the champagne?
- Under the table.
- Great. Thank you.
- We're so proud of you!
I guess you deserve
at least a driver's license for that.
- No!
- Yes.
- For real?
- I promise.
- Charlotte!
- Awesome!
- You have to dance with me.
- No.
- Yes!
- No. Katharina, please no.
- Hey.
Well?
Do you know where this goes?
Over there.
Where's Peter?
Summer cold.
And Michael?
Something similar.
- I'll take this over.
- Sure.
Champagne!
Thank you!
Hannah!
Come on, live a little.
Glad you came.
Glad you all made it! Cheers!
- Hello.
To our health.
- Now dance with me, old-timer.
- Sure.
Jonas?
I thought I heard something.
How come you're not at the Nielsens'?
Did something happen?
Hey...
Everything okay?
What's with your hair?
I know.
What do you know?
I know everything.
What?
Ultimate fist bump?
Why did you just say that?
Because I know, Dad.
I know everything.
I know your real name is Mikkel Nielsen.
It's okay.
Forgive me.
Even younger and prettier.
- I thought you'd pop with the third.
- How mean!
What a sweet girl.
Sweet girl? That's Magnus!
- What's wrong?
- I can't sleep.
Oh, no.
You're burning up.
- Look at these two ugly monsters.
- Let's get you upstairs.
I loved that dress.
You two are very sexy.
There you go.
- Sleep well. Night-night.
- Can you stay here till I fall asleep?
Slide over.
So you're from the future then?
And why are you here now?
Because I need to ask you for something.
What?
Not to do it.
Not to do what?
It's Ulrich and Katharina's anniversary.
You didn't go along, like always.
You stayed here.
But something was different.
I should've noticed something was up.
Jonas...
- I have no idea what...
- Don't lie to me!
I know! God fucking damn it!
I know you'll hang yourself in the studio.
Have you already written the letter?
What letter?
The letter you write to me.
Not to me, to the younger me.
The one marked: "Do not open
before November 4, 10:13 p.m."
DO NOT OPEN BEFORE NOVEMBER 4,
10:13 p.m.
The very minute you vanish.
I'm here so you don't do it.
It's all intertwined.
Like an endless loop.
But you...
you killing yourself,
that's the start.
Promise me you won't do it.
Dad, you have to promise me.
Please.
Promise.
You forgot this at the lake.
I put it on a cord.
Thanks.
I thought about what you said at the lake.
About grandmas? And the internet?
I think you're right.
Okay.
The night you vanished,
you were there and then suddenly gone.
Did you go back to the cave?
How did you find the passage there?
I didn't find it.
Someone showed it to me.
Who?
You.
What do you mean?
We were by the caves.
- What'll you give me for it?
- A kick in the ass.
What's in here is easily worth 500.
It's yours for 200.
- Daddy's got plenty of money.
- Blah-blah-blah.
Stop the bullshit.
Just give it to me.
Jackpot!
There was this strange noise.
What is that?
We were all sure someone was there.
Someone's there.
Shit.
What was that?
- Shit.
- What's going on?
What's wrong with the damn flashlights?
Come on, run!
Now! Let's go!
We ran.
Then I lost you.
I turned around and you were gone.
But suddenly you were back again.
Quick!
This way.
You said there was something there,
in the forest.
Something evil.
And that we had to return to the cave.
You brought me all the way to the door,
and through the tunnel.
I was so afraid.
But you held my hand.
And then you said,
"We have to stay here, all night,
but when morning comes
everything will be all right."
And when I woke up you were gone.
All these years I've tried to understand
why you did that.
But then,
at some point it all just faded away.
It became ever more unreal, like a dream.
But that's impossible.
I never did that.
I saw myself today.
Mikkel.
It's all returning.
That coat, you.
As if it's all falling into place.
Maybe you're not here to stop me at all.
But rather to show me
what it is I have to do.
Maybe you only showed me the letter
so I know what's in it,
so I go and you live.
No, that can't be.
That can't be.
He told me I could stop the origin.
If you don't kill yourself,
none of the rest will happen.
But if none of the rest happens,
you won't be born.
And maybe your role in all this
is much greater than you think.
And perhaps
I'm just a small part of a huge cancer
that is much greater
than any of us can imagine.
- Someone has said that to me before.
- Who?
Me.
God doesn't err.
He has a plan.
For each of us.
I've waited a long time
for the moment we'd meet again.
Who are you?
Are you with Adam?
There are two sides out there.
He is the darkness.
I don't follow him, I follow the light.
He lied to you.
He brought you here to trigger everything
so it happens as it always has.
No, that can't be.
Adam wants this too.
No, he does not.
He doesn't want to fix things.
He wants to destroy them forever.
Your role in all of this
is much greater than you believe.
Only you alone can put an end to all this.
What does that mean?
We're at war,
and you have to wage it against yourself.
Against Adam.
But if I don't exist,
if I'm not born,
then Adam won't exist either.
I've seen the world without you.
Believe me,
it isn't what you're expecting.
There are times in life when you must see
that the decisions you make
affect more than your own destiny.
This isn't just about you and Mikkel.
This is about everyone.
Your mother.
Your friends.
Martha.
You alone can save them.
What does that mean?
We all have to make sacrifices.
Your father must make sacrifices too.
It's okay.
Is this the apocalypse?
A bit disappointing.
I imagined it being louder.
More glaring.
If the world ended tomorrow
and everything started anew,
what would you wish for?
A world without Winden.
And you?
Dear Jonas,
by the time you read this everything
will have already happened, irrevocably.
It can no longer be changed.
I would have liked
to explain things to you sooner,
but I hope once you understand
how everything is connected,
you will understand my decision.
The truth is a strange thing.
You can try to suppress it,
but it will always find its way
to the surface.
We make a lie into our truth
in order to survive.
We try to forget.
Until we can't anymore.
We don't know
even half of the mysteries of this world.
We are wanderers in the darkness.
You could have told him.
You could have told him
what his task in all of this is.
What path you really sent him down.
Not much longer
until the last cycle begins.
We all have to make sacrifices, Magnus.