MAN CAN DO WHAT HE WILLS,
BUT HE CANNOT WILL WHAT HE WILLS.
If we knew
how things would end...
where our journey would take us...
would we still make the same decisions?
Or would we choose a different path?
Could we even escape our fate?
Or would something deep within us
lead us to the same end,
like an invisible hand?
Does it matter which path we choose,
when we end up standing before ourselves
again and again?
♪ Fold out your hands
Give me a sign ♪
♪ Put down your lies ♪
♪ Lay down next to me ♪
♪ Don't listen when I scream ♪
♪ Bury your doubts and fall asleep ♪
♪ For neither ever ♪
♪ Nor never ♪
♪ Goodbye ♪
♪ Neither ever ♪
♪ Nor never ♪
♪ Goodbye ♪
♪ Neither ever ♪
♪ Nor never ♪
♪ Goodbye ♪
DÈJÀ VU
Wait. Martha, this can't be.
- I don't understand...
- We have no time.
What time are you from?
The question isn't what time...
but what world.
How did we get here?
I asked how the hell we got here!
No way you're Martha.
Who are you?
Today is the day everything started.
The day we first met each other.
What are you saying?
That you and I...
your world and my world...
form a knot
that is inextricably intertwined.
Your world?
What do you mean, your world?
I'll make this right. I promise.
Wait! Where are you going?
Why am I here?
Mikkel, put it away.
Morning.
No wonder
you can't sleep at night.
♪ If I could turn back time ♪
What's up with him now?
He's been having the same nightmares.
Mikkel, that's enough.
Maybe that wasn't a dream.
Maybe the here and now is
and none of us are real.
Ever thought about that?
Ha-ha. Hilarious.
Oh, that damn electricity!
Pass the butter.
Come on, Mikkel. Time to get ready now.
The bowl!
Is Magnus awake?
- Martha! I asked if Magnus is up yet.
- I don't know.
- Are you crazy?
- Just checking if you're real.
Magnus!
You'll be late!
Hello?
Magnus, either you get down here
or I'm coming up!
I'll be there in a sec.
- Hey, dumb-ass!
- Race you to school. Morning, Mom.
- Idiot.
- Morning.
You want a ride?
It's supposed to rain later.
No, I'm going to be late. Play rehearsal.
Don't forget,
tomorrow you're staying with your father.
Mom, you know that sucks.
Good morning, sleepy head.
I was awake half the night again.
Hmm.
What took you so long?
First day of school.
The line was long at the bakery.
The apocalypse is nigh.
How about you stick around?
I'm already pretty late.
I'll see you this evening, okay?
Ulrich?
I love you.
You're beautiful.
MISSING ERIK OBENDORF
SCHOOL THEATER WEEK
I win.
Welcome back to hell.
You may be such an idiot you can't realize
education is the way out of here,
but the rest of us
don't share your stupid opinion.
- Don't forget to breathe.
- Don't forget to think.
- Hey.
- You seen Kilian today?
- Nah.
So why all this effort?
I mean, we all die in the end.
Are you totally sure you're not adopted?
Are you totally sure
you don't have a stick up your ass
that needs urgent medical attention?
- Dumbass.
- No, you're the dumb-ass.
- Hey, Martha.
- Kilian.
Is there any news on Erik?
No.
It's really creepy.
Good morning.
We request that all students attend
a first-period assembly in the gymnasium.
- That could be about your brother.
- It's two weeks now. He's never done this.
If he can't take it at home,
he always sends a message, reaches out.
But this time? Nothing.
Let's go. Mom will get angry with us.
MISSING ERIK OBENDORF
It will happen again.
CONTACT THE WINDEN POLICE
WITH INFORMATION
It will happen again.
He hasn't said
anything else all morning.
It will happen again.
How'd it go at the doctor's?
- It will happen again.
- Good. You know, it was just routine.
It will happen again.
I should go. I'll be late.
Something I forgot.
It will happen again.
Ticktock.
Ticktock. Ticktock.
POLICE
Erik Obendorf
has been missing since October 22.
Almost two weeks. No traces, no witnesses.
Questioning the neighbors hasn't produced
any new leads either.
So anybody got a bright idea?
We haven't received the shift schedules
from the nuclear power plant yet.
That's good. Check that out.
Go see Tiedemann.
- Wöller, look into the tire tracks.
- Got it.
- Jankowski, talk to the Obendorfs again.
- Okay.
For all we know he ran away.
This isn't the first time.
So, a black hole forms
when a collapsing central region appears.
And then inside that there are neutrons.
Well, more like neutron matter.
But not enough of it.
So when the light of a star
that is three times the mass of the sun,
is extinguished... it explodes.
No, it implodes.
And it turns into a black hole.
And...
Can I help you?
Hello?
Are you new here?
I'm Jonas.
You sure this is your class?
I wasn't notified about any new students.
I still need to get a signature.
Okay.
Bartosz, you may continue.
Mm-hmm.
So then we have a black hole.
It has a huge gravitational pull.
Everything around the hole is pulled
towards it and dragged inside of it.
Other stars, planets, even light.
The gravitational force is so strong
that even light is pulled into it.
Nothing can escape once it's inside.
Basically, no one knows what's behind it.
Maybe nothing, or maybe a new world...
in which nothing is as we know it.
All I'm asking is to view the schedules
of your employees on that day.
Erik was last seen
walking on the forest road.
We could compare employees' tire tracks
with the tracks we found.
And do you have a court order?
I don't have a warrant.
It's a request.
I'll have the schedules sent to you.
So how are you?
All right.
Okay then.
I've been wondering...
Do you think Erik
could have made his way onto the grounds?
The caves extend out
under the power plant.
No, that's impossible.
The access points
were sealed up years ago.
No one can get in that way.
Okay then.
Reminder:
no activities today after four o'clock
due to the parents' assembly,
with the exception of the drama club,
which must leave the auditorium
an hour early.
Mr. Hopf will supervise the student paper
meeting at the youth cafe today.
Katharina.
Why are you here?
- I wanted to see you.
- Uh-huh.
I don't know...
I know Ulrich and you...
Ulrich and the kids, they...
They're part of him.
And I want you to know
I'll stay out of the way.
That's incredibly generous of you.
Did Ulrich stop by this morning?
He wanted to bring something over.
What was he bringing?
I'm not sure.
It was... for school, for the kids.
No.
Well I guess he forgot.
Please remember
to turn in your presentations next week.
No exceptions.
What is it?
You haven't told me yet why I'm here.
Who are you?
You really don't know me?
You coming?
ARIADNE A PLAY
Jonas, right?
Everything okay?
What day is it today?
November 4.
What year?
2019.
Are you sure you're...
Mom?
I'm sorry?
Did you say something?
Are you okay?
Charlotte?
We have to stop doing this.
That's not
what you were saying earlier today.
Ulrich, not here.
- Oh, uh... Sorry.
- What is it?
Um... The, uh, tire treads.
47 cars and two trucks.
And there are
21,000 registered vehicles in Winden.
What am I supposed to do with that fact?
I...
No idea.
I have the shift schedules from the plant.
We'll do a comparison.
Wöller.
That's when I knew
that nothing changes.
Everything remains the same.
The spinning wheel turns.
Round and round.
One destiny linked to the next.
A thread,
blood-red,
connects all our actions.
You cannot untie the knot.
But you can cut through it.
He cut through our knot,
with a fine knife.
And yet there's something
that remains inseverable.
An invisible bond.
Some nights he pulls on the bond,
then I'm ripped from my sleep
and realize that nothing ever disappears.
That everything remains.
And they were blind with eyes and hearts,
so they were punished for their sins.
Here and now.
What was in flight plummeted to the Earth.
What was on the Earth changed its shape.
Revealed its grotesque face,
which was nothing more
than unholy blasphemy made flesh.
Great. We'll stop here.
We have to finish early today.
Let's get things tidy
for the parents' meeting this evening.
Thank you all.
Nine o'clock by the bridge. Don't forget.
Martha.
Hey, I don't know what you want from me,
but I don't have it, okay?
So go away.
Please listen to me.
Maybe you don't know who I am.
- But today is November 4 and Mikkel...
- What? Mikkel?
Michael Kahnwald. Hannah's husband.
He's not who you think...
Hannah's husband? Are you for real?
I don't know any Michael Kahnwald.
Hannah's husband is my father, Ulrich.
I don't know what your deal is,
but just fuck off already, okay?
Wait. Not so fast.
I...
love you.
I love you.
It will happen again.
It will...
happen again.
It will happen again.
Mom?
Dad?
It will happen again.
It will...
happen again.
Ticktock.
- Grandpa, are you okay?
- Ticktock.
Ticktock.
The beginning is the end.
The end is the beginning.
Ticktock.
Can I help you?
Looking for something?
I wanted to know
if someone was buried here.
Who?
Kahnwald.
Michael Kahnwald.
No, but Daniel Kahnwald's here.
He died in '64.
No Michael Kahnwald.
That could be why I'm here.
So it doesn't happen.
What doesn't happen?
Do I know you?
I feel as if I've seen you
somewhere before.
Hey, wait!
What's your name?
Hello?
I'm sorry, can I help you?
Are you lost or something?
The master key.
For the power plant.
Surely this is a joke.
You kept it hidden.
Do you think this is funny?
If you don't leave,
I'll have to call the police.
Police...
What do you want from me?
Nothing is free.
No breath you take.
No action.
No word.
No pain.
An everlasting miracle...
of oneness.
Who the hell do you think you are?
The police came by today.
You know what you have to do.
Kilian?
Stop messing around.
What are you doing?
What do you want?
I don't want to scare you.
- Why'd you say we know each other?
- Because we do.
Not now. In another time.
What are you saying?
You've seen this before.
The light.
The trees. Me.
It's déjà vu.
Or a glitch in the matrix.
What?
I think I know why I'm here.
Why you came for me.
So I might change it.
Change what?
Who's this then?
- Where is Mikkel?
- Mikkel?
Mikkel isn't with you?
You blind or something?
What's he doing here?
You bring him along?
What is this?
- How do you know my brother?
- This can't be.
You took him with you.
Heide, the babysitter, is sick.
He didn't want to stay home alone.
That's why he came.
I've no clue what the hell's going on,
but Mikkel
is old enough to look after himself.
Now you'd better fuck off.
Get lost, freak.
Come on.
Martha.
POLICE
Charlotte, I'm going
to the parents' meeting.
I'd be happy to give you a lift.
Sure.
- Follow this up?
- Mm-hmm.
We need to reach out
to these names.
Why did he act like he knew you?
- Does he?
- No.
Who knows.
Did you know Nostradamus predicted
that the world would end this year?
What a load of shit.
No. Really.
The apocalypse is just around the corner.
Glad I got a girlfriend
with her own bunker then.
What?
Nothing.
Ow!
What?
What do you think
you'll find here?
Erik sometimes
spent summer nights here.
The police might have missed something.
Ever heard the story of the cave monster?
- Skip the bullshit, man.
- No, this is legit.
About 100 years ago,
just after the war,
they did experiments in the caves.
What kind of experiments?
- What was that?
- What?
Shit.
What's in the cave?
- What is that?
- Oh, shit!
- Fuck!
- What's going on?
- Fuck! What's happening?
- Run!
- What's with the flashlights?
- Kilian!
- Hurry up!
- Martha!
- Martha, come on.
- Run!
Run! Run!
Kilian?
Martha.
♪ Here it ends ♪
♪ No one's gonna shed a tear ♪
♪ You sit and wait ♪
♪ Watching full glasses
Through blank eyes ♪
♪ This is not what you wanted ♪
♪ Not what you had in mind ♪
♪ Vacuous winter stare ♪
♪ Worn out version of yourself ♪
♪ Too tough to fall ♪
♪ But not strong enough to turn ♪
♪ This is not what you wanted ♪
♪ Not what you had in mind ♪
- Is it over?
- I think so.
What...
What is that?
Oh, God.
- Fuck.
- Fuck!
Shit.
Oh, shit. Shit.
Fuck.
- Is he dead?
- Fuck.
Yes, I think so.
Who... Who is that?
STUDENT CARD
MADS NIELSEN, DECEMBER 4,1973
Mads Nielsen.
I've waited for this moment for so long.
For you to come back.
What is this?
Mikkel.
He didn't travel back.
He won't become your father.
And you...
will never be born here.
A world... without you.
Isn't that what you wanted?
Yet, despite that,
this world has the same fate,
it's been damned, like yours.
Everything will fall apart.
In this world just as it will in yours.
Again and again.
Because of you.
And because of me.
Martha.
Jonas?
You're alive.
I am not Martha.
Not your Martha.
What does that mean?
I came here to help you find the origin.
The one thing...
that's the beginning of everything.
In your world...
and in mine.