Hey!
What happened to him?
Where did you get that?
What are you doing here?
I just want to go home.
Maybe he's a returned POW.
Looks like you've been roughed up.
I guess you could use something to eat.
I'm fine, thanks.
Nonsense.
Erna has a soft spot for fellas like you.
Come along.
Agnes, go and let Erna know.
Run.
Where were you stationed?
Eastern front.
- Labor camp.
- Those people aren't human.
We should have won the war.
Do you have a place to sleep?
Tell your brother
to get the chamber ready.
But just for a few days.
Until you're back on your feet.
I know this sounds strange.
But what year is it?
They did quite a job on you, didn't they?
1921.
1921...
JUNE 24, 2020
THREE DAYS UNTIL THE APOCALYPSE
I think we're a perfect match.
Never believe anything else.
Yes?
Mrs. Doppler called in. She's sick.
What's wrong with her?
She didn't say.
Hold on.
- You're Mr. Wöller, right?
- Yes.
Then the pleasure is ours today.
- You do have a car, right?
- Mm-hmm.
Wonderful.
CALL FROM
HANNAH KAHNWALD
Where did you get this?
- Who is this?
- It's complicated.
Mom, why do you have that?
Should I make us breakfast?
What are we going to do with Mom?
I don't know.
What do you want?
- Martha.
- Franziska.
- What do you want?
- We have to talk.
- What?
- If you expect an apology, forget it!
You fucked up.
But I shouldn't have said what I said.
We're even.
Am I supposed to babysit
while you make out?
Why did you bring her along?
My parents haven't been home in two days.
I can't leave her alone.
Why is everyone acting so weird?
- I want to know what's up.
- What? You want to go into the caves?
You can stay here.
You slept nearly 24 hours.
Who are you?
People say Erna can't say no
to any stray dogs.
I'm in the wrong place.
This isn't right.
I pictured you differently.
Why did you just say that?
What does it mean?
Sic mundus creatus est.
Can I help you?
I'm looking for someone.
She used to work here.
It was a while back.
Tiedemann. Claudia Tiedemann.
She used to run the plant.
- Where can I find her?
- There's only one Tiedemann here.
Aleksander Tiedemann.
He runs the plant.
Aleksander Tiedemann?
So that's why you didn't want to let
Ulrich Nielsen onto the grounds?
After Fukushima
safety standards were raised.
I can't just let anyone stroll in here.
His suspicion that his son might be
on the grounds was totally unfounded.
You know about the door in the cave?
It was installed in the 1980s.
It was already welded shut back then,
as a security measure.
- It's still sealed shut.
- You know what I find strange?
Everyone who was born here stays.
Seems odd, in a town of this size.
What do you think?
Why is that?
The nuclear power plant always took care
of people. There's work.
Prosperity, security.
That'll probably change now.
When the plant closes.
- You're not from here.
- No.
Why?
You came to Winden in 1986.
At the same time the boy disappeared.
Mads Nielsen.
Ulrich Nielsen's brother.
No. It was a bit later.
A few weeks.
Why does that matter?
It probably doesn't.
Just one more question.
Why did you take your wife's name?
I don't understand.
Pretty unusual for the time.
The Tiedemanns shaped this town.
Especially Regina's mother.
Regina has no siblings.
We wanted to keep the name alive.
What's your real name?
Köhler. Aleksander Köhler.
Who's next on the list?
Mr. Wöller?
Hannah Kahnwald.
Why do you have a gun
and someone else's passport?
It's insurance.
What do you mean?
Someone needs
to keep both things hidden.
You're blackmailing someone?
Who are you?
Who I am?
Hannah?
I'm sorry.
But we have to tell someone.
Thanks for getting here so soon.
I know none of this makes sense, but...
This is Jonas. He...
He's much older,
and he knows where my Jonas is,
and where Ulrich is.
You're the man from the hotel
Regina talked about.
Who are these people?
This man here. The priest.
Do you know who he is?
That's Noah.
You know him?
What do you know about him?
- He's one of them.
- What is all this?
One of whom?
Sic Mundus.
The travelers.
The travelers?
Sic mundus creatus est?
What are you talking about?
You knew all of this?
The time travel?
There's something you should both see.
Okay.
You want to go in there?
After four kids disappeared here?
You stay with me.
Do what I tell you. Okay?
WINDEN MUNICIPAL LIBRARY
Excuse me.
I am interested in...
the town's history.
Where can I find articles and publications
from the past 30 years?
It's all been digitized.
And where do I find that?
Excuse me.
Where's the keyboard?
There isn't one.
SEARCH
CLAUDIA TIEDEMANN
CLAUDIA TIEDEMANN FIRST WOMAN
TO HEAD A NUCLEAR POWER PLANT
NUCLEAR POWER PLANT BOSS
DISAPPEARS WITHOUT A TRACE
You informed her about the meeting?
Yes.
APPOINTMENTS
Anything about Hannah Kahnwald?
Her husband killed himself last year.
He hanged himself.
Actually, no one here understood
why she married him. She's very pretty.
She could've had any man she wanted.
It was rumored she had an affair
with Ulrich Nielsen.
Did Mrs. Nielsen know about it?
May I ask you something?
Go ahead.
How did you get this position?
Special task force.
Did you volunteer for it?
Oh, yes.
I did.
IS THIS MAN A CHILD MURDERER?
She told Tronte and me what to do.
Claudia Tiedemann.
She knew the exact time
things would happen.
It made no sense. And yet
it was the only thing that made sense.
You knew all this?
Michael?
Mikkel? Ulrich?
You knew it all?
This here.
She gave it to us.
It's all in there. About the children...
Who disappeared when.
Things about time travel.
Symbols and tables
we don't really understand.
The last few pages were ripped out.
Does Katharina know about this?
You have to tell her.
Okay.
But I'll do it.
REGINA AND ALEKSANDER TIEDEMANN
TO WED
WE'RE GETTING MARRIED
REGINA TIEDEMANN - ALEKSANDER TIEDEMANN
WALDHOTEL WINDEN OPENS
WALDHOTEL WINDEN CLOSED
EGON TIEDEMANN
NO TRACE OF MADS NIELSEN
CHIEF INSPECTOR EGON TIEDEMANN...
FORMER WINDEN CHIEF INSPECTOR
FOUND DEAD IN HIS APARTMENT
ON JUNE, 261987
Excuse me.
Can you print from these things?
Sometimes I dream about him.
Jonas.
It feels so real.
As if he were still alive.
How can it feel so real if he's dead?
Do you think he knew something?
Before he disappeared?
What do you mean?
That he found out something
he wasn't supposed to.
The door has to be here.
Where are we going, Charlotte?
Tell me where we're going.
Damn it, Charlotte! Where are we going?
It's easier to explain it
if I show it to you.
Have you found them?
You found them.
We found them. Both of them.
They're not dead. They're alive.
But they're not here.
What does that mean?
They're alive, they're not here?
You better see it with your own eyes.
What's she doing here?
What is this, Charlotte?
You said you thought Mikkel
was in the cave. You were right.
Mikkel was in the cave,
and Ulrich was looking for him there.
But there was something in the caves.
A kind of
crack in time.
Are you screwing with me?
What is all this bullshit?
- Where are Mikkel and Ulrich?
- It's true...
Shut your face!
No one asked for your opinion.
Charlotte is right.
Another one.
Who are you? Her new lover?
I'm Jonas.
Her son.
Your grandson.
She says it's shaking.
- What is it?
- There's someone there.
Go, go!
Flashlights off!
Bartosz?
Why are you here?
What the fuck?
What are you doing here?
My husband is caught in the 1950s,
and my son in the 1980s?
You left him there
because Mikkel is your father. Right?
Yes.
I can't believe it.
That you're buying all his bullshit.
What do you want? Huh?
Money?
Can you talk to the dead? Hm?
Katharina.
I was there.
I saw him.
Mikkel.
You've all lost it.
No.
If you have anything to do
with this shit...
Fuck you!
Stop it. Just tell us why you're here!
Come here.
What is that?
What is it?
Hands off. It's not your business.
If you have anything to do
with Mikkel or Dad...
I'll kill you.
What are we going to do now?
We're taking it.
And him?
We'll leave him here.
Maybe he'll change his mind.
Shit!
You can't do that.
Martha!
You can't do that!
Hey. Fuck... Hey!
Magnus!
Hey! Magnus!
What's your take on all of this?
We have a man-eating cave.
An NPP with a boss
who is obviously hiding something.
An inspector who has gone into hiding.
And a town full of people
who lie, cheat and betray one another.
And who are all only concerned with
concealing what's really going on here.
So, Mr. Wöller?
What do you make of it?
I don't know.
What happened to your eye?
Okay.
But...
you can't tell anyone.
Well...
- Last summer...
- Watch out!
Interesting.
TEACHER'S LOUNGE
PLEASE KNOCK
1986, 1986...
KAHNWALD, MICHAEL - 6B
6b.
6b...
CLASS REGISTER
It's not open yet.
It's going to take
nearly 32 more years until it opens.
So you know about it?
They're waiting for you.
Who?
Sic Mundus.
You want to go home, right?
That's what they say, anyway.
Who are "they"?
The travelers.
And now?
It doesn't matter.
Everything will happen as it always has.
Then why are you here?
- He said there's a loophole.
- Who?
Adam.
Who's Adam?
The leader of Sic Mundus.
The people in the photo,
the travelers?
Yes.
He wants the last cycle to begin.
In three days.
I have to stop him.
That's why I'm here.
She tried.
But in the end she became
what she wanted to fight.
What are we doing here?
You're one of them.
A traveler.
Not yet.
But I will be soon.
It must be strange for you to see me here.
Especially after our last encounter.
You've already made my acquaintance.
You finally want answers, don't you?
ALEKSANDER KÖHLER?
SIC MUNDUS CREATUS EST
What are you doing here?
What is that in there?
You knew it was here!
You were
lying to us the entire time.
What is that?
They say it's a piece of God.
But it's really a piece of the devil.
The prophecy.
How did it arise?
The book. Who wrote it?
Whoever it was who wrote it...
had already seen the future and the past.
What will happen next?
Adam will send him on the path
that has been predetermined for him.
So the last cycle can begin.
You must have a lot of questions.
Traveling doesn't leave one unscathed.
The human body isn't equipped for it
on a continual basis.
What is this place?
Shall we begin?
I don't want to begin anything.
I want this to finally end. All of it!
Don't worry. It will end.
That is inevitable.
Your end.
My end.
Upon closer examination, everyone's end.
Who are you?
Don't you know?
That can't be.
I am you.
Every stone is once again
where it belongs.
Everyone in the place
they were destined to be.
Now all that's needed is a little push.
Subtitle translation by Nathan Fritz