WWW.MY-SUBS.COM
Hey!
What happened to him?
Where did you get that?
What are you doing here?
I just want to return.
Think he's a refugee?
Well, you look like you've been
through some real shit to me.
- You could probably use some food.
- Mm-hmm.
- I'm all right.
- Nonsense.
Erna loves stray dogs. Come on.
Agnes, go get Erna.
Now.
Where were you stationed?
Eastern front.
- Labor camp.
- They aren't human over there.
That's a war we should've won.
Do you have a place to sleep?
Tell your brother to
get the small room ready.
But only for a few days.
Till you're back on your feet.
This is going to sound strange.
But what year is it, please?
They really worked you
hard out there, didn't they?
It's 1921.
1921...
June 24, 2020
Three days until the Apocalypse
You and I are perfect for each other.
Never believe anything else.
Yeah.
Mrs. Doppler called in
sick. She's not coming in.
What's wrong with her?
Don't think she said.
Just a minute.
You're Mr. Wöller, right?
Yeah.
Then we're in for a fun time.
- Do you have a car?
- Mm-hmm.
Wonderful.
Call from Hannah Kahnwald
Where did you get this?
- Who is that?
- It's complicated.
Mom, why do you have that?
Do you want me to make some breakfast?
What do we do with Mom?
I have no idea.
What are you doing here?
- Martha.
- Franziska.
- What do you want!
- We need to talk.
What?
If you think I'll say
sorry, you can forget it.
You fucked up, but I shouldn't
have said what I said.
We're even.
Am I the babysitter while
you make out in here?
Why did you bring her along?
Because our parents haven't
been home for two days.
I can't just leave her there alone.
Why is everyone acting so weird?
I want to know what's going on.
You're going to go into the caves?
You don't have to come.
You slept for almost 24 hours.
Who are you?
Everyone says that Erna
can't turn away a stray dog.
I'm not right here.
This isn't right here.
Hmm.
At first I pictured you differently.
What's that supposed to mean?
Why did you say that?
"Sic mundus creatus est."
Can I help you?
Hi. I'm here looking for someone.
She used to work here, a while back.
Tiedemann. Claudia Tiedemann.
She used to run the facility.
You know where I can find her?
Here there's only one Tiedemann.
Aleksander Tiedemann, the guy in charge.
Aleksander Tiedemann?
So that was why you wouldn't let
Ulrich Nielsen onto the property?
After Fukushima, safety
standards were raised.
I can't just let people walk in here.
His assumption that his
son could be here somewhere
was completely unfounded.
Do you know about the door in the cave?
Installed in the '80s.
It was already welded shut
back then as a security measure.
- It's still shut to this day.
- You know what I find a bit strange?
Everyone who was born here stays.
That's quite unusual
for a town of this size.
Why is that?
What do you think?
The nuclear plant has always provided.
There's work.
Prosperity, security.
Although that's likely to change now.
When we close the facility.
- You're not from around here.
- No. Why?
In 1986 you came to Winden.
That's the same time
the kid disappeared.
Mads Nielsen.
Ulrich Nielsen's brother.
No. I came later.
A few weeks.
How's that relevant?
I guess it isn't.
One more thing.
What made you take
your wife's last name?
Why do you ask?
Pretty unusual, especially back then.
The Tiedemanns shaped
this city, Inspector.
Especially Regina's mother.
Regina has no siblings.
- We wanted to keep the name alive.
- What is your real name?
Köhler.
Aleksander Köhler.
Who's next on the list?
Wöller.
Hannah Kahnwald.
Why do you have a gun and
someone else's passport?
They're for insurance.
Insurance?
There's someone very interested
in keeping those things hidden.
So it's blackmail?
Who are you?
Who am I?
Hannah?
I'm sorry, but we have to tell someone.
Thanks for getting here so soon.
I know none of this
makes any sense, but...
this is Jonas. He...
He's much older, but he knows
where my Jonas is
and where Ulrich is.
You're the man Regina
was talking about, from the hotel.
Who are these people?
This man here, the priest.
Do you know who he is?
That is Noah.
Are you sure?
What do you know about him?
- He's one of them.
- What is this?
One of whom?
Of Sic Mundus.
The travelers.
The travelers?
Sic mundus creatus est?
What are you talking
about? You knew all this?
The time travel.
There's something I
think you both should see.
Okay.
You want to go in there?
After four children disappeared?
You stay by me. I'll make
sure we're safe. Okay?
Winden Municipal Library
Excuse me.
I'd like to learn about...
the town's history.
Where can I find articles and
documents of the last 30 years or so?
That's all digital now.
And where's that?
Excuse me.
Where is the keyboard?
There isn't one.
Search
Claudia Tiedemann first woman
to head a nuclear power plant
Nuclear power plant boss
disappears without a trace
Did you inform her
about the appointment?
Yes.
Appointments
What do you know about Hannah Kahnwald?
Her husband committed suicide.
Hanged himself.
No one here understood
why she married him.
She was so pretty. She
could've had any man she wanted.
There were rumors that she had
an affair with Ulrich Nielsen.
Did Mrs. Nielsen know about that?
Can I ask you something?
Ask away.
How'd you get this position?
Special task force.
Did you volunteer for this?
Oh, yes.
I did.
Is this man a child murderer?
She told me and Tronte
what we have to do.
Claudia Tiedemann.
She knew exactly at what time
things would happen.
It didn't make any sense,
yet it was the only way
anything made sense.
You knew about all of this?
Michael, Mikkel, Ulrich?
About everything?
This here... She gave us this book.
It's all in there, about all the
children. Who disappeared when.
Things about time travel.
Symbols and tables we
can't quite understand.
- The last few pages were ripped out.
- Does Katharina know this?
Well, you have to tell her.
Okay.
But let me do it.
Regina and Alexander Tiedemann to wed
We're getting married Regina Tiedemann
- Alexander Tiedemann
Waldhotel Winden Opens
Waldhotel Winden Closes
No trace of Mads Nielsen Chief
Inspector Egon Tiedemann...
Former Winden Chief Inspector
found dead in his apartment
on June 26, 1987
Excuse me.
Can I print off these things?
Sometimes I dream about him.
Jonas.
It all feels so real.
As if he was still alive.
How could it feel that
way if he's really dead?
It's possible he knew something,
before he disappeared.
What are you saying?
What if he saw something
that he shouldn't have seen?
The door has to be in this direction.
Where are we going, Charlotte?
Tell me where we're going.
Damn it, Charlotte!
Where are you taking me?
It's easier to understand
if you just see it.
What have you found?
You found them.
We found them.
Both.
And they're not dead.
They're still alive.
But they're not here.
They're not here?
But they're alive...
What does that mean?
It's better if you see
it with your own eyes.
Why is she here?
What's all this about, Charlotte?
You said you thought Mikkel went
into the cave. You were right.
Mikkel was in the cave and Ulrich
was looking for him in there.
But they found something in the tunnels.
A kind of tear... in the fabric of time.
You can't be serious.
What is all this shit?
- Where are Mikkel and Ulrich?
- It's true.
Stay out of this! Nobody
asked you for your opinion.
Charlotte is right.
Uh-huh. Another one?
And who are you? Her new boy toy?
I'm Jonas.
Her son.
And your grandson.
She says it's shaking.
- What is it?
- We're not alone.
Go. Go, go!
Turn off the lights.
Bartosz?
What are you doing here?
What the fuck?
Why are you here?
My husband is trapped in the '50s,
and my son in the '80s.
You chose to leave him there
because Mikkel is your father.
That right?
Yes.
I can't take this seriously.
You're buying into all this bullshit?
What's in it for you? Huh?
Do you want money? Can you
speak with the dead? Yeah?
Katharina.
I was there.
I saw him there.
Mikkel.
You've all lost your minds.
No.
Fuck you, Magnus!
I swear to God, if you
have anything to do with this shit...
Fuck you.
- Stop it.
- Tell us what the fuck you're doing here.
Come here.
What is this thing?
- What is that?
- Don't touch it. It doesn't concern you.
If you have anything
to do with Mikkel or my dad...
I'm going to kill you.
What should we do now?
We're taking it.
And him?
We leave him here.
Maybe that'll change his mind.
Fuck.
You can't do this.
Martha! You can't do this!
Hey. Shit. Hey!
Magnus! Stop!
Magnus!
What's your take on all of this?
We have a man-eating cave.
A nuclear plant run by a man
obviously hiding something.
An inspector who seems
to be hiding herself.
And we have a town full of people
who cheat and betray each other.
And they're obviously very invested
in hiding what's happening here.
So, Mr. Wöller...
what do you make of all this?
Uh... I'm not sure.
Tell me, what happened to your eye?
Okay.
But...
you can't tell anyone else.
Uh, so...
- last summer...
- Watch it!
Interesting.
Teacher's lounge please knock
Okay.
Eighty-six.
Six-b.
Six-b, 6b, 6b.
Six-b, 6b.
CLASS REGISTER
It's not open yet.
It'll be another 32
years before it opens.
So you know about this?
They're waiting for you.
Who's waiting for me?
Sic Mundus.
You want to get home, don't you?
That's what they say, anyway.
Who are "they"?
The travelers.
What now?
It doesn't matter.
Everything is going to
happen the way it always has.
Then why are you here?
- He said there'd be a loophole.
- Who?
- Adam.
- Who's Adam?
The leader of Sic Mundus.
The people in the photo? The travelers?
Yeah.
He wants the last cycle
to begin. In three days.
I have to stop it.
That's why I'm here.
She tried to do it.
But in the end, she became
exactly what she was fighting.
Why did you bring me here?
You're one of them.
A traveler.
Not yet.
But soon I will be.
It must feel strange
to see me here as well.
Especially after our last encounter.
But you've already made my acquaintance.
You'll get answers in time.
What are you doing here?
What's in there?
You knew it was in there!
You...
have lied to us the whole time.
What is that?
They say it is a part of God.
But in reality it's a part of the devil.
The prophecy.
How did it arise?
The book, who wrote it?
Whoever it was who wrote it...
had already seen the past and future.
What will happen to him next?
Adam will send him on his way,
the path that's been determined.
So that the last cycle may begin.
You must have a lot of questions.
Traveling leaves its marks on all of us.
The human body isn't
equipped for it in perpetuity.
What is this here?
Shall we begin?
I'm not here to begin anything.
I want this to end, finally. All of it!
Don't worry, it will come to an end.
That can't be avoided.
Your end,
my end.
On closer inspection,
it's everyone's end.
Who are you?
Can't you see it already?
This isn't real.
I am you.
Every stone is back where it belongs,
everyone at their destination.
All that's needed now is a push.