The beginning is the end.
And the end is the beginning.
Everything is interconnected.
Future,
past
and present.
I couldn't tell her who her mother is.
Just as I can't tell you...
what your provision is.
And what I have to do today.
I've reflected on this moment
for many years.
My older me
wanted to tell me something,
but he couldn't.
If you knew what I now know,
then you would no longer do what you must
so I can get to this moment.
Me, as I stand here now, cannot exist
if you don't take the same path as I did.
We're not free
in what we do,
because we're not free in what we desire.
Everything is ready.
You must go now.
A NETFLIX ORIGINAL SERIES
JUNE 27, 2020
THE DAY OF THE APOCALYPSE
FEDERAL REPUBLIC OF GERMANY
PASSPORT
My future me tried to shut the hole.
To reverse it all.
He shut the passage,
but hadn't broken the loop.
But you said we can change
a small part of the equation, so he...
So I will be successful next time.
Then none of this sick shit
will ever happen.
Mikkel won't disappear.
Michael won't die.
Your father won't die.
Big and small things
don't abide by the same laws.
Maybe nothing big can be altered...
but small things can.
We're changing a grain of sand.
And with it, the whole world.
What was Grandma like?
I mean, as a mother.
Why does it suddenly interest you?
She isn't dead, you know?
What do you mean?
She was here.
Last fall.
After Mikkel disappeared.
She...
She left something here.
For you.
She said she was sorry.
And that if she could turn back time,
she'd do lots of things differently.
I'll be back.
I promise.
Where are you going?
Do you know what this is?
A search warrant for the power plant.
Special conditions apply to the plant.
The judge issued the warrant immediately.
I think,
given the ongoing legal proceedings
against you,
he may be interested in
what's to be found there.
WARRANT
Maybe I can't prove you killed my brother,
but I'll get you for what's going on here.
You have to let me out of here.
That's impossible.
I can't do that.
You can't let him onto the site!
Maybe this is better.
Maybe it's good
it's all finally coming out.
Martha,
I didn't want any of this, believe me.
- Please listen...
- What are you doing here?
Come on!
Why are you here?
What do you want?
You have to come with me. Please.
It's my fault everyone dies.
- What?
- It's all going to blow in a few hours.
Everything starts all over again.
The future starts. A new cycle.
What are you talking about?
Please believe me, please.
You have to trust me, please.
This is wrong.
We're wrong.
Please leave now.
No.
I can't let you go.
You're hurting me.
I saw you die once.
I won't let it happen again.
Let me go.
I can't.
I promised you I'd make it right.
I'm making it right.
SIX HOURS TO THE APOCALYPSE
Where's the device?
Where's the fucking device?
My mom has it.
That's not right.
It shouldn't happen this way.
It's all my fault.
Why didn't Noah tell me what to do?
Why did he tell me it all?
Explains the thing to me
and doesn't tell me what to do with it.
Maybe you did
exactly what you were supposed to do.
You showed us how it works.
Maybe that was your sole task.
Fuck!
Where are you going?
To find the fucking device!
Hello?
Jonas?
FOLLOW THE SIGNAL
What's that?
The passage.
We're opening it again.
You said you wanted to shut it.
In the future.
Or the past. Your future!
It took me ages to accept having to be
part of the disaster I wanted to prevent.
How do you know all this?
In the last 12 months.
You taught me everything,
about the future and past.
Everything that happened.
Everything that will happen.
There are two sides out there.
Adam and Sic Mundus
want to create a new world.
You and I want to save this one.
Who's Adam?
What is this?
The only safe place.
Please don't.
Please.
Why are you doing this?
Because I know what happens today.
The Mikkel story...
is it true?
Then I...
I didn't want all this, Martha.
You kept me alive.
I'm still here because of you.
Jonas will come back.
It'll all happen as it always has.
But I can't stop hoping
I can change something.
I have to.
Jonas will come back?
Promise me you won't leave this bunker.
No matter what happens.
I'm sorry.
POLICE
MISSING
Charlotte?
- I thought you were still sick.
- Is Clausen here?
No. Clausen arrested Aleksander.
He got a search warrant
for the power plant.
He's headed there.
Charlotte!
I... I have to tell you something.
On the nuclear power plant grounds,
Aleksander buried something
in concrete there.
Radioactive waste.
I helped him do it.
I'm sorry.
That triggers it.
- What?
- It's all connected.
He said it all has to do
with the power plant.
- Jonas knew it.
- You found Jonas?
No, he traveled back from the future.
We have to go.
Wöller!
Come on.
FOR CHARLOTTE
Charlotte, where are you?
Is Franziska with you?
Call me once you get this.
We're going now.
Where?
I no longer know
what I should believe.
But Noah said
only the people in the bunker
survive.
What about Mom and Franziska?
It'll all be okay.
FOUR HOURS UNTIL THE APOCALYPSE
I don't quite get
what you hope to achieve here.
The site is huge.
Controlled shutdown takes place tomorrow.
My mother always said,
"Just because a task seems too big
doesn't mean it's unsolvable."
What's behind this door?
The...
The spent fuel pool for the old reactor.
It's been out of use since the 90s.
I'd like to see it.
You can't just go see it.
There's residual radiation.
Anyway,
I don't think you'll find anything there.
PHOTO ALBUM
MICHAEL
JUST AFTER HIGH SCHOOL GRADUATION
Katharina?
How does this machine work?
Where did you get it?
How can I bring Mikkel back?
Even if I explain it to you,
it's impossible.
You don't want him to return.
- Because then you'd no longer exist.
- I wish it were so simple.
Things in the past can't be changed.
Mikkel can't return
because I already exist.
Mikkel belongs here, and not you!
You shouldn't exist at all.
Yes.
I'd trade my life for his anytime.
But I can't die,
because my future already exists.
You'd be just as incapable
of bringing Mikkel back.
Then why did you return?
I tried to prevent the origin.
But it's impossible. I can't.
Adam is the endpoint.
Maybe I can't prevent myself
from becoming what he is.
But I can stop what has become of me.
I know you lied to me.
You never meant to save them.
None of them.
We can't escape our fate.
Neither you nor I.
You're not waging war against God.
You're waging it against humanity.
Here are the last pages.
You used me.
You had me do all these things,
but I know now what I must do.
Claudia was right.
You still don't understand
how this game is played.
What are you waiting for?
Time plays its cruel game with us.
You believe your destiny is to kill me.
But that is as little your fate
as it is mine to die here and now.
Only when we're free of all emotion
are we truly free.
Only when one is ready to sacrifice
what one holds dearest.
Charlotte is your daughter.
She is Elisabeth's daughter.
And her mother.
No human is without guilt.
None of them have earned
a place in your paradise.
Agnes?
This knot
can only be undone
by destroying it entirely.
We cannot escape our destiny.
What is happening?
This is time.
We connect past and future.
What's that?
It's Jonas. He opened the passage again.
The thing Mikkel went through?
Yes.
Martha.
Is everything okay?
Who locked you in here?
Hey, wait!
Martha, you can't go out there!
Martha!
- What was that?
- Fuck.
It was the same noise
as the one from in the cave.
- Fuck.
- You got it?
The device isn't up there.
And Mom isn't here. Neither is Martha.
Do you think she's with him?
With Jonas?
Noah was right.
He was right about everything.
I told you guys.
Jonas is to blame for all this shit.
Where are we going?
You have to take it to the bunker.
Near Helge's cabin.
You don't have much time.
And you?
I have to find my mother.
And Martha.
Jonas!
TWO HOURS UNTIL THE APOCALYPSE
Hey, Martha! Call me back.
Neither is answering.
My father is with Elisabeth in the bunker.
- He says I should join him.
- In the bunker?
Shit.
Something's happening.
I have to go there.
If they're not here in 30 minutes,
we'll go join your father.
Where are Mom and Franziska?
I don't know.
So Noah says he's your father
and comes from the future.
No, from the past.
And he said the apocalypse
will begin here in Winden.
Today!
And you think it all has to do
with the barrels.
- What is that?
- The cooling pool for the old reactor.
It has already been sealed
to become part of the green field.
When?
I, um...
don't know exactly.
But it's nothing unusual.
Sealing off the old reactor
is a step in the dismantling process.
I want it broken open.
Now?
Now.
You can't keep him there another night.
He's done nothing wrong.
This is all nonsense.
When can I visit Aleksander?
I understand.
Regina?
Please don't be afraid.
It's really me.
I'm so sorry.
I didn't want to just leave that way.
I'll explain it to you.
Buy you have to come with me now.
Regina.
I'm so sorry.
Noah?
You look different.
Different to when I saw you last.
He sent you.
Adam.
I always wondered when you became him.
I won't do that.
I'll never do what he did.
He said you'd say something like that.
He also said we'd become friends.
Before you betray me.
Why do you follow him?
Why did you follow her?
Claudia.
Because we want to believe.
Because we cling to the salvation
promised to us.
If you kill him...
you kill all hope of salvation.
He's the savior.
You're the savior.
- What is that?
- Read it.
It's from Martha.
This is impossible.
You must save them.
Bartosz, Magnus and Franziska.
And later me and Agnes.
The loop has to be closed
so the next cycle begins.
As the prophesy dictates.
And so Martha can live.
No, this can't be.
Martha!
Regina.
You're her.
You're Claudia.
FOLLOW THE SIGNAL
Your colleague is in the old reactor.
Mom?
Jonas?
You're back.
You really came back.
I've been looking for you.
- I have to tell you something.
- I know.
Everything.
I know why you said that
back then in the rain.
Mikkel...
I know everything.
It was you at the lake.
We're a perfect match.
Don't ever believe anything else.
And so the circle closes.
Jonas, who is that?
Go on, tell her who I am.
I told you that all the pieces
are in their places.
All that's needed is a little push.
You lied to me!
You wanted it all to happen again.
You're the trigger.
We're all the trigger.
Each and every one of us.
Why do you want that?
Why do you want the future to be repeated?
Because what is created today
is the beginning of the end.
The dark matter,
it has to be created so that in the future
I can lead it to its new purpose.
The end of this world.
I am the trigger.
Only not of what you think.
I am the trigger
that will make you become what I am today.
It's okay.
It will all be okay.
Some pain is unforgettable.
You will carry this pain for the rest
of your life.
Look at me.
Until you're finally ready
to let go.
Of her, too.
You can stop me.
Or try to save her.
You'll know what to do.
Please, don't go.
Martha!
Please don't go.
Please don't.
Don't open it!
Stop! Don't open it! It's a mistake.
No, Mrs. Doppler. It's our elephant.
You have no idea
what this is really about.
- What is it this really about?
- Not about the missing people.
It's about the future,
the past
and how it's all interconnected.
- Open it.
- Please don't!
- No, it's a mistake!
Magnus! Open up!
Magnus!
Open the door!
Hurry!
Magnus!
What the hell? Who are you? Hey!
It's him. It's you.
You're Jonas.
It's all your fault.
Yes, it is my fault, all of it.
- But I'm here to save you.
- Save us from what?
- From the apocalypse.
- What apocalypse?
What about Martha?
FOR CHARLOTTE
Mom.
Elisabeth.
It's beginning.
Where are we going?
I promise you.
I'll make it right.
I'm not who you think I am.
- Wait. Martha, that's not possible, I...
- We don't have time.
I'll explain it to you later.
We have to go now.
What time are you from?
The question isn't from what time,
but from what world.