JUNE 24, 2020
THREE DAYS UNTIL THE APOCALYPSE
CALL FROM
HANNAH KAHNWALD
You want to go in there?
After four kids disappeared here?
WINDEN MUNICIPAL LIBRARY
SEARCH
CLAUDIA TIEDEMANN FIRST WOMAN
TO HEAD A NUCLEAR POWER PLANT
NUCLEAR POWER PLANT BOSS
DISAPPEARS WITHOUT A TRACE
APPOINTMENTS
IS THIS MAN A CHILD MURDERER?
REGINA AND ALEKSANDER TIEDEMANN
TO WED
WE'RE GETTING MARRIED
REGINA TIEDEMANN - ALEKSANDER TIEDEMANN
WALDHOTEL WINDEN OPENS
WALDHOTEL WINDEN CLOSED
NO TRACE OF MADS NIELSEN
CHIEF INSPECTOR EGON TIEDEMANN...
FORMER WINDEN CHIEF INSPECTOR
FOUND DEAD IN HIS APARTMENT
ON JUNE, 26 1987
IS THIS MAN A CHILD MURDERER?
TEACHER'S LOUNGE
PLEASE KNOCK
CLASS REGISTER
What are you doing here?
They say it's a piece of God.
But it's really a piece of the devil.
Subtitle translation by Nathan Fritz