"That's when I knew
that nothing changes."
That everything remains the same.
The spinning wheel turns.
Round and round.
One destiny leads to the next.
"A thread, blood-red,
connects all our actions."
This play was beloved by your mother.
She would have surely liked
to come with us tonight,
in the company
of such a distinguished young man.
FOR CHARLOTTE
Why do we die?
The dead are never truly dead.
Maybe they're not here, now.
But everything that once lived
lives on forever
in the eternity of time.
You there!
What are you doing on the road?
I asked what you're doing!
Who is that?
Who are you?
He that has eyes to see
and ears to hear
may convince himself
that no mortal can keep a secret.
If his lips are silent,
he chatters with his fingertips.
Betrayal oozes out of him at every pore.
I...
I don't understand.
Oh, but you do.
You're going to town
with a telegram you want to send.
Because you want
to tell the world about us.
Isn't that so?
You are one of their kind?
A traveler.
All those years...
they said my father was insane.
But now they are here.
The travelers of the future.
The world must know
that they exist.
What we know...
is a drop.
What we do not know
is an ocean.
♪ Fold out your hands
Give me a sign ♪
♪ Put down your lies ♪
♪ Lay down next to me ♪
♪ Don't listen when I scream ♪
♪ Bury your doubts and fall asleep ♪
♪ For neither ever ♪
♪ Nor never ♪
♪ Goodbye ♪
♪ Neither ever ♪
♪ Nor never ♪
♪ Goodbye ♪
♪ Neither ever ♪
♪ Nor never ♪
♪ Goodbye ♪
ADAM AND EVE
Our mistake
in all of our thinking is...
that we each believe ourselves
to be an independent entity.
One self...
beside countless other selves.
While, in reality,
we're all just small fractions
of an infinite whole.
What is this here?
Is it a copy of my world?
Do you remember what you said to me?
Under the bridge.
The light.
The woods.
You.
I.
A glitch in the matrix.
Why am I here?
You and I.
Adam and Eve.
That's what we are.
A glitch in the matrix.
You want to know why you're here.
To save them.
Your world.
And mine.
POLICE
Last night at around 10:00 p.m.
Kilian Obendorf,
Bartosz Tiedemann and Franziska Doppler,
as well as Magnus and Martha Nielsen
found a previously unidentified boy's body
on the Doppler property
by the forest road.
The clothes and the Walkman
are from the 1980s.
We also found...
an ID card on the body.
Wöller, can you continue?
Can I talk to you for a minute?
You don't have to do this.
Wöller can do briefings, and I can handle
forensics myself. Go home.
I've spent 33 years
looking for my brother.
Those are his things.
Those are Mads' things.
Someone held onto them all.
And stashed them
in the bunker with the kid.
33 years later.
Do you think it was the same killer?
That it's connected somehow?
Mads, Erik, the kid in the bunker?
Know why I joined the police
as a young man?
When my brother vanished...
they made every mistake
you could possibly think of.
The detective was a drunken moron.
And me?
I swore that I could do it all better.
That I would do it the right way.
That was 33 years ago.
And what do I do?
I betray my wife.
And now I'm cheating on the woman
who I cheated on my wife with.
I can't do it anymore.
TANNHAUS MACHINERY FACTORY
Where were you?
- What did she tell you?
- We've been stuck here weeks.
The fucking apparatus is dead.
You have no idea how this shit works.
You lied to us.
You knew what would happen
and told us none of it.
You must realize she's just using you!
That isn't Martha.
She's dead.
Nobody comes back from the dead.
Whoever she is,
she may be our only chance
to get back home.
Why don't you tell us the truth?
Tell us how Martha really died that day.
Bartosz! Wait!
Tell them!
Tell them who Adam really is!
I told you all along!
Jonas was always the problem!
It's him.
He is Adam!
With all of it, did you never
wonder why you can't let go of her?
You know you two can never be together.
Yet still,
you can't let her go.
An invisible ribbon...
that for eternity binds you.
Adam tried to sever it.
But it's impossible.
You gave this to me.
You and I.
Black and white.
Light and shadow.
For eternity, we're bound,
bound in this eternally repeating déjà vu.
What are you saying?
What do you want?
Why won't you just tell me
why I'm really here?
You have seen what you will do.
What Adam will do.
If you want to save your Martha,
you have to choose the side of light.
And you must make me
what you see I've become.
I must?
I don't have to do anything anymore.
I'm sick to death of having
all these obligations.
Then consider...
what you want.
Should she live, tell me?
Your Martha?
Dad?
Got a second?
Is Magnus here?
Asleep, I think.
You have to tell me the truth now.
What really happened in the bunker?
What did you see?
I meant everything I said.
We went into the bunker, and it was empty.
There was nobody there.
Then there was this light.
And then this...
this body fell down.
Did you take anything?
What?
Fine. Did Kilian give you anything?
Come on, what did you take?
What is this shit?
Playing the concerned father
all of a sudden?
You usually don't give a shit what we do.
It's exactly what we told you.
There was this noise.
Outside the caves,
coming from the caves or... I don't know.
We went into the bunker.
At first there was nothing, then...
he was lying there.
Is that it?
Mom gets here soon.
I think you'd better get out.
But it was nice of you to drop by
and see how we're doing.
- Hannah.
- Hello.
Is Ulrich here? I've been trying
all morning to get in touch.
Um...
I thought he went home.
You look so different, Charlotte.
Did you get a haircut?
No.
It was nice to see you.
I'll put this in his office.
Can we talk?
Get lost.
Last night.
In the woods.
Did you see anything else?
No.
What else?
Do you ever feel
like you're losing your mind?
Like nothing makes sense anymore?
I guess that Dad was right.
He was already there.
And we...
I know exactly what I saw.
Where are you going?
Leave Mom out of this.
I'll be back for dinner.
Everything repeats itself,
again and again.
For all eternity.
Because none of us are prepared to let go.
It took me a long time to understand that.
That you can't let go of your past.
That you will make that choice,
choose your Martha, every time.
And just as you can't let go of your past,
I've clung to mine as well.
You trusted the path Adam showed you.
Where did it lead you?
You must show her
how all this is intertwined.
There's not much time left.
She needs to see her future to understand
what must be done.
She will follow you.
It's your fate that she's bound to,
just as you are to hers.
You said I was in your world.
With you.
Why can't I remember it?
I don't know.
The letter.
It wasn't me who wrote it.
You must believe me.
Sic mundus.
What is it?
Old Tannhaus' father,
he tried to bring someone back to life.
His wife.
He was convinced that time-travel
would be the world's salvation.
He thought every error could be prevented
before it occurred.
But it doesn't bring salvation.
Only damnation.
They're all dead, Jonas.
In my world.
I can't give up on trying to change that.
I know you think I can't be trusted.
Let me prove to you that I can.
You traveled with that?
It's the last one I have.
It's the only way I can go back again.
You could have told him
which path you would send him down.
How it'll end.
Even if he knows, he will never stop
trying to break the cycle.
He won't understand...
that we must preserve the knot.
That his Martha must perish.
So that all others can live.
The beginning...
and the end.
WINDEN NUCLEAR POWER PLANT
VOLUME CONTROL SYSTEM
Ulrich, it's me, Charlotte. I...
I just wanted to know you're all right.
Call me here, okay?
Tick.
Tock.
Can I see Kilian?
Kilian.
Hey.
It's okay.
- What are you doing here?
- You weren't at the dorm. I was worried.
They kicked me out.
Your father called too.
He asked if I slipped you something.
- Did you?
- That's bullshit. I wouldn't do that.
But okay, sure...
None of you can get it out of your system.
I haven't lived here for two years,
but I'm still the trailer trash
everyone points the finger at.
I knew it.
What did you know?
You were only with me
to stick it to your parents.
You couldn't care less about me or Erik.
You better go now.
Okay.
About Regina...
I'm sorry.
It must be difficult for you.
How are you?
Bartosz?
We're getting by.
I...
I'm here to offer you a deal.
What kind of a deal?
I have something that was yours.
I want to return it.
Do you recognize it?
Don't worry.
The contents are in a safe place.
What do you want?
If it's money...
I don't want that.
I want Charlotte to be destroyed.
I want her to lose everything.
All of it.
Charlotte.
What are you doing here?
Thank you.
You've helped me a lot.
I've been trying to call you.
I went to the bunker.
Why aren't you home with Franziska?
I...
Last night, where was Helge?
You said you had dinner with him.
Where was he afterwards?
What is all this?
In 1987, when you got to Winden,
did your father still live in the cabin?
- I don't understand...
- Did he or didn't he?
No.
He went into the nursing home.
- And the summer before, in '86?
- I think so. Why do you want to know?
Did he use the bunker for anything?
Charlotte, what do you want from me?
This is Helge's.
I found it in the bunker.
That... That's not right.
He was with us all night.
Doppler?
He did what?
Where?
Yes. Yes, I'll come there now.
Helge.
He's at the police station.
He's confessing apparently.
POLICE
Dad, why are you saying that?
It makes no sense at all.
He didn't ever leave the house.
We were there all evening.
Elisabeth was too.
I said I killed that child.
- Stop it, Dad!
- His things.
The Walkman. His clothes.
Those are Mads Nielsen's things,
the boy who disappeared in 1986.
Do you recall that?
I killed the child.
Who? Mads?
Where did you get his stuff?
- Hey!
- What did you do to Mads?
What did you do to Mads?
You're alive.
- What?
- It was you.
What was me?
- It was him.
- What? Let go.
It was him.
- What are you saying?
- It was him!
FEDERAL REPUBLIC OF GERMANY 1986
What do you want?
Are you following me?
Why won't you tell me
how we know each other?
Actually, I've always known you, Martha.
When Magnus knocked out
your tooth in kindergarten.
I was there.
Camping with Mikkel,
when he put spiders in your shoes.
On the class outing, third grade...
when you were so homesick
that Katharina had to come pick you up.
Where I come from...
our pasts are nearly identical.
So you're mad then.
I know that you saw yourself.
Last night in the woods.
You told me that.
Your future self.
What?
I know how completely insane
all this sounds.
For a while
I thought it was all ridiculous too.
That I was crazy.
Who are you really?
I can show you...
how all of this is bound.
Where's Martha?
♪ If I was you I'd run ♪
♪ If I was you I'd hide ♪
♪ If I was you I'd be afraid ♪
♪ Afraid of what's inside ♪
♪ If I was you I'd run ♪
♪ If I was you I'd hide ♪
♪ If I was you I'd be afraid ♪
♪ Afraid of what's inside ♪
♪ And I can hear your voice ♪
♪ I can feel you cry ♪
♪ No matter what you do now ♪
♪ Don't dare to close your eyes ♪
♪ You can't destroy me ♪
♪ I'll tell them that you tried ♪
♪ Shed a single tear now ♪
♪ Time to say goodbye ♪
LET THERE BE LIGHT
Did you give it to him?
I always was too gullible.
You did the right thing.
What is this?
Where are we?
How did you do that?
She said that I had to bring you.
That she'd explain it to you.
Who?
Who is that?
Welcome to the future.