- [sighs] Okay, all of Sara's
favorite things--
double espresso,
bacon not-too-crispy.
- Hang on.
Greek finishing salts.
Did a grocery run to the Agora
in Ancient Athens.
- Nice.
- Just heard her alarm,
it's go time.
- Okay. [sighs]
- Not yet.
Can't skip the garnish.
We eat with our eyes first.
- Is that all of it? Okay.
- Ava, wait.
Passion Dragon Ash enhances
vitality and endurance.
Sara really doesn't
like smoothies,
but ooh, nice flourish, Nate.
- Mm-hmm.
- [snoring]
- Oh, we didn't forget
about you, gorgeous.
- Seriously, Mick, thank you
so, so much for everything.
- Here, recovery Dragon Ash,
usually for hangovers,
but also probably good
if you've been lost in space.
- And A5 Kobe beef.
I dry-aged it
for 15 years this morning.
- Yeah, we seriously need
to talk about your portal-use.
- So, the rest of the team
is hooking up the gizmo
we jacked from Kayla's ship.
- Okay, once that happens,
Gideon can help us
pinpoint
the rest of the alien pods.
- And we will find
the perfect mesh
to welcome the captain back.
- Mm-hmm.
- Ava, relax.
I know we've been
through a lot,
but things are finally back
to normal.
- Are they?
- Talk, talk, talk
Can't a man just eat in peace?
- See?
[clanging]
- If you don't hold it,
I won't be able
to connect the wire.
- If I keep holding it, I won't
be able to feel my arms.
- Could you keep it
down out there?
I am trying to study magic,
but I cannot concentrate
over your constant toiling.
- Okay, well, how about you
memorize your nursery rhymes
when we're done
with the real work over here?
- Tua cutis fiat ignite.
- Whoa!
The hell was that
supposed to do?
- Must have
the pronunciation wrong.
- All right.
Let's get back at it. And--
- Gary, my alien chum.
Let's have a chat, eh.
- Oh, is this about us parking
Kayla's ship at your place?
'cause we were kind of
in a hurry.
- Not that.
What do you know
about the Fountain of Imperium?
- Where'd you hear about that?
[stammers] I mean no.
The, uh--the Fountain of what?
- All right, just let him be.
- Thank you, Spooner.
- No, it's just that
when you're stressed,
I gotta feel it too.
Okay, this whole alien
empath thing was hard enough
before we had
an actual alien on the ship.
- It's back to the books, then.
- Good luck.
- All right. Come on,
let's get back at it. Come on.
- And quieter, this time?
Thanks.
- Ohh, God,
this is so much better
than waking up
on an alien planet.
- Right?
- Here you go my love.
- Thanks.
- And I'm just gonna say this,
okay, whenever you're ready
to talk about what
happened out there, I am here.
- Who wants to talk about space
when we have Legends gossip--
to catch up on.
- [gasps]
Oh, hot and juicy. Okay.
So Spooner's great, well,
when she put away her rail gun.
- Sounds like my kind of girl.
- Yes.
Oh, and I was a binder,
and actually, I think
it turned into a cartoon.
- That's a new one.
- Yeah.
Babe, something wrong
with the food? Come on.
- Oh, babe, no, the food,
it looks amazing.
I just think I'm jet lagged.
- Okay.
- But what's with the smoothie?
- That is from Zari.
It's for passion, which--
why are we wasting time
talking about gossip and aliens
when we could be
focusing on you and me?
- I'm an alien-human-hybrid
clone.
- [snorts] What?
[exciting music]
♪ ♪
- [sighs] So, you're an
alien-human-hybrid-clone
who can regenerate?
- Oh, babe, it sounds so crazy.
- No, I--I mean, yes,
obviously, but---okay.
Babe, you are Sara Lance.
You're still the same
beautiful, tough, and yes,
sometimes very surprising woman
that I fell in love with.
And you're here with me, okay?
So that's all that matters.
- Captains, you're needed
on the Bridge.
An alien pod
has been detected.
- We have to go.
- Babe, wait.
Can we just maybe
not tell the team
about the whole hybrid thing
just for
the first mission back?
I kinda wanna feel normal.
- Yeah, I get it.
And you know what, after
everything we've been through,
they could use
a little normalcy too.
- Yeah. Okay.
- We have to go, though.
- Yeah.
[sighs]
[cheers and applause]
- All right, all right,
all right, that's enough.
Okay, we get it.
Gideon, what do we got?
- Welcome back, Captain!
I've detected a pod in the
Oklahoma territory, 1891,
near an encampment known
as Fist City.
- Woof, that can't be good.
The outpost of First City
was the wildest of the west.
Countless outlaws
passed through--
Butch Cassidy,
Belle Starr, Wild Bill.
- Sounds like a bad scene
on its best days.
Hate to see the kind of havoc
an alien could wreak out there.
- Hey, Spoons, are you okay?
- Yeah, just alien mind-meld's
been firing up
since the space cadets
got back.
- That's coming from--
- Gary, obviously.
- Well, if my read's right,
Gary's hiding
something big from us.
- Well, like, that's okay,
whatever it is, right?
I mean, Gary, you're an alien,
but you're also one of us,
and I think we should
all be more accepting of Gary.
- Okay, but now my read says
Gary wants to jump Ava's bones.
- That sounds about right.
- What? No. I do not--
- Okay. Well, I feel like
getting back in the saddle.
Who's coming with me?
[imitating gunshots]
- Hey, Nate,
just with everything
Sara's been through,
I think she could use
a nice smooth mission, okay?
- So a classic Legends
romp, on it.
- Yeah, but easy.
- Got it.
♪ ♪
[bell dings]
[horse neighs]
- All right, gang, be on watch.
The pod has already landed,
so the alien could be anywhere.
- Try to keep a low profile.
I don't know
what's more dangerous,
the alien or the locals.
- Sounds like my kind of place.
- Yeah, mine too.
My dad put me through
a cowboy phase as a kid,
when he was trying to lean
into American culture.
Some of it stuck.
- Cute, but I was talking
about the lawlessness.
Hell, I might know some of
these people from, hell.
If you want to talk line
dancing lassos, try Spooner.
- I was raised in Texas
not "Hee Haw."
- I don't know what that is,
but it looks
like your hat does, pardner.
- Well, I had to put this back
on to do my alien radar.
So far, getting nothing
but Gary.
- Couldn't help but notice
you flirting with Astra.
- I wasn't flirting.
I was just trying to,
you know, connect, person
to person, soul to soul.
- Yeah, that's called flirting.
Listen, I know it's hard
to have a social life
on a timeship,
so I wanted to offer my help
as someone
who has recently learned
how to balance work
with a healthy
and fulfilling love-life.
- Oh, don't need
to hear about that.
And if this is your way
of finding another test subject
for your passion smoothies,
I'm good.
- Hey, I promised Eva
a classic Legends romp, okay?
So, no getting captured,
no personal drama.
- Bet we'd find
the alien quicker
if Spooner wasn't afraid
of her brain.
- You mean you can't find it
by bungling some Latin phrase?
- Hey, okay, tension. Got it.
You know what this calls for,
the buddy system.
You two, starting now,
are buddies.
By the end of the mission,
you will be friends, okay?
And smiles.
[piano music stops]
- Remember, don't make waves.
They won't take kind outsiders
around here.
[music starts]
♪ ♪
- Can you just find this alien
so we can get out of here?
[ringing tone]
- Getting nothing new.
- And you're not going to
if you keep wearing this thing.
- Whoa--guys.
- Whoa!
[tense music]
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hey, partner, let us--
let's get you another.
- Yeah, that ain't happenin'.
- Look, we really
don't want no trouble.
- Aw, shucks.
Come on, neither do I. [laughs]
'Cause I should be
the one treating you.
Barkeep, may I please have
a round for our new guests?
- Guys, is that a Swear Jar?
- Huh?
- Is this root beer?
- Yep.
- What were you saying about
this place being dangerous?
- Well, folks,
seems by my sights,
we have outsiders come in
to our modest municipal.
So how 'bout we make
these newcomers neighbors
by lettin' 'em in
on our ways around here.
[playing guitar]
- ♪ Well, other towns
they'll get you down ♪
♪ I don't know where to start ♪
♪ There's rifle-play ♪
♪ And fights all day,
it breaks my cowboy heart ♪
♪ But don't you fear
'cause over here ♪
♪ We offer the reverse ♪
♪ Yes, welcome to Fist City ♪
♪ The gladdest place on Earth ♪
all:
♪ Oh, welcome to Fist City ♪
♪ The gladdest place on Earth ♪
[cheers and applause]
- I've seen weird before,
but this is weird.
- Gary, mate,
I found something
that might jog your memory.
This Fountain,
it's an ancient alien artifact
said to amp up magic.
Are you sure you haven't heard
anything about it?
- Why would you need this?
You're already the most
powerful magician there is.
- Yeah, see, that's the thing.
While you were away,
the Legends
got into a bit of a scrape.
And in order to set it right,
I had to surrender my power.
- You lost your magic?
- All right, all right,
don't cry about it,
but you can help me.
This Fountain of Imperium,
it's my one shot
at getting my magic back.
- The Fountain--
right, right, right, Imperium.
Yes, yes, I have heard of it.
It's a total myth.
I'm sorry,
there's just nothing out there.
You should give it up.
♪ ♪
- I'm telling you these people
should be low-down, dirty,
probably diseased,
sons of a--
Evening, ma'am.
- How do?
- Hello.
- Good day.
- Something big must have
happened to turn this place
from Deadwood to Disneyland.
- It must be our alien,
or gentrification.
Either way, we should stop it.
- Let's blend in, spread out,
figure out exactly
when things changed.
- I'd thank you for
another soda, m'lady.
- Deal me in.
- Is this your way of nabbing
the alien?
- No, this is my way of nabbing
that jerk's gold.
- But you're right,
it could be the aliens.
So, could you sense
what cards it has?
- I can barely control
my power as it.
I ain't gonna tap into 'em just
to help you cheat at cards.
- The game's "Go Fish".
You know it?
- What's your wager?
- Oh,
ain't no gambling around here.
That just leads to bad blood.
'Sides, it'd be breaking
rule number three.
So, got any jacks?
- Maybe we should check out
the card tables.
- Okay, I'm sorry,
I cannot let you make
the same mistake again.
You always go
for the bad girls.
What we need is to find you
a woman who appreciates you
for the nice sweet boy you are.
- I don't only go
after the bad girls,
and I don't need a matchmaker.
See? She looks nice.
- Oh, no, bro, bro, bro,
this is a saloon,
it is her profession
to be interested in you.
- No, we don't offer
that sort of business.
It's one of the rules.
- What has gotten
into these people?
- [clears throat]
You're new in town, ain't you?
- Reckon I am.
But that just means
I need
someone to show me around.
Say, what's with
all these here rules.
- Oh, Sheriff's get lots of
do's and don'ts.
There ain't no rule
against playing a girl a tune.
Forgive my forward nature,
I'm Irma Rose.
- Why if that ain't
the sweetest-soundin' name
in the whole wide world.
You got a song in mind?
- Something to put a smile
on my face.
Think you can manage that?
- Think you can
manage that?
- I guess we'll find out.
[sighs]
[playing jaunty piano music]
♪ ♪
- Hey, Barkeep.
Do you notice anything
weird around here lately?
- Weird? Not at all.
Now, what can I get you ladies?
Got sarsaparilla,
phosphates, milkshakes.
- Make it a milkshake.
Extra cherries.
- Yes, ma'am.
- Another one?
- Well, guess I'm finally
getting my appetite back.
- Over here.
- I ain't never seen no one
down 'em like that.
- Bass Reeves.
Reeves was the first
black Deputy Marshall
west of the Mississippi.
He's a hero, not a wanted man.
The alien's changing history.
- Contact Sheriff
Levi Stapleton.
- Oof, I know that name.
Stapleton was a criminal famous
for terrorizing
Oklahoma territory.
But how did an outlaw
end up a sheriff,
and how did the marshal
end up an outlaw?
- Hey, Barkeep, what can you
tell me about Levi Stapleton?
- Well, just that he's about
the finest lawman around.
[door bangs open]
[bird screeching]
[epic Western music]
♪ ♪
- I heard we had
some visitors come in.
[playing guitar]
- ♪ Ohh, Stapleton,
Stapleton, fills us with awe ♪
♪ Restorin' us order
and layin' down law ♪
♪ The sheriff of sheriffs,
he's fair and he's firm ♪
♪ Brings peace to our streets
and we hail him in turn ♪
- I'd say let me be the first
to bid you welcome,
but I see my fine citizenry's
beat me to it.
- It is a fine town
y'all have here.
Fact, we was just wondering
how you made
this place such a haven.
- Now don't you worry
about that.
You just enjoy yourself.
Oh, barkeep, fill our guests
some drink and vittles.
So they can be on their way.
- Guess we know who's scared
this town straight.
Think he's our alien?
- We'll have Spooner
get a read.
Speaking of, where are
Spooner and Astra?
- Spoons.
- [whistling]
- If you won't let me
win your gold,
then tell me where you got it.
- Sorry, she gets hot
under the collar.
No, but we do have a question
about what's happening
around here.
- I don't know
what you're aimin' at,
but you'd be wise
to stop asking
and get like
a good little girl.
[ringing tone]
- [grunts]
[rumbling]
- What is that?
- A fight goin' outside!
[all clamoring]
♪ ♪
- Astra's getting closer.
- Not now, Spooner.
- But even if I was gonna see
where I got my gold,
last one I'd tell's a girl
with the looks of you.
- Don't try me.
- Hell, if I'll let you
touch me.
- Look out!
[roaring]
[high-pitched tone]
♪ ♪
- Shame to see.
But let that remind y'all
of why
we keep our tempers
in check here.
So how 'bout y'all
go back inside
and get back
to having a good time?
Go on, get.
As for you, I think you've seen
just about enough of Fist City.
So y'all don't come back now,
ya hear?
♪ ♪
- Hey, Gary,
do you know any alien species
that live underground,
look like a worm,
and swallow people whole?
- Ooh, that sounds
like a Haverack.
Haverack translates
into "rage eater."
It's drawn to the chemicals
we release
when we're angry,
and then it eats us.
- That's why I felt it gaining
when that guy got all riled up.
- Well, its outer shell
is impenetrable,
so the only way to stop it
is to tame it.
There's this whistle.
- That's the thing
Stapleton used.
It must have been loaded
with the pod.
- So we get the sheriff
to give it up. Great.
I was looking for a reason that
wipe that smile off his face.
- Whoa, whoa, but we need
to avoid a fight,
especially if the worm's
drawn to anger.
- So we're gonna sneak it off
Stapleton,
and I know the perfect way
to get close to him.
Square dancing contest.
High noon.
- Yeah, there was no way
I'm square dancing.
- Yeah, we can't have you two
triggering the worm again.
- Are you benching us?
- Do you even have
that authority?
- I don't know.
It did feel weird.
- But he's right.
If this thing
is attracted to hot tempers,
then you two are definitely
staying here
while the rest of us...
dance.
[square dancing music]
♪ ♪
- Everybody, find the whistle.
- Whoo! Everybody elbow twist.
Square up!
- Hey, babe, this is our first
dance since we've been engaged.
- Oh, yeah.
Didn't expect it to have so
much fiddle, but I'm into it.
- And double go in
one more time.
- Hi, we might just
go grab another milkshake.
- Again?
- Yeah.
- It's okay?
- Yeah, it's just
you've already had--
- Ava. I've missed this.
I've missed us.
- Yeah. So this might be
a really weird question,
but is there any species
of alien that loves cherries?
- Hmm, could be a Wafter.
You're worried about
sharing the ship with an alien?
- Oh, that's not what I said.
- No, don't worry.
I haven't wanted to eat
a human in...years.
- Okay, well, thank you, Gary.
Appreciate it.
[Gary groans]
- Grab your partner,
right hand through,
travel over two-by-two.
- Oh! John. I've missed this.
I've missed us.
- Have you, Gary?
- Yeah.
- Well, you can see why
I'm struggling to believe
a word you say
after you lied to me
all those years
about being a human being.
- Oh, well, come on,
those days are over now.
- Are they?
- So you're telling me
the whole truth
about the Fountain
of Imperium, then?
- Everybody change partners!
- Oh, listen to that!
I gotta go!
- Come on, now,
let's shoot the star.
- I'm almost in position
to grab the whistle.
- And I'm almost in position
to make my move with Irma Rose.
- Listen,
I believe long distance
relationships can work,
but the 1800s,
that's a bit of stretch.
- Two hands up,
make lines on the side,
- I'm going in.
- Everybody, two hand balance.
- Strange, y'all don't strike
me as the square dancing type.
- No?
- What I told y'all to get.
- But Sheriff,
we just love dancing so much.
♪ ♪
- Don't think I'm unawares
why y'all really here,
but that worm is mine.
- You're hurting my arm.
- Take your hands
off her, bastard.
- Oh, is this one yours?
- Rude.
[rumbling]
[people clamoring]
- It's comin'. But go on.
You know you want
to get a good hit in.
- Hey, Stapleton.
[spits]
- You just broke
rule number six.
- Well, I don't give a damn
about your rules.
And your reign here
is about to end.
I challenge you to a duel.
Winner gets your whistle,
loser gets out of town.
- You want a fight,
you got it.
♪ ♪
- You sure about this?
I mean, Sheriff's one thing,
but we've seen
what that worm can do.
- Babe, I'm Sara Lance.
I always keep my cool.
[gunshot]
- We passed this spot
twice already.
But then I can see
your navigation skills
ain't for much.
- Wait, you're following me?
- I knew you wouldn't
last a minute out here alone.
The hell are doing hiking
in alien-infested territories?
- Prospcting.
I'm gonna find that gold.
- Okay, well, if it's gold
you're after,
you should follow
the waterfall--
- Why don't you just
concentrate
on using your radar,
in case that thing
decides to attack again.
- Well, I ain't your tool.
And you know,
I'm pretty sure
the ship can make
all the gold you want.
- It's not about the gold,
or not just about the gold.
It's about showing everyone
in that town
that I get what I want.
- Ah, seems like a lot of work
just to prove a point.
- Yeah, well,
figures you'd say that.
But I've had to fight for
every bit of power that I have.
- Okay, you think
I've had it easy?
- I think you spend your life
creating your own kind of hell.
Hiding and alone, letting
aliens mess with your head
when you could harness
that power.
- Yeah, well, I wasn't hiding.
I was keeping my head down.
And you know,
I wasn't always alone either.
You know, when I lost my mom,
they put me in foster care.
- Your mom?
- Yeah, you know,
people tried
their best with me.
But some kid who, you know,
hears aliens all the time,
they couldn't deal.
- Well, where I'm from,
you have to use whatever power
you have to tip
the scales in your favor.
- You know, you're not
in hell anymore.
- And you're not in Texas.
So, which way do we go?
♪ ♪
- What's up, babe?
You know
I've never lost a shootout.
- Yes, I know.
- And I would tell you
if I didn't feel up for this.
It's like you said,
nothing's changed.
- And I meant it.
With everything
that you've been through--
- With everything I've been
through,
a Wild West shootout
is exactly what I need.
- All right.
Let's go win
ourselves a standoff, shall we?
[playing guitar]
- ♪ We don't know
where she came from ♪
♪ But know that she
ain't going back ♪
♪ 'Cause there ain't no one
faces Stapleton's guns ♪
♪ And walks away lookin'
intact ♪
♪ If she shoots
the worm will eat her ♪
♪ If she don't,
she'll fall from his lead ♪
♪ You could do what you can
to prove you're a man ♪
- Can it, cowboy.
- ♪ Godspeed, Sara Lance ♪
♪ ♪
- You done playing
with your pistol yet?
- [chuckles] Mm.
- Ten paces. Then we draw.
[dramatic music]
- One, two--
- Would you shut up?
[gunshot]
- Sara!
- [laughs]
- [panting]
- What the blood hell
happened on that planet, eh?
♪ ♪
- That--that ain't normal.
You must be
some kind of monster.
- No, not a monster.
But you're right about
the other thing,
I'm definitely not normal.
[firing gun]
♪ ♪
- The deal is off.
You ain't getting this.
[gunshot]
[rumbling]
Why...won't...you...die?
[roaring]
[whistling]
- Oh!
- Would you look at that?
Looks like y'all did it.
- I guess we did.
- You found it.
Not bad, Spooner.
[ringing tone]
What, is the alien nearby?
- Yeah. And I'm looking at it.
- Looks like we both found
what we were looking for.
- Did gold just come out
of that alien's--
- But if that's the deposit,
then that guy, he's
not just protecting the gold.
He's protecting the alien.
- Well, y'all figured it out,
that there worm made
Fist City a boomtown.
But don't come between
those folks and their gold.
Deputy Marshall, Bass Reeves.
- We'll take it
from here, m'lady.
- Like hell you will.
Ain't nobody takin'
our net of worm.
That thing's a literal
goldmine, you know?
[sighs] And the thing about us
shooting y'all, well, actually,
we're happy to do it.
[laughing hysterically]
- What's that?
[gunfire]
- Ahh!
- What happened out there?
- Okay, so maybe not everything
is back to normal. [sighs]
- Ain't no hidin'!
Come on out now!
- Don't want the worm
coming for ya.
'Sides, they ain't going to be
cooped up in there
too long before they lose it.
Once they do, worm'll get 'em.
- So you're bulletproof now?
- Yeah.
- Welcome to the club.
- Okay, it's a long story.
I was gonna tell you guys,
I just--wanted to have
a normal mission first.
And on a normal mission,
I'd be out there fighting.
- If we fight,
we attract the worm,
and I cannot see you
take another bullet.
- Babe, I don't know
what you want me to do.
Look, I'm sorry,
but this is who I am now.
- All right, so let's focus
on getting the whistle
so we can squash
this worm for good.
- Whoa, I have an idea.
How about Behrad just flirts
it away from his girlfriend.
- Hey, just because she's evil
doesn't mean
she's not into me, okay?
- You are dumb.
- You know, magic would be
really useful about now.
Guess I'm not getting
that back anytime soon,
Am I, Gary?
[rumbling]
- Ooh, milkshakes are 10 cents.
- Look, we'll come up
with a new plan.
The important thing
is that we keep our cool.
Gang, remember, we're romping.
Huh?
[howling]
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- All right, we cannot
stay in here forever.
Let's brainstorm. No bad ideas.
- I don't need to hear your
I-told-you-so's.
- Listen, I wish you crazy kids
could have worked things out,
but I don't know.
Maybe there's a lesson here.
You pick these
unattainable girls,
you pine away
silently for years.
And maybe that's easier than
being in a real relationship.
- I know you assume everybody
needs your lifestyle advice,
but I'm actually good.
- Fine.
Ignore me like you always do.
Even though--I don't know.
Maybe as the older sibling,
I would have some wisdom
to offer.
It's fine.
[rumbling]
- You know what do we need?
We need a singalong.
You guys remember
"Sweet Baby James"?
"Thong Song"?
We love the "Thong Song."
- Oi, Gary.
- Take a seat.
Look, I know that
the Fountain's real, mate.
Come on, old soul,
give it up.
- Okay.
Aliens have known
about the Fountain for age.
And once, I even found a lead
in your library,
but anyone who's gone
after it has ended in ruin.
You know, so I only lied to you
because it's too dangerous,
especially without your magic.
- I don't need the likes of you
to protect me
even without my magic.
Just--just tell me
where to find it, Gary.
- Okay.
There's a map for the
Fountain of Imperium out there,
and humans could never really
figure out how to read it
because they thought
it was a map of the heavens.
But aliens, we know
it's a map of your planet.
- So you're telling me
that I could be out there
right now
searching for this map,
but thanks to you,
I'm stuck in a bloody saloon?
[rumbling]
[roaring]
- Oh, no, that can't be good,
but the town's that way.
- I know a way
we can cut him off. Follow me.
♪ ♪
- Hey, speaking of magic,
you guys like card tricks?
- Ooh, that--that sounds
like fun.
- [laughs]
[laughter]
- No.
- Babe, look, I know that was
hard for you to watch.
But look at me now, right?
I'm fine.
- I know you're still you,
but seeing it in action
I don't know, made me realize
we can't just pretend
that everything's normal,
you know?
I was talking to Gary
and I just--
- Why are you talking to Gary
about this
before you're talking to me?
- I wasn't talking to--
- Guys, have a drink.
- God, what is
with the cherries?
- I don't know, okay?
- Just stay out of it.
- Guys, guys.
- First you're mad I'm lying,
now you're mad I'm
telling the truth?
[overlapping arguments]
[rumbling]
- Annoying!
[overlapping arguments]
Enough!
Can't you just hold it together
till we get the job done?
I mean, I don't know
what's harder,
finding the alien or keeping
the peace between you people.
- Um, Nate, the worm, remember?
Just do you want
to simmer it down.
[rumbling]
- You know what?
I won't simmer it down.
I've been having a lot
of big feelings too, lately.
Now's the exact right time
to share them.
When Mick left the ship,
it wasn't easy being
the O-est G.
But did any of you check in
on my existential crisis?
No. Because Nate's so chill,
isn't he?
- Yeah, you're right,
we should talk.
But maybe not
while the worm's coming.
- I used to have Zari
to talk to, right?
And while all of you are
hooking up getting engaged,
I guess she's just stuck
in a totem forever.
No offense,
I think you're great.
It's not really
an either-or-thing.
And don't get me started
about life on the ship.
Six roommates
and I'm the only one
that replaces the cartridges
and the fabricators.
- I didn't know
they took cartridges.
- Well, they do, genius.
They do!
And I know one of you
changes the thermostat
every night,
so don't blame it on Gideon.
Well, since none of you
can hold it together,
I guess I'll draw
the worm to me
so you don't get eaten alive
because I'm so chill.
So come and get me,
you alien slug.
I got your romp right here.
- That white boy's a goner.
- Spooner, you have
to do something.
You don't know what it feels
like when they get in my head.
So get into theirs. Let them
feel what you're feeling.
Don't do it for me,
or for Nate.
Do it for you.
- And another thing,
I asked for a chair
in the Hall of Justice,
big surprise, no response.
[roaring]
- And this is where
my plan stops.
[roars]
- Stop!
- That's right,
it's my power now.
- It's Reeves!
[gunshots]
- Dig?
- Yes, ma'am.
I definitely do dig.
Bass Reeves. Glad to see you
could join the fight.
[roaring]
- I can't--I can't hold it
much longer.
[roaring]
- I got you.
Tua cutis fiat ignis.
[roaring]
- Ha.
- Oh.
- We did it.
- No.
- I feel so much better.
- Me too.
- Huh?
[cheering]
- Gary.
- Whoo!.
- Now that is better.
- This whole place looks
better.
- How are you even able to
keep your head down here?
Worm would have gotten
me in a minute
if I was stuck
with these people.
- Well, I was plenty angry.
But I decided that these folks
want to underestimate me
well, I'll just use it
against 'em.
That's how I've put most
of these bastards away.
- You made it your power.
- You see? This one gets it.
[playing guitar]
- You're probably wondering
what happened
to that band of outsiders.
Well, from what I heard tell...
♪ They cleaned up the town ♪
♪ Got it back to itself ♪
♪ There was beer at the bar
and poker hands dealt ♪
♪ They got on their ship bein'
sure that no one seen 'em ♪
♪ And the only fights left ♪
♪ Were the ones between 'em ♪
- You here to shallow me
with pity, Gary Green?
- No. I, uh--
I know how you can get
a map to the Fountain.
♪ ♪
Shouldn't be much trouble,
actually,
'cause the man who found it
lives in your attic.
- Aleister Crowley.
- If anyone can find
that Fountain
and live to tell of it,
it's you.
So I'll be seeing you,
John Constantine.
- ♪ Well, the magic man's
heading off for the unknown ♪
♪ Bid his lady goodbye
then he set off alone ♪
♪ She told him she trusted
that he'd dodge any doom ♪
♪ Now what of the captains,
well let's their room ♪
- [sighs]
- Hey.
- Hey, babe.
- Made you something.
- Thank you.
I think my normal appetite is
finally starting to come back.
- Good.
- But this does look good.
- Well, dig in.
- Mmm!
You know what, I think
I've been trying way too hard
to pretend that things
around here could be normal.
- Babe, we both were.
- Right? Ugh.
- I wanted so badly
for everything to just
feel like it was before.
But after everything we've been
through, there's no going back.
- But does that
have to be a bad thing?
Maybe we can be something new,
something better.
I mean, let's be honest,
we were never normal
to begin with.
So why start now?
- [gasps]
- What?
- Was that--
- I have no idea
what you're talking about.
- Passion Dragon Ash.
- Yes.
♪ ♪
- I saw John on his way out.
You doing okay?
- Yeah. Trying.
- Well, I'm here
if you need me,
but I know you'll be fine.
You're the wise one, after all.
- Okay, look, I know I can be
a bit overbearing at times,
but I just want you
to be happy.
- Hey, I actually know who
could use both our help.
Can I borrow your totem?
Yo, yo.
- Hey, man. Want a donut?
- Thanks, dude. But I actually
came to give you something.
- No, no, no, no,
I cannot be a totem master.
Maybe with some training,
but there's--
- No, no, no, it's so you can
visit her, so you can see Zari.
- That's possible?
- I'm sure it's been tough
and I should've noticed,
but now you can take
a totem trip to her
and do what you do together.
Just let me know
when you're done.
♪ ♪
- ♪ Now the Guy of Steel's
off to see his girl ♪
♪ Sure it's weird,
but then so is the world ♪
♪ So I leave you
with that takeaway ♪
♪ That there might not be a
normal but that might be okay ♪
- [sighs] I told you guys, we
can't keep the cowboy narrator.
- Sorry! Sorry.
- Hey, man, we'll drop you off.
- Happy trails, Legends.
♪ ♪
- Greg, move your head.