[Sara] Previously on
Legends of Tomorrow...
- How did you do that?
- How did I do that?
Remember when we dented history?
By building Heyworld,
we changed the future.
[Nate] What you think of as a haunting
is a temporal echo.
She is the you before.., you.
[Charlie] Sara, no.
My sister...
[gasping]
-[Atropos] You can't kill me.
- No!
I'm a god.
[grunts]
We're being hunted
by a pair of bloody gods.
This situation just got
a hell of a lot more dicey.
Behrad, he's dead.
Can that Loom bring him back?
If we get the last piece, yeah.
[harp playing]
[Charlie] Oh, there you are.
It's always the artsy types with you,
ain't it?
How many times must I tell you
my powers are not a tool
for your amusement, Clotho?
[Nate] Wait, wait, wait.., time-out.
But you did look different at the time,
though, right?
[Charlie] Shapeshifter. 'Course I did.
But it makes the story easier
to imagine, if you just picture me.
- Yeah, just pay attention.
- Yeah, yeah.
Anyway, then she said her magic word...
Enchantress.
I imagine this has something to do
with your theft of the Loom of Fate?
You disapprove?
No.
Humanity's status quo should be
shaken up every few millennia.
It's good for them.
Well, I'm glad you think so,
because this is a pretty big shake-up.
I need to make sure
that no one ever finds this.
Not even me,
and especially not Lachesis.
- You think you can do that?
-[Agent Sharpe] Question.
- La-who?
- Lachesis.
She's my older sister
and also the leader of the Fates.
Now, she's a real master manipulator.
Atropos kills because Lachesis wills it.
It is you, Clotho,
that has the difficult task.
What, running and hiding?
I am relieving you
of a piece of the Loom
that has been your entire reason
for existence.
Now, that you are free of it...
it will be up to you
to determine what, if anything,
is left of Clotho in its wake.
All I need is to make sure that
that ring is never found.
Existential actualization
can come later.
You cannot run forever, Clotho.
And that's the last thing I remember.
You have no idea
what spell Enchantress cast?
That would defeat the whole point
of goin' to her, now, wouldn't it?
Charlie, all we need is the third ring
to bring Behrad back.
And now, you're telling us
it's impossible to find?
Maybe you could have mentioned that
before your sister got on the ship.
See, this is exactly the kind of thing
I was afraid would happen.
Stop!
Passing blame
is not gonna help anything.
I'm sorry, Z.
This Enchantress is a witch, right?
Well, we have...
whatever it is you are.
So, do some hocus-pocus
and find the ring.
Yeah, well, it's not as simple
as finding Atropos' ring, love.
Locating something hidden by someone
as powerful as Enchantress,
that can take months, maybe even years.
I don't accept that.
Behrad is gone and he's not coming back
until you find the ring.
So, figure it out, magic man.
Fast
[knock at door]
Hey.
You know,
I'm here for you if you ever
want to talk about Behrad.
We're getting him back.
There's no point in dwelling on it,
because everything's going to be fine.
Totally.
By the way, when I went on
that totem journey thing...
I met the other me.
Really?
How.., how is she?
She's great. Tough, cool...
You must have a thing for warrior women.
Only if they're from another time period
and eventually will leave me. Sure.
[Nate clears throat]
Did she have a message for me?
No.
But I can tell
she really cares about you.
I really care about her.
And just so you know, I, uh...
care about you, too.
Oh, all right, lovebirds,
look, I think I've got something.
Now, it won't be pretty,
but it might just work.
So, come on. Chop-chop.
[sighs]
[Charlie] Sara! Are you there?
Hey, Sara!
Sara?
- You all right?
- Yeah. I just, um...
It was nothing. I'm good.
Listen, you got hit full-force
with the power of Atropos.
- Yeah?
- I know you survived,
but there still could be repercussions.
Charlie.., look, I'm telling you,
I'm completely fine. All right?
Assassin's honor.
Fine.
[Constantine] All right, you lot.
Listen up.
Lachesis' ring could be anywhere
in space and time.
I'm going to need to borrow a little bit
of magical energy off you lot
to help amplify the summoning spell.
- Exactly how does that work?
-[Constantine] That's easy.
All you need to do
is keep your mouths shut
and let me use your auras
like batteries.
- Is this safe? It doesn't sound safe.
- It isn't.
Any more questions? Good.
Let's hold hands.
[reciting invocation]
- Whoa. This feels weird!
-[Gary] It is weird.
Kinda like that time
we went mushroom picking.
Focus, or you'll botch the bloody spell!
[Constantine reciting]
[gasps]
- Sara!
-[Constantine] Focus!
[reciting]
[Zari groans]
[classical music playing]
Where is everyone?
[Constantine sighs]
Wait. Something happened.
Oh, bollocks.
When everyone lost focus,
I had successfully
bound the ring to the house,
but I was still working
to anchor it temporally.
So, you, me and the ring
have been whooshed into the past?
Good work.
It's magic, love.
It's more of an art than a science.
[gasps] Oh, my, are those guests?
I didn't hear the bell ring.
Well, hello! I'm Mrs. Hughes.
I'm so sorry to keep you waiting.
Oh, no bother, love.
This is a lovely.., boarding house.
You know,
I could see myself living here.
Now, wherever did my etui get to?
Is it that?
[gasps]
Thank you, my dear.
I would have found it eventually.
Sometimes, one just needs
to stop looking.
-[chuckles]
- Right, totally.
Oh, is that another guest already?
It is, indeed.
Doctor White at your service.
Were you two
going to book a room, or...
Right you are. Yes.
Me and my wife here--
Oh, we're not married. [chuckles]
Well, I'm afraid I'm a bit traditional.
I don't allow single women
to stay in my establishment.
But we are engaged. Yay!
My sincerest congratulations!
- Please sign here.
- Oh, yes, of course.
And you will be in
room number three, upstairs.
Supper is at 8:00, sharp.
All right, thank you. Mr. White.
Huh. You know, you should take note.
This place can actually look decent
with a bit of TLC.
See what a difference a nice set
of curtains can make?
Yeah, all right. Now, let's take stock
of our situation, shall we?
Now, I'm assuming you can wield
the totem like Behrad.
Mm-mm.
I'm just holding onto this for him.
I don't have a superpower.
- Unless you count having flawless brows.
- I don't.
Oh, and by age 15,
I built a social media empire
valued at over 500 million dollars.
The New York Times called me
the most influential influencer
-of my generation.
- Oh, The New York Times, eh?
Yeah, it's, like,
an app that tells you the news.
So, your superpower
is that you're sort of popular?
Oh, calling me "sort of" popular is like
calling da Vinci "sort of" a genius.
Great. Got it.
What about you?
What exactly do you do,
besides wear the same outfit everyday,
and screw up spells?
I've banished demons, slain dragons
and walked through the fires of Hell.
I'm a sneaky bastard and
the greatest sorcerer that ever lived.
Cool, cool, cool. Do you wanna go ahead
and "sorcer" something
so, we can find the ring
and get out of here?
- Hmm. Yeah.
- Yeah.
Okay. So, does that mean it's in there?
Yeah, it seems so.
This is the doctor's room.
Maybe you could, uh, "influence" him out
while I go check it out?
Mm. See? You need my skill set already.
Yeah, all right. Good luck.
[clears throat]
[Zari clears throat]
Can I help you?
[coughs]
I seem to have come down
with something, Doctor.
Might you be able to give me a checkup?
Of course. I'd be happy to help.
Please. Come in.
Perhaps we could go down
to the sitting room.
I am a newly-engaged woman, after all.
I understand. One moment.
[Scoffs]
Ah. Hmm!
No ring?
We're still looking for one.
And you arrived with no luggage,
if I'm not mistaken.
[Zari] Couldn't wait to get away
from the city.
Yes, I could see why your betrothed
would want to get you to himself
as quickly as possible.
- You have a beautiful face.
- Oh, thank you.
- I moisturize.
- It's not like my face.
No one remembers my face.
Huh.
You know, you could, uh, look into
getting a rebranding specialist.
I'm afraid your case is worse
than I thought.
I must insist we return to my room
for a more thorough examination.
Oh, my gosh. Look at that.
No more cough! [laughs]
You're a real miracle worker, Doc.
You should just stay here, relax,
have a drink. And I'm gonna...
Okay, bye-We-
Ew.
John?
John!
It seems we did end up
in my room, after all.
Shall we begin the examination?
[White groans]
[neck snaps]
John, you killed him!
'Course I did.
He's Jack the bloody Ripper!
Behind you!
[gasps]
Blimey!
Old leather apron here
must be an Encore.
Hand me some rope now, will you, love?
Cheers.
[Gideon] Captain Lance is experiencing
unusual activity in the striatum,
a region of the brain
that processes time.
I'm continuing to run tests
to determine the cause.
So, Atropos not only killed Behrad,
but also managed to put Sara in a coma.
I don't think the team's gonna survive
another run-in
with your sister, Charlie.
If we had it my way, we never would've
run into her in the first place.
[Gideon] Pardon me, but Dr. Heywood
and Mr. Green are requesting
your presence on the bridge.
The Prognosticator is showing
unusual Encore activity.
Hey.
You got this, Captain.
Right...
"Captain."
All the Encores are moving through time.
More specifically, they're all heading
towards a particular point.
- Looks like they're hunting something.
- Or someone.
Astra must have sent
the Encores after John.
Gideon, pinpoint
where and when they're converging.
See, guys? I knew all my time spent
creating the Prognosticator
would be worth it.
- Ava Sharpe saves the day again!
-[Gideon] I'm sorry, Captain.
It appears that
the Prognosticator is not equipped
to handle time-traveling Encores.
[grunts]
Ava, take a deep breath.
You know what, we don't even know
if Sara's gonna wake up.
And if she does, she's going to find out
that two of the Legends are missing.
This is beyond unacceptable.
Let's just sit down.
I'll bring you a cup
of your favorite herbal tea--
[grunts] I'm not just gonna sit around
and do nothing.
If we can't track the Encores,
we have to go after them
at the source... Astra.
I seriously doubt she's just gonna agree
to stop doing whatever
her current evil plan is.
That's why I'm not going
to give her a choice.
Nighty-night, Jackie-boy.
Sweet dreams of disembowelment
and all that jazz.
What the hell, John?
[sighs] Astra must have sent him here
after me.
You know, not everything is about you.
Well, it'd be a big, bloody coincidence
if an Encore just happened
to show up in the same time and place
as us for no apparent reason.
Okay, fine. But I thought
you and Astra had a deal.
Clearly, she got impatient, all right?
Yeah, I know the feeling.
Did you find the ring?
It wasn't in his room. Now something
is interfering with my magic.
Yeah, some great sorcerer...
Ooh, some great influencer.
You could barely keep him
distracted for ten minutes.
Oh, I'm sorry, should I have
let myself be serial killed,
so, you would've had five more minutes
to not find the ring?
You know what, we should split up,
so we can both find this in peace.
Fine by me, sweetheart.
[entry bell rings]
- Howdy, ma'am. My name's Clyde Barrow.
- And my name's Bonnie.
[Clyde] And we're in need
of some accommodations.
Bloody hell. They're all Encores.
All right. While I'm down there,
you two need to work on
fixing the Prognosticator,
so we can track down Zari and John.
Well, tech is not really--
Charlie!
Sure. We'll figure it out.
Um, I feel like somebody has to ask you.
Are you 100% certain
you want Gary to take you to Hell?
I was kinda wondering the same thing.
Look, Gary is the only wizard
I have access to.
And besides, I'm not only
taking Gary down there.
I'm gonna need some extra muscle, too.
Well, thank you for noticing
the extra reps
- I've been putting on the lat machine.
-[Agent Sharpe] You ready, Mick?
- Oh.
- Mic:k,
I thought you were taking
some time off to hang out with the kid.
She told me to go to Hell.
Where are we headed?
The portal to Hell is ready, Captain.
All that's left is for...
me to drink some of this demon blood.
- Come on, Gary.
-[Gary] Yeah.
Ugh.
- Oh. It's actually quite tangy.
- Okay. How do we do this?
I will say some words, and then
the sigil will transport us to Hell
for precisely four hours.
After that,
we'll be transported right back here.
Sounds good to me.
Enter.
"Flesh become my flesh.
Soul become my soul.
Hades, firstborn of Cronus and Rhea...
I call upon you."
All right, Mick,
get ready to light it up.
[weapon whirs]
- Beer?
- Yeah.
[Gary] This was a terrible idea.
Should have worn
shoulder pads to blend in.
[Mick] I like it. There's fire.
Let's just find Astra.
About time we killed the bitch.
No! John has been working so hard
to rehabilitate her.
Also, I thought we didn't use
that word anymore.
You know what, I'm gonna let the B-word
slide this time.
She sent a bunch of criminals
after our friends.
How do we even find her?
What are we supposed to do,
just ask a random demon off the streets?
-[gasps]
-[weapon whirs]
- Where's Astra?
- She's at her club.
Uh, it's two streets down, make a left.
Wow. I didn't expect that to work.
Thanks, Micky!
Oh, it's times like this that
I wish I hadn't given up smoking.
Yeah, well, I wish I had brought
my own hairbrush.
Guess we're both out of luck.
Why would Astra send
so many Encores after me?
I mean.., seems like overkill.
Again, maybe it's not all about you.
What if they're after the ring?
You know, I never told Astra
about the Loom of Fate,
but you might be onto something.
[clock chimes]
Oh, look at that. Suppertime!
[chuckles] You're not
seriously suggesting
we go dine with Hell-people?
I'm seriously suggesting that
you stay here, while I handle it.
I'm part of this,
and possess far superior social skills.
Yeah. Well, you bottled it
when Jack the Ripper attacked.
Look, I can't look after you
and figure out what Astra's up to
at the same time.
This might be Behrad's totem,
but there is a little warrior me
inside here
from a different timeline,
and she's gonna protect me.
I don't even know what to say to that.
But I Will say this.
Even if I have to tie you up myself,
you're staying here.
-[thudding]
-[White grunting]
[recites invocation]
What are you doing?
Well, I can't exactly go out there
as John Constantine now, can I?
I think I have an idea.
Clyde and I were tortured
by Manaxos the Mutilator himself.
Your pain was a mere trifle compared
to what the Norfulthing did to me.
And I thought the Hellhounds
were the worst evil a man could suffer.
Who exactly are you
that you were worth Norfulthing's time?
[Henry VIII]
I am, of course, King Henry VIII,
ruler of the British Empire.
And what crime sent you to Hell?
-[Bonnie] Hmm...
- We rob banks.
[Black Caesar] And I plunder boats.
You may have heard of me.
The name's Black Caesar.
Caesar?
Ah, and you must be Brutus.
I always favored beheadings
over stabbing someone in the back.
Less cowardly.
Supper is ready!
Now, stop dilly-dallying
and come and have a seat,
before the food gets cold.
[rock music playing]
[bouncer] Excuse me, Miss Astra?
I found this scum
lurking by the entrance.
"Lurking" seems like an overly
sinister way to describe--
Why are you here, twerp?
John Constantine is outside.
He knows you're impatient with him,
but he has the thing he promised you.
But he doesn't want to come in here
and risk being seen.
So, if you could take a quick break
from eating bugs, and come with me--
Waste my time,
and I'll let my demonic friends here
use you as a human pinata.
[Gary gasps]
So, that's where Genghis Khan's
sword went.
It's over, Astra.
We know you sent your Encores
after John, so, don't play coy.
What the hell's an Encore?
It's what we've been calling
the corrupted souls that
you've been sending back to Earth.
I haven't sent a single "Encore" back
to Earth since John and I last spoke.
- Kill her already.
- Good idea.
[Gary] Wait, Ava!
What if she's telling the truth?
Come inside and I'll prove it to you.
Ah, just in time.
Oh, I love a good carving.
[Henry VIII] And who the devil
are you supposed to be?
I, my friend, am Jack the Ripper.
You've got quite the reputation, Jack.
- Join us.
- Cheers, mate.
My mistake, sugar.
I would have noticed if the ring
was sitting directly in front of me.
So, we are all here for the ring.
I don't share me treasure
with anyone but me crew.
We've been set up.
I assume that we all have
the same deal, yeah?
The ring in exchange
for free reign on Earth.
It would appear,
we're in direct competition.
So, then what the hell are we doing
eating dinner?
Oh, that's a bit on the nose,
isn't it, Bruty?
Just so we're all on the same page here,
each one of us has a Hell weapon,
and we could well and truly
end each other right here, right now.
Clyde, the way I see it,
this here Jack the Ripper,
is our greatest competition.
Yeah, I think you're right, peaches.
Jack here never was
caught by the police.
[Zari] Greetings, subjects.
I am your Queen, Cleopatra.
Yes, I see.
They're very big and impressive.
That's not what I came here for.
Great, you all have scary weapons.
Now that we know that,
is it really necessary for everyone
to get cramps in their arms?
You, of course, remember Brutus?
Yes. Of course.
"It was not that I loved Caesar less,
but that I loved Rome more."
We never had
the chance of meeting before.
But I would have thought my murder
of your lover would be unforgivable.
Damn skippy. Kill him!
I'm not a petty despot
ruled by past grievances.
I'm a strategist.
The most sensible thing to do...
is to work together.
As soon as one of us finds the ring,
it's off to the pits for the rest.
You're just gonna accept that?
As soon as we have the ring
in our hands, we have all the power.
We can march right into Hell
and demand our freedom!
Hey! Hear, hear to that, eh?
All right.
Now, let's eat. Okay?
Okay.
[rock music playing]
So, where's the lughead?
Rory is guarding our exit,
and he's enjoying some entertainment.
Yeah, I'll definitely be seeing
that one again down here.
Oh, you're no fun.
Now, this is where I keep
all my soul coins.
And as you can see, they're all right--
Did you lose something?
No one with an "executive privacy"
button has good intentions.
My vault is empty.
Besides me, you're the only one
with access, Tiberius. Care to explain?
Is this one of those human pranks?
You had me take them out
for you last week.
Like hell I did.
I swear it, I saw you myself.
A shapeshifter. Damn it!
[grunts]
[gasps]
[thud]
Oh, don't look at me like that.
He'll be fine in a few hours.
Better, even, 'cause he'll have learned
to be less gullible.
At least
the most valuable one is still...
Who the hell is Vandal Savage?
- Oh, I actually know that one. He's--
- Shut up!
I can't believe she did this to me.
Wait. You know who stole your coins?
Yeah.
But she is...
too powerful for me to take on.
Okay. What if you had backup, you know?
"Enemy of my enemy" sort of thing.
Fine.
But this will require stealth.
Wakey-wakey.
The boys stay here.
Now, that was influencing.
You really think
there's a saint's chance in Hell
that your truce is gonna hold?
May I remind you
that one of them is ruddy Brutus!
Sorry, was that some weird
British-y way of saying
-"Thank you for saving my life, Zari"?
-[chuckles]
Yeah, okay. All right.
I was in a bit of a pickle.
I admit it,
but may I suggest that we use
the few minutes that you bought us
-to go and look for the ring?
- Shh.
[gun cocks]
Sorry about this, hon.
Please, don't.
Don't be scared.
"The evil that men do lives after them,"
and all that.
So, who's this being we're going to see?
The woman
who found me terrified and alone
when John left me to rot down here.
She took me in, raised me,
taught me how to make it in Hell.
Wow. And now she's betrayed you.
She was the one person
I thought I could trust.
Everything I am, I owe to her.
You know, I don't know if that is
some sob story or what, Astra,
but I know how you feel.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I think it's a pretty specific story.
Yeah, well, I had a mentor once.
The guy's name was Rip.
I trusted him with my life
until I found out that
he fabricated all my memories
to make me good at my job.
That's awful. So what did you do
when you found out, did you kill him?
Ooh. [chuckles]
I wanted to so bad.
But, you know,
the one thing that I learned is...
the only way to keep going
is to take control of your life.
Stop letting everybody act like
they know what's best for you
and make your own choices, you know?
What the--
[Agent Sharpe scoffs]
So, it was a sob story, after all.
No, it was the truth.
Thanks for the therapy session.
Don't have too much fun
without me, boys.
I'll be back soon.
Show me the treasure I seek!
[compass chimes]
That compass must have
some sort of Hell powers.
He's using it to track the ring.
- Okay, then we need to get the compass.
- All right. I'll grab it.
Hey. I'm going with you.
All right. Follow me.
[exclaims]
[Zari clears throat]
Hey.
[chuckles] Well, that was
bloody convenient, wasn't it?
I tried to fight them. Just like Rory.
You folded like
a cheap deck of cards, you bum.
[grunts] Easy.
It's okay, Gary.
I totally got played by Astra.
On the bright side,
there's not much time left on the sigil.
We'll pop back
to the Waverider soon enough.
Um, about that...
I'm the one who cast the spell.
So, I'll pop back to the Waverider,
along with anyone who's touching me
when the time runs out.
I'm sorry.
- Didn't I mention that?
-[both] No!
Listen, you dweeb.
I gotta get out of here. I got a thing.
What thing?
Lita has a soccer match.
She didn't invite me,
but I'm inviting myself.
Sorry, ROW-
And I refuse to die here
without getting to know my daughter.
Do we understand each other?
- What position does she play?
- Gary.
[sighs] Hold on,
we were here just a minute ago.
John, we are going in circles.
Yeah, it seems like it's not just
my magic that's wonky in this place.
Magic or no, there's so many people
looking for this ring,
it should've turned up by now.
It's like [sighs]
it doesn't want to be found.
Hold on a minute,
you might be onto something.
"Sometimes you just have
to stop looking," right?
Why would we stop looking?
Because I'm beginning to suspect
that the spell on the ring
is of a particular breed.
So, if you want to find the ring...
you can't find it.
[chuckles]
You've gotta hand it to Enchantress,
she is a crafty one.
Okay, it's not just gonna
slip our minds. So, what do we do?
We drink.
I know what you did, Lachesis.
- Who's she?
- Astra, my dear,
I'd like you to meet my sister, Atropos.
I've wanted you two to meet
for quite some time now.
Your sister?
We've worn many faces in our long lives,
but we are family.
Anything you need to say to me,
you can say in front of her.
I know you stole my soul coins.
Of course I did. I had to.
Astra, they were becoming a distraction.
You'd amassed all this power
for what? Parties?
Gambling?
- You need to think in grander terms.
- Much grander.
You see, Astra, my sister and I...
are two of the three Fates.
The Loom of Fate belongs to us.
It is our birthright.
- Why.., why didn't you tell me?
-[laughs] You weren't ready.
Oh, Astra, making soul coins
and using them to control
the denizens of Hell
was a cheap reflection
of my former glory.
Now, that the Loom of Fate
is within reach...
I want you to become one of us.
Become our third sister.
You'd have the power of a god.
Astra, this is what
I have been preparing you for
ever since I took you in
as a young girl.
But what about my mom?
John had promised that
he'd use the Loom of Fate
to make it so she never died.
Astra, you need to move beyond
these petty human desires!
I am offering you the power
to design destiny.
You once sought to rule over Hell...
Now, you can rule over the whole cosmos.
Will you join us?
What do you say, girl?
Trust me, Astra.
I know what's best for you.
Sister always knows best.
Of course, I'll join you.
How could I ever turn down
so much power?
Good girl.
There's just one thing.
John Constantine's coin.
He's mine to toy with.
Seems like a fair trade.
[sighs]
[Bonnie] I took care of Brutus.
And I got our pirate friend, Caesar.
Any luck with the ring?
Damn thing might as well be invisible.
Well, Bonnie, guess we got no choice
but to make the rest
-of our fellow guests disappear.
- Mmm.
-[thudding]
-[grunting]
Now, what do we have here?
Another Hell-ian to kill?
Lucky us.
- I'm Jack the Ripper.
- Nice try.
We already met Jack.
That Jack's an imposter. Worse...
- It's John Constantine.
- That liar!
He must be here to send us back to Hell.
Now, don't lose your temper, Bonnie.
We'll teach that grifter a lesson, okay?
[sighs deeply]
Good old Mrs. Hughes.
Okay, I'm not thinking about the ring.
I'm not thinking about the ring.
Yeah, that's not gonna work.
So, you're just gonna accept failure
when we are this close?
I'm not giving up.
Oh, I don't see it as giving up,
so much as...
accepting reality.
I know myself.
I'm a ripe old mix of guilt and torment.
If the Loom of Fate offers me
even one glimmer of hope
of redemption for all my past sins,
particularly Astra, then...
I'll never not be thinking about it.
You know, it's funny,
I'm usually an expert
at getting things out of my head.
Boyfriend cheating on me
with my assistant/best friend?
No time to cry,
I have a fall fashion line to plan.
Overhearing my mother tell a friend
she's embarrassed
her daughter is so shallow
and self-absorbed?
Definitely can't process that,
I will check my Cat-Chat analytics.
But my baby brother dying
because he was trying to protect me?
There is nothing that can get that
out of my head.
I was wearing the totem when he died.
If I hadn't been, maybe he...
Maybe he would have had a chance.
[sniffs]
Look, you can take it from an expert...
[sighs]
Nothing good ever comes
from beating yourself up, love.
Don't try to make me feel better.
John.
What if we don't find the ring?
What if I never get him back?
[Clyde] Yoo-hoo!
- John friggin' Constantine!
- We know who you are,
and there's someone here
you'll be just dying to meet.
They do say imitation
is the sincerest form of flattery.
[breathes heavily]
This passage leads outside.
I'll distract them while you escape.
- No, come with me.
- Go.
This is my house
and I'm just crazy enough to defend it.
And listen...
you can get Behrad back, Zari.
I truly believe that. But unless
you get out of here right now,
then neither of you stand a chance.
Okay.
[sighs]
Ava, I'd just like to say,
you're the best boss I've ever had.
Well, the only boss I've ever had.
I'm more apprentice
than employee with John.
And before the Bureau, well--
Ah! Finally, you've come to kill us.
About time. I was getting bored!
[groans]
[Astra] Get out of here.
Astra, what made you change your mind?
You're helping John
find the Loom for me.
Might as well let you.
Either he'll come through,
or Lachesis is bound to.
Did you say "Lachesis"? The Fate?
Wait, how do you know who--
It's a small underworld after all.
- Time's almost up!
- Come with us.
- What?
[Agent Sharpe] Astra, it's time
for you to take control.
Don't wait for them.
You can help us find the Loom
and save your mother yourself.
Ten seconds left!
The choice is yours.
Wait, did she ever channel an animal
while you were, you know...
She did once.
But it was...
- Is that...
- Meet Astra.
Why does she have the sword?
There's no time to explain.
We got to move.
Where's the ring, John?
I don't know where the ring is.
And even if I did,
I wouldn't tell you muppets.
John. John, be reasonable.
We are going to kill you, regardless.
But it's up to you
how painful that death has to be.
[chuckles]
You'd be surprised how long
you can stay alive without...
certain organs.
- You want your coat back, don't ya?
- Mm.
You can all go to Hell!
Hmm.
Stop!
Cleopatra?
Yes.
I order you to stop.
You don't have
that kind of power here, honey.
Are you both serious? She's with him!
Is that so?
Maybe this will make you talk.
I don't know
where the ring is, all right?
Funny, I believe you. What a shame.
- Cheer up, darlin'. We can kill him now.
- Mmm.
- No!
-[totem howls]
[Clyde grunts, gasps]
[Bonnie screams]
[recites invocation]
You come back--
-[grunts]
-[Bonnie gasps]
[bell rings]
[gasps]
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
Blimey.
What?
The bloody ring.
[chuckles] Must have been here
the whole time.
I guess I stopped thinking about it.
Guys! We're here to save you!
But, uh...
it looks like you took care of that
on your own.
Thank God. Please tell me
that you found the ring?
We did. Thanks to Zari.
- Fantastic.
- Good.
Wait a second. Are those Hell weapons?
Yeah.
We could use those, especially--
Yeah, let's just get them
and get out of here.
- Good morning!
-[all gasp]
Are those even more guests?
Oh! Um, no.
So sorry, ma'am, we were just leaving.
And, uh...
here's me thinking
you weren't allowed to meddle anymore.
You could've been a touch more direct.
I'm sure I don't know what you mean.
[chuckles] Yeah. Right.
See you around, John Constantine.
So, you got the totem to work?
Yeah, I did. It was amazing.
Terrifying, but amazing.
And I sort of felt like
Behrad was there with me.
He'd be so proud of you.
I'm so proud of you. Congratulations.
[Gary] John!
You're safe!
All right, Gary. Oh! Okay, all right.
Calm down, all right?
I'm happy to see you, too, mate.
Hey, how's Sara doing?
Oh, she's still unconscious.
Charlie is sitting with her now.
I'm gonna try to distract myself
by fixing the Prognosticator.
Technical skills aren't
Charlie and I's strong suit.
- I know.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, hold on a tick.
If that contraption is broke,
how the hell did you find us?
Uh, about that...
Hey, John.
I hear we have a Loom to build.
[theme music playing]