[gentle music]
- Hm.
♪ ♪
- Is this your plan, old boy?
Force me to watch you
smack your lips together
like some sort of blonde ape
until I tell you
when I stashed the map
to the Fountain of Imperium?
It won't work.
I offered
to be your partner once,
and you locked me in
a ruddy chest with that witch.
- That's right.
Mmm.
Mmm-mmm.
- Oh, you filthy,
uncouth scoundrel!
- Now you're gonna tell me
where the map is,
or I'm gonna desecrate your
painting with my bodily fluids.
- Just get this
lump off my face!
- Okay.
- I entrusted the map
to a banker to hold on to
until my eventual resurrection.
- All right then, partner.
What's this banker's name, eh?
[doorbell chimes]
Noelle, I presume.
- Constantine.
- Hm.
- Aren't you going
to invite me in?
- You're a vampire.
It's best you come in then.
- Where's Aleister?
- Don't worry about him.
From now on,
you'll deal with me.
- You have my 2 million pounds.
- 2 million quid.
Bloody hell.
How much interest
have you been charging, Vampy?
- [hisses]
- All right, all right.
Calm down, don't get your
knickers all in a knot.
See, I'm offering something far
more valuable than dosh, love.
A favor.
- What could you
possibly do for me?
- Spare your immortal life,
for one.
One word and sunshine
will turn you to ashes.
- Clever.
- Hm.
I'm John Constantine, love.
Clever doesn't even begin
to describe it.
Now hand over what you were
holding for Crowley
and you can be
on your merry little way.
Go on.
Set it on the table.
- Now that you've invited me
in, mon cher,
I can come back
anytime I want.
- [chuckles]
- I have magical runes powerful
enough to keep out worse
than the likes of you,
sweetheart.
- Aleister's as well.
A little potion
I procured for him.
One day, you might get
a taste for it.
One day,
you might be positively
gagging for the stuff.
- Crowley, you sneaky wank.
[exciting music]
♪ ♪
- ♪ Lullaby and good night ♪
♪ With roses bedight ♪
♪ With lilies o'er spread ♪
♪ Is Gussies's wee bed ♪
♪ Lay thee down now, rest ♪
♪ Let thy slumber be blessed ♪
♪ Lay thee down now and rest ♪
[triangle chimes]
- Sleep tight, little buddy.
- [snoring softly]
- Superhero, a totem bearer,
and an alien named Gary
becomes singing mannies.
Did I just invent our spinoff?
- Are you recording
because Sarah and Ava
asked for constant updates?
They don't think
we can survive one weekend
without them, do they?
- Listen, I just want them to
look for their wedding venue
without dealing
with these dummies
- [screeches]
[suspenseful music]
- ♪ Lullaby and goodnight ♪
- No more singing.
I can't take it anymore.
That little snot's not crying
'cause it's tired.
It's got growing pains.
- Well, he does not
look any bigger.
- [snarling, clicking]
- He said the Gusarax life
cycle is only 38 rotations.
- Uh, what does that mean?
- Yeah, I can see where
this is going, new Zari.
- Technically, I'm--
I'm the original, sorry.
- The OZ.
- The one and only.
- Yeah, I'm not
translating for Gary
just because he lost
his glasses.
And I'm definitely
not helping y'all parse
Gus's every gurgle.
If I wanted to take care
of a baby,
I would have stayed in Texas
and married the first jerk
I kissed.
- Yeah, she's really got that
new girl on the ship vibes.
- Leeching human souls
wasn't quite enough for you,
was it, Master Crowley?
No, no, no, no.
You were juicing.
- What a crass term.
I was reaching
for new mystical heights
aided by a rare cocktail
of bloods.
- You absolute tosspot.
You know as well as I do
that magic this powerful,
it comes at a terrible,
terrible price.
- It's because of that potion
that you have the map.
In 1939,
I took a rather large dose
and fell into a trance,
where an extraterrestrial
dictated the map to me.
Pity he didn't speak English.
I might've discovered
where in the heavens
the Fountain was hidden.
- Yes, the heavens.
You see that's where
you were going wrong.
My alien mate, Gary,
he reckons
that the Fountain of Imperium
is somewhere here on Earth,
lost to history.
And this cut-out is the key.
Let's see.
Should fit exactly.
Spain.
That's where the Fountain
was in 1939.
- Take me with you, John.
We're partners now, right?
- Skip it.
I've got a new partner in mind.
- You know, I have other skills
besides being
an alien telepath.
Couldn't literally anyone else
help you with Rory's
brood pooch instead?
- Please.
It'll just take a second.
- [groans]
- Okay, amazing.
I should warn you though,
my dad hasn't really
wrapped his head around
the whole pregnancy thing.
- Men can't get pregnant!
Or didn't they teach you
that at college?
- Dad, a year and a half ago
in my past,
which is your future,
you ceased all contact.
Okay, if you really have
Kayla's eggs in your skull,
then maybe they'll give a clue
to what will happen.
- Ever seen the movie "Alien"?
Yeah, I think we know
what will happen.
- Spooner, please.
Just look at the protrusion.
Have a seat.
- [grunts]
[groans]
- Ay Dios mio.
- Oh-oh-oh, what sordid scene
am I interrupting?
Never mind.
Don't care.
Spooner, join me for a shot
and a chinwag.
Good luck with that.
Long story short, I have been
stripped of my magic in service
of transforming you back
from a fork I might add--
- Okay, what do you want me
to translate, John?
- A map for the Fountain
of Imperium,
which according to my research
is a wellspring of magic
gifted to humans
by aliens long ago
and last seen in Spain.
- Whoa.
This is--this is cool.
Only those whom are worthy
may drink from this fountain.
- That's typical
prophecy malarkey.
I need a location.
- All right, well, this
main star here is Albacete.
- Albacete.
- Mm-hmm.
- That's a city
in the southeast of Spain.
[light dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Well, seeing as we're
in Spain, February 1939,
there's a few things
you ought to understand.
Now, first and foremost,
this country has just suffered
three years of a brutal
and bloody civil war.
- Civil war? When were you
planning on telling me that?
- I just did, and a class war
is more like it.
You see, on one side,
you have the rich
and the military
backed by Nazi Germany.
On the other side,
you have the trade unions
and the democratically
elected government of Spain.
And don't even get me started
on the devious little role
of the Catholic church.
- I'm Catholic, John.
- Yeah, well,
then you'll understand
my attitude towards priests.
I'd sooner rather break bread
with a bloody demon.
- Okay, well, nothing
on here says Fountain.
- What about El Gato?
- The cat?
- Oh, no, no, no.
It's the code name
to a leftist leader
that I've heard stories about.
Apparently, he survived
seven assassination attempts
and one actual crucifixion.
- So?
Maybe he was lucky?
- Lucky?
Nobody's that lucky.
That's magic.
My guess, El Gato
drank from the Fountain.
- Well, if you want
to find a man,
why don't we just ask
at the local watering hole?
- Hm.
[lively music]
♪ ♪
- [speaking Spanish]
- The bar is closed to
outsiders.
Especially fascist spies.
- Are you taking the mickey?
Do I look like
a bloody fascist?
- You look like a German?
- He has a point.
- No, he doesn't.
I'll have you know
that I served
with the POUM militia
at Jarama.
- You were in the trenches
of Jarama?
- I was.
- What did you
grease your rifle with?
- Oh, you mean
the rusted antique
that they supplied me with?
I had to grease it
with olive oil.
Water was in such short supply
that we had to shave with wine,
which is a bloody shame
if you ask me,
but the worst part
was the lice.
Those evil buggers
they were as--
- As big as boils.
- As boils, yes.
- Compadre!
[laughter]
Let us toast to our
fallen brothers in arms, huh?
- Yeah.
- Gideon said John and Spooner
took the jump ship to Spain,
so I thought theme night.
One slice of Tortilla Espanola
for the senorita.
- Are you sure
you should be drinking?
- Yeah, why?
- Hey, I for one
think it's really cool
that you're pregnant.
- The next person
that says pregnant,
I'm taking 'em with me
on a nose dive outside
the emergency hatch.
- Wow, real mature, dad.
So what's your plan?
You're just gonna pretend
this isn't happening?
- That's exactly
what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna pretend Kayla
didn't do this ear stuff to me
without warning me first.
- Well, you didn't
give mom a warning.
Niko and I
didn't plan our baby,
but we're dealing with it.
- Oh, guys, Gus-y is
aging rapidly.
He's like a teenager now.
- Okay.
- No-no, a-a hormonal,
giant teenager.
[loud snarling]
- Come on.
Vamonos!
Pregnant people, stay.
You're pregnant.
- Amigos, the International
Brigade has already left.
Why are you still here?
- We heard of a man
who continues to fight
the fascist bastards.
He goes by the name
of El Gato.
They say he can't be killed.
- I also have heard
of this man, El Gato.
Very mysterious.
- Do you know his secret?
- Mañana, mañana.
It's late.
I have to turn in.
- Come on, mate.
Indulge me, yeah?
- My cousin told me El Gato has
drunk from a magical source.
- Oh.
- Hm.
- What kind of source?
- In the village over,
there's a donkey
with great big--
how do you say?
- Udders.
- Ah, sí.
Magical udders.
- Oh.
- The milk makes El Gato
impervious
to even a hail of bullets
from the fascist scum.
- Well, to the donkey.
- Hey, salud!
- Adios.
- Magical donkey?
- I don't know.
I don't hear a load of crap
like that these days, yeah.
- Agreed. And that man we were
talking to, he was El Gato.
- Undoubtedly.
Probably came down from the
mountains to get some supplies.
- Yeah, you clock
the old farmer?
- Yeah, looks like he was
guarding something, perhaps--
- A door to the cellar
around back.
- With the Fountain below,
yeah.
[light suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
[mystical shimmering]
- Mm, yeah, something alien
is down here all right.
And it's powerful.
[indistinct chatter]
- Hey, it's all right.
It's okay, it's okay.
Ah, La Torrera.
Yeah, yeah,
looks like you, love.
- Oh, very funny, John.
- What's your name, lad?
- Cómo te llamas?
[mystical shimmering]
- Fernando.
- Fernando?
The alien power's
coming from the kid.
He's mute, but I can hear
what he's thinking.
- He must've drunk
from the fountain.
- Hm.
[vehicle engine rumbling]
John.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- [speaking Spanish]
- Corre!
- Good evening.
My name is Capitan Noriega.
I have news from the front.
Madrid has fallen.
The Republic is done.
I've been sent not
just by General Franco,
but by the great
Herr Hitler himself
to hunt down a man
known as El Gato.
You see, this man has drunk
from an occult relic
of immense interest
to Herr Hitler,
the Fountain of Imperium.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Sounds like Herr Hitler
believes in fairy tales.
- You could say my specialty
is fairy tales.
The Spear of Destiny,
the Loom of Fate,
I've studied them all.
Before the night is over,
I will know El Gato's secrets.
- Hm.
I don't know where this
El Gato is,
but I have a lead
on a magical donkey.
- Search him.
Line everyone up and shoot them
one by one until he talks.
[light dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- I'm the one you're
looking for, eh?
- Spooner, Spooner, no!
Bollocks.
- Oh, I know exactly
who you are...
- [groans]
- [people gasp]
- El Gato.
[dramatic music]
- Fernando...
♪ ♪
- [groans]
- [gasps]
- Gracias.
- At last.
Here is the key
to the Fountain.
- No.
Search the rest of the tavern.
Arrest everyone.
[thunder rumbles]
- [groaning]
Bollocks and bloody bollocks!
Come on, Johnny, think.
Think, think, think,
think, think, think.
You can't leave her there.
You can't leave--
[church bell ringing]
[groans]
[ringing continues]
- That's it, Gus,
the gloves are coming off.
- Watch out.
- Oh, you messed up now,
hombre.
- Gus-Gus has continued
to age at a rapid rate.
I'm afraid the Legends
are quite outmatched.
- Should we do something?
- They'll be fine.
[groans softly]
- What is it?
- Nothing.
- Is it your head?
- So?
- So what if this is it?
What if Kayla's eggs
burst out of that thing
on the back of your neck
and kill you?
We need to get you
to the med bay now.
- Not gonna happen.
- Why the hell not?
- 'Cause I deserve it.
- What are you talking about?
[gentle music]
♪ ♪
Dad...
what are you
talking about?
- Kayla didn't disappear.
I left her on a planet
full of lizard people to die.
- Oh.
Well, you must've
had a reason, right?
- Hm.
To get back to you.
But in my line of work,
there's a code.
You never leave your partner
behind, and I did.
- Ooh.
- I deserve everything
that's coming my way.
- Oh, Dad,
I'm going into labor.
- What?
- Yeah.
- [muffled screaming]
[Spanish ballad playing]
♪ ♪
[muffled screaming continues]
[thinking in Spanish]
- El Gato has become
quite chatty.
He tells me you're his nephew.
Fernando,
it's your turn to talk.
- He can't.
He's mute.
- Hm.
We'll see about that.
Tell me the location
of the Fountain,
or I slash her throat.
Hm?
[pounding in door]
- Buongiorno.
Ciao, signores.
I am father Constantine, and I
have orders from the Vatican.
- Mi scusi.
Mi scusi.
I have been sent to by several
senior cardinals of Roma
to track down an ancient
and powerful relic.
- The Fountain of Imperium?
- You know of this relic?
- Herr Hitler is also
after the Fountain.
- Eccellente.
Then we will work together.
- I was just about
to question the boy.
- Please, Capitan, allow me.
[Gus snarling]
- Man, what are you doing?
You gotta get Lita back inside.
- She's having a baby!
- Oh, baby.
- I need to get her
to the med bay!
- Tarazi siblings.
- Activate.
- [groaning]
- Come and get it!
- [snarling]
- Gus.
Again!
- [snarling]
- Oh.
- Gideon!
- Okay, Dad, wait.
I'm so sorry.
- For what?
- I'm not actually in labor.
I just needed to get us
to the med bay
in case you were in labor.
But I might have misjudged
a little bit.
So sorry.
- You tricked me.
- It's 'cause
she loves you, Mick.
We all do.
- No, debatable.
- Everyone out.
- We'll see you at the next
doctor's appointment, okay?
- Out!
- ♪ Dei gratia,
neccesitudo inter duos ♪
I am conducting
a sacred ceremony
creating a telepathic gateway
between this child
and this virgin.
- Your methods
are extraordinary.
- Indeed.
Grazie. Grazie.
Now, where is
the Fountain of Imperium?
- [thinking in Spanish]
- Un dia el año pasado...
- One day last year,
my mom left me with my uncle
to go to the Front.
That night the planes came.
Suddenly everything
was burning
and full of smoke and dust.
- Nunca había
visto tanta sangre.
- I'd never seen so much blood.
A bomb had exploded
next to me,
so I ran as far
and as fast as I could.
I hid in a cave and prayed
for some way to save my uncle.
He was next to me
when the bomb blew up.
- Apareció un precioso ángel.
- A beautiful angel appeared
and told me
to drink from the fountain.
And that's when I felt it,
the power.
I returned to my uncle
and healed his wounds.
- Oh.
Yes, sí sí.
And he has been bringing his
uncle back to life ever since.
- Where is this cave?
- Some water, per favore.
- Forget the water.
The cave!
- Ah, but captain,
I am parched.
Grazie, grazie.
And now you can ask him.
[mystical whirring]
[thinking in Spanish]
- I don't know.
I was lost for days.
- Unacceptable.
- You know,
there is one thing
that I never understood
about the fascists.
What is it that you see
in Herr Hitler, hmm?
Is it that he's a pissant
with one ball?
[screaming]
- Viva la Revolución.
- Save Fernando!
- Come on, let's go.
Spooner!
Spooner, the door!
- John, we have to go back.
- What?
Are you mental? Why?
- The fascists will
kill everyone.
- You know what happened in
the Spanish Civil War, right?
The moral side, it didn't win.
Now get the boy
to lead us to the cave.
Oh, come on, I know you were
bloody lying, all right?
- Yeah, well,
I'm not helping you
finish your ridiculous,
selfish quest.
- Quest? This is real.
My connection to magic is lost.
- Boo-hoo. What's so bad
about being normal?
You don't think that kid
would give just about anything
to have a normal life again?
I know I would.
- Yeah well, some people want
picket fences and ponies,
don't they?
- Oh yeah.
And what do you want?
You want me stay here
and risk my life
so I can help you
get your magic back.
Give me a reason.
- You know where I'm from,
being normal is being crushed
by the boot of capitalism
and then blaming it
on anyone with brown skin.
It's being told
that only degenerates
can fancy men and women.
It's your old man
coming home drunk every night
and beating you to a pulp
because that's what
his old man done to him,
but magic, Spooner,
the ability
to break the rules,
to stick it to the rich
and the powerful,
that's who I am.
And I'm nothing without it,
Spooner. I'm nothing.
[mumbles]
- I can't believe
I'm saying this.
All right, John.
You win.
[speaking Spanish]
- The fountain's dried up.
- Esta aquí.
- He said that's where
the water came from
that the angel gave him.
- This is just a bunch
of bloody rocks!
Bollocks!
- Okay, ease up, John.
- All right,
all right, just--
just give me
a second, all right?
All right, all right.
Now here's what we do.
You know, I told the captain
that I was forging
a connection
between the two of you.
Now that connection
is very, very real.
Now, you can use it to push
Fernando's magic into me.
All you need is
a clear intention.
- Okay, wait, so you want me
to help steal Fernando's magic?
What happens to him?
- No, no, no.
This is a way to
protect Fernando, yeah?
You know, give him a normal
life away from all the Nazis
chasing him
and the alien powers.
- Don't pretend for an instant
you care about Fernando.
Vete al diablo.
- All right. Okay.
Yes, I am the wankiest of all
wankers, but do me a favor.
While I go and check to see
that no one has followed us,
you talk to Fernando.
He can give his magic to me
or he can keep it.
Now that's his choice, innit?
[gentle music]
♪ ♪
- Hombres, más rápido.
Rápido, rápido!
They can't be far off.
- Esta seguro?
- Sí, sí.
- Anyone?
- No, no, all clear.
- Fernando wants
to make a deal.
- Smart play, kid.
What's your price?
- He gives you his powers.
You use them
to help find his mom.
She was supposed to return
to the tavern.
I told them she's probably
not going to come back,
but he doesn't
wanna believe me.
- Done.
- John, I hope
you thought this through.
No, the kid's
made his choice.
Sit down, yeah?
Good boy.
- All right, what do I do?
- Now, all you need to do
is
focus your alien connection
on the boy,
and you focus quickly, yeah?
- Yeah, I'm no wizard, John.
- Oh, aren't you?
So I haven't seen you stop
a giant sandworm
with your mind, have I?
- Hm.
- Exactly.
[light suspenseful music]
[mystical whirring]
- [groans]
I can't.
- Look, magic, you know,
it's all about connection,
all right?
Now, I use words
to focus my mind.
Do you know any quotes?
- I mean, there's a stupid song
stuck in my head.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, that'll do.
It's not about
the words, per se.
It's more about the intention.
Now, remember, you're giving
this kid an opportunity
that you never had, the chance
at a normal life, all right?
You can do this.
- ♪ Lullaby and good night ♪
♪ Red roses bedight ♪
[mystical shimmering]
♪ With lilies o'er spread ♪
♪ Is Gussies's wee bed ♪
♪ Lay thee down now and rest ♪
♪ May thy slumber be blessed ♪
♪ Thy slumber be blessed ♪
- Whoa, whoa,
where's it going?
Where's it going?
I could feel it.
It was right here.
It was right--you give me back
my bloody magic!
- Hey, John.
- Give me my magic.
- Stop, John!
The prophecy.
The prophecy said.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Only the worthy may drink
from the fountain.
- [speaking Spanish]
- You take the boy and hide.
- What are you gonna do, John?
- Only a bastard
could vanquish a monster.
Go.
- [speaking Spanish]
- Bottoms up, Master Crowley.
- Father Constantine.
Where is the Fountain?
I won't ask you again.
[dark music]
[eerie singing]
♪ ♪
- Dios mio.
- [laughs]
♪ ♪
[laughter]
- [screaming]
[music distorts]
[groaning]
♪ ♪
[squelching]
- John.
[gentle music]
♪ ♪
- I'm relieved to announce
Mr. Rory is not in labor.
- Okay, so what about the pain
in his head?
- Perfectly normal
considering 48 Necrian eggs
are rattling around
Mr. Rory's skull.
- 48?
[bright music]
♪ ♪
- Hmm.
Tough little guppies,
aren't they?
- Yeah, but they get
that from you.
- Their mom was tough.
- I'm sure Kayla would be
really happy to know
you're taking care
of her babies.
- She would?
- Yeah, because they need you
to survive just like I do.
- Oh, I found my glasses
and Sara and Ava are back
- What'd we miss?
- Oh, Look at their
itty bitty tentacles.
- Oh, Micky.
- Are those...
- Mine.
- John, what happened
back there?
I saw you drink something.
- Ah, it's just
a nifty little trick
to stop a Nazi numptie
from getting the better of us.
But don't worry, Texas.
I won't be drinking it again.
Truth be told, it scared
the living hell out of me.
- Good.
I mean, me too.
Look, wait.
We don't know
what we'll find in there.
- Fernando.
Ay-ay.
- Tío.
- Thank you.
[thunder crackles]
- No, Spoons, listen,
we failed, all right?
Spain is not gonna be safe for
Fernando, not for a long time.
And I'm just
as ineffectual
as my dear old grandad
fighting bloody fascism.
- That's not true.
You killed a lot
of Franco's soldiers.
- Yeah, I did.
And I bet at least
one of them wasn't a bad bloke
and once again,
my soul is damned.
- You know,
for someone who hates church,
you sound an awful lot
like a Catholic.
- What, just because I'm like
full of guilt
and self-loathing.
- You know,
my mama used to say--
never mind.
- No, no, no, no, no.
What about your mama? Tell me.
- She used to say,
"Somos salvodos
solo po la fe."
We're saved by faith alone.
It's funny, I've--
I've forgotten her face,
but I can still remember
the sound of her voice.
We were both abducted,
and only I returned.
I should have been more like
Fernando and--and refused
to give up on her,
but I lost faith.
- Spoons,
you live on a time ship.
It's never too late, love.
- [snoring]
- Is that painting
of Crowley snoring?
- [laughs]
- Shh.
- [snoring]
Wakey, wakey, Crowley.
[dark music]
John.
- To have magic back, Spooner,
it's worth it.
It's worth the risk.
- Don't do it.
I'll tell Zari.
- No, you won't.
Praeterita obliviscere.
You'll go upstairs
and you'll sleep it off.
Tomorrow you'll return
to the Legends.
You'll tell them
we were successful.
I drank from
the Fountain of Imperium.
- Yes, John.
- My stars. I take it
you didn't find the fountain.
Are you--are you juicing, John?
- Jokes on you, dickweed.
- Is that so?
- Bonsoir, gentlemen.
- You brought what I asked for?
- Oh, and you can take him.
He's yours.
- John, what have you done?
No.
Please, John.
You don't know who
she'll trade my soul to.
- And what a lucrative trade
it will be.
- Get him out
of my sight, will ya?
- Until next time.
- No.
Damn you, John!
Remember all your trials
and tribulations
you only have yourself
to blame.
[door slams]