[dramatic music]
- But I just killed you.
- It's a delicious
little mystery for you
to turn over
in that pretty little head,
isn't it, Sara Lance?
- No, you're dead.
- You're not the only one
who's flirted with death.
- How?
- ♪ You'll never guess
in a billion years ♪
- You're a clone.
- Okay, yes.
You got it.
- Just like the AVAs.
- No.
No, not like the AVAs.
Different.
There's only one of me.
One at a time.
We're all just coding, Sara.
DNA can be mapped and cloned,
and each and every data point
in our brain can be mapped
and cloned.
- You can recreate yourself,
body and mind?
- The mind is just impulses,
synapses, and memory.
No different from any computer.
Look, science has evolved
quite a bit
beyond your comprehension.
You're like a caveman to me--
or like a monkey.
Or like a cave monkey.
- Imagine
what you could've done
if you used that knowledge
for good instead of this.
- I am using it for good.
I am restarting
the doomed human race,
and you will see that
eventually.
[weapon whirs]
You will see it my way in time.
♪ And you've got nothing
but time ♪
♪ Because no one's coming
to save you ♪
♪ ♪
[heroic music]
- You drank all the booze.
- Not my fault
you couldn't keep up.
- I can only hold two glasses
at a time unlike you
who can hold eight with your...
tentacle things.
- Or you're just a lightweight.
- Oxygen mask.
- Atmosphere's Earth-like.
Bishop's terraforming
the place.
As long as you don't go past
his electrostatic barrier,
you'll be fine.
- What if Sara's
past the barrier?
- Then she's already dead.
Air out there would kill
most creatures,
and you don't want to meet
the native ones
who could survive it.
- You seem scared.
I'm not scared.
I'm smart.
Let's go find my ship.
- Then we find Sara.
[soft dramatic music]
[low growl]
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
[quirky string music]
[doorbell rings]
- Oh, what the?
- That's-a me-a.
- Oh, oh.
- Hello there, 12 pizzas
for a Ber--oh, Bernard, uh...
- 12 pizzas, really?
- No fabricator.
Gotta plan ahead, right?
[deliver man stammering]
- Really don't think
Gideon's gonna appreciate
being installed
on a cathode-ray tube
from 1974, John.
- Well, TV rots your brains--
oh, cripes, I'm hungover.
- At least you can track down
aliens so we can do our job
until Rory returns with Sara.
[electricity crackles]
Ow!
Um, is anything in this room
by chance flammable?
- I need some bloody tea.
♪ ♪
What the hell is this, eh?
- The anti-alien
security system.
You know those greenies
are gonna try
to make a move on us here.
We'll be ready.
- Oh, that's who took my tea
then, is it?
- Zari said they make
a good skincare treatment.
No, I got these roadside
caffeine pills though.
- [sighs, snorts]
- Stay off the black tiles!
Unless you like
pumiliotoxin-tipped darts.
- Great.
♪ ♪
Zari!
- See, names and nomenclature
imply we aren't all
the same organism,
living and breathing as one.
- So I'm also Behrad Tarazi?
- Everyone is, and they aren't.
- Oh, bruv.
[guitar chord]
- Johnny!
This guitar is sick.
Can I pluck
a little "Stairway"?
- Oh, yeah, yeah.
Sure, mate.
Yeah, you and your Legend
cohorts can do anything
you like here apparently.
- Ah, thanks, gorg.
[playing guitar]
- Grant me the flame
of knowledge.
Ooh!
Making progress.
- That's great, love.
That's really great.
You carry on.
Go on.
[groans]
My head.
- Oh, John-John.
- Oh!
They've turned this place
into a bloody insane asylum.
- I know, let's go out
and find you some breakfast.
Black pudding, baked beans,
and bubble and squeak?
- Oh, I love bubble and squeak.
- I know.
♪ ♪
[tracker beeping]
- [sighs]
The thing's in rough shape,
and it needs
a whole new fuel cell.
Damn it.
My mother got me that ship
for my 300th rotation.
- Where's Sara?
- Judging by the presence
of that trooper,
she's already captured.
[dramatic music]
- Time for a chat.
Here.
♪ ♪
[weapon whirs]
Drop it!
Where's Sara?
- I need backup.
- Ava?
Clones.
- [grunts]
♪ ♪
- [groans]
Little help here!
Scared, huh?
- Not scared, smart.
[ship whirs]
- Hey!
I was gonna steal that.
[electricity warbles]
- Thank you, Captain Sharpe.
It's good to be back.
[electric guitar feedback]
What is that noise?
- Just the sound of everybody
trying to get comfortable here.
So any time anomalies?
What do you got for me, Gideon?
[electric static, warbling]
- Yes, it seems there was
a massacre by a patient
of the alien variety
at Endless Meadows Asylum
in 1956.
- Perfect.
Anything to keep my mind
off Sara's rescue mission.
- Um...
- "Um"? What's "um"?
Gideon, you don't "um."
- When admitted
to the hospital,
the patient gave
the name Sara Lance.
[guitar crashes]
- I'm okay!
Don't tell John!
[exciting music]
♪ ♪
- According to records,
the patient flew
into a manic episode
during a procedure,
causing the massacre.
Victims were found with sting
marks and exploded hearts.
- We never meet
the chill aliens.
- No. Okay.
So we need to find out
what it knows
and why it's using Sara's name.
- We should probably
also make sure
this thing doesn't kill
a bunch of people.
- Right.
- You could--
and please believe me,
I am not trying to get you all
massacred--
bring it back here.
- Mm, speaking purely
as a house guest,
is bringing a rampaging alien
back to John's house
something we should run by him
first?
- No.
Definitely not.
[dramatic music]
- You know, sanitariums,
not really my thing.
- [sighs] Keep that antenna
going, Spooner.
Let me know if you get
any weird vibes.
- Oh, I got weird vibes.
♪ ♪
- Welcome!
Checking in your wife?
Hysteria or the blues?
- Oh, no, we're here
to pick up my sister.
- Yes, she used
the name Sara Lance.
- Oh, yes, of course.
She was in a frenzy when she
arrived and had to be sedated.
But don't worry,
she's scheduled
for a very effective electric
shock treatment later today.
- Fantastic.
That must be what set her off
to kill.
- Yeah, I'm getting some weird
alien vibes behind those doors.
♪ ♪
- We are just glad
we have someone here
who can give us the real story.
She said that she flew here
in a spaceship.
Could you imagine?
[chuckles]
Sara!
Your brother is here.
Don't be alarmed.
Sometimes she goes by
different names in the moment.
Mary Pickford, Marion Davies.
Her favorite though
is Amelia Earhart.
- Yes?
♪ ♪
Are we going somewhere?
- Could you imagine
if it was the real Amelia?
She'd be 60 by now.
What's her secret, am I right?
- Yeah, what is her secret?
♪ ♪
- Oh, nice one, love.
You know, I thought I was gonna
go batty in this mad house.
What in the bloody blazes
has happened now?
Astra!
- [grunts]
- Shh!
- Who's that woman on my telly?
Is that Amelia Earhart?
- It's an alien shaped
like Amelia Earhart
that also uses
the name Sara Lance,
and she's also totally
knocked out
on some pretty gnarly
'50s 'ludes.
So we're waiting to see
if she's gonna freak out
and try to murder us
when she detoxes.
- Did you guys eat
all the gluten-free mushroom?
For the record, Captain,
this plan is stupid.
Look, I say we go right
in there and talk to it.
Yeah, that's right,
turned a new leaf.
Maybe I'm not a shoot first,
ask questions kinda gal.
- Huh.
- Nice.
- That's great, Spooner.
You're working on yourself.
I am impressed.
- Yeah.
Why just splat them
when you can find out
their deepest fears
and exploit them?
- Hm, Spooner,
now I'm impressed.
- That was dark.
B, why don't you and Spooner go
and play a little bad cop,
Behrad cop,
and see if we get
this Amelia talking, hm?
- I like your style, chief.
- What?
- It's gonna be fine.
Trust me.
- Well, I'm off.
Something about watching
a prisoner interrogated
makes me nostalgic for
the good old days back in Hell.
- [sighs]
Please, just--please, please
tell us where Sara is.
- Are you spying on me?
[sighs]
There, finally alone.
What the--
[sighs]
[groans]
- [grunts, groaning]
[panting]
I finally found you!
I searched through every
sewage pipe in the facility.
- Wh--oh, eugh.
You were in the pipes?
- Yeah.
You ever seen an octopus
squeeze through a hole?
My body's like that.
Necrians take great pride
in our scrunching.
Too bad you can't ride
the pipes with me
because I discovered
where the fuel cells are kept.
We could fly Kayla's ship
out of here.
- Gary, get back in that toilet
and get the fuel cell
to the ship.
I'll find my own way out.
Can I count on you?
- I'm your man.
Alien man.
♪ ♪
Happy trails.
[flesh squelching]
[toilet flushes]
- Rise and shine, Mia.
- Baby steps.
Maybe we can get you
those easy-wake lamps.
For now, there's tea.
- Tea?
- We're taking this
nice and easy.
- Where am I?
- You're at Shady Acres.
It's the chillest sanitarium
there is.
- Okay, Spooner,
are you picking up
any alien brainwaves?
- No.
I mean, there's something going
on, but it's still too quiet.
I'm thinking she's still
feeling the Quaaludes.
♪ ♪
- Oh, don't mind her.
We're just here to ask you
a few questions.
- What kind of questions?
- Easy ones.
- Do you ever get the urge
to freak out and attack people?
- What she meant to ask is,
why do you use the name
Sara Lance?
- Sara Lance.
Doesn't ring a bell.
I don't think
I like you very much.
♪ ♪
You're not very nice.
May I have some more?
- Say, how did you end up
at Endless Meadows?
- Wish I had an answer for you.
Last thing I remember I was
soaring over the Pacific.
Me and my navigator Fred
almost done our flight
around the globe.
- That does sound
like something
the actual Amelia Earhart
would say.
- Or she's just
a very good shapeshifter.
- [chuckles]
- [sniffs]
- Well, the important thing is,
you're back in one piece,
right?
- Don't know if I can say that
about my plane back.
- She's gotta be talking
about the pod.
- Right?
- Yeah.
Hey, hey, find out
where its pod is.
- Do you remember
where you landed it?
- Landed it
right by my old house,
37 Locust St, Rye, New York.
- I love when aliens give
exact addresses.
- Yeah, okay,
keep it calm and friendly.
We're gonna go check out
the pod.
- All right,
there are the cells.
Now all I need
is a distraction.
[splashing sounds]
[chuckles]
Idiot.
Biggest in the galaxy.
[sneaky music]
♪ ♪
Intruder by the cells!
- [grunts]
- Whoa, whoa, whoa!
- Oh!
- Hey, stay where you are.
Hey, you're the freak
that ate D Squad.
Put it back.
- I have regrets about that.
I just need one little battery,
and then I'll be--
- [laughs]
Damn, those clones are handy.
♪ ♪
- We're getting
a radiation reading,
but I don't see a crash site.
- It's gotta be around here
somewhere.
If it can help us get Amelia
to talk,
then maybe we can get an idea
of when Rory and Sara
are coming back, right?
- Then do I hear wedding bells?
[wall gongs]
No...
[vehicle beeps]
[heroic music]
♪ ♪
Amelia Earhart was talking
about the Waverider?
That's impossible.
- Sara, are you there?
Rory?
Sara?
- Hey, Bishop!
[clears throat]
Yoo-hoo!
♪ Hey, man, whatcha doing
out there? ♪
♪ Wanna come chat,
if you dare? ♪
- I love it!
Oh, it thrills me to see
you're in a good mood.
- I am, and you know what?
I have been thinking.
- Uh-oh.
About what?
- You.
I can't deny the fact
that what you've done here,
it is astonishing.
- Oh.
- And I didn't want to admit it
at first,
but it's true.
You are humanity's best hope.
[quirky music]
- Can I just say, thank you?
For seeing me.
- I do, and I want to be
a part of it.
- [gasps]
[grunts]
So I'm hoping that we could
just put the past behind us.
- Put the past behind us.
I am listening.
I am interested.
- Well, I can forget
about the fact
that you imprisoned me,
if you forget about me
snapping your neck?
Bygones?
- Bygones!
I couldn't have said it better
myself.
I love this new turn of events.
- ♪ I love it, too ♪
both: ♪ Ooh, hoo, hoo, hoo ♪
- [laughs]
Tonight.
We'll make a fresh start.
Dinner at 8:00?
Choose something groovy
from the wardrobe.
- Of course.
Oh!
But it might be kind of hard
to get dressed with these.
- Oh.
Yeah, of course.
[laughs]
Aw.
Oh.
- Oh!
- Whoa--oh!
[laughing]
- Oh, you.
[dramatic music]
- Me and my navigator Fred
almost done our flight
around the globe.
- I thought the tea was herbal.
- I may have snuck a few
caffeine pills in there.
At least she's not
freaking out, right?
I can try to read her mind more
when she settles down.
- I blacked out.
Strangest plane I've ever seen,
and then--
You can never know what
a person is really thinking,
even if you open up
their brain.
- That is technically true,
Amelia, yes.
- [laughs]
♪ ♪
- Just keep her calm, right?
She's under no threat.
- You!
Drop the pretense
and start talking.
- Whoa, I thought we weren't
supposed to rile up
the residents.
- She stole the Waverider!
She's from the planet
where Rory took the ship.
- I wouldn't do that.
She's pretty awake now.
[whirring]
[grunts]
She's definitely awake.
- How the hell
did you get our ship?
Tell me
where Rory and Sara are, huh?
Where the hell is Sara?
- [growls]
♪ ♪
[growls]
[groans]
- Get tranq'd, greenie.
- Weird, she looks
like a human again.
- I mean, it feels
like a human, too.
Like, I know that's an alien,
but I just can't sense it.
- Well, she knows where
Mick and Sarah are,
and we don't,
so we need to get it talking.
- There is a spell I used
on an uncooperative person
to rip a memory
they didn't wish to share.
I've only done it on humans
though.
- Okay, fine, but we'll do it
back at the Waverider,
where Gideon can help us
if anything goes wrong.
[bangs on TV]
- Splendid.
- But first, I would like
to enlist the services
of my new apprentice.
[soft dramatic music]
[clears throat]
- What?
[mellow music playing]
- This cannoli...
would make God himself weep.
It is perfection.
- Oh, I'm so happy to hear
you say that, sir.
Here you go--oh!
Sorry.
I owe you everything.
- Mmm, sugary carbs.
One of the true pleasures
of having replacement bodies
to spare.
- Uh-oh.
Sir, AVA troops from sector 12
have apprehended an intruder.
His name's Mick Rory?
He seems to know Sara Lance.
Apparently,
he's very belligerent
and maybe intoxicated.
- Terrific.
It's a rescue attempt.
He doesn't know Sara
has joined us.
We're gonna have to take down
the barrier.
♪ ♪
- Sir?
- Just for an hour.
That'll let in enough
toxic atmosphere
to kill anything living
out there...
♪ And we'll be safe and sound
in here ♪
- But sir, there--sorry.
The troopers are still
out in the field.
They've already apprehended
the intruder, so we can just--
- How do you know he's alone?
- I don't.
- I'm not risking it.
Don't worry.
Your clone sisters
are well-trained.
They'll survive.
Or, you know, be replaced.
[snaps fingers]
Lower the barrier.
♪ ♪
[barrier powers down]
Good girl.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Keep moving.
- [growls]
- Huh?
Are they lowering the barrier?
- Is this a drill?
- No, it's real.
- [coughs]
- Have fun choking to death.
♪ ♪
- Now?
Mm-mm.
I am not dying on this planet!
- When you mine the depths
of another psyche,
you need to move swiftly
and deliberately.
- A little space, John.
- If your concentration
wanders, distracted
by some fleeting memory
of an ancient alien world,
then you'll do irreparable
damage to her mind and yours.
- The only person distracting
me right now is you.
- Apologies, love.
Yeah.
- I can do this.
Got the greatest magic tutor
in the world.
- Seems like a big deal.
Why don't you just handle it
yourself, John?
- Yeah, no offense, Astra,
but if this can go badly,
I'd rather the expert do it.
John?
- No, no danger, none at all.
How else is Astra gonna learn,
anyway?
- All right, showtime.
Tortured mind
with secrets hidden,
show me that which is
forbidden.
♪ ♪
[gasps]
Feels like
a real Amelia Earhart memory.
She's setting off on a journey
around the world.
The thrill of defying the odds.
- I'm confused.
It's an alien, ain't it?
Well then, shouldn't its memory
be about its home planet?
- In the clouds,
she's perfectly free.
Then a bright light,
unconsciousness.
- [groaning]
- She's on an operating table
against her will.
They're experimenting,
altering her.
She's escaped.
She's ostracized.
She doesn't know.
She's alone, intensely alone.
She does what she can
to survive.
- [grunts]
- Where's Sara?
Astra, we need to know
if she's seen her.
- Listen, this creature,
Amelia, she's exhausted,
and we should end this
right now.
- John, we need to know.
- She has a visitor.
Sara Lance.
- Did you say Sara?
Is she okay?
What is she doing?
- [groans]
- I'm trying--
there's some sort of divide
in her memories--
a firewall I can't cross.
- Push through, Astra.
Please, we need more.
- [groans]
- I'm trying to push past.
♪ ♪
[grunts]
Fighting.
Slashing, anger.
Bound, breaking free,
anger, hunting.
Hunting!
- [growls]
- Sever the link.
Sever the link!
- [screams and growls]
♪ ♪
[shrieks]
- [shouts in alien language]
♪ ♪
- Seal it off!
Seal it off!
- [growls]
[alien growling,
objects crashing]
[soft dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Word to the wise:
Gideon's Mezcal
is high grade toilet water.
- I never drink it.
Mezcal, I mean.
Or toilet water.
You seem down, bad cop.
You wanna talk?
- Look, you don't wanna
be friends with me.
It'd make killing me
that much harder.
- So you've figured out
my secret plan
to murder all the Legends?
- No.
That thing started out human.
Something took it out,
and now--
- Hey, Spoon,
you're not like Amelia, okay?
We did the scans.
- I spoke its language today.
I've never done that before.
My powers have been growing
ever since I joined y'all.
What are you gonna do
if I don't just talk
like them anymore?
What if I start to fight
like them?
Sting like them?
- Let me tell you a secret.
It's the only way I survive
in this job.
Don't think about your past,
and don't think
about your future.
You have to live in the now.
I know it seems crazy to say
in a time machine,
but the past and the future
don't really exist.
There's only right here
and right now.
- Thanks, B.
- Oh, and word to the wise:
Gideon's blueberry Kush is...
- [growls]
Spooner...
[thunder booms]
[rope creaking]
- [grunts]
[grunts]
Suckers.
[banging on door]
- [gasps]
- [growls and chitters]
- Wait a minute.
You're that thing
that ate D squad.
Let's get him!
- Stop!
He's a hero.
He saved my life.
- I'm so sorry about D squad.
No matter how delicious
they were.
But I never would have
knowingly eaten an Ava.
You're the most remarkable
women I've ever met.
The Ava I know,
she's a great leader,
has amazing hair just like you,
and still has time
for her one true pairing, Sara.
[quirky music]
- AVAs lead?
No, AVAs serve.
- You don't have to.
I served her.
- [gasps]
Oh, she must be
a great leader
to have a great servant
like you.
- Well, I wouldn't say
I'm the best assistant,
but...yeah.
- [sighs]
- Is Astra okay?
Seemed like a lot
for a beginner.
- She'll recover.
- What about you?
Are you okay?
John, you know you can talk
to me.
- [sighs]
I'm sorry, love.
It's just that, you know,
they nearly destroyed my house.
There's dart holes
all over the plaster.
Nate rendered my guitar
practically unplayable.
I'm sure that it's afflicted
by some tone-deaf banshee.
- Okay, enough.
I know you wouldn't have put
Astra in that position
if you could've done it
yourself.
I may not know magic,
but I do know people.
- That's just not even
remotely true.
You know, I am in complete
command of all of my power--
- Oh, give it up, John.
She knows.
Oh, you're not gonna tell her?
Fine, I will.
John owed me, and I was tired
of playing second fiddle,
so I took the lead.
- Right.
So everything is
perfectly normal with you?
- Everything is
perfectly normal with me.
- [murmuring]
- See?
And what good would
John Constantine be
without magic, eh?
- You know, I'd still find use
for you.
- Well, that is good.
That is more than good.
That is great.
[sighs]
Nice one.
Can't have everyone
in this world and below
knowing that I'm disarmed.
- Yeah, well,
now you really owe me.
- [sighs]
[thunder booms]
- [coughs and gasps]
[gasping]
[laughs]
Sucker.
[mask whooshes]
[panting]
Why?
- It's heavy.
- A battery missing?
Why are you telling me
and not the inventory AVA?
- Everything okay?
- ♪ Everything is perfect ♪
Oh, wow.
[chuckling]
Oh.
I am so glad we can finally
get together like this.
- Yeah, me, too.
- My AVA assistant has prepared
something truly...
transcendent for us.
- Ava, bring on the appies.
She's probably just putting the
final touches on the appies.
- Appies, I can't wait.
- ♪ To you, to you ♪
When I heard
about the great Sara Lance,
I thought...
♪ She's gonna be a tough cookie
to crack ♪
But after our little chat
today,
I think we're finally
on the same page.
- The same page.
- Wonderful.
[glasses clink]
To new beginnings.
[thunder booms]
- That's some storm.
- Oh, well,
your friend Rory arrived.
I had to drop
the artificial atmosphere,
killing every humanoid creature
outside of this compound.
- Rory's here?
- Here on this planet?
Yes.
Here in the sense of being
alive and breathing, no.
Honestly, I don't see
why it matters.
We're putting our pasts
behind us.
Fresh start.
- I meant, let's get to know
each other,
not let's kill
each other's friends.
- Oh, well--
look, there seems to have been
some miscommunication on this.
He's dead.
Best thing now is if we don't
let this ruin the appies.
[grunts]
[dramatic music]
[both grunting]
Why are you fighting me?
You know struggling against me
is useless.
Oh, kill me all you want,
Sara Lance.
I'll be back,
unlike your friend.
[laughs]
- You said you'd help me
rescue Sara.
- I got you here, didn't I?
- Where'd you run off to?
- Steal the Waverider.
Always gotta have
a backup plan.
Someone got there first.
- Backup plan, smart.
Here.
- [grunts]
Necrians have to be smart.
You humans are stupid.
It was inevitable
you'd be the authors
of your own extinction.
What, you don't defend
your species?
[thunder booms]
- No.
They're cowards, liars,
cheats, frauds.
They betray you, lock you up.
Sara's different.
That's why I have to find her.
[soft dramatic music]
[low growling]
[whirring]
- Spoons, you okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
- Everyone's being weird today.
- Spooner.
Spooner...
Come to me.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- we could have at least
gone to the entrees
before you desecrated my face.
- Why don't you feel more pain?
- I modified my pain receptors.
I wasn't born yesterday,
you know.
Whoa--actually, technically
I was born yesterday,
but you get my meaning.
So what's your hopeless plan?
- I am gonna put an end to you.
For good this time.
- [chuckling]
Oh, exciting.
[grunts, groans]
All this violence
when I was planning on showing
you all this for dessert.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
What do you think?
[Zagurons growling]
- Zagurons.
They hide from the light.
They hunt at night.
Come on.
[Zagurons growling]
[Zaguron screeches]
- Door's open!
[grunts]
It's stuck.
- [grunts, coughs]
They outnumber us.
- Then we fight!
- Foolish humans
and your heroics.
- [screeches]
[Zagurons screeching]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[lock hisses]
both: [panting]
- You're shaking.
- I know I've always said
"I'm not scared, I'm smart."
I was definitely scared
back there.
Maybe now we should do
something not smart.
- Well, no one's ever
accused me of being smart.
[sultry music]
♪ ♪
Yeah!
[tentacle squeaks]
Ow, ow, ow!
- [screeching]
[growling]
[objects crash]
Welcome, Spooner.
- Who are you?
[weapon whirs]
Where do you come from?
Look, if you help us,
we can help you.
- [shrieks]
Drop your weapon.
Come inside.
[clicking]
[dramatic music]
[growls]
- [hisses in alien language]
- Are you Amelia Earhart?
- I was fused with this human,
but she just made me weak.
[growls]
♪ ♪
- You fought Amelia
from inside her?
- There is a struggle
inside you as well.
That is your fear.
- [hisses in alien language]
- Fear can be a gift.
Sara Lance did not fear me.
- Sara L--
[hissing in alien language]
- Humans are weak.
- You killed Sara?
- Yes.
- [grunts]
- [growls]
[both hissing]
[shrieks]
- [screams]
[panting]
[soft music]
♪ ♪
- Sara?
What did it tell you?
- I'm so sorry.
It killed her.
[somber music]
♪ ♪
- [sniffles]
[exhales]
- [grunting]
[button chirps]
AVAs!
Still holding on
to all that anger.
Not healthy.
How are we gonna start fresh?
- I don't start fresh.
Now see, this is what you got
wrong about me.
Every scar on my body
is a memory,
a lesson that I learned
in blood.
And it's what makes me
who I am.
And I don't forget any of it.
Now, we've both faced death.
We've both died before.
The difference is I learned
from my scars, and you?
You've just forgotten yours.
- But, Sara,
I don't see any scars on you.
[soft dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[foreboding music]
Oh, there are those scars
on the dead body
of the real Sara Lance.
♪ ♪
- Greg, move your head.