[relaxed music]
♪ ♪
- Hey,
you're gonna have
to pay extra for that.
- Whatever.
[electricity sparking]
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- Whatever you want,
take it.
- Where is your ruler?
- What ruler?
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- "The King Defends
His Throne."
This is your king?
Where is he?
- I-I don't know
who you're talking about.
Please,
don't kill me.
- Yo, that's--
DJ S'more Money.
- T-that's right,
he used to date Zari Tarazi,
before she disappeared.
- I heard rehab.
- Where can I find
this S'more Money?
- Judging some crazy
singing competition
out in Hollywood.
- That is an odd occupation
for a king,
but as is the way,
I will challenge him
to a death duel.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
[exciting music]
[rock music playing]
- ♪ You spurn
my natural emotions ♪
- [panting]
Are you hungry?
I can cook.
- I'm good.
- Why don't you stay
the night this time, eh?
- John,
stop talking.
- Okay.
[ringtone chiming]
[music stops, resumes]
- Wait, what is that sound?
- The Buzzes.
- Hmm.
- The Buzzcocks?
Oh, come on.
It's only one of England's
seminal punk rock bands.
- ♪ In love with someone ♪
♪ You shouldn't've fallen
in love with ♪
- "Ever fallen in love
with someone
you shouldn't have
fallen in love with."
Aww, John, are you trying
to tell me something?
- Of course, not--
unless,
you're trying
to tell me something.
- Course not.
- Good.
And besides, great music
is not just about the lyrics.
It's about the buzz.
The buzz of excitement
that you get
when you play something
that's true
and real.
[notification chiming]
How many bloody phones
do you have?
- Well, a personal phone,
a business phone,
a phone for all
the Persian guys
my mom tries to
set me up with--
And a phone for emergencies.
- It's Les-Lay.
- You can open up your eyes, B,
we're decent.
- Regrettably.
- Sorry.
I know you told me
not to bother you at your--
yoga retreat.
But it's your ex,
DJ S'mores.
He was eviscerated
by an alien.
Ugh.
- Wow, that is a lot to digest.
- Yeah, so I'm thinking
for the funeral,
we need a statement dress.
It's his burial,
but your red carpet.
Bye!
[ship whirring]
- History is literally
being made.
DJ S'more Money's death
is shattering records
for most Cat-Chats in an hour.
The whole world saw it.
Apparently, the alien
killed him during
a live taping of
"Da Throne."
- "Da Throne"?
- In our future it's a wildly
popular singing competition,
and is single-handedly keeping
network television alive
in 2045.
- I don't know
what's more surprising:
an alien attacking
Zara's ex-boyfriend,
or the fact that
network TV still exists.
- Gideon, do us a favor
and bring up the video
for them, will you?
- Smashing.
I love an evisceration.
- My name is
Lord Knoxacrillion,
and I am here
to slay the king.
[screaming]
[crowd screaming]
- Why would one of
Sara's pod aliens
kill a reality star?
- Maybe the alien mistook
S'more for a real king.
- Yeah, and thought
that he could usurp
marshmallow man's power
by offing the bastard.
- Okay, so all we have to do
is stop an alien
from killing a celebrity.
Simple enough.
Let's suit up for La La Land.
- What a load of crap!
- Ooh--yeah, Mick,
uh, shower wouldn't
do you wrong, mate.
- [grunts]
- Mick, use your words.
- This is a spaceship,
is it not?
Why don't we use it
to find Sara?
- [sighs]
Mick, we have been over this.
The galaxy is
hundreds of billions
of lightyears across, okay?
One of those displaced aliens
is going to lead us to Sara.
You and Spooner are gonna QB.
Can you show her the ropes,
please?
- No.
I'm taking the day off.
- You're gonna let him
talk to you like that?
- I don't take it personal,
it's just Rory.
- Yeah, he's worse than usual.
Sara's absence is
really getting to him.
- Yeah, I'm sure
Sara's absence
is really getting to Rory.
Must be very hard for him,
Nate.
- I'm sorry.
We're gonna find her.
I bet Sara's pulling
a "Thor: Ragnarok,"
and she's kicking
some aliens' asses,
and they're all shouting
her name--
"Sara! Sara! Sara!"
- Sara! Sara!
You have to wake up.
Sara,
whatever's out there,
it's still tracking us.
[gasps]
[breathing raggedly]
Don't panic, Gary.
This is Sara freakin' Lance.
A little Amelia Earhart
poison
isn't gonna slow you down.
- I--
I'm too weak, Gary.
I can't fight.
[groans]
It's on you.
- Me?
I-I-I'm no fighter.
- Kayla didn't exactly
fight Spartacus,
now, did she?
[chomps]
- No, no--
absolutely not.
- Gary, Gary,
listen to me.
If I hadn't done
unforgivable things to survive,
I never would have made it out
the other side.
Now, Ava is my other side.
And I don't care
if you have to eat your way
through the entire
solar system,
I am gonna get back to her.
[sighs]
Getting back to her.
[upbeat electronic
dance music]
♪ ♪
- The competition
is heating up
on this year's
"Da Throne."
With the golden buzzer
still in play
and the Wild Card
yet to be revealed,
anyone can still take
Da Throne.
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
[cell phone ringing]
- That's your ex?
- [sighs] Jealous?
- Oh, of some life-size
s'more
who judges some
soulless singing competition?
Real musicians don't compete
to win over the masses
with mediocre,
autotune drivel, love.
- Spoken like a former
punk guitarist.
You want to talk to Mom?
- No.
- Mama, I gotta go.
I love you.
No, I love you more!
Sending you busses
from Hollywood.
Yeah, I'm visiting Zari
in Hollywood.
- All right,
every season has
a secret celebrity contestant.
What?
I read up on the rules.
- Last year, President
Dwayne Johnson showed up
and for an old guy,
he can still get down.
- The Rock's the president?
Please tell me John Cena
is his chief of staff.
- Guys, focus.
We need to find a way
into this place.
[earpiece chirps]
- I got this.
[sighs]
Okay.
Hold, please.
- You're kidding me.
- What?
They're designer.
- Oh, well...
[cameras snapping]
Hi!
- Oh, my God. It's really her!
- Zari!
[overlapping clamoring]
- Zari, where have you been?
[indistinct clamoring]
- Zari, it's great to see you!
[indistinct clamoring
continues]
- Welcome back to "Da Throne."
Our next performance starts...
now.
- ♪ Hand on the wheel ♪
♪ I like to stay in control ♪
♪ 'Cause I get mine
independent ♪
♪ My colors,
silver and gold, ha ♪
♪ Chain hang low like
fruit from a branch ♪
♪ It's a juice avalanche ♪
♪ Dripping from my shoulders,
down to my pants ♪
♪ Diamonds look like me ♪
- Saucéy is on stage,
Can we get Hunter moved
to the left wing?
[radio static crackles]
- Oh, whoa.
Yeah, uh, we really stand out,
don't we?
- You hear that song?
It's kind of catchy.
- ♪ Look at all this fruit ♪
- ♪ You want it ♪
- ♪ Make a whole lot of juice ♪
♪ With that ♪
- ♪ You need it ♪
- ♪ Feel it in my roots ♪
- ♪ I got it ♪
- ♪ Fill a champagne flute ♪
♪ With that ♪
- ♪ They see it, yeah, yeah ♪
[cheers and applause]
- Cat-Chat is losing
it's damn mind
over that juicy performance.
What does last year's winner
and the King of "Da Throne"
have to say?
- Sorry, babes,
but that was weak.
- Weak?
That's not what you said
last night.
You said my fruit was--
- Whoa!
Let's not kiss and tell.
Now, who do we have
to the stage next?
My, you are big and strong.
You must be our Wild Card
contestant.
- I am here to
challenge the King.
- [chuckles]
You and everyone else.
- Can we get a hint, lover?
Who's under the suit?
- My name
is Lord Knoxicrillion,
and I am here
to slay the King.
[roars]
[exciting music]
♪ ♪
[cheers and applause]
[roaring]
- DJ, drop that beat!
[pitch of roar modulating]
♪ ♪
[roaring]
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
[roaring]
[cheers and applause]
- That was tight!
My man, you are committed.
Wha-bam!
[air horn blares]
- The gold buzzer?
Looks like Lord Knoxicrillion
is one step closer
to capturing Da Throne!
- I don't know how you're gonna
top whatever that was,
but if you want to be King,
figure it out fast,
because you're going
straight to the finals.
Ha, ha!
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[playful music]
- You're supposed to be
showing me the ropes.
- Rule number one,
stay out of my way.
- I'm fresh out of
Southern hospitality,
so I ain't gonna tiptoe
across eggshells,
like everybody else
around here.
- Rule number two,
this place is like
a revolving door.
Don't unpack.
- Ah,
I see what's going on.
Yeah, Ava told me
you're the last
of the original recruits.
I guess I'd be pissy too
if I was the last OG.
- What?
Haircut got hitched,
Sara got kidnapped--
and I don't care.
And rule number three,
I drink on the job.
[distant techno music]
♪ ♪
- Guys, meet me in the lab.
The alien's 15 minutes of fame
are up.
Um, excuse me,
Mr. Knoxicrillion.
- It is Lord, flesh-bag.
- Oh, forgive me, Lord.
Um, it seems that
all the finalists
have been upgraded
to their own
exclusive green room.
If you'll just
follow me this way.
Mm-hmm.
So if you would just step
right up there.
- I see no green
in this room.
- [chuckles]
I told you the Iron Giant
wouldn't be a problem.
- Okay.
The energy in here
is way off.
- Oh. Yeah.
Looks like Spooner
took over your den.
- Ah--she moved
my citrine crystal.
- Ooh.
- I was manifesting abundance.
- I know.
- On my planet,
we use crystals to--
hmm, we do not
have that word--
procreate.
- You know what, Knox?
It is factoids like that,
that really captivate
an audience.
Why don't you tell us
a little bit more
about what you know, like,
do you know
where Sara Lance is?
- Your cardiovascular organ
increased
to 80 beats per minute
when you said "Sara Lance."
- Do you know where
Sara Lance is,
yes or no?
- What is a Sara Lance?
- Okay, let's try this again,
shall we?
How'd you get to Earth?
- I was abducted
from my home planet.
18 hours ago,
my pod crashed in a desert.
Then I woke from stasis
to fulfill my prime directive.
- Which is?
- To conquer new planets
by challenging their rulers
to death duels.
- Okay, say you win.
You...hitch a ride home
with, like, a space cabbie?
- My inevitable victory
will be celebrated
with an invasion.
- [exhales]
Picked up the alien vibes
from across the ship,
and lookie here.
We already kidnapped him.
- You did not steal me
like a whelpling.
I followed you here,
but I am no prisoner.
[dramatic music]
- Gideon?
- Gideon!
- Lord Knoxicrillion's
superior technology is...
superior.
[gun clicks]
- Just say the word
and I'll blow him
to kingdom come.
- Impossible,
This suit is resistant
to thermonuclear weapons.
If you and your ruler
cannot fight with honor,
the challenge is cancelled.
I will call my armada
to invade your planet now.
- What? No-no-no-no-no--
Wait, wait, wait,
We, uh, may be low peons--
Just...
[stammering]
And--but--we're honored
to explain to you that you
got the rules all wrong.
- Yeah, Knox--
can I call you Knox?
Listen, bubby,
death duels...
isn't what our planet's
really about.
- Yeah.
Y-yeah, you see, here on Earth,
we compete for the throne
via song and dance.
And with those sick vocals,
buddy,
you're on your way
to becoming the new king.
- Song and dance?
More proof
you are an immature species.
Very well, I accept
the terms of the challenge.
Bring on Earth's
best competitor.
- Yes, Dragon Girls.
[chuckles]
- Sorry.
- Oh!
Sneaky little devil,
isn't she?
- This town's full of them.
Les-Lay,
shouldn't you be off
running Forbes Magazine's
Business of the Year?
- Yeah, well,
we need to talk about
Dragonesque, Zari.
Business is tradge.
- Even the lip kits
aren't selling--
everyone has lips.
- Spoken like
a true capitalist.
- Ignore him.
He thinks dour people
have more depth.
- You still love fame.
- Speaking of, you've been out
of the spotlight for too long.
The public doesn't want
to be someone they can't see.
- Oh, cups are edible in 2045,
eco-friendly is finally in.
Too little, too late,
if you ask me.
Okay, what about
the shareholders?
- They're going to divest
without the face of
the company to promote it.
- How is this happening?
[sighs]
I spent my whole life
building this brand.
- Long, frustrating
story cut short,
the alien has to compete
for "Da Throne."
Nate and Behrad are escorting
him to the studio now.
We need a new game plan.
- Aves, do you trust me?
- Always, Z.
- [sighs]
Look who's back.
Zari T.
Dodged a bullet when
the engagement fell through.
Hashtag blessed!
- Um, actually, you're the one
who proposed, so...
- 'Cause I thought it'd be good
for my brand.
Big mistake.
- Hey, simmer down, sunshine.
- Who's the blond?
- [chuckling]
You know, you Yanks, you're
always behind the 8-ball.
I'm a master of
the Dark Arts, mate.
Name's Johnny C.
- Uh, Zari's boyfriend.
- Yep.
- Dating some Vegas act
isn't gonna abracadabra
your relevancy back, Zari.
You're over.
- [chuckling]
- You should have never
cancelled...
- Ignis!
- Now I'm on top--
Ah. Help, help, help.
Ah, help me, help me!
Come on!
No, no, no, no, no, no!
My S'more Money brand vodka!
That's an accelerant!
Get out of my way.
- Well, I see the appeal
of this celebrity thing.
- Hey, Z-Nation,
it's your girl Zari Tarazi.
So I have been working
on something super top-secret,
and here it is.
[whispering]
I'm the Wild Card.
That's right.
The Dragon Girl is here,
to claim...
"Da Throne."
[upbeat dance music]
♪ ♪
- "Da Throne"'s
latest Wild Card,
superstar Zari Tarazi,
is facing off against
the sisters who can shred
for the chance
to compete against
our golden buzzer winner
in the finals.
Everybody wants it,
but not everyone has
what it takes to win
"Da Throne."
- Friends, foes, and neithers,
the semifinals are here.
Tonight, one contestant
will be sent packing,
so I hope they've brought
their good Louis.
Who will it be?
- Okay, so how exactly
is Zari throwing her head
in the ring in this circus
supposed to put the kibosh
on alien invasion?
- Uh, we're kind of a Swiss
Army knife operation.
Every Legend has a utility.
So when you've got
a social influencer
from the future,
you go with it,
and you hope that
being a triple threat
is still a thing.
- Looks like you know
how to handle your team.
- [chuckles]
- Except Rory.
- Yeah, well,
he's a special case.
- Yeah, back home, dealt with
guys like him all the time.
You give them an inch,
they'll take your truck,
and your virginity.
♪ ♪
- Next up, we've got the twins
who've made K-Pop twice as hot,
versus this round's
Wild Card,
and Da King's ex,
Zari Tarazi.
It's sure to be spicy.
[upbeat dance music]
- ♪ Bonjour ♪
♪ Euros, dollars,
pounds, yen ♪
♪ Everywhere I go,
ballin' ♪
♪ Paparazzi all on me ♪
♪ Shopping spree in Italy ♪
♪ Red carpet,
world premiere ♪
♪ So glamourous,
they love to stare ♪
♪ Merci beaucoup, enchante ♪
♪ Stuntin' in my Cartier ♪
- ♪ Whoa, whoa, whoa ♪
- ♪ Merci beaucoup, enchante ♪
♪ Beat face, flawless ♪
- ♪ Flawless ♪
- ♪ Cash flow
like the River Nile ♪
- ♪ Queen, queen, queen,
queen, queen ♪
- ♪ Cover story
every magazine ♪
- ♪ Queen, queen, queen ♪
- ♪ Merci beaucoup, enchante ♪
♪ Stuntin' in my Cartier ♪
- ♪ Whoa, whoa, whoa ♪
- ♪ Merci beaucoup, enchante ♪
Bon soir.
[cheers and applause]
[upbeat music]
- That gave me drama.
That gave me life.
Now, let's get
into the results.
[cheering]
[electronic chiming]
- Yes! Yes!
[applause]
- The Dragon Girl
took to the skies,
and into the finals.
Guess we know who's
the baddest of the bunch.
[upbeat dance music]
- That's a hell of a way
to save the world.
[suspenseful music]
- [light clicking]
♪ ♪
[distant footsteps]
[clicking and breathing]
[static crackles]
- Hold.
- [clicking and gurgling]
♪ ♪
- [grunts]
- [roars]
[scattered yelling]
[all screaming]
[crunching]
- [roaring]
[dramatic tone]
- Ava?
♪ ♪
[breathing heavily]
- [clicking]
[belches, sighs]
It's all right, Sara--
y-you can come out now.
Sorry, things got a little...
out of hand.
You know how it is
when you, uh,
haven't had bone marrow
in a while, right?
S-Sara?
[distant groaning]
♪ ♪
Director Sharpe?
[breathing heavily]
A planet full of Ava clones?
No!
Why did you taste so good?
- Z, you were ratings gold,
but those votes were a little
too close for comfort.
- [sighs]
It's no big deal.
My next performance
just needs to be bigger
and splashier.
- You know,
those on-air interviews
can really sway an audience,
and "Da Throne" viewers
are suckers
for a good love story.
- Oh, my God.
♪ ♪
- He'll need a new look.
- [chuckles]
Yeah, no. Thanks, love.
I only have the one.
- It'll take a little time
and a lot of cooperation,
but I can work with this.
Your sex appeal is
totally going to waste.
- We have to do something
about that hair.
Girl, it's a mess.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
No, you're not touching
my hair.
I'm not being funny--
Listen, this is
my favorite jacket--
- [chuckles]
[phone chiming]
- [speaking Farsi]
- Mama?
- I saw you on TV,
and I thought, "Surely,
"my daughter would tell me
if she was competing
on my favorite show."
- It was sort of
a last-minute thing.
- And you're dating
a street magician?
First the DJ,
now a con man?
Zari, just because you're old
doesn't mean
you have to settle.
- Okay, not every woman
wants to have
their first kid at 20.
- [speaking Farsi]
I love you, too.
[somber music]
- Do you really care
about that magic man?
I will try my best
to support you,
no matter what.
♪ ♪
- No, um--
it won't last,
John's just a fling.
- [laughing]
Thank goodness.
But, uh, Zari, darling--
you look tired.
You need
a little more makeup.
- Where is he?
We have to start rolling.
- [sighs]
- Ooh.
Nate and Behrad know
what a girl wants.
You look hot.
- Yeah, I look like
that tosser Criss Angel.
- All right, remember,
stick to the talking points
preapproved by Les-Lay.
Chin up, smile.
Easy-breezy.
- In three, two, one.
- Tonight,
we're getting all the tea
in our exclusive interview
with the Dragon Girl,
Zari Tarazi.
And she's joined
by her mysterious new beau,
London street magician
Johnny C.
Zari, girl,
you shocked the world
when you entered "Da Throne"
as a Wild Card,
after a prolonged absence
from the public eye.
The Z-Nation
is dying to know,
where have you been?
- Honestly,
focusing on self-care.
I've been traveling the world
with close friends,
visiting historical sites
to die for--
it's all been super low-key.
- And Johnny, is that where
you enter the picture?
- Yeah, yeah--
I suppose so, mate, yeah.
- Oh, my gosh.
Our meet cute was so romantic.
I was at a snowga retreat
on a historically-preserved
glacier,
and there he was,
showing off
with his perfect scorpion pose.
We fell for each other
instantly.
- Yeah, that's a very poetic
way of putting it.
- Oh, my gosh.
He's so modest.
John doesn't like to brag,
but he's actually...
[whispers] Minor royalty.
- Well, now you know
I gotta ask--
will there be wedding bells
in the Dragon Girl's future?
- I mean,
Princess Tarazi does have quite
the ring to it, right?
- Oh, it sounds magical.
[laughter]
- Yeah, you want to see
some magic?
Watch me...disappear.
[crowd gasps]
- Um,
you know, we had
a really long flight,
he's probably
just jet-lagged.
[chuckles]
[indistinct chatter]
- Damn it, John.
- That was harsh.
- [grunts]
- What the hell was that?
- You know, I could ask you
the same thing, couldn't I?
- What are you talking about?
You just embarrassed me
in front of the entire world.
- Oh, that's what
you care about, isn't it?
Trending, on bloody
Chit-Chat
- Cat-Chat!
- Admit it,
come on, you're using this
mission to get back on top.
- I can save my home
and my business,
and let's not pretend like
we all haven't been caught up
in your personal drama before.
- Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, I'm a bastard,
but at least I admit it.
You'd rather be fake
for the cameras
than real when it counts.
- This isn't real,
- Oh, yeah.
- Remember?
We're not together,
just the way
we both like it.
- You know,
it is really difficult
to keep straight
what's real anymore.
But try this one on
for size, all right?
I am done.
[dramatic music]
- Trouble in paradise?
[dramatic tone]
I got just the thing
to dry those tears.
An empowerment anthem,
something for all the ladies
out there.
'Cause after all,
you wouldn't want
the Z-Nation thinking
some amateur magician
clipped the Dragon Girl's
wings, now would you?
- [sighs]
♪ ♪
- [pained breathing]
[grunts]
Ava, wait.
Slow down.
[winces]
[low droning]
[coughs]
Where are we, babe?
♪ ♪
After you.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
You think I don't know
my own Ava?
- [choking]
♪ ♪
[grunts]
- Gentle beings,
we are joined
by Lord Knoxicrillion.
If this interview goes
anything like the last one,
you can expect
some bombshells.
- I detect no explosives
in the vicinity.
- [laughing]
That dry wit.
That's what "Da Throne" fans
are loving about you.
But here's
the million dollar question.
Where on Earth
did you come from?
I am not from Earth.
I am from the planet Arkana.
- Oh, really?
What do you think of
your competition--
the Dragon Girl, Zari Tarazi?
- That's an alien.
- Unless she is spouting
real fire,
she does not stand a chance.
- Feisty.
So what made you enter
"Da Throne"?
- Why haven't we caught him?
- We did. It's...
- [crunching chips]
- It's complicated.
- I was ambushed by a gangster
feared all over the galaxy.
You would say she has a face
with chicken wings on it.
Her name was Kayla.
- Gideon!
- Yes, Mr. Rory?
- Uncloak.
Initiate
Matador's Last Strike.
- What the hell
are you doing, Rory?
- The last of the OGs
picked up on
a few secret commands.
- You can't just
fire on Hollywood.
- Watch me.
- Activating weapons systems.
[alarm blaring]
- Insolent humans.
You think that's a threat?
- Shall I prepare to fire?
- Yes!
- No!
- Die, you alien scum.
[dramatic choral music]
- Incoming!
♪ ♪
- I am detecting
alien battleships
entering
the Earth's atmosphere.
- Fire on me and your ship
will be destroyed.
Try another trick,
and the invasion will begin.
♪ ♪
- Rory, what the hell
did you do?
- Uh...
the Earth was screwed anyway.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- Mick, we need to talk,
okay?
What, are you gonna shoot me?
What the hell is wrong
with you?
- If you were kidnapped
by aliens,
Sara would have found you
by now.
- You know what?
You're right.
I wish I was the one taken,
but I wasn't.
And I am sick
of your bad attitude
and your drinking
and your lack
of personal hygiene, okay?
What would Lita say?
- She's at college.
- That's great.
- No, it's not.
She never returns my calls,
and when she does,
she's always whispering
or she's at some party
and there are...
boys in the background, and...
[mutters]
- Mick,
just because Lita's busy,
it doesn't mean
she doesn't love you anymore.
It just means
she doesn't need you,
but I need you.
Sara's missing, okay.
It isn't just hard for you.
So get yourself together.
Okay?
Or get the hell off my ship.
- [sighs]
Hello, my old friend.
Oh, bollocks.
- [laughs]
Oh, I'm sorry.
Did I scare you?
Oh, my God.
You're smoking?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, don't tell
me in 2045 it's illegal.
- Yes, but i-it's perfect.
It totally plays up
the whole bad boy image
you've got going on.
Cat-Chat went crazy
when you dissed Z.
- Oh, hang on a minute,
you're telling me that you're
actually pleased that I walked
out on that interview?
- Oh, there's no story
unless Zari's unhappy.
Why do you think S'more Money
was so good for her brand?
He cheated on her
with her assistant
and leaked the photos.
- You're her assistant.
- Yeah.
Get ready to light up.
Ooh.
Do you think you can say
something to make Zari cry?
She's usually so guarded.
[laughs]
- You know what?
I quit.
- Thanks for coming, Lord K.
Now, what's your song
for the finals?
- I will wail, as in battle.
- Mm--not really sure that's
gonna work again,
but listen--
I got this banger
I've been working on.
It's sort of like
a female empowerment anthem.
- On my planet,
we do not follow
a binary gender construct.
We all carry and bear children.
- Perfect.
[laughs]
Perfect!
Then you...
can use the song.
Wha-bam!
- I am synthesizing 500,000
of Earth's supreme vocalists.
I will be king.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- Whoa, hey!
This is my dressing room.
- What are you up to,
you sneaky git?
- I don't gotta tell you guys
nothing.
- Oh, you'll talk,
or I'll rip that stupid donut
off your head
and feed you your tender bits.
- Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Chill, chill. Chill, chill.
I gave Knox and Zara the same
song, he's up first,
no way she can win.
- I cannot wait to punch you
in the face again.
- Well, me first, please.
[dramatic music]
- What?
Can't pacifists blow off
a little steam?
- All right, I don't want him
anywhere near the competition.
Give me a hand.
- Our last two contestants
are one step closer
to taking home the crown.
First to our stage,
give a virtual hand
for the winner
of the gold buzzer,
Lord Knoxicrillion!
[cheers and applause]
[upbeat dance music]
- So this is what it feels
like to be the king?
Dig it.
- Psst, Zari, listen--
- Shh,
I'm watching the competition.
♪ ♪
- [clears throat]
You may begin.
- ♪ I love me,
myself, and I ♪
♪ So hard that I might die ♪
[percussive pop music]
- That cheat.
He's singing my song.
- ♪ Then I resurrect myself ♪
♪ No need for a man's help ♪
♪ Strong, fierce, and free ♪
♪ You'll never behead me ♪
♪ 'Cause I am a dream ♪
♪ Your superstar queen ♪
♪ Soaring through the air ♪
♪ The real Dragon Girl's
here ♪
♪ I won't leave you ♪
♪ I won't deceive you ♪
♪ So bow down and beware ♪
♪ The real Dragon Girl's here ♪
[cheers and applause]
[eerie tones]
[chanting]
Lord Knox! Lord Knox!
- Lord Knoxacrillion rules!
[chanting continues]
♪ ♪
- That wasn't real music.
Tosser couldn't even connect
to the lyrics.
It doesn't mean anything.
- It means everything, John.
It means we lost.
♪ ♪
[upbeat music]
- A finalist who sang
a gender-bending diss track?
That was everything!
And it's going to be a hard act
for Zari to follow.
- I've gotta know, why would
you tell your mother
that this wouldn't last?
- What?
Is this really the time?
- Uh--yeah.
- Because John, you and I can't
even take the first step.
And even if we did, this--
this thing we have
is bound to end.
It always does.
- That's usually my line.
I know that I don't deserve
to be happy,
and I know we'll probably muck
this up, all right,
but I'm willing
to throw the dice.
I want this to be real.
I do.
What do you say?
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[whispers and chatter]
[microphone feedback]
- ♪ You spurn
my natural emotions ♪
♪ You make me feel I'm dirt ♪
♪ And I'm hurt ♪
♪ And if I start a commotion ♪
♪ I run the risk
of losing you ♪
♪ And that's worse ♪
♪ Ever fallen in love
with someone ♪
♪ Ever fallen in love ♪
♪ In love with someone ♪
♪ You shouldn't have fallen
in love with? ♪
[light guitar music]
♪ I can't see much
of a future ♪
♪ Unless we find out
what's to blame ♪
♪ What a shame ♪
[bass line starts]
[cheers and applause]
[upbeat punky music]
♪ And we won't be together
much longer ♪
♪ Unless we realize
that we are the same ♪
♪ ♪
both: ♪ Ever fallen in love
with someone ♪
♪ Ever fallen in love ♪
♪ In love with someone ♪
♪ You shouldn't have
fallen in love with? ♪
♪ Ever fallen in love ♪
♪ With someone you shouldn't
have fallen in love with? ♪
[cheers and applause]
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
- Imposter!
[record scratches]
[panting]
- What is this?
Another trick?
- The trick was,
S'more Money gave you a song
he already gave Zari.
- Drama!
And still, our virtual audience
is Cat-Chatting their votes.
[cats meowing]
- Get out of my throne!
- And the new winner is...
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
[triumphant fanfare]
[cheers and applause]
- Yeah!
- Whoo!
♪ ♪
[cheering]
- Friends, foes, and neithers,
you have spoken.
Zari Tarazi is
the new queen of "Da Throne."
[triumphant music]
♪ ♪
- I am your humble servant,
Queen Z.
- Okay.
♪ ♪
- I never doubted you
for an instant.
- I sure as hell did.
- Well, I couldn't have done it
without my team;
my fashion guru, Behrad,
Nate, on hair,
and, of course...
my boyfriend.
- Now, there's a word
to make lesser men wilt.
[playful music]
♪ ♪
- Scared?
- Terrified.
- Me too.
[light music]
- Mm. Mm!
♪ ♪
- Come on.
- What...
- Whoa, whoa--
- Whoa, whoa.
- Put that thing away.
- Stop that.
♪ ♪
- Can't you see?
He's as small as a grasshopper.
- And like
one of your grasshoppers,
my kind is ancient.
Technology and subterfuge
have been key to our survival.
My s--
- [screams]
- Why?
- Rory!
- Listen, I go to thinking.
If Sara was smuggled
on a ship,
we've been searching
for the wrong cargo.
We need to find the driver.
The alien called her "Kayla."
- You drew that?
- I did.
- Okay,
so we're looking for, um,
an alien that looks like she
has chicken wings on her face?
- Uh...yes.
Anyway, we find Kayla,
we find Sara.
So what do you think, Cap?
- Mm-hmm.
Rory, I think that's...
an excellent idea.
- Oh, hmm. Good.
[distorted indie rock music]
- ♪ Space girl,
floating away ♪
[breathing heavily]
♪ ♪
- ♪ Space girl, oh,
space girl ♪
- You wouldn't happen to be
missing an Ava clone
from your dinner party,
would you?
- The infamous Sara Lance.
I've been waiting...
a long time for you.
[suspenseful music]
- Greg, move your head.