["Space Girl" plays]
- ♪ Has me feelin' so low ♪
♪ I think I could have
loved her ♪
♪ In this world or another ♪
♪ But now I'm stuck ♪
♪ Lookin' up from below ♪
♪ Space girl ♪
♪ Floating away ♪
[thud]
[record scratch]
- What are you doing here?
How are you even alive?
- What a fantastically
boring question.
Kayla downloaded me from
the Cloud onto your printer.
A better question would be why.
- Why shouldn't I just
slit your throat
and watch you bleed out
on my carpet?
- [laughs]
Because...
then you wouldn't have any more
of your questions answered.
- Until you print yourself
out again?
- Alas, you're looking
at the last-gen me.
My data was corrupted when a
certain someone blew up my lab
before my upload was complete,
but that's cool.
I forgive you.
- You kidnapped me.
You manipulated me
in every possible way.
- True, true.
But I also saved you.
No, no. Not looking
to make this about me.
You see, I've changed.
- [snorts]
You've changed?
And why should I believe you?
- Let me prove it to you.
C'mon.
What do you say, Sara Lance?
Is there room
for one more mixed-up outcast
on this
♪ zany little ship of yours? ♪
- Actually,
I think we have a room
that would suit you perfectly.
- That's Bishop?
- Not at all
what I was expecting.
- For a psychotic
super villain,
the guy's got a great look.
- Yeah, they always do.
- So, shall we start
with the introductions?
You are of course, Ava.
Not just any Ava. The Ava.
Congratulations, by the way.
Your engagement ring.
So, do you two kids
have a date yet or--
- All right, that is enough.
Don't listen to him.
Don't even talk to him.
He's just trying to
get into our heads
so that he can do whatever
it is he came here to do.
- Where the hell is she?
- You! My colleague Kayla
had very strong thoughts
about you ceasing to exist.
What happened, I wonder?
- She changed her mind.
- Is that so?
Well, speaking of changes,
love the new 'do.
- Everybody out. Let's go.
Everybody out,
except for Spooner.
- Keep an eye on him.
Tries to escape,
shoot him in the face.
- You got it, Capitana.
- Why would I want to escape
when I feel like
I am finally home?
[exciting music]
♪ ♪
- Something's missing.
- What do you mean
something's missing,
like his moral compass?
- No, like 6% of who Bishop is.
We destroyed his compound
before he could finish
uploading himself.
- You know what, guys, a true
psychopath wouldn't wanna
just murder the woman
who destroyed his life work.
He'd really want to take some
time torturing her, you know.
- Thanks, babe.
That's very reassuring.
- But if Bishop
wants to play chess,
he has chosen
the wrong opponent.
- Uh, no, no, no, no,
absolutely not.
- Please. C'mon, babe.
I've always wanted
to get inside the mind
of an evil genius.
- Who, technically speaking,
created you.
[gasps] Both of you, actually.
- Not helping Nate. Look, babe.
I'll just go in there
and try to find a way
to connect with him.
That way we can figure out
why the hell he's here.
- You sure?
- Yes.
- Okay. All right.
All right.
Just don't let him
get into your head, okay?
- [hisses]
Argh, bloody hell.
Ah, yeah.
It's all coming back
to me now.
I really made a dog's dinner
of that pile again, didn't I?
I take it the beast got me.
- No, John, that was me.
I stabbed the beast
in the back,
and somehow you woke up
with a scar.
- Look, I can explain.
- Oh, can you?
Can you explain how
you nearly killed all of us?
How you lied to me yet again?
- Lying was part
of Gary's game.
I didn't
make up the rules, love.
- Don't call me love.
And don't pretend like this
was all a game.
You know what?
My brother was right about you.
You're different, John.
- Yeah, I'm different.
I mean, how many people
you know who have drunk
from the Fountain
of bloody Imperium.
But don't worry, all right?
I just need
a little bit of time
to get a handle
on my newfound power,
and maybe I should woodshed
my magic by myself, hey?
- Yeah. Yeah.
I think that's best.
- Oh, come on,
don't be like that.
Come on, love.
I mean--
my love, ju--
Damn it, Johnny!
- John's lying to me, again.
- Huh, glad he's feeling
like his old self.
- No, he's--he's trying
to blame his behavior
on the Fountain,
but I don't buy it.
Can't you whip up some kind
of truth serum or whatever?
- Yeah. It's called scotch.
- Hey, I'm serious.
You would still
be stuck in that game
if it weren't for me.
Please.
- Look, if you wanna find out
what happened with John
at the Fountain,
it is not my help you need.
- Spoon's.
That is a great idea.
She can help us, come on.
- I guess my life could use
a little more drama.
- I was hoping we'd have
a chance to kibbitz.
Get to know each other,
just you and me.
- But you already know me.
You had a planet full of mes,
didn't you?
- Don't sell yourself so short.
Sara could have had
her pick of my Avas,
yet she turned over the heavens
to get back to you.
So, what makes you so special?
- [laughs]
Sara said you'd do this.
Try to get into my head.
- Like she isn't interested
in getting into mine?
- I knew this was a mistake.
- No.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Please. Don't go.
We've hardly broken the ice.
- Hmm, thatagirl.
You see that?
Making Bishop think that
she's the vulnerable one.
- You know what, you can play
nice all you want,
but it still doesn't excuse
the fact that you kidnap
the woman that I love.
- But the fact that I did so
in order
to save all of humanity...
changes nothing.
You're right.
I was an arrogant
egomaniacal...
meanie.
- And so what now? Hmm?
You've come here
to turn over a new leaf.
Is that what we're all
supposed to believe?
- [sighs]
Where else would I go?
What else would I do?
Look, I know this is
gonna sound perverse, but...
[exhales]
- But what?
- You and Sara are the closest
thing I have left to family.
I know. Sounds insane.
- No, I get it actually.
You're a clone. I'm a clone
and it's not like I have
any real family, so...sure.
I guess in some perverse way,
we are...like family.
- Playing him like a fiddle.
- Bishop's not gonna
let himself
be manipulated
that easily.
- Can I...tell you a secret?
You...were always
my favorite Ava.
Not you personally, of course.
Your model.
- You mean bossy Ava?
- Ugh. A moniker our marketing
department came up with.
I wanted to call you Boss Ava.
Only people were afraid
of a clone
that would tell them
what to do,
except that is precisely
what you were designed for.
But you have exceeded
my wildest dreams.
You're getting married.
[chuckles]
Didn't see that one coming.
- Why not?
- I lower the oxytocin levels
in all the clones,
the so-called love hormone.
I don't want you
falling in love.
It hurts productivity.
- Huh. Maybe that's why
I'm having such a hard time
planning this damn wedding.
Productivity is usually
my strong suit
and I can't even put together
a seating arrangement.
- Maybe I can help--not like I
have anything else to do it.
And it'll be fun.
- If Sara even knew
I was talking to you--
- Oh, c'mon.
It'll be our little secret.
- How do I know that you're not
just doing this
to get me to let my guard down?
- I am doing this so that
you let your guard down.
I want to get to know you, Ava.
- I have to go.
- I can also help
your friend Rory.
- What? What's wrong with Rory?
- Nothing...yet.
But those babies in his head
are getting hungry.
- How the hell did you
know about--
- Kayla letting him live?
The fact that he's experiencing
headaches, that luxurious hair.
Doesn't take a genius
to realize
he mated with a Necrian.
I spent eons trying
to meld humans and aliens
and never thought to do it
the old-fashioned way.
I can help you save Rory
by giving his spawn
the proper nutrients.
It's either that or...
his brain.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- [moans]
- Oh! Guess it worked.
- Of course it did.
I made Bishop think that
I needed something from him,
and he proved himself
to be trustworthy, for now.
But believe me,
this is just the opening move
of our little chess match.
- What does that make me?
The pawn?
- Hmm.
- It's not that bad.
- Oh!
- What?
I have alien taste buds,
what I can say?
Are you sure It's okay
we leave Spooner in there alone
with Bishop?
- There's no way
he's getting in her head.
[mellow R&B playing]
♪ ♪
- Spoon, we need to talk
about Spain.
[tinny music playing]
- What about Spain?
- Did someone say Spain?
I spend a week in Ibiza once.
Didn't sleep a wink.
Last thing I remember, I was...
- That's Bishop, huh?
- That turtleneck
is doing him no favors.
- One with the music.
- Anyways.
Hey, what happened
when John drank
from the Fountain of Imperium?
- I was with him and the kid
Fernando in the cave.
The fascists were coming and--
- Spoons, you okay?
- The--the fascists
were coming and...
[uneasy music]
- [inaudible]
Whoa. Okay, that was weird.
It's like something's missing,
like a blank spot in my memory.
- Like something's been erased.
- You think John
put a spell on me?
I'm gonna kill him.
- Just not until we find out
what he wanted you to forget.
- Which means I'm gonna have
to put another spell on you.
- Look, I'd love to help
you out, but--
- Ah, Aves, perfect timing.
- Hey.
- What do you guys--anyway,
I need a moment with Bishop.
- He is all yours.
- Just in case somebody
gets out of line.
- Thanks.
- Going this way.
- So...how's your pregnant
friend feeling?
- Better.
Thank you for the advice.
- Perhaps there's some way
I could assist
your friend John.
- What's wrong with John?
- Oh, I don't know.
Just your friend
seemed concerned about him
that maybe he drank something
he shouldn't have.
I am a doctor.
- No, John's fine.
- [coughing]
- Why do you do this
to yourself?
[dramatic chords]
- Oh nice. You're wearing
my clothes now, are ya?
- Well, someone's gotta
pick up the mantle
and you're in no shape for it,
but you don't have to
suffer, Johnny.
[echo] Suffer, Johnny...
- [laughs]
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Another snort
of the Scarlet Lady
and I'll be right as rain.
Is that it?
You know, it's not the
first time I've gotten clean.
- And why haven't
you dumped it?
You'll never be clean, Johnny.
- [laughing]
You know,
you're not even real.
You're just a figment
in my imagination,
some damn junkie hallucination.
- And without magic, you're
just a pathetic ex-smoker
in a trench coat who lies to
the people he loves.
- At least I'll be rid of you.
- Have it your way then.
- No, no, no, no, no. Stop!
- Can you see John?
You'll never be rid of me.
I am you.
[door thuds shut]
[dark music]
- You think that
that's his real name?
- Bishop?
- Mm-hmm.
- It does feel a little
on the nose.
- Gideon.
How we doing with the scan?
- I'm still analyzing
his genetic code.
- What are you hiding?
- 10 bucks
Ava gets it out of him first.
- I don't bet against my girl.
- I spy with my little eye
[singsong]
a wedding binder!
Oh, it's thorough.
- Yes, I've...heard that.
Sara put me in charge because
usually I'm the decisive one,
and I can't seem
to choose a single thing.
- Okay. Let's start simple.
What's the coolest wedding
you've ever been to, huh?
What kind of vibe we talking?
- I've never actually been
to a wedding.
- Hmm?
- Yeah. I was sort of known
as the party pooper
at the Time Bureau, so...
- Hey, look, it's tough
being the boss.
- I know. Thank you.
- Mm-hmm.
Now, look, you're just
putting too much pressure
on yourself.
Just go with your gut.
- I can't, I don't--what
if I choose something weird?
- Who cares? Speed round.
What's your favorite flower?
- Uh, is cactus a flower?
- Color?
- Gray.
- Appetizer?
- See, this thing
about appetizers.
I don't understand why people
have to eat before they eat.
- Okay. So, the ceremony
will be unconventional,
but it's all you.
- [sighs] Admit it.
I'm weird!
Why the hell did you have
to make me so weird?
- Look, first off,
I didn't make you.
Yes, I designed you,
but everything
you've done in your life,
that's your accomplishment,
not mine.
And you not knowing
whether you want a vegan cake
or not doesn't matter.
I'm gonna take that back--
vegan cakes are disgusting.
- [laughs]
Well, thank you
for trying to help.
I really appreciate it.
- Hey, don't forget.
I'm a clone too.
A clone of a clone
of a clone of a clone.
- So how many times?
- Oh, I lost track somewhere
around my 200th reiteration.
- 200th?
And every one of them
was different.
- You know me.
I like to tinker.
- So how exactly is this you
different from the you
Sara knew?
- Hmm. Good question.
- Oh, come on,
you psycho son of a bitch.
Tell her what you're hiding.
- There was something missing
from the me
that Sara met on Pliny X19.
It took me a long time
to find it.
You want to know what it was?
[suspenseful music]
Humility.
- Ah!
What a lying piece of crap.
- Humility?
- Mmm.
- Wow!
- All right. You ready?
- Mm.
Don't want
to bite my tongue off.
- You're such a baby.
Tortured mind
with secrets hidden
show me that
which is forbidden.
[intense music]
♪ ♪
- You did it!
All the magic!
- [breathing hard]
The Fountain.
The Fountain
didn't want John.
It decided he wasn't worthy.
- Well, then how did he get
his magic back?
- He took a sip of something.
Look, I don't know what it was,
but when he drank it,
that's when he killed
the soldiers
who were attacking us.
- Where the hell are you going?
- Oh, I'm just going
to break up
with my lying dumpster fire
of a boyfriend.
- A Juiced up warlock
who likes to kill people?
I don't think so.
First, we need to figure out
exactly what John's
been dosing himself with.
- Your betrothed has good taste
in music and in love.
[gasps] Found it.
- Hmm.
- Lou Reed, 1972.
- Looks punky.
- Mm-hmm.
- Well, I guess Sara and I
got engaged at a punk show.
So...same night that
you kidnapped her, actually.
You wanna know
the even crazier thing?
If you hadn't kidnapped her,
she may never have proposed.
It wasn't until we all went
back that same night
a second time that
she popped the big question.
- A real mind-bender, huh?
- Yeah.
["Perfect Day" begins]
- What do you think?
- It's, um...unconventional.
I like it.
I'm not sure how you--how
do you dance to it?
- Let me show.
It'll be our...
father-daughter dance?
- I'm...not sure
that's a good idea.
- You mean with Sara watching?
- [huffs] You knew.
♪ ♪
- ♪ Just a perfect day ♪
♪ Feed-- ♪
- That can't be good.
- Ava is just making Bishop
think
that she is
playing into his hand.
Like I am doing to you.
♪ ♪
- Oh--ha ha ha!
- ♪ Such a perfect day ♪
- I'm sorry I pried before,
about John.
- Oh, it's okay.
It was nice of you
to try and help.
It's just--he's a little
more complicated than Rory.
- Hmm, tormented by demons
of his own making?
- Yes, literally.
- Mm.
♪ ♪
- ♪ Just a perfect day ♪
- This song.
- Mm.
- Sara's gonna love it.
Makes me wanna smile
and cry all at the same time.
- Yes.
I know exactly how you feel.
- Why? Did you design me
to feel that way?
- What difference does it make?
All of us are just a jumble
of neurons and synapses,
a tiny electrical storm
in our head.
Why should your feelings be any
less real than anyone else's?
♪ ♪
I'm proud of you, Ava.
- ♪ Oh, it's a...♪
- I only wish we could have
a dance of our own
on your special day.
- I-I can't, I'm sorry.
- ♪ Oh, such a perfect day ♪
♪ You just keep me
hanging' on ♪
♪ You just
keep me hangin' on ♪
- [sobbing]
♪ ♪
- Aha! Bravo.
Babe, that was masterful.
The way you played Bishop
off of me to make him think
that you trust him?
What a performance!
That was a performance, right?
- Yeah, yeah. Yeah.
- Gideon's scan came back.
He's a 100% human.
So we know what he is.
You have any theories
on why he's here?
- Tch. Honestly, I think
he wants to get to know us.
I think he sees us as family.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I-I-I know it's part
of his act or whatever,
but doesn't mean
it isn't true, right?
- Yeah, actually, I think
you found his angle.
He is gonna use you guys
to get to me, which is smart.
- Or maybe
this isn't about you.
Maybe the guy's just lonely,
you know?
Not everybody has a family
that they can call their own.
- Oh, hey.
Are you checking up on me?
- Checking in.
You see,
that's what girlfriends do.
- Yeah.
I'm sorry, this magic
just got
a bit of an edge, you know?
- Yeah. Yeah, I see that.
- Are we okay?
- I don't know, John,
you tell me.
- Yeah, yeah, we're good.
I love you.
Pffft. I just--I hate to
piss you off, you know?
- You look tired.
Why don't you go upstairs,
take a bath?
We'll just have a quiet night
at home together. Yeah?
- Yeah.
Thanks, love.
Oh...
old habits die hard.
- Yeah, I know.
- And I'll take a bath.
- Mm. Ha.
- Ah-eh-uh...
- [mouthing] Thank you.
- Aah!
- Three, four, five.
- What the hell was that?
- Contraction.
A six-second contraction,
to be exact.
You are officially in labor.
Sooner than expected,
but you know, we are in
uncharted waters here.
- When does my head explode?
- Your head's not gonna
explode,
not with uncle Gar here.
Although once you hit
the second week of labor,
you might wish it had.
- Is it gonna hurt?
- Well, my father describes it
like eating a handful
of hot peppers
and then passing
50 large pointy rocks
through his Necrian head hole,
which for you
will be your ears.
- Ears? Ah!
I can't do this.
I--I can't do this.
- It's totally normal
to feel this way, Mick.
You know,
this is just you facing
the reality of these babies.
Soon, you're gonna be daddy.
- A single dad of 48 babies.
I didn't sign up for this.
- Well, I mean,
you're not gonna be alone.
You--you got me,
you got all the Legends.
- Right. Yeah.
You're gonna be
the godfather.
- Yeah.
[panting]
- Yeah, sure.
Yeah, I mean, whatever.
- Who are you trying
to impress?
Her?
Or is there another voice,
something more primal?
- Will you just shut up,
all right?
I don't need you.
I've got this under control.
- You believe that, do you?
She certainly doesn't.
- What the bloody hell
are you on about?
- Check your pocket, John.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- What is it?
- Astra?
- It's blood.
In Hell we call this
a Scarlett Lady.
- What does that mean?
- It means John has tapped into
some very volatile,
very dark magic.
If he doesn't stop using it,
it will kill him.
- Okay, what if
we confront him?
- Zari!
- Sounds like he'll kill us.
- Where is it?
- John, don't do this.
- You stay out of this.
You give it here now.
- It's this or me, John.
You can't have both.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- [moans]
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry,
I'm so, so sorry.
I thought I had control
of this thing...
But I don't.
I don't.
- Is it done?
- That was the last of it.
Yeah.
Now look...
I'm gonna
lock myself in that manor.
I am not coming out until this
is out of my system, all right?
I promise you that.
- John.
I'm coming with you.
- Hey.
Look, I'm sorry.
This whole thing is my fault.
I never should have sent you
in there alone.
- You didn't send me in, Sara.
It--it was my idea
to interrogate him.
- Yes. Yeah, you're right.
Oh, babe, I'm sorry, okay?
And I'm sorry if I was putting
too much pressure on you
to plan the wedding.
I didn't--
I thought that
it was what you wanted and I--
- No, I--I did.
I think focusing on dresses
and seating arrangements
was reassuring that things
can be managed, you know.
But what can't be managed
is that I have no idea
how I'm supposed to be feeling.
You know, I-I never
saw my parents
kiss or laugh
or, you know, fight even.
I never had a mom to like
hug me after a heartbreak
or just a dad to tell me
that he was proud of me,
and I just never had
a family...to love me.
And I really don't know
that I'm gonna know
how to love ours.
That's all.
- Babe.
You do not need
to learn how to love.
Everything about you is love.
And it doesn't matter
where you came from.
You made yourself
into who you are.
And I'll tell you what--
that chick,
she is the most intelligent
and funny
and loving person
that I have ever met.
- I love you.
[sighs] Thank you.
- Well, okay.
Will you come and show me
what you've been planning?
- No.
- Come on, I wanna see.
- Okay, wait, wait, wait,
let's start with
something good.
Here we go.
- Is that a lemon
buttercream cake
topped with maraschino
cherries? Perfect!
- The cherries
were Bishop's idea, but--
- Ooh, I love
whatever these are.
Yeah.
- Actually that was all Bishop.
- Tapas. Yes, that's perfect.
I love that idea.
- Oh, well, I was actually
thinking of more traditional,
you know, meal service,
but then he suggested tapas
'cause they're more fun,
they...
- Encourage conversation
and help out the people
stuck at the...
both: boring table.
- Yeah, well...
Bishop is, he's pretty good
at wedding planning, I guess.
It's like he's reading my mind
or something.
This? Yes.
- Uh, babe?
It's not like that.
It is that.
6% that's missing, it's...
it's you.
- He's 6% me?
What the hell does that mean?
- Spaniel, Broad, Tricycle.
- System override.
Your orders, Captain?
- Shut down
the electromagnetic barrier.
[dark music]
♪ ♪
- 12, 13, 14--
your contractions
are getting longer.
Your water could break
any time now.
- Wait, Mick you're in labor?
- I'm gonna be a godfather,
Nate!
- If you need anything like
a--like a Q-tip or something,
because there's disgusting ooze
coming out of your ear.
- [gasps] Aah!
- Whoa!
Your hair's
already falling out.
- No!
- It's all happening so fast.
- Go, go, go, go, go.
I'll get Sara and Eva.
It's happening!
Mick's water broke.
I know, it sounds weird
to say it. Come on.
- Okay. It's go time.
- Wait, wait,
how did he get out?
- I let him out.
Sorry.
He knew the override code.
- Damn it. He got the 6%
with all the useful stuff.
- Gideon, be a peach
and lock down the hallway.
- Rory.
You're not getting to Rory
without getting through me.
And let's be real,
that's not gonna happen.
- Sara, you've got
this all wrong.
I don't wanna hurt him.
I wanna help him.
- And why would I trust you?
- Because I am you.
- You wish.
- You wanna fight?
Aww, what can I say?
I do too.
Gideon...set the mood.
['70s dance hit plays]
♪ ♪
- That music
isn't helping.
Door!
[groans]
- You know what they say
when you fight yourself?
You're destined to lose.
- Destiny's so last season.
♪ ♪
- Ahhhhh!
- Did you hear the good news?
I'm gonna be a godfather.
Why's the door locked?
Rory needs me.
♪ ♪
- I knew you were twisted...
but merging my DNA with yours--
that is next level.
- You blew up my lab before
I could finish my upload.
I needed a few more A, C, G,
and Ts to complete my genome.
Yours were in the system.
So I took them.
♪ ♪
Now I know everything
you know.
Unfortunately for you...
that's all you know too.
- Abren las puertas, por favor.
Lock her up, Gigi.
- Get out of my delivery room.
- And miss all the fun?
[chuckles]
- Aah!
- Just in time.
Looks like that first
little guy is about to crown.
♪ ♪
- He's after the eggs.
He hijacked Gideon.
- Yeah, it's jammed.
- You gotta do system reboot.
- On it.
- [groaning]
- Oh, boy.
Yeah, that does not look good.
- What doesn't look good?
- They're breach.
Gideon,
lubricate his sinus cavity.
- What?
- We're gonna have to deliver
these babies nasally.
- The reboot's
gonna take 30 minutes.
Apparently Gideon's calendar
needs to be updated.
- Damn it. Okay, Spooner,
do you have anything
that can shoot through metal?
- [moaning]
- Now breathe.
[grunting]
Ah! Uhh!
[breathing hard]
Aah! Aaaaah!
Aaaaaah!
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- They're coming fast now.
- How many more?
- Just 45 to go and then
[singsong] I'll have them all.
- What happened?
- Bishop locked himself
in there.
- With Mick.
- We've got you.
All right, stand back.
[power up thrumming]
- Meet the newest Legends.
♪♪ ♪♪
- Look at them. So peaceful.
- Lita's gonna be so happy.
- [groaning]
- As much as it pains me
to say this, thank you.
Rory would have been dead
without you.
- Friends?
- Don't push your luck.
You should be happy
that I thanked you.
- Well, you can thank me
by taking me back to myself.
- You're volunteering
to go back into yourself?
- Please.
- We would have just
let you out
if you'd explain
what you were doing.
- I see now how bad
it looked from your end.
Hindsight is 20/20.
Look, I--I get it. I messed up.
I've been alone so long,
I forgot what it means
to be a friend.
What it's like
to be part of a family.
I know I've got
a lot of work to do.
I just hope you'll give me
a chance to earn your trust.
- We'll see.
- Ciao, ciao, for now.
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
- So, I guess this is it then,
right?
End of the bloody road.
Exorcist, Demonologists,
Master of bloody bull...squat.
- John?
- Yeah, yeah.
- Listen to me.
Hey, I know it doesn't feel
like it at this moment,
but...
this could be
a new beginning.
- You know I meant
what I told you
when I said I loved ya.
Because I do.
I got to end this.
I've got to end--
- John, that--
that doesn't fix anything.
- Look, you deserve someone
who is bloody fantastic,
all right, not some pathetic
has-been, honestly.
- I have spent my whole life
trying to be somebody
for everyone else.
When I'm with you,
I can just be myself.
That is the greatest gift.
I love you.
Not your magic, you.
Hey, I'm not an idiot.
You have told me so many lies.
I need the truth. The truth.
- The truth is, I don't know.
I don't know
who I am without magic...
I don't know how the hell
I'm gonna get through this.
I mean, I want to...
but if you still love me
after everything that
I've put you through then...
I wanna do it with you.
[emotional music]
♪ ♪
- I...am...
going to get you
a cup of tea.
- Okay. All right.
[sniffles]
Oh, yeah, the kettle,
it's in the back
of the cupboard somewhere.
- Oh, sorry. I meant Gidget
is gonna make the tea,
but I'm gonna walk all the way
there and back with the tea.
- I am a right lucky bastard.
- I know.
- Greetings, Mr. Constantine.
- Who's this?
- An old friend you just met.
- Bishop.
- You and I have a lot
in common, it seems.
And perhaps,
if you'll trust me...
- Yeah,
that's not likely, mate.
- Ever notice how people
romanticize humility?
Ironic, since it's power
that changes the world.
I can help you get yours back
if you do me one--
[crackling, static]
- I told Sara
these things were a bad idea.
[clicking]
[dark music]
♪ ♪
- What, you thought
I'd just vanished--poof?
Think I'll stick around,
mate.
- Yeah, like hell you will.
You see, you're just
my own personal demon.
I should have faced you
a long time ago.
- Oh, the gallant hero.
- [laughs]
- Now this Bishop bloke,
what was he on about, hey?
- I don't care.
You heard me--I'm done.
Done with magic,
and I'm done with you.
- [laughing]
- Is that funny to you, is it?
- Oh...hilarious.
[shriek]
Ohh...
- What the...
Ohh--
- What, did you think
I'd just stand idly by
and watch you throw away
all of our power for a woman?
- [coughs, groans]
[labored breathing]
- [echoing]
Oh, Johnny boy.
You need the sense
knocked into you, don't ya?
- Aah!
- Johnny boy.
What a disappointment.
- Aaah--
- I told you John,
I'm not
just some bloody side affect
that you can get rid of
by tossing your flask.
No.
I am you.
- How's the proud Papa?
- [sniffs]
Is that mushroom and--
- Oh, okay.
- Ginger?
- Yeah, it's Bishop's
pregnancy smoothie.
Poured it down Rory's ears,
but I like to drink it.
- Oh, that explains why
Mick delivered so quickly.
Necrians use ginger
to induce labor.
- What?
- Why would Bishop
wanna induce Rory's labor?
It's not like
he wanted the babies.
- Maybe he wanted
something else.
- Not the ear.
- He induces Rory's labor
so that he could get access
to his comms.
- With the comms
he can talk to anyone.
- God, he's been studying us
this whole time,
trying to see
who's most vulnerable,
who he can crack.
- Figuring out
who would help him.
- [grunting, gasping]
[heavy music]
♪ ♪
[groans]
[chime]
- Hello, John.
- Now...
what was it you were saying
about getting my powers back?
[dark music]
- Greg, move your head.