Previously on "The Flash,"
"Arrow," and "Legends of Tomorrow"...
Since we learned of them,
we've been calling them the Dominators.
You can't do this alone.
I don't plan to.
Guys, thanks for coming.
This is Kara Danvers. Supergirl.
I went back in time to
change the timeline.
It's called Flashpoint,
and now things here are different
than before I left.
You just erased a daughter from my life?
He took it upon himself
to change the timeline,
and, because of it,
my brother was killed.
There's no amount of feeling bad
that could ever make up for that.
I'm having memories of a stranger,
but she's not really a stranger.
What if, when you interacted
with your younger self in 1987,
- you...
- Inadvertently changed my past.
You're back!
Oh, it's so good to see you.
I love you, Dad.
Call Lyla.
Tell her these Dominators
aren't here peacefully.
Maybe they chose us because
we couldn't fight back,
because none of you are meta-humans.
What is their plan?
The phrase loosely translates to,
"We are nearing completion
of the weapon."
I can't believe that you guys
escaped an alien spaceship.
Key words: alien spaceship.
- I have questions.
- They can wait.
Thanks for helping me get my sister home.
Yeah, man.
What's our status?
Nothing, since the Dominators
paid their little visit
- to mess with our heads.
- Why would they do that?
What if they were trying
to pit us against each other,
in order to gain intel about meta-humans?
Man, I wish they would just send us
an IM with a questionnaire.
Well, metas pose the biggest
threat to their invasion.
It would make sense they'd want
to get to know their enemies.
By kidnapping people.
Perhaps they were searching your minds
for potential meta-human vulnerabilities.
I think it's time we return the favor.
What do you want to do?
Kidnap one of them now?
Ever since we fought off that one ship,
they've kind of been in short supply.
Actually, I know where to find one.
I've been reviewing old Army footage
of their first encounters
with the Dominators,
and I think I pegged the fight to...
Redmond, Oregon. 1951.
You're suggesting we travel to 1951,
abduct a Dominator, and interrogate it
to determine their intentions.
They kidnapped us. Seems fair.
Whoa. Time travel. I'm definitely in.
Okay, hold on, though.
Professor Stein and Caitlin
have been talking about
a way to take down the Dominators.
They could probably use your help.
Pass.
Yeah, I mean, I'm with him, mostly 'cause
I just don't want to lose my geek cred,
but time travel!
I could take Amaya and Mick.
Do it.
- Yeah!
- Okay.
And, uh, the new president called,
which would be cool under
different circumstances,
but she wants to meet with us.
Let's bring Ray and Sara as backup.
What about me? I can do backup.
Can I talk to you for a second?
I don't know.
I would like to minimize
your involvement in this.
Why? Because I'm an alien?
I also happen to be your biggest weapon.
You are an unknown quantity,
and this is not personal.
Except that's exactly how this feels.
Kara, when I started living this life,
it was just me.
I was going up against human threats...
That I could handle.
Then it was meta-humans,
and I can handle that.
Now I learn that there
are multiple Earths,
and I was brainwashed aboard
an alien spacecraft...
I am sure that was
unnerving, but I don't...
I don't get unnerved.
But when I go up against something new,
I push back.
Right or wrong, it is who I am,
and it is what I do,
so I'm asking for a little bit of space
because I have to draw
the line somewhere.
I need to claw back a sense of normalcy.
Please stay here.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
This ship is everything!
What type of propulsion
system does it use?
- No idea.
- Oh, my God.
That construct on the bow
looks like it could be
- some sort of time sphere.
- Yeah, no idea.
To operate a ship of this size,
the deep-link nets would have to be...
Oh, my God, you'd have to use,
- like, a quantum neural chipset...
- Hey, guys, guys.
Amaya and Rory are waiting
for us on the bridge.
Can we just keep moving this along?
- This ship is...
- Automatic?
- Supersonic.
- Hypnotic.
Funky fresh.
Professor?
It's highly unlikely
we can fashion a weapon
with sufficient force to
overcome the Dominators.
I was thinking the exact same thing,
which is why I invited...
So what if, instead,
we try to attack them
with something infinitesimally small?
I'm... I'm sure you're familiar
with the story of the lion
with the thorn in his paw.
You used to love telling me
that story when I was a kid.
Oh. Hello.
The lion with the thorn
in his paw is a parable,
a story about a big, ferocious creature
that is felled by something small.
So what do you need help with?
Uh, I'm afraid it's... it's classified.
Oh, juicy.
Some sort of secret government
space weapon, no doubt.
Something like that,
only this sort of work
is slightly out of my wheelhouse.
Yeah, if only you knew someone
with a PhD in nanotechnology.
Uh-huh, unfortunately,
Raymond's busy working on other things.
I was talking about me.
Did the six years I spent at
MIT magically slip your mind?
Of course not.
Good. Okay. Let's get to work.
Hmm.
We made it. This is the '50s. Sick.
Severe time jumps can cause nausea,
temporary deafness...
Linguistic disorientation.
You. Clean it up.
We're gonna kidnap an alien.
Okay.
I know I did not just travel through time
so we could stay on the ship.
Ponytail, you're staying on the ship.
I'll take that as,
"Have fun storming the castle".
Oh, for real?
You're gonna use "Princess
Bride" against me?
Against me?
Okay. I got you, girl.
Celebrating July 4th early?
Ray made it for me.
You look like a star-spangled idiot.
We need to find the Army.
I think we found 'em.
What are we waiting for?
Let's grab an alien and get out of here.
Just waiting for one of
the weaker ones in the herd.
I don't think there are any weak ones.
Do you have any idea
what's going on out there?
It's a real-life Spielberg movie,
and we're stuck in here.
Okay.
I think I know what's
really bothering you.
I'm having the worst case of FOMO
while everyone else is out
there kidnapping an alien?
No.
I think you escaped 2016
to get away from Barry.
Mm-mm. Excuse me.
I escaped 2016
so that I could come see the Waverider
and so that I could time travel.
And?
And also, yes,
I wanted to get away from Barry.
Ah! You realize that's insane, right?
You're holding a grudge
against your best friend
when the world is
potentially going to end.
I'm sorry. My "best friend"?
He only killed my brother.
- He didn't kill...
- Okay, you're right.
He didn't literally kill my brother.
What I mean to say is,
he was responsible.
Okay? He just needed to save his family,
and in doing that,
he ended up destroying mine.
You know, all this time traveling,
fighting aliens, this is the stuff
I used to dream about as a kid.
Heh. Yeah, me too.
But it doesn't feel like a dream.
It just feels weird.
Well, exactly, and it's
only gonna get weirder.
So that's why we have to be
able to rely on our friends.
I really wish I could
right now, Felicity.
But he's not my friend.
- They're taking off.
- I don't get it.
Why are the Dominators attacking us,
then just leaving?
It's an RIF mission.
"Reconnaissance in force."
Ah, look.
A straggler.
We need him alive, Mick.
I'm just gonna rough him up a little.
Hey!
Whoa!
Aah! Squeal, you pig!
Hey, Dad?
Dad.
What? Oh, I'm sorry.
Can you hand me those induction clamps?
Yes.
You know, this reminds me of that time
we stayed up all night
building my seventh grade science project.
Remember how mad Mom
got when she found out
you let me drink coffee to stay awake?
No.
I mean, no, no, I should never...
never have let you do that.
Uh, I'm sorry. Will you excuse me?
Are you okay, Dad?
I'm just preoccupied with
my work, that's all.
You know, you're really taking
this whole absent-minded
professor thing to a new level.
- I don't know what you mean.
- Your daughter.
Ever since you've come back,
you've treated her like a total stranger.
That's because she is a total stranger.
I'm sorry. It's just that,
when I last left 2016,
that young woman did not exist.
Wait, you're saying Lily
belongs to another timeline?
That, when Barry created Flashpoint, she...
Unfortunately, this is all my fault.
You see, a month ago, I interacted
with my younger self back in 1987
and unwittingly motivated him...
Me... To sire a child.
So it's because of my carelessness
that this Time Aberration exists.
She is not an Aberration.
She is brilliant and
funny and a lot like you,
just a little less uptight.
Please stop talking about her like this.
She is not a real person.
She is a real person.
She's your daughter.
Wait.
When we finish fighting the Dominators,
you're gonna go back in
time and... erase her?
No.
I am going to restore the timeline.
Unlike your friend Barry,
I have the luxury of fixing my mistakes.
Well done.
I see that you've managed
to catch us a specimen.
I'm afraid we're gonna
have to keep this one.
Who are you?
Just a humble civil servant.
- I don't like guys with badges.
- Easy, Mick.
We just want to ask a few questions.
We'd love to answer 'em, but...
- We're in a bit of a hurry.
- So are we.
Aah!
You don't understand.
We're here to save the future.
And you can tell me all about it...
When you wake up.
Crap, crap, crap.
Where do you think they're taking them?
Those "Men in Black"
types are probably gonna
take 'em to a secret lab
and run experiments on them.
- Have you seen "Stranger Things"?
- Maybe too much TV, Cisco.
Life imitates art, Felicity.
Either way, whether you like it or not,
we're gonna have to be
the ones to rescue them.
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But we're the tech support.
No. This is tech support.
Set your phasers to "stun."
This is why I hate the government.
Can't you two use your powers
and get us out of here?
Whatever they tranqed us with
is screwing with our powers.
Hey, he's still alive.
Although something tells me
none of us are gonna be alive for long.
Wait.
This is the exact opportunity
we've been looking for.
To get captured?
No. To talk with one of the Dominators.
And find out what they
want with our planet.
Well, this is a first.
Talking with an alien.
Excuse me, Mr. Alien Guy.
So where's the president?
She's late.
Well, you got to figure
she's got a lot on her plate,
what with the whole alien invasion thing.
And her predecessor getting killed.
Hey, what'd you say to Kara earlier?
She seemed pretty angry.
I didn't know she was
capable of being angry.
We've got movement.
I'm sorry. President couldn't make it.
Who are you?
If I tell you...
I'll have to kill you.
Look,
we just want to know why
you attacked our planet.
I mean, we're just down here
minding our own business,
then you guys just drop
from the sky and attack us.
Why?
There has been a recent emergence
of meta-humans on your planet.
Wait. He's talking about the JSA.
We are here to determine
if your kind are a threat.
Let's start with him.
Rest of you will have to wait your turn.
Uh, I think we have a misunderstanding.
See, we're the good guys.
The president invited us here.
Barry, I think it's time we do something.
And fast.
- Sniper!
- On it.
We're trying to help you.
This is how you thank us?
You don't understand.
The reason the xenomorphs are here...
Because they have a
beef with the meta-humans.
Tell us something we don't know.
Like what exactly have we done to them?
Nothing. Yet.
But they see individuals
with powers such as yours
as a future threat,
and, frankly, so do I.
What do you think they're doing to him?
Same thing they're gonna do to us
unless we get out of here.
Oh, yeah! Y'all call for tech support?
Great. Saved by geeks.
Waverider's ready to
take us back to 2016.
If we leave him here,
they're gonna kill him.
So what? He's an alien.
Just 'cause they're douches
doesn't mean we have to be.
- Well...
- We got to send him home.
How?
Don't we have one of their
ships aboard the Waverider?
Yeah, but it's damaged.
Felicity's gonna help me fix it.
I am?
I'm gonna help him fix it.
See?
Oh, that doesn't sound good.
Guys, it's up to us
to show the Dominators
we're better than this.
Fascinating.
The creature's nervous
system is not unlike our own,
which means it must be
capable of experiencing pain.
Maybe that's why he's screaming.
Don't worry. We're gonna
get you out of here.
Bye.
He didn't even say thank you.
What is that?
I think it's a transponder.
Where'd you get that?
I may or may not have stolen it.
From his ship.
What does it do?
I think we can use it
to communicate with him
when we get back.
Oh, my God, like an alien pen pal.
- Exactly.
- You kids finished?
- Gideon.
- Yes, Mr. Rory?
- Prepare for, um...
- Time jump.
Course plotted for Central City, 2016.
If you're such BFFs
with the Dominators...
Then why don't you call them off?
We know you sent them packing
once before, back in 1951.
That was just a reconnaissance mission.
What brought them back?
You did, Mr. Allen.
He knows who you are.
You threatened the entire universe
when you used your powers
to upset the normal course of time.
You're talking about Flashpoint?
How do you even know about...
They told us.
I made a mistake. Okay?
I'm not gonna let it happen again.
For the past 60 years,
we have enjoyed a truce with
your so-called Dominators.
You broke the truce.
What do they want?
I've negotiated a deal with them.
If Mr. Allen surrenders himself...
They will leave us in peace.
You really want to save the world?
Here's your chance.
I can't see. Why can't I see?
At least you're not throwing up.
Oh.
- What's it doing?
- I don't know.
Either our food's ready or
this guy's trying to call us.
Hey, how... how do... How do I answer?
I...
Hey. Oh, my God. It's him.
He's even uglier than
the last time we saw him.
65 of your years ago,
you saved me from capture.
Listen, you don't need to thank us.
Yeah, he does.
He can thank us by turning around
and heading home.
I will show you my gratitude
by sparing your lives,
but I cannot do the same for Barry Allen.
If your friend does not turn himself in,
we will have no choice
but to deploy a weapon
that will exterminate all meta-humans.
It's a trap.
If they're that threatened
by meta-humans,
it's hard to believe they'd
be satisfied with just one.
Yeah, well, if I know Barry,
he's gonna want to be that one.
Well, Oliver's trying
to talk him out of it.
And if he does,
what's the collateral damage
of the meta-bomb?
Projected casualty count
is around 2 million non-meta-humans.
Okay, so what if we negotiated with them?
Yeah, I don't know if you noticed,
but our last chat with
him didn't go so well.
Well, what've we got to lose?
Look, maybe we should contact them.
Then make it fast.
We've got incoming.
Dominator ships are coming in worldwide.
Including Central City.
Yeah, but they're not moving or anything.
- They're just sitting there.
- For now.
So much for the truce
Secret Agent Man negotiated.
They're trying to leverage
us into handing Barry over.
Contact the Dominators.
Looks like your friend's
not calling you back.
No, he's not, but I got a plan B.
- Okay.
- If this came from the dropship
and the dropship came
from the mother ship,
theoretically, I could use
it to vibe us up there.
And if you can't?
Then I'd be vibing us into the cold,
unforgiving vacuum of space.
- So let's not do that.
- Yeah, let's not. Okay.
What an unusual gift.
You appear to be a meta-human as well.
Yeah, well, I figured
you'd cut me some slack,
seeing as how we saved you back in 1951.
Remember that?
Much has changed on your planet
in the last 60 years.
The threat of your kind
has become imminent.
Listen, E.T. We're not a threat.
Metas are protecting this planet.
And besides, the guy who
tortured your ugly ass
back in 1951 was human.
But what happens when a man like him
inherits abilities like yours?
We have seen it happen on
countless other worlds,
which is why we must
exterminate your kind
before the scourge of your planet
becomes the scourge of ours.
Well, he's out of his giant mind.
What if he's right?
What if, in using our powers
to make the world better,
we actually end up destroying it?
Dude, I get it. Barry screwed up.
Yeah, so did we.
Back in 1951.
We messed with time
when we freed the Dominator.
Who's now coming to kill us.
This whole time, I've been mad at Barry,
and now I'm the one who messed with time.
I just wanted to make things right,
and we ended up making them worse.
I'm an idiot.
Can't stabilize the nanomolecular reaction.
Damn it!
Well...
Speaking as a daughter,
I'm not sure that outburst had
anything to do with our project.
What, you think it's related to me?
She doesn't know that you
think she's an Aberration.
All she knows is that her father
is keeping her at arm's length.
The world is being invaded by aliens.
I don't think this is the
time for family therapy.
It is, when the world's best
chance at a workable weapon
is focused on getting
her daddy to love her.
Lily?
I'm sorry.
Mom always said I got my temper from you.
No, no. I'm the one who owes the apology.
If it feels like I've
been keeping my distance,
I assure you, it's nothing personal.
Yeah, it... It feels personal.
No, I mean, it's not personal to you.
I'm sorry. I wish I could explain,
but my life has gotten
rather complicated lately.
So?
You raised me to enjoy complexity.
That's...
The nanomolecular reaction
keeps breaking down
because the replication
is sequential, not...
Exponential.
The reaction requires greater complexity.
Yeah.
Why are you looking at me like that?
Because I truly believe
I'm seeing you for the first time.
What is it?
My friend Barry.
He's about to do something terrible.
This isn't up for debate.
It's not even a close call. I mean...
Turn myself over to the Dominators,
they leave the rest of the world alone.
Simple.
No, it's not simple.
Barry, it doesn't matter
what you've done.
You can't do this.
It's been an honor to know all of you,
to fight alongside of you.
Now it's up to you to keep our home safe.
Barry!
I'm not letting you leave.
No offense, Oliver, but
you and what army?
This one.
Listen, Red. I don't like you.
But when you got a crew,
you don't take a hit for the rest.
That was actually pretty inspiring.
I mean, up until the point
that Mick compared us to a
bunch of criminals, but...
According to the Dominators,
we might as well be.
And maybe they're right.
Maybe we do more harm than good,
but this is our chance to find out.
We're not letting you sacrifice yourself.
There's no way.
I don't care if that's
what it means to be a hero.
You're not a hero to me.
You're my friend.
Yo. Guys.
You know that ship that
landed in Central City?
It's opening up.
Here we go.
Reading reports of ships
opening all over the world.
- Oh, frak.
- Talk to me.
Something from the Dominators'
mothership just broke atmo,
and, not to get too technical,
but it's really, really big
and falling to Earth really, really fast.
It's the meta-bomb.
Why would the uglies drop ships on us
if they're just planning
on blowing us up?
Because the ships were a distraction
to keep us from stopping the meta-bomb.
Too bad, 'cause we're gonna stop it.
We're gonna stop it, right?
Let's hope.
We have to keep the Dominators at bay.
This might help.
I've mass-produced a small device
that, when placed
on individual Dominators,
will cause indescribable agony.
Not the nicest invention,
but this is war.
Nice going.
The caveat, of course,
is that if we activate the weapons
before all the devices are
placed on the Dominators,
they'll know what we're up to.
Well, we got to do it fast.
Only way I know how.
Whoa.
Damn, that's big.
I didn't think it was gonna be so big.
- What are we gonna do?
- You got me.
I only know how to stab,
punch, or skewer things.
Fry, you freaks!
See you later, Dominator.
This thing has to have
a tractor beam, right?
Yep.
It's slowing down, but, like, barely.
Thank you, Cisco. I haven't noticed.
Strap in.
Firestorm, if you're done playing
with your friends out there,
we could really use your help.
I'm on it.
Oof!
Good work planting Professor
Stein's nano-weapons,
but we still got Dominators
all over the country.
This looks like a job for Supergirl.
Thanks, Felicity.
I'm not the least bit insulted.
Ah, sorry. I meant Supergirl and Flash.
This is totally a job for the both of you.
That's what I meant.
Supergirl and... Flash.
Firestorm, we're holding it up.
- But, like, barely.
- Not helping, Cisco.
- Firestorm, do it now!
- Do what?
I believe Ms. Lance intends for us
to transmute the meta-bomb
into something harmless.
I was afraid you were gonna say that.
All right, devices are being planted.
Let me know when I can bring the pain.
Come on, Firestorm.
Grey, I can't do it, man. It's too big.
Still waiting on that signal.
Do it!
Done.
- It's working.
- What about the superhero bomb?
I can't! I can't do it!
You must, Jefferson.
I have a daughter.
Her name is Lily,
and she's counting on you.
She's counting on both of us.
They did it!
They can do that?
They did that.
Ground, what's your status?
They're retreating.
It's not just them.
It's all around the world.
He did it.
- No, Oliver...
- We all did it.
Many responsibilities have fallen to me
since the president's passing
at the beginning of this crisis.
Sobering, sad responsibilities.
This is not one of them.
Today, it is my distinct
honor to bestow upon you
a small acknowledgement of the great debt
that the world owes to you all.
Is it just me, or is she really hot?
Although your brave efforts
must remain a secret...
She's hot.
Know that, meta-human or not,
masked or not,
each and every one of you is a hero.
Whoo!
Whoa.
Thank you.
Hmm, hmm? Let's go drink.
Cheers.
It's like looking into a mirror.
Yeah, you know what's funny?
She really kind of looks like my cousin.
- Hey, hey. Guys.
- Hey.
Either of you ever save
the world before?
- Mm-hmm.
- Last year.
It doesn't get old, does it?
Nope. It sure beats
screwing up the world.
Hey, you are too hard on yourself.
That's what people usually tell me.
And for good reason, I'm sure.
But, back on my Earth,
it's just me and my cousin.
Between the two of us,
we're more powerful than...
Yeah, everybody in this room combined.
No, no. That's the point.
That's what you've all proven here.
Meta-humans an not, superpowers or not,
you are Earth's mightiest heroes.
Um...
I owe you an apology.
Keeping you at arm's length
was the wrong move, and...
Well, the truth is that this Earth
could probably use a Supergirl.
Well, that's... that's funny,
'cause I was just thinking
my Earth could use an Oliver Queen.
I know you said you don't get unnerved...
But if you did,
I think hardship is what
makes us stronger.
That's probably why these people
look to you as their rock.
You guys feeling the group hug?
- No.
- Come on. Come on.
All right.
Hey, Kara.
- I made you something.
- What?
- Cisco.
- Yeah.
What, uh... What is it?
Oh, it's a...
It's an inter-dimensional extrapolator.
- Oh, I...
- It creates small breaches,
so you can use it to
cross over to our universe
any time you need to.
Oh, my God. That's amazing.
I also included
communication functionality,
so if you ever need any help,
you can always contact the team.
Hey, Skirt.
Call me.
All right, Grey. Spill.
How is it you have a kid?
I didn't think I had to explain
such matters to you, Jefferson.
Come on. You know what I mean.
When we traveled back to 1987,
I gave my younger self a lecture
about neglecting Clarissa, and he...
And he followed your advice
all the way to pound town.
Wait.
You created an Aberration.
Which is why you cannot tell the team.
If you don't want me to tell the team,
that means you...
I do not want to lose my daughter.
Something tells me you
weren't invited here.
- Dr. Heywood.
- Don't "Dr. Heywood" me.
What the hell are you doing here?
I like parties,
and I'm here for the mop-up.
Cover-up. But you can't cover this up.
Agent Smith!
It's so funny seeing you here.
I was just having the loveliest chat
with your president about you.
I was telling her, on my Earth,
we have a Department of
Extranormal Operations,
which deals specifically with aliens.
She thought as an excellent idea.
She also loved my pitch
about reassigning you to Antarctica.
Maybe next time, you're a little nicer
to strange visitors from another planet.
Pack a jacket!
You ready to see if Cisco's gadget works?
Ready.
And remember, if you guys ever need me,
I'm just a call away.
Same here.
It's weird to think
that all of this started
with the two of us.
You ever think what it would be like
if we never got on that boat?
I don't know if I have to think about it.
I mean, maybe the Dominators showed us
what our lives would have been like.
I know it was a prison, but in a way...
In a way, it was a gift.
- Stay out of trouble.
- Yeah.
There she goes, off to her spaceship,
time traveling as if it's totally normal.
Well, John, it's like you said.
Normal sort of went out the window
when this one arrived.
I may never understand you, man, but...
you're one of the best men I know.
Thanks, Dig.
So... you forgive me for what I did?
Barry, it's like I keep telling this guy.
You have to forgive yourself.
- Yeah.
- Good luck.
Yeah, thanks.
Well, we got to do this more often.
Get together, I mean.
I don't know if the world could take it.
I meant, like, without the
world being threatened.
If the world wasn't being threatened,
what would we do?
I'm just saying,
next time, I'm gonna get you.
I'm just saying, I beat you twice.
- The first time was a tie.
- And the second time?
There were no witnesses the second time.
Superspeed arrow duels...
Our lives aren't exactly normal.
I told Kara that I was
looking to reclaim some normal.
Thinking on it now, I'm... I'm not so sure.
I know what you mean.
We both got a look at what
life would look like normal.
It would've been happy.
But not full.
No. No, nowhere close.
To things not being normal.
To life being full.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --