[Agent Sharpe]
Previously on Legends Of Tomorrow...
Mick frigging Rory. Ali, remember?
[Sara] She wasn't just some girl,
was she?
Remember when we dented history?
Your sister is the dent.
Maybe her being here,
she'll remember who she was.
How did you jailbreak
your way out of here?
[Zari] I was poking around your screens,
and suddenly,
I knew how to hack my way out.
[Constantine] Astra and this whole
bloody mess is on me.
She could continue
releasing souls indefinitely.
What happened here, John?
That witch is Astra's dead mother.
She's through there.
Her spirit is waiting
on the other side of that door, and...
none too happy with me.
-[door slams]
-[gasps]
-[Constantine screams]
- John?
Blimey, he's really
cocked it up this time.
How could you let him go in there?
That thing is hurting him.
Then he probably deserves it.
-[Constantine wails]
- I can't just stand here.
Being an apprentice means
never having to say,
"Sorry, I let you get killed
by a poltergeist."
[Constantine] Get your filthy paws
off of me!
No. No, no, no, no, no.
Move out of the way.
Are you sure you know what you're doing?
Yes.
Maybe.
[Constantine wails]
[Gary reciting incantation]
[screaming]
Oh, my God.
[gasps]
[Gary] John?
[Constantine grunts]
[Gary gasps]
-[screeching]
-[Gary screaming]
[screeching]
[gasping]
Oh, Gary.
What have you done?
[taps toothbrush]
Sorry. Old Assassin habits die hard.
Babe. Now that you've given me
a heart attack,
I was just about to jump in.
Care to join me?
Whoa, co-showering in
the communal bathroom.
You are getting comfy.
Which is a good thing because
I'm gonna need you to woman the ship.
I've got business in Star City.
[Agent Sharpe] Is everything okay?
[Sara] Yeah, it's just some stuff
I need to take care of,
but it might take a few days,
which is why I need an interim captain.
- Captain?
- Mmm-hmm.
No,no,no,no,no.
I was just starting to find my footing
as a Legend.
Nobody likes the boss, babe.
[Sara] Well, they like me.
Yeah, because you're cool Captain Lance.
I'm just a button-pusher
in a boring pantsuit.
No, babe, just have fun with it.
They are going to love you.
- No. No, no, no.
- Yes.
I miss you already, Captain Pantsuit.
[Agent Sharpe] No, babe. I'm not...
Raise you two.
Make it ten.
Finally. A real hand.
[laughing]
- She folds.
- Like hell I do.
[growls] Like Hell you do.
What the hell are you doing?
Keeping us in the black.
You lost another account.
First Rasputin, then Bugsy--
- John Constantine--
- Now, Meyers.
Your little resurrection venture
is getting too risky.
You turn the tide,
or you'll lose everything.
I've played nice long enough.
Now, it's time to play naughty.
That's one angry ghost.
Yeah, but now,
she's loose in the bloody house.
- What, that was Astra's mum?
- And her name is Natalie.
What did you do to her, John boy?
[sighs] That was a long time ago.
She was walking home late from work,
and some drunken idiot
blew a red light and...
Her husband Alex begged me
to bring her back.
- You never told me that.
- Yeah, well, I never told anyone.
Now, let's just say that
that night in Newcastle
when we lost Astra,
it was a little more complicated
than an exorcism.
[spirit howls]
Something tells me
that you're not telling the truth.
Look, I'm trying to fix it, Nat,
all right?
I'm trying to save Astra! Now, help me!
[screeches]
Doesn't seem to be
the answer she was looking for.
The demon that I summoned
brought Natalie back.
But if you brought her back,
why.., why is she a ghost?
Because I botched it, all right?
I thought I had him under control,
but I didn't.
- You can't have her!
- John, get me out of here!
[Constantine] He took Astra.
Natalie couldn't live with herself
knowing that the price of her life
was her daughter's.
She killed herself in this room.
That's so sad! [screams]
Doesn't look like Natalie's done
with you yet, John-o.
[children giggle]
No, it looks like Natalie wants to
take me on a trip down memory lane.
All righty-tighty, then. You ready
for the official Waverider tour?
- Hmm.
- What would you like to see first?
What do you people do
around here for fun?
If you could just follow me this way.
First stop, the galley.
Gideon can whip up any kind of food
you can imagine.
Last week, Nate and I
made cheddar biscuits
and had her fabricate
some squeezable butter.
That tasty treat has been
off the shelf since 2024.
She can make anything,
and you went
with a discontinued condiment.
- Wait. Can she make clothes?
- Of course.
Okay, tell the computer I need a dress
for my perfume launch tonight.
- We'll be back in time for that, right?
- Yes.
And yes, Gideon can do anything.
She flies the ship, makes our food,
cleans the toilets, tracks the timeline.
Tracks the time...
Do you mean, "Tells the future"?
Behrad, we can make billions
off future fall trend reports.
[clears throat]
No, no. Rule number one of time travel,
never look into the future
for personal gain.
Totally, totally.
And rule number two,
no social media on the ship.
[device chirps]
I thought we were dropping you off.
My brother, the actual superhero...
invited me to stay.
Okay. Let's just remember
this is a place of business.
Okay? We get called on a mission,
you need to keep out of our way.
Aye-aye. [clicks tongue]
Okay. We'll talk later.
[sighs]
Sad. What a waste
of a good head of hair.
Here you go. Hide it.
Can your computer lady
make me some cucumber water?
I'm parched from that dry interaction.
She and her mom had been living
out of their car for almost a year,
and now, her mom has
a final round job interview.
You are incredible.
I miss you.
But it feels pretty good
to be out here helping people.
- Out.
- Ah,
It's okay, I have to go anyway.
Okay, well, um, I'll call you later.
I love you.
[stammers] I'm sorry,
I just kind of blurted that out.
No, it's okay. It's okay.
Uh, you don't have to be sorry.
I love you, too.
- You do?
- I said get out.
Okay, I'll call you later. Bye.
[sighs]
Mick, are you feeling all right?
My stomach hurts. I can't eat.
I... I can't drink.
I think Ali gave me an STD
back at the reunion.
[Gideon] Initiating scan.
Those are not symptoms.
Those are feelings.
Mick, I think you're developing a crush.
Is that when you whizz and it hurts?
No. It's biology's way of telling you
you care about someone else.
[Gideon] Dr. Palmer is correct.
The results of my body scan indicate
that you do, in fact, like-like her.
[grumbles]
Interim Captain Sharpe here. Team
meeting in the parlor. Over and out.
Okay. That was good. That was fun,
yet to the point. Not too...
Gideon, are you broadcasting this?
[Gideon] Sorry, Ms. Sharpe.
I'll shut it down.
Okay, thank you.
We women have to stick together.
I always thought of you
as one of the guys.
[Agent Sharpe] Okay,
I don't know what that means--
- He means that as a compliment.
- Yeah.
Okay, that's for you. That's for you.
[Behrad] Okay, then.
Okay.
What did I say about phones?
What? I need to tell my boyfriend
I'm not dead.
Uh, boyfriend?
Yep. Internationally renowned DJ
S'More Money.
Ah, okay, we've got Ray.
Uh, where's Mick?
He's sick. Lovesick.
- Aw.
-[chuckles] Oh, lei.
So, while Sara's in Star City,
I wanted to introduce you all
to something that I developed
at the Time Bureau.
I know what you're all thinking.
"Time Bureau, hashtag stuffy.
What can we learn from those guys?"
But we really did have
a lot of fun over there.
Do you remember Taco Mondays, Nate?
- Yeah, those were some wild taco times.
-[Agent Sharpe] Yeah.
-"Aloha"?
- Yes!
A.L.O.H.A. It stands for assess,
listen, observe, hydrate...
- Attack!
- What the...
- Cool.
- See?
Uh, how many pages is this?
Ava, have you heard the proverb,
"The fox knows many things,
the hedgehog knows one big thing."
I have not.
Well, Legends,
we're a fox kind of organization.
Adaptable, off the cuff.
This is very hedgehog.
Trying to impose one way of doing things
onto every situation.
And not to be rude,
is there, uh, a mission here?
No, I just--
Okay, then, I'm gonna introduce Zari
to the wonders
of Gideon's Austrian toast.
Actually, it's, uh, French toast.
Pretty sure it's Austrian.
[Nate] Nah...
Gideon, Gideon, check the timeline.
[Gideon] It would appear
that there is a disturbance
at the Bastille in Paris, 1793.
While the details are still hazy,
the aftermath is traumatic.
Thousands die
and the French Revolution collapses.
Well, looks like we have a mission.
So, everybody,
stop looking so Les Misérables,
because we are going to France!
Behrad, come on, we need to move.
[sighs]
[door opens]
Hey, guys.
I couldn't stop her.
She found the fabrication room.
Great. She's not coming.
We don't do ride-alongs in the field, B.
Ava, I can handle myself in the field.
I once played capture the flag to
raise awareness about feline OCD, so...
This isn't a PR event, all right?
We're walking into a deadly situation,
facing an Encore with unknown powers.
I do not have time to keep my eye
on a party girl.
- I do.
-[Agent Sharpe] What?
I mean, come on, Ava. What's the harm?
It's against protocol
-to bring civilians into the field.
-[sucks teeth]
- Don't... [sucks teeth]
Yeah, but it would be super-cool
if you just let me come anyway.
Uh...
- Okay, fine.
- Yay!
Just, uh, make sure
you stay out of our way.
- Yay!
-[spraying]
[gags,coughs]
What the hell was that?
My signature perfume, Dragonesque.
I needed to do something to help
that extremely sad outfit.
[coughs]
Spray, delay, walk away.
Yeah, we're going this way. Jesus.
I was just doing a runway turn.
[people clamoring]
[Agent Sharpe] This period in France
was called the Reign of Terror.
Executions were a national pastime.
-[all gasp]
- Oh, yikes.
[Nate] Yeah, we could definitely
be walking into a bloodbath.
And you want us to go in there?
Yeah, that's our job.
[Agent Sharpe clears throat]
Excuse me, sir.
Uh, we need to get in there.
No.
It is of vital importance
that we get in there, sir.
Please? [gasps]
Stand back.
This isn't a club, Zari,
it's an execution.
An event is an event.
Scoot. Out of the way.
Where do you think you're going?
Um, do you know who you're talking to?
What's your name?
- Jean Paul.
- Tres bien.
Now, they'll know who to fire
when they find out you left Zari Tarazi
standing outside.
Un grand faux pas.
Not them.
Jean Paul, my purse isn't going to
walk in by itself.
[lively orchestral music playing]
[Zari] Um, didn't you say
this was an execution?
[Ray] Maybe Gideon got it wrong.
Well, if they were miserable,
they certainly aren't anymore.
Stop with the thing.
You know, you can just say the word
and I'll put you in a prime spot uptown.
[laughs] So I can rub shoulders
with all those arrogant soul traders?
No, thank you.
I need some help
with one of the coins you constructed.
Help. When else do you come see me?
I assume this is why you're here.
- How did you--
-[chuckles] John Constantine.
I remember making this.
- What do you want for him?
- Oh, I don't want to trade him.
I want 110 kill him.
[sighs]
Tourist attraction number two.
The night Alex begged me
to save Natalie.
He was supposed to pick her up
that night she got hit,
but they had a big fight,
so, she walked.
Alex was beside himself, he was torn up.
Astra, she hadn't said a word
since the accident.
How was I supposed to say no?
Alex begged me,
but I knew I should have said no.
[all ringing]
[Charlie] Bollocks, John!
Come on, try again!
Well, Alex wanted it,
and I just provided the how, all right?
What's the difference, Nat?
- So, the resurrection was your idea.
- Yes, all right?
Nat and I, we were best friends.
How could I not try and save her?
See? The truth can set you free.
[rock song blaring]
Is that Mucous Membrane?
[lively orchestral music playing]
[cheering]
This place doesn't seem too evil.
Yeah, well, appearances can be
deceiving. Okay, we need to figure out
who this Encore is
and what powers they may have.
We start with
the A.L.O.H.A, method, okay?
Assessment, lay low, don't engage.
We know how to party-sneak.
Listen to me, you see something,
you say something.
- Captain. You're trying too hard.
- Yeah.
[whispers] It's really desperate.
So, this is your job.
Walking around parties.
- Isn't this kind of what you do?
- Touché.
No.
But something definitely feels off.
At this point in the French Revolution,
most of the royals
had been separated from their heads.
Even wearing a nice dress
could get you sent to the guillotine.
Uh, and you let me
come out in this because?
I'm a sucker for a corset and an updo.
Napoleon?
[Zari] He should be marching on
southern France, not getting freaky.
[scoffs] Guys, steer clear.
Exercise extreme caution.
- Relax, Ava.
- I'm trying.
Nora?
Ava? I think we found our Encore.
She's in the VIP area.
- Nora's our Encore?
- No, Ray.
That's Marie Antoinette.
And she should definitely be
without her head by now.
[Agent Sharpe] Great. On to
phase two of A.L.O.H.A., it's listening.
Now, her powers could be anything.
Teleportation, pyrokinesis.
Fatal attractiveness.
- I mean... Right?
- Right? [chuckles]
Guys? Guys?
They're not usually like this.
- Well, you're not usually captain.
- Thank you.
I just swapped crepe recipes
with a French cooking legend.
This is the best party ever.
Excuse me, since when do you drink?
Whoa.
Where did I even get that?
You know what? You're right,
something is definitely wrong.
Move out of the way.
It is time!
Of course.
The perfect revenge.
A magical guillotine.
Shh.
Guys, be careful.
I think Marie's about to make her move.
Now!
-[reveler gasps]
- Let them eat cake!
[all cheering]
-[in French accent] Pardon me.
- Pardon me.
[both speaking French]
So, it's not a guillotine.
What day is it?
Uh, how long have you been here?
[gasps]
Oh, my God, he's dead.
Ugh. He literally
partied himself to death.
- So tacky.
- Look. No, he's not the only one.
What is happening?
That's why I don't eat carbs.
This woman is next-level popular.
People would rather die than leave.
- Talk about FOMO.
- God, that's it.
Marie Antoinette was beheaded
for partying while France starved,
and now, she is literally
killing the Revolution
with a non-stop party.
Legends, we figured it out.
Charm is her superpower.
Hello? Ray? Nate? Behrad?
It's like she's gotten to everyone
except for us.
So, we have to stop this.
- Wait. I'm on the team?
- Sure.
Okay, what's the plan?
Uh...
We have to find a way
to get Marie Antoinette out of here
without a riot.
The only way to get a celebrity
to leave her own party quietly,
is to make her think
there's a cooler party somewhere else
that she's not at.
- Let's go tell her.
- Uh, girl.
You're not going to get anywhere
in this ensemble.
What are you doing? Stop it.
Hey.
Trust me.
-[sighs]
- Shh.
Come on.
[rock song continues]
That's her. Natalie.
- She's good.
- Yeah.
[both laugh]
You loved her.
It's quite the track record, isn't it?
One lover sent to Hell,
the other one a ghost.
Please, John, it's eating you up.
You have to stop.
Look, Natalie, you're gonna have
to trust me on this one, all right?
I've got it under control.
If Lester hadn't been there,
I would have lost you tonight.
Look, let's just leave all this behind.
We'll go to New York. We'll start clean.
You have to choose. Magic or me.
Screw you, John Constantine!
All right, that's enough, all right?
I don't want you in my head
or in my memories!
No more games!
Look, we're trapped in this house
with a knife-wielding ghost,
and you're still refusing to own up
to your past.
You are a fine one to talk, aren't you?
Why don't we poke around
in your closet for a while, eh?
- Why did you leave, Charlie?
-[Gary] Uh, guys?
- I'm no hero. It was time to go.
- Guys. Guys. Guys!
Yeah? What, you just wandered
into my house looking for a party?
What are you really doing here, eh?
Don't even try and turn this
on me, all right?
It's your lies
that have trapped us here.
[in Natalie's voice] She's right, John.
Natalie, is that really you?
[lively piano music playing]
[Zari] Every level of the party
has its guardians.
Getting past the bouncer, easy.
Getting past the friends...
you need to know someone.
But we don't know anybody.
I know...
that guy.
You know Napoleon?
No, but they don't know that.
Bonjour, Napoleon.
We're with him.
Oh, she's separated from the pack.
Now's the time.
Oh, good. Work your magic.
Oh, teaching moment.
The big secret to being cool?
Confidence.
It makes people think
you have something they don't.
- You got this, Captain. There you go.
- No, but I don't... Ah--
-[sighs]
-[Marie laughs]
Thank you.
[both squealing]
[both laughing]
I do not know you.
What are you doing here?
-[voice trembles] Uh...
- Hmm?
- Leaving.
- Leaving?
Actually, I am going to the after-party.
What is this après party?
Mmm.
It's a party after the party.
It's the best place to be.
- Where is it?
- Mmm, I can't tell you.
-[gasps]
- But I can take you.
Really? Take me.
Oh, Oh.
Um, this is my bestie, Zari.
She's coming with.
Yas, queen. Mmm.
Guys, I have Marie
and we're taking her to the Waverider.
That's a great idea.
We'll have her all to ourselves.
- Whoo!
- Marie, come back!
There is an après party!
[all clamoring]
Guys, you have company.
The after-party is right this way.
[all cheer]
Corsets are so impractical!
Marie, where's the party?
I do not think this is a good idea.
We're gonna party our faces off.
It's gonna be great.
[screams]
Ew.
Should've seen that coming.
Return me to my body this instant--
Okay, body, Here we go.
This is weird.
This party stinks!
Oh, so true, girl.
But not the point.
- She's annoying. You can just...
- Yeah.
[Marie] Take this thing off of me!
Ugh, I can't believe I tried to drink.
I can't believe I ate
all that gluten-filled cake.
I can't believe how heavy that head is.
Yeah, she really had you
under her spell.
If it weren't for
our interim Legend here,
you guys would've partied to death.
Well, just to play it safe, I'm gonna...
[Marie] Stay away! Don't you touch me!
- Gonna take this into the library.
- I'll bite your finger! [yelps]
- I'll help you.
- Don't get creepy, Ray.
So, my sister, the superhero.
Should I get Gideon to make you a cowl?
Mmm, cowls are for middle-aged women
who wanna hide their necks.
But I do need a dress
for the party tonight.
- The fabricator's all yours.
- Yay! Thank you.
[thunder crashing]
Is that really you, Nat?
[in Natalie's voice]
I need to hear you say it.
Why did you bring me back?
Because I loved you, Nat.
I never stopped.
I'm not here for the John Constantine
broken hero act.
Say it to my face.
I need to hear the truth.
I brought you back...
to prove to you that I was right.
To show you that I was right
to choose magic over us.
Thank you.
I needed you to admit
to yourself what you did.
Because if you're going to save Astra,
you need to do it for her,
not for your ego.
Oh, I have tried to save her, Nat.
I have tried, but I don't know how.
I think I found away.
Uh, yoo-hoo. [flaps lips]
Hello? Excuse me?
Can you help me? Where is my body?
You were throwing a party
intended to kill people,
so, no, not gonna help you.
When I was 14,
I was forced to leave my family.
People saw the dresses,
the parties, the hair...
and they assumed I was a spoiled brat.
Really, I was just
a lonely Viennese girl
trying to fit into French society.
I've been famous
since I was six years old.
I don't know if people love me
or love to hate me.
What they don't understand is how hard
I work to create a fantasy for them.
The secret is
to never let the party stop.
If I had known then what I know now...
Gidget, is there anything
I need to worry about?
[Gideon] Interim Captain Sharpe
instructed you
not to look at your future.
[sighs] Just a peek,
little lady computer.
As you wish. October 7th, 2045...
Zari Tarazi faces major backlash
from her fans,
known as Z-Nation, after the FDA
banned her perfume Dragonesque
for destroying users' sense of smell.
Oh, no.
I trusted her! I wanted to be her,
but now, I'll never smell another flower
because of her.
From Z-Nation to Zero-Nation,
Zari Tarazi's Cat-Chat followers
have plummeted
to almost zero.
[gasps]
Meow! [chuckles]
But I didn't know there was anything
wrong with the perfume.
This is so unfair.
Okay, I have to
get out in front of this.
Maybe Gidget can make me a new perfume.
Or I can just take yours.
No, you cannot have it.
I mean, it's not like you're using it.
You have half a neck.
[speaking French]
Why do you care so much
about a bottle of...
Oh! You're not super-charming.
You used magical popularity perfume.
Honestly, that makes me feel
better about myself.
What are you doing?
[muffled protests]
Can't have you ratting me out.
Oh, there you are. Thank God. Thank God.
I have been so worried,
but don't.., don't worry,
I've... I've totally been keeping up
your Cat-Chat account.
Yesterday, I posted a picture
of a cat licking
a tube of Dragonesque lipstick.
Gross, Les-Lay, I would never post that.
I am so sorry, I will delete it.
And here is the hero bottle
for the photoshoot.
Actually, change of plans.
- Oh, so retro. [laughs]
- Take this.
Oh!
- Hey, Z... Whoa, whoa, whoa.
- Hi!
- Watch the s'more. What are you doing?
- Sorry, babe.
So, have you decided where
you want to do the proposal yet?
- The what?
- Didn't my agent call you?
Yeah, I haven't had a chance
to tell you yet, Z,
but S'More's team came up with
the most epic idea.
He should propose to you
at next week's MTV Movie Awards
in advance of your DJ and Z
co-branded sunglasses launch.
We're getting married?
Yo, we could do it
somewhere more chill, you know,
like at the DJ S'More Money
Spring Break House Party live cast,
something like that?
- How romantic.
- Yeah, it's gonna be dope.
-[S'More] Okay, let's do this. Hey!
- You're ready for this. Let's go.
Okay, one spritz should be safe.
Spray, delay, walk away.
You have to do a 23andMe.
I mean, she must be related to you.
Here, doesn't she look exactly like you?
Ray, I am looking at a gagged,
decapitated woman.
If that's what you think I look like,
we have a lot of processing to do.
Oh, no, but... Sorry, Ms. Antoinette.
[high-pitched] Thief!
Can you taste the cardamom?
I can't. I can't taste anything
because your sister's perfume
clogged up my entire olfactory system.
Everything tastes like--
Zari... [panting] Zari stole
Marie Antoinette's perfume.
You should see what Mick
stole from Mexico, it's disgusting.
Consider ourselves lucky.
At least she didn't do something
to screw up history.
Oh, my God, the perfume!
That's how Marie did it.
Zari and I weren't affected
'cause we couldn't smell
because of the Dragonesque.
Who knows what kind of damage
she could do with that?
It's all my fault.
I shouldn't have let her stay.
I knew it was too early
to pat myself on the back.
Ah. Look, it wouldn't be a true Legends'
mission unless something went wrong.
[object clatters]
[object smashes]
Or several things.
Uh, wasn't there
a body on that stretcher?
[photographers clamoring]
-[photographer 1] Zari!
-[photographer 2] Zari! Over here!
[S'More] Have I told you how hot
you look in that dress?
No, but you can tell me now.
Super-hot!
And you smell fantastic!
You know what, screw our agents.
I don't wanna wait
till the fall launch
of our sunglasses in October
to begin my life with you.
Hey, listen up. S'More Money
has an announcement to make.
Zari Tarazi, will you marry me?
Oh, S'More--
[gasps]
[all sniffing]
I think I just got a little too popular.
Oh, God.
Here, body, body, body, body.
Oh.
- Okay, body. No one wants to hurt you.
-[clanking]
Speak for yourself.
Hey, come on, Mick. She's harmless.
It's just a headless body.
[gasps]
Mick, a little help here.
Just target the right arm.
No, Mick, don't...
Okay, we need to protect ourselves.
Zari's deployed Marie's perfume.
Ahh!
[groans]
[all coughing and gagging]
Okay, team, A.L.O.H.A, time.
Run! Run!
Nate, what do you got?
I'm assessing Zari used too much
of the perfume
'cause this crowd is bananas.
- Behrad?
- I'm listening
and I hear another mob coming.
Okay, I'm observing and there are way
too many people for us to stop.
We need to get that perfume
off of her to stop this.
- How?
- I have an idea. I need your help.
[Agent Sharpe] Behrad, now!
[crowd gasping]
- You guys came back for me.
- A Legend never gets left behind,
even an interim one. Follow me.
- What are you doing?
- Trust me.
[Behrad] There's too many of them.
I can't stop them all.
- Come on!
- Okay.
Well, we've tried the A.L.O.H.A, method.
The A.L.O, haven't got us anywhere.
What does the "H" stand for?
Hydrate!
- S'Mores.
- Yeah.
- Zari's boyfriend?
- That's me.
- Okay, guys.
- Oh, God.
Party's over.
Did Zari just jump into the fountain?
[scoffs] Talk about desperate stunts.
I'm calling my agent
to schedule a divorce!
Wait, what does that last "A" stand for?
Attack!
[both panting]
[Natalie] Look at us.
We thought we could change the world
with our little loom.
This one's to bring me mum back.
The Loom of Fate.
It's not just a story, it's real.
Three old Greek birds cutting threads,
hunkering down over a loom to weave
together the fate of humankind.
No, if it's real,
how come I haven't heard of it, eh?
You're asking the wrong person.
Why do you think I brought her here?
[gasps]
What the bloody hell was that?
What do you know about the Loom of Fate?
- I know bugger all.
- How'd you find this place, Charlie?
You told me about it.
Oh, bollocks,
I've never told anyone about it.
Natalie brought you here to help me
save Astra and stop those Encores.
So tell me, what do you know
about the Loom of Fate?
Fate's a load of crap.
You haven't answered
my question, Charlie.
- You wanna know what I'm hiding from?
- Yes, I do!
It's that bloody Loom!
- So, it is real.
- It was.
Until I destroyed it.
"Lady in Cheap Pantsuit Ruins Party."
Ava was right
about no phones on the ship.
I had Gideon whip you up
some new clothes. Hope you like flannel.
I do not. Ew.
Listen, I know you're gonna tell me
how selfish I was
for stealing the perfume
and burning the team.
You guys toil away in obscurity
to save humanity
from unknown baddies
and I just go and spray evil perfume
all over New York City
without a second thought.
I'm a jerk. I'm sorry.
I was gonna ask if you wanted a donut.
I haven't had a donut in 1,743 days.
What is this donut?
-[both] Shut up, Marie.
- Ah... [grumbles]
Getting healthier...
[Behrad] Hey.
Wow. Nice shirt.
Hmm. You would be into lumberjack chic.
[Gideon] There's an incoming hologram
from Captain Lance.
Captain.
How'd the mission go?
Oh, um...
- Well, I--
- Killed it.
She was a foxy hedgehog out there.
[hisses]
Okay.
We got our Encore, Captain.
Oh, good, I'm glad to hear it.
Ava, call me later,
so I can thank you properly.
O captain, my captain.
[Nate] "Call me later, so I can
properly congratulate you..."
[Ray] Guys, come on.
[Agent Sharpe]
She doesn't sound like that.
Zari! [whistles]
Hey, are you okay?
Yeah, I was...
I was just, uh, enjoying this donut.
And thinking...
You locked Marie Antoinette up,
but you let me off the hook.
I mean, she killed people, Zari.
You screwed up.
You know, everybody screws up.
- Not you.
- Me? [chuckles]
I feel like I'm
screwing up all the time.
You were so on-mission.
You crashed an A-list party
in a pantsuit
and threw yourself into a fountain.
Ugh, see? It's a perfect example.
No, it was amazing.
You didn't care what anyone thought.
You were just being you.
I've been trying to get people
to like me for so long, that...
I've forgotten who I really am.
I have millions of followers,
but zero friends.
You got one.
Really?
Come on.
Hmm. Well, as your friend,
I have to tell you,
no more pantsuits.
You're better than that.
Deal.
He still has ten years before
the lung cancer catches up to him.
Can you make it zero?
That's a nasty way to go,
especially all at once.
You sure that's who you wanna be?
Why is it so hard for people
to let little girls grow up?
John may be the villain in your story,
but in mine, he's just
cocktail party conversation.
I have a few enemies of my own.
One day, I'm going to call you
and you are going to do me a favor.
You make "favor" sound like "sin."
This is Hell, sweetie.
Do it.
You broke the Loom of Fate?
How old are you?
Old.
If you broke it,
why are you still running?
I scattered those damn pieces
all across the multi-verse.
Just put an end to it all.
But recently, I sensed that
something had changed.
It's like my past
was catching up with me. So...
[coughing violently]
John, are you okay?
Yeah. I just got a...
Bye-bye, Johnny.
[rapid ticking]
[inaudible]
[theme music playing]