[soft dramatic music]
- So there are aliens
scattered throughout history.
[body thuds]
- [gasps]
- Oh.
- And on our windshield.
- Mick, no.
- No, no, no, no!
- No, you're hurting it.
- Rory!
- Yikes.
- Wow.
- That was a lead.
That alien could have
told us something
about Sara's whereabouts.
- No, girl, that alien is dead.
- We don't know that.
We actually don't know
anything about these creatures.
Hey, some species could survive
head-on collisions.
- With a spaceship?
- Going thousands
of miles an hour?
- Stop.
Spooner, are you
getting any readings?
- It's dead.
- Ugh.
- But the face-sucking
squid beasts
in those other pods
just got dumped
into the river of time.
- Fantastic.
- Sounds like
more unpaid labor to me.
- Okay, so every single one
of those aliens
was on the ship with Sara,
which means we just have
to find one of them,
and it should lead us
back to my girl, right?
- Your fiancée.
- Right.
[chuckles]
- Gidget,
please find us some aliens.
- Please.
- Actually, Ms. Tarazi,
it appears we already
have a bite, so to speak.
- Where?
♪ ♪
[exciting synth music]
- Okay, Gideon, what do we got?
- October 10, 1955,
San Bernardino, California,
A town known as the birthplace
of fast food.
- And ergo the death
of the great American eatery.
Before fast food,
mom and pop burger joints
were the beating heart
of every town.
- Funny you should mention it,
Mr. Tarazi.
The anomaly seems to have
started at Big Bang Burger
owned by local businessman
Bert Beeman,
and within 24 hours,
San Bernardino went
from bustling suburban enclave
to...
[blood splashes]
- Ew.
- Whoa.
- The entire population
was killed overnight
leaving no survivors.
Historians dubbed it
the Massacre on Main Street.
- Mm, no, I would've gone
with Suburban Slaughter.
- Save it for the podcast.
Ah.
- This is good news.
- Y'all are dark.
- We'll go back, stop
the alien, and it can tell us
how to find Sara.
- Okay, so--
- And what exactly
is the plan here?
- Oh, the--
well, you're the plan.
[chuckles]
So you're gonna
help us find the alien
and then you're gonna get it
to tell us where Sara is.
- Uh, no way.
I'm only staying on this ship
till you guys
get this thing out of my head.
That was the deal.
- Apologies, Ms. Cruz,
but that won't be possible.
- What?
- I was gonna tell you
before the whole,
you know, alien pods thing.
Gideon didn't find
anything to remove.
I'm sorry.
- So first you kidnap me,
then you lied.
Take me home now.
- Look, um, I'm really sorry,
but I can't do that.
I need you to talk
to the alien.
- This thing's
not gonna give us directions
to find your girlfriend.
It's gonna kill us.
- Look, you're amongst
board-certified superheroes.
You don't have to worry
about getting killed.
- They took your captain.
If you guys are so super,
then why didn't you
just stop them then?
- Listen to me.
I need you to help us
find Sara, okay?
After you do that,
I will take you
wherever the hell you wanna go.
[soft dramatic music]
[The Cleftones' "Angel Lover"]
- ♪ My angel lover ♪
[car horn honks]
[doo-wop music]
- Oh, look at those
perfect patties.
Get 'em out while they're hot,
and don't forget--
service with a smile.
- Whoo-hoo!
- We got another one
at the window!
Up, let's go, let's go!
Keep it moving!
We got a lot of mouths to feed.
- ♪ Dreams come true today ♪
♪ You make me feel that way ♪
♪ My love ♪
- Wel-wel-wel-welcome
to Big Bang Burger!
Try our new
Cosmic Mushroom Burger!
- What, you think aliens
are funny?
- It's a paycheck.
- The goal is to blend, okay?
You picking up
any alien signals?
- Mm-mm.
- Mm.
Guys, hey, split up, mingle,
find out if anyone's
seen anything that could
lead us to the alien.
- [clicks tongue]
- [sighs]
And Sara.
- ♪ That I could
ever be untrue ♪
- [groans]
Sara...
[groans]
Are you okay?
- We just crash landed
on an alien spaceship.
No, Gary, I am not okay.
- [speaking in alien language]
- Oh, boy, that's not good.
- What did Alien Gideon say?
- Uh, it's a little hard
to translate exactly
since in my language
there are over 70 ways
to say
"explode from the inside."
The general idea
is we, uh, lost all our fuel
when we crashed.
- Whoa.
Where are we?
- Uh, we were on course
to land on Pliny X19,
but Kayla didn't give me
any other details.
- Well, I thought she was
supposed to be your fiancée.
- Ex-fiancée,
and, um, communication
wasn't our strong suit,
uh, but I do know
that we were hired
by some power hungry space lord
to gather the universe's
most dangerous creatures,
and now we're on his planet.
- Huh.
- It could be "Hunger Games"
out there,
or the air
could be poisonous gas.
- Okay, we just--
we need to find
something that can fuel
this ship
so we can get back home.
- Or what if we send out
a distress signal
and then wait for the Legends
to come find us?
And, uh, good news--
I've got my deck
of strong American women
playing cards.
Ruth Bader Ginsburg,
Dolores Huerta,
Representative
Shirley Chisholm.
- Of all the people
to be stuck with.
[dog barks]
- What is--
what is that?
[electricity crackles]
- Dog?
A really cute dog.
- Three moons.
Three moons, yeah,
I can get behind that,
but a dog, that's weird.
But...
if the dog can breathe,
that means we can breathe.
- And it's wearing a scarf!
Okay, Gary,
resist the cuteness.
You've been fooled
by dogs before.
Where are you going?
- I'm gonna follow that dog.
[doo-wop music]
♪ ♪
- Mmm.
- Pretty busy here today.
Anything special going on?
- Oh, it's always busy.
The burgers
are out of this world.
♪ ♪
- What's that?
- Dragon Ash.
It's my line
of herbal nootropic supplements
designed
to enhance brain power,
sex appeal,
sleep cycle, spirit--
- Sounds like
more fries for me.
Takes me back to my days
at Burger Herder.
The satisfying ache
in my forearm
from a day flipping patties.
Of course, those patties
were organic
and free range.
The meat they used in 1955
often contained ingredients
which precluded it
from being called beef.
- Ew.
[air whooshes]
You know,
I've been thinking, bro.
It is time for us to start
sharing the family heirloom.
- So you can dry
your hair faster?
- Ha ha--
I helped defeat a god,
or whatever
that scary blonde lady was.
I'm officially a Legend now.
All I need is my super power.
Here, I made a schedule.
- Hey, hey.
- Whoa, whoa.
- No one is more stoked
than me
to discover your powers,
but the totem chose me.
- No, you literally stole it.
- Debatable.
- Guys, guys, shut up.
[radio chatter]
I'm working here.
- Please respond to a 415.
♪ ♪
- Ooh, I have an idea.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
What are you--
- Just go with it.
- Okay, all right.
- [high-pitched voice]
Uh, pardon me, officers, hi.
We're just here on vacation,
and we were wondering--
how safe is San Bernardino?
- Safe as houses.
- So no arson or robbery?
[sharp humming]
- [with Southern accent]
Or any gruesome eviscerations?
[sharp humming]
- [breathing heavily]
- There's a 459A
in Sal's Deli.
Repeat, 459A.
- Pass me a napkin?
- Uh...A 459A?
[chuckles]
That sounds mighty serious.
- Yes.
- Ma'am, if you wanna stick
your nose
in someone's business,
I suggest you start
with your friend.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I need another burger.
[sharp humming]
- Hey, hey, hey,
are you all right?
- Did you hear something?
- I can feel it.
It's hungry.
- Focus.
Now, where's it
coming from, love?
- Maybe that way.
Okay, the feeling's
getting stronger.
- Yeah, what about
the waitress?
She has glasses like Gary.
- You mean the alien
in a waitress flesh suit?
- Spooner, wait--
- Hey!
All right, what are you really?
- [whimpers]
- Her disguise is good.
- No, no, wait--
Just--just--
I am so sorry.
My friend thought you were an--
[stammers] someone else.
I'm sorry.
What happened?
What's wrong with your powers?
- Nothing.
I felt it.
Look, that thing is nearby.
Believe me.
- Found the alien.
- Rory?
You stole a cop car?
Uh, okay, where is it?
- That 459A at the deli
was followed up by a 415
at the butcher's
and a 240 at the meat aisle
of the local grocery.
- Alarm at the deli,
assault at the groceries,
and disturbance
at the butcher's.
- Mm.
- This thing loves meat.
- That must be
how the massacre starts.
Well, let's find it
before it gets a taste
for another kind of flesh.
- Hey, guys,
we have a lead on the alien.
I need you to guard
the burger joint.
Turns out we have
a very hungry alien
with a taste for meat.
- Already on it, Captain.
Guess who just got summer jobs.
- Nice.
[dramatic music]
[cash register dings]
[doo-wop music]
- So glad you lot
applied for the jobs.
Business is boomin'.
- I never thought
I'd get the chance
to man the grill again
professionally.
- I'm excited to see
the master at work.
[together]
Burger buddies.
- Size nine, right?
- 7 1/2,
and I am not wearing those.
- You're right.
We could use
a handsome man out there.
- It's you.
- Me?
- Yeah.
- No--okay.
- Let's get you on wheels.
- Looks like it's time
to teach you
the ways of the burger.
[bell dings]
Let's go meet the meats.
♪ ♪
- How did I get here?
[liquid gurgling distantly]
- Don't you have
any alien super powers
that can find a dog?
Super smell or echolocation?
- I'm not that kind of alien.
- [sighs]
- I'm not that different
from you, really.
Carbon based,
a few more tentacles.
- Yeah, and you eat people.
- I come from a savage planet.
They killed for sport,
ate their own.
The concept of oral hygiene
was completely unknown.
And I wasn't
so much engaged to Kayla
as traded to her,
and then I was sent to Earth
to find you.
Never imagined a place
like that could exist.
Birthday parties.
Rose water.
Friends.
- [scoffs] Friends.
I've known you
for three years,
and I'm only now learning
you're an alien.
- Well, I took
some creative license
with the details,
you know, so I could fit in
just like Charlie.
- Why me?
- My guess,
whoever's behind all this
has a thing
for powerful women too.
- Lucky me.
[dog whimpers]
[dramatic theremin music]
♪ ♪
- Do we wanna know
where that came from?
♪ ♪
[door chimes]
[eerie music]
♪ ♪
[sharp humming]
- Mm, yeah, it's here.
- Here like before or?
♪ ♪
- Look, I spent my whole life
trying not to let aliens
into my head, and now
to try to save your girlfriend,
I've got them all in there,
which is no freaking picnic.
I don't know
how the hell it works,
but I know it does,
so back off.
- We got something.
♪ ♪
[sharp humming]
- It's close.
♪ ♪
[heavy breathing, grunting]
[groaning]
[weapon powers up]
- Is that
the Big Bang Burger mascot?
- Ugh, that's just a bloke
in an alien's costume.
- Alien disguised as a human
disguised as an alien.
Wow, these things are good.
- The kid is not an alien.
Would you stop
pointing your gun at him?
Look.
- You sure?
'Cause I never saw
a man so mad for meat,
and I grew up
along our nation's
storied buffet belt.
- All right, let's get him
back to the MedBay
and see what we can find out.
- Oh, hey!
- This...
stays with me until after
we talk to the alien.
[dramatic theremin music]
[soft dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Careful, careful.
On my planet, there are plants
that can literally liquify you.
Also ones that can sing,
which I guess
is besides the point, but--
- Gary, what did I say
about talking?
- Uh, well, I believe
your precise word was "don't,"
but, uh, I sensed nuance
in your tone.
[dog barking]
- Huh.
I guess I'm not
the only intelligent life form
on this planet.
- Wait, wait, wait.
We don't know what's in there.
It could be a priblintz,
which is kind of
like a half-jaguar,
half-snake thing
or an apteroc,
which is also half-jaguar,
half-snake, but opposite parts.
- Gary,
it's not like
I haven't faced aliens before.
[dramatic music]
Oh.
- Who the blazes are you?
- Right back at you.
Wait, are you human?
- Not just any human.
It's the queen of diamonds--
Amelia Earhart.
Big fan.
[valiant music]
- Take in that smoke
and hold it,
relaxing those muscles,
releasing any tension.
- Can you please stop
talking to yourself?
- I'm not talking to myself.
I'm talking to my burger.
[soft pop music]
Releasing any tension
and turning it into flavor.
- Oh.
All right, no sign
of trouble out there,
however, I think my shorts
may be a little too short.
None of my customers
are leaving.
Any heat in the kitchen?
- Well, if we're looking
for people
obsessed with meat,
we should probably
lock up
the Burger Whisperer here.
[rings bell]
- With this spatula
comes a duty
to transfer our positive energy
into this burger
and out to that town.
If these are the vibes
that you put into their food,
they're gonna taste it,
and if these are the vibes
you bring to the mission,
the totem's gonna feel it.
- Oh, I get it.
You're just looking
for another excuse
to keep the totem to yourself.
I don't think it cares about
my meaningless burger job.
- Meaningless?
[burger sizzles]
The Burger Herder
was where I started
to find real meaning in life,
the first place
where people cared about me,
not 'cause I was
"Dragon Girl's Brother,"
but because I was Behrad.
- Okay, got it.
So you're gonna
just keep hogging the totem
as payback
because you were jealous of me.
Super mature.
- I wasn't jealous.
Are you even listening?
It just felt good to have
something to myself, okay?
- Fine, keep the totem.
You know what?
Keep the spatula too.
I wouldn't want
to ruin anything else
with my negative energy.
- That's not what I--
- It's me.
I need that table six order.
Come on.
- [humming]
One dry naked single
coming right up.
- Whip!
- Go, go.
Wait, Nate, don't serve that!
They'll taste my bad vibes.
[electronic beeping]
- The scan confirms
the subject's biology
is 100% human.
- [sighs]
Look, his biology
might be human,
but I'm still feeling
strong alien vibes.
- Well, if there is
something in there,
the Divination of Hor
should do the trick.
It extracts
all unwanted influences,
giving you face time
with whatever's in him.
- So you just rattle off
this hooey
and magic stuff happens?
- Yeah, that's right.
- Hoc carmen, conuro--
- Don't finish that sentence,
not unless you wanna summon
a trickster prawn.
- Yeah, I'd like to see
a prawn get one past me.
- Let's get this over with.
- All right.
[ethereal whoosh]
Inntrenger, gi deg til kjenne!
- [retches]
[dramatic music]
Oh.
- Oh.
- That's some high-grade hooey.
- Wait a second.
I think I've seen
this stuff before.
Is that Big Bang Burger's
secret sauce?
- Wait, don't touch that,
and definitely don't eat it.
- Why would I eat it?
[sharp humming]
- That's the alien.
- That's the alien?
- What, you mean
they're charging
25¢ extra to eat an alien?
That's kind of
a bargain, really.
- That's why
I was hearing it
all over town
'cause everyone's
got it in them.
- Like an extra-terrestrial
parasite.
- Driving this town
to eat itself alive.
- Okay, okay,
so if that parasitic condiment
is the alien, fine.
Then that means
you can talk to it.
- That's not how it works.
- Will you just try?
- Sara's one day
closer to dead,
and your plan is to hunt mayo.
- Thank you so much for the
constructive feedback, Mick.
It's very helpful.
- ♪ Let me tell you, honey ♪
♪ Why I love you so ♪
♪ Kiss me, baby ♪
♪ Ooh, kiss me, baby ♪
♪ You set my soul on fire ♪
♪ Kiss me, baby, ooh ♪
- You're doing it!
You're in the zone!
The people are loving
your burgers, man.
- I feel like I'm flying!
- Fly, B, fly!
- Spirit Ash, do your work.
[rock and roll music]
- Guys, listen to me.
- Can I take your order?
- I need you to stop
serving those burgers.
Bottle up all that secret sauce
and bring it back to the ship.
The sauce is the alien.
It's like a parasite.
It infects people
and makes them crave more meat.
- And here I thought
my short shorts
were selling burgers.
- Oh, it's like that old movie,
"The Stuff" except with aioli
instead of ice cream.
- Sorry,
are you saying that anyone
who ate a burger
is gonna go super crazy now?
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Copy that, Ava.
We'll 86 the hockey pucks
on the fly.
- I think he means we're gonna
stop serving people alien goo.
Ew.
- All right,
health code violation!
Come on, boys, you gotta go.
We don't have the permission
to serve food on roller skates.
Get!
Get out of here!
- You get the totem.
I get to take out the trash.
- What is going on out here?
Where are my customers?
Why, you little--
you're stealing
my secret sauce!
- Bert, it's not
what it looks like.
- Who are you spying for?
It's those two brothers,
the Mc--whatevers!
I knew a chef as good as you
was too good to be true.
- Wow.
- It's an honor
to hear that, boss,
but, seriously, this sauce
is making people crazy.
- Yeah.
- Once they eat it,
they can't stop craving meat.
- Son, that's called quality.
- If you keep
feeding people this,
they're going to die, Bert.
- Well, people don't eat
burgers and fries
to live longer.
- Hm.
[door opens]
- Uh, you might wanna--
[dramatic music]
- Ugh.
- [grunts]
Need more!
[screams]
- [screams]
♪ ♪
- [grunting]
- You believe us now, Bert?
- Is this the last of it?
Where do you
even get this stuff?
- Answer him!
- Listen!
I-I don't know.
My wife makes it.
It's her secret recipe.
She won't even tell me.
- [sighs]
- Ugh.
Ava, we got a problem.
We got all the sauce
out of here,
but turns out there's
a lot more of this stuff.
Bert says his wife
makes the sauce at their house.
- Okay, well,
if we find it all,
then Spooner should be able
to talk to it.
I'll head there now.
- I still don't understand.
How did you end up here?
- Well, Earhart's interest
in flying began with a visit
to the Canadian
National Exhibition.
Sorry, it's a fun fact.
- Wish I had an answer for you.
Last thing I remember,
I was soaring over the Pacific.
Me and my navigator Fred
almost done our flight
around the globe.
It was mission accomplished.
Then the left engine
started sputtering,
the Canary bucked,
and I hit my head hard
and blacked out.
When I woke up,
Fred was gone, and I was here.
- And where is here?
- I thought it was heaven
or something,
but to tell you the truth,
I still don't know
where we are exactly.
On the bright side,
the food's good.
- Hey, listen, I'm trying
to repair my aircraft.
Maybe you can
take a look at it.
It needs a fuel source.
- An aircraft?
[soft dramatic music]
But that means
that you can take me home.
- Oh, well, yeah.
I mean, I guess.
Why not?
Let's do it.
Let's go.
- First let me serve you.
Why let this meal go to waste?
It's been so long
since I've had any guests.
♪ ♪
- Uh, yeah.
Sure, okay.
- Hot dog!
I've been frightfully lonesome
since I've been here.
- Yeah.
- You two are lucky
to have each other.
♪ ♪
- Yeah, um...
[brakes screech]
[sharp humming]
- Mm.
Hell yeah, this is the spot.
- Okay, let's go interrogate
this thing.
- I keep trying to tell you
that's not how it works.
I don't speak alien.
It's more like
I can sense them,
know what they're feeling.
- Know what they're feeling?
How is that supposed
to get Sara back?
- You're the one
that brought me here, jefa.
Why do you people
listen to her?
She's gonna get you all killed.
- Don't, mate.
- The hell is
that supposed to mean?
- It means
you don't cross an alien
without losing something.
It means the longer you pretend
she's still out there,
that these things
will help you get her back,
the more you're gonna lose.
- Stop.
- She's gone, and if you can
get that in your head,
at least you can save yourself.
- Shut up, Spooner.
Watch her, John.
- Yeah.
- So you're with the police.
- Mm-hmm.
- Which officer
are you married to?
- Hm?
Oh, well, you probably
haven't met him yet
seeing as we
just moved here and all,
but that's why I wanted
to introduce myself to you.
My, my, my, what a lovely home
you have here.
[gasps]
Is that an electric mixer?
- It sure is.
- No, I have heard about these.
Wow, it's like
I'm in the future.
- It does everything--
cakes, cookies.
Oh, you know,
I just whipped up a batch.
You have to try them.
- Huh?
Oh, no, I couldn't.
I am stuffed.
I just had lunch
at Big Bang Burger.
Talk about a welcome
to the neighborhood.
- Well, isn't that something.
That's my husband's restaurant.
- You don't say.
[chuckles]
You know what makes
those burgers really special?
It's that secret sauce.
Mm, mm, mmm.
And he was bragging to everyone
about how it's
his wife's recipe, and--
- It's true.
My little contribution
to the family business.
- You have to tell me
how you came up with it.
What's your secret ingredient?
- But I couldn't.
- Oh, come on, now.
Just between us girls.
- Well, all right,
but what I'm about to say
cannot leave these walls.
To be honest,
it's a little weird,
and I'm not too sure people
are ready for the truth.
- I am all ears, no lips.
- My secret ingredient,
it's rice vinegar
from the East.
- [gasps]
Wow.
- I know, exotic.
- Yes.
- Well, I really should
be getting dinner started.
- Mm.
- These eggs aren't gonna
devil themselves.
- No, no.
[eerie music]
♪ ♪
Um, I'll just see myself out.
Toodle-oo.
♪ ♪
- This better be the last
of the alien sauce,
or we will call the FDA.
- All right, I got Sandra
set up in the back office
with enough burgers
to last her through the night.
[door chimes]
- Meat!
- Oh!
- Oh, no, not the nice couple
from table six!
[suspenseful music]
- Get back!
- Let me--
- Gotta get 'em!
- [grunting]
- Look alive, team.
The dinner rush is here.
♪ ♪
- What does that
look like to you?
- I don't know.
Mr. Beeman's midlife crisis?
- No, not the car.
That weird, bumpy box.
[eerie music]
♪ ♪
- Anybody up here?
- The alien's pod.
♪ ♪
[sharp humming]
- Wait.
I can read that.
- Oh, yeah?
Well, what's it say, squire?
- Giant air feeder.
- And what the hell is that?
- I don't know,
but it sure don't look
like a sauce monster.
- Yeah, good work.
Ava.
- Just give me a second, John.
♪ ♪
Damn it.
[sighs]
♪ ♪
[gasps]
Oh, my God.
♪ ♪
- I told you
it does everything.
[sighs]
♪ ♪
I won't let her
take you from me.
♪ ♪
I won't let her.
- [sniffs]
Ugh.
[eerie music]
- I knew you were
up to something.
Is your husband
even a policeman?
- Well, you see, my wife--
well, she's my fiancée.
Well, technically,
she hasn't asked me yet,
but I did say yes,
so I guess that makes us--
Never mind.
Sara, my friend,
she was abducted by aliens,
and that's exactly
what that thing is.
It's an alien.
- I have no idea
which part of that sentence
makes the least sense.
I don't care what she is.
She's mine.
My little miracle.
She's the only thing
keeping our business alive.
- Wait a minute--
you've been knowingly
serving your customers
that slime?
- At first, I didn't know
where the stuff came from.
Last Wednesday,
I served Bert his favorite--
Salisbury steak--
when something
from the ceiling
dripped onto his plate.
I tried to stop him,
but he tasted it and loved it.
He thought it was my recipe.
Bert's business
had been failing,
and it was taking
our marriage with it.
He was sure
if we added my secret sauce
to the menu,
we could turn things around,
so I had to find out
where the sauce came from.
While Bert was asleep,
I came up here
and discovered it.
This beautiful creature.
She'd found her way
into our attic.
She was small back then,
and I knew
the universe gave her
to me to save our marriage...
[laughs]
And our family business.
- Rhonda, I need you
to let me take it from here.
We're running out of time.
Look at it.
It's growing.
It could take over
the whole town.
- Wait, you're right.
If she's growing, that means...
♪ ♪
We could franchise!
[gasps]
Finally the Beemans will get
the success they deserve.
Oh, we'll take over
more than this town.
We'll put those brothers
out of business.
Big Bang Burger
will be a household name!
We'll be in every city,
every state!
Oh!
- I hate to see
a small business
go down like that.
- Spooner, I am so glad
that you don't follow orders.
- Well, looks like
doomsday is finally here,
and it's ordered the burger.
[suspenseful music]
- We need to calm
these people down!
- Wait, I have an idea.
Sleepytime Dragon Ash.
Even a small dose will calm
the most restless spirit.
- Yeah, but how do we
get them to eat it?
[people screaming]
- By giving the customer
what they want.
I'll lace the burgers
with Dragon Ash,
feed 'em to the horde!
- Yes.
- But I'll have to serve quick.
♪ ♪
- Behrad, wait, let me help.
- Zari, are you sure?
- I learned from the best.
Today you're not
Dragon Girl's brother.
♪ ♪
I'm Burger Boy's sister.
[people screaming]
- You're gonna need this.
[triumphant music]
♪ ♪
- Okay, so you're saying
this lady found a cocoon
oozing alien pus and thought,
"let's put this on the menu"?
- Yeah, you might
not wanna look
at what's in fast food
these days.
- So if that's the alien,
then why is the sauce
driving everyone
into a feeding frenzy?
- When this thing pops,
she's gonna be hungry.
She's been fattening up
the town
for her first meal.
- The massacre.
[eerie music]
- Oh!
- [grunts]
I won't let you
take this from me!
She's mine, all mine!
I won't let you destroy
our American dream!
♪ ♪
[screams]
- [roars]
- [screaming]
♪ ♪
- [gulps]
[roars]
- Uh, uh,
we need to contain it.
♪ ♪
- [roars]
[soft dramatic music]
- I bet I know
where it's going.
- More patties coming in hot!
[doo-wop music]
♪ ♪
Give 'em the works.
- That would be
four cows buried in snow.
RIP.
[rings bell]
Pick up.
- Take it.
♪ ♪
- It worked!
They're falling asleep.
[together]
Burger buddies!
[triumphant music]
- Hey, guys--
- Hey, we found the alien.
Tell 'em we found the alien.
- Yeah, it turns out the goo
isn't the alien.
- It's a huge, flying bug!
- Like Mothra, cool.
- It has a taste
for human flesh,
and it is headed your way.
- Well, that's less cool.
- [roars]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[roars]
- Guys.
- Oh.
- [roars]
- I liked the alien better
when it was goo.
- Damn it!
[tires screech]
♪ ♪
- How are we supposed
to get it down?
- We need bait.
- Oh, jeez!
Oh, shoo!
- [roars]
- Shoo, you!
Just what I need!
- Hey, get inside,
you silly git!
- [roars]
- Whoa!
[screams]
- [roars]
- You wanna take it
back to the ship?
See if maybe I can talk to it?
- Uh, yeah, light it up.
♪ ♪
[gun hums]
- [roars]
♪ ♪
- Whoa.
[electricity crackles]
- [roars and groans]
[soft dramatic music]
- Whew.
♪ ♪
- I'm not gonna lie.
That was very satisfying.
[soft dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- [clears throat]
Double fisting--
I like your style.
- Oh, I...
[chuckles]
Poured it for Sara.
It's just habit.
Hey, shouldn't let it
go to waste.
[tender music]
- I'm sorry I couldn't help you
find your lady.
- Oh, no, Ava Sharpe
does not give up that easily.
♪ ♪
Listen, I owe you an apology.
I was so desperate
for this alien
to be the answer
to all my prayers
that I didn't even think
about how you'd be feeling
about any of it.
- Nah, I get it.
You know, Sara's a lucky woman.
- Thanks.
You know...
I know what it's like
to have people mess with you,
and it doesn't make you crazy.
Just makes you vigilant.
♪ ♪
So what happened to you
when you were a kid?
- Look, I don't really
talk about--
♪ ♪
My mom.
I don't know where they took us
or what they did to us,
but when I woke up,
she was gone.
♪ ♪
- Maybe she's--
- I had to stop thinking
that way.
No, hoping like that
for that long,
I mean,
that can drive you crazy.
Instead I...
I gave up everything preparing
for the moment
I'd get to blow one of
those things away, you know,
but now that I've done it...
I thought I'd feel
something more.
♪ ♪
Now instead
I just got nothing left.
- I mean, you've got us.
- You mean--
- If you'll stay.
- You want me to stay?
- Yeah.
- I almost killed a furry
in the freezer.
- [chuckles]
We need to adjust some of
your tactics a little, but--
- This thing in my head,
I don't know
how to control it.
- Well, we can help you learn.
This isn't the end
for either of us,
so...
- [chuckles]
Yeah.
♪ ♪
You're right.
It isn't over.
There are still
more aliens out there.
- Exactly.
- You can still find
your girlfriend.
- Oh, I know we will.
- And that I just didn't shoot
enough of 'em.
- Wha--um,
wait, wait, wait, that's--
- All right, I'm in.
We're gonna keep killing aliens
until you find Sara
and I get some closure.
- Yeah, that's not what--
♪ ♪
Actually, that sounds
like a perfect plan.
Okay.
♪ ♪
- [sighs]
- Ah, thanks.
I loved being back
behind the grill,
but my pores did not.
Time to cleanse.
- In the wake
of what has been called
the deadliest butterfly attack
on record,
we have a little bit
of good news.
After the death of the owner
of Big Bang Burger,
head waitress Sandy Sledge
has decided to reopen
the beloved diner
under a new name.
- Yes, girl boss.
I hope she turned it
into a juice place.
- It's belly, belly good!
[cheers and applause]
- She did not.
- Hey, Z,
about before,
you were right.
I have been selfish
about this whole totem thing
and a little patriarchal.
It would be my privilege
to share it with you.
- [clears throat]
No, I need to respect
your boundaries.
The totem is your thing.
I get that.
- It's a Tarazi
family heirloom.
It only makes sense
that we both use it.
- There is no shortage of ways
for me to be super.
I don't need
to take away your power
to harness my own.
Listen, you've given me
a new life, new friends.
I can't take this
away from you.
- It's already yours, Z.
The totem chose both of us.
- Then I chose to give it
back to you, B.
- But think of all the ways
you could use
your wind powers
to help the team.
- You know,
I have been thinking
of talking to Ava.
I could see myself in a more...
managerial capacity
on the ship.
- All right,
I can't take this anymore.
[ethereal whoosh and clank]
- Whoa, it split in two.
- We're, like,
really good at sharing.
[creature caws in the distance]
- Fearless flyer,
fashion icon,
and a great hostess.
I mean, is there anything
she can't do?
- Yeah, and the stew was good.
- Yes.
- Hope you like
your coffee straight.
- Yep.
- You have really made
a home for yourself here.
I mean, how did you get through
those first few nights?
- Wish I had
an answer for you.
Last thing I remember,
I was soaring over the Pacific.
Me and my navigator Fred
were almost done our flight
around the globe.
It was mission accomplished.
- Are--are you feeling okay?
- Wish I had an answer for you.
Last thing I remember,
I was soaring over the Pacific.
Me and my navigator Fred
almost done with our flight
around the globe.
It was mission accomplished.
Then the left engine
started sputtering...
- I have a bad feeling
about this,
and we need to go now.
Come on.
- Where are you going?
- We were just heading back
to the ship
because it's getting dark--
- No!
You can't leave me here.
I need to go with you.
- What--
[eerie music]
- I need to go home!
[screeches]
[dramatic music]
- Ugh.
- Sara, we need to go!
♪ ♪
- [groaning]
[groaning]
- [breathing heavily]
I'm sorry.
This is all my fault.
[soft dramatic music]
I swear I will do
everything in my power
to get you home,
ideally in time
for a spring wedding.
Although with your matching
Nordic complexions,
a winter wedding
would be spectacular.
- [quietly]
Gary.
You are not planning
my wedding.
Ouch.
- Okay.
- Ah.
♪ ♪
Though a winter wedding
would be beautiful.
- Yeah.
- What is that?
♪ ♪
- Firefly...
to guide us to safety.
[eerie music]
♪ ♪
- I hope.
- Greg, move your head!