Wait, wait, wait.
You seriously want
to stop the assassination
of Archduke Franz Ferdinand?
Okay, let's... let's just hear her out.
After the assassination of the archduke,
Europe's rival alliances
declared war on each other.
This singular murder
led to 20 million deaths.
The assassination
of the archduke, therefore,
is what is known
as a fixed point in history.
Sorry, a fixed point?
Fixed point. Noun.
An occurrence so pivotal to history
that no time travel
is allowed on or near it.
I'm a little fuzzy
on my time travel logic.
How is this a good idea?
Yes, I appreciate
your resolve, Miss Gideon,
but, you see, we can't just go
and prevent the Great War.
Now, you were the ones
that taught me that.
Well, exactly. Fixed points
are shrouded in mystery,
even to evil Gideon.
Still, she and her robots
won't be able to resist
restoring the timeline,
and we will let them.
Oh, so we're not actually
going to stop the World War.
We're just gonna let her
think we are to lure her in.
And the assassination was
a notoriously chaotic event,
Which will give us the window
we need to take back the ship.
Making the robots do the work
of fixing the timeline
while we unplug your evil twin.
That is diabolical, Gideon.
- I learned from the best.
- All right, gang.
I know it has been a rough road
since we lost our Waverider,
but that ends now.
This time we're gonna win,
and today we are going home.
All right, gang-gang.
The assassination
was such a famous fiasco,
I kindly decided to draw you
a diagram to help explain.
Ooh, I didn't know you were an artist.
And now I see why.
No, I get it. It's... abstract.
Okay, so my drawing skills
are a little rusty.
You don't have to be
so insensitive, you jerks.
- Now just shut up and focus.
- Sorry.
All right, so there are
members of a secret society
called the Black Hand
on the scene that day,
including the eventual
assassin Gavrilo Princip.
The assassin set up a course
from the archduke's
motorcade route in Sarajevo.
Copy.
Where does the hippopotamus
come into play?
That's the archduke's car.
He's waving.
Oh, very abstract.
Okay, so we will set up here
next to the balloon salesman.
That is the assassin,
and he's holding a grenade.
The assassin tossed
the grenade at the motorcade,
but it bounced off the car
and blew up nearby.
So Princip, with his mission a bust,
went to a nearby sandwich shop.
Hey, I see that sandwich,
and you know what?
That is some attention
to detail on the lettuce.
- Good job, bud.
- Yeah.
That's an explosion.
The motorcade took a wrong turn
and went straight past
Princip's lunch spot.
So Princip sees the archduke,
realizes this is his moment,
and shoots him point-blank.
Okay, so our surest shot
at unfixing the fixpoint
is to take out the three assassins.
And the best place to do that
is at the Cosic Tavern
where the assassins went that morning.
Okay, so we'll knock out the Black Hand
just long enough that
they miss the motorcade.
Meanwhile, we'll need
to hide the time machine.
Astra can work her Permuto spell,
turn it into something more portable,
and bring it back here.
- Yes.
- Nice.
And then the team
will get into position.
- By that swimming pool.
- Field, Gary.
Field. And when Gideon sends her robots
to keep the 20th century on course,
we will be ready
to hijack our home back.
Yeah.
And with that, we have a plan.
Nay, we have a foolproof plan.
There they are, assassins
for the Black Hand.
_
Now's our chance.
I'm sorry, but if you'll come with me.
I think I'll stay right here.
I have to insist.
We wouldn't want to make... a scene.
Look, I think there's
a misunderstanding happening.
You clearly don't belong here.
- We're on our honeymoon.
- We're backpackers.
- What he said.
- What she said.
We really should be
better at this by now.
Ha. Don't worry.
Most time travelers
blow their covers even quicker.
Come with me.
What is this place?
You think you're the only ones
who want to save Archduke Ferdinand?
This is the place
for people like you...
time travelers who are foolish enough
to try and prevent World War I.
Welcome to The Fixed Point.
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -
What the hell is this?
These people are all time travelers.
What are they doing here?
How come I didn't know about this?
What's with the tape?
Oh, it's Gwyn's time machine.
- Gideon had me transform it.
- The tape was my idea.
ELO's "Time"...
it's a whole concept album
about a time traveler torn
between love and technology.
Cute.
All right. Moving on.
- Don't mind if I do.
- Turns out
there's a lot more going on
in Sarajevo than we thought.
Oh, yeah. Fixed points
are catnip for disrupter types.
I created this space
to provide a watering hole
for those who want
a piece of the action...
whether they're here
to stop the assassination
or just to watch people try.
Oh, here we go. Our next competitor.
- Is that a...
- It's a time portal.
Morning of June 28, 1914,
when the motorcade began.
Okay, folks, our next competitor is up.
Making his approach.
It's a live feed. How?
Oh, it's, uh, archival film
taken by bystanders
pieced together to form a view
of the whole motorcade.
The film updates
each time an attempt
becomes history itself.
You get your ticket. You wait your turn.
You take your shot. Them's the rules.
Well, we're not here
to follow your rules.
I wouldn't do that if I were you,
because although the filmstrip changes,
it always ends the same way.
Holy crap!
Wait, d-did he-did he just...
Self-immolation pays out.
Cumurija Road pays out.
You see, you try to change time
at a fixed point, and time...
kills you.
Time can do that?
No one's ever even made it
to the last assassin.
But if you're so determined,
you're in the queue,
and by the look of today's competitors,
your turn will be up soon.
All right, Gwyn,
if we're gonna save Alun,
we have to be smart.
We can't cause any ripples
that might affect
- the larger timeline.
- I understand.
And I have to say,
I am mightily appreciative
that you've changed
your mind on this, Miss Sharpe.
- Thank you.
- We would be dead
if it weren't for you.
We can give you this.
My divine mission is almost complete.
Now let me show you.
This is where Alun was ambushed.
Oh, perfect. Here you go.
- Oh, little soldiers.
- Yes.
I found them in the attic.
Constantine was a bit of a hoarder.
Ooh, seems like a very peculiar fellow.
- Mr. Green!
- Hm?
What? Is the Waverider here?
Uh, not yet.
I'm just here to drop off
Gwyn's time machine.
Astra said it should change back soon.
Well, I'll assume that
that makes sense then.
No, that makes absolutely no sense.
What happened with the archduke?
Oh, we're still waiting our turn
in a sort of time travel
"Cheers" meets Thunder Dome.
- What's a Thunder Dome?
- Uh, you don't want to know.
- Wait, stop, is everyone, uh...
- No, no, we're fine.
We're fine. It's a pub
filled with time travelers.
Yeah, people like us
who are there to save the archduke.
A whole community of time travelers
all with the same aim and purpose.
Wow, Gwyn, none of this
would exist without your invention.
Wait a s... uh-oh.
None of this would exist
without your invention,
which means if we go on to save Alun,
you never invent time travel,
which means
no Waverider, no Legends.
And no one to go back to save Alun
in the first place?
Ah, I can't deal with
all these time loops
and paradoxes all in one day.
I'm just gonna leave this in the foyer.
Okay, okay, okay,
so, uh, it's not as simple
as saving Alun from the Germans, right?
But we just have to
make sure that you go on
to invent time travel.
Oh, I've already
solved that, Miss Sharpe.
You see, my mission is to save Alun.
However, my younger self
must never find out.
I must always end up here.
What? But...
that means he'd be out
there alive, and you'd be...
Alone.
So let me show you
where he was ambushed.
Time is killing people?
I don't even understand
how time can have this power.
But I suppose I've never questioned
what made a fixed point fixed.
Who knew time travel
could be this complicated?
I don't know how you've wrapped
your human brains around it
all these years.
Oh, wait. Yes, I do.
I need a drink.
Hey, I mean, we could grab a...
Do you want to go check out
the betting tables?
- You bet.
- Right, well, I'll see you.
I mean, we could hang out or something.
Unless you have some plans.
No, yeah, we, uh...
you know, we have never
done the one-on-one...
thing.
Yeah. We should... after you.
- O-okay, I'll go.
- Okay.
Ah, what can I get you folks?
Two stouts, please. Anything for you?
Oh, uh, I'll just have the one.
Thank you.
Now, when you say time's
out there killing people,
like, you can't mean literally,
'cause that doesn't make any sense.
Well, I know it's a lot to take in,
but you've gotta trust me on this one.
I've been in the time travel game
for a long... time.
Oh, you've been in it for a long time.
Okay, well, then I guess
that makes you the authority.
Well...
I guess that does
make you the authority.
All these years,
I never even knew
the fixed point had a bar.
Oh, don't be too hard on yourself.
It's always been
a word-of-mouth kinda place,
and besides, you're young.
You can't expect to know
all there is to know.
You're right.
Here I am thinking
I've infinite knowledge,
but, I mean, what do I know?
What do I know, Gary?
Hmm? Okay, for example, okay,
what is a... a pickleback, hm?
Oh, does that come in large?
This is... this is great.
Right?
I mean, this is great.
I mean, like, us. Finally.
Right? I... Yeah.
You know, it usually gets
so crazy around here,
we never get a chance to just... hang.
Totally, totally.
Yeah, 'cause, you know,
what... what people do together
is they...
they talk.
- Yeah. Yes.
- Right? About...
Topics.
Right. Yes, yes.
I mean, we all love topics, right?
I mean, you know, there's...
there's things like...
Makeup.
- Right, yeah?
- Ah, I do.
Yeah, I like makeup, but, you know,
we can also talk about, uh...
guns.
Yeah. Yeah, we could.
Yeah.
The second assassin
is this salt shaker, okay?
Now, he'll get distracted
when this motorcade...
Okay, wait, wait, wait. I got it.
I got the plan that not even time
is going to see coming.
A true Legends plan.
No. No way!
Are you... are you guys
the Legends Of Tomorrow?
It makes sense we'd be known
around these parts, I guess.
We get around.
Yeah, a bunch of washed-up superheroes
who think they can beat
the fixed point... cute.
Okay. Calm down.
We are basically the same age as you.
Sick burn!
Oh, he said that you...
No one cares what he said, all right?
Why don't you guys go giggle
at your own table?
'Cause we have adult things to do.
- Wow, aggressive.
- Okay, sorry.
Number 71.
Okay, all right.
- Forget those guys...
- Yeah.
Because they do not matter.
All that matters is our plan.
- Hear me out.
- Go.
Three assassins fan out.
I follow the guy with the grenade.
Then here, I untie the dog
that's tied to the lamp pole...
And it knocks off the steak
from the table at the corner café?
Exactly, and then I use that...
As a distraction to steal the bike?
Yeah, you got it. How do you know this?
He's doing it right now.
Okay, well, whatever,
because my plan has a second steak
that I will slip into the
assassin's pocket...
and that's exactly what he's doing?
Really? No.
No!
And another one bites the dust.
- Okay.
- Mm.
Okay. Hey, this is a good
thing because now we know
this plan is no good.
On to the next plan.
72.
Lance...
you're up.
Hey, if you need more time,
we can get it.
I got this.
Improvising is what I do best, right?
Let's see what you got, old-timer.
Hey.
You're Sara damn Lance.
With Sara out there, they
won't make it past the tavern.
Damn it.
All right, well, maybe...
maybe she's got something else planned.
Wait.
At least her comedic timing
is impeccable.
There she is.
Bobby, baby.
Valiant attempt, Captain.
Look, I'm sorry, guys.
I froze out there.
I didn't know my next move. I just...
- It wasn't that bad.
- No one noticed.
Y'all... y'all feel
a shift in the timeline?
You know what? Yeah, I did.
Now the assassination's only
the second most epic tragedy
to happen today.
All right, all right.
At least I survived, okay?
Okay, um...
I'm gonna get a drink.
No, if we just
divert the Germans here...
This isn't working.
Oh, but it will now if you look at...
No, it's not good enough, Gwyn.
The plan can't be for you
to live your life heartbroken.
I mean, there has to be
a solve for this.
There's...
What if, uh, what if I take
each of the Legends
and I place them
in different points in time?
- No, we shouldn't do that.
- No, no, no, wait, wait, wait.
- I'm onto something here.
- Now, Miss Sharpe!
My sorry fate... it isn't just a solve
for the paradox, you see.
It's what I deserve...
For loving Alun in the first place.
Gwyn...
there's nothing wrong
with you loving another man.
Now, that might be easy
for you to say, Miss Sharp.
But it's true. It's true.
Listen, I'm so, so sorry
that you have had
to live your life
hiding who you really are.
But I... I promise you
that there are places
where you can feel safe to be yourself
- where people will accept you...
- It is not about the people.
It doesn't matter if I'm
accepted by others, you see.
I will never be accepted by God.
You see, my love for Alun, it, uh...
it goes against who God wants me to be.
It may be my divine mission
to save Alun,
but it must also be my divine punishment
to live without him.
- And that's the plan, okay?
- No.
Hey, watch out for the ladder, sis!
I can't stand people like that.
Yeah, me either.
It's like they're always
playing these tough guys.
Yeah, they think they're
better than everyone else.
Wait, I can talk about
people I don't like
literally all day.
Right, yeah, you know,
and guys like them
is why I stopped
going to places like this.
- Yeah.
- Well, that and, you know,
I kinda got abducted by a timeship.
You know what? So did I, actually.
So did I.
Why was it so hard for us
to do this before?
I thought you didn't like me.
Wow.
You know, I always figured
you thought you were better than me.
No. I am so intimidated by you.
- Shut up.
- Yeah.
- No.
I'm... okay, I'm the one
that's intimidated by you.
- Get out of here!
- Yeah.
Hey, sorry about back there.
The team really didn't
put on the best front.
Yeah, well, they trusted me.
I told them to trust me,
and then I get out there,
and I don't even know
what the hell I'm doing.
Hey, so you got a case of the yips.
It happens to the best of us.
Besides, changing a fixed point
isn't supposed to be easy.
It's not just the fixed point.
It's this whole damn road trip
or whatever the hell we're on.
- Sara, we got this far.
- Yeah, and where are we?
Seriously, where are we?
Running for our lives with
no home, with no plan?
I feel like I used to always
know what the next move was,
and now it's like...
I don't know. Nothing...
nothing's working.
Look, we got this far because of you.
And if it weren't for you,
we'd still be in Odessa making headlines
while the FBI shuts down our circus.
Would have been a good circus.
Would have been a great circus.
- Yeah.
- But you know what?
It's not all on you.
Yeah, I mean, you may be indestructible,
but don't mean you got to go it alone.
That's right.
This time, we'll go out there with you.
You guys I... look, I appreciate it.
I really do, but I can't
put you in danger,
and we don't even have a plan.
Exactly.
We don't need a perfect plan.
We're the Legends Of Tomorrow.
We got something
those hotshots don't have.
That's experience...
experience at failing.
Ah, you know what?
We've broken time before.
Let's do it again.
Since I'm the only one
who can "Live Die Repeat"...
"Live Die Repeat"?
It's a reference to this time loop movie
that's so fire.
I'll show it to you when
we get the Waverider back.
So I'll just keep going
out there again and again
until we figure out
the best way to beat time.
And when you do fail, no offense,
we'll be there every step of the way
during the assassination from the time
the Black Hand shows up to the taverns
to the time Princip takes the shot.
Spoons and I can take
the tavern, if that's okay.
- Yeah, I'm down.
- Cool.
Great, and then
the rest of us will watch
from the outskirts,
analyze your mistakes,
and come up with some
new strategies, huh?
Ooh, like a sideline of coaches.
Number 78.
God!
Sometimes the best play is a trick play.
Looking for this?
- Yeah!
- Whoo!
All right. Two to go, Sara.
You call that a knife?
Now, that's a knife.
Looking for this?
- Yes!
One more assassin to stop.
Come on, Sara.
They got to Princip.
No one's ever made it that far.
No, wait, no, no, no,
look, it wasn't me.
I didn't...
Well, well, well,
if it ain't the failures
of tomorrow failing again.
Stupid kids.
Well, we may be failing,
but at least we're failing together.
Yeah, and we're learning, too, right?
You know what, a couple more times,
and we're gonna figure this out.
Yeah, well, we got to hurry
because we only have two tickets left.
I think we have a few minutes
before the next try.
So smash, marry, kill.
Nate, Gwyn, Gary?
No, not... not... not really
into any of them.
Copy, okay, how about Sara, Ava, Astra?
Not... not... not really
into any of them either.
Also copy. Okay.
What is your type?
You know, I don't really
get those types of feelings for anyone.
Maybe it's one of those things
those mushroom aliens
messed up about me, huh?
Hey, no, no, no.
What you're describing
is totally normal.
It just means maybe you're "Ace".
Asexual, people who identify as Ace
have little or no interest in sex
but many of them still want
to be in relationships.
Wow, uh...
I guess that makes me Ace.
OMG, did you just come out to me?
- I guess I did.
- Yeah.
Okay, well, okay, first of all,
who would have thought you'd be
the first person I'd tell?
- Not me.
- Okay.
Cheers.
Hey, what's so funny?
Nothing.
I guess... I guess you had to be there.
Cool. Cool.
Okay, copy that.
- We should go over here.
- Yeah.
Well, what about you, Z?
Well, besides broody wizards,
what's your type?
What about that guy with the top hat?
What guy with the top hat?
Hey, gang, we were just in the tavern,
and Spooner saw this guy in a top hat,
but when I turned to look
at him, he disappeared.
Yeah, so we walked over
to where he was standing,
and my bad guy radar went off, big time.
- A man in a top hat?
- Yeah.
And I swear I've seen
him along the route.
Maybe he's on the film.
Stop. There.
Rewind the film.
Stop.
Can you go to the next frame?
Hm, he's only in that one frame.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
He appears right before
Sara makes a move,
and then he disappears, so maybe...
It's not time fixing itself.
It's a person.
So it's a person fixing time,
not actually time like we thought.
Yes! I knew it!
Did I do that right?
Sorry, I'm just relieved that
it's a person and not time.
Existential crisis averted. Carry on.
All right, so we got
to figure out how Mr. Peanut
keeps fixing time, then disappearing.
It is like he's stopping time.
What if he is?
Breakthrough. Sara's
having a breakthrough.
What is this top hat guy
has the ability to freeze time?
And then he fixes the timeline,
and then he restarts it
without anyone knowing he was there.
- Called it.
- Nice.
Right, how are we supposed
to beat someone
who can freeze freaking time?
I mean, I just wish there was some way
you could be invulnerable
to his time-freezing powers.
Well, there is one way.
Dr. Davies, do you think
you could let us borrow
the CR-055 superconductor?
The CR-055 superconductor?
Well, what would you want that for then?
To build an anti-time manipulator.
What do you need
an anti-time manipulator for?
Well, my plan to change
the fixed point has led us
to a mysterious bad guy
who can stop time.
Well, I would very much like
to help you, Miss Gideon,
but that would mean completely
dismantling my time machine,
not to mention risk never saving Alun
if I can't put it back together again.
But...
maybe this is part
of God's plan after all,
and I have always
been destined to fail him.
Gwyn, wait. Hey.
Look, I understand that
you have a deep faith in God.
I do, and I don't know
what that feels like, okay?
But I do know that
if... if there is a God,
he or she or they... or
whatever pronoun they prefer...
would... would want you
to experience love, you know,
and to feel acceptance
loving whoever it is you choose, Gwyn,
because love is love
is love is love is love is love is love.
That was profoundly
beautiful, Miss Sharpe.
I didn't know you're a poet.
No, I'm not actually.
That... that last part
is Lin-Manuel Miranda
I don't know him.
What I'm trying to say
is that you deserve love, Gwyn.
You are a good man, okay?
Now that you have
the Legends behind you,
I promise you we will
do whatever it takes
to make sure that you can be with Alun.
It moves me to know that.
What moves me even more is...
your unrelenting belief
- that there is a way.
- Always.
I thank you for that, Miss Sharpe.
Come here.
- Oh, yes, okay.
- It's gonna be okay.
I'm a hugger.
I guess I'm a hugger too now as well.
May we introduce
the anti-time manipulator.
Now, do be expeditious, Miss Lance.
You see, there is only enough power
to shield you from times stopping once.
Okay. No pressure.
- Oh, there's pressure.
- Lots of pressure.
Loads and loads of pressure.
Yeah, okay. Thanks.
- You're welcome.
- Very welcome.
Uh-uh-uh-uh. Ticket.
No one?
There's no more.
We don't have any more.
I'm sorry, but rules are rules.
Here.
Take ours before we change our minds.
These should come in handy too.
Comms? Hell yeah.
Wait, why do you guys want to help us?
I thought we were
a bunch of old geezers, huh?
Yeah, sorry about that.
We tend to lash out
when we feel threatened.
Yeah, we've been working out
our issues in group therapy.
Nice.
Anyways, you guys still
look like you've got it,
and this might be
your biggest legend yet.
So, please.
Thank you. We only need one.
Take a chance on Sara Lance!
Take a chance on Sara lance!
- Go, Sara!
- Yeah!
I got eyes on the prize.
Hey.
Sara Lance!
Take a chance on Sara Lance!
Take a chance on Sara Lance.
Here goes everything.
Thawne?
Big twist, I know.
Who would have thought me of all people
would be here protecting the timeline?
How the hell are you not frozen?
I'm sorry.
I can't take you seriously in that hat.
You look like a railroad villain.
Ah, yeah, well, can a
railroad villain do this?
What happened to your supper speed?
Long story. Give it up, Sara.
You can never defeat a fixed point.
Have you met me?
Just surrender or die again.
Surrender isn't an option.
I've sworn to protect
the fixed point at all costs.
So when you kill me,
you better be ready to take my place,
or all reality will fall apart.
Look, I'm not trying to break reality,
and I definitely don't want
to take your place.
- Then why are you doing this?
- It's a long story.
Well, we have all the time
in the world it seems.
Fine. Let's do this differently.
Care for a drink?
First off, how?
Here's the deal.
Every day is the same day.
I wake up, eat my porridge,
do my stretches, meditate,
and then I go to work,
except my job
is to protect the fixed point.
Job, porridge? Who are you?
The last time I saw you,
you were a despicable villain.
After the Black Flash vaporized me,
the time wraiths pulled me
back from nothingness.
They still had a plan for me.
My powers stripped, I was "re-educated"
and assigned here
to protect this fixed point.
As penance for your past crimes.
No.
Believe it or not, Sara,
I came to see their point
that history cannot
and should not be changed.
So I'm posted here
making sure this fixed point
remains intact with this.
This keeps me trapped in this day,
June 28, 1914.
When this timer hits zero,
it jumps me back 24 hours.
It can also freeze time,
as you've discovered.
It really is just a handy little gadget.
So tell me why you are so fixed
on unfixing this fixed point.
Say that five times fast.
Look, I don't want to stop World War I,
not forever at least.
I just need to stop it long enough
to attract the attention of our timeship
so we can steal it back from the evil Ai
that's controlling it and
her army of evil robots.
I'm just trying to get everyone home.
You may be determined to
protect this point in history,
but my drive to keep my family safe
will break you down.
So unless you have another idea
to get me out of your hair,
I guess we should get back
to fighting forever.
Well...
There is one other idea.
I might be able to buy you some time
by making it look like
the assassination was prevented.
How?
I'll make it so Gabriela Princip
will still assassinate the archduke,
only in 40 minutes,
but your ship's Ai won't know that.
It'll just think that there's
been a five-alarm aberration.
40 minutes is plenty of time
for us to get our ship back.
Fair warning, though,
you go one second over,
and I will have no choice
but to try and kill you again,
and if you kill me, you must swear
to take up my post and
protect the fixed point.
You have a deal.
You got 40 minutes, Sara Lance.
Yes! Yes!
They actually did it.
Now what happens?
Oh, time is being rewritten as we speak.
- Get into your positions.
- Hey, you two, stay here.
Oh, yes, Dr. Haywood. Yes, of course.
Oh! Oh, my lord.
I've always wanted to do that.
Me too.
Wow. Okay, fantastic.
We'll, uh, hold the fort, as it is.
There she is.
Get ready, Legends.
This time, there's no do-overs.
Greg, move your head.
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -