[Constantine] Previously on
Legends Of Tomorrow...
If you're seeing this,
we altered my future at Heyworld.
I don't know where I'll be
or who I'll be, but...
Find me.
-[Masher] John, wait!
- Masher?
Has Astra released
the worst souls from hell onto Earth?
- I'm unkillable! [laughs]
-[grunts]
[Constantine] I'm putting
an end to this.
Are you trying to go back to hell?
I'll return when the sigil is complete.
[sighs]
[alternative music playing]
Ma'am, we caught him lurking outside.
It seems you're having a hard time
staying away from hell these days, John.
Well, what can I say?
I'm a creature of habit.
You might as well get used to it.
You'll be living down here soon enough.
What do you want?
Oh, whiskey neat and a steak well done.
Oh, yeah, and all those souls
you released...
Call them back.
Look, there is enough evil on Earth
without you giving the damned
a second chance.
Those damned souls
are making me rich, John.
Any humans corrupted or killed by them
all belong to me.
And after years of being
under the boot of the triumvirate,
it sure feels good
to grind my heel on someone else.
[Masher groans]
Masher?
[stuttering] John...
Help me.
John's better at getting his friends
into trouble than out of it.
Something you should have known
when you squealed on me.
-[squelches]
-[yells]
You don't have to do this, Astra.
I like doing this.
[groans] No more. Please.
[screams]
Astra, look, I came down here
for a friendly chat, all right?
Now, we don't have to be enemies.
[chuckles] You're not my enemy, John.
You're an important step
in my evolution.
I crawled my way up from the bottom,
and I finally have
some real power around here.
So, if you want to stop me...
you'll have to kill me.
But really, what's the point?
My soul would just end up
back down here anyway.
-[Constantine gasps]
- John.
-[coughs]
- What happened down there?
[panting]
I need a drink.
- No post-mission debrief?
-[sighs] It's part of his process.
Come on, Gideon,
play the damn message again.
[Gideon] You can mistreat me
all you like, Mr. Heywood,
but I assure you there are no secret
messages hiding in my memory banks.
Everything okay, bro?
Oh, um, yeah, I was just, uh,
double-checking something.
Little help?
I think I'm starting to see things.
I know what's going on.
You do?
You get into my stash again?
[both chuckle]
Dude, no worries.
Sara's gathering the team.
- Come on.
- Thanks.
And that is the truth of it, mateys.
Astra and this whole bloody mess
is on me.
And she can't be reasoned with.
So, we need a more permanent solution
to stop her,
or she could continue
releasing souls indefinitely.
Surely Astra can change.
She's still human, right?
I mean, even a Master of the Dark Arts
must believe there's still
some good left in her.
[Constantine] Forget it, big man.
Astra's lust for power,
it zapped the humanity out of her.
[Sara] Well, on the bright side,
at least the Encores
aren't our fault this time.
Hey, up top.
Is there any point in sending
these Encores to hell?
It sounds like Astra would
just send them straight back.
Correct.
Well, then, until we find
a more permanent solution,
we'll house the Encores on the ship.
We're gonna need a bigger pantry.
Hey, Cap, normally I'd be all for
rolling up my sleeves and pitching in,
but I gotta take shore leave
for my pop's birthday.
And Nate's coming with me.
- I am?
-[Sara] You are?
My parents are always
asking questions about my life.
He could pretend to be
one of my biz school professors.
[both mouthing]
I still can't believe that
you haven't told your parents
the truth about what you do.
You mean that
I'm a time-traveling superhero
who stole the family heirloom?
Hmm, okay.
Yeah, stick to business school.
We'll be back before
you can say Timequake.
Don't jinx it.
[Gideon] Too late, Captain.
A new Timequake has been detected.
You are needed on the bridge.
[sighs]
[groans]
What are we looking at?
Ah. The epicenter of the Timequake
is in Los Angeles, 1947.
It's the Golden Age of Hollywood
and the height
of organized crime in the city.
The real golden age.
All right, people, we're gonna
need two teams for the...
Sorry, honey. I think I'm in your spot,
aren't I?
Hey, don't sweat it, babe.
As Ava was saying, two teams.
Ray, John, with me.
Mick, Ava, QB from the ship.
Now let's do it.
Mmm. You hear that?
It's only my second official mission
with the Legends,
and I'm already being trusted
with the football.
Really?
QB means staying on the ship
and doing nothing.
Or it could mean providing the team
with vital information.
Gideon, pull up a topographical survey
of the city, please.
How you feeling?
[sighs] Great. I just needed to get
off the ship, clear my head--
[Speaking Farsi]
[in English] Guys,
this is Nathaniel Heywood.
He's one of my professors.
-[in English] Welcome.
- Thank you.
[in English] Oh, we've never
had a professor over for dinner.
What do you teach?
Advanced Macroeconomics.
Behavioral Economics--
-[Zari] Hey, guys.
- Brace yourself.
Z here. So I'm at my parents' house
celebrating my dad's birthday.
After all, family is everything.
Speaking of which, it looks like
we have a surprise guest this year.
My brother, Behrad.
- Say hello, B. [smooching]
- Hi.
Anyways, guys, I gotta go.
Big love to the Z-Nation.
[Speaking Farsi]
Insert that clip
at the end of the current file.
We'll start cutting tonight.
You two can set up glam
in the bathroom for touch-ups.
Hey, I thought this was
supposed to be a family party.
Huh, says the woman who just invited
her 48 million followers into her house.
It's 51 million. Try to keep up.
Zari, darling, isn't it marvelous?
Your brother brought home
one of his professors from grad school.
Zari, Nate. Nate, Zari.
Hi.
It's you.
[whispers] I saw the video.
Oh. Thanks for subscribing.
You know, it's the fans that really
make all the hard work worth it.
[chuckles]
What a weirdo.
Your sister is the secret woman
from the hologram message.
Secret what?
I thought I was hallucinating,
but Gideon was scrubbing her memory,
and there was a secret message
from your sister...
...telling me to find her,
and she's the reason I came back.
Are you having a psychological break?
No! I'm being serious.
Remember when
we dented history at Heyworld?
Your sister is the dent.
The traces of magical energy
lead into this office.
There's an infernal residue in here.
Sure is. Residue of a dead guy.
[grunts]
Oh, oh, stand back.
Ugh.
The victim was consumed
by ignis inferni.
It's hellfire.
Whoever did this to him
was not of this world.
Well, looks like our killer
is the Encore.
Bollocks!
Huh, there's the ticket.
[heels tapping]
[woman] Don't come any closer!
All right, easy. You can put
the gun down. We're here to help.
Where's Webb?
[Ray] Uh, we are the "& Moore"
of Webb & Moore.
We work with Moore. Webb.
You must be Moore.
[in American accent] Sure.
That's me. Johnny Moore.
Sara is my secretary,
and this fella here--
Has got a cop face.
Oh, thank you.
[chuckles] Sergeant Palmer
at your service. I'm undercover.
Tell Webb to call me when he's back.
He's, uh, on holiday. Vacation.
Which leaves me
handling your case, Miss...
Hill.
Jeanie Hill.
I hired your partner
to protect me from my boyfriend.
Oh, well, you're in good hands, ma'am.
[sighs] Give me a break, Johnny Law.
Half the PD is in Bugsy's pocket.
- Bugsy as in...
- Benjamin Siegel.
Doesn't like it when you call him Bugsy.
But here's the kicker.
He died last week.
And now he's back from the dead.
[Jeanie] And he's more dangerous
than ever.
[band playing swing music]
He took over a joint on Sunset Boulevard
called the Blue Iguana.
Playground of gangsters
and the Hollywood elite.
Whatever vice floats your boat,
that's where you'll find it.
[music concludes]
Ladies and gentlemen...
welcome to the Blue Iguana.
Now, have fun. I insist.
If you don't,
I just might have to shoot you.
[laughter]
[photographer] Mr. Siegel.
Big smile for the camera, Mr. Siegel.
[camera shutter clicking]
Just, uh, cleaning up
a little bit of crumbs.
Please, Miss Hill, continue.
I was there when Bugsy
was assassinated by a mob hitman.
Saw the whole thing.
But then, the very next day,
lover boy shows up on my doorstep,
takes me to his club
like nothing had happened.
And that's just the biscuit.
Here comes the gravy.
He's different now.
More ambitious and fearless.
I want to leave him, but I can't
because I know he'd kill me.
[exhales heavily]
Look, Miss Hill, we can protect you
from your boyfriend.
But you're gonna need
to get out of town for a few days,
stay in a motel. Things could get messy.
But I don't have any money.
Bugsy takes care of all that.
How can I ever repay you?
No need to worry about that.
We just want to make sure you're safe.
Secretary Sara,
can you, uh, show Miss Hill the way out?
[in normal voice] Well, she took you
for an easy mark, Raymondo.
What? She was absolutely terrified.
Sara?
Jury's still out on the missus.
But it sounds like we need
to pay a visit to the Blue Iguana.
[band playing swing music]
All right, this is more like it.
Feels good to be back in the field.
Ava, what's your status?
Uh,been
Rory and I are just
sidling up to the bar now.
We're gonna keep an eye on things.
I'm, uh, seeing two zones of egress.
Back door's a gray zone.
Front door's got about four guys
sitting around it,
which quite frankly feels like overkill.
What do you think, Mick?
I think you need to relax.
[Agent Sharpe scoffs]
Ray, are you ready to grab Bugsy
when he comes out?
Ready and walking the beat.
Gotta say, feeling pretty spiffy
in this uniform.
[Sara] Bugsy's drawn himself
quite a crowd of ass-kissers.
Yeah, and judging by the cheap threads
and conservative haircuts,
I'd say they're politicians.
Well, if it isn't
our damsel in distress.
[scoffs] It's gonna be kind of hard
to protect her from her beau
when she's hanging on his arm.
I knew it.
She's as bent as a nine bob note.
Let's go.
[Sara] Not so fast, sister.
-[sighs]
- What happened to getting out of town?
You think a cab ride could get me away
from what Bugsy's got on me?
[with American accent] You and the rest
of town, by the looks of it.
Look“.
Ever since Bugsy came back,
he gets whatever he wants.
And everyone answers to him.
- Politicians, studio heads--
- Even the cops.
Then tell me, how did he get
so much juice so fast?
By using America's favorite pastime,
of course. Blackmail.
He's got a secret stash of compromising
photographs he uses against all of them.
And what does that have to do with you?
Everything. I'm in those pictures.
Bugsy used me as bait to lure men
and women into his trap.
[chuckles softly]
When I first moved here
from Shaker Heights,
I thought I was gonna be famous.
And sure, I became famous, all right.
Just not the right kind of famous.
I can't leave without those pictures.
Satisfied?
You know, if Bugsy
likes honeytraps so much,
why don't we give him
a taste of his own medicine?
I couldn't help but notice you,
and I gotta tell you,
I like the way you walk.
I learned to do it all by myself,
Mr. Siegel.
Oh, please. Benjamin.
Hmm. Sara Lance. At your service.
Lance,huh?
What's the matter? You don't like it?
Well, I don't know yet.
Just trying it out for size.
You know, even if it fits, I'm a little
curious about the price tag.
Well, if you have to ask,
it's probably too expensive.
[chuckles]
I take what I want.
Does that make you a thief, Mr. Siegel?
I am a lot of things, Miss Lance.
And I am especially a thief.
Well, then let's stop
all the tiddlywinks
and get straight
to the big reveal, shall we?
Now, I'm a reporter
for a new gossip rag,
and I've got some dirt on half the city
councilmen and the new archbishop.
It's in my car.
What do you say we go out back,
and you can take a peek
what's in my trunk?
I say, you keep talking like that,
I just might follow you anywhere.
[chuckles]
- Ray, I'm outside with--
-[earpiece beeps]
Benjamin. Car's this way.
You know, on second thought,
why don't we ditch the club?
How about you and me, we go someplace
with a little less company?
Actually, I think we
already have company.
Your eyesight's 20/20, doll.
Those are Mickey Cohen's boys.
But after going through hell,
I ain't afraid of nothing on this Earth.
You might want to jump out of the pot.
Water's about to boil.
[snarls]
Drop the gun. Put your hands in the air.
[siren wails]
Stand down, son.
We'll take it from here.
[Ray] It feels weird to be foiled
by the good guys.
What's the plan B?
Well, it looks like
you're going downtown, Sergeant.
Tomorrow is huge.
We're making a line of dressy sneakers.
- It's gonna be so major.
- That's nice, dear.
So, Behrad, any girlfriends
we should know about?
No, Ma. There's not really much time
for dating, given all the coursework.
But you need to take your nose
out of your books on occasion,
otherwise you'll never find
a nice Persian girl to marry.
[clears throat] Behrad...
[speaking Farsi]
[in English] By all means.
Add to your entourage.
How much does worshipping you
pay these days?
[in English] My team
is my extended family.
They help me manage a multi-platform,
multi-million-dollar brand,
and I didn't even have
to go to business school.
Wow.
- Is that the Air Totem in the--
-[Behrad stamps foot]
[Mrs. Tarazi]
Why, yes, it is, Professor.
How do you know
about our family heirloom?
Behrad told me.
Really? What did he tell you
about the Air Totem?
[Behrad] Just that...
[voice breaking] I was so broken up
when I found out it was stolen.
We keep the painting up as a memento.
Even though it's lost, I feel like
it's still here with us today
in this very room.
-[earpiece beeps]
- So, Sara,
do you, uh, want us back at the ship
for a post-mission debrief?
[Sara] No. Mission ain't over yet.
I need you guys posted at the club.
Keep your eyes peeled
and your ears open.
Great.
- What?
- Mmm?
[chuckles]
You wouldn't understand.
That you were the boss of
a massive government organization
and now you do diddly-squat?
Wow. I take it back, Rory.
You just summed up my life perfectly.
Can I get a double?
Bugsy is gonna be pretty hard to catch
if he still has that gun.
[in normal voice] Well,
we best get our hands on it pronto,
because only a weapon from hell
can eliminate a hell-spawned Encore.
And that gun, it may be useful
in more ways than one.
Well, good thing
I have my best man on the job.
Jeanie was right.
Bugsy really does have the LAPD
in his pocket.
I'm gonna have to figure out
another way to get that gun.
Can I take those arrest summaries
off your hands?
I'm on my way to records.
Sure. Aah.
That'd be super helpful. Thanks.
[officer] Tough to watch the department
kowtow to a gangster.
That's exactly what I was thinking.
Ah. Good cops like you are hard to find.
Name's Sullivan.
Palmer. Ray Palmer.
Well, see you around, Sergeant.
Officer Sullivan.
[chuckles]
Can certainly set your watch
to that fine constable.
We need a plan B.
If Ray can't get this gun,
the last thing we need is Bugsy
blasting anyone else out of existence.
Yeah, well,
maybe a stretch of the old legs
and some fresh air
will give us some clarity.
I think I know how to get Bugsy's gun.
[with American accent]
So, you got my message.
Look, if this is about the money
your friend gave me, I already spent it.
I knew you were on the grift
from the moment I laid eyes on you.
And I never once fell
for that Yankee accent of yours.
[laughs]
[in normal voice]
Well, all right, then. [sighs]
Well, now that we've
dropped the charades, tell me,
what is your angle?
I want to take Bugsy down.
Free this town from his sway.
The only way to do that
is to destroy his blackmail stash.
Webb said he'd found it,
but I'm guessing Bugsy killed him
for snooping too close.
Well, that's bad news for Webb
and good news for me,
because I know where the stash is.
Well, aren't I the luckiest girl
in the world?
What do you want in exchange?
I want Bugsy's gun.
You're looking to ice Bugsy?
No, that bloke's not worth it.
I'm aiming at the person
who brought him back.
Then we have a deal.
You get your guy, I get my freedom.
Now, how exactly are you planning
on stealing Bugsy's prized weapon, eh?
When we kiss,
I'll press my hand against his chest,
and then I'll run my hand
all the way down his body,
and then I'll grab it, like this.
[grunts]
[objects clatter]
[band playing mellow jazz]
- Do you want to know a secret?
- No.
I just turned in my keys
for my place in D.C.
'($9-
Everything I own is now stuffed inside
a Time Bureau
softball league duffel bag.
I'm essentially homeless, Rory.
Congratulations.
You're part of the team.
Mmm? Mmm-mmm. I'm a vagrant, a Vagabond.
- Hmm. No job, no rent, no kids...
- Mmm-mmm.
Perfect.
I had so many responsibilities
at the Time Bureau. People needed me.
You get it?
You see that clown sitting over there?
The one riddled with responsibilities.
Look at him. He's miserable.
And he's welcome to it.
I just can't get over the fact
that nobody needs me to do anything.
Wait.
Nobody needs me to do anything.
[Sara] You two still at the Blue Iguana?
Uh... Yes, Captain.
Just following orders.
Great. I need you and Ava
to create a diversion.
Clear the place out.
I'm gonna draw Bugsy back to the club,
so we can capture him.
I can do that.
-[music concludes]
-[applause]
Always a pleasure, Chief.
The lobster was excellent.
Stop right there, Mr. Siegel.
What's the problem, Officer?
I, uh.., l just need to search you
before you leave.
This is highly irregular.
Actually, it's quite regular.
A new directive just came down
from Deputy Chief... Wiggum.
- It's just gonna take a second.
- What are you doing, son?
Mr. Siegel, call for you. Sounds urgent.
- Siegel here.
-[Sara] Benjamin, darling,
it's me, your new favorite source
for all things juicy.
Lance. What's the rumpus?
Must be pretty heavy
if you're calling me on the blower.
Well, something is going down
at your club.
Primo blackmail material.
Better leg it over here PDQ.
[officers chatting]
Sorry, guys. Bugsy's leaving
the station. He still has the gun.
[Constantine] Don't worry, big man.
Got it covered.
[Chief] You take care now, Mr. Siegel.
Hey, baby.
[car door closes]
[engine starts]
You back to working the beat, Sergeant?
Ha! I was just admiring
Mr. Siegel's automobile.
I guess crime really does pay.
Not today it doesn't.
'Cause I'm gonna do something about it.
You in, or what?
[band playing "Poison"]
[singing] Girl, I must warn you
I sense something strange in my mind
Situation is serious
Let's cure it
'Cause we're running out of time
Tell 'em, girl
It's oh, so beautiful
Relationships, they seem from the start
It's all so deadly
When love is not together
From the heart
It's driving me out of my mind
That's why it's hard for me to find
Can't get it outta my head
Miss her, kiss her, love her
That girl is poison
Never trust a big butt and smile
[crowd booing]
- What's going on in there?
- Ugh, it's awful.
The worst thing I've seen in my life.
And I was there
when the Hindenburg went down.
[Agent Sharpe scatting]
She's driving me out of my mind
That's my girl.
That's why it's hard for me to find
I can't get it outta my head
What now?
[Agent Sharpe] You know what I'm talking
about. Sing it with me, girl.
We wait. And hope that John gets
that hell gun before Bugsy gets here.
That girl is poison
Right.
See you at home, baby.
[patrons groaning, booing]
I got to go. Something's stirring.
What is all this?
Girl, I'm a warrior
You bring me all the way down here
just so I can watch some no-name dame
humiliate herself on stage?
First of all, she is not a no-name.
That is my girlfriend.
And second,
she's not humiliating herself.
- Yes, she is.
- She's enjoying herself.
So this was just a lousy trick
to get me down here?
There's no dirt, is there?
The dirt is you.
You're supposed to be dead. Instead,
you're blackmailing your way to the top.
After I came back, I realized
that violence and murder,
that only gets you so far.
Information.
That's the real power in this world.
Well, whatever your deal is,
you're screwing up history,
and it is my job to stop you.
So, you don't have to go to hell,
but you can't stay here.
Oh, I ain't going anywhere, Lance.
Jeanie!
[gunfire]
Never trust the one...
[Mick] Should we tell her
the mission is over?
No, let her finish.
[scatting]
So embarrassing.
Dragon Girl.
Is this when you became famous?
Yep. First agent when I was 11.
He was a real piece of work.
Eventually I took control of everything.
- Can I ask you something?
- Hmm?
When you first saw me,
did you feel like we met before?
Maybe. I meet a lot of fans.
No. I mean, we met in another life.
Oh.
Yeah, I totally got that vibe.
Oh, so it's not all in my head.
I feel like I've been living out
this Taylor Swift song,
but it feels crazy good.
We're definitely connected somehow,
but something feels off.
I think the you I remember
wasn't a professor.
Come on. I know Behrad's
been lying to my parents
about business school for years.
I only want to make sure
that he's been taking really good care
of our family's totem.
Which he has been. Right?
[mumbles]
Yo, dude, we're cutting the cake, and
they're asking for the special guest.
Come on.
[clears throat] Chill, B.
Your friend and I were just talking.
- Sure you were. Let's go.
- Good talk.
- Bye, Professor.
- I warned you.
Bye. Stop pushing.
[Jeanie] How did you figure out
what these numbers meant?
Well, I spend more time in graveyards
than I care to admit.
Elysian is a common moniker for them.
And those numbers,
they represent a specific location
for a particular gravestone.
[hollow thunk]
There's something here.
Let's see, shall we?
-[grunts]
-[Jeanie gasps]
That's it.
Well, aren't we
a pair of jammy bastards?
Now, it's time to destroy it.
Forget the matches.
Step away from the briefcase.
Oh, hold on now, love.
We're all on the same side here.
There's only one side I'm on, John.
And that's mine.
You told me you wanted
to destroy that stash
so that you and everyone else
in the town could be free.
Yeah, but I figured why destroy it
when I could just use it for myself?
I'm sick and tired of
people taking advantage of me.
With this briefcase, I'll finally
have some real power around here.
Look, I understand your anger,
but as soon as you touch Bugsy's dirt,
then you'll have a target
on your back, just like him.
But if you leave now...
you can start over,
have a new life.
Look, you don't have to do this, Jeanie.
Just walk away.
Walk away?
Do you really expect me
to give up this power
after being so powerless my whole life?
You know what?
You're right.
Who am I to tell you
what to do anyway?
See? It's working already.
Okay, what do we do now?
Once Bugsy's girl gets back to her car
with the stash,
we're gonna take care
of the whole situation.
Take-- What do you mean, "take care of"?
You really are a straight arrow,
aren't you?
Wait a second. You want to destroy
the stash and Jeanie along with it?
Why'?
She's just collateral damage.
It's the cost of war.
You're a police officer.
Did you ever hear the one about
the last good cop in Los Angeles?
It didn't end well for him.
How's this for an ending?
Get out of the car. Now.
You sure you want to do that?
[guns cocking]
[clears throat]
If you were coming
all the way to Burbank
just to meet up with
your mobster friends and kill Jeanie,
why even bring me along?
'Cause we needed a fall guy.
Come on, boys. Drinks are on the LAPD.
-[accomplice chuckles]
-[sighs]
Well, I guess this is
where we say goodbye, Johnny.
It's been swell.
Five bullets left.
Use them wisely.
- No.
-[honking horn]
[continues honking]
Jeanie!
John! Jeanie!
Jeanie.
Jeanie!
Jeanie, no!
They killed her.
Forget it, Ray.
It's Burbank.
Hey, holding cell still works.
Who are you people?
- You communists?
- Idiots.
I know you're probably
pretty confused, Mr. Siegel,
but you might as well
make yourself comfortable
because you may be here for a while.
I should blast you straight to oblivion,
you dumb bastard.
You made Jeanie's life miserable,
and now she's dead because of you.
I may have corrupted a wannabe starlet,
but you, you created a real monster.
Astra Logue.
You know what?
It's funny that you mention her.
I was just about to go and see her.
John, if you're about to do
what I think you're gonna do,
then you'd better be sure.
Hand him over, big man.
Go on.
That's it, big boy.
See, you're my ticket to hell.
Flesh become my flesh.
Soul become my soul.
Hades, firstborn of Cronus and Rhea,
I call upon you.
Light her up, big man.
Hey, Astra says you're banned.
Is that so?
[patrons screaming]
You just can't stay away, can you?
Careful. He's still got one bullet left.
I appreciate your concern, Benjamin,
but I'm not worried about him.
We're old friends, aren't we, Johnny?
So, why don't you tell me
what you came all the way down here for?
I came all the way down here
to tell you...
that I'm not giving up on you.
And even if it takes me till
the end of my days, I promise you
that I will find a way.
Another meaningless promise
made by the great John Constantine.
You've gone soft.
[both laughing]
Not that soft.
This one's for Jeanie.
[howls]
I'll be seeing you around, love.
So what happened down there?
- I need a drink.
- Not this time.
Is Astra...
[sighs] When I got down there,
I was swarmed.
Astra had the drop on me.
She knew I was coming.
- And the gun?
- Is gone.
We'll figure out another way.
Hey, whatever really happened back there
with Astra, I'm sure it wasn't easy.
What are you talking about, big man?
Just so you know,
if I had "taken care" of Nora
back when we all thought
she was evil,
we wouldn't be happy
and together right now.
I had the chance to
pull the trigger to end all this...
but I couldn't do it.
What's all your grinning about?
I'm just happy there are
still good guys out there.
Even if one of them is
a Master of the Dark Arts.
You know, you're wrong about me, Ray.
But I will save Astra, and you
should know it's just as much for me
as it is for her. All right?
Hey, don't give Ava a hard time
for getting on stage, all right?
I don't want her to be too embarrassed.
[Mick] She's not gonna remember a thing.
Well, hello! Ha.
Where's my invite
to this party, huh, Mickey boy?
I spat in that. Old prison habit.
Mmm.
I cannot believe that I sang
in front of all those people.
I...
[exclaims] I was awesome.
I killed it.
And did you see my backup band?
They were like...
[imitates instruments and smooches]
Please.., please tell me
somebody got a video.
- Actually, we...
-[Sara] Mmm-mmm.
Mmm, and another thing.
Seriously, Sara, I love you so much.
Working that side mish with Rory
was way more fun
than running any stupid Time Bureau.
[slurs] Like, responsibilities?
Ha!
- Who needs them?
- Well, good, babe.
I'm glad you had fun.
Just know there's no small role
on this team. Right, Rory?
Right.
[snoring]
Okay. Night-night, sweetheart.
[exhaling heavily]
Look, there is more to Zari
than you give her credit for.
She's buried down deep inside
underneath all that fame.
You were getting played, man.
Don't feel bad.
She does this all the time.
- I know who you are.
- You do?
Yeah. The more we talked,
the more you looked familiar.
- Then I realized where I knew you from.
- The Waverider.
What's a Waverider? No. Heyworld.
Tell me that's not you there
in the star-spangled outfit.
In fact, you were both there.
That's totally you, Behrad.
Can't believe I never noticed it before.
What I don't get is
how Heyworld was 24 years ago,
but you two haven't aged a day.
What the hell is going on?
Zari, you've finally lost it.
You accuse me of being a fake,
but you're the one living a lie.
- Maman. Baba.
- Okay, shh.
- Just hang on.
- No, I will not hang on.
It's time they finally heard the truth.
What the hell? Where am I?
[Gideon] You are on
a 22nd century Timeship.
Designation W-R-2059.
Currently situated in the temporal zone.
Hey, guys. Who's your friend?
We can explain everything.
Yeah. You better.
Who are you people?
Guys, meet Zari. She's my sister.
Wasps, grunts]
Help. Help.
[yells] Help!
[singing] That girl is poison
[screaming]
[theme music playing]