HI removed, capitalization issues fixed,
cleaned, corrected and resynced by Tronar
In 2166, an immortal tyrant
named Vandal Savage
conquered the world
and murdered my wife and child.
I have assembled an elite team
to hunt him throughout time
and stop his rise to power.
Unfortunately,
my plan is opposed
by the body I'd sworn
my allegiance to:
the Time Masters.
In the future, my friends
may not be heroes,
but if we succeed,
they will be remembered
as legends.
Previously on
"Legends of Tomorrow"...
We're in the temporal zone.
I don't understand.
No one should be able to...
A scan of the vessel
suggests that it is
the bounty hunter, Chronos.
- Argh!
- A crash landing...
in both place and time.
Gideon, camouflage the ship.
This doesn't look like
the type of place
we want to linger
out in the open.
That looks a lot like
a Palmer tech building,
but why does it have
a Smoak logo on it?
Wait, this is Star City.
I thought you said
the timeline was safe.
Yes, Star City was
intact in 2016.
This... this is 2046.
Don't move!
Thank god.
I said don't move.
It's me.
It's Sara.
Hey, Oliver, look.
I know it's been a long time.
But don't you remember
that Rip Hunter
Recruited us to become legends?
I never heard
of any legends.
Get back!
This guy a friend of yours?
I don't like him.
What are you doing?
It's called shooting back.
Can't be the Green Arrow.
That's not Oliver Queen.
Sure dresses like him.
Shoots arrows like him.
Well, whoever he is,
I don't plan on sticking around
to get shish-kebabbed by this dude.
Kid's right.
Let's stay behind and kill him.
We need you in charge
of the ship.
All right, Rip.
Tell us the truth.
You've all seen how
the timeline is malleable...
In flux until it is set.
Well,
this future is not set.
Remember when I told you
it was dangerous
For any of you to know too much
about your own futures?
Well, the events that you dread
could very well come to be
Due to your actions
to prevent them.
You know what I think?
I think you think too much.
Believe me when I tell you
that the best thing
For yourselves
and for this mission
Is to make the repairs
to the Waverider here in 2046
Then head back to your own time
And make that none of this
ever comes to be.
Looks like the whole
propulsion system's jacked.
How do you even know what
we're looking at here?
Doesn't matter if it takes you
down the road or through time.
An engine's still an engine.
How long will it take you
to make repairs?
I'm not too sure,
but it would go a lot faster
If I had some help.
Maybe Kendra
could lend me a hand?
Enlist whoever
is free to help,
I have this to contend with.
This is the neuromorphic
interface
for Gideon's logic
and navigation matrix.
Without it, Gideon
cannot function.
Well, that explains how we got
stranded here in the future.
Palmer tech was working on
a self-learning,
neuromorphic cortex.
They surely would have gone
to prototype by 2046.
We are going to
need that prototype.
Ah, Palmer tech is now
Smoak technologies,
But, uh, I'm sure I can
still get us in.
As I said, we must keep
you and Ms. Lance
separate from your future homes.
In any case, there's a reason
why I recruited individuals
adept at misappropriating
others' property.
It's not money.
It's not jewels.
It's not a valuable artifact.
You're just lucky I'll steal
anything right about now.
- As I suspected.
- We'll get your gizmo.
You just get this bucket
flying again.
- I'm coming with.
- No, no you are not.
You're too emotionally
connected to the city.
- We've been over this.
- I'm over you.
You got us on a mission
to change the timeline
for yourself.
And you won't even let us
look at our futures?
Now, I know this city
better than anyone else,
and you're gonna
need me out there.
So, either I'm coming with,
or we can find out
if the Time Masters
are as good at teaching
people to fight
as the league of assassins.
So the rest of the team's
on a field trip to Palmer tech,
now Smoak technologies.
Palmer tech
sounds better, right?
Be honest.
Honestly, they sound
about the same.
Even assuming our
compatriots return
with a neuromorphic prototype,
we'll still need to prepare
Gideon for the new device.
And the engines could
definitely use some loving.
Actually, I could use
an extra pair of hands.
Well, Raymond, why don't
you and Ms. Saunders
Continue repairing Gideon,
And I'll assist Jefferson
with the engines?
This is just
a potential future.
It doesn't matter if we
kill anyone here, right?
Well, to avoid the risk
of a paradox,
It's probably best to refrain
from killing anyone.
I'm not gonna
promise anything.
My sister's apartment
used to be over here.
I seem to remember something
About your father being
a police Captain.
- Your point?
- Did one hell of a job.
My father and everyone else
would never have
let this happen...
Unless they were all dead.
You really are
pretty good at this.
Yeah, I was a shipyard welder
in 1944.
No way.
A real life Rosie the Riveter?
Is there anything
you can't manage
to put a positive spin on?
Uh, no, I got it:
The DMV.
So you do have a dark side.
You making fun of me?
Little bit.
Doesn't mean I don't find
your unwavering optimism...
Enjoyable.
I find watching
you weld enjoyable.
Dr. Palmer,
in case you weren't aware,
You are on an open channel,
And we can hear
everything you're saying.
Is it too much to ask for some
Professionalism around here,
and...
Why am I getting so upset?
One moment, please.
I'm not upset.
You're upset.
No, I'm not.
My elevated blood pressure
confirms that you are.
I'm just...
I'm just getting annoyed
that those two
Are talking instead of working.
I mean...
- You like her.
- Dude, you're being crazy.
You do remember
that we share
A psychic connection.
I can sense
what you're feeling.
If that were true,
then you would shut up.
Hey, it's no day at the beach
for me, either.
Believe me.
Well, it doesn't matter,
'cause I don't stand
a chance with her anyway.
Now,
why would you say that?
Because right now,
my competition
Is a billionaire genius
who built his own super-suit
And some other dude she's known
for 4,000 years
Who she is destined to be with.
If I may offer
one word of advice...
I really wish you wouldn't.
That word would
be "confidence".
You met my younger self.
I was quite the ladies' man.
Put yourself out there.
Good things will happen.
Palmer tech's
just two blocks up this way.
Or at least it used to be.
Take cover in there!
It's like World War III
out there.
It's beautiful.
We need to find another route.
Argh!
Ms. Lance, don't.
Sara!
Damn it!
You two... don't move.
We'll be right back.
Right.
We're not gonna sit here,
right?
Imagine all the looting
we can do in this chaos.
Why don't we stretch our legs
at that bank we passed
Three blocks back?
Drop your weapons,
and hand over your wallets.
Wait, are you actually
trying to mug us?
What is this, amateur hour?
If you don't do
what my man says,
We're gonna crush you
into the pavement
Like a couple of ants.
Really?
What do you say we teach
these fellas a lesson?
Yeah.
Ooh.
That's what you get when
you don't follow directions.
Interesting.
Hold this.
Second thoughts...
Argh!
Whoa!
Where did you get that?
Ebay.
Now, your boss will
not be needing this.
Well, this has been fun,
but I think it's time to leave.
Leave?
Why would we leave?
Ah!
Come on, sweetheart.
Don't move.
You...
You are persistent.
I saw you get shot
point-blank.
It's high-density Kevlar,
now... Who the hell are you?
- Who are you?
- I'm the Green Arrow.
Oliver Queen
is the Green Arrow.
No, he's not.
Oliver Queen is dead.
How did Oliver die?
I don't know.
No one does.
No one's seen him since...
- Well, since the uprising.
- Uprising?
Is just what people
called it when...
Well, when all this happened.
15 years ago, he brought
an army with him.
- Who brought an army?
- I did.
No, it's not possible.
How did you get off Lian Yu?
Say something, damn it!
Ms. Lance?
Who is this?
Somebody very dangerous.
Then now is not the right
time for me to say it...
But please, remind me later
to tell you that I told you so.
How are you still alive,
Slade?
Slade.
That's a name I haven't heard
in a long time.
How do you know my father?
He called you Ms. Lance.
Any relation to the late
Captain Lance?
If so, you must have heard
stories about my father.
I knew your father.
He was insane.
Seems to run in the family.
I'm going to enjoy
killing you...
Or we will.
Okay, bad idea.
Come on.
All right.
Grey and I have got
the mains back online.
Great. Uh...
Ray's working on something
called the quantum manifold.
But I can't seem to
get this to cooperate.
Let me give it a try.
Hey, you actually seem
to know what you're doing here.
Uh, yeah, machines
are kind of my thing.
Plus, I've been looking
at the instruction manual
in my downtime, so...
Most people can't follow
the instructions to build
their new bookcase,
and here you are working
on a spaceship.
A time-traveling spaceship
from the future, no less.
Well, when you
put it like that,
I am kind of amazing.
And humble.
Hey, if you ever
have any bookcases
need putting together...
I'll know who to call.
So, Raymond,
you were working with
Kendra earlier.
I couldn't help but notice
There might've been a little...
Spark.
- Really?
- Oh, yes.
It was quite apparent
and if I'm not mistaken,
I've noticed her throwing
one or two glances your way.
- Huh.
- Mm-hmm.
Wow, that's...
that's surprising.
- Is it?
- Well, yeah.
I don't know, I hadn't really
considered her in that way.
Why are you bringing this up?
Jeez, I feel like I'm
back in high school.
I honestly wouldn't know.
I skipped 10th grade.
And 11th.
I haven't really spent
that much time with Kendra.
You know, other than time that
we shared with her
And her reincarnated soulmate,
Or people trying to kill us.
All the more reason to avoid
Personal attachments.
This ship may be large,
but our group is small.
Hmm. Yeah.
Preaching to the choir,
Professor.
We're onboard the Waverider
to save the world...
Not hook up.
Yes, quite right.
Hey, you,
I'm terrible with names.
- I'm gonna call you Fonzie.
- Yeah!
- I'm gonna call you Kenickie.
Anyone else here need a name?
Your highness, can I get
a moment of your time, please?
Sure.
Ah, isn't the future great?
We really should be
getting back to Rip and Sara.
Why?
'Cause I'm not looking
to put down roots here.
Why not? It's everything
we've ever wanted.
I got a gang that does
everything I tell them to.
I got a fur coat.
I got a chalice.
Speaking of.
- What about stopping Savage?
- What about it?
You're the one who said
we're in this
For the score, remember?
We could live like kings here.
No cops, no heroes...
Just some fool
in a green hoodie.
It's Christmas every day.
Ah, my sweet.
Slade had a son?
Look, Oliver tried.
He tried to raise an army
to fight Deathstroke, but...
Everyone just wanted
to evacuate.
How can you save a city
that doesn't want to be saved?
A moment. Sara, I know what
you must be thinking,
But none of what
has transpired here
Is your fault,
nor do you have the means
To change it,
but Vandal Savage's future
Is preventable.
I implore you,
Please stay focused
on our mission.
We're very grateful
for your assistance,
but we really must
be moving along
- to Smoak technologies.
- What for?
That place has been
cleared out for years,
but a lot of Felicity Smoak's
projects got relocated.
Where?
Come on.
You didn't say that Felicity's
equipment would be here.
Well, where else would
you think it'd be?
Mr. Queen's base of operations
Appears to have
seen better days.
Yeah, well...
The place got attacked
after Grant Wilson
Outed Queen
as the Green Arrow.
Let's just find what
we're looking for
And get out of here.
Whoever's there, get out.
I said get out!
Whoever you are, get out.
Oliver?
Hello, Sara.
Long time, no see.
- Is that...
- Oliver Queen.
Everyone thinks
that you're dead.
They're not wrong.
Put the arrow down, John.
You're embarrassing yourself.
- John?
- John Diggle junior.
My dad is dead
Because I couldn't save him.
I don't deserve his name.
I'm Connor Hawke.
So you won't take his name,
But it's all right
to parade around
In someone else's outfit?
Well, someone has to,
Because last time
that I checked, you were dead.
Everyone thought you were dead.
I've been trying to hold
this city by myself
Because I thought you were gone.
What happened to you?
To Laurel, to my dad...
- Felicity...
- They're gone.
- All of them.
- What do you mean?
- Ollie...
- Gone.
What do you want me
to say, Sara?
30 years ago, you and Ray
hopped on a spaceship.
- And you never came back.
- We will.
I don't want to say that...
things would have
ended differently
if you and Ray
had been here, but...
But if we were,
it could've made the difference.
You thought I was dead.
What are you doing here?
We were looking for
a neuromorphic prototype
That Felicity Smoak
was working on.
Felicity left after
everything that happened.
Everything her company
was working on
is being kept in a warehouse
at Adams and O'Neil.
- Entry code is 4-5-8-7.
- Thank you, Mr.
You found your way in...
Find your way out.
I got to admit,
that wasn't bad advice, Grey.
So things went well
with Ms. Saunders?
Oh, yeah.
Well, I have more good news.
I was able to very subtly
confirm
That Raymond has
no romantic inclinations
Towards your crush object.
Okay, well, once we've
sorted out my love life,
We need to update
your vocabulary.
Can't wait.
I'm gonna
go check on Kendra.
- Hey... confidence.
- Yeah.
Hey.
I got the initial dampeners
back online.
Once the rest of the team
returns with
The neuromorphic prototype,
Gideon will be good to go.
Excellent.
Sooner we get out of here,
the better.
- And thank you, by the way.
- Whatever for?
Well, till you mentioned it,
I hadn't really thought
about Kendra in that way,
Because, you know,
she and Carter
Were destined to be together
in this lifetime,
But it's all changed
And, uh, you know,
she's quirky
And funny and beautiful
And a pretty good welder.
So... you know,
What about all those things
we were talking about?
The mission and so forth?
Oh, well,
we're all adults here, right?
Getting to know each other
a little bit better,
It's not gonna stop us
from saving the world.
Oh, boy.
Who invited them?
Word on the street
is Deathstroke
Is pissed about something.
Deathstroke...
what kind of name's that?
Party's over.
Everyone hit the streets.
Hit everybody on them.
I want Green Arrow
dead by morning.
Listen, pal,
this is my gang.
The only orders they take
are from me.
Hmm, might be your gang,
but it's my city.
Green Arrow is running with
a female assassin in white
And a Brit in a brown coat.
Kill them all.
Heard the man.
Let's go.
Looks like your new minions
Are about to go on
a citywide manhunt
For Rip and Sara.
So what?
They're gonna kill
our friends.
Since when did they
become our friends?
You tell me.
You and Raymond seemed
to get pretty tight
Back in Russia.
I've never been
tight with anyone.
Mick, it's time to go.
- You're not the boss of me.
- Actually, I am.
Okay, let's both
take a deep breath.
And we'll make
ourselves a deal.
You help me
get to Rip and Sara.
Once they're safe,
we can have this conversation.
Fair?
Thank you for agreeing
to accompany us, Mr. Diggle.
It's Connor.
It's not like I needed
to stick around Oliver Queen
for anything.
- Did you know?
- Know what?
That this is what
would happen in my city?
Oliver said that
the only reason
that things got so bad
is because Ray and I
weren't there to help.
I suspected that
might be the case,
but that's actually
a good thing. Hm?
Now, once our mission
is complete
and you and Dr. Palmer are
returned to Star City in 2016,
you will both be present
to stop Grant Wilson's uprising.
This future is only
a potential timeline.
So this...
this version of Star City...
This doesn't have to happen?
Correct.
The future is always in flux.
Hopefully, this will
never come to pass.
This world isn't real.
Let's split up.
We'll cover more ground.
Hello, beautiful.
There's too many of them!
Gentlemen, your timing
is exemplary.
Where's Connor?
He's been taken.
These are Grant Wilson's men.
Hmm.
The guy with the half face
and the body armor
Has a real mad-on
for the kid in the hoodie.
- Can I have a word?
- Rip...
I know what you're
going to say.
- We have to get him back.
- Yes, that.
You're forgetting this future
Is only a potential timeline.
Yeah, where Grant Wilson
kills Connor.
Wilson's not going
to murder Connor,
Because once you're
returned to 2016,
There won't be a Wilson
or a Connor,
At least not as we know them
both right now.
Now that we rescued them,
Let's have that chat.
You want to stay here.
Thought I made that
pretty clear.
What I'm less clear on
is why you don't.
A city of thieves
and criminals...
Sounds like a lot
of competition.
Then we wipe them out.
What I did to that other guy,
We do the same thing
to this Grant Wilson
And anyone else stupid enough
to get in our way.
Take a look around, Snart.
We're living the dream.
Yeah.
Speaking of which...
Sleep tight, buddy.
What happened to him?
Difference of opinion.
Right.
We need to get this
and Mr. Rory
Back to the Waverider.
Ugh!
Oh, Jefferson, perfect timing.
I'm in need of your
mechanical acumen.
Okay, let's do it.
- What?
- What did you do?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
You did something.
What did you do?
Nothing, nothing.
You know, this psychic
connection thing,
It goes both ways
And the moment that
I walked in here,
I started feeling
really anxious and guilty.
You feel guilty,
so what did you do?
In my defense, I was only
acting in your best interests.
What did you do?
It's possible in my
attempt to discern
Whether Dr. Palmer had competing
feelings for Ms. Saunders...
Oh, you didn't...
I may have inadvertently
prompted him
To think of her in ways
in which...
He hadn't.
- Ugh, Grey!
- I'm sorry.
My intentions were honorable.
Ah, it's cool.
- Is it?
- Yeah.
I mean, nothing's
really changed
Apart from the fact that
now I got competition
I didn't have before,
But I should still have
confidence in myself.
Right?
Right.
Oh, they're back.
Where's Mr. Rory?
Sleeping it off.
We have
the neuromorphic prototype.
Any luck with
the ship's engines?
Yeah, it's all good.
Is there something
wrong, Ms. Lance?
Well, all my friends
and family are dead,
Except for Oliver Queen,
who happens to be dead inside
And missing his left arm.
Sara, I have told you...
That this is just
a potential future
And that it's all gonna go back
When we return to 2016...
If we return.
But what if we don't?
We all know Carter's
not coming back.
It's not like we have
the safest line of work.
I think if Sara wants
to stay and help
That then we should.
I mean, that's what
we signed up for:
- To be heroes.
- I agree with Jefferson.
Yes, of course you both do,
because neither of you
understand the pitfalls
Of changing the timeline.
Meddling with the future
is arguably more dangerous
than changing the past,
because it is still in flux.
Your wife and son's death
are in the future.
You want us to change that.
Do not play that
card with me.
So what?
Are you only willing
to risk the timeline
if it's your own family?
I am not just trying
to save my family
And I'm not just trying
to save one city,
But the entire world!
I'm not being selfish, Sara.
Go to hell.
Most likely.
If you want to go
and save Mr. Hawke,
Then be my guest.
I'll keep the ship here
for one hour,
Then we're leaving.
With you on board or without.
Hello, Mick.
You son of a bitch.
Just calm down.
You lied to me!
Wouldn't be the first time.
Remember the Del Ray
currency exchange?
The blackhawk armored car job?
If I hadn't lied to you
on those scores,
we'd both be
in prison or dead.
I'm the brains.
You're the muscle.
That's how it's always been.
And on occasion,
I've had to call some audibles.
You have a habit of getting
in your own way, Mick.
You're right.
You've lied to me
about jobs before,
But then again,
you lied to me
About this being a job.
It's not about the score
anymore for you.
You'd rather save the world
than be my partner.
A real team player.
'Cause that's what it's
gonna take to defeat Savage.
Then what? More money?
More power?
A life of leisure and sin?
Don't you get it, Mick?
If we take out Savage,
this immortal monster,
Can't you see
what that gets us?
No, tell me.
We'd be the two baddest
sons of bitches of all time.
I don't want
a ticker tape parade.
You know what I want
from this world.
Yes...
To see it burn.
You lay a hand on me again,
You'll burn too.
Oliver.
Oliver!
Thought I told you to go.
Grant Wilson has Connor.
They're gonna kill him.
He knew what he
was signing up for
And you there's nothing
I can do to help him.
That's not the Oliver Queen
that I know.
Maybe I'm not that
person anymore.
Look at me, Sara.
I'm literally half the man
I used to be.
Then that's the half
this city needs.
He's got too many men, Ollie.
I can't do this by myself.
What about your friends?
I'm on my own...
Unless I'm not.
Come on, Sara.
I never got the chance
to ask Connor
Why he wears the hood,
but I know why.
It's because this city
Will always need a Green Arrow.
Is the ship ready
for departure?
No, Ms. Lance is
not yet onboard.
I gave her an hour.
Hardly enough time for...
And she's been 90 minutes.
How much longer are
we supposed to wait?
It doesn't matter that
this is a potential future.
It doesn't matter that this
May never come to pass...
May never be real.
For Sara, this is very real.
I know, which is why
I gave her
An extra 30 minutes.
Gideon, what's our status?
The Waverider
is operational, Captain,
But I can't guarantee
for how long.
- Explain.
- We are cloaked,
but positioned
dangerously close
to where the city's criminal
element is gathering
to witness the execution
of Connor Hawke.
The longer we wait,
the greater the risk
of detection and further
damage to the ship.
Do you really want to risk
being marooned in this version
of 2046 forever?
Certainly more than I
want to maroon Sara here.
She's our friend.
Our teammate.
What's the point
of stopping Savage
If we only become
as immoral as he is
In the process?
You should be honored.
This is hallowed ground.
I took Oliver Queen's arm
In this very spot.
Well, then let me go,
And we'll see which one
of us is tougher:
Me or Queen.
I already know
the answer to that.
Ready the prisoner.
Sir.
We saw her trying to
sneak past the perimeter.
Sloppy.
The league of assassins
would be embarrassed.
What was your strategy here?
You really think you could
just turn up tonight...
Kill me?
No.
It was just my job
to distract you.
You're not Green Arrow.
You're just a punk
in a Halloween costume.
Funny, I was gonna say
the same thing about you.
You want to fight
the Green Arrow?
I'm right here.
You convinced Rip to stay.
Actually, sending in
the cavalry was his idea.
Where's Mr. Queen?
Connor!
Ugh!
Cowards, all!
Oliver?
It's good to see you
again, Ray. Kendra.
Thanks for the assist.
So who's that?
His name is Grant Wilson.
Once upon a time,
his father, Slade,
Tried to ruin my life.
That's not a nice family.
That's good shooting, John.
It's Connor.
Either way,
It's Green Arrow.
We have a lot of work to do.
Grant Wilson did a good job
Of keeping the criminal element
in the city together.
Now, there will
be plenty of people
To fill the vacuum.
I feel like I should stay.
Before Ray left,
He told me why Rip
brought all of you together.
It's important, Sara.
I just hate the idea
Of leaving you here
to fix it alone.
I'm not alone.
Just... just be careful,
all right?
Well, you should know
better than most
I rarely ever am.
You watch his back.
Copy that.
Let's get to work.
All right, confidence.
Confidence.
Okay.
So, uh,
I think Rip might have
Some of that vodka
left in his cabinet.
And?
And...
Maybe we could get a drink?
Are you asking me out?
Yes? No.
I think so.
Is that okay?
Yeah, that...
that's totally okay,
Except that three months ago,
I was a completely
normal person
And now I'm a hawk goddess
Traveling through time,
Trying to avoid being killed
by an immortal psychopath
Who murdered the man
I was destined to be with.
So...
I'm sorry, Ray.
I...
I think my life's
complicated enough
Without throwing
whatever this is
Into the mix.
Yeah, totally understand.
If I was a reincarnated
Egyptian priestess,
I'd probably feel the same way.
I'm gonna go check
on Professor Stein.
Mm-hmm, yup.
All good here.
- Absolutely no problems.
- Everything okay here?
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, fine. You?
Oh, yeah, good. Good.
It's good.
Uh...
How much of that
did you hear?
Uh, enough.
I'm sorry.
Sorry too.
Wait, you knew that I...
- Yeah.
- yeah.
You're not that subtle.
She would've picked me,
by the way.
Keep telling yourself that.
She would've.
I'm just working on
determining
Our next destination.
I've considered your
suggesting of hell,
But I think I'll give it
a miss for the time being.
I just wanted to
say thank you
For sending the team
to back me up.
As it turns out,
you were right.
That must've been
hard to say.
Of late I've discovered
That I still have
a lot to learn, I admit.
Including the fact
that every future
Is worth fighting for.
That said...
This mission is
going to continue
To present us with
difficult choices,
And I need to know that
you are a member of this team.
I guess so.
All right, Gideon,
let's see if these repairs
That Martin, Ray, and Jax made
are up to scratch.
As far as I can tell,
Ms. Saunders
Did most of the work,
while the two gentlemen
Competed for...
just get us out of here.
Please, Gideon.
I'm gonna miss this place.
Yeah, they really seemed
like your kind of people.
I don't know who
my people are anymore.
So where to next, Captain?
Well, the beauty
of this mission is that
The real question
is not where, but when.
In which case,
I suggest that we next hit
Savage when
he least expects it.