Hi removed, capitalization issues fixed,
cleaned and corrected by Tronar
In 2166, an immortal tyrant
named Vandal Savage
conquered the world
and murdered my wife and child.
I have assembled an elite team
to hunt him throughout time
and stop his rise to power.
Unfortunately, my plan
is opposed by the body
I'd sworn my allegiance to,
the Time Masters.
In the future, my friends
may not be heroes,
but if we succeed,
they will be remembered
as legends.
Previously on
"Legends of Tomorrow"...
Time masters.
They took me to a place
called the vanishing point.
I've spent lifetimes
training by them
Mr. Jackson's internal organs
are aging
at an accelerated rate.
The rest of his body
will soon follow.
The trip through
the time stream
should reverse you condition.
If we're separated,
you'll die.
This man you've brought before
us is needed back in 2166.
- Take him away.
- What?
Search their ship
for the others.
- You're under arrest.
- Mick, what's going on?
We need to find
somewhere to hide.
I need to be getting back
to 2166.
I've been waiting to meet
your family.
And because if you don't
follow me,
this is what is in store for
your world 150 years from now.
I could have chosen
any time and any place.
Of all the people
who ever lived,
I chose you eight.
I certainly hope
that you won't let me,
and the world, down.
If your answer is yes,
meet me at this address
in 36 hours.
So what do you think?
I think that's five minutes
of my life I'm not getting back.
He just showed us
the entire world in flames.
You can't turn your back
on that.
Observe.
Well, I think we can
all agree
that the mission will go
a whole lot better
without those two.
I haven't signed on yet.
And I'm not signing on
at all.
- Jefferson...
- No.
I'm not going off to die
in some apocalyptic future.
I'm staying right here
in the present.
Let me talk to him.
Jefferson, can we at least
discuss this?
Oh, that's a first.
And it was always you
trying to tell me what to do.
It's not happening this time.
But if the fate of the world
is at stake...
then the world can find
somebody more capable than me.
I have confidence in us
as Firestorm.
All right, look,
just sleep on it.
Come to my office tomorrow,
and if your answer's still no...
it will be.
Grey, we need to talk.
We were just talking.
How did you change your clothes
so fast?
Something called time travel.
I need your help.
The team's in trouble.
Martin, are you okay?
I'm required to merge
with Jefferson...
Periodically in order
to maintain nuclear cohesion.
Then sending him away
on the jumpship
probably wasn't
the greatest idea.
Given the circumstances
we're under,
I'm surprised any of us
are alive.
Oh, you'll be dead soon.
You're getting off easy.
What gives you the free pass?
- They have other plans for me.
- As Chronos.
They're gonna try
and put me through
the induction process again.
- Brainwashing?
- Kills most men, Professor.
And those that don't die,
end up like mindless goats.
But Snart said
you weren't mindless
when you were Chronos.
Not any more that usual,
anyway.
The whole time,
I stayed focused on one thing.
The one thing
that kept me sane...
Vengeance.
I focused on how much
I hated all of you.
Ah, gentlemen,
I missed you.
Come on in.
Ah, that's it.
Oh, yeah, break my arm.
Hey, what are you doing?
Why are you taking her?
Hey!
Kendra!
Leave us.
I have a query.
Why haven't
we killed you yet?
That's what you've been trying
to do all this time.
Fortunately for you,
two of your crew
are still at large.
Tell me where to find them,
and I'll spare the others.
If it is anything like the
offer you gave me in the USSR,
I'm sorely tempted.
You were a fugitive
from justice.
You're helping Vandal Savage
take over the world.
I have a feeling
that our definition
of the word "justice"
may differ somewhat.
The only difference
between us
is my view of the timeline
reaches further
and wider than yours.
Am I supposed
to be impressed?
In 2175,
less than ten years
from when Savage
conquers the world,
the Earth is attacked
by a warlike race
of extraterrestrials
from the planet Thanagar.
Without Savage to unite
the world under a singular rule,
this is what becomes
of the world.
This is the work of Savage.
No.
This is what will happen
to Earth
if Savage is not there
to lead it.
Without him,
all human life is extinguished.
Even this realm falls
to the Thanagarians.
Are you impressed now?
No.
You are as mad
as your friend vandal
if you think that he
is the world's only hope.
We've examined the timeline.
There is no other hope.
I don't expect you
to take my word for it.
That's why there's something
else I have to show you.
How did you even know
that was down there?
When Rip first recruited us,
I made it my business
to case every square inch
of this tub
in the event there was
something worth stealing.
There wasn't.
Let's get out of here.
Wait, what about the team?
There's nothing more
we can do for them.
You're just gonna leave Mick?
If the Time Masters are half
as twisted as Mick said,
there's an excellent chance
Mick is no longer Mick.
Now why aren't we flying yet?
Because I'm not
going anywhere.
And even if we wanted to,
we're in a hangar
surrounded by an entire armada
of timeships.
It's the Waverider.
We've got guns.
We can blast our way out.
This isn't
"Bonnie and Clyde".
And I'm not going anywhere
without the rest of the team.
Maybe I didn't
make myself clear.
Don't do that.
Don't act like you're that same
cold-hearted bastard
that I first met.
I remember Russia.
And you were the one
who told me not to kill Stein.
Yeah, because you seem
to have a problem
with being a killer.
I, however, don't.
Prove it.
Shoot me.
- Hello?
- Hello, Ms. Lance.
Gideon, you're alive.
If be being "alive" you mean
that my operating system
is intact, yes,
I was able to upload
into the latency core
to avoid being wiped out
when the Time Masters...
We can share
war stories later.
Where the rest of the team?
They're in cell block 4587,
and they, too, are alive...
For the moment.
What do you mean
"for the moment"?
Oh, you're awake.
Oh, I wouldn't bother.
Those straps are forged
from Tiberian steel.
This is a timeship.
A little gift
from my friends.
Oh, Prince Khufu
is with us as well.
He's being held in stasis
down at the cargo hold.
And where are you taking us?
To an appointment
that I have.
With destiny.
You should be familiar
with this procedure, Chronos.
The name's Mick.
Though we've made
some refinements.
Clearly, your conditioning
was not as thorough
as it should have been.
For a Time Master,
you sure waste a lot of it.
Even with only
a partial induction,
you were the greatest
of our hunters, Chronos.
After we're finished,
temporal criminals
and time pirates alike
will quake at the sound
of your bootsteps.
Mm, well, for your sake,
you better hope that plan works.
'Cause if it doesn't, that
boot's gonna crush your skull.
- What is this place?
- Our holy of holies.
The Oculus Viewing Chamber,
our most powerful window
into past, present, and future.
The source of all
our information on the timeline.
Why did I now know
about this?
No Captain does.
The Oculus' existence
is known
only to the high council,
including its greatest secret:
The Oculus not only gives us
a window into time,
but the ability to shape it
as we see fit.
We've been helping Vandal Savage
consolidate his power
by giving him access
to time travel.
But you've been
helping him too.
From the moment we realized only
Savage could save the world,
we've been using the Oculus
to manipulate you.
- That's impossible.
- Think about it.
Thanks to your efforts,
Vandal Savage was not in prison
for the sale of a nuclear weapon
in 1975.
You prevented the Soviet Union
from winning
the cold war in 1986.
Carter hall's death provided
Savage's closest Lieutenants
preternaturally long lives.
You and your team
have been moving
through the course of time.
We've merely redirected it,
and you,
to the outcomes
history requires.
Look, see for yourself.
You're looking into the past.
You see that everything
I've told you is true.
This isn't only the past.
You can also see the future.
Not possible future.
Not a prediction.
You are looking at events
as they will happen.
What about choice?
What about free will?
Illusions.
The only place in the universe
free will exists is here
at the vanishing point.
No!
No matter what you do,
it will happen.
And there is nothing
you can do to stop it.
No, I acted without
your consent.
In... in defiance of your orders.
Everything I've done
has been to save my family.
No one controls me!
We counted on that,
your anger, on you going rogue.
We needed something
to spur you on,
to give you purpose.
That's why we ordered...
Savage to kill your family.
Rip?
Oh, my god,
they've tortured him.
What did they do to you?
They showed me the truth.
Druce showed me something
called the Oculus.
They've been controlling
us all.
Nothing we've done so far
has been of our own accord.
We've been following a script
laid out by the Time Masters.
No, that's...
that's not possible.
I-I refuse to believe that.
Well, you should, Raymond...
Because they showed me
your death.
I'm sorry.
You said the team
was in trouble.
What sort of trouble,
exactly?
I'm not sure exactly,
but I'm getting something
from our psychic connection.
Which means I'm in trouble.
What happens?
Come on, Grey,
you know I can't tell you that.
- Says who?
- Says you...
- In the future.
- Oh.
And even if I didn't have
to worry about the dangers
of giving you future knowledge,
we got bigger things
to worry about.
Hey, you're drawing
too much power
from the Sequestrian manifold.
That's nonsense, Jefferson.
Need I remind you who invented
the Sequestrian manifold?
Oh, dear god.
- Yeah.
- Well, you were right.
Oh, don't sound
so surprised.
Well, it's not often
that an auto mechanic
knows more than
a nuclear physicist.
You know, I forgot
how arrogant you were.
"Were"?
Why are you referring to me
in the past tense?
Do you witness my death?
Relax, you don't die.
Horribly maimed.
Why won't you tell me
what happens?
Instead of pestering me
about the future
and being
an insufferable know-it-all,
why don't you help me
reroute the temporal flow
off the secondary buffer
instead of just
worrying about yourself?
- Hmm?
- All right.
I apologize for how painful
the induction process was.
Many of your memories
were rooted deep.
It took effort
to pull them out.
Tell me...
What is your name?
Your name!
Your name?
- Your...
- Chronos.
Release him.
There is much hunting
to be done.
Let us begin with Sara Lance
and Leonard Snart.
- This is a bad plan.
- It's Gideon's.
You're not helping
your argument.
We need to finish putting
these on the ships,
and get back
to the Waverider.
I can't just stand around here
and wait to die.
Well, if it's any consolation,
you're not alone.
Oh, you're giving up too?
Well, let's just review our
situation, shall we, Raymond?
They're turning Mr. Rory
back into Chronos,
I... I'm about to have
a nuclear meltdown...
and our Captain thinks
our future
is already written for us.
You know what I think?
I think you're both
a couple of quitters.
There's no escape
from either these cells
or from the future.
Face the facts, Raymond.
We're completely
out of allies.
You're forgetting
Sarah and Snart.
As long as
they're on the loose,
we still have a chance.
Just another moment.
I'm almost through.
Even if this works,
we're never gonna be able
to fly out off here.
Well, that's the beauty
of having a timeship.
We don't have to fly
anywhere.
Can you stop doing that?
Why did you start wearing
that thing, anyways?
It's from the first job
I ever pulled off with Mick.
A freeport warehouse.
Oh, you do have
a sentimental side.
It's not a keepsake.
It's a reminder.
Of what?
That even the best laid plans
can go sideways.
Spent a lot of time
prepping for that heist.
Casing the target.
Memorizing shift changes
and delivery schedules,
and then surprise!
Turns out they'd upgraded
their security system.
We had to bolt.
Three weeks of planning
and all I have to show for it...
Was a lousy pinky ring.
So sad.
Considering I'm about
to trade my life for nothing,
I think I came out ahead.
The time drive
is back online.
Strap in.
Sir, the Waverider
just time-jumped.
Order all available
timeships to pursue.
Sir, the Captains
aren't prepared for...
All of them!
- Godfrey, what's happening?
- I'm sorry, Captain.
Critical systems are being
overridden by an external...
♪ singing a song ♪
♪ don't mess around,
you just got to be strong ♪
- ♪  just stop ♪
- Godfrey?
♪  'Cause I really love you ♪
♪ Stop! ♪
♪ I'll be thinking of you ♪
- Godfrey, reboot.
- ♪ look in my heart ♪
♪  and let love ♪
♪ keep us together ♪
♪ whatever
ba-ba-ba-ba-ba, whatever ♪
Your friends
have time-jumped away.
We've lost them.
And I've lost any reason
to keep you alive.
Hold on, let's just talk
about this a moment.
Time master Druce.
Kill them all.
- Starting with him.
- Yes, sir.
But we've calculated
when the Waverider is headed.
Past or future?
The present.
Somebody order up a rescue?
Mr. Snart,
your timing is impeccable.
Or not.
Put the gun down, Mick.
Chronos, fire.
Sure thing.
If I recall,
I made you a certain promise.
No, I beg of you.
No!
Where's everyone else?
Uh, Mr. Snart is helping
the Professor
get situated in the medbay.
He's not doing so how
without his nuclear super-half.
Get me out of this
stupid robot suit.
First get us the hell
out of here... Gideon?
I'm here, Captain,
and if I could take a moment
to add how wonderful it feels
to be back together.
I have missed you too.
Now that we've had
our reunion,
I should mention
we have a slight problem.
Uh, the Time Masters
are locking onto us
with a tractor beam.
Punch it, Gideon.
Sorry, your job.
Ms. Lance,
stay right where you are.
You've proven yourself quite
adept at piloting this ship.
About the tractor beam...
Dr. Palmer is going to help me
remotely disable it.
I've already established
an uplink
to the omnimatrix mainframe,
Captain.
The Time Masters are evil,
but they're not dumb.
There's no way
they're gonna let Gideon
override the tractor beam
remotely.
Whatever you're gonna do,
you better do it now.
- They've locked on.
- Wait.
What if we convince the system
that the override command
- is coming from somewhere else?
- Or someone else.
Someone they trust.
Just need to borrow...
Chronos' operating system.
I'm "hotswapping" Mr. Rory's
hard drive as we speak.
Whatever you're doing,
do it faster.
And... done.
Now, Sara!
Well, I suppose it's time
to say good-bye.
At least for now.
Oh, one more thing,
don't forget to initiate the...
the quantum attenuator once I
lock on to the vanishing point.
Right.
I suppose it's also time
to apologize
for being an
"insufferable know-it-all".
You know,
it used to drive me crazy,
but I understand it's just
your way
of trying to look out for me.
Oh, by the way,
I'm going to be real pissed
about this whole
roofie thing,
- but I do get over it.
- Roofie thing?
- I-I would never dream...
- Yeah, you do...
But it's okay.
It's actually
the best decision I never made.
The future...
You want to know
what happens?
No, no,
it's... it's all right.
I-I know enough.
The young man in front of me
is proof
that something must have
gone right on this adventure.
- So long, Martin.
- So long, Jefferson.
Professor's in the medbay.
Promises not to blow up
while he's on board,
which I thought was considerate.
Yeah, the Professor's
condition is the least
of our worries, I'm afraid.
Yeah, much to my chagrin,
it turns out everything
we've done,
maybe even our whole lives,
has been determined
by the Time Masters.
- What?
- The Time Masters have
this thing called the Oculus,
which allows them
not only to gaze
into the future,
but to engineer it.
A future where I'm dead,
apparently.
And why would
they want you dead?
Have you ever listened
to what comes out of his mouth?
Now, in my opinion,
Dr. Palmer's death
is not part of their plan.
No, that's not reassuring.
Ow!
You saying the Time Masters
wanted me to do that?
What I'm saying is that
they've been engineering
our lives to move
in very specific directions.
And we are playing out
that script even now.
So we can go to 2016,
but that might be
what the Time Masters want.
Or we can go get
Kendra and Carter...
which could also be
what they want.
Then we need to do
what they don't want.
If the Oculus is what
they're using to control us,
then we need to destroy it.
But how do we do that if
the time bastards
are pulling our strings?
Well, Druce told me
that the Oculus' ability
to control our actions doesn't
work in the vanishing point,
most likely because
the vanishing point itself
exists outside of time.
Explains why we were able
to escape.
And why we might actually have
a shot at destroying this thing.
- I'm with Ray.
- Ow.
If I'm gonna be
someone's puppet,
I'm gonna be the one who cuts
his own bloody strings.
And I like blowing stuff up.
We set out on this mission to
stop Savage and save the world.
To become legends
and change our fates.
That mission hasn't changed.
This is madness.
I like it.
Gideon, plot a course
to the Oculus wellspring.
Team...
I think it's about time
we seized our destinies back.
Mmm.
If I'm gonna die,
no sense watching my diet.
The Time Masters
have been known
to make mistakes, you know?
But what if those mistakes
were all part of their plan?
Actually, I gotta stop
thinking about it.
The temporal implications
are infinite.
That's why I don't think.
- Not bad, right?
- Good.
- So how'd you do it?
- Do what?
How did you not
get turned into Chronos?
You said the only way you held
onto yourself the first time
was by focusing on
your hate.
What did I focus on
this time?
The team.
And how much
you cared for us?
I thought about how royally
screwed you'd be without me.
My point being,
if I can survive
not being turned into Chronos,
you can survive anything
they throw at you.
Thanks.
I'll keep it in mind.
Well, you better
because if you tell the team
I actually care,
I'll shave your head.
Man, this is good.
Not in the mood.
I was gonna apologize
for pulling a gun on you,
but apparently
I was just following a script.
Doesn't make you
any less of a jerk.
Guilty.
So what do we think
of Rip's plan?
Does it matter?
Apparently everything
we're going to do
has already been predetermined
by Rip's former bosses.
It's funny, I've always
prided myself on being the guy
who doesn't play
by the rules.
Come to find out,
I'm the one being played.
I don't know.
I still feel responsible
for everything I've done.
And it still keeps me up
at night.
It's the things I didn't do
that keep me up at night.
- What's that?
- Oh, I don't know.
Maybe it's being on this ship
traveling through time
I started to wonder what
the future might hold for me...
And you...
And me and you.
You want to steal a kiss
from me, Leonard?
You better be one hell
of a thief.
How you feeling, Martin?
Well, I'm dying.
I'm also sure that you're dying
and so are all the others.
I'm just a little
ahead of you.
Normally I'd be quite concerned,
but the truth is
discovering one's life
has already been predetermined
is ironically liberating.
I... I've already run through
everything we know
about the Oculus,
and with the help of a few
"back of the envelope"
physics calculations,
I'm determined
that we have a chance.
Infinitesimal as that may be.
Captain, we've arrived
at the Oculus wellspring
on the far side
of the vanishing point.
Based on Captain Hunter's
description,
the Oculus is a massive
temporal computer,
most likely powered
by a scaled-down supernova
contained at the bottom
of the wellspring.
Why aren't any of you
more excited by this?
We're excited
to blow it up.
Dr. Palmer will deactivate
the core contained supernova,
which should create
an anomalistic event.
A very big explosion.
Sounds like a plan.
Hello again, Rip.
Right on schedule.
Uh, I think we've walked
into a trap.
No, it's destiny.
I must say you've all
played your parts well.
As with everything else
you've done,
I'm afraid it was all
for nothing.
All your posturing.
All your claims about doing
what's best for the timeline,
about protecting history,
and it all comes down
to cold blooded murder.
The difference between
murder and execution
is only a matter of authority.
I have it.
You don't.
Kill them.
Returning the jumpship
to the Waverider.
- Good luck, Mr. Jackson.
- Hope I'm not too late.
No, Jefferson,
you're right on time.
- How did you...
- What?
You thought you were
the only one
who knew a thing or two
about time travel?
Good work.
We need to get to the Oculus
before reinforcements arrive.
Take about two minutes
to figure out
how to self-destruct
this thing.
We'll buy you some time.
You lot guard the entrance.
Mr. Rory, you're with me.
Now if you'd excuse me,
I won't be long.
Savage...
Hath-set!
Please.
Don't do this.
Don't kill Rip's family.
In a cosmic sense,
it's already done.
No!
Savage!
- Hurry up, haircut.
- How much longer?
Well, just about to reverse
the polarity matrix.
Once I do that,
I say we have about two minutes
before this whole place
goes boom.
How big of a boom?
On a scale from one to ten...
A googolplex.
- What are you doing?
- I can't work
with all this gear on.
You can't.
- A programmer needs his hands.
- Ray...
- I got this, don't worry.
- No, you don't.
This is what I saw.
This is what Druce showed me.
This is how you die.
It's okay.
All my life I've wanted to
make a difference.
Creating a future for you guys
without the Time Masters
influence,
that counts.
That said,
I'm in no rush to die,
so keep 'em off me, okay?
We got you.
Keep firing!
Ahh!
I'm not doing this
'cause I like you.
Yes, I know.
All right.
Almost done.
- Uh-oh.
- Uh-oh?
There seems to be a failsafe
to prevent tampering,
which probably includes
trying to blow this thing up.
English, haircut.
I have to maintain contact
with the failsafe
it order to destroy
the Oculus.
Not that much English.
Ahh!
Get back to the ship.
We are not leaving
without you.
You've already seen the
future. I'm dead already.
You're right.
- Mick...
- I got this.
I want revenge
on those bastards.
Now get outta here.
Your mother was brave...
Just as your father
was foolish.
Which are you?
We're leaving.
Where's Raymond and Mick?
Ray is in my pocket
and Mick has elected to stay.
- Why?
- Someone needs to be present
to destroy the Oculus.
Mick has elected himself.
No, no, no, no, no, you can't.
There isn't ti...
We gotta go!
- Mick.
- Get outta here.
Not without you, Mick.
Pretty boy said I gotta hold
this stick for the ship to blow.
So I'm holding this stick.
Now leave!
My old friend,
please forgive me.
For what?
- Get him outta here.
- No.
Just do it.
You take after your mother,
huh?
Or not.
No, shut it down.
Shut it down!
There are no strings on me.
He traded his life
for ours.
He was a hero.
Which I'm pretty sure is
the last thing
he wanted to be
remembered as.
But that's what he was.
- Gideon?
- Yes, Captain?
Would you please review
the timeline for me?
There is no timeline data
due to the destruction
of the Oculus.
We're sailing
without a map.
Uh, would you please...
Review news accounts
from 2166 then.
You know what I need
to find out.
I'm sorry, Captain.
News accounts from 2166
confirm that Vandal Savage
has already succeeded in
murdering Miranda and Jonas.
Hey.
Get out.
I want to be alone.
Gideon has confirmed that
the Oculus has been destroyed.
From here on out,
it's Tabula Rasa.
Pretend for a minute
that I don't speak Greek.
Latin.
Sorry.
From this point forward,
our actions are our own.
We have free will.
That supposed to make me
feel better?
Yes.
It means that Leonard
didn't die for nothing.
He planted that on me
before it happened.
I'm sorry, Mick.
I killed Declan,
Druce is dead.
The Time Masters have nothing
now that their ship
was completely destroyed.
Yet I still feel a need
to kill someone for Snart.
Savage still has
Carter and Kendra.
He'll do nicely.
Oh, don't weep for the dead,
Chay-Ara.
They're mortal.
They're beneath us.
I want to speak
with Time Master Druce.
- Mr. Savage.
- I wish to speak with Druce.
Time master Druce is dead.
Hunter.
We've lost the ability
to manipulate time.
And how is that
of concern to me?
You are beyond our aid,
Mr. Savage.
We cannot help you
any longer.
And what of the threat
of the Thanagarians?
Without the Oculus,
time is unmoored.
Events will no longer unfold
as we've foreseen.
Or as we've engineered.
Terminate transmission.
It looks like your friends
have cut you loose.
How long do you think
you can hold onto power
with out the Time Masters
backing you?
Not long, I'm afraid,
but they have provided me
with a timeship.
I no longer need to rule
the world, Chay-Ara.
I now have the ability
to change it.
Greg, move your head.