HI removed, capitalization issues fixed,
cleaned and corrected by Tronar
In 2166, an immortal tyrant
named Vandal Savage
conquered the world
and murdered my wife and child.
I have assembled an elite team
to hunt him throughout time
and stop his rise to power.
Unfortunately,
my plan is opposed
by the body
I'd sworn my allegiance to:
The Time Masters.
In the future, my friends
may not be heroes,
but if we succeed,
they will be remembered
as legends.
Previously
on "Legends of Tomorrow"...
Ray!
Ray, I need you! Please!
I thought you were dead.
Well, not only did you fail
to capture Savage.
You also exposed yourselves
and your powers to him,
Giving away
the element of surprise
For now and all time.
I let you go,
you'll deliver the Waverider.
Boys, ship's all yours.
You're a liability
to the team.
Only one of us is
walking out of here alive.
♪ One, two, three o'clock,
four o'clock rock ♪
♪ five, six, seven o'clock,
eight o'clock rock ♪
♪ nine, ten, eleven o'clock ♪
Tommy, promise me
you won't go too fast.
You got to hold on
to something, honey.
- Preferably me.
- Remember.
Just 'cause you stole
your grandma's wheels
don't mean you got
to drive like her.
You run your mouth
pretty fast.
Let's see if your car
can keep up.
- Whoo!
- Let's go!
Whoo!
Tommy, watch it!
♪ When it's eight, nine, ten,
eleven too ♪
♪ I'll be going strong
and so will you ♪
♪ we're gonna rock
around the clock tonight ♪
♪ we're gonna rock, rock,
rock till broad daylight ♪
♪ we're gonna rock,
gonna rock ♪
♪ around the clock tonight ♪
Yo, James Dean!
Are you...
What's that?
I think that's
a comet or something.
It's a meteorite,
In point of fact.
I was drawn to it as well.
Your presence out here
was unexpected.
Or perhaps that's just
another word for...
Destiny.
I'm not the only one
whose vision is blurry
In their left eye, am I?
- Oh.
- Seeing three of everything?
That's normal, right?
Yes, as I mentioned before,
The effect of time travel
on the human body
Increases with the length
of each jaunt.
So where are we?
Harmony falls, Oregon.
According
to Captain Baxter's intel,
Savage makes an appearance
in this quaint little Hamlet.
What the hell is Savage
doing in Pleasantville?
Murder, apparently.
Several denizens
of harmony falls
have been brutally slain,
and others have gone missing.
Huh. Kind of like Rory.
Reports are vague,
but it seems like
the killer is an expert
with knives.
That sounds like
Savage's MO.
Yeah, but
serial killing isn't.
Sounds pretty small-time
for a guy
who's has had coffee with Hitler.
Yeah, well, clearly we have
to assume that Savage
has a larger,
more nefarious plan.
But since we've
jumped back in time,
Savage isn't expecting us here.
Savage is pretty good
at hiding,
even in a small town,
So how do you plan
to find him?
By investigating
these murders.
Now, there has to be
a common link
between the victims,
Starting with the first.
A piano teacher was found
slain in her home,
which is now on the market.
There is, of course,
crown molding.
All original floors.
Stucco ceiling.
There's a small room
above the garage,
suitable for live-in help.
Oh, well,
we don't need a maid.
My husband and I get along
just fine on our own.
You know, I have
a lovely Tudor style
in another town.
A more... accepting one.
Forward-thinking.
No, that's... that's fine.
I like my towns backward.
Dr. Matt Miller
was found murdered
on the grounds of the asylum
where he worked.
The sanitarium is in need
of a replacement.
It's a very
impressive facility.
I did my doctoral thesis
on socio-pathology
In relationship
to serial murder, actually.
Well, that'll certainly
come in handy around here.
We've been short-staffed
ever since
Dr. Miller's sudden demise.
Of course,
I could never consider
Accepting a position here
Without my faithful
nurse/assistant.
Yes, well,
She looks like
she'll fit right in.
Meanwhile, Jefferson
is the perfect age
To discern the facts
behind the disappearance
Of three teenagers
who went missing
A week before
these murders began.
So Raymond and Kendra
are shacking up,
Sara's nurse ratched,
And Jax's the new kid in town.
Where does that leave me?
We're looking
for the sheriff.
Well, you found him.
Bud Ellison.
How can I help you, folks?
Special agent Rip Hunter.
This is my partner, Leonard.
We are here to investigate
the serial murders
Which have plagued this
sleepy old town of yours.
Whoa.
Now, slow down there, buddy.
There ain't
no serial killer anywhere.
All we got is some unexplained
accidents is all.
How about you hand over
those case files
So we can decide for ourselves?
Or we can come back
with a court order
And a really nasty disposition.
Anything for our friends
at the bureau.
Nice work, partner.
You're not my partner.
There's only one person
I ever trusted on this job,
And we all know
how that turned out.
['50s rock music playing]
Schwinn hornets.
I had the very same one
when I was their age.
Seeing white picket fences
And perfect family houses,
It's enough
to make one nostalgic.
Or nauseated.
Oh, come on, Ms. Lance.
Even someone as jaded
as yourself
can't deny how idyllic
this time was.
Yeah.
If you're white.
And a man.
And straight.
And...
Okay, okay.
I get the point.
Dude, even if this town
wasn't full
of small-minded idiots,
It'd still be creepy as hell.
I used to watch all these old
horror movies with my mom,
and they all started off
in places like this.
See, first it's all perfect,
and then, boom,
some alien monster beast thing
starts killing kids
on Lovers' lane.
- Ooh.
- I'm telling you, man.
What is it?
An unhappy cheerleader.
Now, that is scary.
That girl was from
the newspaper articles
Rip showed us.
She knows the guys
that went missing.
Perhaps she can illuminate us
As to their whereabouts.
Dude, can you not just say,
"hey, Jax, why don't you
go talk to her
And find out what she knows?"
Like a normal person.
Hey, Jax,
Why don't you just go do that?
All right. We mustn't dawdle.
I believe our lunch hour
is nearly at an end.
Come along, nurse.
Just so you know,
Ra's Al Ghul taught me
how to kill someone slowly,
Over the course of days.
Hey, you mind if I sit?
You can't sit with him.
What is up with them?
Um...
I-I don't think
they've seen anyone...
Dip their fries
in their milk shake before?
Oh.
Mm-mm, don't knock it
till you tried it, girl.
No.
Okay.
- Okay, that's really good.
- Right?
Yeah.
- I'm Jax.
- Betty.
Nice to meet you, Betty.
Hey, Betty.
Just because your boyfriend
went AWOL
doesn't mean you have to slum it
with this loser.
Why don't you do yourself
a favor, Biff?
Keep walking before you really,
really embarrass yourself.
What?
You want to take a swing at me?
Hey. Let's go.
This isn't over.
I am so sorry about that.
- Uh, where were we?
- No, that was amazing.
Do you want to hang out
tomorrow night?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
- It's a date.
- Okay.
♪ I was caught
by your kisses ♪
Well, now that we're
done moving in,
Care to dance?
Sure.
♪ Locked in your arms ♪
♪ there's no mistake ♪
So yesterday we kissed,
And now today we're married.
Okay, I know it seems like
we're moving fast,
But this is all pretend.
Soon as we get a divorce,
We'll figure us out.
In the meantime,
Doesn't mean we can't
have fun with it.
This is a waste of time.
We should be out there
looking for Savage,
Not playing doctor.
You know what I mean.
I'd like to think
That in a town
with multiple murders
And missing teenagers,
The local insane asylum
Would be fertile ground
for clues.
Let's start
by reviewing the files
Of every inmate
with a history of violence.
If you wouldn't mind
getting me those files, nurse?
Literally for days.
Is that a new perfume
I smell?
You know, if you're trying
to drive everyone crazy,
I have to tell you,
it's working.
I'm very busy right now.
You know what your problem is?
You don't know
how to have a good time.
Now, what you need
Is a man who can show you one.
Oops.
Thank you.
That was incredible.
Well, maybe next time,
He'll take no for an answer.
Uh, it's not just him.
Most of the doctors here
are looking for a good time,
And most of the nurses
all say yes,
'cause they're looking
to get married.
Oh. Not you, though.
I'm...
Not really looking
for a husband.
Today's my first day.
Care to give
the new girl a tour?
The files you asked for,
doctor.
Excellent, nurse.
I could also go
for a cup of coffee.
Me too.
Black. Two sugars.
And the cafeteria's
over there.
It's better than
what we serve the patients
But not by much.
- Mmm.
- Oh.
What's down there?
Oh, that's hall H,
The restricted ward.
It's for Dr. Knox's patients.
Violent psychotics.
That part of the tour
is worth skipping.
Coming!
I'm coming.
Welcome to the neighborhood.
Thank you.
Thank you so much, Miss...
Mrs. Knox.
Gail Knox, and this
Is my husband, Curtis.
Lovely to meet you.
I'm sorry, have...
Have we met before?
I-I doubt it.
I... we just moved in
From way out of town.
I hope you like
tuna surprise.
Are you kidding?
I love tuna surpri...
- Oh, my God...
- Raymond!
These are our new neighbors,
Curtis and Gail.
What a surprise.
Tuna surprise.
So many surprises.
Well, another reason
why we dropped by
was to let you know that we are
having a soiree tonight.
Stop by anytime after 8:00.
We're just across the street.
Don't bother to ring the bell.
No, you just walk right on in.
It's that kind of neighborhood.
Savage doesn't think
I recognize him,
which means he won't
try to kill me.
He can't steal my powers
before I've found them.
Don't forget, we also
have to figure out
why he's killing the townsfolk.
Are you really eating that?
Say what you want
about Savage.
He makes one hell
of a casserole.
Yes, well, Mr. Snart and I
have been analyzing
these forensic files.
Which reveal nothing except
Savage is very good
At making people disappear.
Hmm, something you both
have in common.
Are we just gonna pretend
like none of this happened?
That Mick Rory wasn't
a part of our team?
If you can just
ice your best friend like that,
I hate to think
what you could do to us.
Right now, we need to stay
focused on the mission.
Look, Savage is going
to be busy
With this little cocktail party.
Whilst you two
keep an eye on him,
Sara and Martin
have the opportunity
To find out what he's doing
In the secret wing
of that asylum.
If you're looking for booze,
You're in the wrong office.
Dr. Knox doesn't drink.
But I know where Dr. Enbom
keeps the good stuff.
♪ Bop-bop-bop,
bop-ba-dop-bop ♪
♪ it seems like
everyone's in love ♪
♪ everyone but me ♪
♪ I can't find a doggone soul ♪
♪ to share my company ♪
Oh, there you are, dear.
I could go for
another glass of bubbly.
Then I suggest
you find a waitress.
Well, I-I just assumed...
You assume wrong.
So why don't you go ahead
and get your own champagne?
Wow, I guess this whole
Interracial marriage thing
really is a novelty.
Well, go ahead
and let them stare.
I've got the most beautiful
woman in the room on my arm.
I couldn't agree
with you more.
Oh, hello.
Uh, thank you for inviting us.
Your home, is, um, very...
Normal.
Oh, we are just glad
that you could attend.
Let me fix you a drink.
Okay, we need to split up.
You check the back rooms,
And I'll see
what I can find up here.
Uh, you sure
that's a good idea?
Leaving you up here
by yourself
With Savage?
I'm pretty sure
he's not gonna kill me
Next to the canapés, Ray.
Go.
I'll let you know
if I need help.
♪ Fall in love with me ♪
You've been so many places.
It's like you've had
three lives.
Me, I've never left
harmony falls.
That's your first mistake.
This town sucks.
Wow, you do not hold back.
I've learned
life's too short.
So you have a girlfriend?
I just mean,
Seems pretty obvious
you're not into guys.
Uh, I, uh...
I don't know
what you're talking about.
Okay.
We don't have to talk about it
if you don't want to.
But just so you know,
I'm really good
at keeping secrets.
Funny you should say that.
I did
kiss a girl once.
I didn't think that made me a...
- You know.
- A lesbian?
What?
It's not a bad word.
Well, it is around here.
Well, good thing I'm not
from around here.
Uh, nurse lance,
May I have
a word with you, please?
Well, now I see
what's been going on.
While I've been busy working,
You were busy
seducing that young woman.
Actually, I was
liberating her.
With an option
to seduce her later.
Then what?
This poor young woman
Will have to remain in
the sexually repressive 1950s
Long after you've returned
to a timeship
And disappeared
from her life forever.
You know what, doc?
I would love for someone
To drop into my life
and tell me
That the future's gonna be
a better place.
Get to hall H!
Your husband must be a fool
To leave a woman
such as yourself
Alone at a party.
He doesn't seem like your type.
That's a rather interesting
thing to say.
You hardly know me.
And yet I feel like I do.
Let me ask you
a question, Kendra.
Do you believe in past lives?
Do you believe in fate?
Fate is a prison.
When free will is gone,
what's left?
Destiny.
Oh.
Hello.
Yeah. I understand.
Of course. I'm on my way.
Looks like we have to finish
our discussion later.
One of my patients
needs attention.
Enjoy the party.
Tommy, Tommy, Tommy.
I-I thought the two of us
Had an understanding.
I've allowed
you and your cohorts
The occasional freedom
to run free
And to feed your thirst,
and then...
Then you do something like this.
I'm sorry, Mr. Palmer.
I'm unfamiliar with
the term "man cave".
Oh, it's a room
in a basement
Where a dude goes
to be alone
Or watch football.
In Savage's case,
it's kill people.
So Ray and I break in
and find out
What Savage is doing
in harmony falls.
- Ho, ho, ho!
- Ooh.
Is tonight the
enchantment under the sea dance?
I got a date tonight
With Tommy Fuller's
cheerleader girlfriend.
Turns out Betty's boyfriend
Was one of the missing
high school kids.
I think she knows more
than she's letting on.
Mm, she's also a white girl
In a very, uh,
unenlightened community.
So please, be careful
When you're out
in public with her.
An immortal psychopath
and racists.
I'm beginning to like
this quaint little town
Less and less.
How's it going over there?
I'm in.
What do you see?
Uh...
Nothing all that hideous.
Except for a terrible collection
of golf pants.
Hang on.
Ray?
Ray, it's Savage. He's back.
Did you hear me, Ray?
You need to get out of there!
I think I found something.
No, no, no, no.
You don't have time.
He's already inside.
Don't you ever get
freaked out?
I mean, being in
an insane asylum
By yourself
In the middle of the night?
Freaked out? No.
Lonely? Yes.
Actually, there is
One place in the hospital
that scares me.
Dr. Knox's restricted wing.
Do you know what he's doing
to the patients down there?
No.
I don't like
to think about it.
What do you like
to think about?
What's wrong?
- Nothing.
- I thought you said...
I-I just...
I have to get back to work.
You look great tonight.
♪ Don't have to tell me ♪
Mm... whoa. Whoa.
- Uh...
- I'm sorry. I thought that...
No, don't be sorry.
It's just, uh,
I thought girls from 1958
moved a little bit slower.
Girls from 1958?
I mean, uh,
I think we should
get to know each other
a little bit better first.
Okay.
What do you want to know?
Those guys
back at the soda shop,
they mentioned something
about your boyfriend going AWOL?
Tommy.
What happened to him?
It's kind of a long story.
Well, I got
all the time in the world.
We were drag racing
down on route 7
with Davis and Billy
when Tommy's car
went into a ditch.
That's when they found it.
Found what?
This...
Been looking all over for you.
- Get out!
- No!
Get out of the car!
Hey, get the hell
off me, man!
Stop it!
Ah!
Get in! Get in!
Go!
Oh, come on!
Tommy?
I am not playing anymore!
Don't worry, Betty.
I'm gonna get you out of here.
Nice driving.
Hang in there.
Gideon's gonna fix you.
Who's Gideon?
Uh, a doctor, of sorts.
Okay.
You need to pull over, Jax.
Hey.
Relax.
Yeah, 'cause it's not like
I'm a black kid
in a small town
With a white girl
bleeding all over my seat.
You were driving
to beat the devil back there.
That explain why
your car looks like hell?
I need to get my friend
to a hospital.
- Friend?
- Yeah.
And there's more wounded
on lovers' lane.
Some... some kind of attack.
What were you doing
with this girl
On lovers' lane, boy?
There are kids back there
that could really use your help,
And she needs medical attention
right now.
Put your hands on the car
and spread 'em.
Listen, you can play boss hogg
all you want,
But I'm not gonna let
that girl bleed to death,
So I tell you what:
I'm gonna get back in my car,
And I'm gonna take her
to the hospital.
Gideon traced Jax's
last biosignature
To this location.
Well, it seems
you had good reason
To be concerned
for Mr. Jackson's safety.
Yeah, sucks
being right all the time.
She has suffered
several severe lacerations.
I am attempting
to cauterize the wound.
- What happened?
- I don't know.
But I'm guessing
Jax and Peggy Sue
had a pretty lousy first date.
Where is Jefferson?
There was no sign of him
in the car.
These wounds don't appear
consistent with a knife.
Correct.
I believe these lacerations
were made by talons.
It was Tommy.
Tommy Fuller,
one of the missing teenagers.
He was like a bird.
He... he was like
a bird monster.
Captain, analysis
of Miss Seaver's blood
reveals traces
of silicate minerals.
Miss Seaver, do you recall
Tommy coming into contact
with a meteor of some kind?
The car crash...
It was...
It was glowing.
She's talking about
an nth metal meteorite.
Say something
that makes sense.
It seems Mr. Fuller
has come into contact
with a meteorite
with mutagenic properties.
Try again.
Apparently,
Miss Seaver's boyfriend
has been exposed
to the same type of meteor
that Kendra
came into contact with.
Me?
Well, you and Carter.
4,000 years ago.
The meteorite which
gave you your powers
appears to be
of the same variety
that mutated Tommy Fuller.
And I'm guessing
it's not curable.
Well, I-I suppose,
if the talons
which lacerated her
left some mutagenic residue,
I could...
Yes or no?
Perhaps.
Why don't you get
to work on that, Martin?
Okay, so if Savage isn't
the one doing the killing,
What is he doing in town?
Doesn't matter.
We can take him down.
The Amon dagger.
Where did you...
Savage's house.
All right, we need
to proceed on two fronts:
Locate Jefferson and make
an all-out assault on Savage.
A full-on attack only plays
to Savage's strengths.
If we want to get him...
We need to target
his weaknesses.
Sadly, very few come to mind.
I can think of one.
Me.
He wants me, and he always has.
So if I can get
close enough to him, then...
Then he'll kill you.
Thank you for
the vote of confidence,
But I don't need
your protection.
There's no reason
to go alone.
We're part of a team
for a reason.
Yes, and the team
seems comfortable
With me doing this,
So that makes it
about you and me.
- Any updates?
- We're making progress.
In the meantime, we need
to get ready to back Kendra up.
She's going into the asylum
to meet Savage tonight.
Another opportunity
for you to see nurse Carlisle.
Yeah, and apologize.
I warned you, Ms. Lance.
Rushing a repressed woman
from the 1950s
Into the freewheeling
sexual mores
Of the 21st century...
Actually, I was the one
who freaked out.
Oh.
Ever since I got
brought back to life,
I haven't really...
Experienced much
in the way of feelings.
And then when Lindsey
kissed me...
It was like
you were being kissed
For the first time.
How romantic.
It was more like terrifying.
That's the thing
that sucks about feelings
Is, you realize how much
You can hurt someone
Or... Get hurt.
- Ah.
- Wakey, wakey.
Ah.
Do the words "police brutality"
Mean anything to you?
You think this is brutal?
You'll be begging for me
After he gets through with you.
That's enough, sheriff.
Thank you. Leave us be.
This young man and I
Have a lot to discuss.
Forgive my friend
for his ignorance.
You will learn that
I'm much more enlightened.
Well, I'll take racist
over crazy any day.
Oh, I would hardly describe
what I'm doing here as...
as "crazy".
Therapy is nothing more
Than a process
of self-discovery.
You're about to experience
an extraterrestrial power.
Shall we begin?
Shh, shh.
Ah!
What a piece of work
is man.
When I was exposed
to a meteorite,
I was blessed
with eternal life,
Immortality.
But sadly, the effect
of this meteorite
Turned out quite different.
But no less advantageous.
Doc, you have a visitor.
What a pleasant surprise.
Is it a surprise...
Or fate?
We didn't get to finish
our discussion the other night.
What of your square-jawed
husband, Raymond?
I didn't come here
to talk about my husband,
Doctor.
May I?
May I take your coat?
Make yourself comfortable.
Nurse?
Nurse, I keep hearing
voices in my head.
My wife with another man,
And it's driving me crazy.
Well, maybe you should learn
to trust your wife
A little bit more.
Orderly?
Show our new patient
to his room.
And don't hesitate
to give him a sedative
If he doesn't calm down.
Right away, nurse.
I'm sure the kid is fine.
Jefferson and I,
as you know,
Share a psychic connection,
But for some
inexplicable reason,
I can't seem to reach him.
I've grown so accustomed
to our partnership,
To suddenly be without him
is disquieting.
I know the feeling.
So have you tried
psychoanalysis before?
No.
My husband thinks it's baloney.
Oh, is that so?
Well, my specialty is
Interpreting dreams.
What do you dream, Kendra?
To be honest,
I've dreamt of you before...
And me...
Together.
Well, that's interesting.
And what do we do
in those dreams?
I'm afraid
you'll think me forward.
Oh, but you are forward.
Coming here in that dress?
Perhaps you should learn
to embrace your desires
So the two of us
can finally be together.
Did you lose something?
I was wondering how long
You could play out
this little charade.
Ah!
You show up on my doorstep,
And then my dagger
goes missing?
You must think me stupid
Not to suspect
that your powers had emerged.
Well, well, well.
An FBI agent moonlighting
at the loony bin.
I'm afraid both of you boys
Have some explaining to do
Down at the station.
Who else have you brought
to the asylum tonight?
No one. No one!
It's just me.
I hope you're better at lying
In your next life.
Oh, boy.
Just when you think
you've seen everything.
Guess those missing kids
are no longer missing.
What have you done?
Ah!
I released my test subjects.
The energy from the meteorite
has changed them.
I set out to build an army
as powerful as you.
Pity they didn't turn out
nearly as beautiful.
Oh, my God.
It's Jefferson.
Jefferson, it's... it's us!
Jax, don't make me do this.
Ah!
I'll deal with this lot.
Find Kendra now.
I can explain.
Just not now.
Perhaps it will
turn out better
in our next life, my love.
Are you okay?
It's time to go.
Not without Jefferson.
Or whatever's left of him.
Gideon was able
to help me devise
A gene therapy
that will hopefully
Restore Jefferson
and those at the asylum
To their former selves.
If genome bonding occurs,
We should know right away.
Course, we would never have had
the slightest chance
Of saving him
were it not for you.
Let's not get sentimental.
Another minute,
and things might have
Gone down very differently.
Despite your bravado,
Mr. Snart,
The actions that I witnessed
last night
Were nothing short of heroic.
It's working.
Hey.
How are our friends doing
over in hall H?
Whatever Dr. Stein
gave those creatures
Seemed to have worked.
They're back to normal.
And you?
Not sure if I'm ever
gonna get fully back to normal.
Good.
Thank you...
For rescuing me.
Well, you rescued me first,
So now we're even.
You have to go, don't you?
I get it.
Should've known better
than to fall for a ninja.
Who knows?
Maybe I'll be back one day.
And if so...
You know where to find me.
So I felt bad
about trashing your dad's.
I thought this might
make up for it.
You bought me a car?
I souped it up too.
In case of future
monster attacks.
I wish you didn't
have to go.
I don't belong here.
And neither do you.
Promise me you'll
get out of this town.
The both of you.
Tommy!
It's a great big world
out there, Betty.
And it's changing fast.
Maybe we'll catch up
down the road somewhere.
Hey.
I was just packing up.
I thought you were
back at the Waverider.
I just forgot something.
I forgot to say I'm sorry.
Look, I was wrong
to think that I could
Actually end Savage
by myself.
Whoa. Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Just slow down.
I made a mistake too.
I got so caught up
playing house
That I forgot about why
we were really here.
And you will end Savage someday.
I guess the last thing
A 4,000-year-old
demigoddess needs
Is an overprotective husband.
What she needs is a partner.
What do you say?
Partner.
Well, look
who's up and around.
Mm, yeah.
I guess I owe you an apology.
Grey told me about what happened
back at the asylum.
You had the chance to kill me,
and you didn't.
After last night, I know enough
about being a monster
To know that you're not one.
Stop.
I'm getting misty-eyed.
I just want you to know...
About what happened with Rory?
I get it.
You were protecting us.
And that doesn't
make you a murderer.
It makes you
a part of this team.
Jefferson,
you should be resting.
Aw, man, I'm...
I'm done laying around.
I just want to get
the hell out of Mayberry.
Agreed... we're still
waiting on Sara
And the two lovebirds
to get back.
Seems they've taken
quite a shine to 1958.
What on earth?
Gideon?
Not this guy again.
Captain, Chronos has breached
the starboard hatch.
How is that possible?
Clearly, he's received
some new toys
from his Time Master friends
since our last encounter.
Gideon, seal the bulkheads
from here until...
Grey, come on! Let's do this!
If we merge on the Waverider,
we could destroy
the entire ship!
Um, are you
not paying attention
To what Chronos is doing?
Fall back!
Get to the jump ship!
1958's swell and all,
But I miss the internet...
And cell phones.
Uh...
What are they doing?
- Hey.
- Hey!
Where did they go?
Better question:
Why did they leave us?
Greg, move your head.