Hi removed, capitalization issues fixed,
cleaned and corrected by Tronar
in 2166, an immortal tyrant
named Vandal Savage
conquered the world
and murdered my wife and child.
I have assembled an elite team
to hunt him throughout time
and stop his rise to power.
Unfortunately, my plan
is opposed by the body
I'd sworn my allegiance to,
the Time Masters.
In the future, my friends
may not be heroes,
but if we succeed,
they will be remembered
as legends.
Previously on
"Legends of Tomorrow"...
Hold on to something!
I want to marry you, Ray.
Tragedy or heartbreak...
that's how it always ends
if the man's not Carter.
Agh!
It's Carter!
He doesn't even
remember who he was.
Kendra,
what are you waiting for?
If I kill Savage,
his mind will be lost.
I'm so sorry, Rip.
Who are you, Gareeb?
Ramses's men inform me
that you still refuse to speak,
to reveal your name
or why you tried to kill me.
Who are you?
The man who is trying
to save the world from you.
And how are your efforts
proceeding?
You can't even stand
for lack of food and water.
I will always rise up
against you.
I will never give up.
Soon the sky rocks
will lay waste to this kingdom,
and you along with it.
This cell will be your tomb.
What do you know of the future
that I don't, Gareeb?
Mission...
Almost accomplished.
That bottle of scotch
was given to me
by Rob Roy MacGregor in 1689.
It's not half bad.
We should be toasting
to Savage's death.
Apart from celebrating murder,
Savage still has Carter
brainwashed.
I don't know if you've been
paying attention, Professor,
but murdering Savage
was always the plan.
Besides, Carter reincarnates,
which is more
than I can say about us.
As long as he's on board
and breathing,
Savage is a threat
to everyone on this ship.
So what, we just kill Savage
and leave Carter
a brainless drone?
Yes.
Sorry we're late,
but we found something.
We've been running diagnostics
on Ray's suit
after his battle with Savage's
rock 'em sock 'em robot.
The telemetry data
included a comparative scan
of the robot's tech.
Amazing.
This neuromorphic profile
is astonishingly futuristic.
Yeah, it's from 2166.
Well, that's the thing.
It's not.
This technology's light years
more advanced
than anything from 2166.
- Who cares?
- The Time Masters.
They refused to take
action against Savage
because he didn't pose
a threat to the timeline.
But if he comes
into possession
of future technology...
It means he's been engaging
in exactly the same manipulation
of time that the time council
were designed to prevent.
So now they'll finally
sign off on undoing
all the damage Savage
has done to the world.
Last time I checked,
the time council
was at the edge
of the timeline,
and this bucket of bolts
can barely hold it together
as it is.
Gideon, what's the status
of the time drive?
Stable, Captain.
Plot a course
for the vanishing point.
Tonight, Vandal Savage
faces justice for his crimes.
Quite the reversal of fortune,
isn't it, Gareeb?
4,000 years ago it was you
who was the prisoner.
Ever since I met you again,
I've always wondered
how you managed to escape.
Another time, perhaps.
For the moment,
I'm more interested in this.
The brains
to your robot super-weapon.
At least a century more advanced
than anything
to be found in 2166.
Do you have something
to ask me?
How did you obtain the ability
to travel through time?
From you.
When I saw you again in 1975,
I realized that time travel
was the only explanation.
You showed a caveman fire.
And I had almost 200 years
to figure out
how to strike the flame.
All this time,
I've been wondering
why it was so difficult
to locate you
throughout history.
Because you've been
moving through history.
Well, you'll come to learn
that this is just one
of many things
we have in common, Gareeb.
We're both doing
what we must to save the world.
Subjugating the world
to your rule is not saving it.
You would create a wasteland
and call it peace.
Do not misquote Tacitus
to me.
I knew him well.
I have lived long enough
to watch civilizations
rise and fall.
You weep for your son.
I have held dozens
of my children
as they perished from old age.
You might be a Time Master,
but I'm a master of time.
And I play a far deeper game
than you could ever hope
to comprehend.
Gideon, go to maximum
on the time drive.
Inadvisable, Captain.
When Dr. Palmer siphoned power
from the auxiliary time drive,
he reduced the ship...
Gideon!
Take us to maximum.
We need to get
to the vanishing point
as fast as possible.
- Where am I?
- Somewhere safe.
Safe as long
as those cuffs hold.
Do you know who you are?
I'm Scythian Torvil,
adjunct to Lord Savage.
And you will release me,
or I will kill you
where you stand.
Your name is Carter hall.
You used to be Prince Khufu
of the middle kingdom.
And I am...
Kendra Saunders.
Oh, you seem surprised.
You didn't think Lord Savage
would warn me of my enemies?
Let me go and I promise you
I will show mercy.
I will kill you without
making you suffer first.
Not to sound
like a six-year-old,
but are we there yet?
No, the Waverider was severely
damaged in Savage's last attack.
Yeah, I can tell by the way
she's flying.
You sure you're not
pushing her too hard?
The longer Savage
is on board the ship,
the greater the danger
to all of us.
To us, or your family?
I checked with Gideon.
Bringing Savage on board
didn't change the timeline,
and your family still dies.
The timeline is
always in flux.
Once we get
to the vanishing point,
all will be well.
Is that why you're pushing
the ship beyond its limits?
This has been my ship
for the last 13 years.
No one knows its limits
better than I do.
Not even Gideon.
The Waverider
will hold together.
I promise you.
Bollocks.
Gideon!
Time drive failure, Captain.
The mains are offline.
- What happened?
- It appears the time drive
is in need of some repair.
Uh, Miss Lance,
if you wouldn't mind going,
checking on our guest?
On it.
Mr. Jackson.
I'm going to need
your assistance
in fixing the time drive.
What if Jefferson
can't get the ship moving again?
Oh, thanks for the vote
of confidence.
No, what I mean is
if the ship can't be repaired,
we're marooned
in the time stream.
There really is no need
to worry.
The jumpship is equipped
with an auxiliary time drive,
capable of a one-time jump
back to 2016.
Which will not be necessary,
considering
you are going to fix
the Waverider.
- I'll do my best.
- That's the spirit.
You look concerned, Martin.
I'm remembering what Mr. Snart
said about Savage's presence
on this ship being a danger
to us all.
Have you spoken
with your sister Laurel lately?
How do you know so much
about us?
Oh, I've only had 191 years
to research my enemies.
Well, then you'd know
I don't scare that easily.
You should be scared...
of Captain Hunter.
His obsession
to save his family
will be the death of you all.
Thanks for the tip.
Enjoy being incarcerated.
Captain Hunter
lied to you so often,
and still you persist
in believing him.
You do know why he selected
all of you for this endeavor,
don't you?
Great bone structure?
He chose people
he could manipulate,
people that would believe
his lies.
Well, the lies
I don't believe are yours.
Do you blame him for putting
his family's lives first?
I'd tell you to go to hell,
but you'd probably
just feel at home there.
Okay, I've got eyes
on the time drive.
There seems to be
a large crack in it.
Well, if the housing's intact,
we should be all right.
I am going to need you
to re-route the power
from the secondary manifold.
Okay.
I'm on it.
Gideon, what is the level
of contamination
in the engine room?
Levels at 3% above maximum,
Captain.
We have to get him
out of there.
Don't worry.
He should be able to finish
before the radiation
has any adverse effect.
Jefferson?
Mom?
What are you doing here?
Good question.
I'm supposed to be
meeting my son at jitters.
But clearly he misses his
old job more than his mother.
I am so sorry.
I must've lost track of time.
Well, this should help.
I know it's not much,
but it belonged to your father.
At least it was going to.
I bought it for him
as a birthday present
before he passed.
It's awesome.
Thanks.
Maybe you can use it tonight.
Dinner at your grandma Louise's.
Yes.
I will be there.
And I won't be late.
I just got to stop
by the university first.
- The university?
- I got to say good-bye
to a friend
who's leaving town.
But I will be there.
6:00.
Okay.
All right, I love you.
I love you too, baby.
Jefferson?
I did it.
I got it working.
You said
he wouldn't be harmed.
It must be the surge
when he brought the time drive
back online.
Gideon?
Mr. Jackson has suffered
an extreme amount
of temporal radiation exposure.
- That sounds ominous.
- Oh, it is.
And there's nothing I can do
to reverse the side effects.
What side effects?
Mr. Jackson's
internal organs
are aging
at an accelerated rate.
The rest of his body
will soon follow.
Why are all the snacks
in the future sugar-free?
So much for progress.
You remember Alexa?
Yeah.
From the security deposit job.
What about it?
Just had a feeling
about that one,
a sixth sense
things would end badly.
And they would have,
if you hadn't
have pulled us
out of there.
So what?
I'm getting
the same feeling now.
Gideon, how effective were
Mr. Jackson's attempts
to bring the time drive
back online?
The drive's functions
have been restored,
but the entire system
will require a master reboot
before we can continue on
to the vanishing point.
Yes, please begin.
And in the meantime,
could you check the timeline
for any variations
in my family's future?
I believe Miss Lance
already told you the results.
Please.
The timeline remains
unchanged.
Were you expecting
something different?
Hope Springs eternal,
Miss Lance.
If it didn't,
I would've surrendered
to despair a long time ago.
I assume Mr. Savage
is still secure in his cell?
He wasn't exactly short
on opinions on you, though.
I'd imagine not.
Among them being
that you would sell us out
to save your family.
He's not wrong.
Mr. Jackson is currently
in the med bay
facing death due
to temporal radiation exposure.
- Wait, what?
- I sent him to fix
the time drive.
I could have gone myself.
And I'm left to wonder if...
In some way,
I did it
because of the risk.
So you sent Jax
on a suicide mission
so that you could stay alive
to save your family?
I don't know, Sara.
That's what vexes me.
You know what vexes me?
Thinking that we've thrown in
with a Captain
who cares more about himself
than he does his crew.
Kendra,
are you sure about this?
Do you remember him?
He was our son.
Aldus.
Do you really
expect me to believe that?
I expect you to remember
your feelings.
We were together.
And we were happy.
We were a family.
Kendra, stay back!
Oops.
Are you okay?
- I should've known better.
- But are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
- Stay away from him.
I'll be right back.
- Where are you going?
- To end this.
Dr. Palmer.
To what do I owe
the pleasure of this visit?
You're gonna tell me
how to free Carter's mind.
Oh, well,
all you had to do was ask.
Are you sure you want me to?
Of course I'm sure.
Because the moment
I release him,
you will lose her forever.
You don't know Kendra.
I know Chay-Ara.
And I know the man who stands
between you and your love
has stood between me and mine
for millennia.
We're actually quite alike,
you and I.
We're nothing alike.
You're insane.
But yet Chay-Ara once loved me
as she professes to love you.
Oh, you didn't know that,
did you?
I don't even think
Chay-Ara remembers,
but 4,000 years ago
I discovered that my Chay-Ara
had been reborn
but with no memory
of what had happened.
Like you murdering her
and Carter.
True.
She had no recollection of my...
my crime of passion.
And she fell in love with me,
very deeply.
And I with her.
That is perverse.
No, that is fact.
That is history.
And we were happy,
Dr. Palmer, very happy.
None of us blinded
by our cursed past
until he came.
He took her away from me.
He poisoned her against me.
He stole the happiness
that we shared, Dr. Palmer.
No.
Carter is a good man.
And you are my only enemy.
Am I?
Or am I just a man
experiencing the same things
as you are right now?
We have the same enemy.
If Carter's free,
you lose her.
But then she would hardly be
the first woman you've lost,
now, would she?
I am really gonna have to beef
up our security around here.
It was pretty easy
to bypass the system,
considering I designed it.
You like my ride?
Those are some
pretty hot wheels.
- Yeah.
- Maybe that's your new name.
How you feeling?
I'm okay.
What are you doing here?
- I came to drop off a note.
- Let me guess.
It says, "Hey, Felicity.
I hope you're well.
I'm off to travel through time
and fight an immortal bad guy."
- Is that me?
- Yeah.
- That was pretty good.
- Thank you.
So, obviously,
Oliver told you.
Don't let his broodiness
fool you.
He can be quite chatty
sometimes.
He also happened to mention
that you're going
on this suicide mission
because you think
there's nothing for you here.
You think it's
a suicide mission?
I don't think going after
Vandal Savage is a vacation.
But don't change the subject.
You have a life here, Ray.
Actually,
everybody thinks I'm dead.
Nothing puts things
in perspective
more than seeing yourself
become a ghost.
You're not a ghost.
You just need to come back
to the world.
And I will,
after we take out Savage.
I became the Atom to make
the world a better place.
And I'm pretty sure
that saving it counts.
I'm pretty sure it does too.
See you soon.
You know,
I would've stayed for you.
I do.
But who knows?
Maybe the future Mrs. Palmer
is out there somewhere
in the past,
the future,
some parallel universe.
Ah, I'm off
to save the world,
not fall in love.
"And though my soul departs
the earth,
"I count the days
till my rebirth.
"I will wait across eternity
for my love to come back
to me."
Please.
Come back.
Ray?
Ray...
Ray, stop!
Please.
Just give me
a chance to explain.
What you saw
back there, it was...
What?
Wasn't what it looked like?
You were reciting a love poem
to your brainwashed
ex-boyfriend.
I am just trying
to help Carter remember
who he really is.
Your soul mate.
Yeah, that's the part
in the conversation where you're
supposed to say,
"No, Ray, you're my soul mate."
Ray, you know
that I love you.
Ah, I know.
It's just not enough.
I can't believe I'm saying it,
but Savage was right.
Loving you is like a curse.
Oh, Ray.
You have to know,
whatever he said,
he's just trying
to get inside your head.
I know that.
But he's right.
Kendra, I-I don't think
I can do this anymore.
What are you saying?
Oh, what?
You want to end things?
Unless you can tell me
that I'll ever be anything more
than just Carter's placeholder.
Ray.
Are you certain
these results are accurate?
Jefferson's blood chemistry
is akin to that of a...
a 63-year-old man.
Actually, I don't feel
a day over 60.
- This isn't funny.
- No, and it's all Rip's fault.
I'm afraid he's also
suffering
from early-stage
osteoarthritis.
The exposure
to the temporal radiation
has led to an accelerated rate
of intracellular degeneration.
This is what happens
when Rip goes with plan B.
Plan A being taking Savage's
head in with that mace.
We're endeavoring to resolve
this without bloodshed.
And how's that working out
for you, Gandhi?
Look, there's nothing
we can do about it now.
We can talk to Hunter.
Even if Kendra
was to kill Savage,
my situation's still the same.
We're talking
about our situation, pops.
We're not waiting around
for the other shoe to drop.
You deserve better.
Alexa?
You bet your ass.
We need to talk.
We saw what you did to Jax.
And we're worried
it's just the beginning.
- The beginning of what?
- It's like I said, Rip.
As long as Savage is alive
and on this ship,
he is dangerous.
The time drive is rebooting.
We will soon be on our way.
I'm asking for
a little faith, gentlemen.
Sorry, fresh out.
I take it you and Mr. Snart
are of the same mind?
Yes.
And what of you, miss Lance?
You're the one
who said you'd sell us out
for your family.
Well, if that's
how you all feel, none of you
is obliged to continue
on this voyage with me.
As I told Martin,
the jumpship
can make a one-time voyage
back to 2016.
Are you saying it's ours?
I'm saying
that this mission
has always been
a voluntary enterprise.
And the mission
was to kill Savage.
Which doesn't seem
to be on the table anymore.
Very well.
Leave, if that's what you...
it's been a blast, Rip.
Good luck getting
to the vanishing point.
Tell your pals Chronos says,
"Kiss my ass".
What about you, Sara?
Never been one
to run from a fight.
Hi.
Impossible.
When I saw you last...
I know.
A miracle...
When I thought there were
none left to be had.
I needed to see you.
Look, I don't know how, but I'm
gonna get you out of here.
This isn't your fight anymore,
Ta-er al-Sahfer.
I'm not gonna
let you rot here.
Not when you're in here
because of me.
I am in here
because of my choices, beloved.
I made them
ready to accept my punishment.
I won't leave you in here.
If you love me, you will.
If you love me, you will leave
this place far behind,
and live a life
unburdened by your past.
It's easier said than done.
Anything worth doing
always is.
Well, finally an intellect
approximate to my own.
My imprisonment was starting
to get dreary, Professor.
I'm not here
to play mind games with you.
I'm here to ask you
if you remember a night
in October, 1975,
a place called
the Greyhill building.
That night,
you and your acolytes...
were celebrating
the acquisition
of your friend
Carter hall's body.
Yes.
It's my understanding
this ritual involved
you sharing your immortality
with your followers.
And you wish for me to do
the same for someone else.
Someone dear to you.
Your nuclear counterpart,
perhaps?
Yes.
And as impertinent
as this may sound,
I need your help.
Well, clearly, your friends
didn't give you
the full account of the ritual.
You see, it was Carter's blood
that worked the magic.
Perhaps you should talk to him.
Or better yet, Dr. Palmer.
I'm sure that he would be
more than happy
to help you spill some.
And I'm certain
you would enjoy that.
Pitting me and Raymond
against Carter, against Kendra.
Having all of us
at each other's throats
while being stranded
in the time stream.
But... We're not stranded.
Not entirely.
Thank you, Mr. Savage.
As I'd hoped, you've provided me
with a solution to my problem.
I don't get it, grey.
What's in here
that's gonna fix me?
Well, nothing
inside the jumpship, Jefferson,
but rather the craft itself.
You see, this ship
is pre-programmed
to return to 2016.
I've made
some additional adjustments
according to the theory
of quantum-retro causality,
and if my math is correct,
the trip
through the time stream
should reverse your condition.
No. No.
I'm not leaving you
or the team.
Which is why
I'm not giving you a choice.
What did you do?
I've administered
a mild sedative.
You roofied me again?
When I tricked you
onto this ship the first time,
I was only thinking of myself.
Now I'm thinking of you.
You can't do this!
If we're separated,
you'll die!
I've already lived my life,
Jefferson.
Now you must live yours.
Give my love to Clarissa.
Tell her I'm sorry.
She deserved
a proper good-bye.
Grey!
Grey, no!
No!
- Knock, knock.
- Oh, hello.
I hope you don't mind,
but I thought I'd see
if I could interest you
in a lunch date.
Oh, my darling.
I'm right in the middle
of some research
that simply cannot wait.
What's the topic?
As a matter of fact,
time itself.
The irony.
Oh!
Damn, I completely forgot.
I promised I'd meet
with some fellow academics
to help resolve
an experiment of theirs.
Does this experiment
have anything to do
with time travel?
Almost certainly.
But it won't take long.
In fact, I'll be home
before you even know it.
Clarissa?
You... you know that I love you.
There's nothing I do
that isn't driven
by that very thought.
Now let's get the hell
out of here.
- What'd you do, Poindexter?
- What do you mean?
The jumpship.
Where is it?
Well, it's really
more a question of when.
But, oh, yes.
You both wanted
to return to 2016.
Got it in one.
I did what I had to do
to save Jefferson's life.
Now we must do
whatever's necessary
to repair the Waverider
and deliver Savage
to the vanishing point.
Oh, back so soon
with the stench of defeat
written all over you.
Can't say I didn't warn you.
Trying to get under my skin?
Is that it?
Got your little game
figured out.
For all your intelligence,
you still didn't manage
to make Chay-Ara yours.
I wouldn't expect a psychopath
like you to understand.
Kendra is free to do
what she wants.
You know what I see
when I look at you?
I see weakness
masquerading as goodness.
I'm not the one
trapped in a cage.
Well, if it weren't
for this cage,
you wouldn't have
that arrogant look on your face.
You think I'm afraid of you?
No.
I know you are.
At least Carter
had the courage
to face me like a man.
No wonder she didn't
choose you.
Oh...
You feel better now,
Dr. Palmer?
Not even close.
And I thought
you were nothing like me.
I'll leave you
to contemplate on that.
Time drive reinitialization
complete, Captain.
The primary systems
are back online and stable.
Begin ignition sequence
and resume our route
to the vanishing point.
You're a fool, Professor.
I'm trying to save
Jefferson's life.
Savage has escaped.
- What?
- I'm sorry.
Pull up all the surveillance
monitors, now!
I'm afraid Vandal Savage
has already freed
Carter hall,
and is preparing
to disengage...
That can't be good.
Gideon's entire
operational matrix is offline.
And without her help...
We'll have to make our
approach the old-fashioned way.
Shouldn't we be
more worried about Savage
and his brainwashed crony?
Yes. Which is why
I need you and Dr. Palmer
to go and recapture him.
In the meantime, if the rest
of us can't figure out
how to pilot the ship
without Gideon,
we're never gonna be able
to leave the time stream.
If we live through this,
you bumbling idiot,
I might just kill you.
Exactly how old-fashioned
are you talking?
So, if the time stream
is like this vast river,
these maps plot
the safest course
along that river's path.
Exactly.
I keep these here
just in case of emergency.
Well,
this certainly qualifies.
What's Jurgens Ridge?
Pray you need never find out.
Martin, you're gonna be
our engineer.
I need you to adjust
our energy output
to avoid over-taxing
the Waverider.
And you, miss Lance,
you're gonna be our navigator.
I was league of assassins,
not NASA.
I need someone
who can make tough calls
under extreme pressure.
No one fits that description
better than you.
Come to join the party?
You should've left me
back in 2166!
Yeah, yeah,
we know that, mullethead.
Who are you to stand up
against me,
Vandal Savage,
destroyer of empires?
Leonard Snart,
robber of ATMs!
We need more power
to the time drive, Martin.
How much further
can we push it?
25%,
and only for a brief burst.
But it might be all we need.
It's still two against four.
Come on!
Aah!
What's our trajectory
looking like, miss Lance?
Just give me a second here.
Well, oddly enough,
as the vanishing point
is at the very end of time.
Yeah, and we're never gonna
make it there if you don't
lower the ship
negative 12 degrees on my mark.
Three, two, one, now!
- Did it work?
- Well, we're not dead.
I got this.
Handle Savage.
Haircut! Move your fat head
so I can get a clean shot!
They seem to be
getting closer.
- I'll go help them.
- No! I'm not gonna place
another one of you
in jeopardy... I'll go.
But who's
gonna pilot the ship?
Gareeb, I was wondering
where you were hiding.
Aah!
Bring her to me.
Chay-Ara, my love.
I'm sorry that it has to end
like this again.
- Carter.
- Aah!
I will wait for eternity.
Come back to me.
Aah!
Kendra...
He's alive.
You saved him.
You saved us all.
Is that...?
Welcome
to the vanishing point.
I can't believe we made it.
And what did you do
to your shoulder?
Hmm? Oh, I might have jumped
in front of a laser blast
intended for miss Saunders.
What?
I couldn't have my team thinking
I cared more about myself
than them, now, could I?
Really?
Uh, I think I just
lost control of the ship.
Yeah, that might have
something to do
with us being
the most wanted time criminals
in all of history.
Timeship Waverider,
we've taken control
of your guidance systems.
Disable your weapons
and prepare to be boarded.
Oh, it's good to be home.
Captain Hunter.
This is unexpected.
Well, I have a reputation
to maintain, don't I?
And I hereby request
an immediate assembly
of the time council
in accordance
with general order 52.
So you've returned
to answer for your crimes?
No. I'm here to justify them.
If this truly is good-bye,
would you mind answering
just one final question?
Well,
it seems only sporting.
How did you manage to escape
my prison all those years ago?
There were no signs of damage,
no clues to your tricks.
It left me puzzled
for centuries.
The best magic tricks
have the simplest solutions.
I bribed your guard
with a novelty pen.
Had a picture
of a woman on it.
Turn it upside down,
her top comes off.
I won it from a drunk GI
in a Philippines bar in 1944.
It's a tacky souvenir,
but in this case,
a lifesaver.
Now, unfortunate for you,
the guards
at the vanishing point
won't be quite so easily swayed.
- Hey.
Uh, I was making sure
that he was okay.
I think most guys would be
more inclined
to smother him with a pillow.
Just because he stole my girl
and tried to take over the ship?
But seriously,
Carter saved your life.
He's a part of this team.
Always has been.
I wish things
could be different.
Yeah, me too.
I need you to know
that what we had was real.
In a way,
a broken heart is
just what the doctor ordered.
- It is?
- Yeah.
When I lost Anna,
I thought that...
I could never find anybody
who I could spend
the rest of my life with.
You proved me wrong.
Thank you for showing me
that it's possible.
Rip Hunter,
on behalf of the time council,
you are hereby ordered...
Yeah, before you do that,
there's someone
I'd like you to meet.
You remember Mr. Savage?
Of course.
And we remember how you pled
for us to remove him
from the timeline once before.
Well, as the first Time Master
was so fond of saying,
that was then, this is now.
Incontrovertible proof
that Vandal Savage
has been engaged
in the manipulation of time!
Including a confession.
When I saw you again
in 1975,
I realized that time travel
was the only explanation.
You showed a caveman fire,
and I had almost 200 years
to figure out how
to strike the flame.
Impressive, Captain Hunter.
You and your team
have accomplished
what none of us here
in the time council
believed you would.
If the prisoner
would step forward...
Vandal Savage,
by the power of this chamber,
it is my duty to return you
to earth immediately.
What?
This man you've brought
before us
is needed back in 2166.
You're in league with him.
I wouldn't expect you
to understand our reasons.
For all your wisdom,
you were never able to take
the long view of history.
Take him away.
Search their ship
for the others.
- Did you hear that?
- Don't try to distract me.
We need to find
somewhere to hide.
Why do we need
to find somewhere to hide?
Alexa.
Damn.
Ah, if you're here for Savage,
you're too late.
- Mick, what's going on?
- You're under arrest.
Oh.
If I had a nickel
for every time I heard that.
Druce's men
have taken your ship.
Your friends are under arrest.
And you are once again
my prisoner.
This time,
I don't plan to lose you.
Oh, and yes, I do remember
the guard very well.
He died.
Now, if you would excuse me,
I'd better be getting back
to 2166.
I've been waiting so very long
to meet your family.
Wouldn't miss it for the world.
No! No!
No!
Greg, move your head.