Hi removed, capitalization issues fixed,
cleaned, corrected and resynced by Tronar
This season on
"Legends of Tomorrow"...
I've assembled you all
because I need your help.
The future of the world
is in peril
because of Vandal Savage.
You've turned your back
on the very institution
you were meant to serve.
The Time Masters,
they refuse
to take action
against Savage
because he didn't pose a threat
to the timeline.
The Oculus not only
gives us a window into time,
- but the ability to shape it.
- If the Oculus
is what they're using
to control us,
then we need to destroy it.
Shut it down!
There are no strings on me.
He traded his life for ours.
He was a hero.
Unfortunately, Vandal Savage
has already succeeded
in murdering
Miranda and Jonas.
Savage still has
Carter and Kendra.
This is a timeship.
A little gift
from our friends.
I no longer need
to rule the world.
I now have the ability
to change it.
What are we doing
back here?
Savage has a timeship,
courtesy of the Time Masters.
The timeline is unclear,
due to our destruction
of the Oculus, meaning
Savage is lost to history.
Which is why
I brought you all home.
- Mission's not over, man.
- Jax is right.
We've lost Savage before.
We'll find him again.
And then what?
We have no way
of killing Savage,
particularly now
that Kendra and Carter
are in his possession,
assuming that
they're still alive,
which is highly unlikely.
So that's it? We're...
we're just giving up?
I'm on my way to the refuge to
retrieve our younger selves
and return them
to the timeline.
It will be as if
you never left.
What, you think
that we can just
return to our old lives,
and then pretend
like none of this
ever happened?
Mm, that might be
a tad difficult.
So I had to bring you back to
May 2016, not January 2016.
Great, so what you're saying
is for the last five months,
my mom probably thinks
that I'm dead.
- Thanks a lot, man.
- Okay, wait, why?
Why the change of plans, Rip?
If you're getting back
on that ship,
we get back on that ship.
In truth, I never left it.
I'm sorry for all
that I've asked of you,
and that it all
came to nothing.
I wish you all well.
I never liked that guy.
Hello?
Dad.
Hey.
- Hi, Daddy.
- Baby.
- When'd you get back?
- I just got back.
I tried calling,
but nobody was answering.
I was at Laurel's,
but she wasn't there.
Where is everyone?
This, uh, Damien Darhk,
he's causing problems.
Well, good to know nothing's
changed in five months.
Dad?
What's wrong?
Is everything okay?
No, baby.
You're starting
to scare me.
Damien Darhk was in prison,
and he escaped,
and everyone tried to...
...stop him.
But your sister, honey,
she, um...
No, dad.
No.
- I'm sorry, baby.
- No, dad.
No.
I got you.
You idiot.
We're in the clear.
He was going after us.
On foot.
You shot him,
- and wasted ammo.
- Cops are coming.
You want to
yell at me some more,
or should we both
get out of here?
Neither.
Hey, Mick.
Oh, it... it's me.
It's Ray.
I-I thought
we should talk.
Drive.
Well you didn't
waste any time
getting back
to your old habits.
I like stealing stuff.
It makes me feel good.
Did you ever think
that maybe you weren't meant
to do this anymore?
What do you want, haircut?
To apologize, sort of.
For Snart.
I was the one who
was supposed to die,
- and I can't help feeling that...
- It wasn't your fault.
It was his.
Son of a bitch never did
anything without a plan.
Maybe you're right.
Maybe he wanted this.
What are you doing
with your hand?
Maybe he wanted us to,
you know,
be partners.
Think I'm going to be sick.
I think Snart knew.
He knew that
I'd keep an eye out for you,
and you'd keep
an eye out for me.
While doing what?
What we haven't
finished doing.
What was H.G. Wells'
childhood nickname?
- Bertie.
- Incredible.
You've gotten every answer
correct tonight.
Since when did you become
such a history buff?
I guess I developed
a passion for it recently.
During your sabbatical?
You hardly ever
talk about it.
Martin?
I know, I'm sorry.
My sabbatical was, um...
I left some very important
work unfinished.
Ship's not
going to be here, Gray.
We saw it take off,
remember?
Yes, and in doing so,
it would have left...
quantum signature.
That's what I've been
trying to tell Mick.
Radio beacon.
Quantum entangler.
Boring.
When do we get
in contact with Hunter?
Ms. Lance,
are you all right?
How do we get the Waverider
back here?
- Hi, daddy, we miss you.
- And love you.
- Captain,
I'm sorry to interrupt.
Tell me
you've located Savage.
No, but we have received
a transmission
from 2016 Star City.
I don't understand.
This should have worked.
Did you account
for subspace interference?
It's the first thing
I thought of.
Did you adjust
for temporal polarity?
Oh, Raymond, you insult me.
Can you reach
the Waverider or not?
We're working on it.
Actually, guys,
I think it just worked.
I thought I made my intentions
perfectly clear.
And we wish to be
equally clear about ours.
- Do you mind?
- Just checking to see
if you're real this time.
You're not
ditching us again.
When the mission's over, then we
can all go our separate ways.
And this mission
is not over.
Yeah, just curious
how much headway you've had
tracking Savage
without all of us.
None.
But neither
have I got myself
into bar fights
in 1975 and the old west,
put dwarf star technology
into the hands of terrorists,
or got myself turned into
a scary bird monster.
We get your point.
Now get ours.
That ship's not taking off
without us.
You got that?
Halt!
Oh, please don't shoot!
Don't shoot.
What the hell are you doing
out here, lady?
I was being held captive.
By Nazis?
No, worse.
- Your helmet.
- What about it?
I've seen it before.
Paper, do you have paper?
Something to write with.
Lady, I think
you're in shock.
Please!
Yeah.
So if it wasn't Nazis,
who were you running from?
I need your helmet.
Now!
I'm sorry, my love,
but this game
is not over yet.
Despite my wishes
to pursue Savage alone,
it seems that
you're all intent
on seeing this thing through
till the bitter...
Oh!
Speaking of bitter.
You knew.
You dropped us off
five months later
because you knew.
Knew what?
You knew that Laurel
was going to die,
and now you're going
to take me back,
and I'm going to
save my sister.
- I'm afraid that that...
- You should be afraid.
I can't allow you...
I don't care
about the timeline.
You're taking me back now.
Look, Sara,
I'm sure there's
a valid reason
why Rip didn't...
Stay out of this!
What the hell, Rip?
Mr. Rory, take Ms. Lance
to sleep it off.
Not to dismiss
what just happened,
but we do have to
find Savage,
assuming that Kendra and Carter
are still on his timeship.
He could...
be anywhere in time and space.
Oh, well that
narrows it down a lot.
Sorry.
Was this always over here?
No, it lives over...
- Did you put it there?
- Nah, man.
- Did you?
- Dude, it's just a helmet.
- Chronometric repositioning.
- What?
Temporal changes can,
on occasion,
reverberate
through the timeline,
physically moving an object
from one place to another.
- Gideon?
- Yes, Captain.
Plot a course
for Saint-Lô, France, 1944.
Why then?
Because that's where
Kendra is.
How is that possible?
She sent us
a message through time.
Go ahead, say it.
Astonishing.
Oh.
I brought you some company.
Oh, he might be
a little disoriented,
after the way
he came out of stasis.
- I know you.
- Oh, you remember her?
Well, his mind
isn't fully gone.
Hey!
Stay away from him!
I'm going to kill you.
You've had 4,000 years
to do so,
with no success.
What are you doing?
Your blood is the key
to unlocking
the Thanagarian technology.
- Thanagarian?
- The alien species which gave
the three of us our powers.
They sent three meteorites
containing technology
beyond human understanding.
When they are activated
by your blood,
I will be able
to erase time itself,
and travel us back
to 1700 B.C.
- No. No!
- I will begin
my immortal life anew,
only this time
I won't be content to whisper in
the ears of powerful men.
This time I will be the one
with the power.
I will be a god.
Please try very hard
not to kill me.
Rip.
Please take me back.
I need your help.
I need to save my sister.
And you know that I would
do this for you, Sara,
but I just can't.
I've never asked you
for anything.
And you of all people
should understand.
You have tried everything.
We...
We have tried everything
to save your family.
And I would not wish the pain
of that failure upon anyone.
I would rather live
with that pain than this.
And that's just the thing,
Sara.
Look, if you were able
to try to save Laurel,
then you wouldn't
be alive at all.
Then fine.
I don't care.
When we left,
when I recruited you,
we... we... we altered
the timeline.
Now had it remained the same,
then Damien Darhk would have...
He would have killed
not only you and...
and your sister,
but your father as well.
But, Rip, if... if we go back,
and we take the team...
the outcome would be
exactly the same.
You don't know that.
- I'm afraid that I do.
- No.
I...
There's got to be a way.
Rip, I have to be able
to do something.
I'm so sorry.
Look, I can't.
Can't do this
without my sister.
- I can't.
- Yes, you can.
You are one of the strongest
people I have ever met, Sara.
Laurel... Laurel may be
beyond your saving,
but Kendra and Carter,
they might not be.
Captain, we are prepared
to make the time jump to 1944.
We're on our way, Gideon.
We've arrived in Saint-Lô.
No sign of Kendra yet,
but I have located
Vandal Savage,
and he does not
seem to be alone.
Aah!
Get them!
Keep Savage
and our Nazi friends occupied.
Gideon has detected
a temporal signature
consistent with a timeship.
If Kendra and Carter
are alive,
that is where
they're going to be.
Yeah, I see it.
- Jax.
- You miss me?
Is he still nuts?
No, he's okay.
Take this to the ship.
What the hell was that?
You transmuted the molecular
properties of the rifle.
What does that even mean?
Okay, let's get out of here.
Kendra's down.
Rip, we're kind of
outnumbered here.
Fall back.
Staying here to fight Nazis
is exacerbating the damage
that we have already
done to the timeline.
- But Kendra...
- is alive,
thankfully,
and we will rescue her
in due course.
I hope.
- So this is a spaceship?
- It's a timeship,
but yes, it does also travel
through space.
You... you've seen it before,
Mr. Hall.
That used to be my name.
Carter Hall.
There really is rather a lot
to fill you in on,
and we really do not
have the time.
- What about...
- Kendra, yes,
we need your assistance
in locating her and Savage.
Perhaps we can start
with what Savage
was doing in 1944.
He said something about, um...
Thanagarian technology.
- Thanagarian...
- The Thanagarians
were a race
of extraterrestrials.
He also said
that this technology
was actually three meteors.
Captain,
I have surveillance footage
which might be relevant.
Thank you, Gideon.
I've seen that rock before.
Savage had one of those
in 1958.
He took our blood.
He said he would use it
in a ritual to erase time,
take the blood
back to 1700 B.C.
- What are you doing?
- Come on, man.
We got to try it again.
That thing that we did
in world war ii.
- It's called transmutation.
- Yeah.
It's a similar process
by which
our uniform materializes
when we merge,
but at the moment,
we need to focus
on figuring out
what Savage is planning.
Come on, just the once.
Is that Raymond and Kendra's
lucky vase?
I don't know, I just found
this junk lying around.
Oh, come on.
Don't you think that
turning something
into something else
might come in handy?
All right, one time only.
Okay, just the once.
All right.
You need to focus, Jefferson.
Why do you always say it
like I'm not focusing?
Just do
what you did before.
Ah, before we had a Nazi
trying to kill us.
This is just a vase.
Come on.
I never thought
I'd utter these words,
but I think we need a Nazi.
- Not funny.
- Look, the reason I keep
telling you to focus
is because
transmutation is a literal
function of mind over matter.
Dude, this sucks.
Why do I always got to
be in the driver's seat?
Oh, don't
despair, Jefferson.
This is only
our second attempt
at transmutation,
and, you know,
they always say,
"the third time's a charm".
What?
Third time.
Three rituals.
I-I think I know
what Savage is planning to do.
I figured out how Savage
plans to erase time.
I believe he intends to detonate
each of these meteors
in a different time period.
How can you
destroy the world
three times
in three different times?
You can't, it would create
a temporal paradox.
Which would result
in a timequake
that would return
the Earth to the point
of the first
chronothermic reaction,
ancient Egypt.
Okay, it's official.
This is the craziest
bad guy plan
in the history
of bad guy plans.
I don't think that sanity
is a yardstick
by which Vandal Savage can
be measured.
Okay, so which time periods
are we talking here?
You said Savage
was in possession
of one of these meteorites
in 1958.
That was a year
of a rare alignment,
with the Earth
and Thanagar.
Evidently he got hold of
a second meteorite in 1944.
Which would be
useless to him in a year
where Earth and Thanagar
weren't in alignment.
Now, if my math is correct,
and trust me, it is,
the next two years
that Earth and Thanagar
are in sync
are 1975 and 2021.
But Savage
still has to do this
in three different
time periods.
That's the beauty of
immortality, Jefferson: He can.
He can literally be
in three places at once.
- Can't be.
- Can.
Thanks to time travel,
and it's because of time travel
that I know you're here.
You're out here tonight,
because you have felt
an immanent presence of...
Something.
- A... a meteorite?
- And I'm going to give you
a use for it
which will give us the power
to rewrite destiny itself.
Change the course
of the entire world.
So if Savage plans on blowing
up the world three times,
- how do we stop him?
- We don't.
- We kill him.
- How?
We've always known
that only you
or Kendra could kill Savage
using items exposed,
as you were,
to the meteor's radiation.
Now,
the radiation works both ways.
It gave Savage
his immortality, but...
it also makes him
vulnerable.
And Savage
is about to unleash
the radiation
from three meteorites
in three different
time periods.
- Triple the exposure.
- Yes.
Which should be sufficient
to render Savage mortal.
And then all we got to do
is kill Savage three times.
Indeed.
Gideon can navigate
the Waverider,
and we can split
into teams of two.
One in 1958, one in 1975,
and one in 2021.
Open it.
Did you know that this is one of
the original meteorites
which fell upon
the middle kingdom?
Drawn from the ground
after a millennia,
straight into Nazi hands.
The object that has bound
the two of us together
for 4,000 years
has the power
to take us back
to where it all began.
But this time,
I will be the Pharaoh,
- and you...
- will hate you,
like I've always hated you.
Patience, Mr. Hall.
All our teams need to act
simultaneously.
I think that's a comet
or something.
It's a meteorite,
in point of fact.
I was drawn to it as well.
- When can I kill him?
- We have to wait
- for the meteor to go critical.
- When's that?
When he starts the ritual
in all three time periods.
Um, we got
a nuclear bomb, here.
Professor, Jax,
we need you.
Oh, man, I forgot how much
of a badass I was.
Look.
What do you mean
you don't have the money?
I was going to sell
a nuclear warhead
and pay you
out of the profit.
Things changed.
You expect me
to just hand
the meteor over for free?
No, I expected
to take it from you by force.
Ah.
Well...
I think that's our cue.
Really?
These guys again?
Now.
Keep them occupied.
You ready to show
these fools
what's really good?
You have no idea.
Glad we're past the point
of worrying about the timeline.
Carter!
Aah!
Ah.
Oh, you're too late.
Time master's never late.
Rip!
Aah!
You can't kill me.
I'm immortal.
Guess you haven't
heard the news.
Good-bye,
my love.
Aah!
Oh!
Ah, you can feel it,
can't you?
Things are different
this time.
- You're mortal.
- But yet, my death
does not save the lives
of your family.
I may die, but you'll live
knowing that you failed
to save the lives of...
aah!
Never speak
their names again.
Do something, Robocop.
I'm on it.
Got a little trick
I've been working on.
Ooh.
It's up to you now,
Jefferson.
Gray, listen.
If we're going to do this,
we got to do it together.
It's going to take
the two of us, all right?
- You're right.
- Okay.
Come on, Gray!
Oh, man.
You got my boots wet.
Jefferson, you did it!
We did it, man.
Gideon,
take us back to Rip.
Damn it!
I wanted to be
the one to kill him.
Again, I mean.
Um...
I don't think
our problems are over yet.
I'm on it.
On what?
It's not working.
The radiation buildup
is too progressive.
I got this.
I don't understand.
I must be all out of power.
What happens if only one of
these goes off?
Uh...
Time will remain intact.
The world?
Not so much.
Okay, guys, let's fly
this thing out of here.
To where?
We would never
get it far enough away.
Maybe the Waverider can.
Rip, we need...
Rip?
Rip!
What are you doing?
I'm flying the Waverider
into the sun,
- with the meteor on board.
- And you on it.
I guess this is good-bye.
It's been a pleasure,
Captain.
Likewise, Dr. Palmer.
But you brought us
all into this, man.
Which is why I'm doing this
alone, Mr. Jackson.
I'll have no one else
die for my choices.
This isn't going
to bring Snart back.
I don't want to lose
another friend.
I appreciate that,
Mr. Rory.
I must say, it's been an honor
to serve as your cap...
Rip.
Daddy?
Miranda.
I...
Where...
I'm still here, Captain.
I know you are, Gideon.
May I share something
with you?
I'm not ready to die.
Me neither.
Which reminds me...
Is our solar ray
still functional?
In fact, it's operating
at an efficiency rate
of 12,000%.
Transfer all available power
to the time drive.
Get ready
to eject the meteor,
and pray that we have enough
power for one
last jump.
What happens if only one of
these goes off?
Our time
will remain intact.
The world, not so much.
Okay, guys, let's fly
this thing out of here.
To where?
We'd never get it far enough away.
Maybe the Waverider can.
Rip, we need...
where's Rip?
And the meteorite?
Will somebody please tell me
what just happened?
Rip?
Sorry if I gave you all
a fright.
What happened
to the meteor?
Uh, I flew it into
the heart of the sun.
Well, I angled the ship
to eject the meteorite
before impact,
and then, uh...
Time jumped away.
- You could have been killed.
- Should have been.
You're a moron.
Now, who fancies
a return trip to 2016?
- I can't believe it's over.
- Well, for some of you, yes.
My journey, it seems,
is only just beginning.
How does that work?
Savage is three times dead.
The Time Masters are no longer
of growing concern,
due to our destruction
of the Oculus.
Someone needs to be responsible
for protecting the timeline.
Who better than
a former Time Master?
And any of you
who'd like to join me.
I should stay
and help you with Darhk.
And get justice for Laurel.
That's happening, honey,
with or with out you.
I promise.
Uh, listen,
I-i can't pretend
to understand this
time travel thing,
but it sounds important.
So is family.
I wasn't going to go
the first time.
Then Laurel convinced me.
And now I'm going
to do this for her.
Well, she'd be proud of you.
How do you know?
'Cause I am.
What German lone word
literally means
- "the desire to hike"?
- Wanderlust.
A word which could
also be used
to describe that look
in your eye.
- What look in my eye?
- Martin, we've been married
for 28 years,
and you're still
a lousy liar.
Now about
this new sabbatical.
I decided to decline
the invitation.
But... I think you should.
I-I think... I think
it's important...
Clarissa,
I'm not leaving you.
That's final.
- Hey, Gray.
- What are you...
I'm so glad
that you could make it, Jax.
What are you up to?
Well,
we had a nice, long talk
- this afternoon, didn't we?
- Yeah.
Oh, my god,
this is an intervention!
Yeah, you could
kind of call it that.
Listen, Gray,
you're meant for more
than sitting around answering
trivia questions about history.
Me, you, Firestorm.
We're made for
changing history.
- This is my life.
- And your life
will be waiting for you
when you get back.
You really want me
to do this?
I could never forgive myself
if I kept you from it,
my husband the superhero.
Why are you
looking at me like that?
Wasn't sure you'd make it.
You left me a message,
I came.
What of it?
I just wanted to talk.
You and I,
we've done a lot of thieving,
a lot of cool stuff,
a lot of fun.
Anyway, I, uh...
I just wanted to make sure
I said something important
that wasn't left unsaid.
Mick, I don't do
touchy-feely.
If you got something to say,
say it.
This wasn't a good idea.
You're the best guy
I ever knew.
You may not think
you're a hero,
but you're a hero to me.
You got that?
Yeah, I got it.
See you around.
You okay?
Fine.
- So did you tell him?
- That he killed himself
to save our destinies?
If it's any consolation,
I can always bring you back
to this particular time
and place.
I'm fine.
Just let it be.
A full compliment.
To be honest,
I had my doubts
that all of you
would be willing
to throw in with me
for a second go.
- Well, actually...
- we're not coming with you.
With Savage gone,
we want to start fresh,
see what happens.
I give it three months, tops.
Look, I just...
I want to say thank you.
To all of you.
- Ray, I...
- No.
This is...
it's meant to be.
I wish both of you
nothing but the best.
Be safe.
See you guys around.
Every time they do that,
I get hungry for chicken.
So, shall we?
- Is that...
- The Waverider.
Another Waverider?
Whatever it is,
it's not slowing down.
Get down!
What the hell's going on?
To be honest, Mr. Jackson,
I have absolutely no idea.
Is this 2016?
Is this may, 2016?
Yeah.
You're exactly where
you said you'd be.
Do not get on that ship.
If you do, you're all dead.
Says who?
Says you, Mr. Rory.
You sent me.
I'm sorry.
Who exactly are you?
My name is Rex Tyler.
I'm a member of the
Justice Society of America.
Greg, move your head.