Hi removed, capitalization issues fixed,
cleaned and corrected by Tronar
in 2166, an immortal tyrant
named Vandal Savage
conquered the world
and murdered my wife and child.
I have assembled an elite team
to hunt him throughout time
and stop his rise to power.
Unfortunately, my plan
is opposed by the body
I’d sworn my allegiance to,
the Time Masters.
In the future, my friends
may not be heroes,
but if we succeed,
they will be remembered
as legends.
Previously
on "Legends of Tomorrow"...
The flashes
I've been having...
They're of Carter.
It must be really weird
feeling like you're
cheating on me with him.
No, Ray,
I feel like I'm cheating on him
with you.
We need to move swiftly
to locate Vandal Savage.
There is one place in time
that we know Savage to be.
2166.
We have, quite literally,
run out of time.
Oh!
We're gonna need to find
a safe place to set down,
Gideon.
I don't believe there are
any safe places, Captain.
Are we over London yet?
- What's left of it.
- Why's London shooting at us?
It's Savage's forces
that are doing the shooting.
Here in 2166, they've subjugated
most of the globe.
Maybe picking up here
wasn't the brightest idea.
Unfortunately,
we no longer have the luxury
of blindly searching
for Savage throughout history.
Indeed;
We have to target Savage
at the time and place that we're
certain he will be, which is...
Right before
he wastes your family.
What?
Yes, Mr. Rory,
Savage will kill my wife and son
in three days' time, but we can
save them and the world
by stopping Savage now.
Captain, I've managed to slip
beneath their artillery fire.
Set us down on the outskirts
of the city, Gideon,
near the encampment of the
remaining resistance forces.
We are going to need
to proceed swiftly.
I realize your family
is in jeopardy,
but perhaps some deliberation...
We really don't have the time,
Martin.
According to Gideon,
Savage is going to be
out in the open tonight...
Vulnerable.
Now, in order to capture him,
I require the services of...
A killer, klepto, and pyro?
Bingo.
Here we stand
at the edge of history.
But as tempting as it might be
to celebrate
our previous victories,
it is only for the next
and final battle
that you will be remembered.
There's no way
we can grab him here.
Not with an army
standing between us.
Shh, I'm trying
to listen to this guy.
He gives a hell of a speech.
Onward to victory!
Onward to immortality!
Present arms!
Quick time. Move!
All set on our end.
Jax is in the jumpship,
ready to extract you guys.
Especially if...
And by if, I mean when...
This thing goes south.
Savage's lady friend
just made us.
Have faith, Mr. Snart.
Gideon, push in on the woman.
That bracelet she's wearing...
Can you get a clearer image?
Oh, my god.
If we don't move real soon,
we could get ourselves killed.
How about we play this
like Chicago?
Could work.
Ugh!
What the hell
did you do that for?
We'll take Savage.
You tie up the guards.
Sara,
the woman you're fighting...
You need to take her bracelet.
Are you seriously
jewelry shopping right now?
We're outnumbered.
Fall back!
Mr. Jackson,
now would be a good time
to pick us up.
What exactly do you think
you were doing back there?
Distracting Savage's pals,
which worked, by the way.
Yes, well,
I could've been killed.
Never said
it worked perfectly.
At least it wasn't
a complete bust.
We found out
about Kendra's bracelet.
What bracelet?
My bracelet... I was wearing it
the night of my first death.
That's great.
Not the death part.
That's terrible.
But you told us
that objects
present on the night
of your death
can be used to kill Savage.
You're my fiancé.
I listen to you.
And that's sweet,
but there's still
one small problem.
It's a bracelet; How are you
supposed to kill Savage with it?
A question we will answer
the moment we have obtained it.
We need our resident
kleptomaniacs
to steal that bracelet.
Captain,
I've detected movement
300 meters southwest
of our position and closing.
- Savage's army?
- Negative.
I believe they are
all that remains
of the resistance forces.
I'm going to make contact
with them.
They might have
information on Savage
that we can use
to our advantage.
In the meantime, Ms. Lance,
get Ms. Saunders ready.
Ray.
How am I supposed
to teach someone to fight
with a piece of jewelry?
Good question.
It wasn't rhetorical.
Thank you, gentlemen,
for accompanying me
on this excursion.
Oh, no problem.
I just love hiking
through the woods
in the middle
of World War III.
What if,
instead of encountering
these resistance fighters,
we meet up with more
of Savage's forces?
Why else do you think
I brought along
Firestorm and the Atom?
Give me one good reason
why we shouldn't
blow you straight to hell.
Better yet, give her
several good reasons.
My wife and son
live in whitechapel.
- It was hit hard.
- I know.
The same fate will befall you
if you don't accept our help.
How do we know
you're not with Savage?
Because if we were,
you'd be dead right now.
Look, feel free to shoot us,
but from the looks of it,
you could use all the allies
you can get.
Whitechapel fell 11 days ago.
We have a lot of refugees.
You think your wife and son
are among them?
Sadly, I'm confident
that they're not.
Still, we would like to help
in whatever way we can.
Very well;
Get yourselves acclimated,
and I'll rejoin you shortly.
Hey.
Uh, I would've brought more,
but...
Jefferson.
Jefferson, let's...
Let's return to the ship,
and we'll bring back
those additional provisions.
Don't worry.
There's plenty more
where that came from.
We'll be back.
So what did you mean
back there,
about your family?
I'd rather not discuss it.
Yeah, I picked up on that.
I also picked up on the fact
that we're in London
just a few days before Savage
tries to kill your wife and son,
and you're not trying
to get them to safety.
After my first attempt
on Savage in ancient Egypt,
my very next stop
was here in 2166.
I found Miranda and Jonas
exactly where I'd left them,
and we... we raced
towards the Waverider,
but we had a run-in
with Savage's shocktroopers.
Miranda and Jonas
were cut down.
So I jumped even further back,
and the outcome
was exactly the same.
I watched my family die
countless times
at the hands of Savage
and his forces
before I realized that...
Time wants to happen.
Funny feeling knowing
that the universe itself
doesn't want you
to save your family.
All right,
what are you all playing at?
I retina-scanned
the four of you.
There's no record of you
anywhere,
and you and your friends
disappeared 150 years ago.
Believe me when I tell you
it would take
about that much time
for us to tell the whole story.
But the most important thing
is that we get as close
to Vandal Savage as possible.
No one gets close to Savage,
especially not now.
Some idiots made an attempt
on his life earlier tonight.
He's gone to ground
in the citadel's bunker
and he's holed up
good and tight.
Delta camp is under attack.
Taking heavy fire.
We need air support.
Where's delta camp?
Establish a perimeter!
Once it's secure,
we'll search for survivors.
Last week, Savage's forces
laid waste to Tokyo.
London is the last patch
of free ground on the planet.
Savage's armies have cut down
the most formidable militaries
in the world.
What do you men think you can do
against an evil like this?
There were no survivors
from the attack.
No, whatever weapon
Savage used against the rebels
was quite effective.
Maybe Professor Stein and I
should survey the wreckage,
analyze some soil samples,
determine what kind of weaponry
Savage is using.
Until we figure out a way
to thwart his firepower,
the rebels are
as good as dead.
But remember
why we're here:
To stop Savage,
not to slow him down.
Do we have a plan
for stealing this bracelet?
We're on it.
Please don't tell me
the plan
is to walk
into Savage's citadel
and steal it off her wrist.
All right,
I won't tell you that.
well, we still have the issue
of how to turn a piece
of jewelry into a lethal weapon.
Perhaps there is reference
to the bracelet
in Professor Boardman's diary.
I doubt it.
I've read through my son's
research a thousand times.
Savage has
a devastating weapon
at his command, and here now,
at the eleventh hour,
we could sorely use
a weapon of our own.
I'll look into it.
This is such a waste of time.
I've already looked through
every single page
of Aldus' notebooks.
If he had written something
specific about the bracelet
and killing Savage,
I would have known it already.
Here it is.
You ever think about him?
Carter?
I try not to.
It's not like
I'll ever see him again.
Not in this lifetime, anyway.
Besides, Carter is my past.
Ray is my future.
Still,
4,000-year-long relationship...
Seems like it'd be
hard to get over.
Yeah.
Maybe once Savage is gone,
I can finally start to.
Wow.
What's the occasion?
- I'll give you one guess.
- Our anniversary?
Look, I'm sorry,
but in my defense,
there's quite a few of them
to remember.
We were only married in...
Eight lifetimes.
That's a lot.
But I do remember
your Victorian England
incarnation
being particularly tough
to be pinned down.
Why are you
handing this to me?
Well,
it's an anniversary gift.
Oh.
You have got to stop giving me
weapons as presents.
I think it's time
you learn how to use it.
But it's your weapon.
Savage has murdered us
countless times,
and we aren't always
lucky enough to die together.
This is awfully depressing
talk for our anniversary,
don't you think?
Kendra, this is important.
I need to know
that if I go first,
you have everything you need
to face him.
I don't want to think
about facing Savage...
or life... without you.
You'll never be without me,
no matter what.
I'll always be near.
Just give it a try.
Who's to say
I'll ever be strong enough
to kill Savage by myself?
Just trust me.
You have everything you need.
What is it?
I think I know what we can use
to kill Savage.
Savage has warned you all
about the radicals
who oppose us.
They will not show you the mercy
I just did.
Dismissed.
I said you're dismissed.
Oh, we thought you said
"missed".
Whoever you are,
you're certainly persistent.
Not really.
We just like
bright, sparkly objects,
like that bracelet.
You'd risk dying
for a bauble?
It works with my outfit.
What now, Mr. Snart?
How do you know my name?
There I was, thinking
we could go a whole week
without kidnapping anyone.
I think you'll find
it would have been better
to simply kill me.
I agree.
It's a little more complicated
than that.
She knew who I was.
I know who all of you are.
It's a pleasure to meet you,
Gareeb.
I see Savage has been rather
chatty with his Lieutenants.
If you think I am
merely Savage's soldier,
you're more idiotic
than he claimed.
I'm not his Lieutenant.
I'm his daughter.
Vandal Savage
has a daughter?
Apparently it's true.
There's a lid for every pot.
And this lid is gonna be
very upset when he finds out
that we took his pot.
You know what I mean.
So what's the problem?
It's not like we're on Savage's
Christmas card list.
And we snagged the bracelet.
You're welcome, by the way.
We need to weaponize
that thing before Savage knows
that it and his daughter
are missing.
Actually, I think
I've got that figured out.
But I'm gonna need you
to burn something for me.
About time.
We also need to figure out
what we're going to do
with our new guest.
She's seen us and the ship.
If she runs back to Savage,
we're giving him
a huge advantage.
So we make her our advantage.
We send papa Savage a finger.
And we keep sending them
till he puts his own head
on the chopping block.
That is a positively
lurid idea.
I know we're in the midst
of a war,
but can't we maintain our honor?
I'd rather maintain my life,
Professor.
If she is Savage's daughter,
then she would know
the details of his defenses.
Yes, well, how exactly
are we going to get
those details out of her?
I'm on it.
Hello, Cassie.
May I call you Cassie?
Here's the deal.
You have information.
I want it.
The question is,
how am I gonna get it?
I'm the daughter
of Vandal Savage,
the immortal ruler
of the world.
Do you think he hasn't
prepared me for this?
Do you think I haven't
already been taught
to endure the
most extreme suffering?
You know, your father
sounds a lot like mine.
Could never really say,
"I love you",
except with his fists.
Our fathers
are nothing alike,
Mr. Snart.
14 years ago, the world
was ruled by a madman,
Per Degaton.
He unleashed
the Armageddon virus
in order to conquer the globe.
It tore through the world
like a fire.
Millions died,
including my mother.
There were riots, wars.
Hell on Earth.
No one dared to stand up
to Degaton,
except for my father.
He may not be a kind man,
but he is
the only one capable
of putting this world
back together.
So you can torture me
if you like.
My suffering's
a small price to pay.
Who said anything
about torture?
You sure you can do this?
Bash Savage's skull
with Carter's mace?
You got a better plan?
It's not the weapon
I'm worried about.
Thousands of years
of reincarnation,
and I'm guessing you've killed
a grand total of nobody.
Yet here you are, entering
into the Olympics of murder.
What's your point?
You sure you can
look Savage in the eye
and kill him?
- I'm sure.
- Well, you better be.
Otherwise, you're gonna end up
like the last guy
who swung that thing.
Savage's superweapon
isn't an explosive.
The exact conclusion
I've just come to
after examining soil samples
from the attack site.
How did you determine it?
Gideon... she found
a defunct spy satellite.
Look at the photos here.
This is the camp.
And here is the camp,
destroyed.
Look at the impact craters.
Sort of squint your eyes.
What do they look like?
What am I supposed
to be seeing?
Oh, my god.
Those are not
impact craters.
They're footprints.
Sir, we've located
the rebels responsible
for your daughter's abduction.
The leviathan is two clicks
from their encampment.
Find my daughter.
And burn them all.
He's coming for me.
Yeah, you and a bunch
of innocent refugees.
If they were innocent,
they wouldn't have rebelled
against my father.
Whatever it is,
it's getting closer.
Well, we're a little short
on weapons.
Look, if we can't outrun it,
we'll just have to fight it.
Well, I mean, we can...
But what about them?
This way.
Move along.
Everything's all right.
Everything's fine.
What the hell
do you think you're doing?
Saving a township,
by the looks of it.
Since when did my vessel
become a life raft?
Since I decided we can't
leave these people here
to be slaughtered.
You recruited us
to save the world.
That includes everyone here.
Gideon, power the engines
and get us into the air
the moment the last refugee
is aboard.
And get the weapons system
online.
What's happening?
It would seem Savage has
come back for his baby girl.
The last of the refugees
are aboard, Captain.
Strap yourself in.
Gideon, external floodlights
to maximum.
- That's...
- Incredible.
Ugh! Fire! Now!
Hold on to something!
Fire, Gideon! Fire everything!
Now might be a good time
to start praying.
- Gideon, what's our status?
- I'm gonna go with "lousy".
Shut down all essential
systems so Savage's robot...
Too late, Captain;
Apparently, it has determined
you are still alive,
because it is closing in
on our location.
What happened?
We seem to have encountered
Savage's megaweapon.
And he kicked our ass.
Gideon, how much time
do we have?
I estimate the robot
should reach our location
within the hour.
Our propulsion engine was
severely damaged in the crash
and is no longer functioning.
So where does that leave us?
All right, our only option
is to take the jumpship
and try and outrun it.
The jumpship seats seven.
The cargo bay's filled
with refugees.
I'm well aware.
Well, we can't
just leave them there; We...
Martin!
Professor, you are gonna be
just fine.
I promise you.
Grey, what happened?
You have to take care
of them.
Don't worry.
We got the team's back.
No. The people.
Those children.
You can't leave them here.
You can't... you can't...
I’ve administered
a mild sedative.
He should be comfortable.
Which is more than can be said
for the rest of us.
I was wrong.
Your dad's a gem.
He's just doing what he must
to save his daughter.
Whatever you say.
Now, where was I?
Oh, right.
Convincing you to help us.
What a charming euphemism
for interrogation.
I know what you're thinking:
"My dad may not be perfect,
but deep down,
he's not a bad guy."
What are you doing?
Showing you that when it comes
to crap fathers,
there is no "deep down".
After you.
These are the ones
we could save.
The rest are ash,
much like delta camp.
You don't know
my father at all
if you think his daughter
could be so easily manipulated.
Just trying to show you
the truth.
The truth is, my father
was trying to save me.
From what, untrained civilians
with barely any weapons?
Your father sent
a 200-foot robot
to level a bunch of tents.
The people in that camp
were rebels, dangerous radicals.
Please.
Do these people look
like radicals to you?
They're nobodies...
Everyday folk hoping to survive
your father's reign of terror.
Look, took me a long time to
accept my old man was a monster.
I'm betting you're smarter
than I am.
At last,
something we agree on.
Oh, Per Degaton didn't release
the Armageddon virus.
That was your father.
Impossible.
He was only
Per Degaton's tutor.
One, Per Degaton was
only a teenager at the time.
Two, he was hardly
a criminal mastermind.
Your father, however...
What makes you think I'd
believe anything you tell me?
Because seeing is believing.
Gideon, show her the footage.
Kasnia, November 3, 2147.
The world's population
is unsustainable
at current levels.
The herd must be thinned.
This isn't true.
You're a liar.
Correct.
But not about this.
And you know it...
Deep down.
How are repairs coming?
Are repairs coming?
Not in 30 minutes,
which is about
as much time as we have.
We brought all those people
on board,
and all we've bought them
is an extra few minutes
to live in fear.
Well, I guess the question is,
what do we do
with those minutes?
The ship is crippled!
Everyone aboard
is as dead as my...
Family?
Look, I know that you think
the universe wants them dead,
but I don't;
I don't believe in fate.
I believe in choices.
And we can choose...
We can choose to fight,
even if the fight
may be futile.
We can save your family, Rip.
It's not impossible.
All we have to do...
Is kill Vandal Savage...
The chances of which
appear to be fading.
Not anymore.
I figured out how to do it.
And my new bestie and I
can get us in.
And I think I've got a way
to stop the giant robot
that's coming to kill us.
Now, you may not believe
in fate, Raymond,
but I certainly do.
And perhaps it was fate
that compelled me
to bring you seven together
so we can change this future
once and for all.
- Hey.
So I'm going to take on
an immortal madman,
and you are fighting
a giant robot.
I can't believe
this is our life.
Well, take him out,
and it won't be.
You can do this.
- Ray, if anything...
- No, no.
Save it for after
you destroy Savage.
Sounds like
it's getting closer.
How's it going back there?
You tell me.
This is your nutso idea.
It's not that nutso
when you consider
the theoretical possibility
that siphoning power
from the auxiliary time drive
should provide enough power
to reverse the polarity
of the dwarf star matrix.
Sorry, Ray, I'm falling asleep
back here, man.
Okay. I think we're done.
All right.
You know,
if this doesn't work...
I'll turn every cell
in my body inside out?
I was gonna go with "die",
but yeah.
You know, we could've escaped
on the jumpship,
but we're doing this
to save everybody
that we brought
on the Waverider.
You're the real hero here, Ray.
All right.
Stand back.
No. Like, way back.
All right.
Here we go.
It worked. I'm not dead.
Yet.
Okay, let's do this.
Okay. Come on.
Ray, you got this.
The leviathan
is encountering resistance.
Impossible.
Dr. Palmer.
Clever.
Sir?
What?
I've been so worried.
How did you...
I am your daughter.
Did you really think some
rabble could hold me captive?
Rabble?
These are the time travelers
I warned you of.
Father?
Your bracelet.
It's gone.
I-I must have lost it
in my escape.
Ah.
As the person who tutored you
in the art of deceit,
you cannot fool me,
Cassandra.
Like you fooled me?
You told me my mother died
from the Armageddon virus.
But you were the one
who released it.
Tell me it isn't true.
I might even pretend
to believe you.
Let me go.
Call them.
Call the ones
that you no doubt helped
gain access to my bunker.
No need to trouble yourself,
Miss Savage.
We're already here.
Oh, I admire your command
of irony, Gareeb...
Using my own child against me.
Sorry to say
it didn't take much.
None at all, you ass.
They showed me the truth
of what you've done.
The innocent...
Do not speak
as if you know anything
about ruling a people.
Do you really want
to align your fate
with these... pretenders?
They're nothing
but grains of sand
in the desert of time.
You are a monster.
Don't just wrestle with him.
Remember,
you got laser blasters.
Actually,
they're compressed light beams.
Well, whatever they're called,
just hit him with them.
Oh, come on!
Yeah!
She's here.
I can sense her.
You do realize
that she can do me no harm?
Clearly,
you didn't get the memo.
Aah!
Agh!
Ha! I could
really get used to this.
Stay on him, Ray.
Stay on him.
Agh!
I had it covered.
Sure, you did.
Get up, Ray!
Ray, get up!
This is for Carter.
Unh!
Your love...
Reincarnated.
He doesn't even remember
who he was...
And he never will.
What?
When I first discovered him,
when I found out that he had
no idea about his real identity,
I took my precautions
and I locked his mind away.
You brainwashed him!
Come on!
Strike me down.
Kill me.
But do so knowing
that I am the only one
holding the key to his mind.
Get up, Ray.
Get up.
Rip said you told him
you don't believe in fate...
Just choices.
Well, you got
a choice to make right now.
You got to choose
to get up and fight.
You got to choose to live.
Whoo! Come on!
That's what I'm talking about,
baby!
Ha-ha!
Kendra,
what are you waiting for?
Finish him!
Destroy me,
and you doom him.
It's Carter.
The reinforcements
are coming!
Whatever you plan on doing,
Kendra, do it!
If I kill Savage,
his mind will be lost.
And if you don't,
I will lose my wife and son.
Well, my love,
what's it gonna be, huh?
Come on!
Ugh!
I can't.
I'm so sorry, Rip. I can't.
We need to get them
back to the ship.
Both of them.
You! What's to keep me from
killing you where you stand?
Because she's an asset
to the cause.
My father may be
incapacitated,
but his forces
are still strong.
I know their tactics,
their weaknesses.
Why the change of heart?
Ask him.
Hey. I saw Sara.
She said you brought Savage
back onto the ship,
but she was a little stingy
on the details.
Is everything okay?
Ray,
we need to talk.
Welcome back.
Ah.
Well, the team managed
to capture Savage,
battle his army
and a giant robot...
And you managed to sleep
through all of it.
Hmm.
The refugees...
They're safe.
Every one of them
is alive and well.
But for how long?
Apparently,
time wants to happen.
Oh, I think you'll find
that time...
For once...
Is on our side.
Now,
if you'll excuse me,
I have to pay a visit
to an old friend.
Well, you seem quite happy
for a man behind bars.
Why shouldn't I be happy?
It seems that you once again
have failed to kill me.
A momentary setback,
I assure you.
Assure yourself.
Providence has allowed me
to place Chay-Ara
in an impossible situation:
A choice between
her own soul mate, Carter...
And yours.
You know, a friend recently
suggested to me
that there is no such thing
as fate.
Destiny is nothing more
than the sum of our own choices.
I see.
So you still think
there's hope, then...
For your family.
Time will tell, Captain.
Time will tell.