HI removed, capitalization issues fixed,
cleaned and corrected by Tronar
In 2166 an immortal tyrant
named Vandal Savage
conquered the world
and murdered my wife and child.
I have assembled an elite team
to hunt him throughout time
and stop his rise to power.
Unfortunately, my plan
is opposed by the body
I'd sworn my allegiance to,
the Time Masters.
In the future,
my friends may not be heroes,
but if we succeed,
they will be remembered
as legends.
Previously on
"Legends of Tomorrow..."
Two years.
You left us stranded in 1958.
I was happy with the life
we built together,
the one I thought
would be our future.
Chronos attacked us.
He sabotaged the ship
and took Snart.
If you're gonna kill,
you could at least tell me
what's going on.
The Time Masters,
they took me to a place
called the vanishing point.
I've spent lifetimes training
by them, being reborn.
Don't kill him.
The Time Masters
took one of our own
and turned him against us.
I say we undo their handiwork.
I trust that
you're comfortable, Mr. Rory.
Or do you answer to Chronos
these days?
I don't take orders from you.
I can't believe I ever did.
Well, that's debatable.
I'm calling on you
for two reasons.
First, we could use your help.
What's the second reason?
We're headed to 2147
to engage Savage.
Is that the second reason
or the first?
Ah, forget it.
I owe you an apology,
Mr. Rory.
I failed you.
I brought you along
on this mission
under false pretenses,
in denial of your true nature.
And when that nature
took its course,
I asked Mr. Snart to...
deal with you.
My point being,
your quarrel should be with me
and not with him.
Well,
if it makes you feel any better,
I want to kill both of you.
Captain,
we've arrived at 2147.
Thank you, Gideon.
Set a course
for the Kasnian Conglomerate.
150 years in the future and
people are still wearing wool?
Man, I hate wool.
Be grateful, Mr. Jackson.
Those living outside
the Kasnian Conglomerate
are dressed in rags.
Conglomerate?
Yes, in the year 2080,
government began to give way
to corporations.
More like 2008.
According to Gideon,
in two hours time,
our favorite immortal psychopath
is scheduled to attend a meeting
of the Conglomerate's
share holders.
Ooh, sounds exciting.
You think Savage takes over
the world by trading stocks?
What we do know is,
in 20 years time,
Kasnia is the foothold
from which Savage
takes over the world,
so we hardly want
to take him on there,
but if we can figure out
how his actions here lead
to his rise to power,
then we won't need to.
Copy that, Captain,
but if we're gonna be
checking out the future...
We should probably
invite the nerd twins.
You know,
I can already hear
what Stan's gonna say
about 2147.
The future, it's...
- fascinating.
- Astonishing.
Well, it was a 50-50 chance
which one he'd choose.
Actually I was going to say,
"remarkable."
Isn't it?
2147 was considered
the world's zenith.
All of these people
have five good years
to look forward to.
Before what?
Before a ruthless dictator
named Per Degaton
comes to power,
releases the Armageddon virus,
and most of them end up dead.
Well, that's depressing.
Whoa.
Is that my suit?
That's my suit.
Aah!
You have been identified as
violating ordinance 12.
That is how
Per Degaton's father Tor
maintains order in Kasnia.
Doesn't look like progress
to me.
Speaking of progress, we need
to get a better lay of the land.
And I need to get
a better look at how
they made
my suit autonomous.
Well, why don't you take
Martin and Jax with you?
Ms. Lance, Mr. Snart, and I
will work on locating Savage.
Tor Degaton
holds daily meetings
with his board of directors.
And it's open to the public?
'Course not.
Just Kasnia's shareholders.
I hate to break it to you,
but we're not shareholders.
I'm more of a hard asset man,
myself.
You're clear to attend.
They'll have to wait outside.
Oh, no, this is my accountant,
and she is
my personal assist... bodyguard.
Stockholders only.
We've been through this.
I won't put the resolution
to a vote.
Sir, with greatest respect,
the situation outside
the Conglomerate's borders
is becoming untenable.
The food riots,
climate change.
I am well aware
that the world outside our walls
is descending into chaos,
but causing chaos cannot be
a proper response
it is not chaos.
It is logic.
The world's population
is unsustainable
at current levels.
The herd must be thinned.
So you've argued,
Mr. Savage,
but no matter how many times
you choose to press your point,
my decision shall stand.
Vandal.
Oh, my boy.
My father would have
you killed for calling me that.
Oh, I wouldn't want
to chance execution.
Per Degaton.
So how did the meeting go?
Well, your father was being
his usual intractable self.
The problem is,
my young student,
to run a corporation
is not the same
as ruling a country.
If you're implying
that my father
doesn't have what it takes...
yes, he would have killed me
for that as well.
Well, I suppose I just have
to live dangerously then.
So how are your studies
progressing?
He's a teacher.
Tutor, it would seem,
to young Per Degaton himself.
You say that like
it's supposed to mean something.
After the death of his father
in five year's time,
Per Degaton
unleashes the Armageddon virus,
which decimates
the world's population,
leaving it ripe for conquest.
Per Degaton primes
the world for dictatorship,
and then when the time
is right...
Savage snatches that power
away from him.
By killing Per Degaton.
Indeed.
Okay, so we don't have
what we need
to take out Savage,
but maybe now we can figure out
a way to stop his rise to power.
By depriving him
of his springboard, Per Degaton.
Okay, how do we do that?
It's quite simple, really.
We kill the little bastard
ourselves.
To be clear,
we're talking about
murdering a child...
Who hasn't done anything
to anyone...
Yet, so why don't we
pick him off now,
while the picking's easy?
There's got to be
a better way.
How do we even know
that this Per Degaton kid's path
to becoming a world-ruling
dictator is inevitable?
Because in the future
that I'm from,
children learn about Per Degaton
in the same way
that children in your time
learn about Adolf Hitler.
What about addressing
the larger societal problems
that would allow
such a despot's rise to power?
We already know
what pushes this punk
to the dark side:
Savage.
Look, it's not the kid's fault
he's got an immortal psychopath
as his tutor.
If we don't kill the kid now,
Savage will as soon
as he's done using him
to take over the world.
If he doesn't build him
into the greatest tyrant
the world has ever known,
Savage can't become
the last tyrant
the world will ever know.
Murdering a child
in cold blood
just like Savage
murdered your own son.
What's the use
in saving the world
if we stoop to his methods
to do so?
I'm with Professor Stein.
Okay, fine.
If y'all don't have
the guts to kill this kid...
Then removing him
from the timeline
might be the next best thing.
Great, we've gone
from infanticide
to child abduction.
Progress.
First we need to devise
how to abduct him
from underneath the noses
of his father's private guard.
And don't forget
the army of A.T.O.M. robots.
We're going to need
an accomplished thief.
Well, while you're kidnapping
baby Hitler,
Professor Stein and I
will sabotage the robot army.
I call team robot army.
Isn't that a waste of time?
Not for the Kasnian citizens
who are tormented
by my technology.
That technology does lead
to Savage's rise to power.
Good backup plan.
Fine, team kidnapping.
Go team.
Hey, you okay?
Yeah, yeah,
I was just... thinking.
Ah, I think I understand.
You do?
Yeah, it's Savage.
He's so close
you can sense him, right?
Yeah.
Do you want to talk about it?
No.
Don't worry about me.
I'll be fine.
Okay.
Honey?
I'm home.
What's the matter?
Nothing.
Can I fix you a drink?
That would be lovely.
And while you do, you can
tell me what's on your mind.
Really, it's nothing.
You are a terrible liar.
Yes, but...
You love me anyway.
Beyond anything
I can describe.
And because I love you, I know
when something's bothering you.
It's... it's just a feeling.
Of him?
It's hard to tell.
I haven't sensed
Savage's presence,
but you do... or you think you do.
I think it's time
for us to go.
I have some vacation
time coming up.
We can drive to coast city
and do some sightseeing.
A vacation
isn't going to fix this.
I know.
Savage isn't just gonna forget
about us because we went away.
I know.
And he's not gonna stop
until...
mommy?
I can't sleep.
Hey, slugger.
- Daddy.
- Come here.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I just love you so much.
I love both of you so much.
No litter. No street crime.
No smog.
How soon can we leave?
Keep your eyes peeled.
According to Gideon,
Per Degaton
should be passing
through any minute
on his way to gymnastics class.
Are you telling me future
Hitler is enrolled
in a gymnastics class?
Yes.
I got eyes on
little Lord Fauntleroy.
I don't see him.
It's because he's surrounded
by daddy's goon squad.
Northeast corner of the Plaza.
Got him.
You sure you don't want
to just shoot him?
It'd be a whole lot easier.
Stick to the plan,
both of you.
Now, Ms. Lance.
I'm in position.
It's up to you now,
Mr. Snart.
Since the introduction
of our latest line
of autonomous law
enforcement officers,
crime has dropped precipitously.
In fact, it's nonexistent.
Really?
Well, thank you for
showing us around, Dr. Brice.
It's my pleasure.
We don't get very many visitors
from Central City
ever since the S.T.A.R. Labs
corporation took it over.
Uh, unless I'm mistaken,
your tech utilizes
a dwarf star alloy.
The technology is proprietary,
but yes.
How did you know, doctor...
Lecter...
Dr. Hannibal Lecter.
So how did you get
into robotics, Dr. Brice?
Oh, well, it's in my blood.
Robotics have been
a passion of my family
ever since my
great-great-great-great
grandfather
founded this company.
Is that...
Oh, my god.
Huh, weird.
You look just like him.
Yes, I-I look just like...
Yeah, that's...
That's pretty weird.
I can't believe it.
I'm like
the Wernher von Braun of robots.
The who?
The Nazi scientist
who invented the V2 rocket,
built it using slave labor,
then used it to level London.
Except my robots will
one day be used
to level the entire world.
Ray, dude, do you not think
you're focusing on
the wrong thing here?
I mean, you have a kid
you didn't even know about.
Had a kid.
In this particular time period,
his offspring
would be long since dead.
Thank you,
as if I wasn't already
feeling bad enough.
How is it even possible
that I'm someone's
great-great-great-great
grandfather?
Before we left in 2016,
the only person I was...
Having sex with?
Ghosted me
the week before we left.
Sh-she died?
No, no, ghosting.
It's where you
pretend to be dead
by not answering
somebody's text.
What a strange age for dating.
You think maybe she didn't
reply to your text because...
She knew she was pregnant?
No wonder my kid
started the company
that manufactures evil robots.
If I'd never left 2016,
my child would have had
a loving father,
and Palmer tech
might not have gone on
to build a robot army
that Savage uses
to conquer the world.
Bit of a stretch,
don't you think?
Either way,
I was someone's father
and didn't even know it.
- Hey.
Are you okay?
Fine.
Oh, I'm fine.
You don't look fine.
I'm just a little... Peckish.
Peckish?
It's nothing
a little energy bar won't fix.
I'll see you.
Edith and Joseph Boardman?
Our new names.
Joe Boardman is a good name.
And besides, I've never
kissed an Edith before,
but I certainly think
I can get used to that.
And what about all this?
How do we explain to our son
why his mother and father keep
moving every couple of years,
changing their names,
looking over their shoulders
at every turn?
I don't know why we thought
we could do this again.
Do you think we're selfish?
To have a family?
Because when Savage finds us...
- He won't.
- He always finds us.
Maybe this life is different.
Do you honestly believe that?
Look...
All I know is that
Savage is not the only thing
that's immortal, my love.
So is this.
What do genocidal maniacs
dream about, I wonder?
He's imagining himself baking
cookies with his mother.
Wait, you can monitor
our dreams?
Of course.
For example, last night,
you had a rollicking fantasy
involving a young nurse...
Okay, Gideon, enough.
Gideon, check the timeline
to make sure
that the kidnapping of the boy
had the desired effect
upon the future.
Oh, dear.
I'm afraid you'll be
disappointed with the results.
What do you mean,
it did nothing?
I mean,
that kidnapping Per Degaton
had a nominal effect
upon the timeline.
Maybe we need to dump
the little brat
somewhere he can't get
into any trouble,
like the stone age.
No matter where and when
you sequester him
in the timeline, Savage
will still rise to power.
But Rip said this kid's
like a baby Hitler.
Yes, I also said
that time wants to happen,
and such a world-changing event
like Savage's rise to power
can't be stopped merely
by kidnapping his young pawn.
So we're back to plan A?
Snuffing the kid
out in his sleep?
Let us not forget
that this kid will one day
be responsible
for billions of deaths,
including those of my family.
Say that you do stop Savage
and save the lives
of your family.
Will you be able
to look your own son in the eye
knowing what you did
so he could live?
When the alternative is that
I shall never see him again.
I got a better idea.
Instead of us arguing about
whether we should kill him,
or where and when
to dump him off,
why don't we just talk to him?
Savage has spent years
corrupting his mind.
It's not too late
for Per Degaton to change.
Says who?
Says someone with two tours
with the league
of assassins and a case
of bloodlust under her belt.
Ah, finally,
someone who's willing
to do a man's job.
Not why I'm here.
It's almost funny
how you guys
keep parading in here
like it's some kind of
confessional or something.
It's also not why I'm here.
Okay, I'll bite.
Everybody's out there
arguing about
whether or not
we should kill this kid,
'cause no one
thinks he can change,
which made me think of you.
You know no one
thinks you can change.
That's why you're in here.
The only reason
I'm in here is if I get out,
I'm gonna give Snart
some payback
he's not walking away from.
He saved your life.
He wussed out on killing me,
not the same thing.
He marooned me.
It's not like
he had many choices.
You know, while you were busy
selling us out
to a homicidal time pirate,
Leonard and I almost died.
He was thinking about you,
told me about your partnership,
your friendship.
Did it make you weepy?
You think it's gonna
make me weepy?
He's your friend,
a loyal one.
You should know that.
Well, thank you.
I'll work it out with him
as soon as I can.
Oh, killing a kid,
not very hero-like.
Mr. Degaton.
For the last 50 years,
everyone inside the Conglomerate
has submitted biosamples
so they can be tracked
and monitored at all times,
but these three...
are not from the Conglomerate,
nor are they even from
the last 50 years.
How do you know?
Long story.
What's important is that
I can get your son back.
How do you know
they haven't killed him already?
Because I know the people
who kidnapped him,
and they are weak...
Squeamish in matters of death.
Who are you?
That's an excellent question.
What was that?
That was our jump ship
taking off.
How could Per Degaton
have escaped?
Gideon,
who else is on the jump ship?
It's being piloted
by Captain Hunter.
Who just turned off
his transponder.
Sounds like someone
doesn't want us following him.
Why?
Because Rip
doesn't want us stopping him.
Stopping him from doing what?
From killing Per Degaton.
Okay, just think about this.
Where could Rip
be taking Per Degaton?
Jump ship's got a range
of 8,000 miles, so... Anywhere.
It doesn't matter
where he's taking him.
All that matters is what
he's gonna do to him
when he gets there.
Rip is not a murderer.
To Captain Hunter,
this isn't about a killing.
It's about saving.
Saving?
His son's life
for Per Degaton's.
Rather simple
if cold-blooded calculus
for a father to undertake.
Do you know who I am?
My father is going to...
thank me?
I imagine there's
a sizeable reward
for your safe return.
Relax.
You'll soon be home.
Come on, honey,
we got to get moving
or the train is going
to leave without us.
Where are we going?
We are going on
a little trip.
Just think of it as
one of your adventures.
The bad man found us,
the one that you and mommy talk
about when I'm asleep?
Why is Vandal Savage chasing us?
It's time that he knew.
Come on.
Can you keep a secret,
Aldus?
There's something... special
about your mommy and daddy.
We've known each other
for a very, very long time
and loved one another
since the day we met.
I already know that story.
You know part of that story.
Have you ever heard of
a place called Egypt?
Well, it all began during
the rule of Ramses II,
when late one night
a big, magical meteor
smashed into the temple of
Horus, the hawk-god.
- Hey, you okay?
- Hey.
Yeah, I'm fine.
I was just thinking.
What are you thinking about?
Let me into that
4,000-year-old mind of yours.
The flashes I've been having,
they aren't of Savage.
They're of Carter.
- Oh.
- And they're not just memories.
They're feelings too.
Oh, well, I get that.
It must be really weird
feeling like
you're cheating
on me with him.
No, Ray.
I feel like I'm cheating
on him with you.
I'm sorry.
No, it's... it's okay.
I mean,
I knew what I was getting into.
The last 206 times
you fell in love,
it was with the same guy.
I guess this isn't
a great time to talk about
what's been bothering you.
Ah, uh...
You're not the only
perceptive one.
So what's wrong?
Turns out that I had a child
I didn't know about
back in 2016,
and here in the future,
my great-great-great-great
granddaughter
creates the army
of robot gestapos
that Savage will one day use
to destroy the world.
Why didn't you tell me?
I didn't want you
to think less of me.
Ray, how could I ever
think less of you?
Well, now that we've got that
off our chests...
What does that mean for us?
No luck
finding our homicidal Captain?
Gideon's still searching,
but I have a feeling
Rip's not gonna be found
if he doesn't want to be.
So what are you doing
down here?
Don't you think you at least
owe him a conversation?
We had our conversation
while he was Chronos,
and he made his feelings
about me very clear.
And what about your feelings?
About you?
About Mick.
I don't have any feelings
about Mick.
Look,
it didn't seem that way
when we were dying in
the engine room of hypothermia.
Look, if you want
to ease your guilty conscience,
that's your business,
but he's still
the same son of a bitch he was
when you all
wanted me to put him down.
I wasn't the one
who mentioned marooning Rory.
You did.
It's obviously still
weighing on your conscience.
So stop being an ass
and go deal with it.
This isn't Kasnia.
I thought a neutral site
would be best for this.
For what?
Exchanging me?
Did your father ever
teach you to swim, Per Degaton?
No, I imagine he had someone
do it for him, didn't he?
You're hardly lacking
in tutors, are you...
Such as Mr. Savage.
What are you talking about?
My son Jonas
always wanted to learn to swim.
I promised him
that I'd teach him,
but there never seemed
to be... time.
My son never learned to swim,
because he was killed.
So... you brought me here
to kill me.
I brought you here
to save my son's life,
your life in exchange for his.
I'm sorry.
No you're not.
You're not sorry,
because you're not
going to kill me.
I have to.
To save my wife and son,
I don't expect you
to understand.
It doesn't matter
if I understand.
I can see it in your eyes.
You're not going to do it.
You're like my father, weak.
Vandal Savage
has taught me many things,
including
what a killer looks like.
You're not a killer.
Your tutor
has taught you well,
despite his ill intentions.
Vandal loves me.
Oh, he wants to
use you as his pawn,
and ultimately,
he will betray you.
No.
No, he wouldn't.
I've said to myself
time and time again
that there is nothing
that I wouldn't do
to save my wife and son,
but now I know that there is.
My reticence to kill you,
Per Degaton,
is not weakness.
It is goodness.
And if there is a shred
of goodness inside of me,
then I have to believe
that there is a shred
of goodness inside of you.
Be the man that your father
wants you to be,
not the man Savage
wants you to be.
Savage, he's coming.
Gideon?
Tor Degaton's forces
have surrounded the ship.
I'm afraid our shields
will not be able to sustain
continued bombardment.
You're afraid?
Here's an idea:
Why don't you fire back?
I would, except...
the flying robots already
targeted our weapons systems.
We don't need weapons.
He's right.
We have super powers.
I think this is yours.
I'll draw their fire.
You handle the ground troops.
Aah!
Ugh!
Ray, are you all right?
So this is what it feels
like to be last year's model.
They're too fast.
We have to find another way.
Forget about them.
We'll hold off the robots.
We'll take out
their command center.
Who are you?
Yeah.
Ray, hurry up.
I can only hold them back
for so long.
Where did you get your suit?
Look,
if you don't let us disable
your evil robot army,
then the whole world
will be destroyed.
They're designed
to bring peace.
I know.
I designed the robots.
What?
I am your
great-great-great-great
grandfather,
the guy you have a bust of
in your lobby,
father of the robotics industry.
You're trying to tell me
that you're Sidney Palmer?
Sidney?
Wait, the bust in your lobby
is of my stupid brother?
Of course.
He must have gone
to work for Felicity
in 2016 after I vanished.
He allowed my tech
to be perverted
by the defense industry.
That is so Sidney.
So that means
that she's not...
I'm not a father.
So we still need your help
disabling the robots.
A-and why
should I believe you?
Because if you have even
a drop of Palmer blood
in your veins,
you'll do what's right.
Looks like Raymond was able
to sabotage his robot army.
Which means mopping up
the rest of these guys
shouldn't be a problem.
Oh, it will be a problem.
What do you want?
I want to exchange
this woman's life
for your Captain,
Rip Hunter.
I have a better idea:
Her life in exchange for his.
Your son will be
returned to you
as soon as you guarantee
our safe passage.
Don't do it, father.
If you let them go now,
they will only come back
for us in the future.
It's your choice.
Your son is right.
We should kill them all.
Put down your weapons!
- No, father.
- Let my son go,
and I will let you
leave in peace.
You have my word.
Better find yourself
a new mentor, kid.
What do you want?
People seem to think
we should have a heart-to-heart.
We don't have hearts.
Where does that leave us?
I've got a dozen reasons
for killing you.
You've got a dozen and one
for killing me, so...
all the talk in the world
is not gonna change a thing.
Exactly,
here's my proposal.
I open this cell,
we let our fists do the talking.
When I kill you...
You take the jump ship,
make your escape,
live out the rest of your life
anywhere you like.
Hmm.
And if you kill me, well,
it's better than being
locked up in this place
like some kind of circus freak.
I take that as a yes.
Sound the bell.
Hey.
You don't have to knock.
- It's your room too.
- Yeah, I know.
It's just...
Things have been weird.
Since I told you
I had a love child
that I didn't really have,
or since you told me
that you're still in love with...
you know what
I love about you, Ray, is,
you always manage
to find the bright side.
And no matter what,
you never give up.
So please,
don't give up on us.
I'm not giving up,
but it's hard
to ignore the math.
You and Carter have
spent lifetimes together,
and in each one,
you've fallen in love,
so why would this lifetime
be any different?
Well,
I never met you before.
Look, Ray, Carter is my past.
You are my future.
Vandal.
Oh, I didn't expect you up
and about so soon.
My father wanted me to rest,
but I wanted
to resume my studies.
Oh, good boy.
So... where should we begin?
Well, I was thinking
Greek mythology.
Do you know the tale
of Oedipus Rex?
He was a prince of thieves
before his father exiled him.
Why?
Well,
because the king was a coward.
He had heard a prophecy
that one day his son
would take his crown,
so he bound his boy's feet
and tossed him
into the woods to die.
What did the boy do?
He did what he had to do.
And one day,
the prophecy came true,
and the prince became
a great and powerful king.
Though it wasn't easy.
Great things are never easy.
Unfortunately, our
interactions have done nothing
to halt
Per Degaton's rise to power.
If anything,
we've merely cemented it.
In fact, the virus,
which wasn't supposed to be
unleashed upon the world
for another five years...
I'm sorry, father.
Will now be released
in a matter of days.
As you all know,
our former chairman's chair
is in the Conglomerate
passed to his son,
who due to his age
elected me to act as his proxy.
First order of business,
I would like to revisit
our discussion
concerning the population crisis
beyond the Conglomerate's
borders.
As we all know,
we already have a solution.
Did I do the right thing,
Gideon?
Not committing murder
is generally considered
the right thing, Captain.
In this instance...
I wonder.
We had a deal, Mick.
Kill me and you walk.
It's what you wanted, isn't it,
to get off the team?
I don't know
what I want anymore.
Truth is, it doesn't matter.
What are you talking about?
Whether I stay
or leave, I'm dead.
We're all dead.
Since I failed
to bring you in,
the Time Master's want to
bring me in,
and this time, they're not
gonna take any chances.
They're called
the Hunters, mercenaries,
and unlike me, there isn't
a human part left in them.
So they want to lock us all up
in the vanishing point?
The Hunters do one thing:
Kill,
whenever, wherever,
and they'll stop at nothing
till every single one of us
is erased from
the face of history.
Do you have any suggestions as
to how we might
outsmart them, Mr. Rory?
Run.
Greg, move your head.