Time travel is real.
And all of history is vulnerable
to the attack of rogue time travelers.
But one group travels throughout time
to stop the spread of these
so-called Time Aberrations
and erase their damage to history.
A group of outcasts and misfits.
These individuals aren't heroes,
they're something else, they're Legends.
Previously on "Legends of Tomorrow"...
Heywood, Dr. Nate Heywood.
I'm a historian.
I specialize in deductive
historical reconstruction.
In layman's terms, I'm a time detective.
Ingestible translator.
You'll be able to speak and understand
any language spoken to you.
You know how fragile
we historians can be.
I know my cuts and bruises.
You're a hemophiliac.
You can bleed to death.
So your superpower is wearing the suit.
Without that fancy suit,
you're nothing but a
self-righteous rich guy.
Mr. Heywood's vitals are dropping.
I think I can save him.
I did a little tinkering to the formula.
Hello, Rex.
Rex!
- Time traveler.
- Rex!
- So how's our patient?
- Still stable.
Gideon has him under sedation.
Any side effects from
the Nazi super-serum
you injected him with?
No, but that may have a
little something to do
with the work I did altering the serum
to remove the Nazi parts.
Yes, it would be a tad inconvenient
to have a monster roaming the ship.
Gideon, can you pilot for a little bit?
I need a break.
Where are all the knives?
Oh, there's one.
Look, if this is about me
taking all the mayonnaise,
you might be slightly overreacting.
You killed him!
Killed him? I've killed lots of people.
You're gonna have to be
a bit more specific.
What the hell happened to you?
I really don't know.
- sync and corrections by Caio -
- www.addic7ed.com -
You injected me with Nazi serum?
Which I'd redesigned to
quintuple my own strength
and transform my skin into an alloy
a hundred times stronger than steel.
Steel, that's a cool name.
Yeah, especially since my grandfather
was called Commander Steel.
But what does that make me?
Corporal Steel? Mr. Steel?
Citizen Steel?
Who cares? You got
superpowers now, dude.
Except I don't know
how I turned to steel
- in the first place.
- Ray'll teach you.
- He will?
- You said it yourself,
- you redesigned the serum.
- Which I did beautifully,
but it's not like I have some
sort of instruction manual.
Guess you'll have to wing it.
Now, I'm gonna go have a chat
with our stowaway.
This is gonna be so much fun!
Hm.
You stowed away before we
time-jumped from 1942.
I'm gonna get out of here,
and I'm gonna finish what I started.
You mean, killing Mick?
Not that I haven't thought
of it myself, but why?
He killed Rex.
What?
Rex Tyler?
As in Hourman?
His killer stole the Askaran Amulet.
Look, I'm sorry. I am.
But Mick didn't do it.
He is a thief and a murderer.
He's also a Legend,
and Mick hasn't been off the ship
since we dropped your
team off at the JSA.
With his last words,
he told me his killer
was a time traveler.
You know, we've been tracking someone
who's been trying to alter history.
We think it's the same person
that gave Krieger the super-serum.
This might be your time traveler.
Look, if I let you out of here,
you promise not to hurt Mick
unless he really deserves it?
Sorry for knocking you out.
Sorry for locking you up.
Call it even?
When I was a kid, I used to play
JSA versus Nazis with my dolls.
Well, they were action figures, really.
But it doesn't matter 'cause
I got superpowers now
and it's awesome.
Your powers manifested
as a result of a heightened
adrenal response.
Basically, Amaya threatened
you and you reacted.
So now
what we need to do is
duplicate the conditions
which caused you to, you know, steel on?
Wait, so you want to threaten me?
- Not exactly.
- Wait, let's discuss this.
I thought this was a time machine.
You saved the Justice Society.
Why can't you save Rex?
Because we're dealing with
another time traveler.
If we go back and save Rex,
the time traveler will just
go back before then and kill Rex again,
so instead of chasing our own tails,
we need to identify
who we're up against.
I don't understand any of this.
Look, I just need you to trust us.
We're gonna find who do this.
I promise you.
In the meantime, Gideon
will fly you home.
I'm not going back until Rex's killer
is brought to justice.
We don't know how long that will take.
Don't worry, we're professionals.
We know what we're doing.
Yeah, come on!
If Grandpa Heywood could see me now.
- Professional?
- Ish.
I know you not
gonna take that, Ray.
Go crush this Tin Man.
- Nice try.
- Come on.
Hold on, I'll close it!
Ah!
Nate!
Ray, get inside! We
have to close the door.
No, I got to go after him.
Gideon, shut the cargo door.
What's happening to the ship?
Jax, what's our status?
I've rerouted power from
the secondary manifolds.
Where are Dr. Palmer and Dr. Heywood?
- Did you check out the window?
- What?
How is it you people haven't
managed to kill yourselves yet?
The day is still young.
- Jax?
- Yeah, I'm working on it.
Gideon, I need you
to track down Ray and Nate
- and take us to their position.
- The explosive decompression
caused us to lose corrective altitude,
which put too much strain on
the station-keeping thrusters.
For God's sake, say it how it is.
We're screwed.
Edo Period.
Mid-17th century Japan.
That's cool.
Well...
I'm still alive.
So far, so good.
Whoa, Samurais.
_
Oh right, almost forgot.
Can you understand me now?
I'm looking for a friend of mine.
Okay, he fell from the sky.
He's about yea tall.
Made out of metal.
No?
You're alive.
Um, hi. How did I get here?
I found you lying at
the bottom of a crater
like you had been dropped from the sky.
Dropped from the sky?
That's the craziest
thing I've ever heard.
Yeah, I sailed here,
you know, across the ocean
with some friends.
Who hopefully are gonna find me.
By the looks of it, I'm gonna say
we're on the island of...
Honshu, in the vicinity of Kyoto?
Yes.
How did you learn to speak my language?
I studied it for many years.
You know, so I could trade
with your countrymen.
Yep, feudal Japan is my jam.
Masako,
what are you doing
talking to this gaijin?
He was hurt, Father.
I brought him home so
you could care for him.
And who would care for us
when the Shogun finds out
- we're aiding a foreigner?
- Please, Father.
You know what they would do to him.
Very well.
Get him inside quickly.
My name is Nate, by the way.
- My name is Masako.
- Masako.
That's a pretty name.
The Shogun asked you a question.
Where did you find your armor?
I made it.
Your armor is mine now.
You don't understand.
I designed the suit
specifically for my body.
Take the armor away.
You're making a big mistake.
It could kill you!
Too hot?
Are you, um, sure your old man's cool
with you giving me a bath?
- Mm.
- My father is not home.
I'm only giving you a bath
because you are dirty and injured.
About that. I'm, uh...
I'm more durable than it looks.
You still have not told
where you are from.
The United States,
which you've never heard of
because it doesn't exist
for another 200 years.
You are a strange man.
You have no idea.
Enough about me,
I overheard your father
talk about the Shogun.
Is that Tokugawa Iemitsu, by any chance?
Historians view him as a
particularly brutal warlord
and...
Did I say something?
Tomorrow I'm to be married
to Tokugawa Iemitsu.
Then my life is over.
How can you bring a thug
on a rescue mission?
I've known men like you.
Men who take and prey on the weak.
Listen, girly,
I'm risking my neck for two morons
who fell out of a ship. Why?
'Cause they'd do the same for me.
Why are you on the ship?
'Cause I'm a member of the
Justice Society of America.
- It's my job to protect everyone.
- Except for me.
You snuck up behind me and
sliced my throat like a ninja.
There's no such thing
as ninjas, you idiot.
- Tell that to Chuck Norris.
- Who's that?
- And I'm the idiot.
- And by the way,
- I'm not your girly.
- All right,
if you two don't quit your squabbling,
I am going to maroon you
in a time period of my choosing.
Together.
Not to brag, but...
Between the
docking stabilizers
and the blast doors,
I think this might be
my best patchwork ever.
Well, charming as your confidence is,
I think we better consult the expert.
Gideon, would you be so kind
as to run a diagnostic report?
Mr. Jackson's work has done the trick.
A scan has revealed that
all 36 compartments of the ship
are in optimal condition.
That's weird.
Actually, I think it's astonishing given
the considerable abuse
we've been under...
No, no, not... not that.
Gideon, did you say 36 compartments?
Correct. The entirety of the ship.
Before Rip, you know, disappeared,
he made me learn every
inch of the Waverider,
and of those inches,
35 compartments.
So either I miscalculated or...
Captain Hunter had a secret compartment
he failed to tell you about.
Gideon, please pull up the
schematics of the ship.
No, we still have to fix the time drive.
And we will.
After.
Please, don't tell me
you're not intrigued.
Masako san,
a word please.
What's wrong?
The Shogun's men are here.
Please come outside.
Konnichiwa. How can I help you?
We found a gaijin in the forest.
The Shogun wants to make sure
there are not any other
foreigners around
- to bother you.
- Oh, that is very kind of him,
but you are the only
visitor we've had today.
Good.
The last thing the Shogun wants
before his wedding is surprises.
Too late!
What are you doing?
Relax, I got this.
- Who are you?
- I'm the guy telling you
that your Shogun's wedding
has been canceled
on account that he's an asshat.
But seriously.
Why don't you boys mosey on
back to your big bad boss
and tell him the news?
Or what?
Or it's gonna get ugly.
I am wearing a Samurai's armor.
You are not.
I wear my armor on the inside.
Nate, stop insulting him. I beg of you.
Relax, I got this.
He caught me off guard.
Ah, he caught me off guard.
Come at me now.
It's not turning on.
Stop! Stop! Please!
You're going to kill him.
That is entirely up to him.
Stay down, gaijin.
She doesn't want to marry him.
We will return tomorrow to
take you to the castle.
I trust there will be no more...
surprises.
The sword did not cut any vital organs
but the blood loss...
Tell me about it.
What were you thinking?
I didn't mean to cause
you any more trouble.
I was just trying to help.
No one can help me.
We have that in common.
Nate? Nate!
The Signal from Ray's ATOM
suit is getting stronger.
Doesn't exactly look inviting, does it?
It's like "Ninja III: The Domination."
Never took you for a cinephile.
All I know is ninjas
like to hide in trees.
- I don't see anything.
- Exactly.
You don't find them, they find you.
Just because you saw ninjas in a movie,
that doesn't make them real.
I have to side with Mick on this one.
They're real.
You think there's a
secret brotherhood of men
trained in the art of assassination?
I hate to break it to you, Amaya,
but I'm basically a ninja.
I miss the JSA.
Compartment 36 should
be right about here.
What are you doing, Grey?
I'm looking for any hidden doors.
We don't
have time for this.
Nate and Ray are lost in Feudal Japan.
Let's just fix the ship and go.
Shh, did you hear that, Jefferson?
Move.
- Oh my god.
- Secret hatch.
With a sequencing lock.
Clearly, Captain Hunter didn't
want anyone getting in.
Or maybe he was trying to keep
something from getting out.
If I've learned one thing from "Lost,"
it's you don't go
opening secret hatches.
Ray's close. Look sharp.
Haircut, let's get out of here.
We're saving your ass, again.
It is you who need rescuing.
Fellas, getting a little cold
in here without my suit.
You are already defeated
before you have even begun.
I have been trained in the art
of war by Shimura himself.
League of Assassins, class of '09.
Don't take it easy on me.
We got to go.
Oh, hey, guys!
- Wrong way, Haircut.
- What about my suit?
We can get it later.
My friend's serum,
it's cured my hemophilia.
Uh, long story.
Short version,
my blood didn't clot like normal people,
so if I were to cut myself shaving
or get a paper cut,
I could... die.
So every day, you were afraid to live?
Pretty much.
In the Samurai tradition,
a warrior is always prepared for death.
A woman celebrates when her
husband dies with honor.
Wow. That's hardcore.
A Samurai who fights without armor,
that is hardcore.
Nate, you're alive.
Oh, hey, guys! You found me.
- Bad timing?
- Nope.
Nope.
Masako, these are,
uh, my friends I was telling you about.
Hajimemashite.
Can I get you something to drink?
Sake, lots of it.
What he meant to say is
thanks for your hospitality,
but we must be going.
- No, I didn't.
- Amaya's right.
Nate, let's go.
I can't.
We can't leave.
Masako's supposed to marry
the Shogun Tokugawa Iemitsu.
Yeah, met him. Not a fan.
Well, the reason he sticks
out in the history books is
because he likes to murder his wives,
and I can't leave Masako to his mercy.
Especially since he stole my ATOM suit.
Exactly. Wait, what?
You let the Shogun steal a
21st century super-suit?
After I crash-landed
trying to rescue you.
How does the Shogun even know
how to operate your ATOM suit?
I designed it so an idiot could use it.
An idiot does.
Guys, bottom line is, if the
Shogun has the ATOM suit,
it's not just Masako and the
village we have to protect.
He can use it to conquer
the whole region.
You said the Shogun's coming
for your new girlfriend.
- Uh-huh.
- Easier to defend a village
- than to attack a castle.
- But anyone who tries
to fight the Shogun will be cut down.
Except if that person
- is made of steel.
- About that,
I'm having a little problem
accessing my powers.
Sounds like you're having
performance issues,
and it looks like you're
not done training him yet.
Now the rest of us need to figure out
how we can defend a village.
Not me.
Wake me up when the action starts.
Whoa, what is this place?
It appears to be some sort of armory.
There's a reason why Rip
didn't want us in here.
Some things you can't un-see.
But why the big secret?
Rip didn't trust us to know that
there were heavy-duty weapons on board?
Well, would you?
Look, Jefferson,
our old friend has hailed the Waverider.
Let's play it.
Sorry to contact you like
this, Captain Hunter.
But I can't risk putting
any more lives in danger.
Thought this was from Barry Allen?
It is.
Only from 40 years in the future.
- And neither can this.
- Fascinating.
Which is why you'll keep what
I'm about to tell you a secret.
Even from the rest of your team.
The ATOM suit is made of and
powered by dwarf star alloy.
It's strong enough to withstand
bullets, arrows, and explosives.
- So it's impenetrable?
- Not quite.
Underneath the left thruster
is the alpha-stabilizer.
- Alpha-stabilizer, got it.
- If you destroy it,
the photons that stream
from suit's weapons systems
will overheat,
theoretically causing somatic overload.
Theoretically, that's...
that's comforting.
You have to get close to the Shogun,
and in order to do that, you
have to be able to harden.
Well, when you're putting it in
those terms it isn't helping.
Ow! Neither is that.
It worked the last time.
Ow.
Come on. My serum is flawless.
Your lack of focus is the problem.
You think I'm not focusing?
Like... enough!
- I can't do it.
- Yes, you can.
You don't think I don't
want to save the girl,
spare the village, and be a
hero for once in my damn life?
I spent half of my
childhood in the hospital
where it didn't even occur to me
to dream about having superpowers.
But guess what? I got 'em, I lost 'em,
now I really, really need 'em,
and I can't get 'em back.
This isn't all about you.
I worked for years, spent
billions of dollars
to develop the ATOM suit.
I nearly died learning to shrink,
and now, I have to teach you
to destroy the very thing,
the only thing, that makes me a hero.
Wait?
"Somatic overload" means
destroy the suit?
Yeah, Nate.
We can't beat the Shogun
while he's wearing the suit,
so we have to blow the suit up.
Your powers are within you.
After today,
I'll have nothing left.
Ray...
You should all be safe here.
They've never seen foreigners before.
I was once just like them.
My village was also small and isolated.
Some would say that my
people were superstitious,
but in truth,
we were protected.
Protected by that?
Legend has it that this
totem was one of five
created by the gods
and given to the five
great tribes of Zambesi.
This totem harnesses the ashe,
or the... the life force,
of the animal kingdom.
It was passed down to me from my mother
and from hers before that.
And why did you leave?
I was recruited by the JSA,
and I realized that
the world was much larger
than just my village,
and that there were
people beyond its borders
who also needed protection.
Sometimes I can't help but worry
that with me gone,
there's no one left to guard my home.
From people like Mr. Rory.
At the end of the day,
Mick does the right thing.
Usually.
You remind me of my son.
Why?
Was he a terrible teacher, too?
He was a great Samurai.
I built him the strongest
and most formidable armor
in all of Japan.
Forged him a sword
fit for an Emperor.
What happened to him?
My son was popular
with the men who served under him,
and the Shogun resented him for it.
So he ordered Oda
to commit seppuku.
We will make sure that the Shogun pays
for what he's done to your family.
Maybe.
Maybe not.
But I ask you,
would I rather hold my son again
or his armor?
Your son, obviously.
An armor is nothing but
iron, leather, and silk.
It can be replaced,
but the man
who wears the armor is...
I get it.
You're saying I don't
need a suit of armor
to defeat the Shogun.
Don't be ridiculous.
He'll kill you in seconds.
Follow me.
I'm gonna die.
Yeah, probably.
That was actually your
cue to cheer me up.
Oh, if you accept death
you have nothing to fear.
I'm more afraid of what's
gonna happen to you if I die.
I know I have these powers inside me.
I just can't figure out how to use them.
Does a child learn to laugh?
Does he sit and practice laughing?
No.
He just laughs.
Hmm.
"Do or do not, there is no try."
Exactly.
Where did you learn that?
From a great sensei
from where I'm from.
Yoda.
Ah, this Master Yoda is very wise.
The Shogun approaches.
Get to the temple.
Where is my bride?
She's not leaving.
Not with you.
I'm just gonna need a second.
_
Find the villagers. Kill them.
Your form is all wrong.
I ordered Ichiro to destroy that blade
after the death of his son.
Very well.
I will destroy it myself.
Konnichiwa, scumbag.
Go get him.
I will kill you
with your own armor.
Check the temple.
Rematch?
- Who is your master?
- I have no master.
A ronin. You're not
worthy of the effort.
You have fought with honor.
Now you will die with it.
About that.
This village is under our protection.
Leave now and we'll spare your lives.
A sword is only as deadly
as the man who wields it.
And armor is only as strong
as the man who wears it.
I don't want to shoot you guys.
I love ninjas.
That was the armature relay.
It enhances the limbs' reaction time.
Where the hell is Mick?
Probably ransacking the village himself.
Told you ninjas were real.
That's the cooling system.
Trust me, it gets hot in there. I know.
You think you are clever.
You dishonor my family
and torture my village.
I will enjoy killing you.
Your family will be
extinguished from history.
We haven't been introduced.
Name's Steel.
- Remember, you got to hit...
- I remember!
Do it!
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
- You did it.
- I did it.
Yeah...
you blew up the ATOM suit.
I am so sorry.
It's okay.
You steeled on.
Kind of proud of you.
Master Yoda taught you well.
Right, uh, Yoda. Well, thank you.
Um...
I was thinking now that,
uh, your wedding is canceled...
You come from the sky.
Something tells me you have to return.
I, um...
I'm glad the katana sword
found a worthy owner.
Me too.
You.
Don't think I didn't see how
you stood up to the Shogun.
Even though he's gone,
your village still needs a protector.
That sword,
what did you say your family name was?
Yamashiro.
Thank you for loaning
me your son's armor.
I'm sorry it got a bit
dinged up in the battle.
Then it served its purpose.
Haircut. Steel.
Sara says we got to clear out.
- Good-bye, Masako.
- Good-bye, Nate.
What an amazing time period.
Definitely my favorite,
besides the Old West.
Why are you two goofy bastards so happy?
You lost your damn suit, the food sucks,
and I've got no proof ninjas exist.
What are you staring at?
I've figured you out.
Congratulations.
You act like this selfish meathead,
but secretly, you're not so bad.
You know, you might even
have the makings of a hero.
Well, that proves one thing.
You don't know me.
Perhaps not.
Trying to kill me again?
Trying to give you a present.
In case you ever need proof
you met an actual ninja.
All right. What's your secret?
What on earth do you mean?
Well, you two must be magicians
considering how badly
damaged the Waverider was
- before we left.
- Oh, that.
Well, Jefferson and I went
over the ship top to bottom.
And safe to say there are no
surprises left on the Waverider.
Great. I'll go prep for takeoff.
So are we gonna say something
about future-Barry's message or not?
Barry was very clear
about the team not knowing
what he told Captain Hunter.
Except now we know.
Indeed.
You were right, Jefferson.
Some things you just can't un-see.
I think it's time we said sayonara
to Feudal Japan. Now, where to next?
I could always open the hatch,
jump out, and see where I land.
I say we just sit back and see
where the timestream takes us.
Aren't you forgetting that Rex's
killer is still at-large?
Not my problem.
I mean, we should find the
bastard and kill him.
Perhaps we can enjoy a
little takeoff music.
Ah, nice one, Gideon.
Captain Hunter always enjoyed this song.
- ♪ Time...
- Speaking of problems.
Don't worry. We're gonna find Rip
and Hourman's killer.
In the meantime, everyone just shut up
and let me do the flying.
- sync and corrections by Caio -
- www.addic7ed.com -