My name is Eobard Thawne.
With the help of Damien Darhk,
Malcolm Merlyn,
Leonard Snart, and Mick Rory,
I've obtained the Spear of Destiny...
An ancient artifact with the power
to rewrite reality itself, and we have.
It's a brave new world.
Aah!
Whoops!
The Mayor would like a word,
Miss Smoak.
Then maybe he should've
come down here himself
instead of sending the bimbo brigade.
Rude!
Uhh!
Well done, ladies.
Star City owes you a debt of gratitude.
Just doing our job, Mr. Mayor.
Yes, but you do it so well,
and with such... style.
And you've done a bang-up job
dealing with my... pest problem,
though that term may
be giving you vigilantes
a little too much credit.
Even a cockroach knows when to pack up
and head out of Dodge.
Star City is my home. I
will never stop fighting.
Sure you will.
Kill her.
Hmm.
Get rid of that.
Oh, but I will take this mask...
so I can add it to my collection.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
No, I will not take a seat
and wait for him to have an opening.
He can make time for me
now. Can't you, Eobard?
I'm so sorry, Mr. Thawne.
He insisted.
I see your friend is
still putting up a fight.
He'll give up. All caged
animals do eventually.
Now, tell me why you've flown
all the way out here again.
You keep ignoring my
requests for a meeting.
Because there's no reason for one.
Our partnership has ended.
You got what you wanted.
Your wife and your son are
both alive and in good spirits.
Your daughter Thea adores you.
Nyssa al Ghul is trapped in
a miserable, closeted life
in the middle of Ohio, and hey,
you can even clap again.
What more could you possibly want?
How about the Spear of Destiny?
There are still some
things in this world
that I would like to see change.
How many times do I have
to tell you this, Malcolm?
The Spear is safest in my hands.
Besides, I'm the only one
who knows how to use it.
That's because you destroyed
the Kalabros Manuscript.
Well, it's not my fault
you don't retain information like I do.
Speedster brains are handy that way.
Mr. Jackson is here to see you.
Send him in.
Good morning, Mr. Thawne.
Jefferson.
How are things down at the lab?
There was a minor setback,
but the situation is under control.
You promised me results.
And you will have them.
I just need to motivate
my employee a little more.
But another test will be
up and running this evening.
I hope so, for his sake...
and yours.
Yes.
I don't know why
you and Damien insist on
toying with the Legends.
It's sloppy. They should
be wiped from existence.
I prefer this arrangement.
I believe it's called "poetic justice."
And, uh, what is this
project you're working on?
I'm a man of science, Malcolm.
I'm compelled to innovate,
invent, and inspire.
A genius brain needs a genius challenge.
Now go. Enjoy your
family, spend your wealth.
The world is as it should be.
Be satisfied with your spoils.
The others are having
the time of their lives.
Stop! Hold it right there!
Cool it, Mick. We already
got what we came for.
Just heating things up.
Don't move! Both of you on the ground!
Mr. Snart. Sorry, sir.
We didn't realize it was you.
Carry on.
What the hell's going
on? No roasting pigs?
No need. We're home free, buddy.
It's good to be the king.
No getaway, no chase?
You want a chase, I can arrange a chase.
Even get us tossed in Iron Heights,
and we can plan an escape
just like old times.
- How does that sound?
- Boring!
Well, we could hit up
the Central City Bank.
They've got a fancy new vault
I've been dying to crack.
What's the point?
You own the bank and half the city.
You mean we own half the city, Mick.
We're partners, remember?
Mm.
Seems our next score will have to wait.
Thawne is...
summoning us.
Since when do we get summoned?
Since the man agreed not to erase
you and your friends from existence.
Gideon, I've finally
perfected my fondant bows.
What do you think?
Your technique has vastly improved
over the last year,
Captain. These cakes are
so much more creative
than your biscuits.
Now, credit where credit is due, Gideon.
Your idea of adding more gelatin
to the mixture was pivotal.
Well done. The best one
yet, in my humble opinion.
It's a shame that you're
the only one here to appreciate it.
I'm sure your team would
be just as impressed.
Assuming that they're all still alive.
Perhaps you should resume your efforts
to send a message out.
What's the point, Gideon?
The Legion have the Spear of Destiny!
They're like gods now!
There's no point in fighting.
Not anymore.
Stein!
Yes, Mr. Jackson?
What's this I hear about
you taking tomorrow off?
It's Saturday, sir, and
it's my daughter's birthday.
Oh. Well, of course. Take the day off.
In fact, why don't you
take the whole week off?
Really?
Of course.
I mean, the project's ready
for Mr. Thawne to use, correct?
- Well, in fact...
- In fact, old man,
you will not be leaving this building
until Mr. Thawne sees results.
I-I have been working
nonstop for the past month.
I haven't seen my wife
and daughter in weeks.
You want to see your family?
Then you will get that reactor
working by tomorrow night.
It's impossible.
There's too much data...
Get it working!
Or you will never see that
precious family of yours again.
Somebody clean this place
up! It's a damn mess.
I'm so sorry, may I help you with that?
Oh. No worries, man. I got it.
Yes, Mr. President,
you know I'll be there.
You know I love receiving medals.
And then, uh, golf on Sunday.
And dinner at your hotel after?
All right, all right, best to Mel.
Bye-bye.
I am so sorry. I had to take that.
There's only so many times you can tell
the President of the United States
that you'll call him back.
- You want to get to the point?
- Yes.
I brought you here to
discuss a... sensitive matter,
and it goes by the
name of Malcolm Merlyn.
What about him?
Want you to keep an eye on him for me.
We're not your watchdogs.
Hmm. What was that?
What he meant was, we're
not spies. We're thieves.
Mr. Thawne, I need to speak with you!
I just need five minutes of your time.
Please.
Reality's at stake.
The world isn't right.
Okay, let him go. Let him go.
Let's just... let's
see what he has to say.
It's okay.
He intentionally hit me in the ribs.
First of all, awesome office.
I guess it pays to be the
smartest man in the world,
which is why I've come to you for help.
You were saying that
the world isn't right.
Yeah, this world we're in now is wrong.
Reality has, uh, has changed somehow.
How do you know all this?
Um, well, there's signs everywhere
if you know where to look.
There's subtle inconsistencies
in the fabric... of reality.
Um, I call 'em scars.
You know, like, after
you've been operated on.
Well, um, reality has been operated on.
Truly fascinating.
I'm giddy with excitement.
What's that got to do with him?
Well, um, Mr. Thawne
could help me fix it.
Look, right, you're a genius.
You figured out cold fusion.
You saved the polar bears,
you fixed global warming.
I mean, you made
desalination sustainable.
I mean, you solve problems
like this, like, every day.
If anyone... anyone can figure
out why these scars exist
and how to put the world
back to the way it was...
it's you, dude.
You know what?
I think you're on to something.
Ah.
Something is definitely
not right here.
Fix it. Take mister...
- Heywood.
- Mr. Heywood.
Take Mr. Heywood out for some fresh air.
And, uh, kill him.
Me?
Look, I don't understand.
If this is about my work,
nobody pays attention to it.
My mom's the only person
that reads my blog.
Stop talking.
Guys, I am not a threat to
anyone... unless I'm right.
Am I right?
Sounds like fitting final words to me.
Whatever... science or magic
altered reality must have left
small scars on my memory that
my subconscious picked up on.
So if I'm not a conspiracy theorist
no one listens to, then...
Who am I?
- Dead.
- Wait.
- What?
- He said, "Wait."
I heard him. He said, "Wait."
You promised me things were
gonna be like old times.
It is like old times, only better.
Central City is ours. No more Flash.
Except another speedster's
calling the shots.
You leave Thawne to me.
I always have a plan. You know this.
Well, fill me in.
When the time is right.
Ah, yes, we're partners,
except when you refuse to
tell me what's going on.
You son of a...
Sorry, buddy. I owed you that.
You saved my life. Why?
Because I'm an idiot.
This could be one of my scars talking,
but I'm sensing you're
telling me the truth.
Let's move.
Okay.
This is crazier than
any of my crazy theories.
You're trying to tell me a group
called "The Legion of Doom"
used something called
"The Spear of Destiny"
to rewrite reality?
Who even names something
"Legion of Doom"?
You did.
Me?
Now, do you only
remember the old reality
because you're part of the Legion?
I'm not part of anything.
I just made a terrible mistake.
You filthy aliens.
Come on, wait a minute.
This is the guy who's gonna fix reality?
- Uh-huh.
- Uh...
who are you guys, and, um,
what are you doing here?
We need your help.
What do you got, like, a
clogged toilet or something?
'Cause, you know,
I'm... I'm off duty now.
You're not a janitor.
Yeah, I am, man. It
says so on my name...
On my name tag.
You're a geek, a nerd, a genius.
That's why we're here.
Oh, is this about the dipole magnets
that I borrowed from S.T.A.R. Labs?
'Cause I'm totally gonna return those.
Look, man,
he said you're the one
that could fix this reality.
Fix this reality?
What do you mean?
You guys think there's
something wrong too?
- Whoa.
- Oh!
That's... that's private stuff, man.
What is it?
Um, I don't know exactly.
I mean... I mean, I think
I know, but I don't...
Spit it out, haircut.
Well, um, I ki...
I kinda built it on impulse.
You know, like, on instinct.
I call it, uh, a
Transreality Multiplexer.
No real reason. Just
thought it sounded cool.
Don't you get it, man?
Your impulse was a reality scar
working on your subconscious.
Reality scar.
So, uh, what does this fun gun do?
Uh, theoretically,
it targets irregularities
in the hippocampus,
acting like a "Control-Z" for memories.
"Control-Z"?
Like an undo command on a computer.
Oh.
Well, I was gonna try the new version
on my latest test subject,
but then I was worried
it might melt his brain.
Axel.
No, it's Tesla, actually.
He looks more like an Indiana to me.
No, he's Axel.
You gave me that little
guy for Christmas.
You haven't been running
any tests on him, have you?
What? No.
Whoa. Whoa! No, no! No!
All right, I think
actually for it to work
you have to shoot him in the head.
Why would you say that?
Hey, how many people
are gonna point guns at me today?
Oh, my God, you killed him!
You son of a bitch.
It works.
So, Mr. Rory's having second thoughts?
Mick's just a little
confused. I can control him.
Obviously you can't.
Yes, I can.
I just need your help getting
him back on the reservation,
before Thawne finds out.
We have bigger problems.
What if Heywood's only the
first of his old teammates
Mr. Rory's feeling nostalgic for?
I knew we should've killed them all.
It was a dangerous oversight
to keep them alive in any capacity.
Does that include Mick?
At the very least we
should've wiped his brain,
such as it is.
You trusted your buddy
a little too much.
Calm yourself, Malcolm.
We'll have Mr. Rory back
before he does too much damage.
Yes, boss?
Mick Rory's got himself lost.
Find him, would you?
Where do you suggest
we start our search?
You can track him with
this. I put a GPS in Mick.
I don't trust anyone.
Okay, on the count of three.
One...
two...
Oh.
You!
I deserved that.
Damn straight you did.
Hey, if it wasn't for
me, you'd all be dead.
Yeah, Mick, thanks a lot.
You trapped each of us
in our own personal hell.
Do you have any idea how
many toilets I've cleaned?
So many.
Amaya.
Sara.
Hey, dumbasses,
they have no clue who you are.
They work for Damien Darhk.
Oh!
Crap.
I don't like the way
she's looking at us.
I like the way she's looking at us.
Love the suits.
Get off my friend!
All right guys, time out,
come on. Come on, look.
I know this may sound
crazy, but doesn't it seem
like there's something
wrong with this world?
Yeah. Rory sold out the boss.
To throw in with you losers.
Losers? I'll have you
know in my reality,
you and I had sex, and we
both liked it very much.
Nate, not helping.
Amaya, look at me.
Tell me you don't recognize me,
like, deep in your subconscious.
Come... look, this isn't
how it's supposed to be.
Okay, you're supposed
to be heroes like us.
Okay. Allow me...
to demonstrate my superpowers. Okay?
Knock it off, you idiot.
The Spear took away your powers.
But it's true.
Nate used to be able to steel up,
and I had a robotic exoskeleton
that allowed me to shrink.
Oh...
These guys are heroes.
That is so great.
We kill heroes.
Aw.
One more person hits
me, I'm gonna punch back.
What the hell happened to me?
It appears that after the Legion
got the Spear and changed reality,
they kept us around as their pets.
Yeah, except for you.
You helped the Legion steal the Spear!
Speaking of, the Legion's
probably on their way here
to kill us. We need to get out of here.
Yeah. Gotta find someplace to hide.
Your mom's basement?
Really?
I pay rent, so legally
it's my basement, kinda.
Mommy makes great sandwiches.
The best. It's the perfect amount
of mayo/meat/bread ratio
that really gives it...
Focus! We need to figure out
how we can rescue the rest of the team,
and get the Spear back so we can undo
everything the Legion has done.
Except now they know we're trying
to get the band back together.
Except they don't know
that you've gotten to me,
- which means...
- You can sneak into the Legion
and pretend to be
Darhk's favorite chick.
It's our best shot
at getting Amaya back.
All right. What about
the rest of the team?
Well, the Professor and Jax are working
on some secret project for Thawne.
I don't know where the Englishman is.
Neither do I.
Mmm. I can only imagine
how those psychopaths
are torturing Rip.
Gideon! I've discovered
the missing ingredient for my recipe.
Rum.
And speaking of which,
I'm gonna need you
to fabricate me another bottle of it.
Ooh, and some nachos.
I will do nothing of the sort.
What?
You will do as I tell you,
Gideon, I'm your captain!
Then it's time for you
to start acting like one.
Now, sit up straight and show
your backbone, Captain Hunter.
Gideon, for the thousandth time,
I've got no way of getting
the reserve power back online,
and I've got no way of...
Of sending out any signal of any sort,
which means...
Which means that I am destined
to live out the rest of my days
right... here...
with you.
While you were honing
your confectionary skills,
I've been working on new algorithms
to redirect power from the
idle quadrants of the ship.
You need to focus on
boosting your distress signal
once power is fully back online.
Now, chin up, Captain.
I don't know if I can do this, Gideon.
I believe in you.
Now, let's get to work.
First...
I'm going to vomit.
And second...
let's do this.
When your minions bring Mick back,
I want to arrange a meeting with Thawne.
When I say "arrange
a meeting," I mean...
One between Thawne and his maker?
Cute. A little
mustache-twirly for my taste.
You're really gonna have to
step up your tactics, Leonard.
Yeah, you didn't think that Thawne was
actually gonna fall for
that fake meeting trick?
This is not "The Godfather."
Although we do agree
with your sentiment.
Eobard has to go.
So glad you both approve.
Which brings us back to
our original conundrum.
How to kill a speedster.
We found your partner,
and he's got himself some friends.
And where, pray tell, is
your partner, Miss Lance?
We got separated in the fight.
I haven't heard from her since,
so I'm guessing she's dead by now.
Ah, that's the thing about Sara Lance,
she never stays dead for very long.
Sorry, we underestimated them.
Won't happen again. We'll fix this.
- Let's go.
- Oh...
not so fast.
Yes?
I have a question for you.
Which one is your favorite trophy?
That's like asking a girl to
pick just one pair of shoes.
Oh, please, everyone
has their favorite kill.
You want to hear mine?
Her name was Black Canary.
I will never forget her. Hmm.
It was so... delicious,
killing her.
They told me that I'd done it before,
but I can't imagine it ever getting old.
The very first thing
I did in this reality
was acquire my magic.
I'm gonna miss you, Ms. Lance.
Having you around to
attend to my every whim
was too enticing to pass up.
Plus, it's so hard to
find good help these days.
Really? Now's the time
for a bad guy monologue?
You should've killed me
when you had the chance.
No better time than the present.
Amaya, the honor is yours.
Good-bye.
What the hell?
Shoot now. Explain later.
Damien, what did I tell you?
For what it's worth,
I thought it was a very
good bad guy monologue.
Everything's on schedule, Mr. Thawne.
You have nothing to worry about.
Hey.
What do you want?
There's just one thing
I don't understand.
If Thawne made this world to punish us,
how are your mom's
sandwiches so good, bro?
Her condiment game's on point, right?
- Mmm.
- She even had
gluten-free bread for me.
Look, let's just get back to the ship.
We don't know where the ship is,
or Rip, which means our next move
should be to rescue the Professor.
Speaking of which, what did
Thawne have you two working on?
Grey did most of the work, and...
I just made his life hell.
But from what I could tell,
he was building some sort of reactor.
He said it would burn
a thousand times hotter
than the sun once it's operational.
I like the sound of that.
Could be a power generator,
a particle accelerator.
What if Thawne is trying
to destroy the Spear?
Uh-uh, impossible. You
need the blood of Christ
to destroy it. That's why Rip
broke it up into so many pieces.
Unless he figured out there's
another way, by incinerating it.
But why would Thawne
want to destroy the Spear?
Oh, no.
If he destroys the Spear,
that means this
reality can not be rewritten.
Okay, we better get that Spear
before he can make that happen.
But even if we find it,
we don't know how to access its powers.
Rory does. You were there,
right, when they used the Spear?
Mm-hmm. They read out of some book
called the, uh, "Calibrick"...
"Cal"... "Caliber"...
"Kalablow"... "Kalabalos"...
Uh, something like that.
Do you remember what language it was in?
Aramaic.
Dude, how do you even know
what Aramaic sounds like?
"Passion of the Christ". Good movie.
Mick, would you be able to
recognize the incantation?
Yeah.
Hey. If they figure out this incantation
and we get our hands on the Spear,
I want you to use it.
I should have listened to
you back in World War I.
If we had used the Spear
when we had the chance...
I might have been tempted to use it
to change my own future.
Now... we've got nothing to lose.
Oh, Marty, Marty, Marty.
I know you've been working
so hard on this project,
and I wanted to come
by and say thank you,
but if it doesn't come online
in the next few minutes,
I'll have to kill you.
One... one moment, Mr. Thawne, I...
I just need one more moment.
There. There.
As you can see, the machine
appears to be fully functional,
though it may take some time
for the core to reach peak temperature.
Well, then you'll stay until it does.
I-I was hoping to
see my family tonight.
Oh, no. No, no, no, you can't
leave in your moment of glory.
You keep monitoring the core
and make sure the
reaction remains stable.
Think we got something.
We pieced together a passage
from the "Kalabros."
AKA the word of God.
All right, Jax, it's on you
to restore Stein's mind
before we get to the lab.
We gotta destroy the reactor
before Thawne can destroy the Spear.
- Yeah, no doubt.
- Now, remember,
you guys are going in
there without your powers.
Don't worry. I know that
place like the back of my hand.
What about Mick?
Mick's staying here.
We can't trust him.
Not after what you've done.
After what I've done?
If it wasn't for me,
you'd all be walking around like sheep.
If it wasn't for you,
we never would have been
turned into sheep in the first place.
We trusted you, Mick.
We can't afford to
make that mistake again.
Let's go.
League of losers cut you loose?
Nobody cuts me loose.
I'm done with those people.
What do you say we burn
this city to the ground?
Knowing Sara, she's
rallied the team by now.
Those idiots aren't
whom I'm worried about.
Relax, boys. Prodigal son has returned.
And he's got some news for us.
Isn't that right, Mick?
Our old friend Eobard has built
a device to destroy the Spear.
No wonder Eobard
doesn't want us using it
before he locks in his
own version of reality.
Which I assume means erasing all of us.
And your pals.
My pals.
They want to steal the
Spear before the deed's done.
I think you can see what
I'm getting at, gentlemen.
The four of us are no
match for a speedster,
so while Thawne is
fighting the Legends...
We'll grab the Spear from
under both their noses.
Exactly. The enemy of my enemy...
Is our opportunity.
The status of the machine, Doctor?
Please tell Mr. Thawne I'm
working as fast as I can.
I've powered up the
reactor. I just need to make
a few adjustments to the core.
Did you already turn it on?
I-I had specific instructions
from Mr. Thawne to do so.
Grey, we need to talk.
Grey?
Please, don't...
Don't kill me, I've done
everything Mr. Thawne wanted.
I'm not gonna kill you. I'm
just gonna make you better.
Grey, what have you done?
If Mr. Thawne wants to kill me,
he'll have to do it himself.
Guys, we got a problem.
You gotta get here ASAP.
We're at the building.
Just keep him there.
Ray, find us the quickest
way into the lab, now.
Look, you gotta believe me, okay?
This is not the way it's supposed to be.
Is this some sort of test of my loyalty?
Does Mr. Thawne even care?
Look, this isn't about Thawne.
It's about you and me.
I assure you, my... my
dedication to Mr. Thawne
has never been stronger.
Did you just press the silent alarm?
What? No, it's...
It's a secondary radiation
sensor for the nuclear core.
Grey, you are a crappy
liar in any reality.
Martin.
I can't talk any sense into him,
and he just triggered an alarm.
Which means Thawne'll be here soon.
Or now.
Well, looks like you losers
managed to remember who you are.
I should've wiped you from existence
when I had the chance.
Do you have any idea
how infuriating it is
to know that Merlyn was right?
Lucky for you, I still believe
in some fates worse than death.
Like me destroying the Spear
and cementing this reality for all time.
Martin.
The reactor is fully operational, sir.
This...
is the only reality
any of you
will ever know.
We'll never give up trying to stop you.
Well...
if it weren't for your futile efforts,
this wouldn't be half so sweet.
Not so fast, speedy. You
have something we want.
You need a lesson in how
to share your toys, Eobard.
Yeah, time for us to get
a turn with the Spear.
And do what with it?
Don't you understand? I'm trying
to protect you from yourselves.
With the Spear destroyed...
Bored now.
Get the Spear!
- Ah!
- Let go of the Spear,
and I won't use it to
turn you into a jockstrap.
Yeah!
Uh, perhaps not.
Ahh.
Give it up!
Oh, Sara.
Why do we always find
ourselves in this situation?
'Cause you keep finding yourself
on the wrong side of history.
Aah!
Nice work, Mick.
Now hand it over.
Mick, no. You already
gave it to him once.
You know what happened.
That was Thawne.
This time will be different, big boy.
Don't do this, Mick.
Mick, I don't care
what anyone else thinks.
I still believe in you.
Enough! Mick...
Hand it over.
Like a good boy.
You mean a good dog.
That's all I am to you.
An attack dog.
Now, that's not true.
Sure, we both know you're not
the sharpest tool in the shed,
but that's why we're partners, remember?
You're right.
I'm not a genius.
But I'm not one's dog,
Leonard. Not anymore.
Well.
I guess you can teach
an old dog new tricks.
Undo this mess.
I am sorry about your friend, Mick.
I know you loved her to pieces.
No!
Well, if you want
something done right...
Well done, Leonard.
You bastard.
I'll kill you all.
Actually, I believe that's my line.
Now, where were we before
I was so rudely interrupted?
Well...
I guess we're done here.
You know the really swell thing
about the Spear being destroyed?
Now you can't stop us from killing you.
Oh, please. Don't insult my intelligence.
Even at your fastest,
you're moving in slow motion to me.
Except they're not alone.
I say we go down fighting.
You kill one of us, we kill all of you.
For Amaya.
Don't.
Even if you survive my men,
you'll never survive me,
not without powers or weapons.
And the truth is, I don't want
to see any more of you dead.
Not out of sentiment, of course.
No, no, quite the opposite.
But because it is so...
delicious,
knowing that you'll be
forced to live your lives
in a reality that I...
Well, that we created.
You will walk this world knowing
that something isn't quite right,
that for all your trying
you only made things worse,
and no one will ever believe
you when you tell them
about all the sacrifices you made
and how close you came to being Legends.
Now, that sounds like a
fitting punishment to me.
What do you think, Professor Stein?
I don't care what you do to them,
as long as I never have
to see Mr. Jackson again.
Ah.
Fair enough.
You're free to go.
You're just gonna let them walk?
Be glad I'm letting you
and your fellow traitors do the same.
And the next time any of you get
what you think is a smart idea,
remember this grace.
And the fact I could kill any of you
in the blink of an eye.
My mom's not gonna be cool with that.
Do I look like I give a damn?
I can't believe that's it.
I refuse to believe that this is it.
Without the Spear, there's no way
we can undo any of this.
There is one way.
Time travel.
What do you mean?
We go back in time to 1916,
and we stop the Legion from ever getting
the Spear of Destiny in the first place.
No, we are not supposed to change
events we participated in.
And if we do, we risk
time folding in on itself.
Even if we weren't worried
about messing with time,
- we can't go anywhere.
- Or anywhen.
We don't even know
where the Waverider is.
If it even exists in this reality.
Well, if it does, there's one person
who knows where it is.
We just have to find him.
I've directed all available power
to the main navigational
controls, Captain.
Thank you, Gideon.
Now, I've started the
communications protocol,
and if I just splice
these two wires together...
Your distress signal will be broadcast.
Surely the rest of the team
must be out there somewhere, listening.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --