Time travel is real, and all of history
is vulnerable to attack,
which is why we must
travel through time to stop the spread
of these so-called time aberrations
and to erase their damage to history.
We are a team of outcasts and misfits,
so, please, don't call us heroes.
We're legends.
Previously, on “Legends of Tomorrow”...
- Mick has elected to stay.
- Why?
Someone needs to be
present to destroy the Oculus.
Get him out of here.
He traded his life
for ours. He was a hero.
Leonard. I must be losing my mind.
You're not riding ahead, Mick.
That's why I'm here...
To set you straight.
The amulet. Why is it so important?
Hand over the box.
I swiped it off Darhk.
You have something
we need. I would like to
- broker a deal with you.
- How did you manage
- to defeat him?
- I gave him the amulet.
It's a compass.
Compasses generally find things.
Have either of you gentlemen
heard of the Spear of Destiny?
It can be used to
rewrite reality itself.
- How do we find it?
- You remember
- Captain Rip Hunter?
- Cut!
_
Oof.
Gideon! What's our status?
The Waverider is surprisingly
not destroyed, Captain.
Though that condition
may not be permanent.
How long will it take to effect repairs?
15 years.
Well, that won't do.
What is that, Captain?
There are some things,
Gideon, I can't even tell you.
Initiate repair procedures.
Auto-repair engaged.
Shogun Ballistic.
Captain, that is the shut down code
for my primary syst...
Angels and ministers of grace...
defend us...
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
You're my best friend.
I love you, man.
What did you hear?
Nothing, absolutely nothing.
Though... Though if
I did, I suppose I...
- I might be flattered.
- I wasn't talking to you.
Perhaps you've had enough
to drink for for one night.
That's the point. I haven't had enough.
So if you weren't talking to me, then...
- Snart.
- Snart what?
I've been talking to Snart.
I've been seeing him lately.
You... You've been having
hallucinations of Leonard Snart?
If you tell anyone, I'll kill you
I believe you.
- You can fix me.
- Me?
- You're a doctor.
- Of nuclear physics.
- Same thing.
- Mr. Rory, I can't...
You can fix me, but you
can't tell anybody about it.
- You got that?
- Yes.
You got that?
Nate.
- Nate.
- Nate!
Sorry, guys. It helps me concentrate.
It's 3:00 in the morning.
Amaya and I were trying to sleep.
Not together.
- What are you doing up so late?
- Just trying to figure out
what the Legion of Doom
wants with those two amulets.
The “Legion of Doom”?
Darhk, Merlyn, and the Speedster.
It's from a Hanna-Barbera cartoon
I liked when I was a kid.
Sorry I woke you guys up.
- We... We weren't together.
- He knows, Ray.
Yeah.
Well, have you figured anything out?
Well, I carbon dated
the amulet that Sara
- took from Darhk in 1987.
- Before she gave it back
to the Legion of Doom, I'm guessing.
Yeah, and Gideon puts
the amulet's date of origin
around 30 A.D.
Huh, high concentrations of
manganese, copper, and zinc,
- which would make bronze.
- Correct.
Now, Roman Centurions put
bronze in all their metalwork
circa 30 A.D. I also sketched
the two amulets the
best I could from memory,
but they don't match
any artifacts on record.
What if they're not two artifacts?
What if they're one?
Shut up.
The Longinus Medallion.
Huh.
Longinus is the name
generally associated
with the Roman Centurion who
pierced the side of Christ
during the Crucifixion.
Yeah, he was blind and
got the blood of Jesus
in his eyes, and then
he could see again.
- Look at you.
- What? I went to Sunday school.
Now that blood allegedly
got on the medallion
and empowered it and the
spear with magical powers.
Well, why does the Legion of Doom
- want the medallion?
- “Legion of Doom”?
- Yeah.
- Don't ask.
Well, according to legend,
the medallion calls for
the spear and basically
takes you right to it.
The spear is also
known as the Holy Lance
or the Spear of Destiny.
Hey, hold on, this all just sounds like
an Indiana Jones movie.
“Raiders of the Lost Ark” is
the reason I became a historian.
- Did you know that?
- Okay, so the Legion
wanted the medallion so
they could get the spear.
But what do they want with the spear?
Well, the spear allegedly has the power
to rewrite reality.
But how's that different
from us traveling through time
and making changes to history?
Changes to history cause
timequakes and aberrations,
which we can undo. Changes
to reality, however,
those are permanent.
Great.
And I just handed them
over the medallion.
Whoa, in exchange for Grey's life.
Any one of us would have made that call.
Would Rip?
_
So much for sunny California.
Wh-we're done here, we need to go
to the 1600 block of Vine Street.
- Why, pray tell?
- It's where Frank Sinatra's
star is on the Walk of Fame.
I have always wanted to see it.
I'm not sure if that's part of
our little trinket's itinerary.
I said “when we're done.”
As far as magical artifacts go,
this one is frustratingly unspecific.
Actually, like most magical artifacts,
its ways are nuanced.
That's just a fancy word for vague,
and I'm getting tired of walking.
True, we could use some transportation.
Oh.
- Oh, wow.
- Afternoon, fellas.
Not so fast, buddy.
Wallets. Now.
- Just give us your motorcycles.
- Excuse me?
Give us the bikes,
and we'll let you live.
What are you, some sort
of comedians or something?
Or something.
That charming-looking
fellow is Cal DeVito.
Instead of being killed,
he's supposed to go on
to invent a new carburetor
for shovelhead motorcycles.
As far as aberrations go,
don't you think that's a bit...
Puny? Yeah.
Well, Gideon was going over
autopsy reports, and, well,
I'll just let her tell you. Gideon?
Both gentlemen were
killed in close quarters
with sezuki strikes to
the xiphoid processes
of their sternums.
A League of Assassins technique.
Weren't Darhk and Merlyn former LOA?
They must be getting
closer to the Holy Lance.
I'm leaning toward Spear of Destiny.
- I prefer Holy Lance.
- Can't imagine why.
Gideon, plot a course
for the point of origin
of the aberration.
I already have, Captain.
Hollywood, 1967.
Is the professor all right?
Uh, depends on what you
mean by “all right.”
He's helping Mick with something.
I don't know. He's being kind of
quiet about it.
Well, I hope he figures it out soon,
'cause if the Legion of Doom is here...
Really like how the name's catching on.
We're gonna need Mick and Firestorm.
Let's figure out what's going on first.
Look, all I know is
Gideon said the motorcycles
Darhk and Merlyn stole are here.
What, so we're just
supposed to walk around
until we see a sign that
says, “this way”?
Good idea.
_
Subjugating the world to
your rule isn't saving it.
You would create a
wasteland, and call it peace.
Do not misquote Tacitus to me.
I knew him well. I lived long enough
to watch civilizations rise and fall...
Cut, just stop. Cut, please.
All right, cut.
And everyone take five.
I just need to... think.
George.
What do I do?
- I mean, it wasn't that bad.
- What?
You saw him. I just can't seem
to get Peter to bring
any menace to the part.
- I may need to recast.
- No, no, no.
You don't have time to recast, okay?
Your thesis film is due
in less than a month.
I know, I know, but a film is only
as good as its villain,
and I have an antagonist
who is as threatening as a wiener dog.
Rip Hunter.
No, I'm the director.
Rip's being played
by Adam Glassman. He's
probably at craft services.
It's nice to see your reputation
for dry humor is well-earned.
You see, this is what I am talking about.
You guys are good.
Yeah, these are...
These are great props.
Did you make these yourself?
Hey, we are on something of a clock here.
Oh, my God. It's Rip.
Don't worry. We got you, Rip.
Who the hell are you guys?
We don't have time for this.
Get out of here. Save yourself.
- No, what about you?
- I can't leave
my film in there.
Get out of here, man! No film is worth
losing your life!
Get Rip out of here.
Hey, come on, we gotta go.
Get... away... from... me.
What the hell, man?
Fall back.
- Stay right there!
- Hands! Hands!
Freeze! Don't move!
- Hey.
- Whoa, where do you think
- you're going?
- Uh, my movie's inside.
- These lunatics just showed up.
- Do you know these people?
- No, no, no, I...
- Against the wall, long hair.
What? No, but my movie...
Can wait. You're under arrest.
What? Oh, my God, oh, my God.
Well, that went apocalyptically awful.
I got Nate and Amaya researching where
the police took Rip. We'll
spring him, and then...
We'll find out what the
hell is going on with him.
Dude tried to bludgeon me
with this... non-lethal weapon.
Look, we don't know
how long he was in 1967.
He could be suffering from time drift,
which is why he doesn't remember us.
The question is how?
Well, he could have
time-scattered himself
like he did with us.
Nah, he sent us his final
message after scattering us.
He wouldn't have been able
to use it for a second time.
Well, he got here somehow
and so did Darhk and Merlyn.
- The Legion of Doom.
- I'm not calling them that.
- Okay.
- But if they came to 1967
looking for Rip, that means...
The medallion must have led them there.
Rip has the Spear of Destiny.
We gotta bust him out of jail
before they get to him first.
And ever since, I've had...
the fear of giant toads.
Mr. Rory, while I appreciate
the thoroughness of insights,
perhaps we could focus
on the issue at hand.
I thought shrinks liked mommy talk.
I'm not a shr...
You know, I think I've
heard enough on that subject.
Now, when did you first
encounter the apparition?
The ghost of Mr. Snart,
when did he first appear?
Back in Chicago.
Can you remember anything specific?
Something that might
have triggered the vision?
He said something
about setting me straight.
Why do you think he'd say that?
I don't know. Maybe he's...
Captain, hello.
How... What can we do for you?
It's Rip. Here's here in 1967.
That's astonishing. How?
We don't know, but Damien Darhk
and Malcolm Merlyn are after him,
which means you two
cannot sit this one out.
Of course, my apologies.
I was just helping
Mr. Rory with his... migraine.
Yes, I... I have a very bad headache.
Well, you're gonna have to suck it up,
'cause I need your help
breaking Rip out of jail.
What's he doing in prison?
And how do you plan on breaking him out?
It involves you playing a shrink.
Do you think you can do it?
- If I must.
- Great.
Good day.
Can I help you?
Yes, I believe you have
one of my patients in custody.
Name?
His name...
Gideon, a little help?
According to his mug shot, he
was booked as “Phil Gasmer”"
Phillip Gasmer.
It's imperative that he be released
into my custody immediately.
He suffers from
delusions of being pursued
by futuristic spacemen.
Oh, yeah. That guy.
This way.
Astonishing. It's really you.
Yeah, it's me. Who are you?
I'm your doctor, Mr. Gasmer.
I'm here to take care of you.
I have never laid eyes
on you before in my life.
Memory problems are
a part of the delusion.
I'll have to admit him.
He can't be treated here.
No, don't leave! This
man is not my doctor.
I am not crazy!
Hey, I know, I know. It's okay.
Look, my name is Sara
Lance. This is Mick Rory
and Martin Stein. We're your friends.
- Two of them are.
- You're one of them.
Help!
- Hey, okay, hey, hey, hey.
- Help! Help!
Listen to me, all right? Calm down.
We're here to help
you. You gotta trust me.
- Your name is Rip Hunter.
- Rip Hunter is a figment
of my imagination. Help!
Mick.
We've got Rip.
We're headed for the extraction point.
- Oh, no.
- What is it?
Oh.
Can I help you?
Hey.
Sara, you got incoming. Darhk and Merlyn
just entered the precinct.
Yeah, I see them. They're
blocking our escape.
There must be another way out.
Ray, how well can you fly the Waverider?
Thought you'd never ask.
Wait, you know how to fly the ship?
Sure do. I just have to channel
my inner Han Solo.
- Gideon does most of the work.
- She does?
- I do.
- Huh.
Where to, Cap?
All right, we're here.
Get to the cargo bay.
Ray, do not crash my ship.
You break it, you buy it.
- Get away from me.
- Captain Hunter,
- you must listen to us.
- Why do you keep
calling me that? Is
this some kind of joke?
Rip, just calm down, okay?
We need you to remember.
Your name is Rip Hunter.
You are a Time Master.
You fly the Waverider. It's a timeship.
Rip! Rip, just wait.
This cannot be happening.
You're... Am I dreaming?
- Rip?
- Ooh, God.
Did I drop some really bad acid?
- Rip, be careful.
- Why?
I'm hallucinating.
There is no such thing
as Rip Hunter, and there's no such thing
as a timeship.
There's a...
Get to the ship. Go!
- Let's go!
- Guys, come on!
- Quick! Get on!
- Let's go!
Well, Gideon?
I'm afraid the news isn't good, Captain.
A deep scan reveals
that Captain Hunter's
neural architecture has
been completely restructured.
His limbic system reprogrammed
with a new identity.
So it isn't time drift.
Rip didn't forget who
he was. He... changed.
Reprogrammed? The technology to alter
the brain at that level
doesn't even exist.
Unless Rip's brain was
somehow altered by impulses
from the... uh... From the...
- From the ship's time drive?
- Uh, yeah.
You're talking temporal electrocution.
As a method of time travel,
it's practically suicidal.
Does that track?
Uh, I'm not sure. Excuse me.
- What's his problem?
- I don't know.
Captain Hunter must
have shut down my systems
because he knew I would never permit him
to make physical contact
with the time drive.
For good reason. He could
have ended up anywhere
and in any period in time.
But before he deactivated me,
he recovered something from his parlor.
A piece of wood
approximately 0.6 meters long.
A piece of wood?
- The Spear of Destiny?
- Could be.
I'm gonna go tell the others.
I got an idea.
So this would be a new
milestone for you then.
What's your idea?
Why don't we use that thing
to see what's up with my brain?
I doubt you'd find the
results you're hoping for.
These tests are meant to
find neurological changes,
while my theory is that your visions
are the result of emotion.
You saying I'm crazy?
I'm saying you're feeling something,
and in the wake of
your partner's demise,
that's perfectly normal.
I don't do feelings.
Run the test, fix my brain.
Hey, what's up?
Sara asked us to find
any physical descriptions
of the spear that might help us find it.
She thinks Rip had it with
him when he traveled to 1967.
And she, um, also wants you to work on
figuring out, um, a way to reverse
the effects, uh, on Rip
since he came in contact with the, um...
Time drive.
I've brought up the
time drive's schematics
for you, Dr. Palmer.
Well, how do you expect me
to understand any of that?
Uh, maybe using one of your four PhDs?
- I don't have four...
- What's wrong?
It's like I should have
memories that aren't there,
and I should understand
what this is, but I don't.
Yeah, I feel it, too,
it's happening right now.
I'm reading this book about
“Santarion Long-inises,”
and it's just a bunch of words.
How long have the two of
you been feeling like this?
Since, uh... Film set.
- Mr. Hunter's film.
- Mm-hmm.
Sara had Jax go and
recover what he could find.
“Glucas.” Wait, isn't that what
you pretend you're allergic to, Ray?
What? First of all, my gluten allergy
is very real and challenging.
Secondly, it's G. Lucas,
as in George Lucas.
Wait. George Lucas.
How do I know that name?
Gideon, pull up George
Lucas on the historical record.
George Lucas, born
in Modesto, California
on May 14th, 1944.
Named Modesto Hartman's
“Insurance Salesman of the Year”
in 1977, 1980, and 1983.
- Three years, hmm.
- That doesn't seem right.
No.
Gideon, is there a version of history
where Mr. Lucas did
something else with his life?
Apparently this Mr.
Lucas is an aberration.
He's not the aberration.
The Legion of Doom
scaring him is the aberration.
An aberration that
directly affects our lives.
Okay, calm down. Take it back.
Gideon thinks that the Legion's attack
on Mr. Hunter's film set caused
this George Lucas guy
to quit movie making.
As a result, he never
made some movie about
space battles or another one about
an improbably handsome archaeologist.
And we care about this because...?
In the unaltered timeline,
Dr. Palmer sees “Star Wars”
as a child, and is inspired
to become an inventor.
Likewise, Dr. Heywood
chooses to be a historian
after seeing “Indiana
Jones” instead of becoming
a yoga instructor.
- Oh, man.
- Wait, so you're telling me
that because some film
geek drops out of school,
my inventor and my historian
are now essentially useless?
- Yes.
- Hey!
If the aberration is not corrected, yes.
We need to fix this now.
I fear you may already be too late.
As of today, George Lucas
is no longer enrolled
in film school.
There he is.
George Lucas, the man who inspires
both of our careers, supposedly.
- Well, let's go inspire him.
- Guys, maybe I should do the...
Hey, George. Remember us?
- Hey!
- I had metallic skin.
- No, no.
- Hey...
- No, no, no, no.
- Look, time takes
time to harden, and sooner or later,
we're gonna lose our
superpowers the same way
we're losing our memories.
If you don't make the
movies that you make,
I don't become a brilliant inventor.
And I don't become an
incredibly handsome historian.
I haven't made any movies yet, okay?
I'm still in film school. Or I was.
That's the point. If you
don't go back to school,
you screw up both of our lives.
We don't live up to our full potential.
And I do not want to be a heart surgeon.
And I don't want to
be a yoga instructor.
Okay, guys, like I
said, why don't I talk to
- our time aberration?
- Yeah, but...
- Shh.
- Stay in school.
I'm sorry about my
friends, they're just...
- Completely insane?
- Yeah.
But what they say is true.
Oh, okay, what... What that you guys
are from the future,
that you've somehow seen
a bunch of movies that
I haven't even made yet?
Well, actually, I'm from the past,
but that's beside the point.
Look, George, I don't care about movies,
but guys like them?
They do.
So before you get in that
car and drive back to Modesto,
just think about them, okay?
Them, and all the
millions of other people
that your stories will someday inspire.
The future of the
entire world is at stake.
And you're our only hope.
I've never actually seen
your quarters, Mr. Rory.
They're charming.
- Oh, my God.
- What is it?
Something unusual,
some sort of receiver.
Judging by its design, one sensitive
to gravitation-wave transmissions.
You're telling me I
have an antenna in my head.
Well, the good news is you're not crazy.
Oh, really?
So, seeing and talking to Snart's real?
Well, in a sense,
yes. Your former partner
was killed when the Oculus exploded
in a blast of temporal energy.
Now, if Mr. Snart was able
to bond with that blast,
the version of him you're
now seeing could be...
Um, how will I put this?
- Like a time-ghost?
- Precisely.
But what I want to know
is how did someone manage
to put a device inside your brain
without you knowing it?
You are Chronos.
The Time Masters.
They did some sick things
to me when I was Chronos.
I'm sorry, I forgot.
So what you're saying
is Snart's stuck out there,
blasted into a billion
pieces, floating around
in time and space?
A rather simplistic way
of looking at it, but yes.
- You're an idiot.
- Excuse me?
It didn't have to end like this.
- Mr. Snart, is he here?
- “Why am I here”?
Why are you here? You're dead.
What's he saying?
He's telling me I've gone soft
because I'm still on the ship.
Doc, Doc...
you gotta get this thing out of my head.
As I explained, I'm
not a medical doctor...
But I'm sure Gideon and I
can figure something out.
- That could work?
- In theory, yes.
Huh.
Groovy office.
It used to be yours.
Come on, none of this is bringing back
- any memories for you?
- Listen, lady,
I-I wish that I could be
the guy you want me to be.
“Rip,” but I am not.
I take it you two were... pretty tight?
- Yeah, he saved my life.
- Cool.
You.
You saved my life. I was lost.
You came, you recruited
me, you gave me purpose.
Oh, it sounds like Sandra.
She's the hero of my... my movie.
- That's weird that...
- What?
A female hero? Get with the times, lady.
Yo, we're all in this movie.
I mean, it's different versions of us,
but this is definitely the team.
Like on, uh, page 89, my character, Max,
- he saves everybody...
- Hold on.
You're telling me that this
burnout used repressed memories
- to write a screenplay?
- That's not all.
He's writing about the Spear of Destiny.
Which you had with you
when you time-jumped
- off the Waverider.
- I don't know...
- what you are talking about.
- Yes, you do.
- Come on, now.
- What?
I just made it all up.
The spear is the MacGuffin.
The what?
The thing in the movie
that everyone's trying to get.
- Well, where is it?
- In the movie?
It... It's in pieces. Rip
just has a fragment of it.
What inspired you to write it that way?
I don't know.
I just had this old piece of wood.
I thought it'd be a cool movie prop.
- Where is it?
- Uh, I gave it
- to my prop master, George.
- Oh, great.
George Lucas has the Spear of Destiny.
Glad you changed
your mind, George Lucas.
Going back to film school?
Definitely the right call.
We agree.
Neat trinket. One of the lost
totems of Zambesi, right?
Ah, Mr. Lucas, you have something
that we have traveled
a very long way to find.
A piece of the Spear of Destiny.
Where is it?
Lady and gentlemen, if you don't mind,
- hands up.
- And if you do mind,
we'd be happy to kill you.
- I'll cover George Lucas.
- And I've got...
- What?
- It's not here.
My suit's not here.
I can't steel up.
Maybe I didn't make myself clear.
Put 'em up!
- He was talking.
- Up. Hands.
- Shut up.
- They're up.
Thank God. I don't think it's here.
All right, Spec-y four-eyes. I'm starting
to lose my patience with
you. Where is the spear?
What spear?
We had a little chat with
the members of your film crew,
and they all claimed the
Spear of Destiny was a prop,
and that you, Mr.
Lucas, were its master.
But the movie was done.
I tossed all the props
down the garbage chute.
They were just trash.
But, but, but... Shh.
I have one question for
you, Mr. Lucas, and your life
depends on answering me honestly.
Where's the city dump?
Gideon, set us down as close
to the location as you can get.
Yes, Captain Lance.
And, while you're
at it, find Mick and...
Grey?
What the hell are you doing?
Brain surgery, what does it look like?
- It's down there somewhere.
- Good.
'Cause you'll never find it.
You're right.
You're going to.
I could be in Modesto by now.
Shut up and dig, George Lucas.
What kind of superheroes
are you guys anyway, huh?
I mean, sure, they have laser
guns, but aren't you guys
- supposed to have superpowers?
- Well, we had superpowers,
but, because you don't make
“Star Wars,” I don't become
a scientist, and I
don't make the atom suit.
Or the serum that turns me into steel.
I can't believe we're all going to die
because of a stupid movie.
Perhaps they need a little incentive.
Oh, agreed.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Oh, no.
What was that? Don't just stand there.
- Try and brace it with something.
- Oh, no.
- Oh, guys, I found it.
- Don't show him.
What? We are in a trash compactor.
- We're going to die.
- No, Ray's right.
If we give them what they want,
they're gonna kill us anyway.
-Okay, well, then, what do we do?
They're going too
slow. Shoot one of them
- to move things along.
- Which one?
Dealer's choice.
What was that?
This rescue mission is
not going very well, is it?
I'm afraid not, Captain.
Would you stop calling me that, please?
I am not a captain.
I'm just a regular guy.
So was Captain Hunter.
He had no superpowers,
unless you count his
courage, intellect, and honor.
Well, what would he do, huh?
Your Captain, if he were here?
You guys, we... we have to give it them.
- There's no other way.
- There is.
You have to become a filmmaker.
You have to make movies,
and you, George Lucas,
have to believe that.
- What?
- You have to make your movies
so that we can become who
we're supposed to become
so we can save you.
Your movies go on to change the world.
All you have to do is
believe in yourself.
You have to believe you're
gonna make amazing movies.
You have to believe it
like there's no tomorrow.
Say it, George. Say it out loud.
George Lucas, what do you really want?
What I really want...
What I really
want is to direct!
Ahh!
Ah!
- About time you showed.
- Where were you?
Always busy, gentleman.
And yet, never late.
So who do we kill first?
That would be me.
Captain Rip Hunter. It's been ages.
I was beginning to think you were dead.
On the contrary, for the first time
in recent memory, I am
finally, truly alive.
Oh, crap.
Hey, does this thing work?
Oh, screw it. Gideon!
Fire! Fire everything!
Go!
Hey, come on!
Rip! Rip!
- Hey, Sara!
- Rip!
We gotta go. He's gone.
- Gideon, get...
- Rip!
You couldn't have got him.
You know that, right?
Yeah.
Look, Sara, you can't
beat yourself up about this.
It is my responsibility
as Captain to make sure
that everyone gets back on this ship.
Everyone.
And I failed.
You call getting a piece
of the Spear of Destiny
and the Medallion a failure?
The Legion have nothing.
They have Rip. We lost him, Jax.
Again.
But they won't have him for long.
If I know one thing about you,
it's that you don't give up.
When you really want
something, you are unstoppable,
and God help anybody that
tries to get in your way.
We are gonna find him, and
we're gonna bring him home.
Is that a promise?
That's a prophecy.
How are you feeling?
Have you seen our mutual
friend around lately?
No.
That's because you took the chip out.
Well, actually...
You did take the chip out.
Yes, I did, but after
further inspection,
I discovered that the device
hasn't functioned in months.
It seems you've taken one
too many blows to the head.
So I am going crazy.
I'm seeing a ghost.
There is no ghost.
Leonard Snart truly is no more.
Then why do I keep hearing his voice?
That voice inside your head is your own.
If Leonard Snart is second-guessing
your moral obligation to this team...
But that's what I feel.
We all hear contradictory voices
inside our heads, Mr. Rory,
creating, what is known
in psychology, as cognitive dissonance.
- My brains hurts.
- Well, I'm sure it does.
The complexities of human emotion
can at times be mind-boggling.
What's this?
I thought you got your smarts back.
- It's movie night.
- Gideon checked the timeline.
It seems all of George's movies
are now part of history again.
Hah, I've almost forgotten how
to perform a median sternotomy.
Well, I guess I'll just go back to being
a billionaire inventor with four PhDs.
So what are we gonna watch first?
I mean, after we watch “Raiders.”
- Clearly his best film.
- Which he never would've made
if he hadn't made “Star Wars” first.
Oh, wait, this one sounds cute.
It's called “Howard the Duck”"
No!
Okay, maybe movie night
wasn't such a good idea.
Maybe you're right.
After all, we did just lose Rip.
I know Nate and I never
really got to know Rip,
but we know how much he
means to the rest of you.
- Yeah.
- Might I offer my opinion?
Fire away.
I believe Captain Hunter would want you
to enjoy yourselves tonight.
All right, then. Dim the lights.
Gideon, pick the movie.
We'll watch “Raiders” after.
- Then “Empire.”
- Then “Last Crusade.”
Get comfy. It's gonna be a long night.
Uh...
hello?
Hello?
Is anybody there?
Hey, man.
Welcome, Captain Hunter.
Right. You know I was bluffing, right?
I am not actually Rip Hunter.
My name is Phil. I am
a full-time film student
and part-time recreational drug user.
Seriously regretting the latter.
Oh, I know exactly who you are.
I know that you're one of the protectors
of the Spear of Destiny,
and I know that you know
where the other pieces are hidden.
I-I don't know anything.
I-I-I-I swear.
I am not Rip Hunter!
I am...
nobody. I...
I can't believe this is happening to me.
You're gonna torture me, aren't you?
Oh, I'm not gonna
torture you, Mr. Hunter.
No?
No.
They are.
No, please, please. Please, please.
Please, let me go!
Let me go!
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --