Dang it.
Man, some days
rewriting history to eradicate
any notion of rebellion
and free will is hard.
Yeah.
You ever wondered
if what we're doing is, like, wrong?
How could it be wrong?
The Fates give everyone food,
and shelter, and television.
You don't want a world that looks
like these history books, do you?
Right. Right, the Fates be praised.
Just doesn't feel quite right.
Geoffrey Burch.
I am Atropos, the Thread Cutter.
Atropos is calling you.
Great.
Your time has come to an end.
Your thread is hereby cut.
It is fated.
Oh, I see.
Well...
Fates be praised.
Sorry, Geoffrey.
The work period has ended.
Return to your domiciles
for mandatory recreation period.
The Fates are always watching.
Relinquish free will.
The world is perfect.
The world is wrong!
Can't you people see?
None of this is how it should be.
He's gonna get his dang thread cut.
Do I know you?
You look familiar.
Do you recognize me?
My name is Gary,
but most people call me "Crazy Guy."
Stay away from me, you weirdo.
Yeah, they call me that, too.
The world is wrong!
This is your new home, little guy.
Another night, another bowl of mush.
Let's see
what's streaming on Fate Plus.
I'm back.
Hey, Behrad.
Did you remember
the gray mush like I asked?
I got the green mush,
the purple mush,
the sticky mush, the slimy mush
and I forgot the gray mush.
- You forgot the gray mush?
- I forgot the gray mush.
Behrad, you're so dumb.
- They're the ultimate buds
- And they're fated to have some fun
Momma needs her Ultimate Buds.
The oven's taking forever to preheat
and the mush is still cold.
My boss is gonna be here
in 30 minutes.
Or maybe she'll be early.
- Nate!
- Nate.
I don't know this Nate you speak off.
Me name is Robin
of Loxley of Starling City.
Why?
I got an audition
to play Robin Hood in Arrow,
a show about a vigilante.
Sounds dumb.
If it was dumb,
why would I stop crime with this?
The gray mush.
I guess I got the gray mush.
At least the family heirloom
didn't get dirty.
I should go clean off.
No, no, no
don't leave me here with...
Nate.
Are you still upset about the time
we almost kissed?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I missed the kiss.
No, I'm mad
because you ruined the place,
and my boss
is going to be here any minute.
What's that thing doing?
I don't know.
It's never done that before.
I say don't touch it.
Right.
But on the other hand, why not?
This show's off the rails.
There's no ghost in Ultimate Buds.
Nate?
Zari?
But how? You found me.
Oh, God.
- What was that?
- What?
Nate?
Yeah. Nate Heywood.
Actor and your neighbor.
Do you remember us?
I mean,
I always wanted there to be an "us."
Could I be more of a kiss misser?
Lot going on here.
Right, need to take
these off immediately.
Right, I knew the timeline
would be different,
and you might not remember me
but this is just bizarre.
Right, where is the Waverider?
Where's Sara and Mick
and John and the others?
Ava Sharpe?
Mona Wu?
Did they just say "Mona Wu"?
Sure. Sure.
All good questions. Great.
Hey, Behrad, your sister
might've hit her head again.
Behrad?
Is that really you?
I thought I'd never see you again.
Did you eat an entire Behrad brownie?
- What?
- Your boss.
Why don't you just stay
in this closet for a sec,
while we entertain your boss?
And your liver processes the brownie.
Welcome. I am Behrad, Zari's brother.
You must be the hot boss.
My, what a charming brother
the Fates have granted Zari.
Where is she?
Not in the closet, that's for sure.
Okay. Boss coming over for dinner?
Think I know what's going on here.
We're stuck in a TV sitcom.
Zari, do you have amnesia again?
You guys don't hear that.
The laughing?
She's hearing voices.
Sis, what do you think is happening?
I think you guys fought the Fates.
Fates be praised.
And you lost.
And for some reason,
you've been loomed here.
What's behind this door?
I don't know. We never opened it.
Never even occurred to us.
Well, we're about to find out.
Has that been here the whole time?
Coming, dummies?
Buds stick together.
Like glue.
Where are we?
We've been expecting you.
Welcome to Highcastle Abbey.
Lady Zari and Lord Behrad,
the second footman
will see to your carriage.
What happened to the first footman?
I've taken the liberty
of ordering you
some Persian treats
to make you feel at home.
Shall I ask the kitchen
to prepare a tea?
Sure.
Unbelievable.
John Constantine,
self-proclaimed nasty piece
of work is a butler.
Please tell me
you guys recognize him.
- No. No.
- Sorry, sis.
- You think this is another TV show?
- Right.
We were from a hilarious
yet heartfelt sitcom,
but now, we're stuck
on some stuffy BBC period piece.
With no obvious way to escape.
Well, it seems like the TV show
is adapting to our presence.
So, I think we just have
to play along
until I can get John
to snap out of it.
Okay, it looks like
we're some kind of aristocrats.
Nice.
That must make you our servant.
Wouldn't you prefer
wearing something a tad
more cheerful, dearest?
I would, if the prospect
of your matchmaking
was worthy of cheer.
Lord Behrad
is your father's closest male heir.
A marriage to him keeps
Highcastle Abbey in our family.
Well, how is he, Mr. Constantine?
Lord Behrad is,
as advertised, a foreigner.
Not you, too.
Lord and Lady Tarazi,
may I present Lady Natalie
and her daughter, Lady Astra.
I do beg your pardon,
Lord Tarazi, but is it customary
where you come from
for the valet to sit?
A thousand apologies, bro.
Mr. Constantine,
why don't you show the Tarazis' valet
to the servant's hall?
Happily, my lady.
Please have a seat.
You must be exhausted
from your travels.
I'm so glad we could find the time
to get to know one another.
Yes.
Before we marry
and you inherit our family's estate.
I'm sorry, did you say "marry"?
I have to go to the bathroom.
To the lavatory.
Don't leave me.
Do you enjoy hunting, Lord Behrad?
I like to play among the animals,
not slaughter them.
Well, that is
an unconventional opinion.
In this household,
servants should be seen and not heard
in the company of their superiors.
Which means
we should all be silent around you.
Is that right, Mr. Constantine?
Mrs. Hutchins,
trying to hold your tongue
would be as easy as swimming
through custard in Wellington boots.
There you are, John.
I do beg your pardon, Lady Zari,
but this is most irregular.
Right, I need to talk to you.
Alone.
They got the blue mush.
- Fancy kind.
- Yum.
How may I assist you, my lady?
All right, listen to me.
You are not some buttoned-up butler.
You are a cynical, chain-smoking,
master of the occult.
You have an apprentice named Gary,
and you are capable of great...
Magic.
Did she just say "Gary" now?
Maybe that crazy guy
isn't so crazy after all.
Can I confide in you, Lord Behrad?
Confide away.
Sometimes, I wish
I'd been born a man.
At least then,
I'd have a chance at adventure.
Your parents can't hold you here.
You're a diva.
What is a diva?
A diva is a female version
of a hustler.
Okay, let me get this straight.
You don't remember me or the Legends,
but you can still cast spells?
To my great shame,
I am at war with myself.
Part of me is...
seduced by dark magic.
That's the real you.
Are you going to inform Lady Natalie?
Yeah, maybe we should.
Please, please don't. I beg you.
You see, I'd be sacked.
You know what?
If you cast one of your spells
and help us escape this world,
we will keep quiet.
- Maybe.
- We will.
Gary, I think people
are trapped on the TV,
and they know us.
You sound crazy.
You were onto something.
The world's all wrong
and the cracks are starting to show.
Just watch.
In order for this spell
to work properly,
I must first know
where it is that you intend to go.
Can you send us to someone?
We need to find our captain.
What is your captain's name?
Sara. Captain Sara Lance.
The Jack of Wands.
Daring exploits
and dangerous challenges lay ahead.
- Great.
- I do hope this works.
I shall be glad to be rid of you.
Actually, John,
we really need you to come with us.
Amusing joke, my lady,
but I will never desert my post.
I tried to stop her.
Mr. Constantine, I have made
the most wonderful decision.
I'm moving to London.
London?
What about Highcastle?
And your mother?
I am a diva.
My bad.
Everyone who wants to leave, link up.
Where are we going?
Lady Astra, I beg you,
please step away.
To live a life that I love,
I must know the world
outside these walls.
Lady Astra, I must insist.
Where did they go?
Did she say "Captain Lance"?
From Star Trip?
We have to get
into Clotho Productions
and find out what's going on.
Officer Maala, report.
It's a Gromulan Warship, Captains.
Hail them, Officer Maala.
Or wouldn't it be more logical
to attack the warship
before it attacks us?
By that logic, we would attack
every ship we encountered.
Is there something wrong with that?
Fine, Officer Maala.
Hail the Gromulans.
Yes, Captain.
Can we kill them now?
Space, the fatal frontier.
These are the adventures
of the USS Faterider.
Its mission,
to seek out rebellious lifeforms
and disobedient civilizations.
And blow them up with lasers.
Captains, we've caught the Gromulans
with their pants down.
Charge the cannons.
Let's give them hell.
Engage the translator, Officer Maala.
I would like to talk to them.
Two captains
is an exciting power dynamic.
Charging cannons
and engaging the translator.
Okay, sorry,
do you guys not understand me?
We understand you.
We come in peace.
Yeah, now, prepare to die.
Wait, hold on, don't shoot. Listen.
None of this is real,
this is a fake reality.
Yeah, it's true,
we're all on television.
Watch, I can press
this plasma cannon button,
and nothing's gonna happen.
No, no, no Nate. No. No.
On the other hand, why not?
Oh, God.
Who knew?
That was bad.
Can't even look.
Well, I mean, it's an absolutely
remarkable vessel really, isn't it?
Officer Maala!
The crew has perished.
No!
There's no need to vocalize
at that decibel.
They're androids.
Right.
This battle isn't over yet.
Crazy episode.
Excuse me, my good sir.
My colleague and I are here
to refill your mush vending machines.
I don't have you on my list.
Lalo, is it?
You don't want
to be known as the guy
who lets the building
run out of mush.
Do ya?
All right, go in.
Fire laser blasters.
Permanently disabled.
Photon torpedoes.
Destroyed.
Hey, ladies,
permission to rescue you?
We can just beam you right over here.
Smells like a Gromulan trap.
Okay, you're losing oxygen.
We're going to rescue you.
We're taking over this ship.
Sure, that works.
We're your crew, anyways.
I know it's complicated,
but we're actually
from an alternate timeline
where you're our captains.
You are our crew.
May I interest you
in some rare Gromulan tea?
It is grand to see
lady adventurers in pantaloons.
What kind of Gromulans are you?
- Ultimate Buds.
All right, I know
it's hard to believe, but...
No. It makes perfect sense.
We encounter
this sort of thing all the time.
You're probably our crew
from an alternate timeline
and you've been trapped
in some sort of...
judging by your mannerisms,
late and early 20th century
prison dimension,
which calls the question
if we ourselves
are existing in a prison dimension.
It's perfectly logical.
Ava, I love you.
Clotho's control room.
Look, that contraption's
spitting out a script for Star Trip.
It looks like
it's being generated automatically
by some sort
of script-writing algorithm.
What are these?
Those are life threads, Gary.
Someone really
is trapped in these shows.
Oh, my Fates.
What is it?
Ultimate Buds swag.
We need to figure out our next move.
What we need
is to get out of this TV show...
Prison dimension.
We've been investigating
an odd radio wave transmission,
coming from the planet Kul-de-sax.
Welcome to my cul-de-sac, friend
That's a street that ends in a circle
Is that a song?
We don't know what to make of it.
This sector should be deserted.
Right. I'm going to make contact.
With alien beings? Are you mad?
Absolutely do not make contact.
Even I think it's a bad idea.
Okay, okay I won't.
On the other hand...
Why not?
Welcome to my cul-de-sac, friend
That's a street that ends in a circle
Children, I think the Fates
have sent us some visitors.
Let's be good hosts.
I'll get the door.
Look who it is, everyone.
It's the community helpers.
We're on Mister Parker's Cul De Sac.
Sewer repair?
That's actually kind of badass.
Could there be such a profession
as a firewoman?
Gather around, friends.
It's story time.
Why don't you take
a walk around the block?
Actually, Officer Lance,
it is a cul-de-sac.
The logic of this world
does not compute.
What exactly is the plan, Dr. Zari?
I have no idea.
We just can't keep hopping shows
ad infinitum now, can we?
We are on public access.
This is a career-killer.
Yeah, come on, sis. What gives?
Look, I don't know.
If you guys would just remember
who you really are,
you could help me
figure this out, but...
None of you remember.
Remember what?
That you're the Legends.
What is a Legend?
You guys were heroes.
But it's not because you do magic
or because
you have superpowers, it...
What makes you guys special,
what makes us special is that
we're just a bunch of...
misfits who are trying
to make a difference.
That is what we need right now.
She's talking about us.
We can be those misfits, Gary.
But how?
I've been sanitizing history
for too long.
It's time to spread the truth.
The Legends remember
who they truly are.
I wanna do right by Astra.
Make sure she was happy
growing up in a big house
and I could keep an eye on her.
Your mom never gave up on you.
You can really bring her back?
I can fix everything.
You don't belong here.
As far as I'm concerned,
we are co-captains for life.
Always.
Sara!
We changed history,
we changed everything.
Dude, you just came back to life.
I know that I love you.
Find me.
I remember everything.
I remember the Legends,
I remember our time with Behrad.
I remember both Zaris.
It's nice to be remembered.
Behrad.
I... I should be dead.
In every timeline
I shouldn't be alive.
Yeah, but you're alive here.
Okay, now.
Look, I actually think
I know what happened.
Look, I told Charlie to come up
with a way to outsmart her sisters.
Maybe hiding us on TV was that way.
Bloody Charlie.
A butler.
I feel violated.
What the hell, John?
Did the Loom
bring my mom back, or not?
I'm sorry, love, I don't know.
Hey.
Hi.
You found me.
I'm never gonna lose you again.
We did it, Gary.
You idiots.
Great Clotho. Praise the Fates.
What have you done?
We restored their memories.
Please don't kill us.
You're gonna ruin everything.
If only we could explain.
Silence!
I can't let the Legends escape.
Guys, love that you're back together.
And let's just say
that I'm processing
what it means that my best bro
is in love with my sister,
who lived my same experiences
in a different timeline.
But where's my Zari?
You took the words
right outta my mouth, mate.
Well, I'm sort
of possessing her body.
I mean, I love both of you.
- It's just...
- I get it.
She belongs here.
Yeah, but what happens to you?
Did someone say "problem"?
It sounds like being stuck
in a TV universe,
and suddenly remembering
two different timelines
is very confusing.
Maybe I can try to help.
I hate to question a living God,
but why are you doing this, Clotho?
Because the Legends
don't realize that
there are consequences
to disobedience.
"I know all about sad feelings."
I know all about sad feelings.
Sad feelings
Bad feelings
Make you so mad
You wanna scream feelings
Everyone sometimes has those feelings
When you do just sing this song
Mr. Parker I know you're trying
to help, but you just...
Repress, repress
I'll go back and repress
It's better to bury my feelings
Than feel as awful as this
Yeah, you're definitely
not Mr. Parker.
Where did you send them?
I just pulled the plug
on this crossover, silly.
You all have to go home now.
Sad feelings
Bad feelings
Make you so mad
You wanna scream feelings
Everyone sometimes has those feelings
When you do just sing this song
Ignore, ignore
Those pesky feelings are a chore
Obey the Fates
Eat your mush
And you'll be happy
Just like two ladybugs
Not today, Satan!
I am so sorry.
I thought I was tackling Mr. Parker.
What kind of mush
are we having tonight?
The "you gotta go" kind, come on.
Yeah, how did
we not hear that before?
After all that,
we're right back where we started.
Motherfater.
I wanna see the Buds break free.
Just try and make a move on us,
and I will burn you, you bastard.
John.
We need to go back.
Yeah, sure, love.
Why don't you really listen to her,
construction worker John?
I wanna see my mother.
You think your mother
will suddenly have
all of her memories?
What if Natalie is just a character
on a TV show, love?
I have to know for sure.
Repress
I'll go back and repress
It's better to bury my feelings
Than feel as awful as this
- Ignore
- Those pesky feelings are a chore
- Obey the Fates
- Eat your mush
- And you'll be happy
- Just like two ladybugs
We're back.
And it's Christmas time, apparently.
Yep.
- There you two are.
- Mom.
My love.
What's all this?
Do you remember anything?
About your life
before Highcastle Abbey?
I...
London? Magic? Dad?
What on Earth are you talking about?
Nevermind.
I love you, Mom.
I love you too, you goose.
You come upstairs
and change for dinner.
Astra, listen to me.
I know what you're gonna say.
She's not real.
We can stay.
What?
- What are you playing at?
- It's no trick, love.
Astra, look at me.
What have I got to show for myself?
Thirty-eight crap years of pain
and broken promises.
You wanna know
what my original sin was?
It was you.
Astra, I rail against the angels
and the demons
for being arrogant bastards,
but I'm worse than
the bloody lot of them.
And I thought
that I could use your innocent soul
as a bargaining chip
to save your mother.
Bollocks.
If you're happy here,
then I will spend
an eternity as ruddy
Mr. Constantine trying
to make it up to you and Natalie.
Is John Constantine really capable
of such a selfless act?
Would it be acceptable
to dine at half past 7,
Lady Astra?
Mrs. Hutchins
is running a trifle late.
Perfectly acceptable,
Mr. Constantine.
That's one show back on track.
My algorithm
should take care of the rest.
But I don't understand.
Why are real people trapped on TV?
The Legends, they're my friends.
And my sisters wanted them dead.
So...
I made a deal.
Weave the Legends
into our streaming service,
where they help
indoctrinate the masses
and they could live.
I always thought of you
as the punk rock Fate.
I didn't have a choice.
Nobody does here.
But that's how it starts,
and then you get used to it.
Obeying, I mean.
Come on, we have to escape.
What's our course, Captains?
Sara, wait. Let's think about this.
What's there to think about?
We have to get back
to the real world.
I know, okay? Just...
In the real world, I saw you die.
Okay? And it...
It was awful.
And I just keep playing it over
and over again in my head, okay?
So, look, out there, we lost.
But in here, we always win, Sara.
Look, you're right.
Okay?
And that's why Charlie did all this.
A crew that can't die,
us beating the bad guys every time,
it's what we asked
for back there in the pub.
But it doesn't exist.
Ava, life is beautiful
and terrible all at the same time.
But if we're only living
part of it...
then we're not living at all.
Let's get the hell out of here.
Captains, I'm picking up
a strange transmission.
It's from your old enemy, Don.
Captain Lance. Captain Sharpe.
Old friends.
- He looks kinda hot.
- Mom.
What? I'm not dead.
That's gross.
So, that's where Rory's been?
It was foolish to think
you could escape my wrath.
Don's charging his torpedoes.
Should I raise the shields?
Hey, you... you said that
we always win, right?
What if the only way to get Charlie
to set us free is...
We have to lose.
What is she on about?
You left me.
You left her
at the center of a dead planet.
Yeah, yeah, yeah
just get to the revenge part.
As you wish.
Torpedoes incoming.
Should I take evasive maneuvers?
Negative, Officer Maala.
What if real people die
in the TV, Clotho?
You have to save them.
Torpedo impact in five,
four, three, two...
one.
No.
- What just happened?
- Did they die?
What did you do?
I canceled their show.
You idiots.
Have you any idea what you've done?
I loved Star Trip and my hair.
Wait, where are we?
And where are the others?
Darling.
But before we go in for dinner,
just open one present.
What's this?
I overheard you talking
to Lord Behrad earlier.
It's a ticket to London.
I don't understand.
I couldn't bear it if you sacrificed
your happiness for my own.
But, what about Highcastle Abbey?
Please, don't make me do this.
I can't say goodbye to you.
Darling, darling.
I'll always be here.
But you have your whole life
ahead of you.
Be courageous, my love.
Live it well.
Mr. Constantine.
Your ladyship.
Is Lady Astra
really leaving Highcastle?
Do I have to say it?
Say what, my lady?
You smug bastard.
We can't stay here.
Nat would be proud.
Do it fast before I change my mind.
(Foreign language)
John, you made it.
Yeah, just about.
What about the others?
Come on, Z.
You didn't live in a totem for a year
just to get stuck on a TV show.
I can't go back to eating mush again.
Not even blue mush.
Yeah, because no one should eat mush.
It's horrible.
And all the colors
are deeply unnatural.
And it has the texture of wet cement.
But, Z, the Fates said
we all have to eat mush.
You know what, Nate?
Screw the Fates.
Those imbeciles can't do this.
They'll inspire an insurrection.
- They're gonna get themselves
- canceled.
For too long,
we've let the Fates rule our lives.
I happen to like mush,
but that's not the point.
Stop being so obedient.
Get off your couches
and take control of your lives.
So good to see you.
Hey.
- So nice to see you.
- It's so good.
So, hey,
that was pretty crazy back there.
We were, like, engaged.
It's a good thing
we're not brainwashed anymore.
Great. Out of the TV show,
still in heels.
You morons!
You just couldn't leave it alone,
could you?
I gave you everything
that you wanted.
You stuck us on TV.
I brought Sara
and Behrad back to life.
Mick, I made you a criminal again.
It's just like you wanted.
I even gave Astra a happy
childhood for you, John-o.
Yeah, bollocks. You just used us
to keep people under control.
It's better that, than you lot dead.
I still have your life threads.
I can put the shows back on air,
I'll do rewrites.
Behrad, you want the old Zari back?
I can do that. Look.
Behrad, is that really you?
You're alive.
- What's happening?
- Yeah, it's like a Zari clone.
I totally get it.
Wait, what? Two sisters?
Yeah, this is weird.
Good weird.
(Foreign language)
It's really you.
Charlie, you can't bribe us
into taking the blue pill.
I'm not bribing, I'm begging.
My sisters will kill you.
That's for sure.
Yeah, well, we'll take our chances.
Lita's out there somewhere.
I'm not staying here.
Let's get out of here.
Yeah, so long, Charlie.
Wait, just accept your fates.
Don't walk out that door.
On the other hand, why not?
They're free.
Then I can't help them anymore.