SARA: Time travel is real
and all of history is vulnerable
to attack,
which is why we must travel through time
to stop the spread of these so-called
Time Aberrations
and erase their damage to history.
We are a team of outcasts and misfits,
so please don't call us heroes,
we're something else.
We're legends.
PROFESSOR STEIN: Previously,
on Legends of Tomorrow...
You're back. (LAUGHS)
I love you, Dad.
When I last left 2016,
that young woman did not exist.
I do not want to lose my daughter.
This amulet looks a lot
like the one we recovered off the Nazis.
There's got to be a connection.
And we know that Damien Darhk
and this speedster
are willing to kill for it.
(CRYING)
Mr. Capone,
it's a pleasure to make your acquaintance.
I canceled tickets to the opera,
'cause I heard
there was new players in town.
No one told me it was Halloween.
- (ALL CHUCKLING)
- Well, it's more like... Christmas.
I like that. That's very good.
See, my associate and I
have come with a proposition.
We've seen how you run your empire
and we're impressed.
- But there's room for improvement.
- We'd like to offer our services.
I got a better idea.
How about I show you how business
is done in my town?
(EOBARD SIGHING)
You or me?
- Oh, I've got...
- (MEN GRUNTING)
This.
By now you've probably surmised,
that my friend and I aren't
from around here.
- What do you freaks want?
- To help.
I thought...
Did I not make that perfectly clear?
New enemies are coming to Chicago
and they will endanger your enterprises.
And you're saying,
you two can help me out?
Actually, there's three of us.
Pleasure to meet you.
My name is Malcolm Merlyn.
(GROANS)
Okay. (GRUNTING)
New suit's good but I think it needs
those modifications Cisco mentioned.
It's a poor hero to blame his super-suit.
(GRUNTS) Exo-skeleton.
Let's do this, I want to get the
kinks worked out before our next mission.
What's the rush?
I think I'm doing a pretty good job
picking up your slack.
We scientists have a name
for that phenomenon.
It's called beginner's luck.
- (BOTH EXCLAIM)
- SARA: Hey!
What do you think you're doing?
- (STUTTERS) Sparring.
- He's helping me calibrate the new suit.
Last time y'all decided to spar,
you wrecked my cargo bay.
- Yeah...
- SARA: Hey!
Don't make me come down here again.
(SIGHS)
- "Don't you make me come down here again."
Come down, I'm watching you.
Hey!
What is going on with them?
You don't have any brothers or sisters,
do you?
- Nope.
- Sibling rivalry.
Nothing to be too worried about.
- (THUDDING)
- (SIGHS)
This is why I'm glad I'm an only child.
Oh, Jefferson, I was just catching up
on some reading.
- "The Fundamentals of Motorcycle Repair"?
- It's a fascinating subject.
Of course, I'm also researching
the amulet.
Ms. Lance stole from Damien Darhk.
You know, you might be a genius
when it comes to nuclear physics,
but when it comes to lying,
you kind of suck at it, bro.
You were thinking about her again,
weren't you?
I can't help it.
Every day, I recover new memories of her,
each one, a gift.
But then I find myself worrying,
what if there's a car accident, or a fire,
or she could be struck by lightning...
Yeah, I'd be more worried about
what happens
when Sara finds out you have
a daughter who's a Time Aberration.
- She is not an Aberration.
- (SCOFFS)
The only reason Lily exists
is because you convinced your younger self
to pay more attention to your wife
and less attention to putting on a condom.
You changed history.
And one of these days,
either Nate or Gideon
or anybody reviewing the historical
timeline is gonna figure that out.
Not necessarily.
According to my calculations,
if Lily's impact on history remains
small enough,
she may be able to go undetected.
(ALARM BEEPING)
GIDEON: Excuse me, but Dr. Heywood's
seismograph has detected an Aberration.
You were saying?
- Who installed the alarms?
- That'd be me.
- I'm gonna kill him.
- We got another one?
Yeah, and judging by these readings,
it's a major one.
Is there really cause for all this alarm?
Perhaps the Aberration isn't as large
as we think.
GIDEON: The temporal tremors originate
from Union Station in Chicago, Illinois,
October 17th, in the year 1927.
That's fantastic. (LAUGHS)
I mean, I've always wanted to visit
the Roaring Twenties,
right in the middle of Prohibition.
That means no drinking, that's no good.
Well, actually, under Al Capone,
Chicago was a hotbed of vice.
There was illegal drinking,
gambling, prostitution...
Well then, let's fire up the tub
and get there.
Grab your fedoras.
We're going to the 1920s.
(AMAYA SIGHS)
I can't believe we're here.
What are you so happy about?
When I was younger, I'd read my mother's
magazines and I'd see photos of Chicago.
I never thought I'd see it
with my own eyes.
Well, keep those eyes focused on
whatever's causing those temporal tremors.
DR. HEYWOOD: Copy that.
That's Eliot Ness!
(SCOFFS)
He doesn't look like Kevin Costner.
What if somebody tipped off Capone
that Ness is a future threat?
Then his life's in danger.
Don't worry. I'm on it.
Here you go.
RAY: Oh! (GRUNTS)
Mr. Ness! Mr. Ness!
Hi, uh, you don't know me,
my name's Ray Palmer.
I have reason to believe that your life
may be in danger.
It'd be best if you came with me.
Mr. Ness,
I'm Sergeant Jones with Chicago PD.
We're your security detail on the way
to the Bureau.
Thank you for your concern, Mr. Palmer,
but it looks like I'm in good hands.
Okay.
- What just happened?
- Well, it's the strangest thing.
Uh, two cops just escorted
Eliot Ness to the Bureau.
They're not escorting him to the Bureau,
they're gonna throw him in the river.
- What?
- Ray,
1920s Chicago PD was the most
corrupt police force in history.
Almost all of them were on
Capone's payroll.
Did you or did you not see
The Untouchables?
Jax, Stein,
I need you to intercept Eliot Ness.
He's being escorted
by two police officers.
(COOING)
Grey! Didn't you hear Sara?
- No.
- Oh!
Oh, hey! Hey! Hey!
(GRUNTS)
SARA: What the hell happened back there?
How come you didn't stop him?
- I'm sorry, I got distracted.
- By what?
- Tell her, Grey.
- It's not the Professor's fault.
Ray let Ness walk right
into Capone's hands.
They were police officers.
And who's to say they didn't take him
to the FBI like they said they would?
Gideon, pull up the Chicago Chronicle,
October 24th, 1931.
Ah, yes, the day Al Capone originally
went down for tax evasion.
Only in this version of history,
he becomes something
far worse than a criminal,
he becomes a politician.
Al Capone becomes mayor?
Okay. I take it back.
Ness probably is screwed.
Well, let's find out where they took him
so we can un-screw him
before this happens.
(GRUNTING)
Special Agent Ness,
you're having a hell of a first day.
How do you know who I am
and when I was coming to town?
Some new friends of mine,
they whispered in my ear.
So me and the boys decided
we would get you a nice welcome present.
Cement galoshes,
very popular in Chicago these days.
I have a feeling these will be
just your size.
Oh, come on, try them on.
(LAUGHS)
Any luck finding Ness?
By the time you find Ness,
he'll be swimming with the fishes.
Mick, you beautiful genius, that's it.
About time someone noticed.
Gideon, set the course to
shipping harbor, Dock 39.
What makes you so sure he'll be there?
In the 20s, Dock 39 is where Capone
brought all of his enemies and
tied cinder blocks to their feet
and tossed them in the harbor.
It became known as "Cadaver's Cove."
(WAVES SPLASHING SOFTLY)
This isn't personal. I'm a businessman
and the Feds,
well, they're bad for business.
The Bureau of Investigation will
never stop fighting,
not until the fight is done.
(LAUGHS) Poetic.
I hope you wrote that down somewhere.
Welcome to Chicago, Mr. Ness.
(SCREAMS)
HEAT WAVE: All this for some booze?
- I like it!
- CAPONE: Nice get-ups!
Seems our new friends have
got some friends of their own.
Get 'em boys.
I'm going after Capone!
Let 'em go, we've got Ness.
HEAT WAVE: Is he dead?
Unconscious, he took in a lot of water.
Merlyn was right, they took the bait.
(ELECTRICAL WHIRRING)
GIDEON: Special Agent Ness has suffered
severe hypoxia.
It will take some time
to reverse his brain damage.
You can undo brain damage?
Why haven't you helped Rory out?
GIDEON: Who says I haven't?
All right, let's get serious.
Obviously, Capone somehow knew that Ness
would be the one to take him down.
When we were at the docks, Capone said
something about having "new friends."
We have a bigger problem.
I mean another problem.
This week, Ness and his team are
supposed to obtain.
Capone's ledger from his bookkeeper.
Now, the IRS' case against Capone
for tax evasion is completely
dependent on that ledger.
Which Ness can't grab while
he's lying here with brain damage.
Exactly, which means one of us has
to take his place.
RORY: That's a stupid idea.
It's pre-internet.
Nobody knows what Ness looks like.
Nate's right. I got this.
Actually, I was thinking I got this.
Well, yeah, I mean, if the mission was
impersonating Brad Pitt, you'd be the man.
But I think we can all agree, if anyone
here looks like a G-man here, it's me.
Well, we're in this situation because you
learned history from a movie.
All right, enough.
Ray, I'm sorry but Nate knows
more about this era than any of us.
What's the plan?
Okay, so if Capone's ledger is anywhere,
it's probably at his primary speakeasy,
The Chelsea Club.
So, Ray and I will go to the Bureau,
assemble Ness' team,
lead them to bust the place up,
grab the ledger.
Great, take Rory with you.
(COUGHS) Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Does this face look like a cop to you?
If this were a JSA mission,
we'd probably also send someone
undercover at the club.
Well, I'm not doing that either.
I'm done playing dress-up.
SARA: Fine.
I'll go to the club with Jax and Stein,
and you can stay here, drink your beers
and watch over Ness.
- AMAYA: What about me?
- You can watch over him.
What?
SARA: Sorry!
(AMAYA SIGHS)
Beer?
There he is.
- Special Agent Cole Bennett?
- Yes and you are?
Special Agent Eliot Ness,
this is my associate, Bob De Niro.
Well, I've assembled the team
your telegram specified, Mr. Ness.
I hope they're ready for some action
because they're going to get it.
Tonight, we're going to take down
The Chelsea Club.
Our files say Capone's got nothing
to do with that place.
Well, your files are
embarrassingly outdated.
We've learned Capone
has a stake in the club,
and furthermore, he hides a sizeable
amount of Canadian whiskey in there.
You fellas sure do know an impressive
amount about Capone's organization.
Well, let's just say we have
people on the inside.
- (PEOPLE SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
- (MUSIC PLAYING)
This place is quite lively,
considering we haven't seen
a single bottle of alcohol.
But Nate said it was a speakeasy?
Yeah, that's why it's
called a "speakeasy."
You gotta know how to ask
for the good stuff.
Ah... (CLEARS THROAT)
Excuse me, I'd like a club soda please.
One club soda coming up.
Here's what I wanna know,
why would somebody from the future
be interested in helping Al Capone?
Well, we're here to find out.
(GAGS) This is just a club soda.
You feeling all right?
Fine.
I guess I'm just surprised
you'd rather stay here on the ship
than be out there.
1920s Chicago seems
like your kind of town.
You know, when I was younger,
I always wanted to be a police officer.
I didn't care that I was a girl.
I just really wanted to wear a badge.
Cute. The bad guys
have all the fun, you know.
It doesn't look like you're having
much fun right now.
MAN: Oh, how the mighty have fallen.
RORY: Leonard?
(GRUNTS)
- I must be losing my mind.
- SNART: Of course you are.
Why else would you still be here,
taking orders like a well-trained puppy?
You're not right in the head, Mick.
That's why I'm here.
To set you straight.
Ray, Nate, what's your status?
DR. HEYWOOD: Be careful, we're coming in.
Don't get caught in our net.
What are squares like you
doing in a place like this?
- You!
- Jefferson?
(GRUNTING)
What the hell!
Jefferson, the speedster is here! Run!
- Nobody move. Federal officers!
- (CLAMORING)
You're all under arrest for violations
of the Volstead Act!
(GRUNTS)
- Man!
- Hey, take it easy, that's our inside guy.
Considering this club's
as dry as the Sahara,
I'd say you need a new inside guy,
Special Agent Ness.
Yeah.
What the hell is happening here?
Damien Darhk showed up, with
the speedster. They took Grey and Sara.
This whole Capone Aberration
was a distraction,
Darhk and his speedster pal knew
it would attract our attention.
But why kidnap Sara and Stein?
I mean, what could he want with them?
- Still trying to work that one out.
- Are you all right, Jax?
- I'm pissed.
- RORY: Let it go, kid.
There's nothing you can do
about the speedsters.
We'll see about that.
Long story short, Rip had a secret armory.
Me and Grey found it alongside future
Barry's message about the oncoming war.
This speedster killed Rex and
kidnapped our friends,
- we need him in the brig before dawn.
- Yeah.
If this weapon does what I think it does,
we'll stop him dead in his tracks.
Yeah. Well, that's all well and good,
but we still need to get Capone's ledger
back, otherwise history is screwed.
Since your last plan was a total bust,
I suggest somebody else
do the strategic thinking.
Let me guess, that's you. All right,
so let's hear your brilliant idea.
Well, I don't have one but it's going
to be better than yours.
RORY: Enough!
If you want to nail
Capone and Rex's killer,
you can't do it by playing a Boy Scout
or a historian or a policeman.
We do this my way.
Like a criminal.
(GASPS)
Yes.
The Ritz Carlton, it is definitely not.
How did we get here?
It appears our speedster friend
got the better of us.
- And he wasn't working alone.
- Yes.
Damien Darhk, a rather
predictable bedfellow for Al Capone.
And don't forget about me.
It's been a long time, Sara.
You look good for someone
who's come back from the dead.
Why am I not surprised that you
and Damien Darhk would find each other?
What do you want with us?
You have something we need.
And while my partners think
I'm a fool for trying,
I would like to broker a deal with you.
You have in your possession an amulet.
Give it to me
and I will give you nine years
of your life back.
What are you talking about?
Oh, maybe Oliver didn't tell you,
but I was the one who arranged to
blow up the Queen's Gambit.
(SCREAMS)
That was the day everything
changed for you, Sara,
hundreds of dominoes toppling.
Dr. Ivo,
Slade Wilson, the League of Assassins.
Losing your sister.
And you losing your son.
We both get clean slates.
Why don't you just ask your
speedster-friend to take you back in time?
Because Malcolm's just his errand boy,
sent to retrieve the amulet.
- Why is it so important?
- What does it matter?
I'm giving you and your sister a chance
to live normal lives.
To go back, maybe go to college,
meet a nice boy or a girl and settle down.
No, thank you.
I was never meant for those things.
And I know that now.
And besides, you can't just go back
and change things like that.
(LAUGHS) What? Why not?
Because time is sacred
and it can't be changed to suit
any one person's desire
without harming the lives
of countless others.
But you wouldn't remember any of this,
would you?
You would be blissfully unaware
of time travel,
of loss, of heartbreak.
You'd be happy. And isn't that what
matters most in the end?
SARA: Hey, Malcolm!
I'll take a nightmare that's real
over a dream that's a lie.
That was remarkably selfless.
Well, I had a good teacher.
Yes. Captain Hunter.
No.
I was talking about you.
What the hell?
Shoot her!
MAN: Come on. Let's get out of here.
Hi, I'm Clyde, that's Bonnie.
Get out of the truck!
Do you have any idea
who you're stealing from?
Yes, where's the truck headed?
Uh, 31st and Fort Dearborn Drive.
- Much obliged.
- (GRUNTS)
Hold that. (GRUNTING)
- Aren't you forgetting something?
- (ENGINE STARTING)
Nate and Ray?
Those idiots have done nothing
but get in the way.
Uh, guys, we're standing right here.
Whoa. Get in the back.
I can't believe Malcolm thought
I would actually take that deal.
You really weren't tempted?
Of course.
But we can't let a man like that
change history.
Imagine the havoc that it would cause.
Ah, yes, when it comes to time travel,
even the best of us can wreak havoc.
What do you mean?
Martin?
You have been acting weird
ever since we fought the Dominators.
What's going on?
It was an innocent mistake.
I was just trying to give myself
a bit of marital advice.
Never did I imagine
it would ever have an effect.
You caused an Aberration?
I have a daughter.
A what?
A full-grown,
human progeny
who I never even knew I had!
This beautiful, brilliant...
And not real.
At first, no, but
then I remembered.
I remembered the countless nights I spent,
pacing the neighborhood with her
stroller trying to get her to sleep.
(STAMMERS) The way my heart
melted the first time she smiled at me.
The distress she caused
her kindergarten teacher,
when she insisted on singing the
periodic table instead of the alphabet.
(STUTTERS) I remembered all of it.
- But none of that happened to you.
- But the memories
are real. (SIGHS)
They're a part of me now.
She is a part of me now.
And I love her.
Martin, you were the one who talked me
into not killing Damien Darhk.
And to not bringing my sister back because
of the damage it would do to history.
(SIGHS) I'm sorry
but my ears were burning.
I understand Malcolm tried to play nice
and offer you a deal.
Since you didn't bite, we're gonna have
to be a little rougher.
Do your worst.
You didn't think that I meant you?
(LAUGHS)
Oh, I fear with your League training,
torture, while fun,
would be a waste of time.
Sara,
whatever you do, don't give them anything!
- No!
- Martin!
Martin!
(GRUNTING)
Professor Stein. Am I right?
Do I know you?
Let's just say it's complicated.
I'm not going to lie to you,
this, um, little toy
usually leaves the subject,
well, dead, but
I've adjusted it so that
you should only feel a little pain.
(WHIRRING)
In theory.
(SCREAMING)
You're not the regular driver.
What happened to Vinny?
Vinny, he's, uh,
hanging out with your mother.
- What?
So, here's the plan...
Is for us to rescue the people
that got caught because of you.
- She's talking about you.
- No, I think she's talking about you.
Shut up! You're supposed to be partners!
- Partners have each others' backs.
- All right, Mick's right.
We can all agree
that we need to get Capone's ledger. Fair?
Agreed.
AMAYA: Sara?
- Are you okay?
- I'm fine, we need to find Stein.
(WHISPERING) You know,
for a homicidal gangster,
Capone was very organized
and he had exquisite penmanship.
- Check it out.
- Is that it?
Bingo! Let's go.
- Watch where you point that thing.
- Snart!
You shouldn't be here, Mick.
Capone's men might be from 1927,
but their bullets work just fine.
Do you really wanna risk your life
for a skirt and a geezer?
- AMAYA: Any sign of the Professor?
- Not yet.
Oh, sounds like a sweet little angel
whispering in your ear.
Problem is, angels always want you
to do the right thing.
And doing the right thing gets you killed.
I should know.
You want to stay alive,
best listen to the devil.
Get out now.
(ALARM RINGING)
Too late.
Hey, you found them!
- You guys okay?
- Yes, I'm fine.
- Let's get out of here.
- Yeah.
- Oh. On!
- (GUNS CLICKING)
(ALARM STOPS)
Oh, my God. You're Al Capone.
- That's Scarface.
- I don't think he likes that nickname.
I don't like when people try and steal
what's mine.
How do you think it makes me feel seeing
all you thieves on my property?
I'm gonna go out on a limb and say,
"Not good."
See, the doctor used to
give me these pills,
said it would help calm me down.
Then one day, I realized the only thing
that makes me feel any better is killing.
Time for some therapy.
(RORY ROARING)
(GRUNTING)
Oh. (PANTS)
- Thanks, buddy.
- Yeah.
- Let's go.
How'd I do?
You totally sold it, Al.
I thought so.
You sure Mr. Thawne ain't gonna be
mad 'cause we let 'em go?
Oh.
Quite the opposite.
Hey, Grey, Grey,
you're safe now, it's okay.
- Grey.
- What?
- Grey?
- Oh...
(STUTTERS) I'm sorry, I didn't hear you.
I'm a little discombobulated.
Whoo! Well, that was close!
But a win's a win
and we got the team back together.
Well, technically you and Rory
got the team back together.
And we got the ledger. Bro hug?
Do it! (GRUNTS)
Okay, I think this is all
a little premature.
We still don't have an ID
on the speedster.
Who has now added Malcolm Merlyn
to his team of time-traveling psychos.
And he wanted the amulet that
I took off of Darhk in 1987.
What would someone with a speedster's
powers want with ancient artifacts?
Perhaps I should take
a look at the amulet.
I may be able to unlock
some of its mysteries.
All right.
(RORY EXHALES SHAKILY)
Uh, so you didn't get a chance to kill
your boyfriend's killer, huh?
It's not vengeance I'm after, Mick.
Jfsjusfice.
- Right!
Right, well, for what it's worth,
you looked good tonight.
Being a bad guy suits you.
Thank you.
Um, I'm hungry.
What's next, Mick? Long walks
on the beach, just the two of you?
For a figment of my imagination,
you're really beginning
to be a pain in my ass.
Look, I get it. She's easy on the eyes,
tough in a fight.
She's just a friend,
the one friend I have.
Since my last friend blew himself up.
- Care for a little advice?
- From a dead guy? No.
Don't let the new girl rope you
into her death wish.
This whole "sacrificing yourself for your
friends" thing isn't as fun as it sounds.
(ECHOING) Trust me.
What the hell?
Sara, stay out of the library.
How you feeling?
I'm all right.
Look, I know you've
been through a lot, but
we really need to talk
about the Aberration that you caused.
Perhaps another time.
What were you doing in here anyways?
- Righty tighty, lefty loosy.
- I speak six languages, why would I...
Stein's about to kill Sara in the library!
- With the rope or the candlestick?
- Guys, I'm serious.
Somehow the speedster's
disguised himself as Stein
and he's turning over the whole ship!
- I'll suit up.
- And I'll get Sara away from fake Stein.
- What about that speedster gun?
- I'm already on it!
Martin, you've been acting pretty
different ever since Darhk tortured you.
Did they offer you a deal,
like they did me?
"Help us and we won't hurt your daughter"?
My daughter?
Sara, uh, Jax and I were just
on the bridge and, um... (CLEARS THROAT)
He wants to talk to you about ship stuff.
- "Ship stuff"?
- Yeah.
Okay.
I'm sure there's no need to rush off.
Jax can wait.
Since when do you call him "Jax"?
Actually, it's pretty urgent
and we should go now.
Okay.
(GRUNTING)
(GROANS AND PANTS)
A speedster weapon. Impressive.
Unfortunately, for you,
the effects are only temporary.
What did you do with Stein?
Oh, I wouldn't waste my energy
worrying about him right now.
Whatever you're gonna do, do it now.
In a rush to die, are we?
I wasn't talking to you.
He's headed towards the bridge,
come on.
No, no, no, no, no.
(PANTS)
What the hell is he doing in there?
GIDEON: Cloaking shield disengaged.
That's not good.
Cargo bay door now opening.
That is definitely not good.
Tear the ship apart,
kill anyone you find.
The speedster just locked himself
inside the bridge.
Great, so we've got him trapped.
(SCOFFS) Call me an optimist.
And by the sound of it,
he's letting his buddies onto the ship.
(GUNSHOTS)
Guys! Could use a little help here.
Okay, Nate and I
will help Sara hold them off.
- I'll guard Ness.
- What about the speedster?
Well, he's after the amulet so all we have
to do is just keep him in the bridge...
What are you doing?
Capone's men are taking over the ship!
We got bigger fish to fry, honey.
Rex's killer.
He's tossing the ship.
He is looking for the amulet.
It's only going to be a matter of time
before he finds it.
Then how do we stop him?
- What would a criminal do?
- Run.
Steel up!
- (RIFLES CLICKING)
- (BOTH GRUNTING)
Isn't that just like a thug?
Who brings a Tommy gun to
an ion-blaster fight?
Ah, yeah.
Hey, I stole that fair and square!
This belongs to me.
Surprise!
The League taught you well.
But unless you hand over the amulet,
I'm going to have to teach you
a few new lessons.
Those who cannot do, teach.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(PANTING)
I remember you.
You're here because I killed
that moronic leader of the JSA.
Mr. Rex Tyler, was it?
Don't worry.
You'll be joining Mr. Tyler soon enough.
(ELECTRONIC BEEPING)
(COUGHING)
Lucky girl!
(PANTING)
I gave you an out.
Not just a chance to survive,
but to live a better life.
I've already found a better life,
one without you in it.
(GRUNTS)
- What about your friend, Martin Stein?
- Where is he?
My dear, that information comes at a cost.
Don't look so glum, Professor.
You'll be in good company at the bottom
of this here river.
Thieves, snitches, do-gooder cops. They've
all run afoul of my organization, but you!
I've never had to whack
a professor before.
Guess I'm moving up
in the world, eh, boys?
(CHUCKLING)
The speedster,
how did you manage to defeat him?
I didn't, I made him a counter-offer.
I gave him the amulet.
I still don't understand. The last thing
I remember was getting off the train.
Everything else is a blur.
I wouldn't worry about that, Mr. Ness.
After our investigation, we concluded
you were kidnapped by an imposter.
Some idiot posing as you,
trying to bring down Capone.
The gentleman who was impersonating you
was trying to do the right thing.
Luckily, he found some useful information.
What's this?
Everything you need to know
to take down Capone.
If you look closely, you'll find some
discrepancies in his bookkeeping.
You expect me to believe that Al Capone
is gonna be taken down by tax evasion?
Sounds screwy.
Actually, it'll make
a pretty good movie one day.
You know, if this is the week
the Feds get Capone's ledger,
why does it take four more years
for them to take him down?
Because it's the federal government.
Now, that's the Mick Rory I remember,
always thinking with his stomach.
Shut up!
Who are you talking to?
Nobody.
Anyway, I thought I'd find you in here.
- That speedster hit you pretty hard, huh?
- I got a thick head.
- What's that? (CLEARS THROAT)
- A little present.
For keeping me alive and for helping me
almost get Rex's killer.
Open it.
I lifted it back at Capone's warehouse.
You stole it, huh?
You were right.
The bad guys really do have more fun.
Not that you're a bad guy.
I hope it was worth it.
All this for a kiss on the cheek
and a cheap bottle of booze.
That speedster could have
killed you, Mick.
What then?
I'd be dead like you.
(SCOFFS) My evil doppelgänger left
quite a mess.
It will take me weeks
to reorganize my notes.
It's good to have you back. The real you.
Well, thanks to your efforts.
Though I have to say I am a bit puzzled.
Professor Stein, puzzled?
Protecting history is our
team's raison d'être.
Yet you traded the amulet to our enemies.
A choice which will no doubt
have countless repercussions on history.
I'm starting to think that
maybe some things are
more important than history.
You know, you, me and this team,
we're a family.
A messed up one but still a family.
I might not be able to save Laurel
but I can protect this family.
And that includes yours.
What's her name?
Lily.
It's a beautiful name.
We should leave soon.
You're certainly in a hurry
to get out of 1927.
Not your concern, Malcolm, particularly
now that we have what we came for.
Well, now that we have the matching set,
do you care to tell us why we went through
so much trouble?
They are not a matching set.
In fact, they are not a "they."
They are an "it."
It's an amulet, in two pieces.
I knew that you were more than
just a pretty face, Malcolm.
Wow. It's a portable planetarium.
It's a compass.
Compasses generally find things.
Indeed.
Have either of you gentlemen
heard of the Spear of Destiny?
Yes, It was the spear that was reportedly
used to penetrate the side of Christ,
after he died on the cross.
And now it can be used to rewrite
reality itself.
- So how do we find it?
- Well, it's complicated.
But the first step is with the person
that Mr. Darhk met briefly in New York.
You remember Captain Rip Hunter?
Rip Hunter, stop where you are!
- RIP: Cut!
- (ALARM RINGING)
I told you idiots to move
these garbage cans.
Can we try
to get this right, people?
I don't wanna be here all night.
Am I talking to myself? Today!