Previously
on Legends Of Tomorrow...
I want to break up Firestorm.
If you guys are getting cold feet,
we can call the whole thing off.
It's time for Jefferson to claim
the power of Firestorm for himself.
This totem is my family's.
- Only my blood may bear it.
- And they do.
- That's impossible.
- That I am your granddaughter?
What does Darhk care
if we fix anachronisms or not?
That's the thing
about daughters.
When they see you die at the hands
of one self-righteous hero,
they really don't want to see it
happen again.
We're stronger together.
We know that. Darhk knows that.
Still nothing.
- What are you doing, Grey?
- Oh.
Since Gideon took Sara off sedatives,
I've been looking for a salient stimulus
to pull her out of her coma.
What the hell is that?
Salient stimulus, a noise or sound
she might have an emotional connection
to, that will wake her up.
Here. Would you like to give it a try?
No. Actually,
I was wondering if you needed help
with our other project.
Uncoupling Firestorm.
Oh. Yes. Yes, that project.
I've been looking into those equations,
and it's very promising, indeed.
All of Firestorm's power
will safely reside in you.
Well, you're the smartest man I know.
So, if anybody can figure it out,
it's you.
That's why the smartest man you know
is heading right back to the lab
to double-check his calculations.
Everything okay?
You've been hitting the bag
like it's insulted your mother.
And you haven't said anything for,
like, 30 minutes.
What's there to say?
I don't know.
Talk about your granddaughter?
And not the super-hero, either.
The psycho water witch.
The who?
Your granddaughter. I mean,
I'm sure she's really not that bad.
You just called her a
"psycho water-witch."
Yeah, and I instantly regret it.
I'm sure she's just, you know, confused.
Well, I'm not.
Kuasa and I will confront
each other again. It's inevitable.
When we do,
I won't hesitate to stop her.
Even if she's my granddaughter.
Okay. Good talk.
Way to get the emotions out.
I really wish I had
better news about Sara.
But she's still in the coma
thanks to Damien Darhk's daughter
laying her out.
Well, in the meantime,
we could do what we do best,
and fix a few anachronisms?
How about you drop me off
on an island full of beautiful women,
like Zari did with that Helen chick?
Rory, you weren't supposed to
say anything.
Wait, you didn't take Helen
back to Troy, where she belongs?
That's what the Time Bureau does.
But we, we do something different.
No, we do it different-ly.
Yeah. More messy.
Okay. If you look
at the historical record,
the Trojan War happens
with or without Helen.
See. No Anachronism.
How do you think the Captain would
feel about you re-engineering time?
We can argue about that later
because I know exactly what she'd say
if she wakes up
and finds us doing nothing.
We owe it to Sara
to keep doing our job.
So, where do we start?
Well, I was thinking we just
leave it up to chance
and my index finger.
Oof. Vietnam, 1967? Also known as
the height of the Vietnam War?
Gideon, what kind of anachronism
are we dealing with?
A Level 8.
Scans of the historical record reveal
redacted Pentagon reports
about a creature of unknown origin
attacking American
and Viet Cong soldiers in the jungle.
Dozens have disappeared
without a trace.
No way I'm going to 'Nam.
All I know is that if
American soldiers are being targeted,
I'm ready to do my duty.
This war is a little different.
Unlike World War II,
the military objectives in Vietnam
weren't so cut and dry.
Yeah. It was controversial. And the
reasons for getting involved were murky.
Well, come to think about it,
this team should be right at home.
Sole survivor of the last patrol
attacked is named Ryan Sanders.
He's supposed to be on R&R here.
This doesn't look like a good place
for American GIs to rest and recuperate.
Looks more like
they're just trying to escape.
Hey, I found our guy.
Mr. Sanders,
we're with the Associated Press.
We wanted to ask you a few questions
about what happened with your squad.
- I don't want to talk about it.
- We won't take up much of your time.
Yeah, people need to hear your story.
You could save lives
telling us what you saw.
It must have stalked us
for several klicks.
Took us by surprise.
Whatever was out there, was pure evil.
And it had a message for us.
Stay out of the jungle.
I hate the jungle.
- You sure this is the right way?
- Well, according to the field reports,
the last known location
of Alpha Team was right...
Here.
I should have stayed in Aruba.
What could have taken out
a whole patrol of U.S. soldiers?
Nothing good. But this missing squad
is gonna stay missing.
Let's get out of here.
I hope Mick and Nate
are watching their backs.
If what Sanders said is true,
they're in real danger.
Who knows if what he said was true.
He was clearly intoxicated.
Forget about him.
Think I found someone
who can tell us what's going on.
Hey, you've been staring at us
since we got here.
I heard you asking about the jungle.
It can be a dangerous place
even if you are carrying a machine gun.
- Well, we're journalists here...
- Eh.
Who the hell are you?
My name is Anh Ly.
And I know what's out in that jungle.
You've seen
what's been attacking the soldiers?
Attacking them? Come with me.
I won't just tell you what's happening.
I'll show you.
- Too many trees! Too many plants!
- We'll be back in concrete in no time.
Ah! Bugs! Flies!
What's going on with you?
You're grumpier than usual.
What? I'm in a good mood.
Is it because I made your boots too big?
Look, I forget you've got small feet.
And why would you not want
to come to Vietnam?
This place was, like, made for you!
- My dad.
- What about him?
He's here. 'Nam. The war.
Oh, buddy, you don't really think
you're gonna see him, do you?
There's almost no chance
we're gonna run into your father
in a jungle this big.
You said "almost."
Meaning there is a chance.
I'll buy you a six-pack
if we bump into him.
Hands up, pretty boy!
You owe me a six-pack.
No.
Hands up. Now.
Dude, what are you doing?
I'm Operations Officer Nathaniel Heywood
with the CIA.
This is my partner,
Officer Schwarzenegger.
We're here to investigate
the disappearance of Alpha Team.
Can't be too careful.
Sergeant Dick Rory, Echo Team.
I think it's in our
mutual best interest
if we conduct
this investigation together,
- find out what happened to our men.
- Actually, we were just leaving.
Sounds like a plan.
But I gotta say, your partner here
doesn't look so gung-ho.
Give us a minute.
Look, I'm sorry you have to see
your father, but you need to suck it up.
If it wasn't for
this time-traveling stuff,
I would have
never run into that bastard.
Okay. You know what,
we are changing this operation.
This has become Operation Tough Love.
Yeah. I'm gonna go
all Dr. Phil on your ass.
It's time for you to man up
and sort out...
Daddy issues.
I was going to say "unresolved grief,"
but let's go with what you're saying.
You wanna know
why I've never seen a shrink?
- Why?
- I don't regret killing my old man.
- What?
- That's right, pretty. You heard me.
I let my old man burn to death.
How's that for tough love?
Oh, hell no!
What kind of monster
eats my mom's pecan pie,
and puts the container back
in the fridge?
Gideon, who is the thief?
There must be a theorem
that supports the deceleration
of a subject's rate of fission
to individually power the thermocore.
Any insights, Sir Isaac Newton?
Or do I have to throw
an apple at your head?
Perhaps if you afforded us
a brief reprieve.
We've been working for hours.
And when, dare I ask,
do I get to return home?
You'll go home
when I say you can, Galileo.
What about you, Madame Curie?
You've been awfully quiet.
How many times do I have to
explain it to you, Martin?
There is only one way
to safely split the thermocore.
Yes, but doing so would result in
both Jefferson and I losing our powers.
I personally have no compunctions
about that, but Jefferson...
There you are.
My colleagues and I were just...
You didn't have to lie to me
if you couldn't find a solution, man.
Look, I'm sure it's not easy learning
that your granddaughter is in league
with Damien Darhk.
- If you ever wanna talk about it...
- What happened to men?
When did you all start talking
about your feelings?
Uh... Early '90s.
- You are unusual journalists.
- Tell me about it.
Most people run away when they hear
about a monster
grabbing soldiers in the jungle.
- Us, we run towards it.
- Monster?
What kind of monster
stops the fighting
between the Americans
and the Viet Cong?
He's no monster.
He's Ong Troi Moi, the New God.
Hey, what's going on?
Must be some sort of dead zone.
We are here.
Ray? Can you hear me?
Can't go a whole day
without talking to your boyfriend, huh?
I think their comms went out.
Don't drink the ground water.
It's probably contaminated.
Those are some pretty rough burns
you got there, son.
You get hit by napalm?
I ain't your son.
Yeah.
Do you know
what's on your father's head?
A little Frenchy hat?
That is a green beret.
President Kennedy called them
"a symbol of excellence,
a badge of courage."
- Courage?
- Yeah.
The only thing my old man was good at
was sitting in a chair,
a cigarette in one hand,
and a beer in the other.
And the only time
he ever got up was to...
No, Mick. Come on.
Come on. This is good.
This is good. Thanks to time travel,
I got to talk to my grandfather.
I got to work out
a lot of my father issues.
Stand down, stand down!
Is that you, Petey Adams?
What are you doing out here
on your own?
- You get lost, or something?
- Lost?
No. I've become enlightened.
You can be enlightened, too,
if you join us.
- Who's us?
- This country does not belong to you.
It belongs to Ong Troi Moi.
I don't like where this is heading.
You hand me that rifle, Petey.
We'll work on getting you a hot meal.
You will surrender to him.
Or die.
Get off me!
Put 'em down!
Bunch of damn traitors.
American and North Vietnamese
soldiers working arm-in-arm?
This anachronism is
even crazier than we thought.
And I think I know how they're
blocking our communications.
Hey, what is this place? I thought
we were looking for a monster.
You wish to speak to Ong Troi Moi?
I've got a really bad feeling
about this.
We would be honored.
We have guests.
They're reporters as you wanted.
I am Grodd.
Welcome to my kingdom.
You saw what I saw, right?
There was a gorilla sitting
on a throne?
He spoke better English than Mick.
Well, he's clearly intelligent enough to
trick these GIs to abandon their posts.
He's a monster.
He needs to be stopped.
He's turned these men
into his slaves.
Ong Troi Moi freed these soldiers.
He is the reason they are
no longer killing one another.
Yeah, it's a real utopia
he's created for himself.
I brought you here to help spread
Ong Troi Moi's message to the world.
You are only here
to document what you see.
Of course.
I need your shrink-ray.
Uh... Dislike that the name
is catching on.
Look, even if you can miniaturize Grodd,
there's still ten miles of jungle
warfare between us and the Waverider.
Yeah. Which is why
you guys are going to take down
the communications jammer
and call for backup.
While you take down
a hyper-intelligent telepathic
primate by yourself?
All I need is one clean shot.
You saved my life today.
Didn't wanna have to put you on my list.
These are the names of all the men
who died under my watch.
I keep them with me
to remind myself it's my job
to protect my men, get them back home.
That's my girl.
Gonna marry her when I get back.
Quit looking at her.
Maybe even start a family someday.
You want kids?
Why not?
As long as they never end up
in some godforsaken jungle.
I've seen things out here,
hope I never bring home with me.
I've never told anybody this before,
but I'm scared.
I don't know who I am
if I'm not a part of Firestorm.
But then, you've never had
any superpowers.
That's never stopped you from being
the most kick-ass person I've ever met.
Well, good talk, Captain.
Wow!
I knew Grodd
was a power-hungry tyrant, but...
He's one hell
of an electrical engineer.
The key is to jam the jammer
without anyone realizing it's jammed.
- Does that make sense?
- Perfect.
Where are we taking Grodd when
we return him to where he belongs?
Well, last I heard
he was in an A.R.G.U.S. prison.
Wait, he's just
another persecuted meta?
Okay, I know you're not a fan of
A.R.G.U.S., but Grodd is a psychopath.
And, well, a giant gorilla.
Ray? Jax? Can you hear me?
I think there's
something up with Mick.
He's got that look.
You know, when his eyes get all crazed.
I think the jungle's
finally getting to him.
Hey, man, you good?
Mick?
- What are you doing?
- What's it look like?
Uh...
Look like you were...
Burning your own skin.
But that would be
completely insane, right?
My whole life, I saw him as a monster.
Blamed him for
all the sick things that I've done.
But now, I see...
I'm worse than him.
Should've been me
that burned in that house.
Ha!
- You're a genius.
- Thanks.
- Sorry. I was talking to myself.
- Huh?
- Hello? Can anybody hear me?
- Nate, is that you?
Yes. Our comms are down.
No, no, no. They were jammed.
I just fixed...
I mean, Zari unjammed it.
Where are you guys? We need to
get out of this jungle ASAP.
Oh, no. What's wrong, buddy?
Well, when Mick and I started,
we were doing Predator.
Then we ran into Mick's dad,
and now we're doing Apocalypse Now.
That's why Mick didn't want to
come to Vietnam
on the off-chance
he'd run into his father.
Which is about as unlikely as
Marty meeting his
great-great grandfather Sir Stein.
Right. Or young you
befriending a time-displaced alien.
Do you people not hear me?
Listen. The monster/anachronism
is Gorilla Grodd.
We're stuck in his compound.
Did you just say Gorilla Grodd?
Grodd's displacement in 1967
probably explains that.
Guys, our anachronism just jumped
from an eight to a Level 10.
Gideon, what have you got?
The time line
is currently in flux.
However, the following headline
recently appeared in my archives.
It appears that
Grodd is using the powder keg
that is the Vietnam War
to somehow ignite World War III.
What?
Where's Amaya? We have to figure out
Grodd's plan and get out of here.
Yeah.
This is how you repay Grodd
for his hospitality,
by trying to kill me?
Let me help you
with that weapon of yours.
You think I am the enemy.
Look at what you humans
have done to one another.
Look at what humans did to me.
So, you're raising an army of humans
to get your revenge?
Revenge? No.
My only wish
is to help your kind find peace.
And how do you plan to do that?
Welcome to Vietnam, Mr. President.
Good Lord, it's hotter
than a preacher's knee out here.
You hit the nail on the head,
Mr. President.
Follow me, we'll get you
into some air conditioning.
You're planning to kill the President?
We are defending our home
against those who have attacked us.
Which I'm all for, believe me,
but you need to draw a line somewhere.
Grodd is only doing what is necessary.
Necessary for who?
He only cares about himself.
That's how dictators work.
I have lost both my parents,
my brother, my village.
Ong Troi Moi is the only one left
to protect us.
I know what it's like to lose the
people you love in a senseless war.
Makes you desperate.
But if you really want peace,
it starts with you.
Did you guys hear that? They're
targeting the President's convoy.
- Anh is weak.
- Grodd...
- Where are you going?
- You heard Zari.
To save L.B.J. It sounds like
the team's got their hands full.
It's too dangerous.
We'll go together as Firestorm.
No, we won't.
I got to do this on my own.
Please don't. I'm still working
on a way to split the thermocore.
Okay. I don't know if this is your
way of making yourself feel better
about us splitting up
by making sure I've got powers,
but I can do this without any.
And soon enough, I'm gonna have
to stand on my own without you.
We just intercepted
radio communications and triangulated
the enemy's position
to a base just east of here.
That's where they're holed up.
Don't know about you boys,
but I'm ready to go to work.
We can't let them get near that camp.
Okay. These yahoos are gonna shoot
anything that moves
and our friends are in there.
Amaya's in there. Do you hear me?
You fellas ready?
Actually, Sarge, you're gonna have to
tell your men to stand down.
I just received intel that
the encampment's in a no-fire zone.
Nobody told me about any intel.
Well, the intel was
on a need-to-know basis.
And you didn't need to know until now.
Can you explain the situation to my men?
Yeah. No problem.
Listen up...
I don't take orders from the CIA.
- You in, or you out, son?
- I'm in, Pops.
Figure of speech.
- What's going on?
- Grodd wants to start World War III.
The sooner your great nations
destroy one another,
the sooner there will be peace.
One nation under Grodd!
The U.S. President
will pay for his atrocities.
You don't have to do this
to get what you want.
She's right.
We're here to bring you home.
You have every right to be angry.
This world is cruel.
What was done to you by humans,
it's unforgivable.
But you must understand
that we are not here to hurt you.
And how will you bring me back home?
Unless...
Ah.
You're time travelers.
I will not go with you.
There is nothing for me
where I'm from.
- Only pain!
- You're right.
Maybe we don't take you home.
We don't?
We can take you
to a time before humans.
A time where you can live out
your days in peace.
And why would Grodd trust you?
Because I'm different.
There's been a breach!
All squads defend the perimeter!
- You betrayed me!
- No!
I promise,
we had nothing to do with this!
I didn't mean for any of this to happen!
You have to believe me!
Humans will always fear Grodd,
hunt Grodd.
But with your time machine
at Grodd's command,
there will be no humans!
Grodd will alter
the course of evolution.
He will no longer need
a gorilla country.
Because Grodd will have
a gorilla planet!
You better tell the Professor
he's gonna have company.
Who's in charge around here?
What in the world...
Get off of me!
Call in an air-strike!
We'll let napalm take care of
whatever the hell that was.
We've got deserters to deal with.
Raymond, I must have misheard you.
Did you say
Grodd was on his way here?
I sure did, man. He's planning
on stealing the Waverider.
I swear to you. If I die today
because of a telepathic gorilla,
I'm gonna be very upset.
Yeah. Well, then
get the Waverider moving.
Hands on your head, traitor.
Let's go. Move it.
- Amaya.
- Nathaniel.
- Shut up!
- Are you okay?
Yeah. Mick?
Mick. What's wrong with him?
I'm afraid he's gone full Kurtz.
- What does that mean?
- It's a movie reference.
Great movie, terrible situation.
They say life is the sum total
of all the choices you make.
As your misfortune sinks in,
maybe you wanna ask yourself
"What choices did I make
to find myself here?"
Today, I want payback
for what that monster did
to my men, my brothers.
- Excuse me.
- Shut up.
- We're journalists.
And we've uncovered a plot
to kill President Johnson.
We need to alert the proper authorities.
Shut up.
- See?
- He's telling the truth.
The President landed in Vietnam.
But we can still save him.
You're reporters. What are you
gonna do, question him to safety?
It's a little more
complicated than that.
But just trust me, okay?
We're the good guys.
Haven't you heard?
There are no good guys here.
Stop!
Stop! Stop! Stop!
Wait! Wait!
No, don't shoot! Don't shoot!
I'm an American.
You've got to back the hell up.
Son, I'm gonna be on you
like a duck on a junebug
if we don't start moving again.
Mr. President,
your life's in danger. Okay?
That roadblock is a trap.
You've got to get back to base.
- Step back, sir...
- No, no, no, no!
Mr. President, stop!
Whoa, Mr. President!
Don't move! Don't move!
Enough talk.
Time to pay the entrance fee
to this circus.
- Don't.
- What are you doing?
- Saving your life.
- What are you talking about?
I know what's going on
in that head of yours.
But killing these people
is not gonna bring back your men.
What do you know about anything?
Mick, you do realize
what will happen if you kill him.
Don't care.
This is insubordination, son.
I wouldn't have expected that from you.
- Well, you don't know me.
- Lower your weapon.
Lower yours.
I've got nothing to lose.
But you do. You get to go home.
But if you kill these people,
you'll hear their screams forever.
And one day, when you have a family,
you won't be able to
look them in the eye.
Because this day,
this act you're about to commit,
will be burned
in your memory forever.
- Why'd you do that?
- I always wanted to.
Route is clear. Weapons hot.
Okay.
You guys walked through a mine field,
and I'm pretty sure you're caught
in a Soviet trip mine.
But by freezing it,
you should be able to step away.
"Should"?
Okay on the count of three,
I want you to step away slowly.
One, two, three.
I'll be a damn humdinger!
Sounds like our Viet Cong friends
are circling in.
Okay. Well, we better
hustle through this minefield.
Follow my lead, and, uh,
if I don't blow up,
- path's clear.
- And if you blow up?
Then you're on you're own, sir.
- Well, that wasn't so hard.
- That's because I'm helping.
Is that your idea of helping?
I'm afraid
we have an unexpected passenger.
You're afraid?
- Follow my steps exactly.
- I wasn't planning on improvising.
Okay, come on, Mr. President.
One more step. You got this. Come on.
Where is Captain Lance when I need her?
Sara. What, were you
just waiting for the right moment
to make a dramatic entrance?
Are you all right?
There is no Sara.
What?
Only Grodd.
It appears that the Captain is
under some sort of telepathic control.
Really, Gideon? You think so?
I claim this ship for the New God.
Kneel before Gro...
Oh, how I do love proving
my Laws of Motion.
Please save that lecture
for another day.
Professor Stein, a U.S. military
airstrike is approaching,
and Grodd is still clinging
to the Waverider.
I have an idea.
Hey, are you sure
you won't reconsider?
I can get you out of here.
You can start over somewhere
where there's no war.
No, my struggle is here.
I realize now, my people,
they do not need a god.
They need a leader.
Like you said, peace starts with me.
Got some R&R scheduled
in a few days down at Eagle Beach.
You CIA boys ever get time off,
maybe I'll see you down there.
Anything's possible.
You saved innocent lives. You saved me.
Pulled me back from crossing that line.
Well, I've been pulled back from
that line a couple of times myself.
Listen, uh, if that kid of yours
- happens to be a boy...
- Yeah?
Never mind.
Looks like
Operation Tough Love was a success.
Yeah. Figured you'd want this back.
I don't need it anymore.
- Raymond, are you in there?
- Yeah, I'm in here.
Just trying to rebuild
the Molecular Hyper Compressor.
You mean the shrink-ray
that I didn't get to use on Grodd.
Yes, it took quite a beating.
Uh... What are you doing here?
I came by to say that you were right.
Well, you and Nathaniel.
But I'd rather you didn't say anything.
No, of course not.
I won't say a word.
- About what exactly?
- Kuasa.
This experience with Grodd...
He wasn't born a monster.
He was made into one.
And for all I know,
the same is true with my granddaughter.
- So, thank you.
- Yeah, you're welcome.
Well, I'm relieved you're all right.
Got a little close back there.
By the way, you were right.
I was putting myself
under a lot of pressure to resolve
our separation problem.
I just wanted to make sure
I had done everything I could
to keep you safe before I left.
But you're gonna be just fine.
You already carry the most important
part of Firestorm within you,
his spirit.
You're getting all soft on me, Grey?
But, for real, I'm gonna miss you
when you're gone, man.
Anyway, you said
you had something to show me.
Oh, uh...
Yeah, so, after I saved L.B.J.'s life,
I thought I'd get a medal, or something.
But he just tells me he's got some
top secret information.
And hands me this.
Oh, dear God. This is incredible.
So, instead of a medal for bravery,
President Johnson gave you a pie recipe?
Well, not just any recipe.
Lady Bird Johnson's pecan pie
was legendary.
The ingredients were a very
closely-kept secret for a long time.
Man, it's almost
as good as my mama's pie.
I don't know.
First Lady pie is pretty good.
This is a great gift.
Way better than a medal.
'Cause you can eat it.
Whoa!
What? You guys weren't gonna
save me any pie?
Welcome back
to the land of the living, Captain.
Gideon gave me
a clean bill of health.
Hello, love. But I don't know
about this bump on my head?
- Who's the new guy?
- Oh, don't ask.
This was quite an adventure.
Where to next?
Shut up, you fop.
Ah... Vietnam.
Crappy war. Bitchin' music.
Where is Grodd? Who are you?
Is that any way to treat
your number one fan?
Nuclear crisis in Central City?
Masterful.
Why else do you think
I'd pull you out of Vietnam
before you fell into
that napalm inferno?
Send me back.
I know you wanted a timeship.
But who needs a lumbering tin-can
when you can time travel
with a single thought?