Previously onThe Flash
andLegends Of Tomorrow...
- I love you, Jesse.
- I love you too.
Jesse's breaking up with me.
She told me she needs
to focus on herself.
You and Ms. Lance?
I think there's something
real there, she's special.
I'm guessing that's bad.
Those are tears
in the fabric of time itself.
The first totem bearers
imprisoned a great evil
and time is his cage.
The more the timeline's corrupted,
the weaker the prison
holding Mallus becomes.
Maybe these totems
are the keys to stopping him.
The good news is, we already have
the Air, Earth, and Fire Totem.
Death Totem?
The most volatile
of all of the totems.
Whoever wields it
has dominion over the dead.
We need to make sure we keep
that Death Totem on lock.
You thought I forgot about you.
It's okay.
Hey, I'm right here.
Here I thought you gave nightmares,
not have them.
First time for everything.
Want to talk about it?
No, I'm... I'm fine.
So, who's John?
What?
Soon as you called his name
out in your sleep
and I was trying very hard
not to be jealous.
No, it's probably John Constantine.
He's a Demonologist
that helped me with Mallus.
And he kinda looks like Sting.
And he's just a... just a friend?
Yeah, you could say that.
You know we did sleep together.
It was the 60s,
and everybody was getting wild.
The 60s, huh?
I thought I waited a long time
between partners.
The year was 1969, but...
it was, like, three weeks ago.
Three weeks?
Yeah, well, three weeks
before I had a girlfriend.
Did you just call me your girlfriend?
Maybe.
I mean, why not?
John's fun.
Oh, please don't talk about John.
Well, he is no Ava Sharpe.
Pardon the interruption, Captain,
but you're needed on the bridge.
Oh, come on.
Hey.
Morning, Captain.
Where's Mrs. Captain?
Ava had to work.
With all the new anachronisms,
the time tears are getting worse.
Yeah, I thought we were calling
them time cracks.
Hey, what happens
if we don't repair history?
Working theory:
time is frapped together
like a smoothie,
so instead of just dealing
with Julius Caesar in Aruba,
we have to fight off Genghis Khan,
a herd of wooly mammoths,
and a swarm of locusts
from the Old Testament.
And Mallus is freed from time jail,
so he could rule over
this giant mess.
So, worse than Flashpoint?
Is that what we're calling
the thing that Barry did?
I think it's something similar.
All right, enough hand wringing.
Mallus and his team are doubling down
on anachronisms, so, so are we.
From now on, we're going
to do our repairs in teams.
Where's Rory?
Wally, wait.
Nice robe.
Who dressed me?
Me.
FYI, Heat Wave sleeps in the nude.
Yeah, tried to warn you, kid.
As riveting as this conversation is,
Gideon, please.
So, Z and Amaya,
you take the Time Courier
to Billings, Montana in 1997.
The Mona Lisa is about make
a very special appearance
on the Antiques Roadshow.
Nate and I will pick up Einstein
in the Ice Age,
and you two are on the Jumpship
to find and return a dog named Laika
to the Soviet space program.
No.
Excuse me?
I'm not chasing a Ruskie pooch.
I could actually use Mick's help
reforming the Fire Totem.
Fine.
Nate, you go with Wally,
and I'll go get Einstein alone.
Are you okay?
Yeah, do...
I'm fine.
All right, that's it.
No snazzy send-off.
Mama's got a headache.
Even when you don't try,
you still got it.
My hypothesis is that the Fire Totem
can only be reignited
if it reaches Big Bang conditions.
Which is where this handy-dandy
cold fusion reactor comes in.
We will be two of the only people
to have ever experienced
cold fusion in action.
Can you even imagine?
I'm bored.
Wait, where are you going?
What if I need your help?
I... I just put a mystical
totem into a nuclear reactor.
Don't you wanna see what happens?
No.
Do me a favor, Gideon,
get John Constantine on the line.
I'm afraid Mr. Constantine
does not currently own a phone.
Because God forbid
he'd do anything normal.
It calls to you, doesn't it?
The Death Totem chose you.
- You're...
- You.
After you died.
This is the Death Totem.
It yearns for a new bearer.
Imagine all you could do
with dominion over the dead.
You could banish
that little girl from your dreams,
bring back your sister.
I'm no totem bearer.
You've conquered your demons.
You're strong enough to wield it.
Pick up the totem, Sara.
It's the only way to defeat Mallus.
The six totems
need six totem bearers.
Who else on your team
was born to wield death?
Wait, wait, so the Mona Lisa
was a self-portrait?
Da Vinci in drag.
Mick?
What, what, what?
Well, at least he's wearing clothes.
- True.
- Hey, Ray, we're back.
You read me, Schmience guy?
Gideon, where's Ray?
I'm sorry, Ms. Tomaz, but all of my
internal monitoring systems
have been disabled.
I've been rendered blind, I'm afraid.
Ray!
I can't tell if he's breathing.
I have a pulse.
It's smoking.
This just happened.
Whoever did
this is still on the ship.
Gideon, run a scan.
Dr. Palmer has suffered
a collapsed lung,
three broken ribs,
a shattered femur and...
Okay, okay, okay, we get it.
Just fix him and find out
who disabled your cams.
I take one lousy nap...
If I was capable of rage,
I would feel it.
The saboteur must be punished.
You stay with Ray,
Mick and I will search the ship.
Wait, guys, you don't know
what's out there.
Second thought, you got this.
Gideon, we need to reach Sara.
Is there any way to message her
in the Ice Age?
There's no need.
The Jumpship never left its hangar.
Holy mother of God.
Sara, what happened?
Sara Lance is lost to you.
I am...
Death!
Sara, I know you're still in there.
Amaya?
She can't hear you.
Mallus.
You've always secretly feared
you're a monster.
And now, a monster
is what you've become.
Sara, please, no!
Amaya, what happened?
It's Sara,
she's wearing the Death thingy.
The Death Totem, why would
Elvis' totem make Sara evil?
The totems work by amplifying
the true nature
of, of whoever wears them.
But Constantine warned Ray
that Mallus' power was inside Sara.
Maybe he's taken her over.
So, if Elvis could raise
the dead with a totem,
what could a former assassin
connected to a demon be capable of?
Captain Lance, I strongly recommend
you reconsider this command.
Hey.
So, I was thinking about the whole
GF conversation we had earlier,
and I...
You look...
Good, great.
Just, sometimes these holo-feeds
can really wash out your skin.
Did you do something
different with your hair?
What the hell is going on here?
Mr. Rory, would you please move?
Sara's bonded with the Death Totem.
What?
We think Mallus tricked
her into wearing it.
Look, the woman
on that bridge was not Sara.
All I care about right
now is getting her back.
We need to find John Constantine.
The demonologist?
Yeah, I know, he wears his tie
a little too loose for my liking,
but he has saved Sara
from Mallus before.
Gideon, can you up
my pain medication?
My leg is killing me.
Gideon?
The Nostromo sequence
has been activated
and will commence
in T minus three seconds.
T minus two seconds.
Gideon, un-commence.
That option has expired.
Door's locked.
I'm gonna kill that witch!
If you kill her, then Sara dies too.
- Better her than me.
- Dude, how can you say that?
- By moving my lips.
- Hey guys?
And where were you when Ray
was getting the crap beat out of him?
Day-drinking again?
Better than kidnapping a dog!
- We rescued the dog, Mick!
- I'm claustrophobic!
Everyone, just stop yelling.
Guys, everyone just relax.
I'm gonna knock her out, tie her up,
and no one gets hurt.
Oh, we're screwed.
Wally.
Hey.
Never thought
we'd see each other again.
You look good.
This isn't you, you're not real.
You sure about that?
Yeah.
I've seen apparitions before.
You know, I remember the first night
I said, "I love you."
We were in the back seat of your car.
You acted like you couldn't hear me.
Yeah, because I couldn't understand
why someone like you would love me.
Why not?
Oh, come on, Jesse.
Wally, you're a good-looking guy.
Great smile.
I know you've had girlfriends
before me.
None of them were you.
You're everything.
You're, like, an actual genius,
and...
the family you come from,
and then I...
You're just a speed junkie
with a drug addict for a mom?
I wonder why it didn't work out
between us.
So, you're just here to hurt me?
Well, you can't.
I'm, I'm actually glad
that you broke my heart.
You know, I traveled because of you.
I found some kind of inner peace.
I made new friends.
One day I'm gonna fall
in love with someone,
and that person isn't gonna be you.
Well said.
Unfortunately...
I can hurt you.
NEW YORK CITY, 2018
John Constantine, age 36,
one older sister,
both parents deceased?
He's part of the Newcastle crew.
He accidentally summoned a demon
that dragged a child,
Astra Logue, into Hell.
Sounds like a real weirdo.
He's a Warlock.
You know, I happen to be
a level nine Warlock.
Dungeons and Dragons
doesn't count, Gary.
Stay back.
Don't move, Gary.
-Gonna get you. I'm gonna...
-What the...
All right, all right.
Just, go on, go, go!
Okay.
Hey, do us a favor,
give us a hand, will you?
Grab it, grab it, grab it!
Oh, there you are.
All right, nice one, lad.
Hey, you're a feisty little bastard,
aren't you?
Are you guys from Housing co-op?
Because it's perfectly legal
to win an apartment in a duel.
We're here about Sara Lance.
Right, well,
Mrs. Veras, we will have
to continue the ritual tomorrow.
But not to worry, love.
We'll have your son married
in no time, all right?
Gracias, Señor Constantine.
Okay.
It's a gig economy.
I have to take the work
where I can find it, you know?
Now, let me guess.
Sara has succumbed
to the demon Mallus.
I sensed his power growing,
but not to worry,
I gave Ray very specific instructions
to kill her if that ever happened.
- What?
- Eggs and omelets, love.
And extreme measures.
Well, I'm here to save Sara.
She's bonded with the Death Totem.
- Oh, bollocks.
- What does that mean?
Oh, it's a British expletive
used to...
I know what bollocks means, Gary.
What did you mean by it?
Well, about this so-called
Death Totem.
Recently, whilst heavily influenced
by ayahuasca,
I came to learn why
the sixth lost tribe of Zambesi
was stricken from the oral record.
This lost tribe,
which had been entrusted
to watch over
the domain of the dead,
sided with Mallus
while the other five tribes
rallied to imprison him
perhaps explaining
why the Death Totem
is inextricably linked
with our demon friend.
Wally, can you hear me?
Wally, talk to me, man.
Kid's dead.
I gotta go after him.
Just be careful out there.
If I'm not back in five minutes...
Just wait longer?
No, come rescue me.
Okay, guys, this is ridiculous.
We can't just wait here.
Sara's gonna take us out one by one.
But I can decouple the Jumpship
from Gideon's mainframe.
We are getting off of this ship.
Sara's soul is likely trapped
in Mallus' realm.
Usually...
I'd have to cast the demon
into myself to rescue her,
but luckily, I already
have a link to Sara's soul.
So, I'll enlist Aken,
the Egyptian ferryman of the dead.
What do you mean you already
have a link to Sara's soul?
Well, let's just say
our souls have been one.
Leaves a metaphysical
connection, love.
- Don't call me, "love."
- Oh, pardon me, pet.
Sara and I also share a very,
very strong metaphysical
connection, so...
Wait. I can't believe...
You both slept with Captain Lance?
- Gary.
- Did we now?
Well then, we both have
excellent taste in damaged women.
- Sara's not damaged.
- Yeah.
And I'm the bloody Pope.
You know what,
let's get on with this.
What the hell do you think
you're doing?
You're going after Sara,
I'm coming with you.
To the realm of Mallus?
Start chanting.
Very well, give me your hand.
Are you serious?
Deadly.
Mallus, Aken, Ka, Ren, Ba, Ib, Sheut,
Mallus Aken Ma'at.
John Constantine.
You dare enter my realm?
So, any sign of the Captain, Nate?
No, but I found Wally.
- Is he...
- Alive.
Sara must have shot him
with the anti-speedster gun.
We're gonna need a bigger Medbay.
Don't worry, guys, I'm almost there.
Just get ready to meet me
at the Jumpship.
Sorry, Giddy, this is gonna hurt you
more than me.
Zari?
Behrad.
I can't sleep.
Will you read me a story, Zari?
No, no, this is...
this is the Death Totem
messing with my mind,
you're not real.
Of course I am.
Please, you know the one.
"The Prince of Timbuktu."
Please stop.
"The Prince of Timbuktu took
a swim in the ocean blue."
-"He met a tortoise
-who told him his purpose
-was to be the king of Timbuktu."
-Behrad.
Goodbye.
Sara, stop, please.
Sara.
You have to fight Mallus.
Stop!
You're hurting me.
Impressive.
But no one can fight Mallus forever.
What have you got on
your socks there, squire?
Oh, it's Beebo.
My Aunt Stacy bought them for me,
you like Beebo?
Once, when I was on a massive bender,
I put a spell on that
toy to make him talk.
He told me things
that'll make your toes curl.
Oh, like what?
Okay, Sara's soul is trapped
in the realm of a demon
and her ship and entire crew
are lost in time.
Who cares about Beebo?
Well, his Aunt Stacy does.
You're wound tight as a bloody drum,
aren't you, love?
Pardon me, pet.
You know, you need to loosen up.
And then the work just flows.
Oh, is that work you're doing?
Sorry, I couldn't tell.
There isn't exactly
a paint-by-number spell
for locating a spaceship
floating through a temporal stream.
My business card says,
"Master of the Dark Arts,"
not "Doctor Ruddy What's-His-Face."
- Who?
Exactly.
What, okay, you know what, Gary?
Let's just get outta here
because Mr. Constantine
- has wasted enough of our time.
- Oh, that's where you are.
You beauty.
Okay, so you have a foot,
but you don't have a phone?
I, I just... I really don't
understand how Sara could've...
What, shagged me
in a mental institute?
Oh, my God!
Ah, you have nothing
to be jealous about.
I am not jealous, I'm just...
Okay, maybe I'm a little bit jealous.
Ah, we were just trying to find
some calm in the storm.
I don't understand,
who sleeps with a Warlock
and then turns around and starts
calling me her girlfriend?
She called you her girlfriend?
Yeah, and I really wanna believe her.
- But?
- But I don't think that
Sara's really a one-woman woman.
Well, if the price of admission
is looking like a fool
or getting your heart broken
then well, I'd say Ms. Lance
is pretty well worth it.
Okay.
Boys, there has to be a way
to find the Waverider.
I have an idea.
We're all ears, mate.
The Legends remind me
of my D and D group.
- Don't laugh.
- Too late.
And last year, we were on a campaign,
"The Trials of Eagan."
Our party was made up of a monk...
a druid...
a half-orc rogue...
a bard,
and like, a... like, a cheerful gnome
who was also
a very accomplished wizard.
With two men down, we were trapped
in the Tomb of Ruination,
and we were being hunted
by Zanatar the Unburnt.
We were exhausted,
running low on food.
Hungry.
Zari, come in.
Zari, do you copy?
Our sorceress was missing,
feared dead.
Gary, how does any of this help us
find Sara and the Legends?
Hey, hey, hey.
Let the man finish his story,
all right?
As you were, mate.
Zanatar the Unburnt
wielded the Death Sword,
one of the Six Swords of Sorrow.
To defeat him, we needed...
Another of the Six Swords.
The best way to defeat a totem bearer
is with another totem.
Yeah, that worked out well for Z.
Seeing as I am out of commission,
one of you two needs
to wield the Earth Totem.
Which turned Blackbeard's
lady friend into a zombie.
It merely manifested
the pirate queen's true nature.
A righteous warrior has nothing
to fear from wielding a totem.
A righteous warrior, count me out.
All right, well,
Earth Totem...
meet Steel Man.
So, how did your D and D crew thingy
find one of the six Swords of Sorrow?
We didn't, we died a grizzly death
at the hands of Zanatar.
-Gary!
-But, but...
that's because we weren't
working in concert.
The Legends will be fine as long
as they just don't split up.
Mick and I will find Zari.
All right,
and I'll go get the Earth Totem.
You're gonna die.
- Hey.
- Thanks, Mick.
You can do this.
The point of my story is, even though
we were defeated by Zanatar,
we were able to track
the mystical object he was wielding.
The Sword of bloody Sorrow.
You are a bloody genius, Barry.
Gary.
Gary, right.
I need the vile from my desk,
Mother's tears,
and my ruination stones,
and from you, Ava, I'm gonna need...
- Oh, please don't say it.
- The foot.
Sorry, can we just pretend
for a moment that I have no idea
what you two are doing?
Well, it's like our Gary said
the easiest way to locate
the Legends' ship
is to locate the Death Totem.
You know, it's a shame that you had
to join the family business.
You were a sweet kid.
Last time we were here,
I was a little girl,
but I was never sweet.
Your friend, Oliver, made sure
of that when he killed my father.
Oliver's not responsible
for the path that you chose.
You're right.
You see, Sara, you and I...
we're alike.
The darkness
has always been within us.
Please.
Ra's Al Ghul will never know
you let me live.
Papi!
Once a killer, always a killer.
Why are you crying, Sara?
You've done nothing wrong.
Imagine what you could do
if you just released your guilt.
You can't erase your past, Sara,
so just embrace it.
You want me to join your team.
It's your destiny.
Eons ago, the sixth tribe of Zambesi
defended Mallus from their brethren.
Their tribe wielded the Death Totem.
Now the cycle's starting again.
You weren't just born to wield
the Death Totem, Sara.
You were born to wield
the Death Totem for Mallus.
Z.
I'm all right, barely.
Nathaniel, we have Z.
Did you find the Earth Totem?
Actually I did, but, guys,
Sara found me.
Nathaniel, where are you?
Nathaniel?
What's the matter, Nathaniel?
You look like you've seen a ghost.
Nathaniel?
Nathaniel, where are you?
Right, the Fire Totem's
our last chance to defeat her.
Oh, and here I thought escaping
to the Jumpship was a good plan.
I don't care what she's done.
I'm not abandoning Sara
or anyone else on this team.
Too bad, you're down a leg,
and you look like a cat stuck
in a dryer.
That's not funny, I love cats.
I'll wield the totem.
Let's just get to the lab.
Here's hoping Ray
knew what he was doing.
Get a grip, Nate.
That's not your grandfather.
Houston, 1970.
I wanted to be with my wife and son,
but you convinced me
that was impossible.
You were relieved
when I blew the cargo bay door.
I didn't want you to die.
You were desperate
to save your own hide.
And what have you made
of yourself, boy?
You're a damn disappointment
to your father
and you're sure as hell
a disappointment to me.
You think Amaya loves you?
You're not worthy of her love.
There.
Haircut nuked the stone.
This totem wasn't meant for me.
You have to use it.
- Forget it.
- You've spent your entire life
obsessed with fire and heat.
What if this is the reason why?
How many times do I have to tell you
I'm not a hero?
Sara's a hero
and look what the Death Totem
did to her.
That was the work of Mallus.
Most people who've seen
what you've seen
would've succumbed to darkness,
but you didn't.
You chose to become a Legend.
You may try and hide it, Mick,
but you're a good man.
What if you're wrong?
There's only one way to find out.
Exorcizamus te,
omnis immundus spiritius.
Omnis satanic potestas,
omnis infernalis adversarii,
in nomine at virtute Domini.
Hit her with the holy water.
There's somebody
who wants to talk to you, John.
John?
You glamoured your voice.
That's the oldest bloody trick
in the book.
You don't remember me?
I know it's been a long time.
- Astra.
- Mallus will free me from hell,
but you have to give him Sara.
A life for a life.
You know, better than anybody.
Magic always has a price.
I wanna speak to Sara.
Okay.
All right, Astra.
I'll do it.
Give me your hand, Astra.
Come on.
It's all right, love.
It's just me.
It's Johnny.
No one escapes Hell.
The sacred cross commands you
to free this woman from your prison.
To free this woman from your prison.
Wielding a totem's bad enough.
Now, you want me to wear a necklace?
There's no time, Mick.
See? Doesn't work.
Are you still with me, Mick?
Sara!
Sara? Sara?
Does Ava know
who you really are, Sara?
What you've done?
What are you gonna tell her?
That the totem was wrong?
You aren't a killer?
The totem's power is within you,
Sara, all you have to do is decide.
A life...
free of pain and regret with us,
or the tormented half-life
you're living now?
Sara?
I know you are still in there.
You are the strongest,
most fearless person I've ever met
and you never back down.
Don't you remember?
When did a Legend ever go quietly?
I'm here.
I'm here, Sara,
and I need you to come back to me.
I need you to come home.
Sara, can't you feel me?
No.
You're making a mistake.
No, to a life without pain or regret.
No, to being a demon's lackey
and no, to bringing more death
into this world.
I owe that little girl at least that.
You could have everything.
You saved me again.
I had a little help.
Well, while we're here.
A light?
Chin chin.
I should definitely come
to your aid more often.
Well, at this point,
I might as well just make you
a bed on the ship.
Tempting.
If you thought Mallus
really would've freed Astra,
you would have traded me,
wouldn't you?
- In a heartbeat.
- Yeah.
Well, what can I say?
I'm a nasty piece of work.
So am I.
- You survived, love.
- For now.
You know, there's a reason why
I prefer to walk this path alone.
It's...
So, I don't have to share
with anyone how lost I really am.
But you're not alone, are you, Sara?
Maybe I should be.
She's a good one.
Try not to hurt her.
That's what I'm afraid of.
Pinch me.
Okay.
Sara.
Is it the real Sara?
Yeah, it's me.
I'm sorry, Ray.
I'm...
I'm sorry, everyone.
I'm really sorry.
It's good to have you back, Captain.
Yeah, because evil you is a pain
in the ass to fight.
I'm still trying to wrap
my head around this mess.
Why would Mallus want
to show me Jesse?
- Or me my grandpa?
- I don't know.
Mallus was trying
to recruit me to his side
and using my darkest fears.
Maybe that's just what he does,
he looks into our hearts and...
broadcasts our deepest secrets.
That's terrifying.
Okay. You up.
I need your speed
to re-couple the mainframe.
Music to my ears.
Oh, although,
I was really digging the silver hair.
Hey.
We need to talk.
No good conversation
ever started that way.
- Ava, I'm sorry.
- Listen...
I can't pretend to understand
what you went through
or... or what happened to you
but I know that wasn't you, Sara.
That's just it.
That was me.
Just like fire is to Rory,
there is part of me that...
it's always been there.
And I really tried to pretend
that that wasn't true.
But deep down...
I am death.
No, Sara, okay, so...
so we can fight that part
of you together,
- just tell me what to do.
- Hey.
Ava, you read my file.
But I still showed up
at that restaurant,
in that horribly uncomfortable
dress trying to impress you
because I don't care
about your past, Sara.
Well, maybe you should.
You are wonderful.
And I...
and I've never been this happy
in my life.
But this doesn't look happy.
Look, I don't deserve you.
- Yes, Sara, yes, you do.
- No, Ava, I don't.
You deserve better,
you deserve so much better.
And I care about you, but...
I'm not gonna do this. I won't.
- Sara.
- I'm sorry.
Fresh from a successful crusade,
our team knew
the fight was far from over.
In fact, the true battle
was only just beginning.
This spot reserved for the girlfriend
of Sara Lance
In order to defeat the demon
and his cabal of evil,
we need to be at full strength,
which is going
to be hard given the losses
we sustained on our last quest.
Some wounds are so deep,
they never truly heal.
So, the question is,
are you prepared to join us
on this mission most deadly?
Well, tonight, squire...
I'm all yours.
18 2 20 14