EOBARD: My name is Eobard Thawne.
With the help
of Damien Darhk, Malcolm Merlyn,
Leonard Snart and Mick Rory,
I've obtained the Spear of Destiny,
an ancient artifact
with the power to rewrite reality itself.
And we have.
It's a brave new world.
Whoops.
The Mayor would like a word.
Miss Smoak.
Then maybe he should've
come down here himself
instead of sending the bimbo brigade.
Rude.
Well done, ladies.
Star City owes you a debt of gratitude.
Just doing our job, Mr. Mayor.
Yes, but you do it so well.
And with such style.
And you've done a bang-up job
dealing with my pest problem.
Though that term might be giving
you vigilantes a little too much credit.
Even a cockroach knows when to pack up
and head out of Dodge.
Star City is my home.
I will never stop fighting.
Sure you will. Kill her.
Get rid of that. Oh!
But I will take this mask.
So I can add it to my collection.
No, I will not take a seat
and wait for him to have an opening.
He can make time for me now.
MALCOLM: Can't you, Eobard?
ASSISTANT: I'm so sorry, Mr. Thawne.
He insisted.
MALCOLM: I see your friend is
still putting up a fight.
He'll give up.
All caged animals do, eventually.
Now, tell me why you've
flown all the way out here again?
You keep ignoring
my requests for a meeting.
Because there's no reason for one.
Our partnership has ended.
You got what you wanted.
Your wife and your son
are both alive and in good spirits.
Your daughter, Thea, adores you.
Nyssa al Ghul is trapped in a miserable,
closeted life in the middle of Ohio.
And hey, you can even clap again.
What more could you possibly want?
How about the Spear of Destiny?
There are still some things in this world
that I would like to see change.
How many times
do I have to tell you this, Malcolm?
The Spear is safest in my hands.
Besides, I'm the only one
who knows how to use it.
That's because
you destroyed the Kalabros manuscript!
Well, it's not my fault
you don't retain information like I do.
Speedster brains are handy that way.
Mr. Jackson is here to see you.
Send him in.
JAX: Good morning, Mr. Thawne.
Jefferson.
How are things down at the lab?
There was a minor setback,
but the situation is under control.
You promised me results.
And you will have them.
I just need to
motivate my employee a little more.
But another test
will be up and running this evening.
I hope so. For his sake.
And yours.
Yes.
I don't know why you and Damien insist
on toying with the Legends. It's sloppy.
They should be wiped from existence.
Well, I prefer this arrangement.
I believe it's called "poetic justice."
And what is this project
you're working on?
I'm a man of science, Malcolm.
I'm compelled to innovate,
invent, and inspire.
A genius brain needs a genius challenge.
Now, go. Enjoy your family.
Spend your wealth.
The world is as it should be.
Be satisfied with your spoils.
The others are having
the time of their lives.
SECURITY OFFICER: Stop!
Hold it right there!
Cool it, Mick.
We already got what we came for.
Just heating things up.
Don't move!
Both of you on the ground!
Mr. Snart! Sorry, sir.
We didn't realize it was you.
Carry on.
What the hell's going on?
No roasting pigs?
No need. We're home free, buddy.
It's good to be the king.
No getaway. No chase.
If you want a chase,
I can arrange a chase.
We could even
get us tossed in Iron Heights
and we could plan an escape
just like old times.
- How does that sound?
- Boring!
Well, we could
hit up the Central City Bank.
They've got a fancy new vault
I've been dying to crack.
What's the point?
You own the bank and half the city.
You mean we own half the city, Mick.
We're partners, remember?
Mmm.
Seems our next score will have to wait.
Thawne is summoning us.
Since when do we get summoned?
Since the man agreed not to erase
you and your friends from existence.
Gideon.
I've finally perfected my fondant bows.
What do you think?
GIDEON: Your technique has vastly improved
over the last year, Captain.
These cakes are
so much more creative than your biscuits.
Now, credit where credit is due, Gideon.
Your idea of adding
more gelatin to the mixture was pivotal.
GIDEON: Well done. The best one yet,
in my humble opinion.
It's a shame that
you're the only one here to appreciate it.
GIDEON: I'm sure your team
would be just as impressed.
Assuming that they're all still alive.
Perhaps you should resume your efforts
to send a message out.
What's the point, Gideon?
The Legion have the Spear of Destiny!
They are like gods now!
There's no point in fighting.
Not anymore.
JAX: Stein!
Yes, Mr. Jackson?
What's this I hear
about you taking tomorrow off?
It's Saturday, sir,
and it's my daughter's birthday.
Oh, well, of course. Take the day off.
In fact, why don't you
take the whole week off.
Really?
Of course.
I mean, the project is ready
for Mr. Thawne to use, correct?
- Well, in fact...
- In fact, old man,
you will not be leaving this building
until Mr. Thawne sees results.
I've been working non-stop
for the past month.
I haven't seen
my wife and daughter in weeks.
You want to see your family?
Then you will get that reactor
working by tomorrow night.
It's impossible. There's too much data...
Get it working!
Or you will never
see that precious family of yours again.
Somebody clean this place up!
It's a damn mess!
I'm so sorry. May I help you with that?
Oh. No worries, man.
I got it.
Yes, Mr. President.
You know I'll be there.
You know I love receiving medals.
And then golf on Sunday.
And dinner at your hotel after?
All right. All right.
Best to Mel. Bye-bye.
I am so sorry. I had to take that.
There's only so many times you can tell
the President of the United States
that you'll call him back.
- You wanna get to the point?
- EOBARD: Yes.
I brought you here
to discuss a sensitive matter.
And it goes by the name of Malcolm Merlyn.
What about him?
I want you to keep an eye on him for me.
We're not your watchdogs.
What was that?
What he meant was we're not spies,
we're thieves.
Mr. Thawne! I need to speak with you!
I just need five minutes of your time.
Please! Reality is at stake!
The world isn't right!
Okay. Let him go. Let him go.
Let's see what he has to say.
It's okay.
He intentionally hit me in the ribs.
First of all, awesome office.
I guess it pays to be
the smartest man in the world,
which is why
I've come to you for help.
You were saying
that the world isn't right?
Yeah. This world we're in now is wrong.
Reality has changed somehow.
How do you know all this?
Um, well, there are signs everywhere,
if you know where to look.
There's subtle inconsistencies
in the fabric of reality.
I call them scars.
You know, like
after you've been operated on.
Well, reality has been operated on.
Truly fascinating.
- Yeah.
- I'm giddy with excitement.
What's that got to do with him?
Well, Mr. Thawne could help me fix it.
Look, all right. You're a genius.
You figured out cold fusion,
you saved the polar bears.
You fixed global warming.
I mean, you made desalination sustainable.
I mean, you solve problems like this,
like, every day.
If anyone, anyone,
can figure out why these scars exist
and how to put the world back
to the way it was, it's you, dude.
You know what?
I think you're on to something.
Something is definitely not right here.
Fix it.
- Take Mr...
- Heywood.
Mr. Heywood.
Take Mr. Heywood out for some fresh air.
And, uh, kill him.
Me?
Look, I don't understand.
If this is about my work,
nobody pays attention to it. My mom's
the only person that reads my blog!
Stop talking.
Guys. I am not a threat to anyone.
Unless I'm right.
Am I right?
Sounds like fitting final words to me.
Whatever science or magic altered reality
must have left small scars in my memory
that my subconscious picked up on.
So, if I'm not a conspiracy theorist
no one listens to, then...
- Who am I?
- Dead.
- Wait!
- What?
He said, "Wait." I heard him.
He said, "Wait."
You promised me
things were gonna be like old times.
It is like old times, only better.
Central City is ours! No more Flash!
Except another speedster's
calling the shots.
Leave Thawne to me. I always have a plan.
- You know this.
- Well, fill me in.
SNART: When the time is right.
RORY: Ah, yes, we're partners.
Except when you refuse to
tell me what's going on.
You son of a...
Sorry, buddy.
I owed you that.
You saved my life. Why?
Because I'm an idiot.
This could be one of my scars talking.
But I'm sensing
you're telling me the truth.
Let's move.
Okay.
DR. HEYWOOD: This is crazier
than any of my crazy theories.
You're trying to tell me
a group called "The Legion of Doom"
used something called
"The Spear of Destiny" to rewrite reality?
Who even names something
"Legion of Doom"?
- You did.
- Me?
Now, do you only remember the old reality
because you're part of the Legion?
I'm not a part of anything.
I just made a terrible mistake.
Die, you filthy aliens!
Come on. Wait a minute.
- This is the guy who's gonna fix reality?
- Uh-huh.
Uh...
Who are you guys
and what are you doing here?
We need your help.
What do you got?
A clogged toilet or something?
'Cause, you know, I'm off duty now.
- You're not a janitor.
- Yeah, I am. It says so on my name...
- On my nametag.
- You're a geek, a nerd.
A genius. It's why we're here.
Is this about the dipole magnets
that I borrowed from S.T.A.R. Labs?
'Cause I'm totally gonna return those.
Look, man. He said you're the one
that can fix this reality.
"Fix this reality"? What do you mean?
You guys think
there's something wrong, too?
RORY: Woah.
- That's private stuff, man.
- What is it?
I don't know exactly.
- I mean, I think I know, but I don't...
- Spit it out, Haircut.
Well, um...
I kinda built it on impulse.
You know, like on instinct.
I call it a Trans-reality Multiplexer.
No real reason.
I just thought it sounded cool.
Don't you get it, man?
Your "impulse" was a reality scar
working on your subconscious.
"Reality scar."
So, what does this fun gun do?
Theoretically, it targets irregularities
in the hippocampus.
Acting like a Control-Z for memories.
- "Control-Z?"
- Like an "undo" command on a computer.
I was going to try the new version
on my latest test subject,
but then I was
worried it might melt his brain.
- Axel.
- No, it's Tesla, actually.
He looks more like an Indiana to me.
No. He's Axel.
You gave me that little guy for Christmas.
You haven't been
running any tests on him, have you?
What? No.
No! No!
All right. Actually, for it to work,
you have to shoot him in the head.
Why would you say that?
How many people
are gonna point guns at me today?
Oh, my God, you killed him!
You son of a bitch!
It works.
So, Mr. Rory is having second thoughts?
Mick's just a little confused.
I can control him.
- Obviously, you can't.
- Yes, I can.
I just need your help
getting him back on the reservation
before Thawne finds out.
We have bigger problems.
What if Heywood's only
the first of his old teammates
Mr. Rory's feeling nostalgic for.
I knew we should've killed them all.
It was a dangerous oversight
to keep them alive in any capacity.
Does that include Mick?
At the very least,
we should have wiped his brain.
MALCOLM: Such as it is.
You trusted your buddy a little too much.
Calm yourself, Malcolm.
We'll have Mr. Rory back
before he does too much damage.
Yes, boss?
DARHK: Mick Rory's gotten himself lost.
Find him, would you?
Where do you suggest we start our search?
You can track him with this.
I put a GPS in Mick.
I don't trust anyone.
Okay, on the count of three. One, two...
You!
I deserved that.
Damn straight you did.
Hey, if it wasn't for me,
you'd all be dead.
Yeah, Mick, thanks a lot. You trapped
each of us in our own personal hell.
Do you have any idea
how many toilets I've cleaned?
So many.
Amaya.
- Sara.
- Hey, dumbasses.
They have no clue who you are.
They work for Damien Darhk.
Oh!
Crap.
- I don't like the way she's looking at us.
- I like the way she's looking at us.
Love the suits.
Get off my friend!
All right, guys, time out!
Come on! Come on, look!
I know this may sound crazy,
but doesn't it seem like
there's something wrong with this world?
- Yeah, Rory sold out the boss...
- AMAYA: To throw in with you losers.
"Losers"? I'll have you know,
in my reality,
you and I had sex,
and we both liked it very much.
- RAY: Nate, not helping.
- Amaya, look at me.
Tell me you don't recognize me,
like, deep in your subconscious.
Look, this isn't how it's supposed to be.
Okay, you're supposed to be heroes,
like us.
Okay. Allow me
to demonstrate my superpowers. Okay?
Knock it off, you idiot.
The Spear took away your powers.
But it's true.
Nate used to be able to steel-up
and I had a robotic exoskeleton
that allowed me to shrink.
These guys are heroes.
That is so great.
We kill heroes.
One more person hits me,
I'm gonna punch back.
What the hell happened to me?
It appears that after the Legion
got the Spear and changed reality,
they kept us around as their pets.
Yeah, except for you.
You helped the Legion steal the Spear.
Speaking of, the Legion is
probably on their way here to kill us.
We need to get out of here.
Yeah, we got to find some place to hide.
RAY: Your mom's basement?
- Really?
- I pay rent.
So, legally, it's my basement. Kind of.
Mommy makes great sandwiches.
The best. It's the perfect amount of
mayo-meat-bread ratio that really gives...
Focus! We need to figure out
how we can rescue the rest of the team.
And get the Spear back so we can
undo everything the Legion has done.
Except, now they know we're trying
to get the band back together.
Except, they don't know
that you've gotten to me. Which means...
You can sneak into the Legion
and pretend to be Darhk's favorite chick.
It's our best shot at getting Amaya back.
All right.
What about the rest of the team?
Well, the Professor and Jax are working
on some secret project for Thawne.
I don't know where the Englishman is.
Neither do I.
I can only imagine
how those psychopaths are torturing Rip.
Gideon, I've discovered
the missing ingredient for my recipe.
Rum.
And speaking of which, I'm gonna need you
to fabricate me another bottle of it.
Ooh. And some nachos.
- I will do nothing of the sort.
- What?
You will do as I tell you, Gideon.
I'm your captain!
Then it's time for you
to start acting like one!
Now sit up straight
and show your backbone, Captain Hunter.
Gideon.
For the thousandth time, I've got no way
of getting the reserve power back online.
And I've got no way
of sending out any signal of any sort.
Which means...
Which means that I am destined
to live out
the rest of my days right here.
With you.
While you were
honing your confectionery skills,
I've been working on new algorithms
to redirect power
from the idle quadrants of the ship.
You need to focus
on boosting your distress signal
once power is fully back online.
Now, chin up, Captain!
I don't know if I can do this, Gideon.
I believe in you.
Now, let's get to work.
First, I'm going to vomit.
And second...
Let's do this.
When your minions bring Mick back,
I want to arrange a meeting with Thawne.
And when I say
"arrange a meeting," I mean...
- One between Thawne and his maker?
- DARHK: Cute.
A little mustache-twirly for my taste.
You're really gonna have to
step up your tactics, Leonard.
You didn't think that Thawne was actually
going to fall for that fake meeting trick?
This is not The Godfather.
Although we do agree with your sentiment,
Eobard has to go.
So glad you both approve.
Which brings us back
to our original conundrum.
"How to kill a speedster?"
We found your partner.
And he's got himself some friends.
And where, pray tell,
is your partner Ms. Lance?
We got separated in the fight.
I haven't heard from her since.
So, I'm guessing she's dead by now.
That's the thing about Sara Lance.
She never stays dead for very long.
Sorry. We underestimated them.
Won't happen again. We'll fix this.
- Let's go.
- Wait a minute. Not so fast.
Yes?
I have a question for you.
Which one is your favorite trophy?
That's like asking a girl
to pick just one pair of shoes.
Oh, please.
Everyone has their favorite kill.
Do you want to hear mine?
Her name was "Black Canary."
I will never forget her.
It was so delicious.
Killing her.
They told me that I'd done it before,
but I can't imagine it ever getting old.
The very first thing I did in this reality
was acquire my magic.
I'm going to miss you, Ms. Lance.
Having you around to attend to
my every whim was too enticing to pass up.
Plus, it's so hard
to find good help these days.
Really? Now's the time
for a bad guy monologue?
You should have killed me
when you had the chance.
No better time than the present.
Amaya. The honor is yours.
Good bye.
What the hell?
Shoot now! Explain later.
Damien, what did I tell you?
For what it's worth, I thought
it was a very good bad guy monologue.
Everything's on schedule, Mr. Thawne.
You have nothing to worry about.
Hey!
What do you want?
There's just one thing I don't understand.
If Thawne made this world to punish us,
how are your mom's sandwiches
so good, bro?
Her condiment game is on point, right?
She even had gluten-free bread for me.
Well, let's just get back to the ship.
We don't know where the ship is, or Rip.
Which means our next move
should be to rescue the Professor.
Speaking of which, what did Thawne
have you two working on?
Grey did most of the work.
I just made his life hell.
From what I could tell,
he was building some sort of reactor.
He said it would burn 1,000 times
hotter than the sun once it's operational.
I like the sound of that.
Could be a power generator,
or a particle accelerator.
What if Thawne is
trying to destroy the Spear?
Impossible. You need
the blood of Christ to destroy it.
That's why Rip
broke it up into so many pieces.
Unless he figured out there's another way,
by incinerating it.
But why would Thawne
want to destroy the Spear?
Oh, no.
If he destroys the Spear,
that means this reality
cannot be rewritten.
Okay. We better get that Spear
before he can make that happen.
But, even if we find it,
we don't know how to access its powers.
Rory does. You were there, right,
when they used the Spear?
They read out of some book
called The Calibrate.
Caliber.
Kalablos.
Something like that.
Do you remember what language it was in?
Aramaic.
Dude, how do you even know
what Aramaic sounds like?
Passion of the Christ. Good movie.
Mick, would you be able
to recognize the incantation?
Yeah.
Hey, if they figure out this incantation,
and we get our hands on the Spear,
I want you to use it.
I should've listened to you
back in World War I.
If we had used the Spear
when we had the chance...
I might've been tempted to use it
to change my own future.
Now, we've got nothing to lose.
Marty, Marty, Marty.
I know you've been
working so hard on this project,
and I wanted to come by and say thank you.
But if it doesn't come online
in the next few minutes,
I'll have to kill you.
One moment, Mr. Thawne.
I just need one more moment.
There. There.
As you can see, the machine
appears to be fully functional.
Though it may take some time
for the core to reach peak temperature.
Well, then you'll stay until it does.
I was hoping to see my family tonight.
No. No, no. You can't leave
in your moment of glory.
No, you keep monitoring the core
and make sure the reaction remains stable.
DR. HEYWOOD: I think we've got something!
We pieced together a passage
from the Kalabros.
Aka "the Word of God."
All right, Jax. It's on you to restore
Stein's mind before we get to the lab.
We got to destroy the reactor
before Thawne can destroy the Spear.
- Yeah, no doubt.
- And remember,
you guys are going in there
without your powers.
Don't worry. I know that place
like the back of my hand.
- What about Mick?
- Mick's staying here.
We can't trust him.
Not after what you've done.
After what I've done?
If it wasn't for me, you'd all be
walking around like sheep.
If it wasn't for you, we never would've
been turned into sheep in the first place.
We trusted you, Mick.
We can't afford
to make that mistake again.
Let's go.
League of Losers cut you loose?
Nobody cuts me loose.
I'm done with those people.
What do you say
we burn this city to the ground?
Knowing Sara,
she's rallied the team by now.
Those idiots aren't who I'm worried about.
Relax, boys.
The prodigal son has returned.
And he's got some news for us,
isn't that right, Mick?
Our old friend Eobard has built a device
to destroy the Spear.
No wonder Eobard doesn't want us using it
before he locks in
his own version of reality.
Which, I assume, means erasing all of us?
And your pals?
My Pals?
They wanna steal the Spear
before the deed's done.
I think you can see
what I'm getting at, gentlemen.
The four of us
are no match for a speedster,
so while Thawne is fighting the Legends...
We'll grab the Spear
from under both their noses.
Exactly.
- The enemy of my enemy...
- Is our opportunity.
The status of the machine, Doctor.
Please tell Mr. Thawne
I'm working as fast as I can.
I've powered up the reactor. I just need
to make a few adjustments to the core.
Wait. You already turned it on?
I had specific instructions
from Mr. Thawne to do so.
Grey, we need to talk.
"Grey?"
Please. Don't kill me!
I've done everything Mr. Thawne wanted.
I'm not gonna kill you.
I'm just gonna make you better...
Grey, what have you done?
If Mr. Thawne wants to kill me,
he'll have to do it himself.
Guys, we got a problem.
You got to get here ASAP.
We're at the building.
Just keep him there.
Ray, find us
the quickest way into the lab, now!
Look, you got to believe me, okay?
This is not the way it's supposed to be.
Is this some sort of test? Of my loyalty?
- Does Mr. Thawne even...
- Look, this isn't about Thawne.
It's about you and me.
I assure you, my dedication to Mr. Thawne
has never been stronger.
Did you just press the silent alarm?
What?
No, it's a secondary
radiation sensor for the nuclear core.
Grey, you are a crappy liar
in any reality.
SARA: Martin?
I can't talk any sense into him.
And he just triggered an alarm.
Which means Thawne will be here soon.
Or now.
Well...
Looks like you losers
managed to remember who you are.
I should have wiped you from existence
when I had the chance.
Do you have any idea
how infuriating it is
to know that Merlyn was right?
Lucky for you, I still believe
in some fates worse than death.
Like me destroying this Spear
and cementing this reality for all time.
Martin?
The reactor is fully operational, sir.
This is the only reality
any of you will ever know.
We'll never give up trying to stop you.
Well...
If it weren't for your futile efforts,
this wouldn't be half so sweet.
Not so fast, Speedy.
You have something we want.
You need a lesson
on how to share your toys, Eobard.
Yeah, time for us
to get a turn with the Spear.
And do what with it?
Don't you understand?
I'm trying to protect you from yourselves.
- With the Spear destroyed...
- Bored now.
Get the Spear!
Let go of the Spear, and I won't use it
to turn you into a jockstrap.
Yeah!
Perhaps not.
Give it up.
Sara. Why do we always
find ourselves in this situation?
Because you keep finding yourself
on the wrong side of history.
Nice work, Mick.
Now hand it over.
Mick, no.
You already gave it to them once.
- You know what happened.
- That was Thawne.
- This time will be different, big boy.
- Don't do this, Mick.
Mick, I don't care what anyone
else thinks, I still believe in you.
Enough!
Mick.
Hand it over.
Like a good boy.
You mean a good dog.
That's all I am to you.
An attack dog.
Now that's not true.
Sure, we both know
you're not the sharpest tool in the shed,
but that's why we're partners.
Remember?
You're right.
I'm not a genius.
But I'm no one's dog, Leonard.
RORY: Not anymore.
Well, I guess
you can teach an old dog new tricks.
Undo this mess.
I am sorry about your friend, Mick.
I know you loved her to pieces.
No.
Well, if you want something done right...
Well done, Leonard.
You bastard.
I'll kill you all.
Actually, I believe that's my line.
Now, where were we
before I was so rudely interrupted?
Well...
I guess we're done here.
You know the really swell thing
about the Spear being destroyed?
Now you can't stop us from killing you.
Please, don't insult my intelligence.
Even at your fastest,
you're moving in slow motion to me.
Except, they're not alone.
I say we go down fighting.
You kill one of us, we kill all of you.
For Amaya.
EOBARD: Don't.
Even if you survive my men,
you'll never survive me.
Not without powers or weapons.
And the truth is,
I don't want to see any more of you dead.
Not out of sentiment, of course.
No, no. Quite the opposite.
But because it is so delicious
knowing that you'll be forced to
live your lives in a reality that I...
Well, that we created.
You will walk this world
knowing that something isn't quite right.
That for all your trying,
you only made things worse.
And no one will ever believe you
when you tell them
about all the sacrifices you made,
and how close you came to being Legends.
That sounds
like a fitting punishment to me.
What do you think, Professor Stein?
I don't care what you do to them as long
as I never have to see Mr. Jackson again.
EOBARD: Ah.
Fair enough.
You're free to go.
You're just gonna let them walk?
Be glad I'm letting you
and your fellow traitors do the same.
And the next time any of you get
what you think is a smart idea,
remember this grace
and the fact that I could
kill any of you in the blink of an eye.
My mom's not gonna be cool with that.
Do I look like I give a damn?
I can't believe that's it.
I refuse to believe that this is it.
Without the Spear,
there's no way we can undo any of this.
There is one way.
Time travel.
What do you mean?
We go back in time, to 1916,
and we stop the Legion from ever getting
the Spear of Destiny in the first place.
No, we are not supposed to
change events we participated in.
And if we do,
we risk time folding in on itself.
Even if we weren't
worried about messing with time,
we can't go anywhere.
Or anywhen.
We don't even know
where the Waverider is.
If it even exists in this reality.
Well, if it does,
there's one person who knows where it is.
We just have to find him.
GIDEON: I've directed all available power
to the main navigational
controls, Captain.
Thank you, Gideon.
Now, I've started
the communications protocol,
and if I just
splice these two wires together...
Your distress signal will be broadcast.
Surely, the rest of the team
must be out there somewhere, listening.