RIP: In 2166,
an immortal tyrant
named Vandal Savage
conquered the world
and murdered my wife and child.
I have assembled an elite team
to hunt him throughout time
and stop his rise to power.
Unfortunately, my plan
is opposed by the body
I had sworn my allegiance to,
the Time Masters.
In the future,
my friends may not be heroes,
but if we succeed,
they will be remembered
as legends.
RORY: Previously, on
Legends of Tomorrow...
The Time Masters.
They took me to a place
called the Vanishing Point.
I've spent lifetimes
training by them.
GIDEON: Mr. Jackson's
internal organs are aging
at an accelerated rate.
The rest of his body
will soon follow.
The trip through the Time Stream
should reverse your condition.
If we're separated, you'll die.
This man you've brought before
us is needed back in 2166.
- Take him away.
- What?
DRUCE: Search their ship
for the others.
You're under arrest.
Mick, what's going on?
We need to find
somewhere to hide.
SAVAGE: I better be
getting back to 2166.
I've been waiting
to meet your family.
And because
if you don't follow me,
this is what is in store for
your world, 150 years from now.
I could've chosen any time
and any place.
Of all the people
who ever lived,
I chose you eight.
I certainly hope that you
won't let me and the world down.
If your answer is yes, meet me
at this address in 36 hours.
So what do you think?
I think that's five minutes
of my life I'm not getting back.
He just showed us
the entire world in flames.
You can't turn your back
on that.
Observe.
Well, I think we can all agree
that the mission
would go a whole lot better
without those two.
I haven't signed on yet.
And I'm not signing on at all.
- Jefferson.
- No.
I'm not going off to die
in some apocalyptic future.
I'm staying right here
in the present.
Let me talk to him.
Jefferson.
Can we at least discuss this?
Oh, that's a first.
You know, it's always you
trying to tell me what to do.
It's not happening this time.
But if the fate of the world
is at stake--
Then the world can find somebody
more capable than me.
I have confidence in us
as Firestorm.
All right, look.
Just sleep on it.
Come to my office tomorrow,
and if your answer is still no--
It will be.
Grey, we need to talk.
We were... We were just talking.
How did you change your clothes
so fast?
Something called time travel.
I need your help.
The team's in trouble.
(PROFESSOR STEIN COUGHING)
KENDRA: Martin, are you okay?
I'm required to merge
with Jefferson periodically
in order to maintain
nuclear cohesion.
Then sending him away
in the Jumpship
probably wasn't
the greatest idea.
Given the circumstances
we're under,
I'm surprised
any of us are alive.
Oh, you'll be dead soon.
You're getting off easy.
What gives you the free pass?
They have other plans for me.
As Chronos.
They're gonna try and put me
through the induction
process again.
Brainwashing.
RORY: Kills most men, Professor.
And those that don't die,
end up like mindless goats.
But Snart said you weren't
mindless when you were Chronos.
Not any more than usual, anyway.
Mmm.
The whole time I stayed focused
on one thing.
The one thing that kept me sane.
Vengeance.
I focused on how much
I hated all of you.
Ah, gentlemen, I missed you.
Come on in.
Oh, that's it. Oh, yeah. Break my arm.
RAY: Hey!
What are you doing?
Why are you taking her?
Hey!
(GRUNTING)
Kendra!
Leave us.
I have a query.
Why haven't we killed you yet?
That's what you've been trying
to do all this time.
Fortunately for you, two of your
crew are still at large.
Tell me where to find them,
and I'll spare the others.
If it is anything like the offer
you gave me in the USSR,
I'm sorely tempted.
You were a fugitive
from justice.
You're helping Vandal Savage
take over the world.
I have a feeling that our
definition of the word "justice"
may differ somewhat.
The only difference
between us is,
my view of the timeline reaches
further and wider than yours.
Am I supposed to be impressed?
In 2175, less than 10 years from
when Savage conquers the world,
the Earth is attacked
by a warlike race
of extraterrestrials
from the planet Thanagar.
Without Savage
to unite the world
under a singular rule,
this is what becomes
of the world.
This is the work of Savage.
No.
This is what will happen
to Earth
if Savage is not there
to lead it.
Without him,
all human life is extinguished.
Even this realm falls
to the Thanagarians.
Are you impressed now?
No.
You are as mad
as your friend Vandal
if you think that
he is the world's only hope.
We've examined the timeline,
there is no other hope.
I don't expect you
to take my word for it.
That's why there is something
else I have to show you.
(GRUNTS)
How did you even know
that was down there?
When Rip first recruited us,
I made it my business to case
every square inch of this tub
in the event there was something
worth stealing.
There wasn't.
Let's get out of here.
Wait, what about the team?
There's nothing more we can do
for them.
You're just going to leave Mick?
If the Time Masters are half
as twisted as Mick said,
there is an excellent chance
Mick is no longer Mick.
Now, why aren't we flying yet?
Because I'm not going anywhere.
And even if we wanted to,
we're in a hangar surrounded by
an entire armada of Timeships.
It's the Waverider.
We've got guns.
We can blast our way out.
This isn't Bonnie and Clyde,
and I'm not going anywhere
without the rest of the team.
(POWERING UP)
Maybe I didn't make
myself clear.
Don't do that.
Don't act like you're that
same coldhearted bastard
that I first met.
I remember Russia,
and you were the one
who told me not to kill Stein.
Yeah, because you seem to have
a problem with being a killer.
I, however, don't.
Prove it.
Shoot me.
(PHONE RINGING)
- Hello.
- GIDEON: Hello, Ms. Lance.
Gideon, you're alive.
If by being alive,
you mean that my
operating system is intact, yes.
I was able to upload
into the latency core
to avoid being wiped out
when the Time Master--
We can share war stories later.
Where is the rest of the team?
They are in cell block 4587,
and they too are alive.
For the moment.
Wait, what do you mean,
"For the moment"?
Oh, you're awake.
(GRUNTING)
I wouldn't bother.
Those straps are forged
from Tiberian steel.
(CHUCKLES)
- This is a Timeship.
- Yes.
A little gift from our friends.
(GROANS)
Oh, Prince Khufu is with us as well.
He's being held in stasis
down at the cargo hold.
And where are you taking us?
To an appointment that I have
with destiny.
You should be familiar
with this procedure, Chronos.
The name's Mick.
Though we've made
some refinements,
clearly your conditioning
was not as thorough
as it should have been.
For a Time Master,
you sure waste a lot of it.
Even with only
a partial induction,
you were the greatest
of our hunters, Chronos.
After we're finished,
temporal criminals
and time pirates alike,
will quake
at the sound of your bootsteps.
Hmm. Well, for your sake,
you better hope that plan works,
'cause if it doesn't, that
boot's gonna crush your skull.
- (ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
- (GROANING)
(SCREAMING)
RIP: What is this place?
DRUCE: Our holy of holies.
The Oculus viewing chamber.
Our most powerful window
into past, present and future.
The source of all
our information on the timeline.
Why did I not know about this?
No captain does.
The Oculus' existence is known
only to the High Council,
including its greatest secret.
The Oculus not only gives us
a window into time,
but the ability to shape it
as we see fit.
We've been helping Vandal Savage
consolidate his power
by giving him access
to time travel.
But you've been
helping him, too.
From the moment we realized only
Savage could save the world,
we've been using the Oculus
to manipulate you.
That's impossible.
Think about it.
Thanks to your efforts,
Vandal Savage was not imprisoned
for the sale of
a nuclear weapon in 1975.
You prevented the Soviet Union
from winning the Cold War
in 1986.
Carter Hall's death provided
Savage's closest lieutenants
preternaturally long lives.
You and your team
have been moving
through the course of time.
We've merely redirected
it and you
to the outcomes
history requires.
(INHALES SHARPLY)
Look.
See for yourself.
You're looking into the past.
You'll see that everything
I've told you is true.
This isn't only the past.
You can also see the future.
Not a possible future.
Not a prediction.
You are looking at events
as they will happen.
What about choice?
What about free will?
Illusions.
The only place in the universe
free will exists
is here at the Vanishing Point.
No!
No matter what you do,
it will happen,
and there is nothing you can do
to stop it.
No, I acted
without your consent.
In defiance of your orders.
Everything I have done
has been to save my family.
No one controls me!
We counted on that, your anger,
on you going rogue.
We needed something
to spur you on.
To give you purpose.
That's why we ordered Savage
to kill your family.
RAY: Rip?
PROFESSOR STEIN: Oh, my God.
They've tortured him.
What did they do to you?
They showed me the truth.
Druce showed me
something called the Oculus.
They've been controlling us all.
Nothing we've done so far
has been of our own accord.
We've been following a script
laid out by the Time Masters.
No. That's not possible.
I refuse to believe that.
Well, you should, Raymond,
because they showed me
your death.
I'm sorry.
PROFESSOR STEIN: You said
the team was in trouble.
What sort of trouble, exactly?
JAX: I'm not sure exactly,
but I'm getting something
from my psychic connection.
Which means, I'm in trouble.
What happens?
Come on, Grey,
you know I can't tell you that.
Says who?
Says you in the future.
- Oh.
- And even if I didn't have to worry
about the dangers
of giving you future knowledge,
we got bigger things
to worry about.
And you're drawing
too much power
from the sequestrian manifold.
That's nonsense, Jefferson.
Need I remind you who invented
the sequestrian manifold?
(FIZZLING)
- Oh, dear God!
- Yeah.
Well, you were right.
Oh, don't sound so surprised.
Well, it's not often
that an auto mechanic
knows more
than a nuclear physicist.
You know, I forgot
how arrogant you were.
"Were"?
Why are you referring to me
in the past tense?
Do you witness my death?
Relax.
You don't die.
Horribly maimed?
Why won't you tell me
what happens?
Instead of pestering me
about the future,
and being
an insufferable know-it-all,
why don't you help me reroute
the temporal flow
off the secondary buffer
instead of just worrying
about yourself?
Hmm?
All right.
(GASPS)
I apologize for how painful
the induction process was.
Many of your memories
were rooted deep.
Took effort to pull them out.
Tell me,
what is your name?
- (GROANS)
- Your name.
Your name.
- Your--
- Chronos.
Release him.
There is much hunting
to be done.
Let us begin with Sara Lance
and Leonard Snart.
This is a bad plan.
It's Gideon's.
You're not helping
your argument.
We need to finish putting these
on the ships,
so we can get back
to the Waverider.
(STEADY BEEPING)
I can't just stand around here
and wait to die.
Well, if it's any consolation,
you're not alone.
What? You're giving up, too?
Well, let's just review our
situation, shall we, Raymond?
They're turning Mr. Rory
back into Chronos,
I'm about to have
a nuclear meltdown--
And our captain thinks
that our future
is already written for us.
You know what I think?
I think you both
are a couple of quitters.
There's no escape from neither
these cells or from the future.
Face the facts, Raymond,
we're completely out of allies.
You're forgetting
Sara and Snart.
As long as they're on the loose,
we still have a chance.
GIDEON: Just another moment.
I'm almost through.
SNART: Even if this works,
we're never going to be able
to fly out of here.
SARA: Well, that's the beauty
of having a Timeship,
you don't have to fly anywhere.
Can you stop doing that?
Why did you start wearing
that thing, anyways?
It's from the first job
I ever pulled off with Mick.
Freeport warehouse.
Aw, you do have a sentimental side.
It's not a keepsake.
It's a reminder.
Of what?
That even the best laid plans
can go sideways.
Spent a lot of time
prepping for that heist.
Casing the target,
memorizing shift changes
and delivery schedules,
and then, surprise, turns out
they had upgraded
their security system.
We had to bolt.
Three weeks of planning,
and all I have to show for it...
Was a lousy pinky ring.
So sad.
Considering I'm about to trade
my life for nothing,
I think I came out ahead.
- (POWERING UP)
- GIDEON: The time drive is back online.
Strap in.
Sir, the Waverider
just time-jumped.
Order all available Timeships
to pursue.
Sir, the captains
aren't prepared for--
All of them!
(BEEPING)
(POWERING UP)
Godfrey, what's happening?
GODFREY: I'm sorry, Captain.
Critical systems are being
overridden by an external...
(GODFREY SINGING)
Godfrey?
Godfrey, reboot.
(POWERING DOWN)
Your friends
have time-jumped away.
We've lost them, and I've lost
any reason to keep you alive.
Hold on. Let's just talk
about this a moment.
Time Master Druce.
Kill them all.
- Starting with him.
- Yes, sir.
But we've calculated
when the Waverider is headed.
Past or future?
- The present.
- (EXPLOSION)
(GROANS)
Somebody order up a rescue?
Mr. Snart,
your timing is impeccable.
Or not.
Put the gun down, Mick.
Chronos, fire.
Sure thing.
If I recall,
I made you a certain promise.
(GROANS)
No! I beg of you!
- No!
- (SQUELCHING)
Where's everyone else?
Uh, Mr. Snart
is helping the professor
get situated in the MedBay.
Not doing so hot
without his nuclear super-half.
Get me out of this stupid
robot suit.
First, get us the hell
out of here! Gideon!
GIDEON: I'm here, Captain.
And if I could take a moment
to add
how wonderful it feels
to be back together.
I have missed you, too.
Now that we've had our reunion,
I should mention
we have a slight problem.
The Time Masters are locking
on to us with a tractor beam.
Punch it, Gideon.
Sorry, your job.
No, Ms. Lance,
stay right where you are.
You're proving yourself quite
adept at piloting this ship.
About the tractor beam...
Dr. Palmer's going to help me
remotely disable it.
GIDEON: I've already established
an uplink
to the omnimatrix
mainframe, Captain.
The Time Masters are evil,
but they're not dumb.
There's no way they're going
to let Gideon override
- the tractor beam remotely.
- (RUMBLING)
Whatever you're gonna do,
you better do it now.
They've locked on.
Wait, what if we convince
the system
that the override command
is coming from somewhere else?
- Or someone else.
- Someone they trust.
Just need to borrow
Chronos' operating system.
GIDEON: I'm hot swapping Mr. Rory's
hard drive as we speak.
Whatever you're doing,
do it faster!
And done!
(BEEPING)
Now, Sara!
(POWERING UP)
(JAX SIGHS)
Well, I suppose,
it's time to say good-bye.
At least, for now.
Oh, one more thing,
don't forget to initiate the--
The quantum attenuator
once I lock
on to the Vanishing Point.
Right. (SIGHING)
I suppose it's also time
to apologize
for being
an insufferable know-it-all.
(CHUCKLES) You know,
you used to drive me crazy.
But I understand
it's just your way
of trying to look out for me.
Oh, by the way,
I'm going to be real pissed
about this whole roofie thing.
But I do get over it.
Roofie thing?
- (STAMMERS) I would never dream--
- Yeah. You do. (CHUCKLES)
But it's okay.
It's actually the best decision
I never made.
The future...
You wanted to know what happens.
No, no. It's all right.
I know enough.
The young man in front of me
is proof
that something must have
gone right on this adventure.
- So long, Martin.
- So long, Jefferson.
(JAX SIGHS)
Professor's in the MedBay.
Promises not to blow up
while he's onboard.
Which I thought was considerate.
Yeah, the professor's condition
is the least of our worries,
I'm afraid.
Yeah. Much to my chagrin,
turns out everything we've done,
maybe even our whole lives,
has been determined
by the Time Masters.
What?
The Time Masters have this thing
called the Oculus.
Which allows them
not only to gaze into
the future, but to engineer it.
A future
where I'm dead, apparently.
And why would they want
you dead?
Have you ever listened
to what comes out of his mouth?
Now, in my opinion, Dr. Palmer's
death is not part of their plan.
No. That's not reassuring.
Ow!
You're saying the Time Masters
wanted me to do that?
What I'm saying
is that they've been engineering
our lives to move
in very specific directions
and we are playing out
that script, even now.
So we can go to 2016,
but that might be
what the Time Masters want.
Or we could go get Kendra
and Carter--
Which could also be
what they want.
Then we need to do
what they don't want.
If the Oculus is what
they're using to control us,
then, we need to destroy it.
But how do we do that
if the Time bastards
are pulling our strings?
Druce told me that the Oculus'
ability to control our actions
doesn't work in
the Vanishing Point.
Most likely because
the Vanishing Point
itself exists outside of time.
Explains why we were able
to escape.
And why we might actually have
a shot at destroying this thing.
- I'm with Ray.
- Ow.
If I'm gonna be
someone's puppet,
I'm gonna be one
who cuts his own bloody strings.
And I like blowing stuff up.
We set out on this mission to
stop Savage and save the world.
To become legends
and change our fates.
That mission hasn't changed.
This is madness.
I like it.
Gideon.
Plot a course
to the Oculus Wellspring.
Team...
I think it's about time
we seized our destinies back.
Mmm.
- If I'm gonna die...
- Huh.
...no sense watching my diet.
Time Masters have been known
to make mistakes, you know.
What if those mistakes
were all part of their plan?
Actually, I gotta stop thinking
about it.
The temporal implications
are infinite.
That's why I don't think.
- Not bad, right?
- Good.
- So, how did you do it?
- Do what?
How did you not get turned
into Chronos?
You said the only way you held
on to yourself, the first time,
was by focusing on your hate.
What did I focus on this time?
The team.
And how much you cared for us?
And thought about how royally
screwed you'd be without me.
My point being,
if I can survive
not being turned into Chronos,
you can survive anything
they throw at you.
Thanks. I'll keep it in mind.
Well, you better.
Because if you tell the team
I actually care,
I'll shave your head.
Wow. This is good.
Not in the mood.
I was gonna apologize
for pulling a gun on you.
But apparently,
I was just following a script.
Doesn't make you
any less of a jerk.
Guilty.
So, what do we think
of Rip's plan?
Does it matter?
Apparently,
everything we're gonna do
has already been predetermined
by Rip's former bosses.
It's funny.
I've always prided myself
on being the guy
who doesn't play by the rules.
Come to find out,
I'm the one being played.
I don't know.
I still feel responsible
for everything I've done.
And it still keeps me up
at night.
It's the things I didn't do,
that keep me up at night.
- What's that?
- Oh, I don't know.
Maybe it's being on this ship,
traveling through time.
Started to wonder what
the future might hold for me.
And you.
And me and you.
You want to steal
a kiss from me, Leonard?
You better be
one hell of a thief.
How are you feeling, Martin?
Well, I'm dying.
I'm also sure that you're dying
and so are all the others.
I'm just a little ahead of you.
Normally, I'd be quite
concerned, but the truth is
discovering one's life has
already been predetermined, is
ironically liberating.
I've already run through
everything we know
about the Oculus.
And with the help of a few
back-of-the-envelope
physics calculations,
I've determined that
we have a chance.
Infinitesimal as that may be.
GIDEON: Captain. We've arrived
at the Oculus Wellspring
on the far side
of the Vanishing Point.
Based on
Captain Hunter's description,
the Oculus is a massive,
temporal computer,
most likely powered
by a scaled-down supernova
contained at the bottom
of the Wellspring.
Why aren't any of you
more excited about this?
We're excited to blow it up.
Dr. Palmer will deactivate
the core containment supernova,
which should create
an anomalistic event.
- A very big explosion.
- Sounds like a plan.
- (THUD)
- (POWERING DOWN)
(POWERING UP)
DRUCE: Hello again, Rip.
Right on schedule.
Uh, I think
we've walked into a trap.
No. It's destiny.
DRUCE: I must say, you've all
played your parts well.
As with everything else
you've done,
I'm afraid
it was all for nothing.
All your posturing.
All your claims about doing
what's best for the timeline,
about protecting history,
it all comes down
to cold-blooded murder.
The difference between
murder and execution,
is only a matter of authority.
I have it.
You don't.
Kill them.
(POWERING UP)
(FIRING)
(GROANING)
(PROFESSOR STEIN CHUCKLES)
GIDEON: Returning the Jumpship
to the Waverider.
Good luck, Mr. Jackson.
Hope I'm not too late.
No, Jefferson.
You're right on time!
- How did you--
- What?
You thought
you were the only one
who knew a thing or two
about time travel?
Good work.
We need to get to the Oculus
before reinforcements arrive.
Take about two minutes
to figure out
how to self-destruct this thing.
We'll buy you some time.
You lot guard the entrance.
Mr. Rory, you're with me.
Now, if you would excuse me.
- I won't be long.
- Savage! Hath-Set!
(WHISPERING) Please.
Don't do this.
Don't kill Rip's family.
In a cosmic sense,
it's already done.
No! Savage!
(GROANS)
(GRUNTING)
(GROANING)
RORY: Hurry up, Haircut!
RIP: How much longer?
RAY: Well, just about to reverse
the polarity matrix.
Once I do that,
I say we have about two minutes
before this whole place
goes boom.
How big of a boom?
On a scale from one to 10,
a googolplex.
(GROANS)
What are you doing?
Can't work
with all this gear on.
- You can't!
- A working man needs his hands.
- Ray--
- I got this,
- don't worry.
- No, you don't.
This is what I saw.
This is what Druce showed me.
This is how you die.
It's okay. All my life, I've
wanted to make a difference.
Creating a future for you guys
without the
Time Masters' influence,
that counts.
(YELLING)
That said,
I'm in no rush to die.
So, keep them off, okay?
We got you.
Ah!
RORY: Keep firing!
(GROANING)
(GRUNTS) I'm not doing this
because I like you.
Yes. I know.
(FIRING CONTINUES)
All right. Almost done. (GRUNTS)
Uh-oh.
- Uh-oh.
- Uh-oh?
There seems to be a fail-safe.
To prevent tampering.
Which probably includes
trying to blow this thing up.
English, Haircut.
I have to maintain contact
with the fail-safe
in order to destroy the Oculus.
Not that much English.
(SCREAMS)
Get back to the ship.
We are not leaving without you.
We've already seen the future.
I'm dead already.
You're right.
(GRUNTING)
- Mick.
- I got this.
I want revenge
on those bastards.
Now get out of here.
(SCREAMING)
Your mother was brave.
Just as your father was foolish.
Which are you?
We're leaving!
Where's Raymond and Mick?
Well, Ray is in my pocket
and Mick has elected to stay.
Why?
Someone needs to be present
to destroy the Oculus.
Mick has elected himself.
No, no, no, you can't!
There isn't time!
You gotta go!
(SCREAMING)
(FIRING)
(EXPLOSION)
SNART: Mick!
RORY: Get out of here.
Not without you, Mick.
Pretty boy said I gotta hold
this stick for the ship to blow.
So, I'm holding this stick.
Now leave!
My old friend...
- Please, forgive me.
- For what?
- Get him out of here!
- No.
Just do it.
You take after your mother, huh?
Or not.
No. Shut it down!
Shut it down!
There are no strings on me.
(POWERING UP)
RAY: He traded his life for ours.
He was a hero.
Which, I'm pretty sure,
is the last thing
he wanted to be remembered as.
But that's what he was.
- Gideon.
- GIDEON: Yes, Captain?
Would you please review
the timeline for me?
There is no timeline data due to
the destruction of the Oculus.
We're sailing without a map.
(CHUCKLES)
(GROANS)
Would you please
review news accounts
from 2166, then?
You know what I need
to find out.
GIDEON: I'm sorry, Captain.
News accounts from 2166
confirm that Vandal Savage
has already succeeded
in murdering Miranda and Jonas.
(DOOR OPENING)
Hey.
Get out. I want to be alone.
Gideon has confirmed that
the Oculus has been destroyed.
From here on out,
it's tabula rasa.
Pretend for a minute
I don't speak Greek.
Latin.
Sorry.
From this point forward,
our actions are our own.
We have free will.
Is that supposed to make me
feel better?
Yes. It means that
Leonard didn't die for nothing.
He planted that on me
before it happened.
I'm sorry, Mick.
I killed Declan. Druce is dead.
The Time Masters have nothing,
now that their ship
is completely destroyed.
Yet, I still feel a need
to kill someone for Snart.
Savage still has Carter
and Kendra.
He'll do nicely.
Oh, don't weep
for the dead, Chay-Ara.
They're mortal.
They're beneath us.
I want to speak
with Time Master Druce.
Mr. Savage.
I wish to speak with Druce.
Time Master Druce is dead.
Hunter.
We've lost the ability
to manipulate time.
And how is that a concern to me?
You are beyond our aid,
Mr. Savage.
We cannot help you any longer.
And what of the threat
of the Thanagarians?
Without the Oculus,
time is unmoored.
Events will no longer unfold
as we've foreseen.
Or as we've engineered.
SAVAGE: Terminate transmission.
(KENDRA LAUGHING)
Looks like your friends
have cut you loose.
How long do you think
you can hold on to power
without the Time Masters
backing you?
Not long, I'm afraid.
But they have provided me
with a Timeship.
I no longer need
to rule the world, Chay-Ara.
I now have the ability
to change it.
(POWERING UP)