Previously on "Legends of Tomorrow"...
What kind of egg is that?
- It's a dragon egg.
- Oh.
Okay, you got possessed by Neron.
I can't stop!
I give up. Do you hear me, Neron?
Spare Nate and I'll let you have me.
- Neron?
- I can make you whole again.
- My nipple.
- Gary, no!
Nora, I need your help.
I am asking you to face another demon
as a member of the Time Bureau.
Let's do this.
All right, enough of the
sightseeing. Can we go now?
I'm a bit knackered, to
be honest with you, mate.
We're not here as tourists, Johnny.
Ah, right, you're gonna get rid of me
in some dramatic fashion.
Get on with it, will you?
I'm not gonna kill you. Not yet, anyway.
- I need you for a favor.
- Is that right?
Mm, I need you to open
up a doorway to hell.
Oh, right. Well, why didn't you say so?
I will gladly open
up a vortex right here
and give you the old
heave-ho to the great beyond.
The door is not for me, Johnny.
It's to bring someone
here from the other side.
Tabitha. Ah, that's right.
If she comes straight
through the doorway,
she doesn't need a human vessel.
And what in that demented
demon brain of yours
makes you think that I'm going
to open a vortex for you, eh?
Unlike Gary, I've still
got both my nipples,
so you don't have much to bargain with.
Speaking of which,
what have you done with the Muppet?
Gary's just fine.
He's back at the Time Bureau
taking care of business.
Okay, Nora, you can do this.
Just... be normal.
You can be normal.
'Cause you are normal.
- Next.
- Come on!
That's your ID picture?
They wouldn't let me retake it.
Oh, it can't be that bad. Let me see.
Uh, maybe we'll just use your
photo from the wanted poster.
So your ID is in process.
And you have me to help
you with your orientation.
All that's left is this.
What the hell's that?
It's your start paperwork.
No, I should be out looking for Ray.
I really have to fill all this out?
I know. I know, Nora.
But until we have a line on Neron,
there's really nothing we can do.
And let's be honest, Nora.
You have a storied history here.
I need you to prove that
you can be a team player.
Have fun.
Oh, and you know what, Nora?
I'm really, really proud of you.
Welcome to the Bureau.
Director Sharpe. I've
been waiting for you.
Gary, I told you, no
playing with my chair
until after hours.
Oh, playtime's over.
Shut the door.
We need to talk.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
If Neron wanted John dead,
he would have killed him on the spot.
He must need something from him.
We have to find them before
he can get what he wants.
Who knows what he's
doing in Ray's name...
or his perfectly grass-fed
organic butter body?
If Haircut's even there.
We don't know that Ray is gone.
Look, everybody just breathe.
Gideon's already on it.
I've attuned the magic-o-meter
to Constantine's frequency.
When he uses his abilities, I
can zero in on his location.
And what do we do till then?
- Stress eat.
- Drink.
Yeah, how'd you lot survive until now?
Look, until we get an alert, we wait.
Right, we wait.
I gotta go clear my head.
What do you think this is about?
With everything that's been going on,
I bet Director Sharpe is about
to lay down the plan of attack.
I've gathered you here because
today we're setting time aside
to conduct performance reviews.
But this time, I thought
it would be useful
if you were assessed
by one of your peers,
Agent Gary Green.
Gary?
- Seriously?
- Huh?
Thanks, doll.
How are my babies doing?
Let's rap for a sec.
Is Gary cool now?
That's impossible.
Now, I know performance
reviews can be quite a drag,
but this year's gonna be
different 'cause you've got
superagent Gary Green in your corner.
So no need to stress...
unless your infraction is
looking too good in that suit.
Agent Reyes knows
what I'm talking about.
Oh, my God. I think she just swooned.
This is a nightmare.
So I'll be meeting
with agents one-on-one,
and, uh, wait till I call your name.
Looking forward to some good face time.
Ava, are you sure this is the best time
for performance reviews?
There's no better time
to assess the performance
of our operation.
But are you sure Gary's qualified for...
responsibilities?
Of course, Mona.
Gary Green is all the man we need.
Oh, my, what a big,
scary knife you've got.
I'd sooner be filleted
than do your bidding.
This knife is not for you.
It's for Raymond.
The human body is fascinating.
Delicate, fragile.
Did you know that if I
cut this artery right here,
it will take only a matter of minutes
before Ray's body goes into shock
and eventually expires?
Hey, big man.
Come on. I know you're in there.
Snap out of it, eh?
Ray's gone.
I've taken over his
body. We made a deal.
And you of all people
should know what it means
to make a deal with a demon.
Now, if Ray was still in here,
would he do this?
I knew I could make you use your magic.
Great, yeah. So you got me.
What's that big grin all about, eh?
Patience.
You'll see.
Huh, I always took you
to be more Springsteen
than "The Rite of Spring."
It's not for me. It's...
I read that classical
music is good for babies.
Wow, this is very, um, impressive.
Yeah, I found a book about dragons
in Constantine's collection.
"The egg must incubate under the mother
at her body temperature
lest the egg expire."
Yeah, I'm not gonna sit on that thing.
I figured as much. That's
why I got a heat lamp.
We have to do everything possible
to make sure nothing
bad happens to this egg.
- Hey.
- Hmm?
The egg's gonna be okay.
I know it.
Wait till Ray sees
that we have a dragon.
- He's gonna love it.
- Yeah.
I've picked up an alert
with Constantine's magical signature.
That's them.
The signal is coming from
1.3 million years ago.
That's the Ice Age.
He's in the part of North America
that would come to be
known as the Donner Pass,
named after a doomed group
of settlers in the 1800s
who resorted to cannibalism
after their food supplies ran out.
There is such thing as too
much exposition, Gideon.
Hah, there they are. Our heroes.
Captain Lance, thanks
for coming all this way.
If you're looking for Ray,
he's, uh, checked out.
Is Neron on comms?
But if you'd like to join him,
I can make arrangements.
Sara, open fire now.
This may be your only chance.
We can't fire. That's Ray.
Ray made a deal with a demon. He's gone.
We can't lose anyone
else to this bastard.
- Do it.
- What about you?
Blow us both to kingdom come.
I'll be happy to go
to hell for the cause.
Gideon, ready the blasters.
Yes, Captain.
Whoa, whoa. Hold up!
If we kill Neron in Ray's
body, we lose Ray forever.
But if you let Neron walk,
then things are gonna get
much, much worse. Trust me.
Sara? Well, come on, boss.
Something's wrong.
Awaiting orders, Captain.
Gideon...
Fire.
It's a trap!
We gotta move! They're getting away!
Get us out of here, Gideon!
That's not good.
By my calculations,
we're buried beneath 357
feet of ice and snow.
Plus, our primary temporal
delineator has been rendered
nonfunctional with the extreme weather.
Well, so that's it, then?
We're just snowed in?
Yeah, at the Donner Pass.
No one's turning me into beef jerky!
Everyone calm down.
Gideon, hail the Bureau.
Should we leave a voice mail?
Ava will get the alert.
In the meantime, we wait.
Gideon, how long until the ice thaws?
The Ice Age ends in 11,121 years.
All right, who we eating first?
'Cause shotgun, not.
Captain, we're running
on reserve power.
I recommend disabling all
nonessential functions
to conserve energy
for life support.
Do it.
We need to be responsible
and conserve power.
Cut off the main
generator, the fabricator,
and the thermostat.
Neron is out there
with Ray and Constantine
all because we fell for his
trap because you fired on Ray.
And what was your plan, pretty?
Beat him to death in a snowball fight?
We were supposed to take him in,
- not take him out, Mick.
- Ray's gone!
When a team member goes dark,
you end them before they end you.
Rory, with me.
You made the call.
You're helping us get out of here.
- No problem.
- All right.
Always assumed I'd go out alone, anyway.
First you kill my friends,
and now you bring me
to this miserable era.
Oh, Johnny, quit being such a crybaby.
I just did what I had to do.
Can't have your friends
getting in the way of us
creating that door to hell.
There's still no way I'm helping you.
Besides, the vortexes I
make are strictly one-way.
They suck you in.
And don't you think, if my
magic was powerful enough
to stabilize a vortex, I
wouldn't have saved Desmond
or Astra?
Yes, and that's why we're here.
As powerful as your magic
is, you can always teach
an old dog new tricks.
And it's more than magic
that you need to learn.
Oh, yeah, right.
So I'm supposed to
learn something off one
of these yokels, am I?
No, Johnny.
Not from them.
From a king.
Hold on a minute. That
bloke's got my face.
That's because he's your ancestor.
King Konstentyn, ruler of these parts
and progenitor of
your magical bloodline.
What kind of creature do
you think they're hunting?
Can't be sure,
but I'm guessing it wasn't rabbits.
Make way for your king!
Start paperwork, am I right?
My forms keep getting
rejected because records show
I'm 15 and living in
a mental institution.
I forget that we don't have
normal problems anymore.
Speaking of which, Ava's having Gary
- do performance reviews.
- Okay.
I mean, he's not my first
choice for... responsibilities,
but don't we have bigger issues?
Exactly.
And when I pointed that
out, Ava shut me down.
Not to stereotype, but I think a clone
might have replaced her,
and we need to look into it.
- No.
- Yes.
- No!
- Yes!
No! I just earned my freedom.
And I don't wanna get caught
going behind Ava's back.
You heard what she said.
I need to focus on being a team player.
She said Gary is all the man we need.
That's not weird to you?
Why is that weird?
Gary Green is all the man we need.
Okay, I will check on Gary,
and you contact the Waverider
and see if Sara knows anything.
- Mm-hmm.
- And then...
we're gonna find out what form 37-C is.
Okay.
Ah, this is useless!
Why don't we just blast a way out?
Using your heat gun in here, Mr. Rory,
will deplete our low supply of oxygen.
Yeah, ease up, Mick.
Last time you pulled the trigger,
we ended up here.
You're pissed at me
for firing on Haircut.
Well, it's a good thing
that this Snart bloke
kept a supply of
jackets, though, isn't it?
They smell good too, actually.
What is that? Is it sandalwood?
Look, I'm pissed at you because that
- wasn't your call to make.
- Someone had to make it.
It was our only chance
to take out Neron.
I made the call you should have.
All right, guys, come on.
Just pick away, will you?
No, this is good.
All of a sudden, now you
care about the mission?
Where were you when Neron
took Ray in the first place?
Oh, you're gonna put that on me as well!
All right, as much as I wanna
watch you guys duke it out,
lets save it for when
we're not freezing to death.
You know what?
Both of you off scamming
people at some book convention
while there is a demon on our ship.
Mm, let me get this straight, Captain.
You're the only one that
can have fun outside of this
rusted bucket of bolts?
All you do is spend
time with the girlfriend
and nothing's ever, ever your fault!
You know what?
You have all the answers.
You get us out of here.
Oh, when I was a boy,
we used to run wild
in these woods around the village.
Not a care in the world.
These same woods where
your children play today
and where my hunting
party just encountered
another dangerous beast that
threatens not just our safety
but our entire way of life.
Oh, this bloke is right tedious.
Why are we here?
Because I want you to learn
that it was your ancestor
that created the rift
between humans and magical creatures.
And why would he do that?
Because fear is a powerful
source of energy for magic.
The more he exploits these
creatures to stir up fear
in his people, the more powerful
his magic becomes.
I come from a long line of bastards,
but not even we would resort to that.
Because your kin are always so right.
Yes.
And if the king is sending
this creature to hell,
then surely it deserves it.
Do you really think
that everyone in hell
deserves to be there?
What about Astra
or Raymond Palmer
or my Tabitha?
This is your opportunity
to make things right,
starting with her.
You know, if your plan is to guilt me
into doing what you want
by showing me the sins
of my forefather, it
ain't working, sunshine.
But to another.
Behold the unholy beast!
Hold on a minute. That's a Púca.
May not look threatening, but sometimes
in order to see the true
nature of a creature,
one must draw it out.
No, no, no. He's got it all wrong.
They aren't evil.
Guess your bloodline isn't as
righteous as you think it is.
He's clearly misinformed.
Well, if you think
that, maybe you should go
and have a chat with the king.
You are truly blessed that I am here,
for I alone can save
you from these monsters.
And tonight at the rise of the low moon,
I will banish this
creature straight to hell.
Agent Powell, please report to my office
for your performance review.
Just need a signal on the Waverider.
That's weird.
What are you doing in here?
Uh, just thought I would
check on the timeline.
Yep, looks good.
You have clearance for this?
Have you completed
your performance review?
Yes, I've had my performance review.
And how did it go?
Gary Green is all the man we need.
Mm.
Nora!
You were right. We have to talk.
But we can't do it here.
The heat lamp must have turned off
when Sara shut down the generator.
It's okay, Wickstable.
You're gonna be okay.
What... what did you call it?
Wickstable.
The drawing I made of
Heyworld when I was a kid,
the one that inspired
my dad, the dragon in it,
I named it Wickstable.
I thought we could just name it that.
But I'm open to other ideas.
No, uh, I-I like... I like Wickstable.
Our little Wicksty.
I can't believe I'm about to say this,
but I think it needs
skin-to-skin contact
like the book said.
I think it's working.
Hey, uh, why does it
feel like we skipped past
all the fun stuff into, you know, this?
We can still do the fun stuff.
What about the egg?
Um, there's other ways
we could create heat.
Seriously, dude?
Yeah.
Come on, Gideon.
There's gotta be a way
to boost the engines.
Ray would know how to read this.
How much longer do we
have on life support?
Power reserves are at 34 hours, Captain.
- Hey, you got a second?
- Not now, Rory.
I actually came here
to apologize for, uh,
blowing up before.
Wow, that's... Thank you.
- And I should have never...
- And another thing!
Give it up, Charlie.
Why were you wearing my face?
And were you about to apologize?
Only because Charlie was catfishing me.
All right, shut up.
Do you think Ray would
be fighting right now?
No, he would be trying
to get us out of here.
Yeah, you're right.
He's always got a plan.
It's annoying.
All right, let's search Ray's quarters,
see if we can find something helpful.
Thanks.
Hmm.
I tried talking to Ava,
and all she'd say was,
"Gary Green is all the man we need."
Gary must be controlling
the Bureau somehow.
It's those performance reviews.
If we can find out how he's doing it,
maybe we can find a way
to snap them out of it.
I can try tapping into my powers,
see if I can read him.
- If I can get to his office...
- No!
We're all we have left.
We can't risk losing each other.
I've got it.
We'll tell Gary you
found some security issues
in the containment cells.
You walk him over here like this.
Then I'll close the cell
doors and you courier out,
- trapping him.
- That's a great idea.
Yeah, just like that.
Okay, it works.
You can let me out now.
I'm sorry. I can't do that right now.
Sure, you can. Just use the hand thing.
No, Mona, you need a time-out.
Gary Green is all the man we need.
No.
Go and tell the others to
prepare the ritual for tonight.
As you wish, my lord.
You're wasting your time,
focusing on that monster.
A Púca only reflects
the person it's with.
It's only angry because
you scared the fur off it.
That creature doesn't
deserve to go to hell.
I see not why I should heed
the advice of a stranger.
Then perhaps you will heed
the advice... of your kin.
I know not of any kin
outside of this village.
And yet the similarities
of your features...
I'm a cousin from afar and a
practitioner of magic like you.
If you want to rid your
village of a real monster,
then I know of a demon in our midst
that we can banish together.
A demon?
In my village?
Well, then lead the way, my kin.
But this face stealer
with the other creature.
Aye, my liege.
Hell shall have two more guests
by the end of the night.
"Cards to Save the Timeline:
a team-building card
game by Ray Palmer."
Ah, I miss hating him.
You remember that night when we all met,
standing up on that
rooftop, and Rip told us
that we were gonna be legends?
Mm-hmm, embarrassing.
You know what?
We're the last of the originals.
Weird.
Yeah, weird.
Legends were different back then.
We were different back then.
Look, I know that book convention
was important to you.
And I'm really glad that you got to go.
I'm glad you have Ava.
Thanks.
Guess we're growing up...
and hopefully not growing apart.
Ah, here we are.
What is it?
"Ray Palmer's Survival Guide."
Let me see this.
Oh, hey.
"What to do if you're
caught in an avalanche."
Uh-huh, what does it say?
Yeah, we've already tried all of these.
"If all fails, remember
you still have each other,
so enjoy that as long as it lasts."
Ah, we're dead.
Yeah. Maybe.
Hey, it's all right, little one.
I don't bite.
Ah!
I see your talk went well.
Knew you'd be here.
Ah, so I come from a long
line of bloody bastards.
Big reveal.
Have you even considered
what it's really gonna be like
for you in hell with all those
pissed-off folks you sent there
just waiting for you?
Including my Tabitha.
Tabitha.
Who is this bird, anyway?
Why is she so important?
- Who is she?
- Yeah.
You're just like your ancestor.
So convinced you're always right.
You don't even know
who you're sending away.
Fitting that he's about
to do the same to you.
But once you see how
powerful magic can be
when fueled by fear,
you can save yourself
from being sucked to hell.
Oh, you would love for me
to stabilize that vortex,
wouldn't you?
You see, the thing is,
I'm not afraid of going to hell.
I've always counted on the fact
that I'd end up there one day
no matter what.
And what about this
innocent creature beside you?
Well, I guess I'm just a
bloody bastard, then, aren't I?
What's the bad news now?
Oh, no bad news.
And no more fighting.
Gideon, fire up the ship.
If I do that, life support capacity
will be reduced by half.
You heard me, Gideon.
Turn on the fabricators
and turn on the heat.
I'm thinking s'mores,
maybe some hot cocoa.
The captain's gone mad.
She's not mad. She's right.
I could go for a s'more.
Look, Ray would want us to have faith
that we will escape.
He wouldn't want us cold and miserable.
So right now, we are going
to enjoy our time together.
Let's go.
Finally. Let's get some music going.
Who's gonna bring me
food if I'm stuck in here?
This is how I'm gonna die, isn't it?
Without any books or laughter
in the basement of a
government building?
Whoa.
You're right. I'm not alone.
I have you.
I'm sorry you're stuck
here with me, little one.
Ah, you should be out there
in the woods, frolicking about.
Or whatever it is you
Púcas get up to these days.
You know, to tell you the truth,
I'm bloody well terrified.
No.
It's not the eternity of torture
or the people who are after my head, no.
It's that I'll have to
watch Raymond and Astra
and all the others I've failed
be tortured along with me.
Even led the Legends to their death.
And you're next in line.
Yeah, that's right.
You sense the rottenness
inside me, don't you?
No better than the bloody king.
Why would you heal a bastard like me?
Up with you.
Time to see the king.
All right, then, little one.
Let's go see what this
party's all about, shall we?
We live in a world of
wonder and amazement.
At times, it's beautiful, breathtaking.
At other times, cruel, dangerous...
And monstrous.
Before you are two foul
creatures of the dark,
one a grotesque woodland creature
that would not hesitate
to tear out your heart,
the other an imposter,
a wielder of the dark arts
that would usurp my very body and soul.
Now, my people, I seek your wisdom
in these matters.
What would you have me do
with such wretched beasts?
To hell! To hell!
To hell! To hell! To hell!
We're very excited for you to receive
your performance review.
But what actually
happens at the meeting?
Feel free to give me any spoilers.
Don't worry. I had my doubts too.
But then I met with Gary and realized
Gary Green is all the man we need.
Bye.
Please step forward, Ms. Wu.
Take a seat. Make yourself comfortable.
Mint?
Eh, no, thanks.
Don't mind if I do.
Let's see.
Mm.
I see you've made quite an impression
in your brief time here.
But lately you've been slacking off.
It says right here
you've been very disloyal
to the Time Bureau.
Not yet, Wolfie.
Okay, I'll judge this round.
You and your team are
stuck in a trash compactor
in an impromptu and possibly
fatal homage to "Star Wars."
What do you do?
Boom, that's the one.
- Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
- Yep.
Ooh, gonna have to go with,
"Steel up as Sara scales a wall."
- Another point for me.
- Favoritism!
Why would I display favoritism?
'Cause you two are obviously shagging.
- What?
- Hmm?
Yeah.
Yes, finally! This is great.
Maybe you guys won't be so weird now.
Okay, I'll judge next.
A teammate turns on you,
lost to the dark side.
What do you do?
Mm.
"Escape via musical number."
Not this time.
"Fabricate eveningwear
and infiltrate a party."
You guys know I love a good party sneak.
"Don't give up on each
other. Work together.
You're more than a
team. You are a family."
Well, I guess that
card's the winner, then.
Point to Charlie. I'm on the board.
- The hell was that?
- Due to your reckless use
of our rapidly depleting energy,
internal temperature
of the ship has melted
the surrounding ice enough
to shake the ship loose.
What do we do?
We work as a team.
Zari, engine room. Get
the thrusters back online.
Seal the cargo bay. You two with me.
My dear people!
I hear your cries and feel your anger.
And therefore, by your command,
I send these creatures
where they belong.
Straight to hell!
Straight to hell! Straight to hell!
Begone, you unclean beasts!
Come on, Johnny. You
know what you need to do.
Oh, bollocks.
Here. Run, run.
What have you done?
I've used your own magic against you.
We may be kin, but we are not the same.
Now, you may not agree with my methods,
but I will always protect my people.
Now, the question is, Ms. Wu,
what shall we do about your disloyalty?
Uh, maybe...
I lose my snack room
privileges for a week.
Oh, no! Not my almonds!
Oh, I wouldn't worry about your almonds.
Because as I'm sure you've heard,
Gary Green is all the man you need.
Now, gaze into the nipple.
Wolfie! Now!
What's a Wolfie?
W-W-W-Wolfie?
Bravo.
I knew you could exploit
fear to make yourself
even more powerful.
Well, it looks like
you taught this old dog
some new tricks after all.
But now I'm gonna use those
new tricks to strike you down.
You know, I do have a
few tricks of my own.
We're running on very low reserve power.
The odds of us successfully
pushing through the avalanche
above us are 3,720 to 1.
Never tell me the odds, Gideon.
Everyone hold on tight.
Oh, this better work.
It will.
- You got Wicksty?
- Yeah, I'm not letting go.
Come on, come on.
- Boom!
- Whoo!
Yes!
All systems are back online, Captain.
Fantastic, Gideon.
Now let's go find Constantine and Ray.
Oh, damn executive privacy button.
Uh, hey.
Can you do me a solid and
press that button over there,
if you...
Do you really think I'm letting
you get out of here alive?
Help!
Get away from him, you beast!
What happened?
I don't know.
But I'm guessing he had
something to do with it.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
It may be too late to save Ray
or Desmond or the Legends.
But at least I'll get to send
you back where you belong.
Oh, you bastards. You did it.
You bloody survived.
I've never been so happy
to be wrong in my life.
Don't do it, John. Don't kill him.
Don't give up on Haircut.
What are you gonna do, Johnny?
You're all out of moves.
No, I'm not.
I'll see you lovely lot at the end.
I'm gonna save Ray.
John!
The magic-o-meter's picking up
strange activity on the ground.
Tabitha, show yourself.
Ah.
So wonderful to be back.
Brimstone was so awful
for my complexion.
Oh, but you look ravishing, my love.
Hold on. Is he kissing...
Oh, the Fairy Godmother.
Is that tongue?
More singing.
We're so screwed.
Come with me, my pet.
Let's find you a new host.
It's his nipple.
He tried to hypnotize
Mona with his nipple.
His nipple?
Neron gave you back your
nipple which became bad in hell,
which is now poisoning your
mind and making you evil,
and that's why you came
back to the Time Bureau...
So that you could nip-notize everyone
- and Neron could take over.
- Yeah.
You will do no more
harm with your nipple!
No, no, no, no!
No, no, please no!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
It wasn't me. It was my nipple.
I swear.
Save me!
As you wish.
You have to go.
Tell the Legends what's going on.
- Wait, what about you?
- I'm not leaving Mona behind.
Always knew you were a team player.
Ava. You okay?
It's a long story, but
Gary took over the Bureau.
He nip-notized everyone.
Yeah, you're gonna have to explain that.
The germ turned.
Well, it's not just
him. It's Neron and...
The Fairy Godmother, Tabitha.
She's Tabitha?
Yeah, you missed a lot.
And Ray is still in hell.
I know he hasn't given up,
so we're not gonna give up on him.
Now, let's do this...
for Ray.
Bloody hell.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --