Previously,
onLegends Of Tomorrow...
- I'm Charlie.
- We're The Smell. We're a band.
She's a shapeshifter.
Remember when we dented history?
I have encountered a glitch
during the Heyworld event.
- Find me.
- Your sister is the dent.
Maybe her being here,
she'll remember who she was.
Hope The Smell plays
Assassination Nation, tonight.
Could give a rat's ass
what they play,
long as Charlie isn't AWOL
two nights in a row.
Six quid. Don't be cheeky.
Ian's dead, Dec.
We've got to get out of here
before that psycho finds us.
What do you want?
Clotho.
Who the bloody hell is a Clotho?
The lead singer of your band.
You mean Charlie? She left days ago.
Don't hurt me.
My sister should know by now
she can't outrun fate.
Wait. Are we screaming because this
is weird, or because it's awesome?
This is...
a nightmare.
How did I even get in your room?
You slept walked into Dr. Heywood's
room at approximately 2.30am.
I tried to wake you,
but you assaulted my mainframe,
repeating, snooze.
All right,
let's just be cool about this, okay?
I still have my pajamas on,
which means we didn't...
- Oh, my God.
- Like, take it easy.
You slept walked into my room,
which means something
must have brought you in here,
and let's not forget,
in another timeline, you and I...
Wait, don't start with
the dream girl crap.
I'm still trying to process
how I spent the last five hours on...
- What is this, 200-thread count?
- Yeah.
I got to go.
You're up early.
What are you doing?
Looks like somebody was playing
Operation with Gideon's mainframe.
Or maybe it was something.
You think they have raccoons
in the temporal zone?
- Actually, Mr. Tarazi, it was...
- Snooze, Gidget!
Hey. You left this in my bedroom.
- Oh, wow!
- Well, looky, looky.
- We didn't hook up.
- We did not hook up.
It doesn't have to be a walk of shame
if you enjoyed it.
But if you're walking at all,
you didn't enjoy it enough.
Gross, Charlie.
Hey, B, me and Z did not do,
you know...
- No.
- The nasty.
This is a judgment free zone.
I'm not one to shame the sexual
activity of two consenting adults.
Shame's a good thing.
Keeps you from hooking up
with someone and...
ending up the parent
of a 16-year-old daughter.
Oh, ooh! Well, what naughty business
have I stumbled across, then?
Nothing, we just...
We like hanging out
in the hallways, now...
Goodbye.
Well, then, Charlie,
we have some business to attend to,
love.
We do, but first whiskey.
All right, then.
A stiff drink may indeed be in order.
I have some rather unfortunate news
for you, Charlie.
Charlie.
We came as soon as we heard.
Look, the Prognosticator's scanning
the timeline for Encore activity.
Trust me, we're going to figure out
who's responsible for this.
This wasn't the work of an Encore.
This was my sister. Atropos.
How can you tell?
The victim was burned
from the inside.
She's a God.
That's her signature move.
Well, I'm sorry about your friends,
Charlie,
but your sister just fired one hell
of a warning shot.
Now we need to get back out there
and find that Loom piece
before she does.
God. Will you just piss off, John?
Hey, Charlie...
Look, I'm sorry,
I've... I've lost friends, too.
I know what you're going through.
Look, I respect your condolences,
but you don't have a bloody clue
what I'm going through.
Well, she's right.
We're putting the hunt
for the Loom on hold.
And it's probably for the best.
With Ray gone,
we're still trying to find our feet.
It gives us time to make a game plan.
But we do have a game plan.
We need to get the next piece.
Look, John, if you want to help,
then look into what we're up against.
She's a God.
I don't want to take the team
into a situation we can't get out of.
Yeah, yeah, all right. All right.
I overstepped the mark, didn't I?
I'm sorry.
I am sorry, Charlie.
But my promise to Astra and her mum
cannot wait for your tears to dry.
Ostende mihi viam.
Welcome back... sis.
Lachesis.
You smell of that slowly dying world
filled with apathy.
Any luck?
Clotho has taken on a vulgar
mortal name.
Charlie.
Oh, this is too good to be true.
Elaborate.
My protege, Astra, happens to know
of a time-traveler
who's looking for our Loom.
One of his companions is a woman
who goes by Charlie.
A time-traveler.
That's how Clotho has eluded me.
Fortunately,
I can track John Constantine.
Without Fate, the mortals are making
a mess of their lives.
With our Loom,
order can be restored.
Find John Constantine,
and you'll find our sister.
And when you do...
make it a hell of a family reunion.
Gideon, the next time
John steals the Jumpship,
a little heads-up would be nice.
Thanks to Ms. Tarazi,
I'm still stuck on snooze mode.
Is your sister just looking for you,
or is she looking for the Loom?
Both, I reckon.
We have to go after him.
"We"?
That bastard is the reason
I'm mortal, I don't owe him squat.
He's going after the ring.
You're the only one who knows
where he's headed.
Look, we'll be in and out.
Okay, fine.
The sooner we get going, the sooner
I can get back to drinking in peace.
Great, let's portal.
Parenting sucks!
Maybe I should stay, huh?
Are you volunteering for Rory duty?
Ava Sharpe,
you are a better woman than I.
Okay, babe,
catch you on the flip side.
Stay safe.
The ring's that way.
He couldn't have gotten too far.
Let's gear up in the Jumpship.
Kid's not into bears, huh?
- She ripped its head off.
- Yeah, I see that.
Well, like father, like daughter.
I mean, hey, you should be proud.
At least she's tough like you.
She said I ruined her life.
Now I got to portal back
to that stupid reunion party
and stop myself from sleeping
with Ali.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. There are so many
reasons why that's a bad idea.
- Don't care.
- Stop!
You can't just erase
your daughter's existence, Mick.
There... there has to be
another option.
What?
What if we go back through
the last 15 years and we...
And we place you into all
of her key memories?
Like a highlight reel?
Yeah, I mean,
it's kind of what Rip did with me,
programmed me with a bunch
of memories
that added up to be a childhood.
It wasn't perfect,
but I turned out okay.
She's not a clone.
Ouch. Yeah, she's not a...
But she is programmable, in a sense.
- Won't work.
- Why?
I spent the first ten years
of her life in prison.
Right.
I have an idea.
You sure hid this one well.
Didn't think I'd ever be coming
back here, did I?
Huh. That's cool!
It looks likeSupernatural's
filming here.
Super what?
You've never seen it?
It's this show about these
two hot brothers who fight demons.
I wonder if the Winchester brothers
are here.
- Seriously?
- Dean is my hall pass.
I bet you used to wild out
back in the day.
There was no drinking on the job.
It's kind of the occupational hazard
of having the fate of humanity
in your hands.
So you guys literally
used to weave fate?
I mean, it's not like it is
in the storybooks, but... yeah.
I spun up the threads of each life.
Old Lachesis, she measured out
how long each life got to be.
And then Atropos, she...
- So she killed...
- Everyone.
And she bloody loved it.
Hello?
Greetings, sibling of mine.
Meow?
You okay, Z?
Is this about the Nate thing?
I hope not, because then I'm going to
be wondering why you just said meow,
and I definitely don't want to know.
I think I may be losing it.
And not like when I saw Tupac's
hologram at the 2044 Grammys...
but, like, mentally losing it.
Something is wrong with me.
Hey, hey! Deep breaths.
This is like a form of therapy where
you get to beat up your problems.
Trust me.
Whoa. Did you just beat me?
Behrad, I don't know how
to play video games.
But it's like I'm being haunted
by someone who does.
Someone who dresses like
a teenage boy
and makes me do awful things like
eat donuts and cuddle with Nate.
Whoa.
- How did you do that?
- How did I do that?
Well, what have we got here?
Oh, what the bloody hell is that?
It's a prop.
Now, what did I tell you
about Loom patrol?
Yeah well, we're out here, aren't we?
So let's just find the damn thing.
Oh, yeah, have you scanned
the woods for activity?
Huh? You have a plan
if Atropos shows up?
Well, I clipped Charlie's
shapeshifter wings.
So no offense, love,
I think I can handle her sister.
Have you not heard anything
Charlie said?
Because it's not gonna be that easy.
- Clotho!
- As long as you're crashing
on my ship, you're my responsibility,
and I say we are going back to figure
out a secure way to do this.
Yeah, well, that Loom is your ticket
to stopping the Encores.
- I'm helping you out.
- You can't hide from your family.
Guys!
The Jumpship.
I'm coming for you, Clotho.
My sister...
She's here.
Ava, we need backup.
Ava!
Damn it. With the Jumpship gone,
the comms are down.
What, so we're stuck here?
The team will come
looking for us eventually.
We need these more than Sam and Dean.
You've walked us right
into a bloody death trap.
And that was my only option,
all right?
If she gets a hand on one piece
of the Loom,
then she can get the next,
and then she's that much closer
to controlling us all.
And I'd bet my bottom dollar
she's out there now looking for it,
not standing around having a row
in the middle of the bloody forest.
Damn it, John.
The stupid thing is that way.
By building Heyworld,
we changed the future,
which caused a bifurcation
in the timeline
radiating from that one moment.
Think of it as a historical traffic
accident, and you're the dent.
Yeah, I'm not thinking of myself
as a dent.
Okay, so what you think
of as a haunting is a temporal echo.
She is the you before...
well, you.
Okay, let's just get
something straight,
there is only one Zari Tarazi.
I filed a trademark.
Do you know what this means?
You were a Legend.
From what you said about the hacking,
you were probably our computer
expert.
And the Air Totem responded to you.
You two probably shared it.
- Wonder Twins!
And we probably had a really
super cute couple name,
just off the top of my head,
probably something like SteelHacker.
The three of us probably hung out
all the time, getting stoned.
- Oh, man.
- Playing ring-toss with donuts.
She probably helped you save
the world.
- More than once.
- Yeah.
She sounds pretty cool, huh?
Yeah.
Yeah, she does.
We got to move faster.
She could be anywhere.
Clotho, you can't escape.
- You okay?
- I'm okay.
We need to keep moving, love.
Where are you now?
Come to me...
or your friends will die.
Charlie?
- Mick?
- What?
I think Ali was discharged
from the hospital early
because a taxi cab
just pulled up outside.
- Wait, this was supposed to be a...
- Yeah.
surprise.
Is that what they're gonna say
at Iron Heights
when they find your empty cell?
What the hell are you doing here,
Mick?
Oh, hi, I'm Ava Sharpe.
I'm Mr. Rory's CO.
Yeah, I arranged for some visitation
in exchange for some information.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Mr. Rory's helped us bring in some
of history's most dangerous...
- criminals.
- What? I...
Okay, well, visiting hours are over.
Me and my baby are tired.
Right.
Wow.
- From the Victorian England time...
- Collection.
Collection at... at Pottery Barn.
I don't know much about
Victorian England, but...
it's really beautiful.
I bet she is, too.
Mick, meet your daughter.
Lita.
Hey, how about we all get together
so that Lita can remember this moment
with her dad forever.
Yeah? Let's take a picture.
Mickey!
Smiles.
Wait a minute.
Did you break into my house?
Garima lifted the king's
decapitated head.
Dumb bastard.
You like that?
Daddy?
Do you believe in the Tooth Fairy?
Yes!
Whoa!
Say, cheese.
Kirk, we can get you new pants.
How's that for a highlight reel?
Pretty good.
Hello, Clotho.
Look at you.
Alone, after destroying our family.
Look, I didn't do it to hurt you,
all right?
We took care of you,
and you took everything we had.
People deserve to be free.
And what have they done
with this freedom you gave them?
They got women the vote.
They invented punk rock.
Introduced mass genocide,
nuclear bombs, pollution,
systematic incarceration.
- No. I didn't...
- And after all you did to help them,
how did they thank you?
By locking you in prison.
We would never let anyone
hurt you like that, little sister.
Now, lead me to our Loom.
And perhaps, in time,
we can forgive you.
Hey!
Why don't you pick on someone
your own size?
John, I could use a little help!
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm on it. I'm on it.
Let's try...
Hemlock! All right, all right. Yes.
Toadstool.
Got it.
Now all I need is a little bit of...
Blood.
Te vocare, veni in auxilium mihi.
Go. Grab Charlie,
get the hell out of here.
I'll find you.
You're gonna be okay. Come on.
Hey, let's wait for John here.
John's dead, Sara.
Atropos doesn't let people live.
Come on. We've got to keep going.
- It's okay.
- It's not.
I mean, you saw what happened
back there. I'm one of them.
No matter what I do, I'm never gonna
be able to escape them.
And now I've gone
and got John killed.
Hey, look, John always finds a way.
Always finds a way to do what?
Oh, thank God.
Yeah. I'd rather not, love.
Hey, your sister,
she's a nasty piece of work,
but it takes more than
amateur knife tricks to do me in.
Now, let's get the hell out of here,
shall we,
before she realizes I'm not
bleeding out on the forest floor.
Who are you?
Talking to donuts now?
LOL.
This alternate timeline stuff's
got you really shaken up, huh?
Ever since Mithra came into my life,
I've been the center of attention.
It's weird to have to share
the spotlight.
Says the older sister
to the younger brother.
Right. Sorry.
Back to me, it's a lot to take in.
I mean, this other Zari sounds so...
smart and substantive,
like a cool third-wave feminist
superhero that you and...
Nate seemed to like better than me.
First off, Nate is just a sucker
for doomed romances.
Secondly, of course
I don't like her better than you.
You're my favorite Zari of all time.
But...
But?
You said you wanted to leave
your whole Z-Nation life behind,
find out what else you're capable of.
This whole situation seems
like a giftwrapped opportunity
for self-exploration.
Self-exploration?
Oh, I propose...
a totem quest.
Go into the totem,
speak to our ancestors.
How do I go into the totem?
With a little psychotropic
assistance.
I knew this would lead to drugs.
It's totally safe.
I've done it in the past when
I've been wrestling with big problem.
It's no crazier than talking
to a donut.
I know that face.
That's the one where you don't want
to admit I'm right.
No, it isn't.
Totem-town, here we come.
She played me like a fiddle.
I almost gave her the Loom.
Our family knows all
of our weaknesses.
I don't know. Maybe she's right.
- I belong with them.
- Come on, Charlie.
Look, I'm a coward, Sara.
I can't even stand up
to my own sister.
Hey, listen to me.
No one is responsible
for the family they're born into.
All that matters
is who they decide to be,
and you've decided to be brave
and big-hearted.
Thanks, boss.
But I am what I am.
She's gonna love it.
- Surprise.
- What's this?
Nice. It's a keepsake album.
So I can never forget all the times
that you bailed on me.
Well, I was in prison.
Not since 2015.
You know, I never actually
went to homecoming.
I went back inside to get my purse,
and when I came back out,
you were gone.
And I kept telling Kirk to wait
because I wanted to say
goodbye to you.
But you had bailed like always.
So, keep it.
Fine.
Oh, and there's that patented
Mick Rory fade.
You know, good old Dad.
Just run away like you always do,
yeah?
Wait. Wait, wait, wait. I...
I'm sorry.
Rory, it was a terrible idea,
and I never should have suggested it,
okay?
Rory. Listen to me, we can fix this.
- No, we can't.
- Yes, we can.
Look, I made a mistake
and I feel really bad,
but that doesn't give us the right
to keep hurting Lita
any more than we already have. Right?
Maybe it's not about the gifts
and the money, and the big birthday
parties, you know?
I think it's time that you go back
in there
and do what we should have done
from the beginning.
- Go back and kick myself in the
- No!
No.
Just go tell her you're sorry.
I guess you're right.
No shortcuts.
What happened to this place?
Whoa.
It's the crew.
Wait. If they're dead,
who's shooting Season 15?
You leave a piece of the Loom of Fate
somewhere long enough,
there's gonna be consequences.
Don't worry about it. I'll nab it.
No, John.
Look, this is my mess, all right?
I'll do it.
Look, all I got to do is run over
there,
put my hand in that hole,
grab the ring, Bob's your uncle.
All right, well, then let's go
before your sister shows up.
What's going on? Hey, girl.
Zari just took some Lyoga root.
She needs a little totem trip
to figure out her stuff.
Gideon, what's the status
with the away team?
The Jumpship is not responding.
Gideon, we talked about this.
Unsnooze, you need to tell me about
things before they happen, not after.
Okay, we should help them.
Ooh. Oh. I feel high already.
Is it too late to detox?
That's the fun of drugs.
You can't untake them.
Besides, this is important.
Everything is going to be fine, sis.
Okay.
I surrender.
Hello?
Ancestors?
Where are all the old people at?
Who you calling old?
So, if you're here, does that mean...
Maman and Baba...
Behrad?
No, B's back on the Waverider.
Who do you think gave me the drugs?
He's alive?
Yeah, of course. Maman and Baba, too.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
So, why are you even asking me
about Behrad?
I thought this was about me and
the strange visions I've been having.
Wow. New me came out shockingly
self-absorbed.
Who are you calling the new you?
Who even are you?
Well, you...
if the Legends hadn't saved
the world,
and you grew up in dystopian
Seattle.
Once the timeline crystallized,
you were out in the real world,
and I was thrown in here
with the rest of the totem bearers.
Wait, does that mean Nate was right?
Are you a cooler me?
We have a lot to talk about.
Hey, do carbs count
if you eat them in a totem?
- Nope.
- Oh.
Whoa, whoa.
Thanks.
Okay.
Yes.
I got it!
Charlie!
Sara, no.
No!
Sara, go!
You're bleeding.
You're mortal. Just like them.
Pathetic.
Apologize...
and we can heal you.
We can restore order to this madness.
I like the madness.
Sara was right.
I'm no Fate...
I'm a Legend.
And now she's dead.
Which makes you nothing.
You'll never find the other pieces.
No.
Once again,
your humans have let you down.
Goodbye, little sister.
So...
how are things with Nate?
Good, you know. Yeah, super.
Super cool.
Weird to feel jealous of myself.
Well, don't be too jealous.
Sorry. Are you not together?
He's my brother's best friend,
it would...
It would be weird.
Sorry, he and Behrad are friends?
They have this ridiculous handshake.
It's sweet.
Behrad a Legend?
I wish I could see that.
You must be disappointed?
Yeah, I was hoping Totem-town
would have a few video games.
No, I mean disappointed in me.
Why?
I mean, you were a superhero
who wielded a totem
and saved the world.
Twice.
I'm just a failed Cat-Chat celebrity.
My family's alive.
And you...
You actually seem like a lot of fun.
I'm good with it.
They could be anywhere out here.
Sara?
Charlie?
I thought you were dead.
Me too.
My sister, she's...
She's heading for the ship.
Ava, we have a problem.
There is a very slinky lady in a red
leather pantsuit on the ship.
Which usually I would be into,
but she is giving off a super,
'I want to kill you in the worst
possible way' vibe.
Oh, my God,
that must be Charlie's sister.
Listen, you need to wake up Zari
and get off the ship.
Already on it.
Ava! Come quick!
- Oh, my God.
- I think he's dead.
Don't count me out so soon, handsome.
The forest is a natural apothecary.
Zari, Zari.
Wake up. Wake up!
Zari, wake up.
Zari. Zari!
Where's the ring?
Hey. Look, since you're Charlie's
sister,
can't we just be cool about all this?
You two share blood.
She's your sister.
Yeah.
Pretty.
I'm taking the ring.
Whether she dies is up to you.
You don't belong here.
No more defying fate.
No!
Behrad!
- Is he...
- Get the ship in the air.
- She's still on the ship.
- Just do it!
You're not getting off this ship
alive.
You saw my true form and survived.
What are you?
Your worst nightmare.
You can't kill me.
I'm a God.
Yeah? I've faced worse.
Gideon, you'd better be awake because
I need you to open the doors, now.
Fate's a bitch, ain't it?
Not bad.
Nice.
Come back soon.
Maybe next time bring Behrad.
I'd like that.
Oh, my God, guys.
I just had the most amazing
experience.
Where's Behrad?
Z...
What's going on?
Where is...
Oh, my God.
Behrad.
Why?
Why? How did this happen?
He's dead.
Wait, who's dead?
Behrad.
You got us into this mess,
and now he's dead because of you.
Can that Loom bring him back?
If we get the last piece, yeah.
Great. Get up, let's go.
Hold on a second.
It's not that simple, all right?
We're being hunted by a pair
of bloody gods.
This situation just got
a hell of a lot more dicey.
I can handle dicey!
I can handle whatever it takes
to save my brother.
And until you bring him back,
I am with you every minute
of every damn day.