Previously onThe Flash
andLegends Of Tomorrow...
Thanks, man. We're good.
I'm leaving Central City.
Every hero has their own journey.
If yours is taking you on a new path,
you owe it to yourself to go.
I watched the men murder you.
Mother ran with Mari.
She abandoned me.
I'm sorry, Kuasa.
When Nora was possessed by Mallus,
he seemed scared of my totem.
You're one of the six.
Maybe these totems are the keys
to stopping him.
I only know about five totems.
Could there be more?
That woman clearly
has a crush on you.
I thought that maybe if you'd like to
come to the ship...
There's no time.
Director Hunter has escaped.
Wally West, I need your help.
BAHAMAS 1717
This way, lads.
Fifteen men on a dead man's chest
Yo ho ho and a bottle of rum
This be the spot.
Get to digging.
Surely you don't need
for these men to be known
where we buried our treasure.
Our treasure, my love?
Ours and no one else's.
Oh, no, no, don't concern
yourself over a few doubloons.
I didn't show these sorry sea dogs
the most valuable trinket
in me possession.
An emerald fit.
For a pirate queen.
How do I look?
Anne?
Edward!
Take it off.
I don't know what I'm looking at.
Looks like a hemorrhoid.
What? No, it, it's Mallus.
Demon horns?
Anyway, the hunt
for the six totems has begun.
There are only five tribes
in Zambesi.
Each was gifted with a totem.
And I checked,
there's no record of a sixth.
Well, the good news is that we have
the Air and the Spirit Totems.
Kuasa has the Water Totem.
And since the final totem
is a complete mystery,
that leaves us looking
for Earth and Fire.
Now, the Fire Totem,
which is currently smashed, BTW,
was last seen in
a Detroit museum in 2018.
Wait, how do you know that?
Because it is with your
granddaughter Mari's,
Or AKA the other Vixen's,
Boyfriend, Dr. Adam Macalester.
He's dedicated his life to the study
of the Zambesi totems.
Well, if Constantine is right
and the only thing that
Mallus fears is the sixth,
then we need to get our hands
on the Fire Totem.
Collect the set, win a prize.
We need to tell Sara
we gotta get to Detroit.
Nope, she's off to Star City.
She's been texting some guy.
They're going on a date.
How do you know?
What, are you looking at her phone?
I look at everyone's phone.
Helps pass the time.
Well, who's she going on a date with?
Obviously it's Ava.
Oh, that's hot.
What's hot?
The Fire Totem. Hot, hot.
Very hot and currently in Detroit,
so what do you say
we motor off to the Motor City?
Right now?
I might sit this one out,
because I have to do...
business back home.
I bet you do.
STAR CITY 2018
Hi.
You look...
Weird.
I look weird, right?
I was gonna say beautiful, but...
Thank you. So do you. It's...
Do you wanna...
Right.
- Oh, you know what,
- Madam?
I'll just have whatever
she's having, please.
Vodka Martini, extra dirty, stirred.
- Of course.
- Stirred, not shaken?
Shaken's for lightweights
who like their booze watered down.
- And James Bond.
- James Bond never had
to fight off a horde of Vikings
or help me escape a demon realm.
True.
How was work?
Work is...
this is awful.
You know what, I have an idea.
Let's just try to be normal
for one night.
No Legends, no bureau.
What do you think?
- There you are.
- Thank you.
I feel like relationships
are complicated enough
without time-travel
and supervillains, don't you?
Okay.
Then here's to being
two regular women
on a completely normal first date.
Completely normal.
DETROIT 2018
Hey...
you okay?
My granddaughter,
the good one, she's out there.
I wanna see her more than anything.
But you can't
without screwing up history.
Some days, I wish I had never heard
of time-travel.
Yeah.
Oh, I like what you've done
with your hair.
Oh, really? I hate it.
- Good news.
- Bad news.
What's going on?
- I know where their totem is.
- The Fire Totem's gone.
Ray-Ray, you go first.
We tried to steal the Fire Totem
from your granddaughter's boyfriend,
but someone beat us to it.
Damien Darhk.
"Dear, Legends, now I have two."
You know, for a megalomaniac,
he has very lovely penmanship.
- I know, right? Oh, and by the way,
- Yeah.
don't worry, Macalester's fine.
Can I talk now, please?
Yeah. You said you had good news.
I know where the Earth Totem is,
or, more precisely...
when...
1717, Saint Lisette.
St. Lisette?
Sister ship of La Concorde?
Get to the point, pretty.
La Concorde was boarded by pirates,
and later named Queen Anne's Revenge.
It's Blackbeard the Pirate's ship.
So, Blackbeard has the Earth Totem.
Well, let's steal it.
No, guys, hold on, Sara's on a date.
We should probably avoid messing
with history
while she's still on appetizers?
But, think how happy she'd be
if we had the Earth Totem by dessert.
At this juncture,
the responsible thing to do
would be to consult Captain Lance.
Who would tell us we can't risk
the Darhks getting another totem.
All those in favor
of setting a course to 1717...
Aye.
BAHAMAS 1717
How are we supposed to find
Blackbeard in this rabble?
Well, we could ask a pirate nicely.
Nicely? Wait, pirates are terrified
of Blackbeard.
They're not gonna just
offer up some...
So, you're looking for Blackbeard?
How do I know you's not spies
for the Royal Navy?
Because we wanna join
Blackbeard's crew, you germ.
YUNNAN PROVINCE, CHINA 2018
It's...
it's rather a lovely place
you've traveled to, Mr. West.
How'd you find me?
By tracking the geolocation
of your MP3 player.
Your playlist consists
of a rather amazing
number of repetitions
of George Michael's
"Careless Whisper."
Jesse loved that song.
I assume that your recent heartbreak
is the reason
for your spiritual quest.
However, with the fate
of the world at stake,
I, I'm afraid that you
can no longer sit idly by.
Well, I, I'm sorry, my friend,
but my days
of "fwathooming" are over.
Right now, I'm living my life
one quarter-mile at a time.
Was that a Buddhist koan?
Dom Toretto,
"The Fast and the Furious."
Aren't you BFFs with the Legends?
I'm sure my boy, Nate,
can help you out.
It seems that my days
of Legending are over.
Alas, you're quite secure
in your decision to slow things down?
I am.
Well, the last time
I was this far east
was in the Opium Wars.
It'd be a shame to waste a trip.
Fancy a drink?
Another flagon of ale!
NASSAU 1717
So, this is where Blackbeard
hangs out.
- Classy.
- Yep.
Line 'em up.
What's up?
Nothing.
I said what's up.
Fine, you're an unbiased listener.
I want to change
my granddaughter Kuasa's past,
and, well, improve her future.
So, do it.
It's not that simple.
What if I inadvertently change
my other granddaughter's destiny?
So, don't do it.
And then there's Nate.
I still have to go back
to 1942 and marry someone else,
so that Kuasa and Mari are even born.
We can never end up together.
I feel paralyzed.
Every step I take,
it feels like it could just have
disastrous consequences.
Take a look around.
Do you think these people give a damn
about consequences?
Take the night off.
A true pirate doesn't live
for tomorrow.
They only live for the moment.
Thanks, Mick...
but I don't know the first thing
about acting like a pirate.
Well...
I do.
It was just Laurel and I.
I was always the rebel,
and she was always the good one.
Why do you look like
you already know this?
What'd, you Google me?
No.
I may have read your file
back when you were a fugitive
from the bureau.
And, look,
I know that sounds stalkery,
but in my defense,
I did not see this coming.
Well, what do you wanna know?
Okay. You always seem
so composed and cool,
but you can't be
all cool all the time.
What's the most embarrassed
you've ever been?
That's an easy one,
first time I ever had
a weapon in my hand.
- Lian Yu?
- Nope,
Starling City Elementary.
I was Peter Pan in the school play.
I got up on stage in the first scene,
and I just totally froze.
I couldn't remember any of my lines.
It was like my mind just went blank.
What'd you do?
Well, I broke out into
a tap dance, of course,
and then I ran off stage crying.
You can dance?
Go ahead. You can check it.
I... I'm sure it's nothing,
but just...
it's a voicemail. I'm just gonna...
- It's okay.
- listen.
It wasn't my idea,
but the team has taken
the Waverider on a joyride
to the Bahamas 1717,
in a futile attempt to locate
the missing Earth Totem.
Just thought you should know.
Is everything okay?
Yeah, totally fine. Normal, in fact.
Captain wants to see you.
Man, Sara's here?
Not that one, you dumbass.
I'm talking about
the most fearsome pirate queen
to sail the Seven Seas.
The Dread Pirate Jiwe.
She needs to loosen up.
Yeah.
I heard she once cut out
a man's tongue
for not obeying her orders.
Yeah, and she still carries it
to this day.
I never heard of no lady pirate.
That's because dead men
tell no tales.
They say she lost her ship
to a Kraken, and in retribution,
she hunted down
the monster's wee bairn
and ate the gupper raw.
I heard she was spat back in hell
by the devil himself.
I hear she be more bold
and fearless
than Captain Blackbeard.
Begging your pardon, Captain.
What was that you said?
I have it under good authority
we be in the company
of the Dread Pirate Jiwe.
Why is everyone staring at me?
If there's one thing pirates
love more than treasure,
it's a good story.
Blackbeard. He's heading this way.
- Hit me.
- What?
The mission is yours.
Have fun getting Earth Totem back.
Hit me.
Now get out of my sight
before I really lose my temper.
So, you're the...
Dread Pirate Jiwe?
Welcome to Nassau.
Rory, Amaya, come in, over?
Some sort of interference
with the communications system.
Guys, answer me. Over?
Hey, calm down.
I'm sure they're okay.
My apologies, but I'm experiencing
a Level 4 systems failure.
Wasn't me. Nothing to do with it.
I believe the fault lies
in our present coordinates.
You did park us in the middle
of the Bermuda Triangle.
Sailors call it the Devil's Triangle.
No, the stories of ships disappearing
are grossly exaggerated.
You sure about that, Ray?
The scuttlebutt is...
you're wanting to join me crew.
The Dread Pirate Jiwe works
for no man.
What we seek is treasure.
As does every pirate worth his...
or her salt.
You know...
I believe that you have
this particular treasure
in your possession.
It's a necklace
with a very large emerald.
That description doesn't strike
a chord.
Let me jog your memory.
A couple of pirates
after me own cold black heart.
I'll tell you where the trinket is...
but at a price.
I'm here for the pirate known
as Blackbeard.
I expect you'll be wanting to see
me letter of mark.
A forgery, no doubt.
Your letter will win
no favor with me.
I wouldn't so much as breathe
if I were you.
Good evening, Ms. Jiwe.
They say the third time is a charm...
but this charm is the third.
No.
You know, I must commend you,
Lieutenant Maynard,
for leading us straight to Blackbeard
and his associates.
- You're most welcome, Admiral.
- Admiral?
I know, right? I look so handsome.
And I'll be made Commodore,
once Blackbeard's severed head
swings from my ship's bowspirit.
You know, the last Kingsman
o threatened me
ended up begging for his own life.
Gentlemen, please.
You may continue all threats
and counter-threats
as soon as I get what I need.
The Emerald Necklace.
Where is it?
That's Blackbeard you're talking to,
- and he ain't gonna say...
- I buried it on Grace Island.
Would you like me to draw you a map?
I can't promise to make it to scale,
but, I can do my damndest.
You heard the man.
Let's have another drink.
I appear to be empty.
Give me some of that.
No, this, this is not for you.
Please, I drank Hemingway
and van Gogh under the table.
Cisco gave this to me
before I left Central City.
The only way a speedster
could get drunk
is off of this rocket fuel.
- Rocket fuel?
- Yeah.
Cisco's a bloody genius.
Yeah, he is.
So is Barry and Caitlin and Wells.
Wait, maybe that's
why I never fit on Team Flash.
And here I was, thinking you
were roaming the Chinese countryside,
because your girlfriend
needed more space.
Yeah, I can do one
better than that, mate.
Both of my favorite prodigies
conspired to have me put in prison.
What happened?
Well, I lied to Sara, in addition
to accidentally aiding
in the resurrection of the man
who killed her sister
And Ava is angry at me
for sending good agents...
to their deaths.
Sounds like you're a bit of a douche.
No, no offense.
No, none taken, no.
I intend to make it up
to both of them,
but first, I need the teenciest,
teenciest of favors.
Hey, Agent McNeil,
just calling to say congrats
on being named agent of the month.
The bureau's lucky to have you.
I'm coming for you, McNeil.
Hello?
Who's there?
Not again.
This is way more fun than meditating.
I know.
Wait, there is one item
we must procure
from the bureau's storage closet,
and one...
that is very near
and dear to my heart.
We're screwed.
The ship's electrical systems
are experiencing multiple
unexplained malfunctions.
- It's the Devil's Triangle.
- Look, that's just a myth.
Whatever it is,
we need to time-jump out of here.
What? And leave Mick
and Amaya stranded in pirate times?
It's a miracle
we're still in the air.
Well, I'm sure they're having
a whale of a time with Blackbeard.
What's so funny about
getting your head chopped off?
There are worse ends,
like the one I brought on that
fool admiral.
That necklace is cursed.
I saw its dastardly work
with me own eyes.
Get your hands off me, you blaggards.
I'm so sorry, Mick.
If I really was
the Dread Pirate Jiwe,
I never would've let
Darhk steal my totem.
What the hell
are you apologizing for?
You're better than a story,
and a hell of a lot more fearsome
than some pirate queen,
with or without your totem.
This man, Edward Teach,
has been convicted of unlawful
piracy and plunder.
Therefore, it is my duty
as an instrument of the crown to...
Watch out.
You're in sore need
of a sword, pirate.
Gideon, maybe you could
help us settle an argument.
What are the chances of survival
if we stay in the Bermuda Triangle?
Zero. There are multiple cannonballs
headed towards our starboard bow
as we speak.
Sorry, cannonballs?
I thought we were cloaked.
I tried to told you coming here
was a bad idea.
Who the heck is firing at us?
I want that ship brought down.
Fire another volley.
Aye, sir.
You wouldn't kill an unarmed man.
You're showing him mercy.
Shut up.
We just saved your hairy neck.
Try to keep up, boys.
Gideon, jump us out of here.
My heart is pounding,
my palms are sweating,
and I know that I only have
a few rounds left in my pocket.
So, what'd you do?
I grabbed a guy and used him
as a human shield.
And from that point on,
no one would ever play paintball
with me ever again.
Well, it sounds like a hell
of a 15th birthday party.
You okay?
Gonna run to the restroom
really quickly.
I'm sorry.
We're gonna need the check.
Please tell me that the Waverider
did not just crash into Star City.
Star City? Is that where we are?
- Oh, you gotta be kidding me.
- Well, the good news is
the cannonball didn't hit
the time-core.
And Nate made a beautiful landing.
Yeah.
Thanks, big guy.
So, Sara, how's the date going?
It's over.
Come here, come here.
What the hell are you doing here?
Please don't be mad.
You weren't answering your phone.
This better be a life
or death emergency, Gary.
Worse.
A speedster stole my time courier,
- and then pantsed me.
- And then...
did you check if HQ is secure?
Snug as a bug.
Except one item,
was reported missing from storage,
a long brown coat that
used to belong to...
Rip Hunter.
Yeah.
Okay.
You look great by the way.
- Shut up, Gary.
- Oh, yeah.
Remember when we talked
about personal space?
Yeah, okay.
Come on.
Ouch.
- You nee...
- Double ouch.
Do you want me to box it up?
No, Gary. Okay, we need to find Rip.
He's got a time courier,
which means he could be
anywhere any time,
causing a whole mess of problems.
Time can never mend
The careless whisper
Of a good friend
To the heart and mind, mind
Ignorance is blind
There's no comfort in the truth
Pain is all you'll find
I'm never gonna dance again
Guilty feet ain't got no rhythm
Though it's easy to pretend
I know you're not a fool
When I left,
you were headed to Detroit.
Yeah, it's a, it's, it's a really,
it's a really long story.
Mick and Amaya are marooned in 1717,
the Darhks have the Fire Totem,
and Blackbeard has the Earth Totem.
Yes, I just thought it was gonna be
a longer story.
Thank God you're back.
You look great.
The engine room's a disaster.
We're not going anywhere.
I don't know
who looks more ridiculous,
you guys in your pirate britches
or me in this...
stupid dress.
Definitely them.
Hey, I know it looks like a mess,
but we really wanted you
to have a nice night out.
Yeah, if you really like that
mean Time Bureau lady,
you shouldn't give up on her.
Look, I'm not giving up on anything,
other than maybe the idea that
I'll ever have a normal life.
Zari, get the ship back
in fighting shape,
because until then...
Rory and Amaya are on their own.
All right, listen up.
We can't let the Darhks beat us
to Grace Island
and to the Earth Totem,
so...
we're in need of a ship.
You want to sail
the Queen Anne's Revenge?
I told you, that necklace is cursed.
What?
You're gonna let a curse stop you
from taking the gold?
- Aye.
- Why did you become a pirate
in the first place, ey?
To let an admiral get
the best of you?
Or to claim your destiny
on the wide open sea?
I don't know what's waiting for us
on the other side of this journey,
but whatever it is,
it beats cowering in some alleyway,
waiting for your black beard
to turn gray.
I swore I'd never go back
to that island...
and I'm a man of me word.
Fair winds, me hearties.
Blackbeard's a coward.
Come on.
We don't need Blackbeard.
We just need his ship.
Another drink?
Listen up...
the Dread Pirate Jiwe is looking
for a crew.
Your old Captain Blackbeard...
buried his treasure on Grace Island.
So, you've heard the rumors then...
that the treasure is cursed?
But while old Blackbeard is afraid
of his own shadow,
you men...
you vile and despicable men,
are willing
to face Davy Jones himself
for a crack at gold and glory.
- Yeah.
- Who's willing to join me
as we take over Blackbeard's ship?
Yeah.
Mutiny.
Is that what this is, ey?
You'd rather follow
the Dread Pirate Jiwe
than your own captain?
Then I'm bloody joining you.
I'll dig up me chest
and share the spoils with ye men.
Hats off to the Pirate Queen!
- All hands on deck.
- Aye, sir.
Secure the backstays
and hoist the Jolly Roger high.
There's land ahead.
Sara.
Yeah, what now?
We have another anachronism in 1717.
The HMS Fortitude got into
a naval battle
with Blackbeard's ship off
the coast of Grace Island.
- So?
- So...
that is a portrait of their admiral.
Damien Darhk.
I don't care if Zari has to duct-tape
the Waverider back together,
we have to get it in the air.
Well, I wouldn't advise returning
to the Bermuda Triangle.
It's the Devil's Triangle,
and Mick and Amaya are in danger.
Ava. Hey.
Don't "hi, Ava" me.
You stood me up, jerk.
Awkward.
Blackbeard draws one hell of a map.
Dig.
Oh, blast.
I've... I've... I've left me compass
on the ship.
It's a family heirloom,
- so I should...
- Turn back and I'll kill you.
What aren't you telling us, ey?
Well, in... in me haste,
I may have left out some
miniscule details about
the cursed necklace.
I gifted it to me love and queen,
the most devious,
and dastardly woman I've ever had
the pleasure of meeting...
apart from you, I mean.
But as soon as Anne put it on,
something dark
and unholy overtook her.
Totems draw on the life force
of their bearer.
So, if Anne was as wicked
as you suggest,
the totem would've only amplified
her worst impulses.
It turned her into a monster.
How did you live to tell the tale?
Well, I... I did the only
decent thing any man would do.
I put a musket ball in her head
and buried her along
with the treasure.
That cursed necklace
won't let her rest in peace.
Me Anne will rise again.
Stiffen your backbones, men.
I gotta hand it to you, Ms. Lance,
you take the phrase "dine and dash"
to a whole new level.
Look, the Waverider fell out
of the sky.
My team needed help.
Why does not surprise me?
Should we interrupt?
No...
but Ava gave me an idea.
Her time courier.
I'm coming with you.
First I have to get
the Nanite pistol.
No, Ray, do...
Steady.
Oh, hello, Annie.
Good to see you're...
You're looking so...
beautiful.
You know,
this was never gonna work out.
Really?
What, because I'm a mature person
who actually can communicate?
Oh, really? Such a communicator.
Like when you said
you were going to the bathroom?
- What are you talking about?
- You think I didn't see Gary?
Oh, my Rip broke into
the Time Bureau.
I was coming back
to the table to tell you.
- You know, this is pointless.
- Yeah, it is.
We should have never tried
to be normal.
I'm not normal, all right?
I'm never gonna be normal,
and I'm not gonna be normal
for anyone.
I don't want you to be normal.
You don't?
Hell no.
What?
Oh, no, the kissing was great.
It's just...
We claim this ship
and ye two women...
as ours.
Come on.
Hey.
Let's do this.
Come on, you namby-pamby.
They're mere lassies.
Listen to me...
that totem can burden
even one born to wear it.
I know it must feel like
a noose around your neck.
Let me help you break free
of this curse.
Thank you for distracting her.
Unfortunately,
now I have to kill you.
Surprisingly powerful.
Well, that was fun,
but playtime is over.
Hey, you guys!
I want my totem back.
You fool.
We don't need swords to kill you.
No.
Good shot, haircut.
No, no.
Stay with me.
Stay with me, sweetheart. Come on.
You're gonna be okay. Stay with me.
Come on.
Let's go.
Don't let her come on.
That was too easy.
You two bonnie lasses
be the best fighters I've ever seen.
How would you like to join me crew?
The Waverider, ey?
She's...
an usual ship.
But I can think of no more
appropriate vessel
for the Dread Pirate Jiwe.
Thanks for saving me life
and for stopping your bonnie mates
from keelhauling me.
Well, thank you for leading me
to the accursed treasure.
And make sure you tell them that
Captain Jiwe spared you.
Absolutely. Of course, I...
Fair winds, Captain Jiwe.
Amaya, I am... I am so sorry.
If I didn't push everybody
to go after the Earth Totem,
you wouldn't have lost yours.
It's all right, Nathaniel.
We'll fix this.
We'll get your totem back.
My birthright, it's always dictated
the path I choose.
It's like a compass that
just points the way.
It must be so difficult
not to have it.
It's also freeing.
For the first time in my life,
I get to decide.
Amaya?
You know, I learned something
from hanging out with pirates.
They always focus
on the problem in front of them.
And what is that problem?
Do you yield, sir?
Aye, Captain.
Rum floats were a very good idea.
Only seemed fair
since we missed dessert.
What?
Sometimes, we screw things up
for the better.
I will drink to that.
Cheers.
It's good.
Hey, look, I'm sorry
about bailing on you earlier.
I should have been honest with you
about what was going on
with my team...
No, no, no.
I never should've put
the kibosh on talking shop.
You're right, it's your fault.
You, oh, man.
Besides, I'd rather fight pirates
with you any day
than sit in some stupid restaurant.
Well, in that case,
I was thinking Genghis Khan
for our second date?
Done...
but only if I can call you Peter Pan.
- Don't. Don't.
- Ms. Ms.
Okay.
So, you got a room on this ship or...
Let's go find out.
Why do you look so chipper?
Oh, no, I had a terrible hangover.
It lasted three minutes.
The benefits of a speedster's
metabolism.
Here, take these.
Thank you.
You know, last night was pretty fun.
Yeah.
I had gotten a bit lonely here,
I think.
Yeah, I've been a bit lonely too.
Hey, your girlfriend dumped you,
your team treated you like
an outcast.
It's no wonder you went walk-about.
But the world needs Wallace West
to step in from the cold.
And I know a place
where outcasts fit right in.
In fact, some might say that
they become...
Legends.
Care to join me?
Wha...
Is "Careless Whisper" not
the best karaoke song of all time?
It is the way we sing it, mate.
Haircut, you want a beer?
Everyone's off doing their own thing.
Just you and me.
Sure could use a beer,
even if I am your last choice
of companion.
Oh, that?
I was just doing
a bit of light theorizing,
and then I had a breakthrough.
I am gonna develop a liquid
for the perfect dry erase marker.
Strong viscosity, clean lines.
You're a terrible liar.
Yeah.
It's Nora.
The Nanite pistol is gonna kill her,
and that's what
it was supposed to do,
but now I feel...
Like a badass?
No.
Guilty.
What?
- You saved Amaya.
- I know.
Doesn't really make sense,
except that I met her...
as a kid.
Well, now she's all grown up
and joined the demon's side.
Yeah.
But you, you have changed
since I first met you,
and I hate to break it to you,
Mick, but...
you are a much better person.
And maybe Nora could have
become one too.
There was hope for her, anyway,
before I took it away.
BAHAMAS 1717
Come on, sweetheart, you gotta fight.
Stay with me. Come on.
Look, I... I know...
I'm the last person you wanna see.
What did you do to my daughter?
Nothing that can't be undone.
I have a cure.
You and your great big heart.
You just couldn't handle
the guilt, could you?
I've come for a trade.
Amaya's totem, and I will save Nora.
I honestly thought that
would be harder.
My daughter is all that matters.
Come on.
Stay.
That's it.
Ray?
You remember me?
Yes.
Darling...
wait...
He may be of value.
Welcome back.