The Time Masters were an organization
charged with protecting history
from rogue time travelers,
but they were destroyed.
Under the leadership of Rip Hunter,
we have taken up their mantle.
Sara Lance, former member
of the League of Assassins.
Dr. Raymond Palmer, The Atom.
The Arsonist, Mick Rory,
and Firestorm, the merged super form
of Jefferson Jackson
and myself, Martin Stein.
We are the only ones left
to protect history.
We are the Legends Of Tomorrow.
Sorry! My bad!
What the hell is going on out here?
Sorry, sir. He broke through
the security cordon downstairs.
Only because they wouldn't let me up
without an appointment.
But, how does a regular guy
get an appointment
with the Mayor anyway?
Heywood, Dr. Nate Heywood.
I'm... here to talk
about Sara Lance, Ray Palmer
and the rest of the Legends.
I think they're all in trouble.
Thank you for not having me
arrested back there.
Those security guards
really overreacted.
You know, one of them tried
to Mace me.
Dr. Heywood, I only agreed
to give you five minutes
which was three minutes ago
because Ray and Sara
are friends of mine.
But I don't know the first thing
about any Legends.
Of course you do,
because you're the Green Arrow.
- Excuse me?
- Huh?
We're done here.
Look, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to drop a bomb
on you like that.
It's just, I've exhausted
all my normal avenues
and you're the only person left
who won't think I'm crazy.
Are you sure about that?
I'm a historian.
I specialize in deductive
historical reconstruction.
In layman's terms,
I'm a time detective
which I really don't have to be
to look at a calendar to see
one week after you came to this city,
Robin Hood showed up.
You said that Sara and Ray are...
Traveling throughout time
with the other Legends.
"Legends" is what they
call themselves.
Now, for the past six months,
I've been noticing subtle changes
to history, almost imperceptible.
Actually, if it wasn't
for a friend of mine
who's a quantum physicist,
I wouldn't have been able to detect
the subliminal alterations.
The point being, I think
your friends are responsible.
You're looking at me
like you want evidence.
Evidence, okay.
An illuminated manuscript
from 1216 depicting a knight.
Looks a lot like your friend
Dr. Palmer, same nose and... chin.
Erratic text describing a woman
in white with a bo staff.
Hieroglyphic from Mesopotamia
depicting an albeit crude ship
that flies through the air
and disappears.
Let's skip to the part
where they're in trouble.
UFO sighting, New York City, 1942.
Multiple witnesses report a flying
machine diving into the Atlantic
which matches not only
the Mesopotamian hieroglyphics but...
The part where they're in trouble!
Contemporaneous with the sighting
were multiple reports
of an underwater detonation
of an atomic bomb!
Now, the government has denied this.
You said 1942.
That's three years before...
Before the atomic bomb
was supposedly invented, yes.
I told you history was changing.
Dr. Heywood, if the Legends' ship
met an A-bomb...
they're not in trouble...
They're dead.
We're closing in on your coordinates,
Dr. Heywood.
Are you seeing the sonar
readings of the sea floor?
Either that's a really
weird-looking rock formation
or, the wreckage of a time ship.
If the Legends went down
with the ship...
Where are the bodies?
The ship's keeping him in stasis.
How do you know that?
My name is Oliver Queen
and my preference
is to not break your arm.
So I want you to calm down
and tell us
what happened to your team.
You wouldn't believe me
even if I told you.
All I remember is being knocked out
by that skinny, little Englishman.
Very embarrassing.
I know that Sara told her father
she was leaving to protect history.
Why?
Why does history need protecting?
Because the idiots
who were protecting it,
the Time Masters, were blown up.
So you and the Legends took over?
Chasing down time criminals
and fixing the parts of history
they screwed up.
Aberrations, the captain called them.
We were chasing them
for about six months
without a problem.
Well... the occasional problem.
I knew we were all in trouble
when Rip made us put on blouses
just to save the King of France.
I look like an idiot.
I rather like the style of
Le Mousquetaires de la Garde.
- You would.
- Can we concentrate, please?
King Louis XIII is scheduled
to meet an untimely end
at the hand
of Cardinal Richelieu's men
at any moment.
Roger that.
I have eyes on the King.
Whatever you do, do not
let him out of your sight.
But if today's when he's supposed to,
you know, with the queen, I...
Raymond, without that consummation
there will be no Louis coutures,
no Sun King
and no golden age of France.
Which means, by extension,
no Madame Curie, no Louis Pasteur.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I get it.
History will be totally screwed.
But I don't have to be there
for the actual...
you know, consummation. Do I?
It's beautiful, Your Grace.
As is yours.
Who gave it to you?
My sister.
You speak of her as if she is gone.
I hate to see a lady
so beautiful so sad.
Your husband...
Enjoys the company
of his male courtiers.
Why should I be denied
similar pleasures?
Sara...
I need to know that the Queen
is secure.
Meantime, I believe
I've identified our assassins.
And I'd wager, those aren't
just swords on their hips.
Yes, that would explain
the aberration.
My love, there is no need
for you to...
knock.
Sorry to spoil the mood.
Where the hell's Sara?
Everyone back to the ship!
That's easier said than done.
Ray, meet me on the north side
of the house!
It's actually a chateau.
What's your plan?
You'll see!
Oh, you've got to be kidding.
Oh, bloody hell.
That was the last assassin.
What did we say about using powers
and future tech, Dr. Palmer?
Well, yeah, but they started it.
Don't look at me.
I left my gun on the ship
like a good little Boy Scout.
What's going on?
Who are you people?
I believe the Queen
is waiting for you in her bedroom.
And I'll bet she's
all warmed up for you.
Shut your mouth, Jax,
or I'll cut your eyes out
and feed them to you.
I believe our work here is done.
Wait, how'd you go
from the court of Louis XIII
to the bottom of the Atlantic Ocean?
You said you wanted
to hear the full story.
We do, just some of us have lives
that we'd like to get back to.
We got ourselves in trouble
by visiting a time
we were told not to.
1942?
Who told you not to go to 1942?
Some guy in a hood named...
Rex Tyler.
Said if we set foot in 1942,
we'd be all screwed.
And then, he just vanished.
Okay. If he told you not
to go to 1942...
then why'd you go?
Put another successful mission
down in the books.
Where are we off to next?
Gideon and I have calculated
a 96 percent likelihood
of another aberration
in Bhopal, 1912.
Why can't it be Aruba, 2016?
For real. We've been going non-stop
for the past six months.
Nobody wants to address the fact
that Cardinal Richelieu's men
were armed with laser guns?
Clearly provided to them
by a time pirate or some-such.
Grey's right.
We need to find out who so...
You can get another chance
of destroying the very history
that you're supposed
to be protecting?
I knew I forgot something.
The part where Rip tells us
everything that we did wrong.
As in, seducing the Queen of France
just before she's supposed
to conceive
the country's greatest hope
for the future?
She seduced me.
All wrong, as in violating our policy
of not using super powers
in front of people?
They had laser guns.
At least, I didn't
screw up this time.
Stealing's not screwing up.
Another successful mission, Captain?
Yes. Well, it seems I don't share
our team's definition of success.
But let's see if our labors came
to a certain fruition, shall we?
Well, that was fun.
I'm in no mood for a lecture, Sara.
Too tired from dishing them out?
Replacing the Time Masters
is an enormous responsibility,
Sara, and one which I fear
our team is ill-equipped...
Gideon, are we under attack?
Negative, that was a shock wave
generated by a time quake.
A what?
A disturbance in the temporal zone
caused by an unusually
large aberration.
You never mentioned
a time quake before.
I've never experienced one
before. Gideon?
The shock wave's point of origin
was New York City, 1942.
That's not possible.
Wait, what wasn't possible?
What?
You said you and the Legends
discovered an aberration
in 1942, what was it?
My guess is it involved Nazis.
You could say that.
The krauts nuked
New York City in 1942.
Wow, someone just blew up New York.
During World War II.
Think we can all guess
who that someone is.
Nazis.
I hate Nazis.
Aided by some sort of time-traveling
ally, obviously.
Wait, does that mean
the Allied forces lost the war?
In which case, why aren't
we speaking German right now?
Because we're in the temporal zone.
And because it takes time
for the consequences
of an aberration, even one
as cataclysmic as this one,
to ripple throughout time.
So how much time
do we have to stop it?
Isn't traveling
to that particular time
precisely what Rex Tyler
told us not to do?
Well, what's the alternative?
We let New York blow up?
It's not like there are
Time Masters left to stop it.
Miss Lance is right.
We are history's
last line of defense.
- I like the sound of that.
- I'd rather die than speak German.
Best case scenario,
let's assume that Mr. Tyler is wrong
and we all end up not dying in 1942.
What if, in endeavoring to save
New York, we make things worse?
What could be worse
than a genocidal fascist
nuclear-armed superpower?
Relax, Captain.
We got this.
Gideon, I need you to pull up
everything you can
on the target in 1942.
I assume that by "target"
you mean Damien Darhk.
You are finally getting the hang
of this whole revenge thing.
All right, so we know
that he was alive during 1942,
so we just need to know where he is.
According to a 1942 FBI file,
the target was spotted here.
Hope I'm not interrupting.
No, just reading up on 1942.
You've been spending a lot of time
down here lately, alone.
Am I not allowed in the library?
You just never struck me
as a bookworm.
I'm just making sure
that you're not holding
onto anything.
I... I know a thing
or two about grief
so, if you ever want
to talk about Laurel...
Then I know where to find you.
Thank you.
Miss Lance.
Any luck pinpointing the epicenter
- of the temporal aberration?
- No.
Perhaps these news reports
will prove useful.
Oh, that's good news.
Even though we get nuked,
we still win the war.
Look at the date, Dr. Palmer.
In this version of history
World War II lasts two more years.
And claims 12 million more lives.
Including Albert Einstein.
Actually, Einstein went missing
just prior to the attack on New York.
Wait. Wait.
Perhaps these... these two events
aren't merely coincidental.
Think about it, a Nobel Prize
winning physicist goes missing.
And miraculously, the Germans
get the bomb three years ahead of us.
They must've kidnapped Einstein,
forced him to build them an A-bomb
which means, the only way
for us to fix the aberration...
Is for us to kidnap him first.
Yes!
Gideon, please chart a course
for New York City, 1942.
Oh, my God.
I can't believe I'm going
to meet Albert Einstein.
I can't believe
you're making me stay on the ship.
I'm asking you to stay
on the ship, Mr. Jackson.
While the rest of you get to have
all the fun battling Nazis.
You're the only one that I trust
to give the time drive
a long overdue tune up.
And build the time library
and modify the bridge
and half the other hundred things
you've been getting me to do.
All right, give me your tools then.
- What?
- Pack up your tools
and give them to me.
Why would I do that?
Well, I'm gonna give them to Mr. Rory
to see if he wants to be
the ship's mechanic.
You see, that's not funny.
Quite right, because in the event
that we can't stop
this nuclear explosion...
a fully-functioning time drive
is going to come in handy.
So how do we find Einstein
in a city of seven million people?
Well, we just look for the physicist
with the crazy white hair.
I mean the other one.
According to Gideon,
there's a cocktail party
at Columbia this evening.
Cocktail party?
Means booze. Where is it?
At Columbia, I just...
Why does no one ever listen to me?
Hey, where you going?
I have a grandfather
that's in the FBI.
I figured I'd check in
in case we need backup.
Oh. Good plan.
Hey!
Where do you think you're going?
Follow Sara,
in case she needs backup.
Oh, God.
Take me to Conway and Fifth.
Oh, jeez.
Never been to a nerd party before.
You mean a physics symposium.
- Nerd party.
- Keep your eyes open.
We're sure to be in the company
of German spies.
That's... that's him.
Good evening, ladies.
The greatest mind
the world has ever known.
I am merely demonstrating
Newton's third law.
"For every action, there is an equal
and opposite reaction."
I like him.
He's a pig.
I just found our spies.
- Them?
- Notice their uniforms.
The stitching on the lapels,
it's exquisite.
You mean to say fake.
Surprise.
How long have you been following me?
How long have you been
following Darhk?
Shut your mouth, Ray.
We got company.
Guten abend, mein Herren.
- Are they speaking...
- German.
The extraction team is on the move.
Let me talk. I speak "physicist".
Oh, Herr Professor,
I'm so sorry to interrupt.
- Who are you?
- My colleague and I
were just having
a rather spirited debate
about your theory of relativity.
Perhaps you can help us settle it.
I was this close to getting them both
to come back to my room.
Well, what about your wife?
The one who died or the one
who divorced me 30 years ago?
Come on, it's time to go.
You don't have to speak German
to know what "uranium" means.
So what?
Even Einstein can't build
a bomb without fuel.
Darhk must be the one
supplying the Nazis.
Damien Darhk murdered
my sister in 2016.
- If I take him out here in 1942...
- You save her.
I've been waiting six months
to get this son of a gun.
You're gonna have to wait
a little while longer.
We gotta let him go.
Until we get our hands
on the uranium he's selling,
New York City's hanging
in the balance.
I really hate you sometimes, Ray.
What do you two think you're doing?
We have to get you out of here.
Your life is in danger.
This is why I never travel
without my security detail.
Help! I'm being kidnapped!
We might not look like it,
but we're the good guys.
Why should I believe
that you are really a physicist?
Because for every action...
there's an equal
and opposite reaction.
So how'd it go with Einstein?
Depends on who you ask.
But apparently, the professor
has one hell of a right hook.
Seriously? Ray punched him out?
Yeah. He's sleeping it off
in the brig.
So can we get the hell
out of 1942 now?
It looks like.
- Gideon?
- I'm afraid not, Miss Lance.
But without Einstein's help,
the Nazis...
Still manage to destroy New York City
with an atomic blast.
The historical aberration
remains unchanged.
How is that possible?
The Nazis must've gotten the bomb
from someone other than Einstein.
Guten morgen.
What is this? Some sort of prison?
What am I doing in here?
Good question.
I'm sorry. I never had
the opportunity to introduce myself.
I'm Professor Martin Stein,
just like "Einstein" minus the "Ein."
There's just so much
I'd like to discuss with you.
Such as, your paper
on unified field theory.
I have not yet published my paper
on unified field theory!
Who are you?
Why have you abducted me?
The guys at the party
wanted you to make
an atomic bomb for "ze Führer".
No.
Not even a man
as mad as Adolph Hitler
would want to create
such a terrible weapon.
You yourself once said
that two things are infinite,
the universe and human stupidity.
And you are living proof
of the latter.
He just called you stupid.
Now, open this door and let me out!
We will, soon. I promise.
We saved you from the Nazis.
The least you could do
is help us save New York.
From what?
From some theoretical attack?
Some eventuality that not even
I could have predicted?
The only way you...
Mein Gott.
Yes, obviously, you know.
I deduced it, Herr Doktor.
Perhaps you could deduce
how the Germans managed
- to create a nuclear bomb...
- Atomic.
When you are the only man on Earth
capable of performing such a feat.
Ja.
That is correct.
I am the only man.
Wait a minute.
You saying there's some lady
out there
that can make an atomic bomb?
Wunderbar.
Why am I talking to him
when you are clearly
the brains of the operation?
Your ex-wife is also a physicist.
Without Mileva's help...
I would still be working
as a patent clerk in Vienna.
So, while we were busy
safeguarding Professor Einstein...
The Nazis were busy
kidnapping his ex.
Her name is Mileva Maric.
She's a fellow nuclear physicist.
Who, let me guess,
had no one guarding her.
Yes, Einstein's collaborations
with Ms. Maric
were a closely guarded secret
between the two of them.
A secret that the Germans
apparently knew.
So, unless we can determine
where they're keeping her
while she manufactures their bomb...
If I had to guess, I'd say she's
with Damien Darhk's uranium.
Damien Darhk? As in...
The man who murdered your sister.
How is Damien Darhk
even alive in 1942?
Thanks to the Lazarus Pit,
he hardly ages.
Sara's kind of an expert
on Damien Darhk.
Drop it, Ray.
I'm sorry, but while you were
all saving Einstein,
Sara was off on her own
secret side mission
to kill Laurel's killer in the past.
And I suppose you never thought
about saving your fiancée?
Yeah, of course I did.
But I never did it
because it's against the rules.
What rules?
We're not Time Masters.
There are no rules.
Well, if there were,
there'd certainly be one
about lying to your team.
Listen to yourself.
Look, we get it, you're perfect.
Always the Boy Scout,
aren't you, Raymond?
Yeah, well, I could say
the same thing
about you being an assassin.
Well, if we're being honest...
then let me get something
off of my chest.
Let's all just take a deep breath,
shall we?
You think that
you're such a big hero, Ray?
Without that fancy suit,
you're nothing
but a self-righteous rich guy.
Maybe you're right...
but without my suit, there's no way
of finding Einstein's ex-wife
or Damien Darhk for that matter.
Sorry, what are you saying?
That anyone who spends
a lot of time around uranium,
in this case Damien Darhk,
picks up trace amounts of radiation,
which my suit can track.
And lead us straight
to the Nazis' nuclear bomb.
Beautiful work, Mileva.
Dr. Einstein should never
have let you get away.
I did what you want.
Now let me go.
Actually, we still have need of you.
This thing didn't exactly come
with an owner's manual.
Get her and the bomb onboard.
We can't allow them
to get that bomb onboard.
What about Mileva?
Don't worry, Doctor,
we'll be sure to keep her safe.
But we must secure
the nuclear bomb...
- Atomic.
- About to be placed
aboard a Nazis submarine.
This is no time for subtlety.
Agreed.
Let's make sure
we all follow the plan.
Let's just get this done.
Step away from the lady and the bomb!
Final warning!
Schnell! Töten sie!
I love roasting Nazis!
Mein Gott!
We need to get Miss Maric to safety!
Sara!
Get down.
Interesting technique.
League of Assassins, am I right?
I've been waiting
a long time for this.
A long time? For what?
- To kill you.
- Try to, you mean.
Dr. Palmer, let's take precautions.
And disable the bomb?
Already on it.
Guys, a little problem here.
Suit's not as radiation-proof
as I thought.
Sara! Fall back!
Guys, actually a big problem.
Haircut! Watch out!
Mick, look out!
Fall back!
Sara!
Mr. Rory's injured.
Dr. Palmer is incapacitated.
We need to fall back now!
Firestorm, cover Dr. Palmer and Sara.
Okay, Mick's on the mend
and Einstein and his ex
are safe and sound
with the security detail.
Thank you, Jax.
But the Nazis still have the nuke.
What are we doing leaving New York?
Because the Nazis still have a nuke
which we saw being loaded
onto a U-boat.
They're gonna hit New York
from underwater.
Yeah, I'm tracking
the uranium signature
recorded by Dr. Palmer's suit.
But before we engage the Nazis,
I need you to make
these modifications.
Really? Is now the time
for me to be playing mechanic?
Look, I know
that you consider the chores
that I've been assigning you
to be a waste of time, Jefferson.
But believe me,
they're more than just an exercise.
What's the subliminal variance
of the quantum manifold?
- Two microns.
- And if one wanted
to divert power from the axial array?
Can't be done, you'd have
to go through the clavian adjunct.
All of the stuff
you've been having me do,
you've been teaching me
about the Waverider.
I'm a time traveler, Jefferson.
I spend most of my time
thinking about the future,
specifically my own. And...
it occurs to me that that future
might not involve me
being aboard this ship.
And I need someone to know
its secrets in my absence.
Nice try, dude,
but you're not quitting on us.
What's a "Timescatter"?
A last ditch option...
and one that I pray
we will never have to use.
We going swimming or something?
I'm tracking the Nazi U-boat.
Where is it now?
It's close.
They've knocked out
our telemetry, Captain.
What's going on?
As you can see, the Waverider
is ill-suited for underwater combat.
I'm trying to bypass
the tertiary subsystem array.
Make it fast, haircut.
Yes!
Is the weapon ready?
Yes, Herr Darhk.
Fire!
- What was that?
- They're not firing on us.
It's the nuclear bomb.
Atomic.
Whatever it is, we gotta stop it.
I fear that there is only one way
to do that.
Okay. I don't know
what you wanted me to do
but, I did it.
Excellent work, Jax.
What's going on?
I am piloting us on a collision
course with the torpedo.
Now, with any luck, it will hit us
before New York City.
How is that lucky?
Can the Waverider handle the blast?
Honestly, I have absolutely no idea.
Which is why, I'm doing this.
Where is everybody?
The appropriate question is when.
Other the last few months,
I've implemented a safeguard
in case of a catastrophe.
A high burst of temporal energy
has scattered our team
throughout history.
I knew you never liked me.
I'm afraid, injured as you are,
you wouldn't survive
the rigors of time travel.
Which is why, I'm doing this.
Gideon, how much time do we have?
Thirty seconds, Captain.
- Gideon?
- I'm here, Captain.
You always are.
Okay, there's just one question
that you haven't answered.
Where's Captain Hunter?
I don't know.
Must have time-scattered himself
like the rest of them.
Guess I gotta play hero
and find them.
Do you even think
this ship still flies?
I don't see why not.
Fridge works.
I don't have time to time travel,
but if your team is stuck in history,
who better to help find them
than a historian?
This guy?
Without Dr. Heywood,
you'd still be in stasis.
Good point.
Library, this way.
Hey, wait. Time-out.
This was supposed
to be a salvage mission.
Who are you kidding?
You've been waiting your whole life
for a chance like this.
Well, I... I did some digging.
But I think I finally got a lead
on Ray Palmer.
Are you, sure you know
how to fly this thing?
Let's find out.
Maybe you should slow down?
Maybe you should shut up
and strap in.
I can't believe this.
We're about to travel through time!
Did I tell you
about the side effects?
What side effects?
Mick! Buddy!
- How'd you find me?
- I didn't.
Pretty did.
Is he okay?
Side effects of time travel.
Speaking of,
you're never gonna believe
where the rest of your team ended up.
This festival is boring.
Bring me my wizards!
My liege, how may we entertain you?
Do you wish to gaze
into my magic mirror, Your Majesty?
I grow bored of your tricks.
Off with their heads.
- What?
- You little brat.
This is incredible.
An actual medieval execution?
I never imagined
I'd see this with my own eyes.
Who... who's that?
The new guy.
- New guy! Duck!
- Hiyah!
I'm Dr. Heywood.
I heard so much about you.
Hey, how about we get
to know each other
- back on the ship?
- Okay.
But first we have to find Sara.
Vile witch!
You have corrupted
the women of our village!
In my defense,
they were happily corrupted.
Hang the witch!
You must be Sara Lance.
It's okay. He's with us.
Hey.
Is she always this violent?
I'm sorry, but so far
I haven't been able to detect
any historical alteration
that would indicate
Mr. Hunter was stranded in a time.
Why don't we ask Gideon where he is?
Who's Gideon?
Greetings, Dr. Heywood.
I am the ship's
artificial consciousness.
Gideon, we need you to tell us
where Rip is.
I'm afraid I have no idea.
But I would be happy to play
his final message for you all.
Final message?
Sorry for stranding
you all throughout history,
but it was the only way to save you.
Well, you know what they say,
Captain must never abandon his ship.
Well, neither shall I abandon hope
of seeing you all again someday,
somewhere in time.
As flawed and unruly
as you are individually,
together you are the best crew.
The best team a captain
could ever hope for.
So...
stick together.
And remember...
history is yours now,
my dear Legends.
Good luck.
So, what do we do now?
We drink.
It's not like we were exactly
Time Masters, even with Rip.
But I think he knew that one day
we might have to do this without him.
And we all heard his message.
He wanted us to keep going.
We have to keep going.
There's a rogue time traveler
out there somewhere.
Yeah, a time nemesis
whose idea of fun
is helping Damien Darhk
and the Nazis blow up New York City.
What's to stop them
from going back in time
and kidnapping Einstein
and his ex-wife again?
We can't be everywhere at once.
But you can safeguard the Einsteins.
Safeguard the Einsteins?
How?
By making one slight
alteration to history.
We'd like to talk
to Mr. Einstein. CIA.
He means OSS.
This is related
to the Manhattan Project.
You're headed to Columbia University,
right, for the symphony?
- Symposium.
- Same thing.
Once you're there, we're gonna
need you to publicly announce
that Miss Mileva Maric
has been your silent partner
for over 30 years.
You see, acknowledgment
of Mileva's contributions
is the only way to keep her safe.
Besides, it's the right thing to do.
Don't be a jerk.
Today, I want to tell you
about a very special woman...
my longtime collaborator,
Mileva Maric.
What does that mean?
Krauts won't be able to get to her?
Yes, and then people won't say,
"Hey, you're a regular Einstein."
They'll say,
"You're like one of the Einsteins".
That's so crazy.
I can't believe
we just changed history.
No, Dr. Heywood. We saved it.
You promised no trouble, Herr Darhk.
And you promised me competency.
Perhaps, we'll have better luck
with the next bomb.
That's cute,
but there won't be a next bomb.
You see, my partner wants
to move on to other things.
But your partner isn't here, is he?
According to who?
Hello, Eobard.
Mr. Darhk.
How'd it go with Einstein?
Good, until someone gives
the Confederate Army machine guns
or breaks Mozart's fingers, or...
One aberration at a time.
Hey, remember that thing
that I said before
about you being a...
Billionaire Boy Scout?
You weren't all wrong.
Yeah, but you're more than that.
Thanks.
And we'll get justice for Laurel,
Sara, promise.
What do you guys say
we get out of 1942?
Not until you answer a few questions.
We're the Justice Society of America.
And you're coming with us.