In 2166, an immortal tyrant
named Vandal Savage
conquered the world
and murdered my wife and child.
I have assembled an elite team
to hunt him throughout time
and stop his rise to power.
Unfortunately,
my plan is opposed by the body.
I'd sworn my allegiance
to the Time Masters.
In the future, my friends may not be
heroes but if we succeed,
they will be remembered as legends.
Previously,
onLegends Of Tomorrow...
Ray! Ray, I need you! Please!
I thought you were dead.
Well, not only did you fail
to capture Savage.
You also exposed yourselves
and your powers to him,
giving away the element of surprise
for now and all time.
I let you go,
you'll deliver the Waverider.
Boys, ship's all yours.
You're a liability to the team.
Only one of us is walking
out of here alive.
One, two, 3.00, 4.00 rock
Five, six, 7.00, 8.00 rock
Nine, ten, 11.00
Tommy, promise me
you won't go too fast.
You got to hold on
to something, honey.
- Preferably me.
- Remember.
Just because you stole
your grandma's wheels
don't mean you got to drive like her.
You run your mouth pretty fast.
Let's see if your car can keep up.
Let's go!
Tommy, watch it!
When it's eight, nine, ten, 11 too
I'll be going strong
And so will you
We're gonna rock
Around the clock tonight
We're gonna rock, rock,
Rock till broad daylight
We're gonna rock, gonna rock
Around the clock tonight
Yo, James Dean! Are you...
What's that?
I think that's a comet or something.
It's a meteorite...
in point of fact.
I was drawn to it as well.
Your presence out here
was unexpected.
Or perhaps that's just
another word for
destiny.
I'm not the only one whose vision
is blurry in their left eye, am I?
- Oh.
- Seeing three of everything?
That's normal, right?
Yes, as I mentioned before,
the effect of time travel
on the human body
increases with the length
of each jaunt.
- So, where are we?
- Harmony Falls, Oregon.
According to Captain Baxter's intel,
Savage makes an appearance
in this quaint little hamlet.
What the hell is Savage
doing in Pleasantville?
Murder, apparently.
Several denizens of Harmony Falls
have been brutally slain
and others have gone missing.
Kind of like Rory.
Reports are vague but it seems like
the killer is an expert with knives.
- That sounds like Savage's MO.
- Yeah, but serial killing isn't.
Sounds pretty small-time for a guy
who's has coffee with Hitler.
Yeah, well, clearly we have to assume
that Savage has a larger
more nefarious plan.
But since we've jumped back in time,
Savage isn't expecting us here.
Savage is pretty good at hiding,
even in a small town
so how do you plan to find him?
By investigating these murders.
Now, there has to be a common link
between the victims
starting with the first.
A piano teacher was found
slain in her home
which is now on the market.
There is, of course, crown molding.
All original floors. Stucco ceiling.
There's a small room
above the garage
suitable for live-in help.
Oh, well, we don't need a maid.
My husband and I get along
just fine on our own.
You know, I have a lovely
Tudor style in another town.
A more accepting one.
Forward-thinking.
No, that's... that's fine.
I like my towns backward.
Dr. Matt Miller was found murdered
on the grounds of the asylum
where he worked.
The sanitarium is in need
of a replacement.
It's a very impressive facility.
I did my doctoral thesis
on socio-pathology in relationship
to serial murder, actually.
Well, that'll certainly come in
handy around here.
We've been short-staffed ever since
Dr. Miller's sudden demise.
Of course, I could never consider
accepting a position here
without my faithful nurse/assistant.
Yes, well, she looks like
she'll fit right in.
Meanwhile, Jefferson is the perfect
age to discern the facts
behind the disappearance
of three teenagers
who went missing a week
before these murders began.
So, Raymond and Kendra
are shacking up
Sara's Nurse ratched
and Jax's the new kid in town.
Where does that leave me?
We're looking for the sheriff.
Well, you found him. Bud Ellison.
How can I help you, folks?
Special Agent Rip Hunter.
This is my partner, Leonard.
We are here to investigate
the serial murders
which have plagued this
sleepy old town of yours.
Now, slow down there, buddy.
There ain't no serial killer
anywhere.
All we got is some
unexplained accidents is all.
How about you hand over
those case files
so we can decide for ourselves?
Or we can come back
with a court order
and a really nasty disposition.
Anything for our friends
at the bureau.
Nice work, partner.
You're not my partner.
There's only one person
I ever trusted on this job,
and we all know how that turned out.
Schwinn Hornets.
I had the very same one
when I was their age.
Seeing white picket fences
and perfect family houses
it's enough to make one nostalgic.
- Or nauseated.
- Oh, come on, Ms. Lance.
Even someone as jaded as yourself
can't deny how idyllic this time was.
Yeah.
- If you're white.
- And a man.
- And straight. And...
- Okay, okay. I get the point.
Dude, even if this town
wasn't full of small-minded idiots
it'd still be creepy as hell.
I used to watch all these old
horror movies with my mom,
and they all started off
in places like this.
See, first it's all perfect
and then, boom,
some alien monster beast thing
starts killing kids on Lovers Lane.
- Oh.
- I'm telling you, man.
What is it?
An unhappy cheerleader.
Now, that is scary.
That girl was from the newspaper
articles Rip showed us.
She knows the guys that went missing.
Perhaps she can illuminate us
as to their whereabouts.
Dude, can you not just say,
"Hey, Jax, why don't you
go talk to her
and find out what she knows?"
Like a normal person.
Hey, Jax,
why don't you just go do that?
All right. We mustn't dawdle.
I believe our lunch hour
is nearly at an end.
Come along, Nurse.
Just so you know
Ra's al Ghul taught me
how to kill someone slowly,
over the course of days.
Hey, you mind if I sit?
- You can't sit with him.
- What is up with them?
I... I don't think
they've seen anyone.
Dip their fries in their milk
shake before?
Oh.
Don't knock it
till you tried it, girl.
No.
Okay.
- Okay, that's really good. Right?
- Yeah.
I'm Jax.
- Betty.
- Nice to meet you, Betty.
Hey, Betty.
Just because your boyfriend went AWOL
doesn't mean you have to slum it
with this loser.
Why don't you do yourself
a favor, Biff?
Keep walking before you really,
really embarrass yourself.
What? You want to take a swing at me?
Hey. Let's go.
This isn't over.
I am so sorry about that.
- Where were we?
- No, that was amazing.
Do you want to hang out
tomorrow night?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
- It's a date.
- Okay.
I was caught by your kisses
Well, now that we're done moving in,
care to dance?
Sure.
Locked in your arms
There's no mistake
So, yesterday, we kissed
and now, today, we're married.
Okay, I know it seems like
we're moving fast
but this is all pretend.
Soon as we get a divorce
we'll figure us out.
In the meantime
doesn't mean
we can't have fun with it.
This is a waste of time.
We should be out there looking
for Savage, not playing doctor.
You know what I mean.
I'd like to think that in a town
with multiple murders
and missing teenagers,
the local insane asylum would be
fertile ground for clues.
Let's start by reviewing
the files of every inmate
with a history of violence.
If you wouldn't mind getting me
those files, Nurse?
Literally for days.
Is that a new perfume I smell?
You know, if you're trying
to drive everyone crazy
I have to tell you, it's working.
I'm very busy right now.
You know what your problem is?
You don't know
how to have a good time.
Now, what you need is a man
who can show you one.
Thank you.
That was incredible.
Well, maybe next time,
he'll take no for an answer.
It's not just him.
Most of the doctors here
are looking for a good time
and most of the nurses all say yes
because they're looking
to get married.
Oh. Not you, though.
I'm not really looking for a husband.
Today's my first day.
Care to give the new girl a tour?
The files you asked for, Doctor.
Excellent, Nurse.
I could also go for a cup of coffee.
Me too. Black. Two sugars.
And the cafeteria's over there.
It's better than what we serve
the patients but not by much.
Oh.
What's down there?
Oh, that's Hall H,
the restricted ward.
It's for Dr. Knox's patients.
Violent psychotics.
That part of the tour
is worth skipping.
Coming!
I'm coming.
- Welcome to the neighborhood.
- Thank you.
- Thank you so much, Miss.
- Mrs. Knox.
Gail Knox and this is my husband,
Curtis.
Lovely to meet you.
I'm sorry, have... have
we met before?
I... I doubt it.
I, we just moved in
from way out of town.
I hope you like tuna surprise.
Are you kidding?
I love tuna surprise.
Oh, my God, Raymond!
These are our new neighbors,
Curtis and Gail.
- What a surprise.
- Tuna surprise.
So many surprises.
Well, another reason why we dropped
by was to let you know
that we are having a soiree tonight.
Stop by any time after 8.00.
We're just across the street.
- Don't bother to ring the bell.
- No, you just walk right on in.
It's that kind of neighborhood.
Savage doesn't think I recognize him,
which means he won't try to kill me.
He can't steal my powers
before I've found them.
Don't forget, we also have to figure
out why he's killing the townsfolk.
Are you really eating that?
Say what you want about Savage.
He makes one hell of a casserole.
Yes, well, Mr. Snart and I have been
analyzing these forensic files.
Which reveal nothing except
Savage is very good
at making people disappear.
Something you both have in common.
Are we just gonna pretend
like none of this happened?
That Mick Rory
wasn't a part of our team?
If you can just ice
your best friend like that
I hate to think
what you could do to us.
Right now, we need to stay
focused on the mission.
Look, Savage is going to be busy
with this little cocktail party.
Whilst you two keep an eye on him,
Sara and Martin have the opportunity
to find out what he's doing in
the secret wing of that asylum.
If you're looking for booze,
you're in the wrong office.
Dr. Knox doesn't drink.
But I know where Dr. Enbom
keeps the good stuff.
It seems like everyone's in love
Everyone but me
I can't find a doggone soul
To share my company
Oh, there you are, dear.
I could go for another
glass of bubbly.
Then I suggest you find a waitress.
- Well, I... I just assumed.
- You assume wrong.
So, why don't you go ahead
and get your own champagne?
Wow, I guess this whole interracial
marriage thing really is a novelty.
Well, go ahead and let them stare.
I've got the most beautiful
woman in the room on my arm.
I couldn't agree with you more.
Oh, hello.
Thank you for inviting us.
Your home, is very normal.
Oh, we are just glad
that you could attend.
Let me fix you a drink.
Okay, we need to split up.
You check the back rooms
and I'll see what I can find up here.
You sure that's a good idea?
Leaving you up here
by yourself with Savage?
I'm pretty sure he's not gonna
kill me next to the canapés, Ray.
Go. I'll let you know if I need help.
Fall in love with me
You've been so many places.
It's like you've had three lives.
Me, I've never left Harmony Falls.
That's your first mistake.
This town sucks.
Wow, you do not hold back.
I've learned life's too short.
So you have a girlfriend?
I just mean, seems pretty
obvious you're not into guys.
I... I don't know
what you're talking about.
Okay.
We don't have to talk about it
if you don't want to.
But just so you know,
I'm really good at keeping secrets.
Funny you should say that.
I did kiss a girl once.
I didn't think that made me a...
- You know.
- A lesbian?
- What?
- It's not a bad word.
Well, it is around here.
Well, good thing
I'm not from around here.
Nurse Lance, may I have
a word with you, please?
Well, now I see what's been going on.
While I've been busy working,
you were busy seducing
that young woman.
Actually, I was liberating her.
- With an option to seduce her later.
- Then what?
This poor young woman
will have to remain in the sexually
repressive 1950s
long after you've returned
to a time ship
and disappeared
from her life forever.
You know what, Doc?
I would love for someone
to drop into my life and tell me
that the future's gonna be
a better place.
Get to Hall H!
Your husband must be a fool
to leave a woman such as yourself
alone at a party.
He doesn't seem like your type.
That's a rather interesting
thing to say.
You hardly know me.
And yet I feel like I do.
Let me ask you a question, Kendra.
Do you believe in past lives?
Do you believe in fate?
Fate is a prison.
When free will is gone, what's left?
Destiny.
Hello.
Yeah. I understand.
Of course. I'm on my way.
Looks like we have to finish
our discussion later.
One of my patients needs attention.
Enjoy the party.
Tommy, Tommy, Tommy.
I... I thought the two of us
had an understanding.
I've allowed you and your cohorts
the occasional freedom to run free
and to feed your thirst and then...
then you do something like this.
I'm sorry, Mr. Palmer.
I'm unfamiliar
with the term "man cave."
Oh, it's a room in a basement
where a dude goes to be alone
or watch football.
In Savage's case, it's kill people.
So Ray and I break in and find out
what Savage is doing
in Harmony Falls.
Is tonight the Enchantment
Under the Sea dance?
I got a date tonight
with Tommy Fuller's
cheerleader girlfriend.
Turns out Betty's boyfriend
was one of the missing
high school kids.
I think she knows more than
she's letting on.
She's also a white girl
in a very, unenlightened community.
So please, be careful
when you're out in public with her.
An immortal psychopath and racists.
I'm beginning to like this quaint
little town less and less.
How's it going over there?
I'm in.
What do you see?
Nothing all that hideous.
Except for a terrible
collection of golf pants.
Hang on.
Ray?
Ray, it's Savage. He's back.
Did you hear me, Ray?
You need to get out of there!
I think I found something.
No, no, no, no.
You don't have time.
He's already inside.
Don't you ever get freaked out?
I mean, being in an insane asylum
by yourself in the middle
of the night?
Freaked out? No.
Lonely? Yes.
Actually, there is one place
in the hospital that scares me.
Dr. Knox's restricted wing.
Do you know what he's doing
to the patients down there?
No.
I don't like to think about it.
What do you like to think about?
- What's wrong?
- Nothing. I thought you said...
I... I just have to get back to work.
You look great tonight.
Don't have to tell me
- I'm sorry. I thought that...
- No, don't be sorry.
It's just, I thought girls from 1958
moved a little bit slower.
Girls from 1958?
I mean
I think we should
get to know each other
a little bit better first.
Okay.
What do you want to know?
Those guys back at the soda shop,
they mentioned something
about your boyfriend going AWOL?
Tommy.
What happened to him?
It's kind of a long story.
Well, I got all the time
in the world.
We were drag racing down on Route 7
with Davis and Billy
when Tommy's car went into a ditch.
- That's when they found it.
- Found what?
- This...
- Been looking all over for you.
- Get out!
- No!
Get out of the car!
Hey, get the hell off me, man!
Stop it! Stop it!
Get in! Get in!
Go!
Oh, come on!
Tommy?
I am not playing anymore!
Don't worry, Betty.
I'm gonna get you out of here.
Nice driving.
Hang in there.
Gideon's gonna fix you.
Who's Gideon?
- A doctor, of sorts.
- Okay.
You need to pull over, Jax.
Hey.
Relax.
Yeah, because it's not like
I'm a black kid in a small town
with a white girl bleeding
all over my seat.
You were driving to beat
the devil back there.
That explain why
your car looks like hell?
I need to get my friend
to a hospital.
- Friend?
- Yeah.
And there's more wounded
on Lovers' Lane.
Some... some kind of attack.
What were you doing with this girl
on Lovers Lane, boy?
There are kids back there
that could really use your help
and she needs medical attention
right now.
Put your hands on the car
and spread them.
Listen, you can play Boss Hogg
all you want
but I'm not gonna let
that girl bleed to death
so I tell you what,
I'm gonna get back in my car
and I'm gonna take her
to the hospital.
Gideon traced Jax's last
bio signature to this location.
Well, it seems you had good reason
to be concerned
for Mr. Jackson's safety.
Yeah, sucks being right all the time.
She has suffered
several severe lacerations.
I am attempting
to cauterize the wound.
- What happened?
- I don't know.
But I'm guessing Jax and Peggy Sue
had a pretty lousy first date.
Where is Jefferson?
There was no sign of him in the car.
These wounds don't appear
consistent with a knife.
Correct.
I believe these lacerations
were made by talons.
It was Tommy.
Tommy Fuller,
one of the missing teenagers.
He was like a bird.
He... he was like a bird monster.
Captain, analysis
of Miss Seaver's blood
reveals traces of silicate minerals.
Miss Seaver, do you recall
Tommy coming into contact
with a meteor of some kind?
The car crash...
it was...
it was glowing.
She's talking about
an Nth Metal meteorite.
Say something that makes sense.
It seems Mr. Fuller
has come into contact
with a meteorite
with mutagenic properties.
Try again.
Apparently, Miss Seaver's boyfriend
has been exposed
to the same type of meteor
that Kendra came into contact with.
Me?
Well, you and Carter.
4,000 years ago.
The meteorite
which gave you your powers
appears to be of the same variety
that mutated Tommy Fuller.
And I'm guessing it's not curable.
Well, I... I suppose,
if the talons which lacerated her
left some mutagenic residue,
I could...
Yes or no?
Perhaps.
Why don't you get
to work on that, Martin?
Okay, so if Savage
isn't the one doing the killing
what is he doing in town?
Doesn't matter.
We can take him down.
- The Amon Dagger. Where did you...
- Savage's house.
All right, we need
to proceed on two fronts
locate Jefferson and make
an all-out assault on Savage.
A full-on attack only plays
to Savage's strengths.
If we want to get him...
We need to target his weaknesses.
Sadly, very few come to mind.
I can think of one.
Me.
He wants me and he always has.
So if I can get close enough
to him, then...
Then he'll kill you.
Thank you for the vote of confidence,
but I don't need your protection.
There's no reason to go alone.
We're part of a team for a reason.
Yes, and the team seems comfortable
with me doing this
so that makes it about you and me.
- Any updates?
- We're making progress.
In the meantime, we need
to get ready to back Kendra up.
She's going into the asylum
to meet Savage tonight.
Another opportunity for you
to see Nurse Carlisle.
Yeah, and apologize.
I warned you, Ms. Lance.
Rushing a repressed woman
from the 1950s into the freewheeling
sexual mores of the 21st century.
Actually, I was the one
who freaked out.
Ever since I got brought
back to life, I haven't really
experienced much
in the way of feelings.
And then when Lindsey kissed me.
It was like you were being kissed
for the first time.
- How romantic.
- It was more like terrifying.
That's the thing
that sucks about feelings is,
you realize how much
you can hurt someone
or get hurt.
Wakey, wakey.
Do the words "police brutality"
mean anything to you?
You think this is brutal?
You'll be begging for me
after he gets through with you.
That's enough, Sheriff.
Thank you. Leave us be.
This young man and I have a lot
to discuss.
Forgive my friend for his ignorance.
You will learn
that I'm much more enlightened.
Well, I'll take racist
over crazy any day.
Oh, I would hardly describe
what I'm doing here as... as "crazy."
Therapy is nothing more than
a process of self-discovery.
You're about to experience
an extraterrestrial power.
Shall we begin?
What a piece of work is man.
When I was exposed to a meteorite,
I was blessed with eternal life,
immortality.
But sadly, the effect of this
meteorite turned out quite different.
But no less advantageous.
Doc, you have a visitor.
What a pleasant surprise.
Is it a surprise
or fate?
We didn't get to finish
our discussion the other night.
What of your square-jawed
husband, Raymond?
I didn't come here to talk
about my husband,
Doctor.
May I?
May I take your coat?
Make yourself comfortable.
Nurse?
Nurse, I keep hearing
voices in my head.
My wife with another man
and it's driving me crazy.
Well, maybe you should learn
to trust your wife a little bit more.
Orderly?
Show our new patient to his room.
And don't hesitate to give him
a sedative if he doesn't calm down.
Right away, Nurse.
I'm sure the kid is fine.
Jefferson and I, as you know,
share a psychic connection,
but for some inexplicable reason,
I can't seem to reach him.
I've grown so accustomed
to our partnership,
to suddenly be without him
is disquieting.
I know the feeling.
So have you tried
psychoanalysis before?
No.
- My husband thinks it's baloney.
- Oh, is that so?
Well, my specialty is
interpreting dreams.
What do you dream, Kendra?
To be honest,
I've dreamt of you before and me
together.
Well, that's interesting.
And what do we do in those dreams?
I'm afraid you'll think me forward.
Oh, but you are forward.
Coming here in that dress?
Perhaps you should learn
to embrace your desires
so the two of us
can finally be together.
Did you lose something?
I was wondering how long you could
play out this little charade.
You show up on my doorstep
and then my dagger goes missing?
You must think me stupid not to
suspect that your powers had emerged.
Well, well, well.
An FBI agent moonlighting
at the loony bin.
I'm afraid both of you boys
have some explaining to do
down at the station.
Who else have you brought
to the asylum tonight?
No one. No one! It's just me.
I hope you're better at lying
in your next life.
Oh, boy.
Just when you think
you've seen everything.
Guess those missing kids
are no longer missing.
What have you done?
I released my test subjects.
The energy from the meteorite
has changed them.
I set out to build an army
as powerful as you.
Pity they didn't turn out
nearly as beautiful.
Oh, my God.
It's Jefferson.
Jefferson, it's... it's us!
Jax, don't make me do this.
I'll deal with this lot.
Find Kendra now.
I can explain. Just not now.
Perhaps it will turn out better
in our next life, my love.
Are you okay?
It's time to go.
Not without Jefferson.
Or whatever's left of him.
Gideon was able to help me devise
a gene therapy that will hopefully
restore Jefferson and those at
the asylum to their former selves.
If genome bonding occurs,
we should know right away.
Course, we would never have had
the slightest chance of saving him
were it not for you.
Let's not get sentimental.
Another minute and things might have
gone down very differently.
Despite your bravado, Mr. Snart
the actions that I witnessed last
night were nothing short of heroic.
It's working.
Hey.
How are our friends
doing over in Hall H?
Whatever Dr. Stein gave those
creatures seemed to have worked.
They're back to normal.
And you?
Not sure if I'm ever gonna get
fully back to normal.
Good.
Thank you
for rescuing me.
Well, you rescued me first,
so now we're even.
You have to go, don't you?
I get it.
Should've known better
than to fall for a ninja.
Who knows?
Maybe I'll be back one day.
And if so...
You know where to find me.
So, I felt bad about trashing
your dad's.
I thought this might make up for it.
- You bought me a car?
- I souped it up too.
In case of future monster attacks.
I wish you didn't have to go.
I don't belong here.
And neither do you.
Promise me you'll
get out of this town.
The both of you.
Tommy!
It's a great big world out there,
Betty.
And it's changing fast.
Maybe we'll catch up down
the road somewhere.
Hey. I was just packing up.
I thought you were back
at the Waverider.
I just forgot something.
I forgot to say I'm sorry.
Look, I was wrong to think
that I could actually end
Savage by myself.
Just slow down.
I made a mistake too.
I got so caught up playing house
that I forgot about why
we were really here.
And you will end Savage someday.
I guess the last thing
a 4,000-year-old demigoddess needs
is an overprotective husband.
What she needs is a partner.
What do you say?
Partner.
Well, look who's up and around.
Yeah.
I guess I owe you an apology.
Grey told me about what happened
back at the asylum.
You had the chance to kill me
and you didn't.
After last night, I know enough
about being a monster
to know that you're not one.
Stop. I'm getting misty eyed.
I just want you to know
about what happened with Rory?
I get it.
You were protecting us.
And that doesn't make you a murderer.
It makes you a part of this team.
Jefferson, you should be resting.
Man, I'm... I'm done laying around.
I just want to get
the hell out of Mayberry.
Agreed, we're still waiting on Sara
and the two lovebirds to get back.
Seems they've taken quite
a shine to 1958.
- What on earth?
- Gideon?
Not this guy again.
Captain, Chronos has breached
the starboard hatch.
How is that possible?
Clearly, he's received some new toys
from his Time Master friends
since our last encounter.
Gideon, seal the bulkheads
from here until...
Grey, come on. Let us do this.
If we merge on the Waverider,
we could destroy the entire ship!
Are you not paying attention
to what Chronos is doing?
Fall back!
Get to the jump ship!
1958's swell and all
but I miss the Internet
and cell phones.
What are they doing?
- Hey.
- Hey!
Where did they go?
Better question,
why did they leave us?