In 2166,
an immortal tyrant named Vandal Savage
conquered the world
and murdered my wife and child.
I have assembled an elite team
to hunt him throughout time
and stop his rise to power.
Unfortunately, my plan is opposed
by the body I had sworn my allegiance to,
the Time Masters.
In the future,
my friends may not be heroes,
but if we succeed,
they will be remembered as legends.
Previously,
on Legends of Tomorrow...
Ray! Ray, I need you, please!
I thought you were dead.
Not only did you
fail to capture Savage,
but you exposed yourselves
and your powers to him,
giving away the element of
surprise for now and all time.
I let you go,
you'll deliver the Waverider?
Boys! The ship's all yours.
You're a liability to the team.
Only one of us
is walking outta here alive.
Tommy, promise me you won't go too fast.
You gotta hold on to something, honey.
Preferably me.
Remember, just 'cause you stole
your grandma's wheels
don't mean you gotta drive like her.
Oh, you run your mouth pretty fast,
let's see if
your car can keep up.
Tommy, hold tight.
Yo, James Dean, are you...
What's that?
I think that's a comet or something.
It's a meteorite.
In point of fact,
I was drawn to it as well.
Your presence out here was unexpected.
Or perhaps that's
just another word for destiny.
I'm not the only one
whose vision is blurry
in their left eye, am I?
Seeing three of everything,
that's normal, right?
Yes, as I mentioned before,
the effect of time travel
on the human body
increases with the length of each jaunt.
So, where are we?
Harmony Falls, Oregon.
According to Captain Baxter's intel,
Savage makes an appearance
in this quaint little hamlet.
What the hell is Savage doing
in Pleasantville?
Murder, apparently.
Several denizens of Harmony Falls
have been brutally slain
and others have gone missing.
Huh. Kind of like Rory.
Reports are vague,
but it seems like the killer's
an expert with knives.
That sounds like Savage's MO.
Yeah, but serial killing isn't.
Sounds pretty small time
for a guy who's had coffee with Hitler.
Clearly, we have to assume that Savage
has a larger, more nefarious plan
but since we've jumped back in time,
Savage isn't expecting us here.
Savage is pretty good at hiding
even in a small town,
so how do you plan to find him?
By investigating these murders.
Now, there has to be a common
link between the victims,
starting with the first.
A piano teacher was found
slain in her home
which is now on the market.
There is, of course, crown molding.
All original floors, stucco ceiling.
There's a small room above the garage
suitable for live-in help.
Oh, well, we don't need a maid.
My husband and I
get along just fine on our own.
You know, I have a lovely
Tudor style in another town.
A more accepting one.
Forward-thinking.
No, that's fine.
I like my towns backward.
Dr. Matt Miller
was found murdered
on the grounds of the asylum
where he worked.
The sanitarium
was in need of a replacement.
It's a very impressive facility.
I did my doctoral thesis
on sociopathology
in relationship to serial murder actually.
Now, that'll certainly
come in handy around here.
We've been short-staffed
ever since Dr. Miller's sudden demise.
Of course, I could never consider
accepting a position here
without my faithful nurse/assistant.
Yes, well, she looks like
she'll fit right in.
Meanwhile,
Jefferson is the perfect age
to discern the facts behind the
disappearance of three teenagers
who went missing a week before
these murders began.
So, Raymond and Kendra are shacking up,
Sara's Nurse Ratched,
and Jax's the new kid in town.
Where does that leave me?
We're looking for the Sheriff.
Well, you found him. Bud Ellison.
How can I help you, folks?
Special Agent Rip Hunter.
This is my partner, Leonard.
We are here to investigate
the serial murders,
which have plagued this
sleepy old town of yours.
Whoa. Now, slow down there, buddy, there.
There ain't no serial killer anywhere.
All we've got is some
unexplained accidents, is all.
How about you hand over those case files,
so we can decide for ourselves?
Or we can come back
with a court order
and a really nasty disposition.
Anything for our friends at the Bureau.
Nice work, partner.
You're not my partner.
There's only one person
I ever trusted on this job,
and we all know how that turned out.
Schwinn Hornets. I had the
very same when I was their age.
Seeing white picket fences
and perfect family houses,
it's enough to make one nostalgic.
Or nauseated.
Oh, come on, Ms. Lance.
Even someone as jaded as yourself
can't deny how idyllic this time was.
Yeah, if you're white.
And a man.
- And straight, and--
- Okay, okay. I get the point.
Dude, even if this town wasn't
full of small-minded idiots,
it'd still be creepy as hell.
I used to watch all these
old horror movies with my mom
and they all started off
in places like this.
See, first it's all perfect,
and then, boom,
some alien monster beast thing
starts killing kids on Lovers' Lane.
- Ooh.
- I'm telling you, man.
What is it?
An unhappy cheerleader.
Now, that is scary.
That girl was from the newspaper
articles Rip showed us.
She knows the guys that went missing.
Perhaps she can illuminate us
as to their whereabouts.
Dude, can you not just say,
"Hey, Jax, why don't you go talk to her
"and find out what she knows?"
Like a normal person?
Hey, Jax, why don't you just go do that?
All right, we mustn't dawdle.
I believe our lunch hour
is nearly at an end.
Come along, Nurse.
Just so you know,
Ra's al Ghul taught me how to
kill someone slowly
over the course of days.
Hey, do you mind if I sit?
What is up with them?
Um...
I don't think they've seen anyone--
Dip their fries in their milkshake before?
Oh.
Uh-uh. Don't knock it
till you tried it, girl.
No.
Okay.
Okay, that's really good.
- Right?
- Yeah.
- I'm Jax.
- Betty.
Nice to meet you, Betty.
Hey, Betty, just because
your boyfriend went AWOL
doesn't mean you have to slum it
with this loser.
Why don't you do yourself a favor, Biff?
Keep walking before you really,
really embarrass yourself.
What? You want to take a swing at me?
Hey, let's go.
This isn't over.
I'm so sorry about that.
Uh, where were we?
No, that was amazing.
Do you want to hang out tomorrow night?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
- It's a date.
- Okay.
Well, now that we're done moving in...
Care to dance?
Sure.
So, yesterday we kissed
and now today we're married.
Okay, I know it seems
like we're moving fast,
but this is all pretend.
As soon as we get a divorce,
we'll figure us out.
In the meantime, doesn't mean
we can't have fun with it.
This is a waste of time.
We should be out there looking
for Savage, not playing doctor.
You know what I mean.
I'd like to think that
in a town with multiple murders
and missing teenagers,
the local insane asylum would be
a fertile ground for clues.
Let's start by reviewing the files
of every inmate
with a history of violence.
If you wouldn't mind getting me
those files, Nurse?
Literally, four days.
Is that
a new perfume I smell?
You know, if you're trying to
drive everyone crazy,
I have to tell you, it's working.
I'm very busy right now.
You know what your problem is?
You don't know how to have a good time.
Now, what you need is a man
who can show you--
Uh...
Oops.
Thank you. That was incredible.
Well, maybe next time he'll take
no for an answer.
Uh, it's not just him.
Most of the doctors here
are looking for a good time,
and most of the nurses all say yes
'cause they're looking to get married.
Hmm. Not you, though?
I'm not really looking for a husband.
Today is my first day.
Care to give the new girl a tour?
The files you asked for, Doctor.
Excellent, Nurse.
I could also go for a cup of coffee.
Me, too. Black. Two sugars.
And the cafeteria is over there.
It's better than what we serve
the patients, but not by much.
- Mmm.
- Oh.
And what's down there?
Oh, that's Hall H, the restricted ward.
It's for Dr. Knox's patients.
Violent psychotics.
That part of the tour is worth skipping.
Coming. I'm coming.
Welcome to the neighborhood!
Thank you. Thank you so much, Miss...
Mrs. Knox. Gail Knox.
And this is my husband Curtis.
Lovely to meet you.
I'm sorry, have we met before?
I doubt it.
Uh... We just moved in
from way out of town.
I hope you like tuna surprise.
You kidding? I love
tuna surprise... Oh, my God!
Raymond, these are our new neighbors.
Curtis and Gail.
What a surprise! Tuna surprise.
So many surprises.
Well, another reason why we dropped by
was to let you know that
we're having a soiree tonight.
Stop by any time after 8:00,
we're just across the street.
Don't bother to ring the bell.
No, you just walk right on in.
It's that kind of neighborhood.
Savage doesn't think I recognize him,
which means he won't try to kill me.
He can't steal my powers
before I found them.
Don't forget, we also have to figure out
why he's killing the townsfolk.
Are you really eating that?
Say what you want about Savage,
he makes one hell of a casserole.
Yes, well, Mr. Snart and I
have been analyzing these forensic files.
Which reveal nothing
except Savage is very good
at making people disappear.
That's something you both have in common.
What, we're just gonna pretend
like none of this happened?
That Mick Rory wasn't a part of our team?
If you can just ice
your best friend like that,
I hate to think what you could do to us.
Right now, we need to
stay focused on the mission.
Look, Savage is going to be busy
with his little cocktail party.
Whilst you two keep an eye on him,
Sara and Martin have the opportunity
to find out what he's doing in
the secret wing of that asylum.
If you're looking for booze,
you're in the wrong office.
Dr. Knox doesn't drink.
But I know where Dr. Enbom
keeps the good stuff.
Oh, there you are, dear. I could
go for another glass of bubbly.
Then I suggest you find a waitress.
- I just assumed--
- You assumed wrong.
So why don't you go ahead
and get your own champagne?
Wow. I guess this whole
interracial marriage thing
really is a novelty.
Go ahead and let them stare.
I've got the most beautiful
woman in the room in my arm.
I couldn't agree with you more.
Oh. Hello.
Uh, thank you for inviting us.
Your home is, um, very normal.
Well, we're just glad
that you could attend.
Let me fix you a drink.
Okay, we need to split up.
You check the back rooms,
and I'll see what I can find up here.
Are you sure that's a good idea
leaving you up here by yourself
with Savage?
I'm pretty sure
he's not gonna kill me
next to the canapés, Ray?
Go. I'll let you know if I need help.
You've been so many places.
It's like you've had three lives.
Me, I've never left Harmony Falls.
That's your first mistake.
This town sucks.
Wow. You do not hold back.
I've learned life's too short.
So, you have a girlfriend?
Well, I just mean
it seems pretty obvious
you're not into guys.
Uh, I don't know
what you're talking about.
Okay. We don't have to talk
about it if you don't want to.
But, just so you know, I'm
really good at keeping secrets.
Funny you should say that,
I did kiss a girl once.
And I didn't think
that made me, you know...
A lesbian?
What?
It's not a bad word.
Well, it is around here.
Well, good thing
I'm not from around here.
Uh, Nurse Lance, may I have
a word with you, please?
Well, now I see what's been going on.
While I've been busy working,
you were busy seducing that young woman.
Actually, I was liberating her
with an option to seduce her later.
Then what? This poor young woman
will have to remain
in the sexually oppressive 1950s,
long after you've returned to a Timeship
and disappeared from her life forever.
You know what, Doc?
I would love for someone
to drop into my life
and tell me that the future
is gonna be a better place.
Oh.
Get to Hall H.
Your husband must be a fool
to leave a woman such as
yourself alone at a party.
He doesn't seem like your type.
It's a rather interesting thing
to say, you hardly know me.
And yet I feel like I do.
Let me ask you a question, Kendra.
Do you believe in past lives?
Do you believe in fate?
Fate is a prison.
When free will is gone, what's left?
Destiny.
Oh.
Hello.
Yeah, I understand.
Of course, I'm on my way.
Looks like we have to finish
our discussion later.
One of my patients needs attention.
Enjoy the party.
Tommy, Tommy, Tommy,
I thought the two of us
had an understanding.
I've allowed you and your cohorts
the occasional freedom to run free
and to feast your thirst and
then you do something like this?
I'm sorry, Mr. Palmer,
I'm unfamiliar with the term "man cave."
Oh, it's a room in a basement
where a dude goes to be alone,
or watch football.
Uh, in Savage's case, it's kill people.
So, Ray and I break in
and find out what Savage
is doing in Harmony Falls.
- Oh, ho, ho!
- Oh-ho.
Is tonight the Enchantment
Under the Sea dance?
I got a date tonight
with Tommy Fuller's
cheerleader girlfriend.
Turns out Betty's boyfriend
was one of the missing high school kids.
I think she knows
more than she's letting on.
Hmm. She's also a white girl in a
very, uh, unenlightened community.
So, please be careful when
you are out in public with her.
An immortal psychopath and racists.
I'm beginning to like
this quaint little town less and less.
How's it going over there?
I'm in.
What do you see?
Uh...
Nothing all that hideous.
Except for a terrible collection
of golf pants.
Hang on.
Ray.
Ray, it's Savage. He's back.
Did you hear me, Ray?
You need to get out of there!
I think I found something.
No, no, no. You don't have time.
He's already inside.
Do you ever get freaked out
in being in an insane asylum
by yourself in the middle of the night?
Freaked out, no.
Lonely, yes.
Actually, there is one place
in the hospital that scares me.
Dr. Knox's restricted wing.
Do you know what he is doing
to the patients down there?
No. I don't like to think about it.
What do you like to think about?
What's wrong?
Nothing. I just...
I have to get back to work.
You look great tonight.
Whoa. Whoa.
I'm sorry. I thought that...
No, don't be sorry. It's just, uh...
I thought girls from 1958
moved a little bit slower.
"Girls from 1958"?
I mean, uh... I think we should
get to know each other
a little bit better first.
Okay, what do you wanna know?
Those guys back at the soda shop,
they mentioned something
about your boyfriend going AWOL.
Tommy.
What happened to him?
It's kind of a long story.
Well, I got all the time in the world.
We were drag racing down
on Route 7 with Davis and Billy
when Tommy's car went into a ditch.
- That's when they found it.
- Found what?
This--
Been looking all over for you.
- Get out! Get out of the car!
- No!
Hey, get the hell off me, man.
Stop it! Stop it!
Get in! Get in!
Go!
Oh, come on!
Tommy?
I'm not playing anymore.
Don't worry, Betty,
I'm gonna get you out of here.
Nice driving.
Hang in there. Gideon's gonna fix you.
- Who's Gideon?
- A doctor, of sorts.
You need to pull over, Jax.
Hey, relax.
Yeah, 'cause it's not like I'm
a black kid in a small town
with a white girl
bleeding all over my seat.
You were driving
to beat the devil back there.
That explain
why your car looks like hell?
I need to get my friend to a hospital.
- Friend?
- Yeah.
And there's more wounded on Lovers' Lane.
Some kind of attack.
Now, what were you doing with
this girl on Lovers' Lane, boy?
There are kids back there
that could really use your help
and she needs medical attention right now.
Put your hands on the car and spread 'em.
Listen, you can play
Boss Hogg all you want,
but I'm not gonna
let that girl bleed to death.
So, I'll tell you what.
I'm gonna get back in my car,
and I'm gonna take her to the hospital.
Gideon traced Jax's last
bio-signature to this location.
Well, it seems you had good reason
to be concerned for Mr. Jackson's safety.
Yeah, sucks being right all the time.
She has suffered several
severe lacerations.
I'm attempting to cauterize the wound.
- What happened?
- I don't know,
but I'm guessing Jax and Peggy Sue
had a pretty lousy first date.
Where is Jefferson?
There was no sign of him
in the car.
These wounds don't appear
consistent with a knife.
Correct. I believe these
lacerations were made by talons.
It's Tommy.
Tommy Fuller,
one of the missing teenagers.
He's like a bird, he...
Like a bird monster.
Captain, analysis of
Ms. Seaver's blood
reveals traces of silicate minerals.
Ms. Seaver, do you recall
Tommy coming into contact
with a meteor of some kind?
The car crash.
It was...
It was glowing.
She's talking
about an Nth metal meteorite.
Say something that makes sense.
It seems Mr. Fuller's come into contact
with a meteorite
with mutagenic properties.
Try again.
Apparently, Ms. Seaver's boyfriend
has been exposed to
the same type of meteor
that Kendra came into contact with.
Me?
Well, you and Carter, 4,000 years ago.
The meteorite which gave you your powers
appears to be of the same variety
that mutated Tommy Fuller.
And I'm guessing it's not curable.
I suppose if the talons
which lacerated her
left some mutagenic residue
- I could--
- Yes or no?
Perhaps.
Why don't you get to work on that, Martin?
Okay, so if Savage isn't the one
doing the killing,
what is he doing in town?
Doesn't matter.
We can take him down.
The Amon Dagger. Where did you...
Savage's house.
All right. We need to
proceed on two fronts.
Locate Jefferson and make
an all-out assault on Savage.
A full-on attack only plays
to Savage's strengths.
If we want to get him...
We need to target his weaknesses.
Sadly, very few come to mind.
I can think of one.
Me.
He wants me and he always has.
So, if I can get
close enough to him, then--
Then he'll kill you.
Thank you for the vote of confidence,
but I don't need your protection.
There's no reason to go alone.
We're a part of a team for a reason.
Yes, and the team seems
comfortable with me doing this.
So, that makes it about you and me.
- Any updates?
- We're making progress.
In the meantime, we need to
get ready to back Kendra up.
She's going into the asylum
to meet Savage tonight.
Another opportunity for you
to see Nurse Carlisle.
Yeah, and apologize.
I warned you, Ms. Lance.
Rushing a repressed woman from the 1950s
into the freewheeling sexual mores
of the 21st century--
Actually, I was the one who freaked out.
Oh.
Ever since I got brought back to life,
I haven't really experienced
much in the way of feelings,
and then when Lindsey kissed me--
It was like you were
being kissed for the first time.
How romantic.
It was more like terrifying.
That's the thing
that sucks about feelings,
is you realize how much
you can hurt someone
or get hurt.
Wakey-wakey.
Do the words "police brutality"
mean anything to you?
You think this is brutal?
You'll be begging for me
after he gets through with you.
That's enough, Sheriff.
Thank you. Leave us be.
This young man
and I have a lot to discuss.
Forgive my friend for his ignorance.
You will learn that
I'm much more enlightened.
Well, I'll take racist
over crazy any day.
Oh, I'd hardly describe
what I'm doing here as crazy.
Therapy is nothing more than
a process of self-discovery.
And you are about to experience
an extraterrestrial power.
Shall we begin?
What a piece of work is man.
When I was exposed to a meteorite
I was blessed with eternal life,
immortality.
But sadly, the effect of this meteorite
turned out quite differently.
But no less advantageous.
Doc, you have a visitor.
What a pleasant surprise.
Is it a surprise?
Or fate?
We didn't get to finish
our discussion the other night.
What of your
square-jawed husband Raymond?
I didn't come here
to talk about my husband,
Doctor.
May I?
May I take your coat?
Make yourself comfortable.
Nurse.
Nurse, I keep hearing voices in my head.
My wife with another man,
and it's driving me crazy.
Maybe you should learn to trust
your wife a little bit more.
Orderly. Show our new patient
to his room.
And don't hesitate to give him a sedative
if he doesn't calm down.
Right away, Nurse.
I'm sure the kid is fine.
Jefferson and I, as you know,
share a psychic connection.
But for some inexplicable reason
I can't seem to reach him.
I've grown so accustomed
to our partnership,
to suddenly be without him is disquieting.
I know the feeling.
So, have you tried psychoanalysis before?
No.
My husband thinks it's baloney.
Oh, is that so?
Well, my specialty is
interpreting dreams.
What do you dream, Kendra?
To be honest,
I've dreamt of you before,
and me.
Together.
Well, that's interesting.
And what do we do in those dreams?
I'm afraid you'll think me forward.
Oh, but you are forward,
coming here in that dress.
Perhaps you should
learn to embrace your desires
so the two of us can finally be together.
Did you lose something?
I was wondering how long
you could play out this little charade.
You show up on my doorstep
and then my dagger goes missing.
You must think me stupid
not to suspect
that your powers had emerged.
Well, well, well, an FBI agent
moonlighting at the loony bin.
I'm afraid both of you boys
have some explaining to do,
down at the station.
Who else have you
brought to the asylum tonight?
No one. No one! It's just me.
I hope you're better at lying
in your next life.
Oh, boy.
Just when you think
you've seen everything.
Guess those missing kids
are no longer missing.
What have you done?
I released my test subjects.
The energy from the meteorite
has changed them.
I set out to build
an army as powerful as you,
pity they didn't turn out
nearly as beautiful.
Oh, my God.
It's Jefferson.
Jefferson, it's us!
Jax! Don't make me do this!
I'll deal with this lot. Find Kendra now.
I can explain, just not now.
Perhaps it'll turn out better
in our next life, my love.
Are you okay?
It's time to go.
Not without Jefferson.
Or whatever's left of him.
Gideon was able to help me
devise a gene therapy
that will hopefully restore Jefferson
and those at the asylum
to their former selves.
If genome bonding occurs
we should know right away.
Of course, we'd never have had
the slightest chance of saving
him were it not for you.
Let's not get sentimental.
Another minute and things might
have gone down very differently.
Despite your bravado, Mr. Snart,
the actions that I witnessed last night
were nothing short of heroic.
It's working.
Hey.
How are our friends doing over in Hall H?
Whatever Dr. Stein gave those
creatures seemed to have worked.
They're back to normal.
And you?
I'm not sure if I'm ever
gonna get fully back to normal.
Good.
Thank you
for rescuing me.
Well, you rescued me first so...
Now we're even.
You have to go, don't you?
I get it.
Should've known better
than to fall for a ninja.
Who knows? Maybe I'll be back one day.
- And if so...
- You know where to find me.
So, I felt bad about trashing your dad's.
Uh, I thought this might make up for it.
You bought me a car?
I souped it up too, in case of
future monster attacks.
- I wish you didn't have to go.
- Yeah.
I don't belong here.
And neither do you.
Promise me you'll get out
of this town, the both of you.
Tommy.
It's a great big world out there, Betty,
and it's changing fast.
Maybe we'll catch up
down the road somewhere.
Hey. I was just packing up.
I thought you were back at the Waverider.
I just forgot something.
I forgot to say I'm sorry.
Look, I was wrong to think that I could
- actually end Savage by myself.
- Whoa. Whoa.
Whoa, whoa. Just slow down.
I made a mistake, too.
I got so caught up playing house
that I forgot about
why we were really here.
And you will end Savage someday.
I guess that last thing
a 4,000-year-old demi-goddess needs
is an over-protective husband.
What she needs is a partner.
What do you say?
Partner.
Well, look who's up and around.
Hmm. Yeah.
I guess I owe you an apology.
Grey told me about what happened
back at the asylum.
You had the chance to kill me
and you didn't.
After last night, I know
enough about being a monster
to know that you're not one.
Stop. I'm getting misty-eyed.
I just want you to know,
about what happened with Rory,
I get it.
You were protecting us.
And that doesn't make you a murderer,
it makes you a part of this team.
Jefferson, you should be resting.
Oh, man, I'm done laying around.
I just want to get
the hell out of Mayberry.
Agreed.
We're still waiting on Sara and
the two lovebirds to get back.
It seems they've taken
quite a shine to 1958.
What on earth?
Gideon?
Not this guy again.
Captain, Chronos has breached
the starboard hatch.
How is that possible?
Clearly, he's received some new toys
from his Time Master friend,
since our last encounter.
Gideon, seal the bulkheads
from here until--
Grey, come on! Let's do this!
If we merge on the Waverider,
we could destroy the entire ship!
Are you not paying attention
to what Chronos is doing?
Fall back!
Get to the Jumpship!
1958's swell and all,
but I miss the Internet.
And cell phones.
Uh...
What are they doing?
- Hey!
Where did they go?
Better question, why did they leave us?
English - SDH