[Constantine screaming]
[Zari] Previously on
Legends Of Tomorrow...
Astra. This place, it's twisted you.
It's made me more like you.
When you took on the wand's power,
you also took on its charge.
Oh, Fairy Godmother?
Go find John and help him
rescue Ray from Hell.
Gary, you dick.
I have created a simple app.
You will be able to share
monster sightings.
"In exchange for this service,
the user agrees
to forfeit their eternal soul
to the demon Neron."
He may be planning a monster attack.
Get every single one of those monsters
out of the Time Bureau.
- It's a bloody jailbreak!
- No.
What kind of egg is that?
[Gideon] It's a dragon egg.
My name is Zari.
[exhales]
[Mona exclaims] Oh, Sa...
Hey! You haven't happened to see
an ogre wandering around,
about yea high,
likes to grunt, drink beer?
Ask Rory.
Ah. Ogre wins again.
Cheating bastard.
No one out-drinks Mick Rory.
[Ogre burps]
Hey, fellas!
Sorry to break up all the fun,
but, uh, technically,
I wasn't supposed to allow
any magical creatures
out of the lab, so...
[growls]
On second thought,
why don't you two finish up here,
and I'll go, uh,
track down the Minotaur?
[slow music playing]
You're not a horrible mother.
You just had a lot on your mind.
I left our dragon egg in the care
of nine-year-old me.
[Agent Sharpe] Has anybody seen Gary?
Wait, what did you just say?
I was distracted.
I just found out the EYES app
is stealing people's souls,
and then baby me comes home and I...
You two need to grab that egg
before it hatches.
We can't risk Ne-Ray getting his hands
on a baby dragon.
It's already bad enough
that he has Charlie.
- Okay.
- Fair.
Get up. Time's a-wasting.
There are souls just waiting to be sold.
You're off your rocker, you old nag.
This here shapeshifter
don't take requests.
Shapeshifter?
Is that all you think you are?
You may have
your human friends fooled, dearie,
but you and I both know
what you're truly capable of.
- You don't know me!
- Don't I?
This shape you're wearing,
though lovely, is a costume.
It's not who you really are.
You aren't meant to hide, my pet.
You are meant to show humans
their greatest fears.
And lucky for you,
helping monsters
fulfill their potential...
is what I do.
[Nora screaming]
Yes.
[grunts]
Damn it, Gary.
Oh.
Excuse me. Hi. Excuse me...
Hi, pardon me, I just...
I don't belong here.
No, and I'm...
I'm a Fairy Godmother
sent to find John Constantine!
Really?
What, are the King and Queen of Hell
making their grand debut?
Not our debut, dearie.
No, no, no.
Stop! What are you doing?
As much as I'd like to pontificate
about my grander plan...
I've taught him better than that.
[screaming]
Ah.
Who the hell are you?
Really? The dress doesn't sell it?
You didn't tell me
you had a Fairy Godmother, John.
Not his. Gary's.
[grunts] And I thought
I was the one being tortured.
[Calibraxis] Look, princess.
We got rules here in Hell.
All right, you can't just...
[Nora] Let's go.
What are you doing?
Going to find Ray
the same way I found you.
The only difference is,
Ray doesn't have a body.
So, let's go find his soul.
His soul token.
That's the currency in Hell.
While his soul is being tortured,
then his token is traded around town
like money.
As long as you have it,
then you'll always
have access to the soul.
[groans]
But since Neron is still topside,
then his token's likely locked
in his vault.
Then let's go find it.
Why isn't this working?
I'm sorry, love, you can't just go
poofing yourself
into the vaults of Hell.
We'll have to find someone
to help us break in.
And I think I know just the person.
[Nate] I don't see her.
[Zari] How do you know
what nine-year-old me looks like?
I'm just looking for
the coolest kid in school.
Yeah, there's a lot I haven't told you
about my childhood.
There. That's the spot where
kids used to gang up on me and say,
"Zari, Zari,
why are your clothes so sorry?"
Bah.
I would have said,
"Zari, Zari, you smell like calamari."
Bullying is bad. It's...
All right, let's break this up
and find out where I stashed the egg.
- [boy 1] He's so cool.
- [boy 2] Aw. Look how cute he is.
- [girl 1] I want a dragon.
- [girl 2] He's so adorable.
[girl 1] I wanna take him home with me.
Oh, my God. He hatched.
And I brought him to school.
- Okay, so, we gotta get him before...
- Wait, wait, wait, look.
Mithra, dance.
[chittering]
[sneezes]
[kids cheering]
- [girl 3] Awesome, Zari.
- Thank you.
Mmm.
Come on.
What's going on, children?
It's okay. He's my pet, Mithra.
I named him after the...
Run, children! It's a monster.
[children screaming]
Wait, Zari, Zari. Wait! Wait.
Don't hurt him!
Hmph.
Oh, my God, I lost him again.
[Gideon] Captain, I've located Neron.
[newsreader] Now, live to Capitol Hill,
where the Palmer ex-CEO
is testifying before
the Senate subcommittee.
[Ne-Ray] Look, I know
Senator Wellington doesn't believe
that it's up to the private sector
to intervene in such an
unprecedented crisis.
But I should mention, not a single one
of my subscribers has been harmed
in a monster attack.
Senator, do you care to respond?
This bloke is just trying to scare folks
into downloading his evil,
soul-sucking app.
There ain't no such thing as...
This isn't me!
- [woman] Senator!
- I'm not doing this!
Like I said,
they could be hiding anywhere.
And only you can stop them.
Wait. He might be Charlie.
Who am I supposed to shoot?
There.
Damn pigs! I'm trying to help you out!
[officer] Stay there.
[grunts]
We gotta go!
[Mick] Come on.
Let her go. She's served her purpose.
[rock music playing]
Astra Logue.
The name's Neron.
I hear good things about you.
Now, that I'm taking over
for your former employers, I...
Give it a rest, John.
You think I can't see through
your cheap little parlor trick?
How'd you get out of
the torture pits, anyway?
Nice sparkles.
Nice shoulder pads.
What do you want, John?
And please tell me you're not here
to make some sad, sappy plea
for me to remember who I really am.
I know exactly who you are.
You're someone I can work with.
The triumvirate, they were
too short-sighted to take my deal,
and now,
they are roasting rats for supper.
But you're smarter than that, Astra.
All I need is access to one measly soul,
and in exchange, I'll go kill Neron,
and your boys will be back on top.
So, this soul you're after...
Must be pretty special.
He is.
I was special to you too, John.
Once.
And yet you left me down here
to rot all those years.
- Astra, you can't just...
- I'm over it.
I made the best of a bad situation,
and guess what?
I flourished.
Down here, I had prospects.
Until Neron wiped his ass with them.
So, do we have a deal?
Let's go rob the King.
[news reporter]
Today's attack at the US Capitol
has sparked worldwide panic and paranoia
over the threat of magical creatures.
Enough, Gideon.
Where is Neron in all this?
Why isn't he responding
to his magical creature alerts?
What alerts? All the creatures
are here on the ship.
You know what? It doesn't even matter.
Neron's shown the world
that anyone can be a monster.
People are turning on each other,
everyone's terrified.
I thought Neron wanted to collect souls.
How does hacking the app,
only to let it fail,
get him what he wants?
[Charlie] It's not about souls anymore.
It's something worse.
They didn't share their endgame,
but from what I could figure out,
they don't give a fart
about ruling Hell.
- It's actually fear that they're after.
- Why?
Fear is power. It's energy.
And thanks to me, they have
a wallop of it to muck about with.
[Gideon] That might explain
the strange meteorological event
forming over Washington DC.
Right above the Time Bureau.
Gideon, do you have a visual?
You're welcome, world.
[Ne-Ray] The air is thick
with human fear.
The hour of our coronation
draws near, my pet.
It's time to send your message
to your legions below.
The bank's right around the corner.
[rumbling]
[Nora] What's happening?
[Ne-Ray] Denizens of Hell,
for far too long, we have been forced
to live like insects
underneath the Earth.
Soon, a door will open.
Look to the sky, and await my signal.
With me as your king,
we will make Earth Hell again.
[cheering]
So, that's been his play all along.
We best keep moving, loves.
Before all Hell literally breaks loose.
[growling]
Stay calm. They smell fear.
What if fear's my natural scent?
[growling]
Good afternoon, everyone.
We have your favorites.
I know it's a bit crowded in here,
but we're making the best of it.
Anybody want a sammy-whammy?
[exclaims]
Put that in your whammy, you dick!
Okay... Uh...
Bon appetit.
[all growling]
They are savages.
Oh, calm down, Gary.
The longer we keep
the magical creatures locked up,
the more
they're gonna act like actual monsters.
They are monsters, you twit.
And so are you. We all are.
How are we supposed
to defeat fear itself?
I mean, people afraid of metas,
magical creatures
afraid of people and...
[sighs]
Monsters hated by everyone.
Not everyone.
Gideon, play the...
[Gideon] The dancing dragon
sneeze video?
- [Nora] Yep, that.
- Mithra, dance.
- [Sara] What is this?
- Wicksty.
[sneezes]
[kids cheering]
- Aw.
Yeah, this innocent moment
where kids aren't afraid,
it's resonating with people.
They don't see a monster,
they see something amazing.
So do I.
Me on that playground,
surrounded by people
who wanna be my friend.
Even if it was just for a day,
that little baby dragon
changed my world.
You sound like my dad's pitch for...
Heyworld!
Oh, my God, guys, that's it.
What... What's... What?
My dad had a dream to build a theme park
that people would come to see
because of magic.
That's what the world needs right now.
A place for people to come and see
the wonder of these creatures in person.
What, so, they can
just shoot us all in one place?
Yeah, that's bloody brilliant, that.
No, so, they can see creatures
the way that you helped us
see creatures, Charlie.
Not as monsters, but as misfits
just trying to find their place.
Look, if we can learn that lesson,
then so can the rest of the world.
We just need to bring people
and creatures together.
Think of it like a magical version
of Woodstock.
If we build it...
- [snaps fingers]
- They will come.
How long until
we can get it up and running?
Uh, if Mikey T and the boys
work weekends, quick math in my head,
two, maybe three years.
Oh.
- He's not a coin.
- Observant.
No flesh bags, just souls.
That's why they call it
the Soul Exchange.
All right, then.
I'll be on me way, then.
This is John Constantine.
Oh.
And me without my autograph book.
No worries, love. Next time, yeah?
[clicks tongue]
Look, if you would like
to convert his soul into cash, you...
Maybe you don't get it.
Neron owns the marker on his soul.
And Neron wants to torture him
as soon as he gets here.
But, hey,
if you want to tell the new boss
why his prize victim
isn't waiting in his vault...
This way.
Not so rough.
FYI, there's no bathroom in here,
and I'm not feeding him.
I'm a bank teller, not a zoo...
[grunts]
Pretty cool for a grown woman
wearing taffeta and a tiara.
How does this work?
We find a coin?
There are thousands.
Some of history's worst.
[Constantine] Yeah, I'd wager
he's keeping it somewhere special.
Hey, what are you doing?
What? Revolution's in the air.
I've got to look out for number one.
You were a golden opportunity
to bank roll my future.
I took it.
What about Brigid's diary?
If we put it in Nate's hands,
he could just dream us up a theme park.
Z! You are a genius!
Oh. It's in the Time Bureau.
It's okay. So, we just break in.
But it's not gonna be easy.
Even if it isn't demon central,
the vault that it's being held in
is practically impenetrable.
Oh, it's penetrable.
Oh, my God!
- I love you, Rory.
- Mmm-hmm.
Give it back when you're done.
Buck and Garima's sexual odyssey
is far from over.
All right, team. Nate,
you have a theme park to dream up.
Gary, help Mona
Pretty Woman our creatures
into something
a little more kid-friendly.
And the rest of us...
It's time to come up
with a marketing plan
for the happiest place on the planet.
[Gideon] Ms. Tomaz,
your simulation program
has detected a change
in your presently predicted future.
A good change or bad change?
In one potential 2042,
building Heyworld leads to an era
of understanding and tolerance.
The Anti-Meta-Human Act of 2029
never passes,
your parents live out their lives
peacefully in Seattle.
The future, as you know it,
would be completely changed.
My parents... Behrad...
That means a piece of this crazy plan
actually works.
This is great news, right?
God, I have been running
that stupid program for so long,
I had given up hope
of it actually working.
If this works, my brother survives,
I never steal his totem back from ARGUS,
I never join the Legends.
The last two years
wouldn't have happened.
Who knows where I'll be or who I'll be?
[Sara] You'll be you.
Because while we're at Heyworld,
you'll be here on the ship,
in the temporal zone,
and you'll be safe.
Sara, I can't, I can't sit this one out.
Look, I'm not gonna lose another Legend.
And who said
we're not putting you to work?
Look, we need to make sure what happens
at Heyworld is seen globally.
I can use the EYES app as a backdoor
into the phones that downloaded it.
- Thank you.
- [inaudible]
I found it. I found it. Ray's coin.
So long, then, John Boy. For now.
Oh, hold on a minute.
Our deal was for his soul,
not a bleeding coin.
Fine. A promise is a promise.
[Ray screaming]
What are they doing to him in there?
Prepare yourself, love.
What's behind this door,
it won't be pretty.
Down here, they twist a man's soul
until he's no longer human.
After what they've done to the big man,
he might not even be...
- [Ray] No!
- Ray! Ray!
Nora! John!
We're just about to start another game
of giant Jenga.
You gotta meet my old friend.
Well, technically, my new friend.
We used to be mortal enemies.
Oh, hi, guys.
You're just in time for the next round.
[Sara] When the world
needs heroes, they answer the call.
We'll be at Heyworld,
the new adventure capital
of Eastern Maryland.
Where we will hit fun...
in the bull's-eye.
And we'll give your children a...
flash of excitement.
And... cut!
- That was good, guys.
- That was a good take.
- Yeah.
- That was a great take.
Uh, guys, I feel like
that would have worked
a little bit better
with the real trinity.
Yeah, well, I asked,
and they said, "Hard pass."
- We should have done the crossover.
- Yeah.
Who needs the trinity anyway, right?
I mean, the Legends are super enough!
But Heyworld isn't a superhero park.
Promising them something
and giving them something else
feels wrong, doesn't it?
People aren't going to go to a park
filled with things they're terrified of.
People need franchise superheroes
to feel safe,
so, that's how we're gonna
get them in the door.
- [creatures growling]
- [Mona] Okay, everyone,
let's just go around the room one by one
and say what talent you can contribute
to the Heyworld review.
Oh, Minotaur, let's start with you.
I hear you like guitar.
Don't tell her nothin', Bullface.
- [Ogre] Let us out of here.
- We can't do that, Mr. Ogre.
It's not safe out there.
Well, we ain't helping you,
what with you moving us around
from one prison to another.
So, why should we trust you?
Listen up, if you lot don't want
to go back to a real prison,
then this is your chance.
This is your chance to change the way
that humans see you.
Show them that
just because you look scary...
doesn't mean you are scary.
[Charlie] That's right, Wolfie.
Look, I know how infuriating
humans can be.
They have a hard time seeing past
their own noses, don't they?
But they can change.
If you help them to look deeper.
And if they see the amount of good
that you lot are capable of,
then maybe, maybe they'll believe in you
even when you doubt yourself.
[purrs]
Now, I know there's more to all of you
than meets the eye.
Like you, Ogre.
My name is Frederick.
But what's the point?
Every time I try
to show a human who I really am,
they run away or try to kill me.
And that must really hurt your feelings.
Yeah, it does.
All I ever wanted to do was sing.
[grunts]
It looks like
we found ourselves a double act.
Now, who else has a hidden talent?
Brilliant. Beautiful.
I think we've got ourselves a show.
[Ray] Wait. What are you doing here?
Are you dead?
Oh, please tell me you're not dead.
What are you doing in that dress?
Not that I don't like it, but...
Wow.
Idiot!
What were you thinking,
selling your soul to a demon? Ray?
- I...
- You doomed the whole planet.
Look, I didn't have a choice.
He was going to kill Nate.
And it was the only way I could
make sure my best friend would be safe.
So, that was the deal you made.
His life for your body.
Oh, Raymond, you sweet,
dumb, son-of-a-softie.
Yeah, right? What a guy.
I was sent here to torture him,
but then we got to talking.
Oh, it got really deep, man.
It really did.
What were we even fighting about
all those years ago?
Your compulsion for world domination
and inability to accept rejection.
[Vandal] Ah.
Translation, it was about a girl.
A girl? What girl?
Doesn't matter. We should go.
Wait.
Something's happening.
I think I fulfilled Gary's wish.
Ray, take my hand. John.
Oh, all right. Ciao for now.
Say hi to the Legends for me, will you?
Oh, I love those groovy guys.
Jenga time!
[laughing]
Oh.
Almost forgot, extra hot sauce
for the Chupacabra.
[bottle shatters]
What in the hell?
More like, out of it, mate.
- It worked! You got Constantine.
- All right.
- Okay, just be cool. Simmer down.
- Okay.
Where's Ray?
He was just here, he...
Yeah, that's the only way he can travel
as long as Neron's using his body.
Fairy Godmother, I wish for Ray
to get his body back.
All magic has its limitations, you know,
stroke of midnight and all that,
but don't worry.
I'm sure the Legends have
something up their sleeves.
This isn't playtime, you twits.
Neron is using fear
to open up the gates of Hell.
Well, that's why we have to fight fear
with something wonderful.
We have to show the world
that these magical creatures
are just that.
They're magical.
And everyone else is
on board with this?
- Yeah.
- Yeah. Pretty much.
- Bloody hell.
- [Sara] All right. Great.
Now, that you're all on board,
we have work to do.
There is another way.
Whilst in Hell, we learnt that
Neron's possession of Ray's body
is contingent on Nate not being killed.
Is that why Ne-Ray didn't strangle me
when he had the chance?
Yeah.
That demon is only as good as his word.
If Neron breaks that deal,
he'd be ejected from Ray's body.
I could kill him.
And once I do,
all the souls he's nabbed
will be released.
And all Neron has to do is...
[clicks tongue]
me?
No. Absolutely not.
Look, there is no plan B.
Only plan A. Got it?
Yeah. Got it.
[clears throat]
Look, I meant what I said earlier.
I am not losing another Legend.
So, forget what you heard back there
because we are all in on Heyworld.
Now, I believe in you.
And if I'm not mistaken,
someone has a theme park to build.
Yeah.
[sighs]
I can't believe
it all comes down to this.
After years of anxiety of whether or not
I could live up
to my dad's expectations.
I'm about to
bring his crazy dream to life.
Knowing what it could cost me.
Nate, I'm not going anywhere.
You got this.
[inhales deeply]
Okay.
Let's do this.
I'm standing in front of Heyworld,
a new superhero-inspired theme park
that seems to have sprung up overnight,
like magic.
Welcome to Heyworld,
the happiest place on the globe.
Hey, kid, welcome to Heyworld.
Try the churros.
And not just because
the real money is in the concessions.
They're also delicious.
Z, um, you and your mom are here.
I see them. I mean, us.
All right, stream's up.
You look great, by the way.
Ah, thank you for noticing, I showered.
How's the clickety-clackety-hackety
coming along?
Once Ava hits record,
this will stream out to about,
you know, three billion people or so.
No pressure.
Come one, come all,
to our thrilling stage spectacular,
superheroes versus monsters.
Okay. You got the choreography down?
Everyone, follow her lead. Uh...
Oh, Baba Yaga, remember,
those kids are audience members,
not appetizers.
Mike, watch your language out there.
All right?
We don't want those gormless wankers
from standards and practices
up our you-know-whats.
Everyone, they're gonna love you guys.
All right, gang. It's showtime.
[growling]
[cheering]
Ladies and gentlemen,
please don't call them heroes,
call them Legends.
Now, let's see what derring-do
the Legends of Tomorrow get into today.
[applause and cheering]
[both grunting]
And that'll teach those bad guys
that crime doesn't pay.
Thanks for the assist, Green Arrow!
See you later, Supergirl.
Whoa. Did you see that?
That's The Flash,
and he wants to hang out.
Should we go hang out?
[cheering]
Break a leg, guys.
Wait a second! Shh.
I think that I hear something.
[Nate] Monsters!
What do you think, White Canary?
Should we show 'em what we got?
Wait. Hold on.
What if, instead of showing 'em
what we got,
we ask them what they have?
Hmm?
You mean, get to know them?
What if, getting to know them,
we realize that we have nothing to fear?
[Nate] Minotaur, your passion is music.
Why don't you show us what you got?
[booing]
They said this was a superhero show.
These brats don't respect art.
Hey, hey, I think we're losing them.
[roaring]
What was that?
[audience exclaiming]
[footsteps thumping]
Bloody hell. I know that sound.
[screeching]
Finally, a real life dragon.
[roars]
Oh, no, is that...
Wicksty?
Now, this is a show!
You really thought you could stop us?
These fools you brought here
will only serve our hellish end.
Everyone remain calm!
This is all just a, a part of the show.
[roars]
[groans]
Damn it, Gary. Now, I'm powerless.
Enough, filling your heads
with this silly, little morality play.
Now, all of you will bear witness
to the birth of a new era.
She wants these people scared.
They'll open up the portal right here.
[audience screaming]
This way.
Go, go!
We gotta get that staff.
We gotta get these kids out of here. Go!
Follow them!
[roars]
Everybody go back inside, back inside!
[all screaming]
[Sara grunting]
[screams]
It's all right. It's all right.
Burn her! Burn them all!
[young Zari] Stop!
Stop.
Burn the child!
Do it, now!
Kid, you gotta run.
Mithra, dance!
[grunts]
[roars]
No!
Tabitha!
[chittering]
Mithra, wait.
Rise, my demon brethren!
The door is open!
Rise!
It's gonna take
more than a musical number to stop this.
Neron!
This fight is between me and you.
So, let's settle it once and for all.
Gladly.
[choking]
I've already won.
Killing you is just a bonus.
You might take me, Neron,
but the Legends will always win.
What's happening?
Looks like the deal's off, mate.
No.
[Zari] Nate.
Gideon, take us to Heyworld.
[Gideon] I must advise
against that course of action.
The change to your future
is still in progress.
If you leave the Temporal Zone,
your current memories won't be safe.
You didn't...
[Constantine] I'm sorry, love.
It was his choice.
Finish it off, John.
Gladly.
[chanting]
[screeching]
Come on, Ray.
Raymond Palmer,
I return your soul to your body.
[gasps]
What is happening? Where am I?
I'm in Heyworld?
Everybody's here.
Nate. No. No.
- [Nora] Ray. Ray.
- No, no, no.
- Ray, I'm so sorry.
- But, but...
- You can't be here.
- Come on, hey.
Nate, you can't be dead. Come on.
Okay. Hey, come on.
Come on. You can't be...
Bring him back to life, weasel!
Sure I wish I could, Rory.
But that requires magic
beyond my means, mate.
[sobbing]
Not a bad show, if you ask me.
Dad?
Hello, Nate.
I missed you so much, Dad.
I haven't been far.
Ah...
I guess, um... I guess it sucks,
dying before you're ready? Huh?
It sure does.
Believe me,
I went through all the emotions.
I mean, uh, anger, worry, uh...
I had so many regrets, I almost missed
my ticket to the happy place.
What changed?
I had faith.
You're saying there's actually a...
In you, Nate.
And I was right to believe
that my boy and all his freaky buddies
would see this thing through.
But you know, the only thing missing
from that big show of yours?
Music.
There is a young cowboy
Who lives on the range
His horse and his cattle
are his only companions
Do I have something on my face?
Did you just sing?
James Taylor?
I don't sing.
[playing guitar]
I think someone from beyond
is trying to help us out.
You gotta be kidding me.
He works in the saddle
And sleeps in the canyons
Waiting for summer
His pastures to change
And as the moon rises
He sits by his fire
Thinking about women and glasses of beer
Look.
And closing his eyes
Keep singing.
As the doggies retire
He sings out a song
Of course.
If fear could be energy,
it only stands to reason
that love can be energy, too.
Everyone, you wanna see Nate
up and kicking?
He needs to hear your voices right now!
We need everyone to hold hands.
And we mean everyone.
Are we really doing this?
It couldn't hurt.
Didn't we do this last year?
At least we're part
of the circle this time.
Deep greens and blues
Dad, you hear that?
It's for you, son.
Won't you let me go down in my dreams?
And rockabye sweet baby, James
[Constantine] Oh, come on, people.
Do you want him to stay dead?
Come on, sing!
Good night, you moonlight ladies
Rockabye sweet baby James
It's working.
Deep greens and blues
are the colors I choose
I love you, Nate.
Down in my dreams
And rockabye sweet baby James
[gasps]
[all exclaim]
Yes!
No. No, no, no.
You're not in the Temporal Zone.
We changed history,
we changed everything.
I couldn't let you die.
Dude, you just came back to life.
Something's wrong.
Uh, there's more pelvis in that hug
than usual.
It's all good Nate Dog.
Love you too, bro.
Yeah, my bad, Behrad.
It feels like...
It's like something's missing.
Ray. Oh, buddy.
I can't believe you went all the way
to Hell to stop Neron from killing me.
[scoffs] You would've
done the same thing.
I kinda just did.
Yeah, you did.
- [laughs]
- [shrieks]
All right, Time Bros.
And Time Ladies.
And Time Monsters.
And Gary?
As I was saying,
Legends, our work here is done.
Gideon, fire up the ship.
It's time to hit it.
[screaming]
I'm here to make a withdrawal.
Whoa.
These are some truly serious sinners.
Cut down too soon, all of them.
It's a real shame when someone
doesn't get to fulfill their destiny,
don't you think?
Everyone deserves a second act.
[theme music playing]