RAY: Time travel is real,
and all of history
is vulnerable to attack.
Which is why we must travel through time
to stop the spread
of these so-called Time Aberrations
and to erase their damage to history.
We are a team of outcasts and misfits,
so please don't call us heroes.
We're something else.
We're legends.
SARA: Previously, on
Legends of Tomorrow...
We're the Justice Society of America.
PROFESSOR STEIN: Dr. Mid-Nite, Stargirl.
Copy that.
Have either of you gentlemen
heard of the Spear of Destiny?
The Spear allegedly
has the power to rewrite reality.
EOBARD: I know that you're one of
the protectors of the Spear of Destiny.
And I know that you know
where the other pieces are hidden.
(GRUNTS)
Okay, okay.
The piece of the Spear's
inside your telescope.
SARA: Will you put the gun down, Jax?
He's with the Legion now.
Why are you protecting him?
I'm protecting you.
(GRUNTS)
Hello, Charles.
I see you've found a way
to cure your blindness.
The future is full of marvels,
Captain Hunter.
I'm no longer a captain, I'm afraid.
(SCOFFS)
Wow.
What do we have here?
This is a bio-morphic implant,
capable of modifying
its host's neural processes.
One day this could end
violence as we know it.
Or, by the same means, amplify it.
I thought none of us were supposed to
contact the other again.
A new threat, I'm afraid,
a cabal of sorts is after the Spear.
- I'm rounding up the fragments.
- Why?
They're safer apart
than they are together.
They'll be safe at the Vanishing Point.
Really? You said the Time Masters
couldn't be trusted.
Did I? Bollocks. So I did.
I suppose we're gonna have to do this
the hard way, then.
(GROANS)
Now, where is the fragment of the Spear
that I had you protect?
I don't know why you want it,
but you'll never find it.
Well, seeing as you've been posing as
a researcher in cybernetic implants,
my guess is that you have
hidden the fragment
inside you.
RORY: What's going on?
Lily's algorithm located
a piece of the Spear of Destiny.
When? I mean, I know just now,
but where are we headed?
GIDEON: Detroit. The year 3000 A.D.
Journey into the distant future.
How exciting.
Speak for yourself.
Come on, man, who doesn't like the future?
I like history. Yeah, I know it's filled
with terror and violence,
- but the future just...
- It's uncertain?
Yeah and it freaks me out a little.
- Then just stay on the ship.
- You think I should stay on the ship?
I don't care, it's up to you.
I am a time-travel professional.
If you need me to visit the future,
I can visit the future.
And I'm just saying
it's entirely up to you.
And I'm "just saying," shut up!
Nate, you'll stay on the ship,
the rest of us will go find the Spear.
GIDEON: Unfortunately,
the Medallion is no longer sensing
the presence of the Spear fragment.
(COMPUTER BEEPING)
- So, we came here for nothing.
- RORY: Maybe not.
Gideon, do they have booze
in the year 3000?
Better yet, Gideon, do you have the last
position of the fragment?
SARA: Somebody find a light switch
or something.
JAX: The hell does a light switch look
like in the year 3000?
Ah.
Yeah, I guess there's not many places
you can go with a light switch.
But everything else is leaps
and bounds beyond our current science.
Amaya...
- (SIGHS) Charles.
- How do you know this stiff?
This is Dr. Mid-Nite
of the Justice Society.
What's a member of the JSA
doing this far into the future?
- Rest in peace.
- That's sweet, Mick.
No, it's what he wrote on the floor.
"R-I-P."
That's not "Rest in peace."
It's the name of Dr. Mid-Nite's killer.
I just don't get it.
Please be more specific.
That could be a very long list.
Okay, even assuming
the Legion took the Spear fragment
from here,
- how did they know it was here?
- Without the Medallion, you mean.
Rip must have told them.
Somehow, he remembers where the pieces
of the Spear are.
Well, then it's a good thing
you let him escape.
Do you want to say something to me?
Jax told me about how
he was going to kill Rip in 1776.
- And about how you stopped him.
- Because we're not killers, Amaya.
Except for yourself and Mr. Rory and...
I'll stop helping now.
I'm not condoning murder.
But the JSA would have captured Rip
without regard for sentiment.
You think I let Rip go
because of sentiment?
- Yes.
- All right, let's just all take a breath...
I'm sorry that your friend got killed.
And it may be "sentimental,"
but my team comes before tactics.
And as a result,
you put the whole of reality at risk.
Maybe this is why your team
loses so often.
- Pardon the interruption.
- Excellent timing, Gideon.
Your daughter Lily's algorithm
has identified
a location for another piece of the Spear.
Well, when it rains, it pours.
Where is it, Gideon?
A small island known as Britannia
in the year 507 A.D.
(SIGHS) Medieval England.
See, this is what I'm talking about.
A nice, well-documented piece of history.
Knights in shining armor,
damsels in distress,
and best of all... Jousts! Ha!
Well, jousting didn't appear in England
until 1300 A.D.
- Don't take this away from me.
- Raymond.
(SIGHS) Just forget history for once,
all right, we're in the age of legend.
Well, remember what Santayana once said,
"Those who cannot remember history
are condemned to repeat it."
Was he a knight?
I don't remember his name.
And I was pretty obsessed
with Arthurian lore as a kid.
Mmm, well, if you were, you would know
there were no jousts.
Oh. Well, agree to disagree.
Fair.
(RORY GRUNTS)
You're skipping
Medieval Times as well, Professor?
Yes, I was just catching up
on some research.
- What'd you do?
- Excuse me?
Don't say, "Excuse me."
Makes you sound guilty.
I haven't the foggiest idea
what you're talking...
(SNIFFS)
- What are you doing?
- Thieves. They have a certain smell.
I thought that was just because
you didn't bathe.
- What did you steal?
- How dare you even suggest...
What did you steal?
Dr. Mid-Nite wouldn't be needing it,
so I figured I'd...
(STAMMERING) I couldn't resist.
Though, I prefer the term "borrowed."
(CHUCKLES)
Impressive, there's hope for you yet.
(LAUGHS)
DR. HEYWOOD: Look, all I'm saying is,
the stories you grew up on
are just that, stories.
All right?
The medieval world was a time of turmoil.
It was the collapse of Rome, which led
to the collapse of civilization itself.
And don't even get me started
on health and sanitation.
Yeah, please don't.
Cholera, diphtheria, typhoid fever...
And I'm not even touching skin diseases.
Speaking of which, why did you choose
to dress like a leper?
I didn't. This is historically accurate.
You all look like you're going
to a Renaissance fair.
- What is it?
- We're being followed.
And by the way, even if I was a leper,
it would be way less obvious than
a bunch of knights in shining armor.
(RUSTLING)
Wait! I mean, ho! I mean hark.
Good knight, we intend you no harm.
We are but mere travelers in this land.
Your dialect is way off.
I, Raymond of the Palms,
and my band of merry men and women...
(GROANS)
humbly request safe passage to Camelot
and an audience with King Arthur.
- King Arthur?
- Yes, you can see his crest on the shield.
I am Guinevere.
We shall escort you to Camelot,
but your leper must
remain outside the castle walls.
I'm not a leper!
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
(DOOR CLOSES)
- Still think this is just a story?
- This place shouldn't exist.
There's no need of that here.
All are equal in the court of Camelot.
(WHISPERING) That's why I love this guy.
Our paths crossed in the wood while
tracking the Black Knight, Your Grace.
How then are we to know that they are not
in league with that vile rogue?
- Ray...
- Your Grace,
I swear, we are not your enemies.
We are warriors on a quest,
a race against evil.
A great evil haunts my land,
these many days,
kidnapping my noble Knights of
the Round Table, therefore,
it shall fall on my wisest advisor
to measure the truth of your words.
- Oh, please don't say it...
- Summon Merlin!
(GASPS)
Get ready to fight our way out of here
if Merlin rules against us.
That's Stargirl.
What are you doing in Camelot?
This ship. It never ceases to amaze me.
Speaking of amazing... Merlin?
Just an identity I adopted
to fit into this era.
But what are you even doing in this era?
Let me guess, it has something to
do with the Spear of Destiny.
We found Dr. Mid-Nite in year 3000.
He's dead, Courtney.
We think he was killed because
he possessed a piece of the Spear.
What do you know about the JSA's
final mission?
Obsidian told me the JSA disappeared
after a trip to Leipzig in 1956.
The mission was to recover
the Spear of Destiny
and keep it from falling into enemy hands.
SARA: And how was it that you were all
scattered throughout time?
We were joined on our mission by someone
who called himself a Time Master.
- Rip Hunter?
- Yes.
He said the Spear
could alter reality itself,
that it was too powerful for
any man or woman to possess.
So we broke it into four separate pieces.
Mr. Hunter took one...
And took the rest of you
to three different time periods.
When I arrived in Camelot,
it was a middling kingdom.
To help me protect my piece of the Spear,
I fashioned it into
the legendary court of King Arthur
and his Knights of the Round Table.
(MEDIEVAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(PEOPLE LAUGHING AND CHATTERING)
Courtney, I respect your devotion,
but shouldn't you at least tell me
where the fragment is hidden?
Don't worry, Amaya. I promise the piece
is somewhere very safe.
Your tracking in the woods was excellent.
There's not many people who can get
the jump on me like that.
I was a warrior long before I was Queen.
Why does it sound like you preferred that?
Politics is not one of my passions.
But Arthur is a true friend and ally,
and I believe in his vision
for a more just and peaceful kingdom.
From what I see,
Camelot lives up to its reputation.
Where is the good King?
On the hunt.
No doubt chasing a boar through a brush
as we speak.
(GRUNTING)
(PANTING)
(GROANS)
Do your worst, knave.
I'd rather die than surrender!
Then you are an idiot.
- You're not going to run me through?
- No...
We have something else in mind
for you, Your Majesty.
Mmm.
- RAY: Ah!
- (JAX COUGHS)
I can't believe Marty and Mick
are missing this.
Like, right?
I mean, when's the next time
we're gonna get to feast in Camelot.
- Mmm.
- Hey, guys, check it out.
- Sir Galahad.
- How do you know that?
Because he's sitting
in the Siege Perilous.
The what?
Come on. Some kind of historian you are.
The Siege Perilous is a special seat
reserved for only the purest of knights.
I don't know how many times
I have to tell you,
there's a difference
between legend and history.
I'm gonna go introduce myself.
Sir Galahad.
(GRUNTS)
Urn, is this seat taken?
- It is now, my friend.
- (LAUGHS)
Apologies, you must get this all the time,
but I must tell you, I'm a really big fan.
A fan?
So you make wind?
No, no, no. Well...
I mean, maybe after all this food...
(LAUGHS)
(CLEARS THROAT)
No, what I mean is
I'm a big admirer of yours.
- You've heard tell of my exploits?
- Yes, yes.
Since I was a wee lad.
It's hard to explain.
I am but a servant.
It is my honor to serve
the true inspiration of Camelot's glory,
King Arthur.
For was it not he who said that
might must serve right,
lest it bloom
into the cruel flower of tyranny?
Yet another reason I love him.
- (TRUMPETS PLAYING)
- (DOOR OPENS)
They sound the return of the King!
Arthur's captured the Black Knight.
(BLACK KNIGHT GROANS)
Arthur, I was beginning to...
(EXCLAIMS)
Oh, sorry about the ruse, but I figured
it was the only way to get inside.
Oh! Hey, guys.
I see you've met my friend Arthur here.
Give us a smile, Arthur.
(DEVICE BEEPING)
Arthur...
The King has left the building.
You don't get the reference?
Oh, pity.
Basically, your King now does
anything I want him to do.
So if you don't want him to spill your
blood all over this floor,
I suggest that you hand over
your fragment of the Spear.
My patience is running short.
The fragment. Where is it?
As long as I live,
you will never have it.
Ah, that might turn out to be shorter
than you think.
(SARA GRUNTS)
(GASPING)
(DEVICE BEEPING)
Stand fast or your King dies!
All I have to do is think it
and he slits his own throat.
DARHK: Ultimatum time.
Deliver the fragment to me by dawn
or I'll come back with an army
just as obedient as Arthur here.
The choice is yours...
Camelot or the Spear.
(BELLS TOLLING)
Galahad, may you rest in peace.
Your sorrow and pain are banished.
May the everlasting light of Camelot
shine upon you.
How do you know this Black Knight?
(SIGHS) His name is Damien Darhk.
He works with the speedster who
turned Rip Hunter against the JSA.
Rip's not the only one
under their control now.
That thing's dark magic
has turned my King, my own husband
- into my enemy.
- It's not his fault.
And yet I watched him strike down
Sir Galahad with my own eyes.
You have to believe that your husband can
be saved or else he will be truly lost.
Unless we stop the Black Knight's
army, we may never find out.
My Queen, you must be strong.
With King Arthur missing,
the Knights of the Round Table
will look to you to lead them.
The mantle of King is Arthur's, not mine.
Guinevere. Wait.
Look, sometimes the mantle
just falls into your lap.
Trust me.
I know that it's hard. You're clever.
You're brave
and you are a natural born commander.
I know you can do this.
(SIGHS)
You saw what they did to Arthur.
Imagine what they could do with
an army of brainwashed knights.
- What are you suggesting?
- The fragment of the Spear...
We need to get it out of the castle.
How can your team protect the Spear?
You couldn't even protect Dr. Mid-Nite.
That's not fair.
I'm not going anywhere,
and neither is the fragment.
Fascinating.
It seems to contain some sort of
sophisticated receiver...
Clearly it's the same technology I...
I found in Dr. Mid-Nite's lab.
- Grey? You didn't...
- RORY: You bet he did.
Nicked it off the dead guy.
Even I was impressed.
- I was simply curious.
- (CHUCKLES)
And it's a good thing I did.
These components appear to be a set,
perhaps functioning together as
transmitter and receiver.
Or commander and soldier.
Exactly.
The commander wears the transmitter,
sending orders via
an electro-telepathic signal
to this receiver worn by the soldier.
Anything with a signal could get hacked.
That's the hope, yes.
So all we need to do is somehow boost the
brain power of whoever's wearing this...
Or find someone with
a preternaturally powerful brain.
You mean, you?
Fine. If you insist.
Now, all we need
is a test subject.
Someone whose mind is pliable.
(GROANS)
What?
DARHK: Hey, Sir Drools-A-Lot...
Prepare the rest of your tin men
to get ready to march.
Perhaps I didn't make myself clear.
- Prepare your men, King Arthur.
- As you wish, my liege.
ARTHUR: Prepare to march!
I knew these things would come in handy.
Now, Mr. Rory, I want you to get up
out of that chair.
No, I command you to get up
out of that chair!
Do you feel anything at all?
A foreign impulse?
A slight twinge perhaps.
Wait.
I'm picking up on something.
Oh, my God, it's working.
- I'm hungry.
- This is a disaster.
(RORY SIGHS)
- (DEVICE CHIMES)
- Wait.
It seems our adversaries are
sending a signal of their own.
What does that mean?
Oh, dear God!
It means the Legion is coming for Camelot.
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
Valiant knights of Camelot.
I know the fear you feel.
We stand now on the precipice of doom.
Our King has been taken from us.
Evil draws close,
and hope, it seems, is lost.
But we must rise
and face this challenge,
as Arthur would have wanted.
We must remember who we are,
we brothers and sisters,
we fighters and friends.
We are not mere knights,
we are Camelot!
ALL: (CHANTING) We are Camelot!
We are Camelot!
MAN: The dark army approaches!
- It has reached the great wood!
- It seems your wizard is too late.
Is she talking about Professor Stein?
No matter. We shall settle this
at the point of our swords.
Camelot calls to you in its hour of need.
Will you answer?
Who will follow me
onto the field of battle?
(ALL YELLING)
Dude, what are they doing?
These guys don't stand a chance out there.
Is this really worth the risk
for some dream?
Yes.
Because a long time ago, that dream
meant the world to a little boy.
And he still remembers.
(SIGHS) This isn't gonna end well.
(DEVICE BEEPING)
What are you doing?
(SIGHS)
If Stargirl won't give us the fragment
for safe-keeping...
- You're stealing it?
- She's not thinking straight.
(DEVICE BEEPING)
I should have known.
You sure this is the way you wanna do it?
Stargirl was your teammate,
not to mention your friend.
The Legion of Doom
are closing in on us as we speak.
There's no time for sentiment.
Do you really want to chance Damien Darhk
having the power to rewrite reality?
I guess not.
It's set in stone.
Not for long.
(GORILLA ROARS)
(BIRD SCREECHES)
(BEAR ROARS)
(GRUNTING)
Damn, that was badass.
(GRUNTS)
Let's get out of here.
Put it down.
We should attack now.
(ALL YELLING)
(DEVICES BEEPING)
Let me tell you how an ultimatum works.
The so-called "Legends" have until dawn
to deliver the Spear.
(SCOFFS) You don't actually believe
that they'll hand it over, do you?
Perhaps not, but meeting on a battlefield
is infinitely more wise
than laying siege to the castle.
Right.
I just thought you would want
my expertise. After all, I have
already retrieved two fragments
of the Spear, but...
A word to the wise.
Speak to me with respect.
That little thing on your head
doesn't control me.
I don't want to fight with you, Amaya.
But I will if I have to.
Then get ready, because
I'm not leaving without the fragment.
Hey, we have enough enemies
as it is without fighting each other.
You left us, Amaya.
I was there to protect the Spear.
And I will continue to protect it
until I take my last breath.
Because you know that
doing the right thing is more important
than doing what feels right.
You are still a member
of the Justice Society.
No. I'm not. My heart belongs in Camelot.
Your heart?
You of all people should understand.
It wasn't duty that led you
to join the Legends.
(SIGHS)
You've fallen in love with Arthur.
Your make-believe kingdom
is a real soap opera.
How can you expect me to turn away
from the truest thing
I've ever known?
All I know
is that the Legion of Doom will not stop
until they get this.
And once they do,
the world as we know it is over.
Which is why you're taking it, Amaya.
I can't go.
So you have to fulfill my oath.
Protect the Spear.
(HORN BLOWING)
All right, you heard the wizard.
Let's boogie.
(SOLDIERS CHATTERING)
(CHUCKLES)
Ray, this is wrong.
And please tell me
that's not Galahad's sword.
(SIGHS)
I know, it's not "historically accurate,"
but I couldn't resist.
- (CHUCKLES)
- (DEVICE WINDING)
It's like a saber made of light!
Yeah.
Just don't call it a lightsaber.
Major trademark issues, right?
Yeah. Trademark!
Have you lost your complete mind?
No, I focused the ionic energy flow
into Galahad's sword.
That's great, Ray,
but Sara says it's time to go, so...
- What? But the battle hasn't even begun.
- Precisely why we're leaving now.
Listen. Amaya found the fragment, so
there's no need for this medieval warfare.
That's great news, right? Let's go.
In case you weren't listening,
this is the part where we run.
I can't.
Sure you can.
Left foot, right foot, repeat. Let's go.
No, Nate, look around you.
All of these men are willing to die
on the battlefield,
not for some Spear but for an idea.
I get it now, Camelot isn't about history,
it's not even about some dusty old books
that got a lonely kid through childhood.
It's about one noble idea,
that we can all stand up for what's right,
no matter what.
I can't walk away from that.
I believe you, Ray.
I do. And Camelot's great,
but if you don't leave right now,
you're gonna die here.
Would it kill you to be
just a little bit more supportive?
You don't get it, man, I checked
the manuscript, I saw your funeral.
Well...
It sounds to me like
the stuff legends are made of.
All right, Gideon.
Let's get ready for takeoff.
GIDEON: Yes, Captain.
This doesn't feel right.
We don't just leave people in trouble.
They're knights.
And they're fighting so we can get away.
- With the piece of the Spear.
- And without Rip.
Take comfort we live
to fight another day.
The Legion already has two pieces
of the Spear. I don't like it,
but we cannot risk them getting a Yahtzee.
What the hell is a Yahtzee?
GIDEON: Systems online, Captain Lance.
We are ready to time jump.
Where's Raymond?
With this sword, I dub thee.
Sir Raymond of the Palms,
defender of Camelot.
Rise, good knight!
I tried talking to him, but he's hell-bent
on getting himself killed.
Doesn't he know we have
the piece of the Spear?
All he seems to care about is being
remembered in some BS bedtime story.
- We can't leave him behind.
- We're not leaving him. He chose to stay.
Amaya, I know you're following
JSA protocol at whatever cost,
but this is seriously screwed up.
We can't risk losing a piece of the Spear,
especially when the Legion is backed
by evil Knights of the Round Table.
I thought you were going to
un-evilfy them.
We were.
If we just had a little more time.
- We still can.
- And what happens if you can't?
Well, as much as Haircut's a pain in
my ass, I'm not gonna let him fight alone.
Sit down. That's an order.
- What's an order?
- Don't test me, Mick.
Don't threaten me, Blondie.
I can't believe,
I'm actually agreeing with Mr. Rory...
- I said, sit down!
- AMAYA: Stop!
I've already lost one team.
I'll be damned if my decision rips
the Legends apart, too.
- What are you saying?
- Listen to your gut, Captain.
Don't abandon Ray.
It may be sentimental, but
the team should come before tactics.
(SIGHS)
All right, let's do this.
Guinevere's knights are not gonna be able
to last long against Damien Darhk's army
unless you three...
Take out Mid-Nite's mind-control tech.
We're on it.
We are?
Amaya, Nate,
you ready to go get medieval out there?
Wait! You got it reversed. I need the
transmitting device not the receiver.
I got an idea.
What if it's not about brain power
but about intensity, like his?
- We don't have time for this.
- Put the dog collar on, Professor.
I have more patents than Mr. Rory
has felonies and that's saying something.
To think that his mind is
more powerful than mine...
Shut up!
(DEVICE BEEPS)
Wait, did you shut up because you wanted
to, or because he told you to?
- Hmm.
- Make him answer.
Answer the man, Professor.
(EXHALES)
- Astonishing!
- (CHUCKLING) It worked.
I knew it. Okay.
Now all we gotta do
is amplify the signal.
- What do you want me to do?
- Just rest your brain, Mr. Rory.
We'll let you know when it's time
to take control of the evil army.
- Ah, finally, I get to fulfill my destiny.
- God help us.
(SIGHS)
(ALL YELLING)
(YELLS)
(HORSE WHINNIES)
(GRUNTS)
So... You came to fight for an imaginary
kingdom after all.
I came to fight for a friend.
(GRUNTING)
A really dumb friend.
(HORSE WHINNIES)
(GRUNTS)
Okay, I need you to unleash the darkness
on those brainwashed knights.
Let them inside your head.
Fill their minds with every brutish
impulse, every traumatic memory.
That just might be enough
to overload the system.
- (GRUNTS)
- Spare nothing!
Poor babies.
(DEVICE BEEPING)
(GROANING)
(DEVICES BEEPING)
Be gone, devilish sorcerer!
(BOTH YELLING)
(GRUNTS)
(PANTING)
Damien...
Sorry, I don't do rescues.
Yah!
Damn it, Ray.
(GROANING)
(CHUCKLES)
You're here to finish me off, Captain?
- (WAVERIDER APPROACHING)
- (EXHALES)
What are you doing?
Saving your life.
Give it up, Raymond.
You're a glorified nerd, not a knight.
It's Sir Raymond of the Palms.
And on behalf of my 12-year-old self,
allow me to retort.
(GRUNTS)
(LAUGHS)
(STRAINING)
(GROANING)
Yield, Damien.
(PANTING) Okay, okay, I submit.
(GRUNTS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Ray!
Ray?
Oh, come on, buddy, open your eyes,
you stupid bastard!
Ray! Come on.
- Ray!
- (GROANING) Stop yelling at me.
Ray, you brilliant bastard.
It's not Ray anymore.
- It's Sir Raymond of the Palms.
- Yeah.
I'm never gonna call you that, buddy.
(SIGHS)
Thank you, Amaya.
Tales of your deeds will honor these halls
for longer than you can imagine.
The honor is mine, Your Grace.
Hey, so you're staying?
- Like you, I've found a new home.
- "Like me"?
With the Legends. The team suits you.
Take care of yourself, Courtney.
You, too, Amaya.
- What was that all about?
- Just a little friendly advice.
Yeah?
We should get going. Where's Ray?
Um, he said something about paying his
respects to the Queen before we left.
Hmm.
Funny, Sara said the exact same thing.
I just wanted to say goodbye.
I enjoyed meeting you.
And I you, Sara Lance.
- A lot.
- (CHUCKLES)
Sara Lancelot...
I should go.
Do you really have to leave?
It is I, Raymond of the Palms, my lady,
come to bid my fair lady adieu.
Oh.
Well, (CLEARS THROAT)
a thousand pardons, Your Majesty.
- Sara.
- It's okay, Ray. Come in.
And a thousand thanks
for your service to the realm.
If ever your travels bring you back,
there will always be a seat at the
Round Table for Sir Raymond of the Palms.
Thank you, my lady.
You know, every good legend
ends with a kiss.
Goodbye, Guinevere.
Surely, you must admit that it's not
a superior intelligence, but rather
the murky depths of your mind
that proved vital.
(BURPS) Just admit it,
my brain saved the day.
I will admit nothing of the sort!
All right, I'll admit it,
walking around a legend felt just as real
as walking around any part of history.
You know, maybe legend and history
are not so different after all.
Maybe they're just
stories to remind us where we
come from and who we can become.
- Hmm.
- So what do you say?
You wanna find out how you'll be
remembered in everyone's bedtime story?
Nah.
I think I'd rather make up
my future as I go.
Nice.
I've got something I want to say to you.
Well, I'm a captive audience, aren't I?
I was gonna kill you
for what you did to Sara.
But she stopped me,
and I'm glad.
But make no mistake,
you are not captain
and this is not your ship.
Not anymore. So if you even think
about hurting anyone on my team,
I will not hesitate to end you.
Feel good to get that
off your chest, did it?
- Gideon?
- I'm here, Captain.
You always are.
(SNICKERS)