Time travel is real
and all of history
is vulnerable to attack which is why
we must travel through time
to stop the spread
of these so-called time aberrations
and to erase their damage to history.
We are a team
of outcasts and misfits,
so please don't call us heroes.
We're something else, we're legends.
Previously,
onLegends Of Tomorrow...
I'd forgotten how handsome I was.
Hi, I'm Marty.
Have a wonderful life, Martin.
This belonged to the greatest
outsider I ever knew.
I'm looking for a partner.
Hello, Rex.
With his last words, he told me
his killer was a time traveler.
Damien Darhk murdered my sister.
If I take him out here...
You save her. We gotta let him go.
So it's all here, then?
Every sweet-smelling speck of it.
As for my compensation?
Strange form of payment.
Why this and not cash?
Everyone has a hobby.
Some men collect stamps.
I collect relics.
This "thing" is called a fasces,
a ceremonial axe carried
by the bodyguard of Emperor Nero
from which a term "fascism" derived.
No?
A form of rule, which, in my opinion,
is getting a bit of a bad rap lately.
DEA! Get your hands in the air, now!
You know, I had this under control.
My way's faster.
Speed isn't everything, Mr. Thawne.
You should've learned
that lesson by now.
What's it been, 45 years
since you hired me to nuke New York?
Well, 45 years for you,
maybe, but for me?
Good seeing you again, old friend.
Old? That's fair. Friend?
Now that's something
that has to be earned.
Lovely piece. What is this?
First century AD,
if I'm not mistaken?
What is it that you want?
A partner.
Pass, I prefer to work alone.
Oh, yeah, gathering
your hive of followers,
building your empire,
designing your ark.
Yeah, I know what you're planning.
And how it works out.
You want to reshape the world?
Try reshaping history.
Try rewriting destiny...
Try putting our partnership
into concrete terms,
as in, what's in it for me?
Well, perhaps content collecting
symbols of power, but...
I can give you actual power.
We have the tools
to make a difference.
We can make history better.
Even if we act
with the best of intentions,
these changes can ripple
throughout time,
a temporal domino effect
with disastrous consequences.
So we start small.
Make changes we can control.
What you're talking
about can't be done.
It's, it's like playing God,
and it goes against everything
we're trying to do.
I thought we were
trying to help people.
We're helping by fixing aberrations,
not creating them.
You're not thinking
fourth dimensionally.
Did you really
just use Doc Brown on me?
Who the hell is that?
Sara, come on, you can't
be Switzerland on this one.
In my heart, I agree with you...
but that's not what Rip
entrusted us to do.
Our job is to protect history.
You mean clean it up
after somebody else
makes a mess of it.
Time janitors...
That's all we are.
Easy, point and shoot.
You're up.
All right, point and shoot.
You killed my beers.
Come on, the trigger's
really sensitive,
and these goggles make
everything look blue.
You know, it'd be really easy
for me to improve
this whole setup by just
iterating the power source.
There's nothing wrong with the gun.
You've just gotta be cool.
Like Snart.
Yeah, I can be cool.
What are you doing?
Trying to be cool.
Maybe this was a bad idea.
You know, this may shock you,
but I was considered extremely cool
when I left my cushy six-figure
Silicon Valley job
and started my own tech company.
Ladies were lining up.
Listen, Haircut, if you want to fit
into Snart's shoes,
you gotta find the pain,
the darkness, the anger.
You got it in you?
Call me Haircut again
and I'll ice you.
Not bad.
Hey, what are you doing?
A little side project
I've been working on
with Ray and the professor.
It said that temporal aberrations
cause these things called timequakes.
So I started thinking,
if there was a way
of locating their epicenters,
maybe we'll be able to fix
the aberrations before they happen.
Like a time seismograph.
That's an awesome name,
and I'm totally gonna steal that.
If the JSA could get even a glimpse
of all this, they would...
They'd what?
Never mind.
Hey, wait.
We've barely had half a conversation
since you came on board,
and you were friends
with my grandfather.
Talk to me.
What was he like as a person?
Your grandfather was a great man.
That's it? He's a great man?
Is it because your missions
were classified, or is it
because you really didn't
know him well as a person?
It's because the JSA didn't encourage
its members to fraternize.
Something you and your team
should consider.
It worked?
Oh, it worked all right.
Where's it coming from?
Washington D.C., December 7, 1987.
1600 Pennsylvania Avenue.
- So?
- Dude, that's the White House.
- So what?
- December 7th was the day
before Reagan and Gorbachev
signed the INF Treaty,
reducing both countries'
nuclear arsenals
and paving the way for the end
of the Cold War.
- How do you know all that?
- Because I was in the capital
for that very summit.
The Reagan Administration
would call upon the top
nuclear physicists
to act as technical advisors.
You think someone might have
traveled back in time
to stop the treaty from being signed?
That, or worse.
Think about it, Reagan
and Gorbachev under the same roof
at one of the most
volatile moments in history?
The JSA has a training
academy in D.C.
I could reach out
to the current membership,
see if they have any Intel
or resources we could use.
Good idea,
but you shouldn't go alone.
1987 is a long way from 1942,
and it's dangerous to know
too much about the future.
- I can handle myself.
- I'll go with her.
Great, you two reach out
to the JSA while the rest of us
break into the most secure
residence in the country.
And how exactly do we do that?
Welcome to the White House.
This is Cross Hall,
a magnificent space
that connects the State Dining Room
with the East Room.
All right, fan out, stay on the coms,
and report if anything
seems out of place.
Women actually wore
these things in the '80s?
Shoulder pads?
Yeah, they were supposed
to make women more imposing,
more, I don't know...
- Manly?
- Yeah.
I'd hoped that by this decade,
women wouldn't need to use
clothing to compensate
for their status.
Surely by now men and women
are considered equals.
Never lose that optimism.
This is it.
This is the JSA Academy?
Inside a crummy warehouse?
The JSA Academy is hidden
inside a crummy warehouse.
Prepare to see the most elite
training facility in all of history.
Maybe "elite" means something
different in 1987.
When I was recruited,
this is where I was brought to train.
What happened to the JSA?
No clue...
but a lot can change in 45 years.
I thought you said
you were a historian.
How can you not know?
Hey, every memo,
every executive action
relating to the JSA is top secret.
I only pieced together
their World War II activities
from my father's bedtime stories,
witness testimonies,
and government leaks.
I never should have left 1942.
Look, Amaya, whatever
happened to them, that's,
that's not your fault.
You don't know that.
Like you said, you don't know
what happened to them.
1987, the halcyon days
of Whitney Houston
and "Star Trek: The Next Generation."
I can remember this year
as if it were yesterday.
Well, it looks like there's
something you forgot about.
Mr. Stein, so nice to meet you.
That's me.
Go, go.
I thought you said
you were stuck in meetings
- on the Hill all day.
- I was.
I never stepped foot
inside the White House.
The aberration must've caused
infinitesimal ripples
that affected the movements
of my younger self.
The temporal domino effect,
this is why we should
never interfere with history.
Well, we'll agree to disagree.
But one thing's for sure,
we cannot let him see you.
Indeed, the last time
he and I interacted
nearly erased our marriage
from existence.
Those are jelly beans.
I can see that.
President Reagan's jelly beans.
So what? Eat them.
What? I'm pretty sure
that's against the rules.
We don't follow rules, remember?
Oh, right.
Reagan wasn't even one
of my top three favorite presidents.
- Want some?
- Yeah.
Oh, it'll take some massaging,
but I believe we can get the Soviets
to agree to eliminating all nuclear
ground-launched, ballistic,
and cruise missiles.
I'll even make them believe
it was their idea.
I don't know what we'd do
without you, Mr. Darhk.
Oh, you'd manage,
but winning is always better.
I think we found our aberration.
Our next stop is the...
Damien Darhk is here.
Sara, don't do anything rash.
Sara? Sara, are you lis...
Here's another diplomatic cable
from 1956
from the British ambassador
warning the JSA about
Soviet spies in their midst.
I thought fighting Hitler
would unite the U.S.
and the Soviet Union.
Oh, we have so much Cold War
history to catch you up on.
Okay, what's this?
Todd?
Why? Why did you abandon us?
Who is that?
It's Obsidian.
From the JSA?
Soviets to agree to...
Ma'am, I'm gonna need you
to drop the weapon.
Drop the knife and place
your hands behind your head.
We've got a situation
in the East Wing.
I know you want vengeance for Laura,
but it's not that simple.
Get out of the way.
Don't move!
- Stay where you are!
- Damn it.
- We gonna fight or leave?
- Fight.
All right, get out of here.
- I got this.
- No, you go. I got this.
I said go!
What did I say
about crossing streams?
You said we don't follow the rules.
That's the one rule,
one rule we follow!
Go!
We interrupt this broadcast
with breaking news:
Chaos in the capital.
Just a day before
President Reagan is set
to welcome General Secretary
Gorbachev to the White House
to sign the INF Treaty,
a White House tour ends in violence
and what witnesses describe
as "a rocket man."
Was this an act of terrorism...
Please, turn it off, Gideon.
I can't bear it.
So your thirst
for vengeance nearly landed
the entire team in prison.
I guess it's only okay
to change history
if it's with your personal vendetta.
Wasn't all Blondie's fault.
Haircut screwed up as well.
If you would just let me tinker
with the cold gun,
I told you I could figure out
the whole crossing
the streams problem.
There's nothing wrong
with the cold gun.
It's you, you goof.
The bigger question is:
Why did Damien Darhk
become an advisor
to Reagan's White House
on the eve of a nuclear treaty
with the USSR?
If his involvement
with the Nazis in 1942
is any indication, he's working
with our time traveling nemesis.
It's the same person
who killed Hourman.
Amaya needs to hear about this.
So she can also lose focus,
risking everything in a selfish
pursuit of revenge?
Do you have something
you'd like to say to me, Martin?
Yes, that killing
Damien Darhk almost 30 years
before his actual death will have
countless unforeseeable effects
on the history that we are charged
with protecting.
Well, what about protecting
my sister?
She brought me back from the dead.
She risked everything for me.
How could I not do the same for her?
Because you answer
to a higher calling, Sara.
I'm sorry, but we cannot stray
from our guiding principle.
Well, I'm sorry, too.
It sounds like you've never
really cared about anyone.
Do you think I killed him?
I hope I didn't kill him.
He's gotta be in his
late '70s at least.
Maybe he couldn't take the hit.
Oh, my God, I just killed a member
of the Justice Society.
Why are you whispering?
In case he's not dead,
he could probably use the nap.
I'm not an invalid...
Just old.
And you, you haven't aged a day.
It's one of the few benefits
of time travel.
So you left us to join
the loveable losers.
I was trying to find Rex's killer.
And you never thought to tell me?
I found Rex dying.
His last words were "time traveler."
I didn't think. I just acted.
What happened to them, Todd?
After the war, our friendship
with the Soviet Union ended,
and we continued fighting
as what was known
as the "Iron Curtain" descended
over central and eastern Europe.
Does "we" include my grandfather?
Right to the end.
In 1956, President Eisenhower
sent a team on a mission to Leipzig.
They never made it back.
Why didn't you go?
'56 was a charged time.
They were concerned
that I couldn't be trusted.
- Why not?
- Leave it be, Nathaniel.
Nate, Amaya,
report back to the Waverider.
I promise you, Todd, I will fix this.
What's done is done, Amaya.
Not when you have a time machine.
I'm sorry for leaving, Todd.
I truly am.
Rex's killer is here? In 1987?
Potentially, if Damien Darhk
is still working with him.
No way, Damien Darhk
joined the Reagan Administration
as an advisor
at the Reykjavík Summit?
And after the collapse of the summit,
Darhk was credited with reviving
the disarmament talks?
Darhk prefers stockpiling nukes,
not getting rid of them.
The nuclear treaty must be a cover.
- For what purpose?
- That's what we need to find out.
Gideon, where is Damien Darhk now?
I'm accessing the calendar
on his secretary's
IBM personal computer.
Mr. Darhk has a meeting
in Georgetown Park at 8.00pm.
Late night meeting in the park,
that's not suspicious.
Ray, take Mick. Find out
who Darhk is meeting with and why.
Wait, just us?
Look, it's not a good idea
for me to be anywhere
near Damien Darhk right now.
I... I agree.
Okay, we're a go on audio.
Cutting it close, haircut.
That's Snart's jacket.
I, thought it would help me
get into character.
I'm Colonel Cold.
The hell you are.
You're not gonna give
yourself a promotion.
Fine.
What are you doing?
Well, we're on a stake-out.
Brought snacks.
Apple slice?
Guess you're still upset
about the White House.
Look, I can be more careful.
I can be more meticulous,
more like Snart.
I don't want you to be like Snart.
What?
You gave me his gun, you told me
I had to try to fill his shoes.
I was wrong.
You keep reminding me
of my, my dead friend.
It's bringing up...
- Feelings?
- Yes.
So just stop and be you.
Well, that's a little difficult,
considering I lost my suit,
my company, my powers.
Is this what an existential
crisis feels like?
Shut up. Just shut up.
Oh, I, I just died
In your arms tonight
I hate the '80s!
Is there any sign of
who Darhk's meeting with?
Not yet!
Clandestine meeting in a D.C. park.
It feels like the beginning
of a John le Carré spy novel.
I'm more of an Ian Fleming guy.
More explosions, less clothing.
What if Darhk is meeting
with Rex's killer?
Then we don't let either
of them leave.
We've got movement.
A man just entered the park.
Ray, we need audio.
Yep, way ahead of you, Cap.
Thankfully, there was
a Tech Village nearby.
You wouldn't believe
what you can hack together
with a few household items.
Dobriy Vecher, Mr. Darhk.
Sounds like he's meeting
with a member
of the Soviet delegation,
not Rex's killer.
The package is procured.
Excellent news, Boris.
That is your name, isn't it?
Boris? Or is it Igor?
I find it's always one
or the other with you KGB agents.
Anyhoo, once the treaty is signed,
during the State Dinner,
you'll deliver the package.
And you will uphold
your half of the bargain?
As agreed.
But first, a toast.
To peace between our two nations.
Darhk was never interested
in the nuclear treaty.
He's working a side deal
with the KGB.
Mayday!
My... My name is Martin Stein.
You must have heard of me.
You may have heard of me.
Marty, younger
you just entered the park.
What? But that... that's impossible.
Today is December 7th,
Clarissa's birthday.
I distinctly remember
we had a dinner reservation
for this evening which
took me months to procure.
Well, you must have blown her off.
This ought to be good.
Should we stop him?
Stop what? What am I doing?
Mr. Darhk allow me
to introduce myself.
My name is Martin Stein.
You may have heard of me.
I'm on the negotiating team
and was recently nominated
for my sixth Carlin Award in physics.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
- Did you follow me here?
- I did.
You see, I'm... I'm working on
a transmutation project that
is vital to national security.
I was hoping you might pass
the proposal on to the President.
Excuse me, I can't help
but notice you're wearing
a Komandirskie watch,
typically supplied to
the Soviet Ministry of Defense.
Meeting with a Soviet outside
of the official negotiation schedule?
That is highly irregular.
Ray, Mick, get in there, now.
Okay.
Clearly, there's been some
kind of misunderstanding.
I'll just leave
and pretend these last
five minutes didn't happen.
Unfortunately, my imagination
isn't quite that vivid.
- Gray!
- Martin!
Ray, what happened?
Darhk just stabbed
Marty's younger self.
Where's Darhk?
We lost him.
It's gonna be okay.
I'm gonna get you back.
Where is he?
He's on his way now.
Don't worry, you're gonna be fine.
You again?
I mean, me again.
Guess you figured it out.
How did this happen?
I'm too young to die.
Too brilliant to die.
Will one of you please shut me up?
Gladly.
Gideon?
I'm cauterizing
the younger Martin's wound.
I'm afraid it will leave both
patients with a rather nasty scar.
You should've let me punch him.
This is about time travel, isn't it?
That's why Special Advisor Darhk
stabbed me.
He wouldn't have stabbed you
if you had been having dinner
with Clarissa at L'Auberge
as previously planned.
Good God, Clarissa.
She's waiting for me at the hotel.
How could you have left her
alone on her birthday?
She ordered room service.
You are a careless,
self-centered idiot.
Gray, Gray,
look, I'll go to the hotel,
and I'll tell Clarissa
that her husband's working late.
Okay? Just relax.
Oh, oh, Martin, what on Earth
were you thinking?
Hubba-hubba, who's that?
Professor Stein's wife.
Jax is at her hotel
explaining why she has to
spend her birthday alone.
Wait a minute, if he used everyone's
favorite talking computer
to find her...
Gideon, do you have
the location on Damien Darhk?
Unfortunately, I have no Intel
on his current whereabouts.
But we know where he's gonna be.
His little side deal
with the Soviets is going down
at the State Dinner tomorrow night.
Which is probably
the most heavily guarded
dinner in history.
I think we know someone
who may be able to help.
Is that so?
One of Amaya's old JSA buddies,
and, by old, I mean old.
He may still have
some government contacts
we can exploit.
Absolutely not.
Whatever Darhk is planning
to exchange with the Soviets,
it can't be good.
Well, I'll contact the FBI.
You don't have to worry about it.
Except we do.
Darhk's working with a time traveler.
That's way
out of the Bureau's league.
I believe
this time traveler killed Rex.
All the more reason to stay
clear of that State Dinner.
You can't remain professional.
Are you kidding me?
She's nothing but professional.
She's all about being professional.
The only reason I could ever see
her not being...
Oh, my God, you
and Rex Tyler were together.
- No.
- They were together, weren't they?
This makes total sense.
We weren't together.
Like I said before,
fraternization among
teammates is unprofessional.
Rex and I were going to leave
the JSA after the war,
try and start a new life
with each other.
And then he was cut down.
That's why I left the team,
and that's why I wouldn't
talk to you about them.
It's too hard.
And this is why
I'm reluctant to help you.
Because your emotions
are clouding your judgment.
She won't be facing Darhk alone.
We need your help.
I know you feel like I abandoned you,
but, please, don't abandon me.
Hey, how you doing?
I'm all right.
You know, the truth is,
this young man
is like a stranger to me.
Every time I encounter him,
I can't imagine
I was ever that person.
I think anyone would feel
that way about meeting
their younger self.
I don't recognize my current self.
Mick told me
I need to be more like me.
And he's right, which is rare.
Indeed.
The problem is I don't know
what being me means right now.
I don't know if that makes any sense.
Of course it does.
I think everyone struggles
at least on occasion
with who they are
and then what their place is
in the world.
So what's the answer?
I have no idea.
But, I suppose it's just to live.
It's all any of us can really do.
And then, hopefully,
through the act of living
we discover who we truly are
and learn to grow from that.
Amaya got us invites
to the State Dinner.
Are you feeling up to it?
Yes, I'm feeling much better.
You feeling up to it?
I think what he means is
are you gonna create
a diplomatic crisis
and risk unknown damage
to history by killing Damien Darhk?
I know what he means, Ray.
Earlier, you accused me
of not ever caring for anyone,
but you know that's not true.
I care very much about you.
And I'm less concerned about history
than I am about your conscience.
You're no longer an assassin, Sara.
You're our Captain.
Well, let's hope I remember
that when the time comes.
Now let's do this.
Revving up your engine
Thank you for helping us get in.
Feels good to be back in the game.
I don't see Damien Darhk anywhere.
He'll be here.
Oh, my God, what is she doing here?
Probably looking
for her husband, no doubt.
She's... she's coming this way,
what... what should I do?
Just... Just talk to her.
Mr. Jackson, I expected
to meet my husband here.
Have you seen him yet?
I'm sorry, no. I haven't.
I'd be worried,
but it's just like Martin
to lose track of time.
Well, I'm sure, wherever he is,
you are foremost in his mind.
Who are you?
I'm... I'm a colleague of his.
My name is also Martin.
He never mentioned you.
Well, I'm sure he has more
important things to talk about.
Oh, would you...
would you care to dance?
I never seem to take the time
to enjoy these State Dinners.
Sure.
You all right?
You seem tense.
When you find Rex's killer,
what are you gonna do to him?
Arrest him.
What else is there?
You could kill him.
I'm a member of the Justice Society,
or at least I was when it existed,
I'm not some vigilante.
I'm sorry, I don't mean to pry,
but you don't
seem too happy to be here.
It's just... Martin invited me
on this trip for my birthday,
and I've spent the better
part of it alone.
Perhaps you should talk to him.
I've tried, but Martin's
love for nuclear science...
it's irrepressible.
Sometimes my husband
has tunnel vision.
Well, Martin is a fool,
but, believe me, he loves you.
You're far more important to him than
any of his scientific achievements.
I have the strangest feeling,
like we've danced before.
Sara, Darhk's in the hallway.
Mick, Ray, guard the exits.
And everybody else,
get ready to move.
Now that our governments
are waging peace upstairs,
what do you say we get down
to the real business?
You have brought us the codes?
It's called a CD-ROM, the latest
in Defense Department technology.
As for my half of the exchange?
Hand over the box.
And the kick-ass CD-ROM.
What is this?
He thinks we're working with Darhk.
Never.
No one has to get hurt.
That's not really my style.
Now, we can waste time chit-chatting,
or you can deal
with the explosive my people
have secreted inside
the State Dining Room.
See, in about six minutes,
Reagan, Gorbachev,
and every hope of peace goes kaboom.
- Ray?
- We're on it.
I am sorry... inconvenient,
I know, but try being me.
Todd?
We're on the move to find the bomb.
The bomb we must save Clarissa.
I got this, Sara. Go stop Darhk.
That's cool, man.
Mary Todd's hope chest.
Oh, you have gone too far!
Everyone.
Get the hell out of here, right now.
Now that we have your attention,
would you all please leave
the dining room immediately?
We believe there's
a bomb on the premises.
- You okay?
- Who are you?
A friend of your husband's.
Good news, I found the bomb.
Bad news, this type of firing
system is obsolete.
I have no idea how to
disarm such a crude weapon.
Figure it out, Ray.
I'm a little busy.
There's nothing I can do.
Yes, there is.
I was wrong trying to make
you like Snart.
You're Ray Palmer...
you can science your way
out of anything.
I'm Ray Palmer. I'm Ray Palmer.
I can science my way
out of anything.
I...
If I can send an electrical
pulse from an outside
power source,
I might be able to overload
the bomb's incendiary trigger,
but I'd have to dismantle
to cold gun.
Less talking, more doing.
No!
Ray?
- Tell me the bomb's disarmed.
- That would be a lie.
Well, ten seconds to live.
There are worse ways of dying.
I did it.
- I did it.
- Good.
Hold on, Todd.
Okay? Just hold on.
You and I have met before.
New York City, 1942.
You haven't aged a bit.
Lazarus Pit?
Oh, woman of mystery.
I know that look in your eye, though.
That's the look of someone
that I've taken everything from.
Not everything.
You haven't taken my soul,
which I've already lost,
and I'm not eager to do again.
And that's why I'm sparing your life.
How merciful of you.
I'm sparing you
to prolong your suffering.
'Cause I'm from the future,
Damien, and I know
how this all ends.
Your ark, your grand vision.
Just as you're about to accomplish
everything you desire,
your wife is murdered,
the love of your life.
And in total despair,
you even try to kill
your own daughter.
An entire city rises up against you,
and then you die...
defeated and alone.
What happened?
Where's Darhk?
He took him.
The time traveler
working against us...
He's a speedster.
Like the Flash?
Faster.
So the speedster and Darhk,
they have whatever
the KGB gave Darhk?
Unless...
Unless?
I swiped it off Darhk.
Shut up.
Can I hug you?
Do we hug?
- Okay, just this once.
- There's gonna be more.
Yeah!
You took a bullet for me.
For a fellow member
of the JSA, it was nothing.
Astonishing to be back here again.
A ship that can travel through
time and heal any wound.
Think of the possibilities...
Let me remind you,
it's imperative that you
carry on as if you never
saw me or anything else
from the future.
That you would pass up
the chance to show me
even the barest glimpse
of that future,
catapulting our transmutation
research into the 21st century,
I had no idea
I could ever be so selfish.
Interesting, considering
that's exactly
how you've been to Clarissa.
She nearly died last night
because of your blind devotion
to your work.
You of all people understand
the importance of our research.
I understand the importance
of one thing and one thing only.
After everything
I've accomplished, all...
all of the awards I've won...
Did we win the sixth Carlin?
The only thing that brings
meaning to my life is Clarissa.
Yes, Martin, our wife, who you spent
the last two days ignoring.
But I love Clarissa.
Then cherish her, Martin,
because I promise you,
she is the only thing
you will care to remember.
And I promise you...
I'll make sure she knows I love her.
I pray that you do.
Are you sure you won't come with us?
Rex's killer is still out there.
We could find him together.
I think last night proved
my fighting days are over.
You were amazing out there.
It felt like old times.
But there's something keeping
you here in 1987, isn't there?
After the JSA disbanded,
I spent a lot of lonely years
until I finally met someone, Amaya.
And he's waiting for me at home.
I have ameliorated
Mr. Rice's injuries.
That's incredible. Wow.
A word of advice from an old man
who's lived long enough
to see the world change,
and mostly for the better.
If you are lucky enough
to find love again...
Embrace it.
Are you leaving already?
I was hoping we'd have a beer.
Oh, unlike you, my time is limited,
and I don't need the carbs.
Good-bye, Todd.
Well, I guess I just...
He loved to sing.
Henry, your grandfather.
He had a beautiful voice.
During long convoys or stake-outs,
he would serenade the team.
He made it his personal mission
to get me to sing along,
but he never succeeded.
But when the chips were down
and all hope seemed lost,
we could always count on
Henry to lift our spirits.
That's the kind of man
your grandfather was.
Then take me back there now.
I will get your item back for you.
The Legends have left 1987.
The item is beyond your reach.
That blonde woman...
She's a time traveler like you.
She knows what happens
to me in the future.
- I'm sure she does.
- Then take me with you.
I need to change my destiny.
Tell you what,
why don't we work together
to change both of our destinies?
Step inside.