RIP: In 2166,
an immortal tyrant named Vandal Savage
conquered the world
and murdered my wife and child.
I have assembled an elite team
to hunt him throughout time
and stop his rise to power.
Unfortunately, my plan is opposed
by the body I had sworn my allegiance to,
the Time Masters.
In the future,
my friends may not be heroes,
but if we succeed,
they will be remembered as legends.
RORY: Previously,
on Legends of Tomorrow...
- Boys! The ship's all yours.
- SNART: Mick!
What are you gonna do, Snart?
My husband and I
get along just fine on our own.
We're still waiting on Sara and
the two lovebirds to get back.
It seems they've taken
quite a shine to 1958.
(GRUNTING)
Sara swore her allegiance
to the League of Assassins.
It's time for her to return home.
My friend Thea calls it a bloodlust.
(GRUNTING)
Sara, stop!
I'm a monster.
Not this guy again.
GIDEON: Captain, Chronos has breached
the starboard hatch.
How is that possible?
Clearly, he's received some new toys
from his Time Master friend,
since our last encounter.
1958's swell and all,
but I miss the Internet.
And cell phones.
Gideon, seal the bulkheads
from here until--
(GRUNTS)
Grey, come on! Let's do this!
If we merge on the Waverider,
it could destroy the entire ship!
Are you not paying attention
to what Chronos is doing?
Fall back!
Get to the Jumpship!
- Hey, come on!
- You sure it was a good idea
leaving the Terminator on the bridge?
Gideon has lockout protocols which--
GIDEON: Have been overridden, Captain.
Chronos is utilizing superior
Time Master technology.
I cannot countermand his orders.
Uh...
What are they doing?
- Hey!
Where did they go?
Better question, why did they leave us?
(GRUNTS)
He's time-jumping the ship.
The ladies will be left in 1958.
- What about Ray?
- Like I said...
Let's go! We have to stop him.
(GROANS)
Gideon, open the doors on my mark.
Get to the Jumpship and escape.
We are not abandoning you.
No, you're obeying a
direct order from your captain.
Now, Gideon.
(YELLS)
I don't know if the Jumpship
will even fly through the Temporal Zone.
- (RIP YELLING)
- (LASER BLASTS)
It doesn't matter.
We're not leaving our team.
What happened to "We could
destroy the whole ship"?
Preferable alternative
to losing our friends,
don't you agree?
Yeah.
PROFESSOR STEIN: We could've just
opened the door, Jefferson.
Sorry, I got a little carried away.
(GASPS) Hey, hey, hey.
(GROANING) Oh, God!
Where's Chronos?
GIDEON: He absconded with Mister Snart
on the Jumpship.
I'm sorry, Captain.
Why would Chronos take Snart?
Gideon, can you track them?
GIDEON: We have a more pressing matter.
(BEEPING)
Strap yourselves in.
What's going on?
Chronos has sabotaged
the navigation system.
Unless we find a way to alter the course,
we'll be trapped in
the Temporal Zone for all time.
Gideon--
Cannot override Chronos' commands.
(POWERING FLUCTUATING)
What did you do?
I rebooted Gideon.
Until she's fully operational,
we're free-falling through time.
(GRUNTING)
(SCREAMING)
We just have to stay calm.
Wherever they time-jumped... Whenever,
they'll come back
to this exact same moment.
They're not coming back. Let's go.
Look, as a former Eagle Scout
with over 100 merit badges,
no big deal,
the first rule of getting lost
is to stay in the same place.
That way you can be found.
And as a former member of
the League of Assassins,
the first rule when you've been
attacked is to keep moving.
I sort of think League wisdom
trumps the Eagle Scouts here.
Plus, Savage is still out there.
Guys, the rest of the team would
not leave us marooned in 1958.
Except for that's exactly what they did.
You said it yourself,
you have a time machine
and you're never late.
They're not coming back.
One good thing about 1958, no car alarms.
I didn't think they had cars
in Nanda Parbat.
Dated a lot of delinquents as a teenager.
(ENGINE STARTS)
And now, we're the delinquents.
If we leave Harmony Falls,
how's the rest of the team gonna find us?
SARA: We don't know
if they're looking for us,
but we do know Savage is.
We can't take him.
That means, we can't stay here.
Let's go.
(SIGHS) What did you do to our apartment?
I'm creating a time beacon.
A transponder which matches
the Waverider's quantum signature,
basically creating a radio wave firewall
that only our team can see.
It's so cute that you think either of us
understood a word of that.
But I hope it works.
In the meantime, maybe we should
invest in some real beds.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
Congratulations. You are a doctor.
You know, I thought about
going to medical school once.
(SIGHS) Here you go, $10,000 salary.
That's it?
I made more as a barista.
Oh, it's 1958. You're lucky to
make that as a woman.
Touche.
- Your turn.
- (SIGHS)
I miss Netflix.
- (BEEPS)
- (CHUCKLES)
The time beacon Ray-dio
is officially complete!
Great.
Okay. Here we go. Come on.
Here we go.
Hope there's a spot on that game
that says, "Return to that Waverider"
because that's what's about to happen.
- Here we go.
- (DEVICE POWERING UP)
- (CIRCUITS CRACKLING)
- Ooh!
I just have to fix few of the kinks.
The next version
will be much less explosive.
Next version?
I thought you said you were
gonna say something to him.
- Say what?
- That your beacon,
it's a waste of time.
They're not coming back, Ray.
And it's not because
the Waverider is broken,
or they're lost, or they
can't find us, or whatever.
It's because they're dead.
And the sooner that you accept that,
the sooner you can move on.
The sooner we can all move on.
So what? We're just supposed to give up?
On being rescued, yeah.
Sara, what are you doing?
I can't stay here. I need to
find somewhere I belong.
Sara, wait. You can't go.
Savage is still out there.
Don't draw undue attention on yourselves.
Sara.
Look, you two have each other.
Most people, in any time period,
aren't that lucky.
Take care.
(SOFT SCOFF)
Which gives us mesoscopic polymer
and biomolecular simulations.
Yes, Mr. Gates.
If that's true and you can soften matter,
then doesn't that mean
you could theoretically
miniaturize an atom?
(SOFT CHUCKLE) In theory, yes.
But trust me,
you don't wanna try it at home.
And definitely not for at least
another... Mmm, 40 years.
Uh, aren't you supposed to be at home?
I thought you said your son was sick.
Yes. William.
My in-laws are at my house.
So if you don't mind
I'd rather be in here.
Your son is Bill Gates?
"Bill." That has a nice ring to it.
Midterms are next week.
Go ahead and pick up
an exam book on your way out.
Class dismissed.
Happy second anniversary.
Happy anniversary.
Ah.
I thought we said no gifts.
I know. Just open it.
Your time beacon?
I thought we could destroy it together.
You don't have to do that.
I want to.
You know, I never thought
that I could build a life
with anybody but Anna.
But that's exactly what I've done,
in the most unlikely time
and place imaginable.
And I know it may sound strange
but I'm glad we're stranded here.
Me, too.
I have one more surprise for you.
Ray.
(BEEPING)
The beacon...
It's picking up a signal.
(ENGINE CHUGGING, SPUTTERING)
Uh... (SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
You are suffering
from linguistic disorientation.
It's a side effect
of such a severe timejump.
I can't hear anything.
- It'll pass.
- What?
Gideon, status update?
I am detecting a time beacon
signaling the Waverider.
But then again, this is 1960.
1960?
GIDEON: The temporal navigation system
was compromised
and did its best to return us
as close as possible to 1958.
(BEEPING)
Yeah, sorry we're late.
Two years...
You left us stranded in 1958.
That was never my intention.
Can we rev the ship back up,
go back to 1958, and pick that us up?
You know very well that we can't.
Travel back to events we participated in
without time folding in on itself.
Raymond.
- Good to see you.
- I'm glad you're back.
- Martin.
- (CHUCKLING)
- Mmm.
It's just... I have 50 midterms
to grade next week,
by hand.
And I'd just come to terms with
living in the technological dark ages.
I have students who count on me.
Kendra and I have friends and a life.
Ray, this is what we've been waiting for.
Remember the mission.
We can finally be ourselves again.
Look, I'm sorry.
This is all... (SIGHS) Very intense.
It's been two years for us.
We thought you guys were dead.
That very well might have been the case.
Chronos attacked us.
He sabotaged the ship and took Snart.
We need to recover Ms. Lance as well.
Where is she?
Uh, no idea.
People go their separate ways.
Lose track of each other.
Gideon, search the timeline
for any reference
of a Sara Lance or
a blonde vigilante circa 1960.
GIDEON: Right away, Captain.
Why did Chronos take Snart?
Couldn't he have taken you all in?
You sound dubious.
If Chronos was going to settle
for taking one person,
you'd think it would be you.
He took Snart for a reason.
(ELECTRONIC WHIRRING)
Uh, hello?
A UFO sighting in Hub City in 1960
has created a time anomaly.
It looks like your friends survived.
And, uh, what would they be doing in 1960?
That is out of the question, Mr. Palmer.
What are we talking about?
You changed.
Yeah. I couldn't wait
to get back in jeans.
So what's going on?
I have to go back to our apartment.
Why?
Because when we were
unexpectedly picked up by a timeship,
I was not carrying the Atom suit.
And not for nothing,
but we spent the last two years
together in that apartment.
Is there anything you want me
to pick up for you?
You favorite coffee mug.
Our lucky water vase.
"Lucky water vase"?
Yeah. It's a long but endearing story.
Nothing?
Don't you care about anything
that we left behind?
Uh, yes, but I don't think that
I need to go back to the apartment
to get any of our old junk.
"Old junk."
We lived there this morning.
We certainly can't leave
Raymond's exosuit back in 1960.
I'll accompany you back to your apartment.
We'll recover the future tech
and any lucky ceramics.
Ray--
I'll get those blouses you like.
Well, I hope that Sara
takes to being back on the team
better than Ray seems to taking it.
Depends, I suppose,
on where exactly she ended up.
- (GRUNTING)
- (SWORDS CLASHING)
Ta-er al-Sahfer.
I can see that the herbs
and meditation are working.
Your thirst to kill no longer
clouds your judgment.
Proceed.
(GRUNTING)
Stand up.
I've enjoyed watching you train.
I have never seen a pupil
advance so quickly.
I've had time to learn who I am.
And what it is I'm meant to do.
Well, watch this one closely, Talia.
There is much you can learn from her.
So, uh, what's so special about me?
I mean, aside from
my sparkling personality.
Back on the Waverider,
you could've taken your boy Rip.
But you took me instead. Why?
Hey, if you're gonna kill me,
you could at least tell me
what's going on.
You should have figured it out by now.
After all,
I am supposed to be the dumb one.
How?
I think I deserve to know
what the hell is going on here!
You deserve nothing.
Says the man who sold us out
to the pirates.
When I dropped you off in that forest,
I meant to kill you.
That was the plan.
You should have stuck with
the plan and done me a favor.
SNART: I wish there were
some other way, Mick.
(GUN POWERING UP)
You haven't got the guts.
You wanna kill me? Kill me.
Only one of us
is walking out of here alive.
You're right.
I knew you lacked the guts.
(GRUNTS)
I am sorry, Mick.
I may not have trusted you
on the ship with the team,
but I always,
always was coming back for you.
Seems like one of us lost track of time.
- How long did you--
- By the time they found me,
I'd nearly lost my mind.
I was so weak, I was
strangling rats to survive.
When who found you?
The Time Masters.
They took me to a place
called the Vanishing Point.
Time doesn't exist there
the way it does on Earth.
I've spent lifetimes
being restored by them,
training by them, fighting by them,
being reborn.
And, uh, when exactly did your new
friends give you the, uh, lobotomy?
You think I was hunting you and friends
because the Time Masters made me?
They barely had to ask.
Hey. Uh, can we talk for a sec?
Just, with everything that's going on,
I don't know that this is the best time.
You say that like
there's gonna be a better time.
Okay.
Look, we have spent every night
the last two years together,
playing board games, eating,
and deciding who was gonna cook
and who was gonna wash dishes,
falling asleep to The Ed Sullivan Show.
But the second you saw the Waverider,
it was like those two years
never happened.
Look, we were both trying to adapt
to an impossible situation.
But you're not a college professor
and I'm definitely not a librarian.
So honestly, I'm just excited
to be able to be myself again.
I mean, aren't you even a little bit happy
to be back on the ship?
I was happy with the life
we built together.
What I thought would be our future.
This all just feels like moving backwards.
- (SIGHS)
- Moving backwards.
What if Sara didn't
move forwards with her life,
she moved backwards?
She said she wanted to go to
a place where she belonged.
What's the one place in 1958
she already called home?
The League of Assassins.
There is one source that we
could check to test your theory.
Gideon, bring up the Shadow Record.
Shadow Record?
GIDEON: The list of every member of
the League of Assassins
since the invention of writing
in 3200 B.C.
Fascinating. Except these sheets
of papyrus are entirely blank.
No, no, no.
The League uses invisible ink.
I did my graduate thesis at
the Academy on their history.
Gideon.
Sara said that Ra's al Ghul
had lived nearly a century
before she met him.
Thanks to the Lazarus Pit.
It's basically a life-extending jacuzzi.
Located in a place that's
the opposite of life-extending.
Uh, you should count
yourself lucky, Dr. Palmer.
Only a handful of outsiders
have been inside the League's fortress
and lived to tell the tale.
GIDEON: You are correct, Captain.
There is a mention of Ta-er al-Sahfer.
That's, uh, Sara's
League of Assassins name.
According to the Shadow Record,
she joined the League in 1958.
Incredible. Sara became a member
of the secret organization
that trained her to be an assassin
50 years prior to
when she initially joined.
Sara needs our help.
By all accounts, Ra's al Ghul is
a very controlling,
very homicidal fanatic.
Gideon, chart a course for Nanda Parbat.
Look, if you're gonna kill me,
just do it already.
I'm not gonna kill you.
I'm gonna take a trip back to Central City
and visit your baby sister.
The beautiful thing about time travel
is I get to kill her more than once.
I can kill Lisa in front of you.
Go back in time, and kill her
in front of you again.
And again and again.
MALE VOICE: Sir, several anomalies
in the timeline
suggest that the Waverider has
touched down in Nanda Parbat.
Chart a course.
(ELECTRONIC WHIRRING)
I used to think the
most beautiful thing on Earth
was fire.
Now I know it's vengeance.
Uh, perhaps Jefferson and I should--
Extricating Sara from the likes
of the League requires stealth.
So no Firestorm for the two of you.
And you're out of practice.
So no Atom suit
unless absolutely necessary.
- Look out!
- (GRUNTS)
(GRUNTING)
Thanks.
Well done, Jefferson.
You guard the exit while I find Sara.
We'll be in and out of here
faster than you can say Ra's al Ghul. Shh.
Sara.
It's me.
Rip?
I'm here to bring you back.
I'm so sorry that it's taken me so long.
- Who else is here?
- The entire team.
Well, except for Mr. Snart.
I'll explain everything back on the ship.
(GRUNTING)
Something's wrong.
They should've been back by now.
Well, I think this counts as
"absolutely necessary."
I've got my exo-suit shrunk down.
I can miniaturize
and do some tiny sneaking.
It's been two years
since you've used that suit,
and that's after you scavenged it
for parts for your time beacon.
You don't even know if it works.
Is now really the time
for your little marital spat?
We're not married.
Can we just keep it down, please.
Sara.
Found her.
Hey.
Sara, what the hell?
You shouldn't have come here.
Yeah, I'm starting to get that.
We came here to rescue you.
I don't need to be rescued.
I've found peace here.
RIP: Peace with
the League of Assassins?
That must be the first time that
that sentence has ever been uttered.
(SIGHS) I can't believe I'm back here.
If this is retribution of some kind
for stranding you in 1958--
It's the will of Ra's al Ghul.
Trespassers are to be executed.
We just need a little more time
to get through to her.
Do Time Masters have
a different understanding
of the word "executed"?
No, no, no. It's called "time drift."
When one spends too long
in an alien timeline,
one loses ties with one's
former self, uh, former identity.
- Oh, my God.
- What?
I didn't understand it before, but...
My powers, they went dormant.
- What are you talking about?
- My wings.
You must have noticed that I
haven't been able to "hawk out"
in almost two years.
I just thought that you didn't want to.
Why didn't you tell me?
Because it was so hard for you
to give up hope
that the team would return.
When you finally did,
you started to be happy again.
And I couldn't bear
telling you that I wasn't.
- (HISSES) That ain't good.
- I had no idea.
Look, Ray, I loved being with you.
I wasn't just losing my powers,
I was losing my memories of my past lives.
I was starting to lose myself.
I'm sorry, I...
(SIGHS) You didn't have to protect me.
I could have handled the truth.
It couldn't have been so easy
for Raymond, either,
having to give up being the Atom.
I'm sorry. Can we have a private moment.
I think we all wish
you would have had this moment in private.
(CHAINS CLANK)
Don't you think that we were
meant for something greater
than being stuck in 1960,
eating fondue with the neighbors?
Yeah, we were meant to be
tortured and executed in
Nanda "I can't believe
I am back here" Parbat.
If we die, at least it would be
in pursuit of a greater purpose.
- That's it.
- What's it?
Ra's al Ghul's purpose in life
is to see that the League continues
with all of its ancient traditions intact.
Including murdering intruders.
I will appeal to Ra's al Ghul's respect
for the League's traditions
invoking one of them right now.
What kind of traditions, man?
Guards?
Guards!
Would you mind
loosening these up a little bit
before you leave?
Just out of curiosity,
what do you think your new masters
are going to do with you
once you've delivered the team up to them?
I don't expect there's a pension plan
for old bounty hunters.
Once they get what they want from you,
they're gonna toss you aside.
Like you tossed me aside?
You and I both made choices
that led us to this moment.
What matters, Mick, is your next move.
And I'm willing to bet that
some little piece of the old you
is in that armor somewhere.
No, you're wrong.
Mr. Hunter.
Captain, as a point of fact.
Right.
Well, I do hope your request
for an audience
is not an attempt to justify
your trespass here.
Certainly not.
But it would be remiss of me
if I didn't use this opportunity
to reiterate that Sara
is very important to me.
To all of us.
And as she is to me.
And as you can all see,
she has chosen to remain here.
Yes, well, if that is her wish,
we will indeed honor it.
Well, thank you.
But your deaths will make
that concession irrelevant.
Well, according to my
understanding of League Law,
the whole, uh, death thing can be avoided
should we prevail at trial.
Yeah, uh, I don't think these guys
are the People's Court type.
I demand a trial by combat.
And how's a man such as you
so well-versed on our traditions?
Do we have an accord?
May victory be yours.
I was under the impression
that I would be fighting you.
Then it would seem
your understanding of our laws
requires some refinement.
You see, I may choose any champion I wish.
As may you.
I'll do it.
You haven't had very much experience
in swordsmanship, Mr. Palmer.
I nominate Ms. Saunders.
What? No.
Didn't you hear? She can't even--
I accept.
- Kendra, you can't--
- I've got this.
(GRUNTS)
- (GRUNTS)
- (METAL CLANGING)
(GUN POWERS UP)
You have to put a stop to this.
Sara taught Kendra
to control her warrior side.
I believe that Kendra can remind
Sara of her humanity.
Before or after Sara kills her?
Sara. Ta-er al-Sahfer.
Whatever your name is now.
I know you don't want to kill me.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Want is irrelevant.
I serve Ra's al Ghul.
(METAL CLANKING)
(GUN POWERS UP)
(SCREAMING)
- (GRUNTING)
- (SWORDS CLASHING)
Remember that move? You taught it to me.
Your teacher was excellent.
(GRUNTING)
Sara, no.
(KENDRA PANTING)
Sara.
You're not a murderer, or an assassin.
No!
You're the White Canary.
(EXHALES)
- (THUD)
- (LASERS BLASTING)
I know that sound.
Chronos.
(GRUNTS)
(MEN GRUNTING)
You can't face him. You can't defeat him.
(SWORDS CLASHING)
(GRUNTING)
(METAL CLANGING)
You brought him here.
It's only right you kill him.
It's a long story, pal.
Ray!
(PANTING)
(GRUNTS)
(SCREAMING)
(GRUNTING, PANTING)
(GRUNTS)
(GRUNTING)
(GUN POWERING UP)
You son of a bitch.
Don't do it.
Don't kill him.
Snart?
Sorry, don't kill Chronos?
He's not Chronos.
Show 'em.
Oh, my God.
There is no God.
(GRUNTING)
RIP: I imagine you have some questions
about what you witnessed.
When the lady you call
"Sara Lance" first arrived here,
her skills were unmatched.
It was as if she had
completed the training before.
I suppose that's because
you're both from the future.
When I came to your doorstep
for the second time in my life,
I thought that I could find a home here.
That this is where I really belong.
But your soul is divided
by your ability to kill
and your desire to show mercy.
And there is no place for one
so conflicted within the League.
Ta-er al-Sahfer, I release you.
You can reclaim your previous
name and your past life.
Thank you.
In October 2008,
please see that your daughter
is off the coast of an island
in the North China Sea,
Lian Yu.
Why would I send Talia on such a journey?
Not Talia.
Your daughter yet to be born.
I'm pretty sure you'll call her Nyssa.
You think this is all over?
I will kill every single one of you.
I will watch you all burn!
You!
You should have killed me
when you had the--
(BEEPS)
You owe us an explanation.
PROFESSOR STEIN: Yes,
it's quite remarkable Mr. Rory
is working for the Time Masters
considering you killed him.
If you think back,
I never actually said I killed him.
No, you just let us think that you did.
I didn't have to try too hard, did I?
Well, maybe I should have.
Then at least he wouldn't have wound up
a chew toy for the Time Masters.
But if you did, we wouldn't
have this opportunity.
Opportunity? To do what?
To reform Mr. Rory.
He killed Aldus.
Under the influence of the Time Masters.
"Chronos" killed Aldus.
Mr. Rory was fighting
on our side that day.
I know what it's like
to be trained by an organization
for one purpose, to kill.
And the kind of loyalty
that it can inspire.
I need to know that we can reach Rory.
For my own sake.
The Time Masters took one of our own
and turned him against us.
I say we undo their handiwork.
Rory saved my life back in the Gulag.
He's more than just
a criminal and an arsonist.
- He's a member of our team.
- He's a lost cause.
RIP: Oh, I wouldn't be so sure about that.
You will see that miracles
abound on this old timeship.
Gideon, start the regeneration process.
What do you mean "regeneration"?
Uh, I took genetic samples
from each of you
at the start of our voyage
for this exact eventuality.
Why am I only hearing about this now?
Because none of you had lost a limb yet.
(DEVICE POWERING UP)
Ow.
(ELECTRONIC WHIRRING)
(CHUCKLES)
(DOOR SLIDES OPEN)
So, were you gonna tell me?
Sorry, tell you what?
That you're moving
into your room without me.
Oh, um...
I just assumed
that you wanted some space.
You've made it pretty clear
that you were over our old life.
Look,
just because I wasn't satisfied
with the circumstances
doesn't mean
I didn't fall in love with you.
(SOFT CHUCKLE)
It's just, I... I don't wanna lose you.
And I don't wanna lose you.
For the first time, in probably centuries,
I actually got to decide
who I want to fall in love with,
instead of having it decided for me.
So it doesn't matter where or when we are.
You're the person I want to be with.
Wow, that was...
Was that, like, rehearsed?
(CHUCKLES)
'Cause it was really good.
So, what do you want?
(HEAVY BREATHING)
(GASPS)
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
I believe we're ready to leave 1960.
And go where? I mean, when.
2147.
Mere decades before
Vandal Savage conquered the world.
I thought you had no idea where he was.
You said Savage had been lost to history.
Not world-changing history.
Records of the period are scarce,
but I've always known that
Vandal Savage could be located in 2147.
So why haven't you told us this sooner?
Because that period of history
is fraught with more peril
than I was willing to risk.
We have no choice but to stop
Vandal Savage in 2147.
Or to die trying.
Well, I've died before.
So have I.
Gideon, plot a course
for Kasnia Conglomerate.
(ELECTRONIC BEEPING, WHIRRING)
The year 2147.
English - SDH