Previously,
onLegends Of Tomorrow...
- Is this your new girlfriend?
- Yeah.
You and I dating
would be totally weird.
Totally weird.
Wow, that's beautiful.
Step away from the creature, miss.
You murdered him!
Hank is running some secret project.
He's not just taking the fugitives.
He's testing on them.
I don't need you anymore.
I don't need you anymore, either.
- What did you do?
- I'm sorry.
Maybe I shouldn't intrude.
Nate needs all of our support
right now.
Well, what am I supposed
to say to him?
"Sorry the woman I've been exchanging
love letters with in prison
killed your dad"?
They ought to put that
on a condolence card.
Look, we are going inside
and we are going to strive with grace
to help our friend cope
with his loss.
Damn it.
Here, let me help.
Hey, thanks for sticking around
this past week.
What are pretend girlfriends for?
My mom's going to be so crushed
when I tell her we broke up.
Then don't.
I mean, she's going through a lot.
We can pretend break up
any time we want.
We should... we should probably
get out there.
You ready for this?
Oh, Nathaniel.
I need you to make a toast later.
Tell everyone what an amazing man
your father was.
Yeah, Mom,
I don't think that's a great idea.
What? Of course, it is.
And Zari, I am so glad
that you're here for Nathaniel
to lean on right now.
Yeah, you know me,
I'm... I'm his rock.
I can't... I can't face him.
Wait... wait.
I hope you're not stress-eating,
squire.
I don't know what else to do.
I can't believe this is happening.
You feel the energy in this room?
It's like sitting on a keg
of dynamite.
You see,
wakes are notorious soft spots
where the supernatural meets
the living world.
See Nate's aunt?
That particular prayer
is to ward off evil spirits
and they've covered the mirrors,
so the bad lads can't get in.
Well, that's creepy.
Yeah, well, creepy is my business.
And it looks like business is good.
Nate, Nate, I'm... I'm sorry.
I'm... I'm so sorry.
No, it's... it's okay, Ray.
No, no, no, it's not.
I keep giving Nora second chances
and she goes and does this.
Look, you thought Nora
could change and...
I never thought my dad
would be torturing magical creatures
so I guess...
I guess we're both wrong.
Can't believe
you're the one comforting me.
Oh, come on. I love you, bro.
That's never going to change.
Love you, too.
Oh, no.
Don't, no, no, no, don't.
Don't, don't, don't do it, Ray.
Don't... you're going to do it.
You're going to do it.
Nora?
How... how are you doing this?
It's a reflection spell.
I can't hold it much longer.
Well, good, because there's nothing
you could possibly say
that would make any difference.
This time there will be no more
second chances.
Ray! I didn't kill Nate's dad.
Oh, thank God, you're innocent.
Tell me where you are,
I need to talk to you in person.
Now, who wants a nice, juicy steak?
Charlie,
you know that I'm a vegetarian.
No, no, no,
you used to be a vegetarian
when you were a normal, boring human.
- But now you are...
- A monster?
Exactly. I mean, how cool is that?
Wait, are you trying to get me
to shift into Wolfie?
Of course, I am.
You've been moping about the ship,
thinking about your lost love.
I think that he would really want you
to just embrace your wild side.
Konane liked me as Mona.
Elizabeth & Jane & Emma
The words on your shirt.
These are the names of my favorite
Jane Austen characters.
It appears that you're experiencing
the impact of a magical fugitive.
This better be good, Mona.
A fugitive got to Jane Austen.
She never wrote
"Sense and Sensibility."
And "Pride and Prejudice"
disappeared, too.
Whatever it is,
it's going to have to wait.
Did someone say history's in trouble?
Legends assemble!
Okay, I really need
to get out of here, too.
Hey, what's up?
Nothing.
There's a fugitive alert,
but it can wait.
No, you should go.
It's hard enough
I have to play pretend.
You guys shouldn't.
Okay.
- Bye, Nate.
- Bye, Zari.
Gideon traced a new Fugitive
to a wedding Jane Austen attended
in Bath, England, 1802.
I already had Gideon chart a course.
Can I come on the mission?
Please?
Sure.
Yeah, and as much as I love
a good wedding sneak
I'm going to QB from...
from my bedroom.
Is he acting weirder than normal?
-Yeah.
Speaking of weird...
I think my sense of smell
has improved because of Wolfie.
And you smell exactly like...
Nate.
No, I don't.
It's definitely Nate.
Nate and something else.
Arousal?
No, I don't... don't like Nate.
- That would be wrong and...
- He likes you.
He confessed it
when he swallowed the truth bug.
We're so not passing
the Bechdel Test right now.
It's okay to talk
about guys sometimes.
Come on. I bet it's been months
since you got laid.
Now, why don't you
just go smash Nate?
Or better yet,
you should go smash somebody else
because if you're still thinking
about Nate
then you know you're really into him.
Why don't you talk to Nate?
Tell him how you feel.
- Oh, boo.
- That is a terrible idea.
Okay, I'm going. Bye.
This is like a Jane Austen novel
come to life.
Oh, my bonnet!
Look out!
Forgive me, miss.
Are you hurt?
Only my pride.
Injured pride is a small thing...
if it allowed us to meet.
What's the holdup there?
Come, come, I say.
Duty calls.
Apologies, Lord Remington.
We'll be on our way shortly.
Here.
Not a word.
Was that a curtsey?
"Only my pride."
Okay, let's go. Shut up.
A damsel.
If you don't jump
that buff coachman's bones, I will.
We are at this wedding
to catch a magical creature.
If that's the groom,
then I'm glad I'm not the bride.
A man's charms
are equal to his fortunes.
And Mr. Dockerty's fortunes
are prodigious.
Jane.
Don't be rude.
That's Jane Austen.
I cannot marry you, Mr. Dockerty.
My heart yearns for another.
Our family's scullery maid.
Ellen, are you here?
I'm here!
I love you too!
Scandal!
Holy Lord!
I give not one fig, Ms. Sinclair
for my heart,
and my lower extremities
yearn for your mother.
Get over here, gorgeous.
Come here, my love.
Now this is what I call a wedding.
Coast is clear.
I really don't want you
to get in trouble with your friends.
Oh, it's no trouble.
It looks like everyone else
is still on mission.
Okay.
So, who did kill Hank?
- The demon.
- Okay, good.
I... obviously,
I mean, obviously, it's bad.
If it's a demon, that means that John
will be able to find proof
and you just need to lay low
until he comes back.
You really don't mind me
staying here?
Yeah, no, it'd be nice
if you stayed here.
Oy, Rayge.
Where are you?
I've got an update on the mission,
it's me to see a result...
- "Rayge"?
- It's a long story.
- need to do some research...
- What's...
What...
What are you hiding in there?
What? Nothing.
Buffing the old bishop, was we?
It's all right, mate.
No judgment here, all right?
- Come on.
- Yeah.
So, the bride and the scullery maid,
that was...
- Insane?
- Romantic
I was gonna say hot.
Regardless, that definitely
did not happen in actual history.
Ray, Charlie, what you got?
This wedding
was the second of a series
of lust outbreaks in 1802.
Yeah, the sexual revolution came
a couple hundred years too early.
Why would it make
Jane Austen stop writing?
We need more info.
Well, Jane Austen was known
for being a keen social observer
so if anyone would have noticed
a new magical arrival in town
it would be her.
Okay, let's go interview Jane.
Oh, wait, hang on a tick.
People with the real dirt,
always the servants.
Like a handsome coachman perhaps?
Fine, I'll go ask him some questions,
but that's it.
- You go get it, girl.
- Okay.
Sister, dear, this is Ms. Lance
and Ms. Wu.
They're new in town.
Try not to scare them away.
I shall do my best, Cassandra.
We are so sorry
to interrupt your writing,
Ms. Austen.
This? Just a letter.
Shall we take a turn around the room
while we converse?
We'd be delighted to.
It's a Regency thing. Go with it.
So, the bride, Ms. Sinclair
her behavior
must have been quite a shock.
Ever since Lord Remington arrived
a week ago,
the entire town
has been acting most imprudently.
But Ms. Sinclair's situation
is truly horrendous.
Oh, I'd think you, of all people
would celebrate the triumph
of romance.
What's to celebrate?
Ms. Sinclair will be cut off
from her fortune
and the two women
will have nothing to live on.
But it's because of you... I mean...
I have come to believe
that love will find a way
to overcome any obstacle.
Then you're either lying
or you're a fool.
Tell me, has love worked out
so well for you?
- No, but...
- Then you are a fool.
For you shouldn't have
to learn a lesson twice.
Let's go find Lord Remington.
We should be going.
Hello?
This is stupid.
What a pleasure to see you again.
Hey, man.
What's up, pretty?
This whole toasting
is eating me up on the inside.
My... my dad was such a dick.
He lied about everything
and now he's turning me
into a liar, too.
Listen, your old man's gone.
Whatever you say out there,
that's for you.
You know what, Mick?
I think you're onto something.
Nathaniel!
Hey, where's Nate?
Well, we need to find him
because Hank's spirit is still here.
Hey, cheer up.
I mean, what does Jane Austen know?
How to be witty,
wise and mix satire with romance.
I bet you these girls know
where Lord Remington is.
They do look like fan girls.
Okay, you know the era.
You take the lead.
He's simply the handsomest man
I've ever laid eyes on.
I know what you mean.
Lord Remington
is such a fine specimen.
I can't say I share your sentiment.
His coachman, though,
what he lacks in means
he makes up for in magnetism.
I concur.
His arrival
has sent many hearts aflutter.
Coachman,
as in the guy we pushed Zari
to hook up with.
Zari's going to smash the fugitive.
Oh, God!
Sorry, this is moving really fast.
I agree.
You do?
What's your name?
My name is Zari, what's your name?
You know what?
Don't... don't answer that.
You don't kiss
like any man I've ever known.
What are you?
I am Kamadeva.
The Hindu God of love.
Awesome.
We're too late!
Zari!
We think you might be dealing with...
The fugitive?
Yeah, I know.
This is Kamadeva.
As in, namesake of the Kama Sutra,
Kamadeva?
That, I did not know.
Look, I'm not going to sleep
with a magical fugitive.
You are incredible.
A woman has never before
resisted my charms.
All right, you're coming with us.
I would follow Ms. Zari
to the world's end.
Well, your days
of ruining Regency-era marriages
are over, Kamadeva.
I only sought
to grant people the courage
to follow their heart's desire.
Oh, think he likes you.
Gideon, get us out of here.
I'm not so sure we can go yet.
Ms. Wu is correct.
The historical records still indicate
that Jane Austen's career
is in jeopardy.
We caught the fugitive,
what's the problem?
Well, it's too late to knock
on Jane Austen's door tonight.
We'll talk to her tomorrow.
So, I'm to spend the night...
Alone.
Oh, what a waste.
All right, everybody out.
- Hi.
- Come on.
Surely I can have a bed.
Well, I had Gideon fabricate
some jim-jams
because, you know,
it's a slumber party.
Thanks.
Obviously, since you're my guest,
you will get the bed.
Oh, well, it's big enough
for the both of us.
We can just share.
Oh, okay.
You can turn around now.
It really covers everything.
Thing is, I pride myself
on being a gentleman
and the gentlemanly thing to do
would be to sleep in the chair, so...
But you... you... you can't...
there's no way you...
That's not...
Okay.
Hey, Nate.
How's the old toast going?
Is there one or two N's
in "conniving"?
Right, then.
May I suggest
a slight change of plan?
No, Mick is right.
It's time for me
to tell the truth about my dad.
How was I supposed to know
Hank's ghost was here?
- Wait, what?
- Yeah.
That's about the gist of it,
Natey boy.
You see, your old man's spirit
is working very hard
to stay attached to the mortal realm.
I can only surmise
that he has something he wants
to say to you,
so if you wouldn't mind leaving off
your roast for a bit,
joining us for a brief séance
and I'll have him on his way
in no time.
No.
There's nothing Hank can say now
to excuse him from embezzling money
and hurting creatures.
In fact, I'm glad he's still here,
because it's his turn
to listen to me.
You don't scare me, Hank!
Ray?
You want me in bed with you?
Yes, I did.
I do.
Is this okay?
Yes.
Ava.
Damn it, this is definitely a dream.
The fugitive get to you, too?
Yeah.
Well, personally,
I really enjoyed my night,
blowing David Bowie's mind.
Who'd you get a leg over, Z?
Wait, let me guess, Nate?
No, Kamadeva.
Both?
It was both! Blimey, Z, I didn't know
you had it in you.
What about you, Wolfie?
You dreamt about Konane.
Mona.
I'll get it.
Hey, hey, hey.
It's okay.
He had the sweetest eyes.
And when he would look at me,
the whole world would disappear.
And now he's dead.
Mona, I know it's hard,
but try to have some perspective.
You didn't know him for very long.
So, you think I'm a fool, too?
No, I just don't think anyone
should give their heart away
without thinking about
the consequences.
But romance is taking a chance
on someone without knowing
how it's going to end up!
Romance is something used
to sell novels.
- It's not real.
- Well, it'll never be real for you.
Not if you never try.
Not if you never take a risk!
You know, it's hard to take advice
from someone whose boyfriend
turned her into a werewolf.
Hey, guys.
Let's just take a breath.
You're right.
I might be stupid for being
a romantic,
but it's not Konane's fault.
Bloody hell!
Finally! You look wicked, mate!
Mona, wait!
Jane Austen.
It's time for you to pay!
Stay back, beast!
If I'm a beast, it's because of you!
Your books made me
an incurable romantic!
You're the reason I risked everything
for love!
And now Konane's dead!
And look at me!
You don't believe in romance!
Your writing is all lies!
Are you the girl from earlier?
Mona is weak.
Wolfie is strong.
Well, Wolfie, I believe
from the depths of my soul
that one should only marry for love.
- You do?
- So much so,
that I rejected the only man
who has ever asked for my hand.
He was a smug simpleton
who only read sermons.
How remarkable.
You shouldn't mess
with people's dreams.
My powers don't create passion
out of thin air.
Whomever you dreamt about,
you truly desire.
It doesn't mean I have to act on it.
It's called impulse control.
You sound like a woman
who has never let herself
fall in love.
Where I'm from, love is a liability.
And yet a life without love
is no life at all.
Tell me, what does a God know
about the human heart?
My real name is Sunjay.
I was born thousands of years ago.
When the actual Kamadeva
was immolated by Shiva,
I gathered his ashes in this vial.
They bestowed powers
I could have scarcely imagined.
Why are you telling me this?
Because I like you.
And I think you secretly yearn
to be impulsive and free.
Unless you lack the courage.
Okay.
- Give me a hit.
- Might I suggest...
Nope. If I'm going to do this,
I want to experience love, lust,
the whole shebang.
That is, unless you lack the courage.
One, two, three.
Most of you here, knew Hank well.
Or, thought you did.
I'm going to talk about
a different Hank,
a Hank I got to know this year.
Hank was a workaholic
who never took a day off.
Well, Hank, you can,
finally rest in peace.
Hank never knew his own father.
That's why he wanted to be there
for Nathaniel growing up.
But work often got in the way.
So one year,
we planned to use Hank's leave
to stay for a week in Disney World.
Nathaniel was over the moon.
But the morning that we were to fly
to Orlando, we...
ended up having to take Nathaniel
to the hospital instead.
When Hank saw the look
of disappointment in his son's eyes,
he went out and rented
a Mickey Mouse costume,
put it on and went to the hospital.
He convinced everyone there
that Mickey Mouse had come
to see them.
Hank Heywood was not a perfect man.
But when he was at his best,
that is who he was,
a man who could make you believe
in magic.
To Hank.
- To Hank.
Why did you tell me that by following
their hearts,
those women would only fall
into despair?
Because my decision was a result
of my pride.
When my father dies, my sister
and I will be reduced to penury.
- But your writing...
- Has been rejected
by every publisher.
It's no wonder.
I satirize the manners of a society
that seems to have lost
all sense of decorum.
Therefore,
I've decided to stop writing.
But you will publish.
You can't give up now,
because your books are timeless.
How can you be so sure?
Because...
you're my favorite author.
May I offer you a bit of advice?
My books advocate a partnership
based on love and mutual respect,
not on losing control.
What shall we do next?
I have an idea.
Let's get married.
Do you hear that?
No. Hear what?
There's definitely music playing.
Kamadeva loved music.
Perhaps you should sing.
I don't sing.
Every day I find a way
To shove my past and anger down
Go on, my love.
That was beautiful.
My humor's dry I never cry
If I start I'd surely drown
When I'm on my own I can't help
Wanting something more
Today instead of closing off
I'm opening a door
- Now I'm tossing sense aside
- And I surrender
- To the fantasy and pleasure
- I surrender
- To my happy ever after
- I won't fight it
- Won't deny it
- Do you have a ring? I'll try it
- I surrender
In the morning we should go ask
the parson to marry us.
A Christian wedding?
For a Muslim woman and a Hindu man?
Let's not think with our heads,
but feel with our hearts.
Gideon, where's that music
coming from?
I took the liberty of broadcasting
Ms. Tomaz's comms.
Rather infectious.
Ray, this music,
- I think it's magical.
- You're right.
I want to express my feelings to you
in verse.
Is that really necessary?
I had a dirty dream of you.
I'll bet mine was dirtier.
Why didn't you go and make a move?
I would have, if you'd been flirtier.
Okay. It's just complicated.
If Nate knew, he'd be enraged.
I know and I'm sorry,
but my desire's been uncaged.
Don't let this moment pass us by.
It could be our only chance.
You're right. I need you now.
Sorry, Nate and Captain Lance.
I fixed the timeline as a cat
Saved a cowboy kept his hat
Took Salem's breath away
Got stuck reliving the same day
Through it all I kept my cool
Never thought I'd play the fool
Now I've surrendered to you
It's time for me to say I do
"I do"? What are you talking about?
We need to find Mona.
Wait a sec, is this
a Bollywood musical number?
You bet your ass, it is.
Now we're tossing sense aside
And we surrender
To the fantasy
And pleasure we surrender
To our happy ever afters
We won't fight it won't deny it
Losing all control we'll try it
We surrender
I want you badly as my bride
Please make my wish come true
These feelings can't be denied
So yes I say I...
Stop!
You're making a mistake!
Zari
Whoa, why did I just sing that?
Okay, I guess I'm just going to roll
with the whole singing thing.
Every day we find a way to hold grief
And not let them see
We feel so wrong we often long
Get swept away in fantasy
You've been so brave wise and strong
By opening your door
Please Zari have courage now
To wait for something more
Don't listen to her, my love.
No, Mona's right, Z,
you don't even know this guy.
He's been using the powers
of a Love God for years,
guaranteed he's got a wife.
- Is that true?
- Not exactly.
I have 1000 wives.
But lucky number 1001
is the most important.
Seriously?
So, you still want to marry me?
No, I definitely do not.
Now I've got my senses back
But I'll surrender
Life's not done I'll love again
I'll surrender
- With my friends now by my side
- I won't hide it won't deny it
- Real love comes my way I'll try it
- I'll surrender
Voi-bloody-la.
Now, only the particular spirit
we're after will be able to enter
the vessel.
What vessel?
The vessel's you.
I'm going to kill you, weasel.
(Foreign language)
Hank Heywood,
I summon you.
(Foreign language)
Hank?
Who else would it be?
Where's Nathaniel?
Oh, old Nate gave you
the big middle finger,
so I'm afraid you're stuck with me.
Still angry, is he?
Us Heywoods, we hold a good grudge.
Now what's so important that you had
to stick around?
It pains me to admit it but I made
a terrible mistake.
A man approached me about a deal.
Unlimited funding...
and all I had to do
was give him access
to all the magical creatures
within the Time Bureau.
But this man was no ordinary
beltway bandit,
he was a demon.
Disneyland
Only after he murdered me,
did I realize the truth.
What was the demon's name?
Promise me you'll keep
Nathaniel safe.
Yes, yes, yes. I promise.
Now, come on, Hank, you can't delay
the inevitable forever.
What was the demon's name?
His name...
was Neron.
Hey, world!
I'm Hank Heywood
and I'm here to tell you
about an exciting opportunity.
When I learned about the existence
of magical creatures, yes!
Magical creatures exist!
I ran right home, pulled out
a drawing made by my son, Nathaniel,
when he was only 9 years old.
My son envisioned a theme park
where everyone could gaze in wonder
at dragons and unicorns,
werewolves and minotaurs.
This is insane.
Now, you may be thinking,
"This is insane."
But what great man
hasn't been thought
of as insane at one point
in his life?
I believe this park can bring
our country together.
And with your help, I'm going to turn
my son's dream into a reality.
I call it Heyworld.
Oh, Hank.
Why?
I have so many questions.
You weren't torturing
magical creatures.
You were training them
to be in a theme park.
That is nuts.
But I got to respect you
for dreaming big.
It was your moonshot,
your way of risking it all
to make the world a better place.
I was so wrong about you.
At the end of the day,
you were just as wacky
and well-intentioned as any legend.
And I wish I had a chance to get
to know that side of you.
I'm going to miss you.
I love you, Hank.
I love you, Dad.
Look at you.
Take a look at yourself,
you miserable git.
That's right.
Soak it in.
Your big sacrifice,
it was for nothing.
But instead of rolling up
your sleeves
and taking it to that demon bastard,
you're getting rat-ass drunk
in a shed.
I can't fight him.
He's too strong.
Oh, this isn't about Neron.
You failed Desmond.
You failed Astra.
And you'll fail Nate.
And you know why?
Because deep down,
you want them all to go to Hell.
You want the company.
You liar!
Hey, Johnny.
Miss me?
Des.
I'm surprised you haven't
figured it out yet.
Neron.